Hey! Come on, Kerry!
Hurry! Hurry up!
Kerry, jump in! Come on!
Come on! Come on!
It's so nice! Hurry up!
That was sweet, Kerry!
That was so cool! You're so awesome.
That was nothing. You're so cool.
That was really great.
Shirley!
Kerry!
Sorry I'm late.
Hey, Kerry,
do you know where this island's name comes from?
Uh‐uh.
Oh, isn't Arimago the word for crab?
Yep.
Long ago, this was a place where they
would make offerings to the sea gods.
But then one day a girl who was very poor and
had absolutely nothing to feed her sick mother
took some of the food that had been
set out by the village as an offering.
The sea gods were so upset by this that they
cursed the girl and transformed her into a crab.
That's where it comes from?
What an awful story.
Well, according to the legend,
the shrine where the village worshipped those gods
was located way up in the mountains,
right about the place where your house is.
That's why none of the villagers in
this area ever want to go up there.
They say it's bad luck.
They tell me that if I go there too often,
I'll end up cursed for life.
You're kidding.
Really?
But everyone's nice to me.
Of course they are.
You're not an outsider to them anymore.
In the village, they just treat
you like you're my little brother.
Your little brother, huh?
You know, Kerry, you've really settled in nicely here.
Yeah?
Back when you first arrived, everyone used to
really bully you, saying you had a weird name.
Hey!
You were the very first one to call my name weird,
and it was your big idea to call me Kerry.
Well, yeah, because your actual
name is really hard to say.
Kerry, uh...
Kerry...
Kiritsugu.
Jeez.
Kerrystugu!
Not even close.
Really?
Oops.
Okay.
Hm?
Hey, Dad, is that a new one?
That's right.
This would make my 100th success.
Amazing.
These flowers don't wither.
That's because I've altered the flow of time.
They will never grow beyond
this, but they will never die.
Unbelievable.
The big question is whether or not we can
get the same theory to work on humans.
Sorry for the wait!
Shirley, what you got?
Check it out.
It's my first successful flower.
Shirley has been watching closely
and learning while she assists me.
She does seem to have the natural gift to be a mage.
Aw, come on now, Professor.
You did most of the work.
I only did a little bit, and it was right at the end.
Maybe, but it's amazing.
Uh, hey, Dad?
Huh, what?
You think I could give it a try?
What Shirley did, I mean.
That'd be great!
I think if you had a little bit of help,
you could do it.
Right, Professor?
No.
Kiritsugu, it's still too early for you.
Mm.
This isn't a game.
There are dangers.
I only let Shirley try it because she has the
necessary knowledge and experience to succeed.
Hm.
Father Simon, why won't you try to understand?
Shirley.
Everyone in town has the professor all wrong!
Shirley, listen to me.
You must stop going up to that mansion.
Let's talk inside.
I think Dad should spend some
time with the villagers too.
I don't know.
Father Simon just has it in for him for some reason.
He keeps lecturing me all the time.
He says if I stay working there,
I'll get possessed by a demon someday.
Check this out.
He gave this to me yesterday.
Says I should always keep it near me.
He told me that it's a powerful talisman.
So you're not scared, you know, of my dad?
Not at all.
I realize that magical research
like he does isn't exactly normal.
But the professor's research
and discoveries are a big deal.
I mean, they could make history.
Actually, I think he's amazing.
Are you sure you should be...
What; It's sharp and it's really easy to use.
Well, see you tomorrow.
Shirley, something wrong?
Keeping a flower blooming forever.
It's really amazing magic.
But you're doing it too, Shirley.
The work with flowers is all I can do.
But he can do a lot more than that.
The medicines he makes could make
human beings effectively immortal.
I really want him to use his power
for the good of the whole world
so that everyone will finally
understand how incredible he is.
He's given up on that.
But, Kerry, I think you can do it.
Oh, come on.
You're the best student he's ever had.
If anyone could carry on his work,
it'd be you.
Kerry, I'm not really his student.
At best, I'm his assistant.
Running his errands,
helping out.
See, I'm not his student.
Far from it.
So even when Father Simon says bad things about
him, there's nothing I can say.
Kerry, you're his heir, there's no doubt about it.
You do realize that everything he's working
on now he plans for you to continue.
It's just a little too soon, that's all.
Hey, come with me.
Whoa.
Tell me, Kerry,
what do you want to grow up to be?
Huh?
If you decide to take up your dad's work,
what do you think you'll use it for?
It's a world changing power,
and one day it will be yours.
So, go change the world.
You can do it.
I guarantee it.
Well, I, uh...
That's a secret.
Hm.
Then I guess I'll have to wait until you grow
up to see what you're gonna do with your power.
I'll stay with you until that day comes, okay?
Yeah, right, whatever.
Stop it!
No way!
Oh, good morning, Dad.
Kiritsugu, you didn't go into
my workshop last night, did you?
Huh?
No, I didn't.
I see.
Listen, don't leave the house.
Huh?
Stay here.
Don't go into the village today.
What's gotten into him?
Shirley's late, I wonder why.
Hey!
Have you guys seen Shirley?
Uh‐uh.
Shirley?
Hm.
Huh?
What the?
What happened?
Kerry.
Shirley!
I...
I only wanted to prove him right.
His resear... research.
But I guess
it didn't work.
Kill me.
Use that.
Please.
You have to kill me.
Do it now
before it's too late.
Please do it!
I can't stop.
Can't hold it back anymore.
Hurry!
Hm.
Are you certain it was Shirley who did this?
Kerry, I want you to stay here for the time being.
I'll go inform the village.
Agh!
What?
What is all this?
Father Simon?
Yah!
Agh!
Looks like we got here just a little too late.
Wait a minute.
Who are... who are you?
Agh!
Don't you think you should worry about yourself first?
Well, if you just sit there like that,
you'll be joining them soon enough.
So what's going on?
Who did all this?
Why would they burn the village?
Surely you must have heard of them before.
You would know them as vampires.
The name we use is Dead Apostles.
Apostles?
They drink blood to increase their numbers.
Nearly everyone living on this
island has become one now,
and here we are having to clean up the mess.
So, we have two groups down there
right now trying to eliminate them all.
One of the groups is made up of Church Inquisitors,
those who believe beyond the shadow of a doubt
that it's all right to slaughter
anyone who defies the will of God.
They'll show no mercy to any Dead Apostles they find,
and they'll kill anyone they even
suspect of having had their blood sucked.
The other group is from the Mage's Association,
and they're harder to explain.
Suffice it to say, they'd very much like to
keep the secret of who made such bizarre things
as the Dead Apostles to themselves.
Naturally, since their motto is All To Ourselves,
they'll kill anyone they suspect of knowing the secret.
They'll do anything to cover this up.
It was the mages who set a torch to the village.
So then whose side are you on?
I'm something akin to a salesman
to the Mage's Association.
All right, it's your turn, kid.
Time to answer one of my questions.
I'm looking for a mage who's marked for sealing.
What's a mage?
I suppose that word doesn't really mean anything to you.
There was someone who became a Dead Apostle first,
someone infected them with the medium
that turns people into those creatures,
the trigger that started their transformation.
The son of a bitch mage who conjured that medium up
should be laying low somewhere on this island.
Can you think of any likely spots where I should look?
Oh, good.
There you are.
You're okay.
Well, thank goodness.
Didn't I tell you not to go into the village?
Dad, why were you researching Dead Apostles?
How did you know about that?
Shirley used the magic on herself.
Oh, well, that's most unfortunate.
But you can't change what's already happened.
It just means Shirley gave me
an answer I was looking for,
that's all.
Dad, will... will you use me
like you used Shirley?
Don't be stupid.
A Dead Apostle that can't control its blood lust
is a failure.
But the Emiya family research
requires an unlimited amount of time.
The Root will never be attained
by someone with a mortal body.
It was a time consuming task,
but it seems to have ended in failure.
I'm going to have to reconsider my entire theory.
Kiritsugu, let's save this matter for another time.
For now, escaping comes first.
It's not too late to escape?
I suspected something like this might happen one day,
so I've kept a motorboat hidden on the south coast.
I'm sorry, Kiritsugu,
but we don't have time to let you gather your things.
Come on.
I'm gonna do it.
There's a Bounded Field around the forest,
an extremely powerful one.
It'll take a little bit of time to break through it,
but I'll be able to get in.
I have to be the one.
Tell me, Kerry...
What do you want to grow up to be?
That Bounded Field,
I was able to break through it easily.
Are you mad or stupid?
It was only dumb luck that you showed up in time.
If this man had escaped,
he'd have continued his Dead
Apostles research somewhere else.
Yeah, well, that's a pretty crappy
reason for a kid to kill his father.
You're a good person, aren't you?
I'll get you off this godforsaken island.
You can decide the rest for yourself.
Wanna take anything?
Nothing at all.