This way, sir.
What is that?
All of you, return to your post.
Looks like an enormous ball of mercury doesn't it?
It's almost as if the damn thing is alive.
I need to get this out of here...
What's the matter, is something wrong?
I need to get this out of here,
I need to get this out of here.
Sir?
Load that thing onto the truck!
Quickly!
I'm afraid I must inform you
that the Grail War is in grave peril.
We have identified Caster's master as the
person behind the recent kidnappings in Fuyuki,
a disturbing revelation, indeed.
Thus, in accordance with the emergency powers
granted to me as overseer,
I am temporarily altering the rules of the Grail War.
Masters are to hereby cease all
ongoing combat in pursuit of the grail
and focus on the elimination of Caster instead.
And the one who succeeds in
defeating Caster and his master
will receive an additional
Command Seal as their reward.
These are the unused Command Seals left behind
by the fallen masters of past grail wars.
One of them should prove to be of
immeasurable value to whoever receives it.
Once Caster's destruction has been positively confirmed,
the Holy Grail War will
recommence until a victor emerges.
Now then, if anyone has questions,
please ask them now.
But, of course, that offer is limited to those
who can actually speak in human languages.
Well played, Father.
Now all the masters will do whatever they
can to hunt him down and destroy him.
There were five familiars gathered at the
church for my announcement, which means that...
Which means that the elusive missing master
Lord El‐Melloi is still very much alive.
Indeed.
And the offer of a Command Seal as the reward
should draw him out
given that he's already used one of his.
Of course, the other masters will be drawn out as well.
They'll seek to keep the Command Seal from the rest
by making certain they can claim it for themselves.
That's true, but it also means
that the master who wins the seal
will gain a formidable
advantage over the others.
Naturally, it's not ideal.
Once Caster has been thoroughly weakened
and is on the run from all the
other masters who are chasing him,
Archer must be the one to deal the final blow.
Um...
Excuse me, is this the Mackenzie residence?
I have a delivery.
Yes, that is the name of this domicile's residents.
Well, then, might there be a Mr. Iskandar,
King of Conquerors here?
That would be me.
I see, right.
I should've known.
Uh, could I have your signature on this receipt here?
My signature?
Very well.
You have my thanks.
Well, thank you very much for your business, sir.
To have the entire world emblazoned across my chest.
What a great feeling!
Wait, why are you dressed like that?
The package I was awaiting arrived.
So you went outside the house?
Ta‐da, I merely tried out that
mail‐order thing I heard about.
But I told you that you were
never to leave the second floor!
If the residents are not at home and you are off
somewhere all day occupied with your familiar,
who else is there to answer the door?
I had no choice.
A summons to appear by the Holy
Church is a big deal and I had to go.
Don't be so grouchy.
After seeing Saber last night,
I came to a realization.
If one wears modern attire, there should be no
issue whatsoever with going outside the domicile.
Hey, wait!
Stop!
At least put on some pants before you go out!
Oh, yes, leggings.
That's true, I forgot.
Everyone in this land wears them.
Do I have to wear them?
Yes, of course you have to!
And just to be perfectly clear,
I'm definitely not going to make
a special trip all the way to town
just to buy you a pair of
triple XL pants, understand?
You won't, why?
Boy, would you actually stand in the way
of my triumphant conquest of the world?
You conquering the world and
whether or not you have pants have
nothing, not even the slightest
thing to do with each other!
Before you start planning to go screwing around outside,
why don't you go out and do your job
and beat one of the other servants?
Then I'll buy your pants or anything else you want.
Very well.
I understand.
Do you swear that once I defeat
one of the other servants
you will go and buy me a modern pair
of pants so that I can go outside?
Unbelievable.
You really want to put on modern clothes
and go walking outside that much?
The King of Knights was walking around outside.
I simply cannot allow myself to be undone.
I like the design on this shirt.
It is fitting attire for a strong ruler.
Look, we have to go find and defeat Caster too.
What the hell are we doing?
There is a powerful barrier over Mount Enzo
with Ryuudou Temple at its center.
Because of that,
except for natural spirits like servants,
anything can enter only via the temple path.
Keep that in mind as you're using Saber.
There are three other spots
where the ley lines converge:
Tohsaka Manor, Fuyuki Chapel,
and this new residential area, east of the city center.
Consequently, this means that there
are four locations in Fuyuki
that have all the spiritual characteristics
needed for the grail to appear.
In the war's second phase,
when there are fewer servants left in the fight,
we'll have to secure one of these spots
as our base of operations, won't we?
Yes, that's correct.
Well, that just about covers the lay of the land.
Are there any questions?
Is there anything that you aren't clear on?
I understand perfectly.
It was an adequate explanation.
Kiritsugu, can we assume that all the
other masters will go after Caster?
It's a safe bet.
However, we have an advantage
as far as Caster is concerned.
In his madness,
he believes that our Saber is actually his Jeanne d'Arc
which is to our benefit.
We need only wait for him to come to us.
But, master, that is not enough.
His evil deeds must be punished.
We should take the fight straight to him
before he can do any more damage.
Iri, do you have a handle on
this forest's barrier spells?
Yes, I do, however,
our real problem is the unbreakable
curse on Saber's left hand.
Eighteen hours have already passed
since your defeat of Canaan,
but Saber's wound has still yet to heal.
Lancer must still be alive.
Shouldn't we go find and defeat Lancer first so we
can face a battle with Caster at our full strength?
That isn't necessary.
You just need to use your knowledge of the area
to confuse the enemy, keeping Saber moving around.
You won't have her fight Caster?
No, someone else will deal with him even if we don't.
The masters and servants hunting Caster in
a frenzy will make excellent targets for us.
I'll attack from their flanks and take them out.
Master, you can't.
To what depths do you intend to sink in your pursuit?
You do insult to heroic spirits.
Why do you not allow me to go out and fight?
Do you mean to imply that you cannot trust me,
your own servant?
There's a truce against everyone
but Caster, isn't there?
It'll be fine.
This overseer of ours can't be trusted.
He harbors Assassin's master in his church
and doesn't say anything about it to anyone.
He may also be working with Tohsaka.
We should be skeptical of his actions.
All right, dismissed.
Kiritsugu.
If...
If I...
If I decided to abandon everything
and simply run away from all of this,
Iri, would you consider coming with me?
But what about Illya?
She's still waiting back at our castle.
I'd return for her, killing anyone in our way,
and then I would just...
I'd give all I have
for you and Illya, and no one else!
Could we really get away?
We could escape if we go now!
You're lying.
That's a lie.
You could never run away from this.
You would never forgive yourself
for abandoning the Holy Grail,
for failing to save the world.
You would be riddled with guilt,
and as your first and final accuser,
you would eventually kill yourself.
I'm scared.
He... Kirei Kotomine is after me.
Maiya told me.
He used Canaan as bait to draw me out.
He anticipated my actions.
I've already sacrificed you, Iri,
and I've left Illya behind,
but the most dangerous of them all
has already set his sights on me,
the one that I had hoped
to never cross paths with!
I won't allow you to fight alone.
I will protect you, and Saber will, too,
and also Maiya is here.
Kiritsugu.
An attack.
We're lucky I hadn't sent Maiya out yet.
We can mount an all‐out defense.
Iri, find us a remote‐viewing crystal ball.
There they are.
Irisviel.
He's trying to lure us out.
It looks like he has hostages.
I'll have to go out there and
do what I can to save them.
He knows that we're watching him.
Just as I promised you last night, I,
Gilles de Rais, have come for you, my darling.
I wish to see you, fair Jeanne, my enchanting
and radiantly beautiful holy virgin of my dreams.
Irisviel.
You may take your time if you wish.
I have come fully prepared for a lengthy wait, and will
be as attentive and patient as you need for me to be.
Now, children, it's time for
us to play some hide‐and‐seek.
The rules are simple.
You need only to elude me.
But if I find you...
No, don't!
Run, children.
When I count to a hundred, the chase begins.
Well, Jeanne, how long do you think it will
take for me to catch them all and win the game?
Saber, go!
Defeat Caster!
Yes!
Huh?
Welcome, fair Jeanne.
How do you like this horrible sight?
Does it not pain you?
Do you despise me, Jeanne?
Yes, I'm sure you must.
I'm certain you'll never forgive
me for turning from God's love.
Unhand the child, monster!
Jeanne, if you so dearly wish to save the boy, then,
child, you should rejoice and be exceedingly glad.
God's devout messenger says that she will save
you from the fate of your departed friend.
It's dangerous here.
Now, you need to run.
Just follow this path and you'll find a castle.
Ha‐ha, do you not remember what I told you?
I said that the very next time we would meet
I would be prepared for you.
Very well.
My fight with you is no longer over.
The Grail!
Oh, my fair Jeanne, how noble, how beautiful!
Oh, holy virgin,
even God's beauty pales before you.
Caster, I take up my sword solely to destroy you!
Prepare!
If only I could use my left hand.
Even Caster's mana isn't infinite.
If she can last until it runs out,
Saber can with this battle, right, Kiritsugu?
More importantly, there's still no sign
of other masters entering the forest.
Maiya, take Iri and get away from the castle
in the opposite direction of the fight.
But why can't I just remain here?
With Saber fighting away from you,
it simply isn't safe for you here.
At least one of the other masters is
certain to have had the same idea.
All right, I'll go.
What's wrong, Iri?
It appears that another one has arrived.
How is this?
Is there no end to his mana?
Impossible.
The source of his mana is...
So that book is your Noble Phantasm?
That's right, the grimoire left to
me by the legendary teacher, Prelati,
gives me the ample means to command
a demonic legion to do my will.
What do you think, my fair Jeanne?
It brings back memories, doesn't it?
Everything is just as it was then.
Your indomitable warrior spirit and noble bearing
proves you to be none other than Jeanne d'Arc!
So why, fair Jeanne,
why do you not awaken to the truth of this?
Do you still believe in God's grace even now?
Faced with mortal peril,
you still believe a miracle will save you?
How terribly tragic.
Have you forgotten the Battle of Compiègne?
Even after that awful humiliation,
you still chose to remain God's puppet!
Ah!
Rather pathetic.
Such swordsmanship is unworthy
of the title King of Knights.
Hmm.
Who are you?
And who gave you leave to
interfere with our private affair?
Yes, well, that is my question to you, monster.
It will be my lance alone that takes Saber's life.
Ah, no, it was my prayer!
It was my Holy Grail that brought her back to life!
She is mine, intruder.
Every scrap of flesh, every drop of
blood, even her very soul belongs to me!
Listen, Caster, I am not gonna comment
on your bizarre notion of romance here.
So if you really believe that you're
gonna make Saber yours here today,
then go ahead and try it,
but know that I, Diarmuid, will never allow you
to defeat a crippled Saber in any sort of battle
before I can!
You came to help?
Don't get the wrong idea.
The only thing that brought me here today
was the order to find and defeat Caster.
And, so, I believe cooperation
is our best option, right?
Mmhmm.
Just to be perfectly clear, Lancer,
right now, I could kill a hundred of
those things with just my left arm.
Hmm, a mere hundred of them is child's play.
You will pay.
Don't be conceited, you savage!
Fervor, mei sanguis.
Kayneth El‐Melloi has arrived,
the ninth patriarch of the Archibald family.
Mage of the Einzbern, come forth and let
us duel for possession of the Holy Grail
with our lives and our sacred honor.
Mechanical traps, of all things.
Have you fallen so low, Einzbern?
Very well, then this is no longer a
duel, but an extermination.
I see.
Automated probes.
I found you, pathetic rat.
Now scalp!
Time alter, double accelerate.
Huh?
Oh.
He manipulated the flow of time to greatly accelerate
himself by using his own body as a reality marble.
It seems that he knows a little magic after all.
Still, only a miserable, little coward would depend
on petty tricks after being trained as a mage.
Perhaps dying will teach him his place.
Ire sanctio.
If he's manipulating his inner time,
it must be placing enormous stress on his body.
I found him.
Now then, how far can you run as exhausted as you are?
Time alter, triple stagnate.
These things don't have eyes.
If I can slow my internal time to a third
and lower my pulse and
respiration as far as they can go,
they can't sense me.
Kayneth!
You're a fool!
It's a waste of time.
Hmm.