What are we gonna do now, Rider?
Hmm.
So what now, Mad Dog?
Tokiomi.
I'll kill you, bastard.
Saber!
They can't make it through.
If only Saber could use her left hand.
Hey, Saber!
We're not getting anywhere like this!
Let us withdraw!
Don't be a fool!
We must stop its advance!
That may well be, but we're in a stalemate!
Just fall back for now!
I have an idea!
Listen, everyone.
Whatever strategy we devise tonight,
we first need to buy some time to organize it.
For the time being, I will drag
that beast into my Ionian Hetairoi,
but it will be impossible for my elite troops to slay it
even if they attack in full force.
The best we can hope for is to halt
its advance within the Reality Marble.
And after that?
No idea.
Huh?
After swallowing something as big as that,
my bounded field and its army will
only hold for a matter of mere minutes.
In that short time, we must act.
Heroic spirits, I want you to
find some way for us to prevail.
Boy, disembark!
You're staying here with them.
Huh?
Hey!
Once my reality marble is deployed,
I will not know what is going on in the outside world,
and so if anything happens, concentrate and call to me.
I'll send a messenger to you.
Saber and Lancer,
the rest is up to you.
Right.
Understood.
Yah!
You only prolong the inevitable.
Mom!
What is that?
How does plunging headfirst into that
filthy creature sound to you, you mongrel?
After all that raging and ranting against me.
When it comes time to act, this is all you can do?
Is he trying to kill himself?
Kariya, consider this an act of mercy.
Intensive, Einäscherung
I can't kill you.
I'll kill you.
Tokiomi...
What now?
I know he said he'd buy us some time,
but if we don't think of something really fast,
We'll be right back where we started.
Come on now, Einzbern.
Don't you have any ideas?
Say something!
Wait a minute.
I don't know how to use this.
Iri.
Um, no, I'm... wait, who is this?
Ah, well, you must be Rider's master.
Good timing.
There's something I wanna discuss with you.
Who... who are you?
That's not important.
Caster's disappearance...
I gather that was your servant's doing?
That's right, basically.
Question... Rider's reality marble, when he releases it,
can he put down the contents in a specific area?
To a point.
He can get within 100 meters or so, I think.
It should be possible.
Rider has control over where
he enters back into this world.
Good enough.
When the timing seems like it's
right, I'll send up a flare.
Release Caster directly underneath it.
Can you do that?
I can, probably, I think.
One more thing... give this message to Lancer.
Tell him Saber's left hand contains
an anti‐fortress Noble Phantasm.
Huh?
Something the matter?
Well, he asked me to give you a message.
Saber's left hand has an anti‐fortress Noble Phantasm.
Is this true, Saber?
I see.
Do you think it's capable of
obliterating Caster's monster?
I believe so.
But Lancer, my blade and my pride are the same.
This wound you inflicted on me
is a mark of pride, not shame.
If that loss was the price of
securing Diarmuid Ua Duibhne's aid,
then it was worth a veritable host.
Listen, Saber,
I cannot abide this Caster.
He finds the despair of others both right and
good and takes pleasure in spreading terror.
On my word as a knight,
his is an evil that I cannot let go unchallenged.
Lancer, no, you mustn't do that!
Must it be Saber who is victorious today or Lancer?
No, it is neither of us.
What must triumph here today is the path of chivalry.
Agreed, heroic Arturia?
Lancer.
I entrust our victory to the single
strike of the King of Knights.
I'm counting on you, brave Saber.
Rest assured, Lancer. Upon my blade, I will prevail!
That is from the Arthurian legends.
Saber!
Berserker?
Why now?
You dare turn your back on me, you lowly mongrel?
Blasphemy!
What?
Saber!
What the hell does Berserker think he's doing?
I've finally regained the use
of my left hand and now this.
Regardless of its own self awareness of this fact,
a soul instinctively seeks out joy in its life.
He was the only one you ordered Assassin
to investigate thoroughly enough such that
you could understand those circumstances.
And this was due to your unconscious interest in him.
Still too soon.
What are all these tremors?
An omen that Rider's reality marble
is approaching its limits, I imagine.
Come, Rider.
I am Mithrenes, Soldier of the Hetairoi.
I have come here to act as my king's eyes and ears.
Tell him to wait for our signal,
then release the bounded field and
dump Caster at the designated location.
Can you do it?
We can, sir, but it will be a race against time.
We of the Hetairoi are no longer able
to slow the progress of that
horror within the bounded field.
I understand that!
I know!
Damn that Berserker!
Can't we do anything about him?
Allow me.
Lancer!
I am putting an end to this mad warrior!
It's all or nothing.
Archer!
There it is!
Right under there.
Yes, sir.
Finally... what took them so damn long?
Oh.
All right now, Saber, show me your best!
I shall judge your worth as a heroic spirit
with my own two eyes!
The light.
It shines bright.
It is the true embodiment
of the sad yet noble dream of all soldiers
past, present, and future who lie
dying on the fields of battle,
clutched to their hearts with their last breath,
holding aloft their dying wish,
making certain that their loyalty will not be in vain.
The invincible king is about to cry out the true name
of the miracle she wields in her hands.
That name is...
Excalibur!
This brilliant light!
There is no doubt, this is the light
from when Jean and I were
blessed with such profound joy!
What...have I...
Did you see that, King of Conquerors?
Such is Saber's brilliant skill.
Having seen such light,
you still refuse to grant her your respect?
Hmm... that light is a result of her accepting
the hopes and dreams of the people of her time.
It hurts me because it's so bright.
And because I know that this burden
was thrust upon the shoulders of a little girl.
What I see is what became of a girl
who was never allowed to admire
butterflies or flowers or fall in love,
but was instead taken hold of by the curse of ideals.
It is too painful to look upon.
Which is exactly what makes her so endearing...
the unattainable dream she held so dear
was certain to explode in a brilliant
flare that would burn her to ash.
The tears of bitter lamentation she shed,
how sweet they'd have tasted as she laid there dying.
You and I will never get along,
Babylonian King of Heroes.
Really?
You only now realized that fact?
What are you going to do, Rider?
Perhaps give vent to your righteous anger here and now?
It would give me great pleasure were I to do so.
But if you and I were to do battle, it would mean
expending more energy tonight than I would care to.
Of course, if you were to decide that you
couldn't pass up the chance to attack,
I would be forced to respond in kind.
This once, I shall allow you to escape.
There would be no satisfaction in crushing you
if you were not in your prime.
Or is it that you yourself are injured from
being shot down by that ridiculous lunatic?
I respond to provocation with death.
We'll save it for next time, King of Heroes.
Ours will be the epic battle that will determine
who is the champion of the Holy Grail War.
Don't be so certain.
I have yet to decide if there is but one who is
worthy of the gift of my greatest treasure, Rider.
You glorious fool who strives to achieve
that which man was not meant to have.
In all of Heaven and Earth, none but I, Gilgamesh,
can truly appreciate your destruction.
You who shine so brightly yet so briefly,
come to my arms.
This I have decided.
I am first Bure of Fianna,
Diarmuid Ua Duibhne.
Saber, I am glad I was able to meet you.
Splendid... for this night,
Arturia Pendragon accepts your challenge.
‐Come then! ‐I come for you!