Did you hate me?
Did you hate me so much that you became this?
Origin rounds. They cause the
target's mana to go out of control,
causing their body to rip itself apart.
What?
Time alter.
Double accel!
The origin rounds are working.
No, I understand.
He's using command seals as his mana source.
By the time the round strikes and takes effect,
the command seal mana source has already vanished.
Since he doesn't use his own magic circuits for attacks,
the origin rounds' magic won't work.
But if I can land a solid hit,
it'll still be strong enough to kill him.
Don't think you'll escape next time.
Now that I know you're moving at double speed,
I simply need to adjust the
distance to compensate for it.
He's fast!
The depth of your violent madness...
...is that my fault as well?
Is it?
Is it my fault?
Time alter, double accel.
I'm at a massive disadvantage at close range.
I've lost my Calico.
My Contender needs reloading.
However, Avalon.
He has healing ability that allows him to
instantly regenerate a demolished heart?
Well then, I'll have to destroy the brain.
But I can't use my right arm.
Avalon will even work on self‐inflicted wounds.
I have a knife I can use and two grenades left.
I have 12 blades remaining
and eight spare command seals.
Time alter.
Triple accel.
Square accel!
But, even so, I will win the Grail.
If I do not, there will be nothing I can do
to atone to you.
Even after all that has happened
you would still take up your sword
for a reason such as that?
What a difficult person you are.
Where am I?
I knew you would come, Kiritsugu.
I had faith that you would be
the one to reach this place.
Iri.
This is where the wish you
have lived for will be granted.
We are inside the Grail that you have been seeking.
That is the Holy Grail.
It has yet to take form,
but the vessel itself is more than filled.
All you need do now is offer it your prayer.
Only then will it be able to
go out into the physical world.
Now, please, hurry and give the Grail its form!
Kiritsugu, you have proven yourself more
than worthy to define its existence.
Who are you, really?
I am Irisviel, as you see.
No.
If the Grail is prepared to receive a wish,
then she is already...
Answer me!
It's true.
I will not deny that this is no more than a mask.
You see, unless I use a
preexisting personality as a shell,
I cannot communicate with others.
However, the personality of Irisviel that I recorded
is undeniably the real thing.
And so I have inherited the last
wish that Irisviel held in her heart.
Are you the will of the Holy Grail?
I am, that interpretation is not incorrect.
I have my own will and my own wish.
I have the will to be born into the world.
No way.
If that's the case, then how does the Grail
intend to totally fulfill my wish?
Well, Kiritsugu, that is something
that you should know far better
than anyone else could possibly know.
What?
You learned exactly how to save the world
a long, long time ago.
So I will do exactly as you always did...
to carry out your will and to
ultimately answer your prayer.
What are you talking about?
I have no choice.
The only way is to have you go and explore
that same question through your inner self.
This is...
Three hundred are on one ship,
200 on another.
What the...
hundred total Five passengers and
crew, plus Kiritsugu Emiya.
Let's assume that these 501 people
are humanity's last survivors.
Giant holes simultaneously open
up in both ships, crippling them.
Kiritsugu alone has the skills needed to repair a ship.
Now then, which one of the
ships would you choose to fix?
Simple... the one holding 300 people.
As soon as you make that decision,
the 200 passengers on the other ship
kidnap you and take you prisoner.
They demand that you fix their ship first.
What will you do?
I would...
You would kill all 200 passengers.
That is correct, that is the Kiritsugu Emiya we know.
Next, the surviving 300 passengers
abandon their damaged craft.
They split themselves between two
new ships and continue their journey.
This time, there are 200 on one,
and 100 on the other.
But again, holes open the hulls of both ships
at exactly the same time.
Wait.
The hundred in the smaller ship take you prisoner,
and like the others,
demand that you fix their ship first.
Now what will you do?
You already know, but you...
Yes, you made the right decision.
No, that's impossible!
How can that be the right decision?
Two hundred survived, but 300 died so they could live.
The scales are tipped the wrong way!
No, your calculations were correct.
You made a choice to sacrifice the few to save the many.
Isn't that right, Kiritsugu Emiya?
You have consistently chosen to kill
those in the lighter side of the scales,
even if it meant leaving a long trail
of bodies behind you in your wake.
If it saved lives, the lives of the saved
must've been worth more than those you destroyed.
This...
this is what you wanted to show me?
Yes, this is your truth.
The answer that lies within Kiritsugu Emiya.
The course of action that should be taken by the Grail
as an all‐powerful wish‐granter.
No.
No, this is not what I want!
I want there to be another way to save the world.
That's why I believed
that a miracle was my only hope.
Your wish cannot include
a method you yourself don't already know.
If your wish is the save the world,
it must be done in a manner
that you can fully comprehend.
Like hell!
How in the hell can you call that a miracle?
But it is.
The deed you tried so hard to accomplish
and failed to do on your own
can be accomplished on a scale
beyond the power of any man.
If that is not a miracle, what is?
Father.
Natalia.
Kiritsugu Emiya.
You truly are Angra Mainyu...
the one worthy to bear all the evil in the world.
Now, the final question.
Three remain.
Will you save two or choose one?
Welcome home, Daddy!
Oh, I'm so happy that you're finally back!
You understand now, right?
This is all the Holy Grail granting
your heart's fervent prayer.
All you need do now is to wish for it,
to bring back your wife, to take back your daughter.
I won't be able to go looking
for chestnuts with you anymore.
It's okay, don't worry about it!
I'll be happy just as long as you
and Mother are with me from now on.
Thank you.
Daddy loves you, my precious Ilya.
If nothing else, I swear that's true.
Goodbye, Ilya.
Ilya!
Ilya, Ilya!
Ilya.
But why?
Why would you do this?
My love, you killed our Ilya!
My love...
why?
Why do you...refuse us...
and the Grail?
Six billion people on the Earth.
I...
curse you...
Kiritsugu Emiya.
Versus you two.
Angra Mainyu curses you.
That's why.
You'll suffer...
That's why...
...till the day you die.
... I have to kill you.
I will...
And I will save...
the world.
Never forget...
What a boring conclusion to this fight.
Why did you refuse it?
You were able to see all that?
I thought you sacrificed everything you had including
your family in order to make it to this point.
How can you simply deny the worth of
something you worked so hard to attain?
It's so foolish, I cannot understand it.
The tremendous toll it demands
is far greater than anything it can offer.
That's the simple truth.
That thing is no omnipotent wish‐granter.
Then give the damn thing to me!
You may not think you need it,
but I most certainly do.
If it... if it is given the life it is seeking,
then it can surely answer my every doubt
and finally bring everything into clarity.
The Grail longs for a life of its own,
longs for its own birth!
Please, don't kill it,
it's...
No, you are the fool I can't understand.
Oh, Iris, you...
You're late, Saber!
I realized you were enjoying
yourself with your old Mad Dog,
but it is imprudent to the extreme
to keep me waiting like you did.
Archer.
Look at that delightful expression,
like that of a ravenous wild dog.
Get out of my way.
You haven't won.
The Holy Grail belongs to me!
Dear Saber, it is when you are
delusional and crawling in the dirt
that you are at your most beautiful.
Lay down your blade and be my wife.
A Grail that grants miracles?
Where is the sense in totally
obsessing over something so dubious?
Abandon these foolish ideals and childish vows of yours.
From now on, seek only me and
devote yourself to me alone.
If you do, I swear as King of All Creation
that I shall give you every
pleasure the world has to offer.
You would steal the Holy Grail from me
for such utter nonsense?
I was not asking for your opinion.
I am informing you of my decision.
Now, let us hear your response.
I refuse.
I would never...
Shyness has left you at a loss for words, I see.
That's fine.
You may answer wrongly as many times as you like.
If you would learn the joy of serving me,
you must first learn the exquisite pain of it as well.
Kiritsugu!
Ah, then you have finally made your decision.
In the name of Kiritsugu Emiya,
and by my command seal...
Give me the Holy Grail.
...I order you, use your Noble Phantasm.
Destroy the Grail.
Impossible... what are you doing, Saber!
No!
By my third command seal,
I order you again.
But why, Kiritsugu...  you of all people?
Why this?
Damn you to Hell.
You dare interrupt my nuptials?
Mongrel!
Saber, destroy...
Stop!
...the Holy Grail.