You have a charm spell.
Apologies, but I'm afraid it's a
little curse that I was born with.
There's really nothing that can be done about it.
Blame it on my birth, or if you prefer,
the fact that you were born a woman.
Surely you don't actually believe that
a pleasant face and a charming swagger
will save you from the bite of my blade, spear man.
I certainly hope not...  it would spoil the fun.
I see now that the tales of the Saber
classes' resistance to magic are true.
Very well... I prefer not to kill a
girl who's throwing herself at me.
It would sully my reputation.
I'm pleased that my first
opponent is made of stern stuff.
Oh, so what you desire is a fair fight.
I consider myself fortunate to encounter
such a strong and proud hero.
Then let us begin.
It's started.
Someone has put up a barrier,
probably the master of the enemy's servant.
From up on that crane, it would be
possible to survey the whole battlefield.
Indeed... that certainly is the best vantage point.
Anyone seeing it would agree.
All right, you circle around to the Eastern Wharf.
I'll go the other way and take the west.
You and I need to find good spots
where we can be totally invisible while we closely
monitor both Saber's battle and that crane, got it?
Yes, understood.
Now, then, let's see what you can do,
my adorable King of Knights.
Saber is watching both spears simultaneously.
Lancer's greatest advantage is his opponent's
uncertainty as to which he will use.
The long spear in the right hand
or the short spear in the left?
Which was the Noble Phantasm?
If I could be certain which one it
was, I could attack and defeat him.
If only we knew his true name.
Whoever he is, he's a master of the spear.
However, that is not enough.
What's wrong, Saber?
You're on the defensive.
This man is impressive.
Curse that blade of hers.
Without knowing its exact length,
I can't get close enough to strike.
The fact that she's able to repel my strikes so easily
means that she must be a master swordsman.
Hmm, Maiya, northeast of Saber and Iri.
On the roof of that warehouse, it's Lancer's master.
Can you see him?
Negative... I can't see him from my position.
Understood.
I'll take him out from here.
Assassin?
There is activity at the warehouse
district at the mouth of the Mion River.
It seems the first battle has finally begun.
Not the first battle.
To the others, this would be the second battle, Kirei.
It would appear that Lancer and
Saber are the combatants in this one.
Can you ascertain their status
utilizing Assassin's eyes?
With ease.
Saber's formidable abilities are especially high.
Most of her parameters are ranked
A or higher on the standard scale.
I see.
It's no wonder they are considered the strongest class.
Saber likely presents a greater threat than Lancer.
Can you see other masters?
There's only one person besides the servants
who is out in the open and visible to Assassin.
She's standing next to Saber.
It's a woman with silver hair.
Huh, that means that Lancer's master is wise enough to
remain hidden from view, and that he's not a novice.
He understands the rules of the Holy Grail War.
Wait a minute... a silver‐haired woman?
Yes, a Caucasian...
with silver hair and red eyes.
Very unusual.
She doesn't look at all human.
An Einzbern Homunculus.
It seems they created another artificial master.
I thought that the only pawn Yupstehide had on the board
was Kiritsugu Emiya.
It would appear that I was wrong.
So then that woman is the Einzbern master?
Either way, she's certainly going to be a critical
factor throughout the rest of the Grail War.
Kirei, keep a close eye on her.
Agreed.
I shall keep one Assassin tasked to her at all times.
I see him, too.
But Assassin should be dead, so why is he here?
I knew something had to be up.
Let's see how this all plays out.
Continue to observe Assassin.
I'll watch Lancer.
Let me launch an attack on Assassin.
And then, while I have him distracted,
you can take out Lancer's master.
No, Maiya.
I don't want you to make any moves against Assassin.
We're not equipped to fight servants right now.
It would be disastrous.
Understood.
There is really no honor in a battle
fought without a proper exchange of names,
but allow me to offer my regards.
It's impressive for a woman to fight so hard
without even breaking a sweat as she does it.
You needn't be so humble, Lancer.
Even without my knowing your name,
those words from such a master of the spear do me honor.
I gratefully accept them.
That's enough fun for now, Lancer.
Lancer's master?
Do not allow this battle to go on.
Saber is a formidable opponent.
Eliminate her at once.
You may use your Noble Phantasm.
As you command, I will comply.
So the long spear is his Noble Phantasm.
You heard the command.
The time has come for me to kill you.
Saber, are you using focused wind mana
to keep your blade concealed?
I see.
I'll wager that you have a very good reason
to conceal your sword from me.
I think the sword reveals your true name.
How unfortunate for you.
I'm afraid you'll never know the true name of my blade.
I'll finish this before you ever get the chance.
We shall see about that.
I will discover whatever it is you're hiding, Saber.
You've exposed your sword to me.
The Invisible Air is coming apart.
What's going on with Saber?
That red spear is chipping away at the Invisible Air.
I've figured out the length of your blade now,
so I needn't worry about being struck by you anymore!
He wields a formidable weapon,
but I still have ways to counter it.
If I wait for an attack...
...one less powerful than the rest.
Saber?
My thanks, Irisviel.
I'm fine... the healing is working.
I see... so this won't be an easy victory after all.
How could this be?
My armor should've easily deflected that strike.
So how did the blade of his spear...
The armor itself isn't damaged.
What's at work here?
The only answer is that Lancer's spear
bypassed the magically woven armor.
So that's it.
I know the secret of your spear, Lancer.
Oh?
That red spear of yours is able to negate magic.
Hmm.
So your armor was created using magic, huh?
Well, if you were counting on it to protect
you, you should surrender now, Saber.
You're as good as naked before my spear.
Don't think that simply defeating my armor
will give you the upper hand in this fight.
If I cannot block your blade,
I need only kill you before it strikes.
Prepare to die, Lancer!
A bold move.
You're betting everything on a single strike.
You are attempting to overcome the
disadvantage of your broken armor
with the advantages you gain by abandoning it.
Excellent.
A courageous decision.
I like it... it's audacious and bold.
But in this case, I'm afraid that it
was a very foolish mistake, Saber.
We shall see.
You can tell me your opinion again after my next attack.
That was a misstep.
A Noble Phantasm needn't be merely a single weapon.
A trap!
This is extremely bad.
What is?
Lancer has begun his ultimate attack.
He intends to end the battle here.
Well, wouldn't that be a lot better for us?
Ahh!
You idiot... what are you talking about?
I wanted to sit back and watch until
we saw a few more masters fight.
But at this rate, Saber may just fall.
And then it will be too late.
T... t... too late for what?
I mean, the plan was to attack after they'd
fought a few battles and weakened each other.
I have to admit that I had really
hoped at least one other servant
would've been sent out to
answer Lancer's challenge,
because, of course, it would be
much faster to fight them altogether
than to seek them all out one by one.
You wanna fight 'em together?
Indeed!
Rarely does one have the extraordinary chance to
exchange blows with great heroes from another time.
And with a chance to fight as many as six of them,
I'd hate to miss out on a single one.
Just observe Saber and Lancer.
Both of them are strong, valiant warriors whom I
would dearly love to face in an all‐out battle.
I cannot let either one die.
But isn't that the whole point?
The Grail Wars objective is
to kill one another isn't it?
To win, but never to destroy,
to subjugate, but never to humiliate...
that is a truly good and honorable conquest.
Now, we will watch no longer!
We shall join the fray, boy!
Let us go!
You stupid idiot!
What you're doing is totally insane!
If you really don't approve,
then why don't you just stay up here and observe?
No, I'll go!
Take me with you, dammit!
Excellent, that is my master.
Not good... he severed the tendon.
I can't move my thumb.
Good counter.
You aren't gonna make this easy for me, are you?
But I like your indomitable spirit.
Stop talking and get to work, you fool!
Finish her... what are you waiting for?
My master... much appreciated.
Irisviel, I require healing.
But I have.
I've already done it.
I mean, I did it...
the healing worked, I'm certain of it!
Saber, you should already be fully healed!
I don't understand!
It was very sharp of you to figure out,
that my Gae Dearg was able to penetrate any armor,
but it was foolish to abandon it.
Had you not done so,
my Gae Buidhe would not have gotten you.
I see.
You wield a cursed spear,
which inflicts devastating
wounds that can never be healed.
I should've realized it sooner.
A red spear that destroys magic,
a cursed yellow spear, and beneath the right
eye, a mole that enchants women.
First of the Knights of Fianna,
Diarmuid of the Love Spot.
Never did I think I'd have the
honor of facing you in combat.
Such is a sublime pleasure of the Holy Grail War,
but it's I who has the distinct honor here.
No hero summoned into service by the Holy Grail
could ever mistake that golden blade.
To face the legendary King of Knights in battle
and land even a single glancing blow is extraordinary.
I must not be too bad.
Now then, since we both know each other's name,
we can finally conduct our duel honorably
as knights should.
Or does this displease you,
occurring only after you've lost use of an arm?
You jest.
It is humiliating that you would show so much concern
over such a scratch.
Prepare yourself, Saber!
This time you're mine!
Only if I fail to inflict the
first decisive strike, Lancer.
That's a chariot!
Both of you, sheath your blades,
for I am a King!
I am Iskander, King of Conquerors!
In this battle for the Holy Grail,
I am of the Rider class of servants!