Hurts, huh?
Mages carry the pain of that crest forever.
You know, I think your dad
really gave you the perfect name.
Your origin is based on cutting and tying, kid.
The nuance is a little different
than destroy and regenerate.
If you cut a thread and then re‐tie it,
it will be thicker where you cut it,
isn't that right?
In that sense, it carries a
connotation of irreversible change.
Kiritsugu, with the characters for cut and tie,
these will be your ace in the hole.
I've powdered some of your ribs
and put a little bit in here.
Your origin will materialize in
anything shot by this bullet.
If your target attempts to use any magic against it,
it will cut his circuits and thoroughly fry them.
Just one shot will incapacitate him.
I've made 66 in total.
Don't waste them.
Natalia, do you read me?
I'm almost there.
Roger.
Natalia, do it.
Huh?
In the end, after leaving the island,
I spent the next several years
living with Natalia Kaminski.
That meant choosing the same path as Natalia.
The solitary path of a highly skilled master hunter.
Natalia belonged to no organization.
She was a total freelancer,
interested only in the money she could earn.
The Mage's Association and the Church,
the rivalry between those two enormous organizations
kept her business booming.
During that time,
I witnessed many tragedies
like the one on Arimago Island.
I also learned that all around the world
on every single continent,
the same horrors happened every day.
Just missed.
Are you trying to be a hero or something?
Was there no meaning to it?
I thought...
I thought I had killed my father to
keep more people like them from dying.
Killing merely one man isn't the solution.
It's not that simple.
Kill every single person all around
the world who's like our target here.
If you could somehow manage to do that,
maybe it would be possible.
No matter what happens, do whatever you must to survive.
That's a rule I set for myself when
I got started in this business.
Regardless of what you face,
put your own life ahead of anything or anyone.
Look, kid, if you try to save someone and you
get yourself killed, it'll all be for nothing.
I don't think it's possible to save everyone.
But I do want to save as many as I possibly can.
Well, suit yourself.
This target really is a nasty piece of work.
Do you know him?
The Mage Odd Vorzak.
He's a Dead Apostle who uses his
bee familiars to create his ghouls.
The Mage's Association has
put a huge bounty on his head.
You know a lot about him.
He causes destruction wherever he goes.
The last town he visited was
completely and utterly annihilated.
Our town.
Natalia, can I have one of those too?
How old do you have to be in
your country to smoke tobacco?
I won't try to stop you,
but they aren't good for you.
What's his destination?
There's a flight from Paris to New York in four days.
Vorzak will be on board.
I'll be handling this myself.
This guy is a clever target who
managed to give me the slip once.
You gotta clean up your own messes, right?
So, even you fail sometimes?
That should tell you how tough he really is.
What should I do?
I'm fairly certain he has associates
working for him in New York.
I want you to go there and eliminate them.
Then you'll fight Vorzak alone.
He can't keep his bees with him
in a carry‐on when he flies.
I see.
There's no risk of him getting away from you this time.
Shut your mouth, kid.
Kid, do you copy?
Roger.
Loud and clear.
All right, good luck to both of us then.
That was much easier than I expected.
Yes, well, I'm just glad you were able
to kill him with a minimum of force.
All right, Kiritsugu,
his corpse is in the passenger cabin.
Are you ready to carry it out?
I've secured a vehicle.
The only thing we need now is a doctor
who will carry out our sick patient.
I don't have a license, but that's okay.
Hey.
Natalia, what's wrong?
A ghoul!
We have a big problem here.
He was keeping the bees inside of his own body.
Natalia, you have to get out.
I'm not exactly close to the ground here.
I didn't come prepared to sky dive out of here.
This isn't good.
Looks like they've taken the cockpit.
I've got no choice.
Natalia, what are you gonna do?
I am coming home.
I'm coming home alive
carrying Vorzak's body.
But first I need to do something about this plane.
You got something to say?
Yeah.
You can do this, Natalia.
That'll do.
Prepare a nice warm bed for me and wait.
Hey, kid, do you read me?
You didn't fall asleep, did you?
Reading you loud and clear, Natalia.
We've both been up all night.
It's a rough morning.
If you'd slept in a bad last
night with me stuck up here,
I would have to kill
you after this is over.
Now, I have good news and bad news.
Which do you want first?
Isn't it a rule that you always
start with the good news?
Okay.
I guess I'll start with the good news then.
For the time being, I'm alive.
The plane is also undamaged.
I made it up to the cockpit fairly easy,
though repairing the comms array wasn't easy at all.
I also think I can pilot it, assuming
the controls are similar to a Cessna.
Have you contacted the control tower?
I have.
At first they thought I was
pulling some kind of prank.
Those kind folks say they'll escort me in.
All right.
And the bad news?
I'm the only one here who hasn't been bitten or stung.
300 passengers and crew, they're all ghouls now.
All that separates me from the
Night of the Living Flying Dead
is the damn cockpit security door.
Spooky, right?
Given everything you've just told me,
will you be able to make it out of this alive?
Well, the cockpit door is actually pretty tough.
They're scratching at it as we speak,
but they can't seem to break it down.
It's the landing that's worrying me.
This thing may be too big for me to handle by myself.
Natalia, I know you'll be able to manage it.
Were those words of encouragement?
It's good to hear them from you.
I can handle the landing.
But what do I do with all these monsters in back?
Hm.
Don't worry about that.
I have it all worked out, Natalia.
Hm?
I can always count on you.
50 more minutes till we get to the airport.
That's a little bit too long to spend praying.
Kid, keep me company for a while, okay?
I can do that.
Way back when you first said you
wanted to help me with my work,
I really didn't know how to respond.
You just didn't look ready to
relent no matter what I said.
So, I showed that little promise as a student?
No, it's not that.
You had a lot of potential.
Too much.
What does that mean?
The ability to pull a trigger to
kill regardless of your feelings
is a skill most killers take
many years to fully develop.
You had that skill from the very start.
It's a hell of a gift.
But choosing your occupation based solely on your
talents doesn't necessarily guarantee your happiness.
If you think only of what you should do
and completely ignore what you want to do,
then you're just a simple
machine, a force of nature.
That isn't how a human being should live.
I'm surprised.
You know, I always thought of you
as a much colder person than that.
What are you talking about?
Of course I'm cold.
In all these years, have I ever
spoiled you or coddled you even once?
True, you've always been a rather strict teacher.
You never held anything back
and taught me what you could.
Under normal circumstances,
training a boy like you is the father's job.
But...well...
I'm afraid that in your case
I basically took away your chance
for that kind of upbringing.
Anyway, I...
I did feel a little bad about it.
This was the only way of life I knew how to teach you.
So you consider yourself my dad?
I'm a full‐grown woman, you rude little jerk.
At least call me mother.
You're right.
Sorry.
I spent an awfully long time on
my own in this bloody business.
So long that I even lost track
of the fact that I was alone.
But...it's been pretty entertaining in its own way,
having something like a family in my life.
For me too.
For all these years,
I did always think of you as a mother.
I was happy to have you.
Look, kid, I think we'd better quit saying stuff
that'll embarrass us next time we see each other, okay?
You're throwing me off my game.
I've got to land this thing in 20 minutes or so.
If I'm laughing over what we were just talking
about and screw up, I'll end up dead, you know?
Sorry, I'll stop.
You know, maybe I'm just getting too old for this job.
Maybe the reason I screwed up so badly
is because playing at having a
family made me lower my guard.
If that's true, I should walk away.
Maybe it's time to retire.
If you quit this job,
what would you do with your life?
If I weren't working...
The only thing left for me to do
would be to really act like a mother, I guess.
Natalia, you are...
...my real family.
Did you see that, Shirley?
I killed someone again,
just like I did with my dad.
I didn't screw up like I did with you.
I saved an awful lot of lives.
If Natalia had landed that plane safely,
there's no telling how many people
might have died.
Her sacrifice prevented all of that.
So I...
Shirley, I...
Shut your mouth.
Just shut up.
Bastard!
Tell me, Kerry,
what do you want to grow up to be?
I...
I want to...