Finally made it.
Hey, Waver!
No, no, not there. Over here.
Grandpa, what are you doing up there?
Enough with the questions, just come on up here.
Let's talk for a while.
He wants to talk?
Why do we have to talk on the roof?
Grandpa, can't it wait a while?
Oh, come on, don't be like that.
He really does like you, boy.
Rider, come on, they're just under my spell and...
Oh, go up there.
The old man seems to have something
important he wants to tell you.
Relax, boy, I'll patrol the area and keep watch.
Don't be shy.
That's not the problem.
I love it up here.
This is the best place to catch
the first rays of the morning sun.
Take a seat.
Here, I even have some coffee for you,
it'll warm you up.
Grandpa, just how long have you been sitting up here?
When I woke up this morning and checked in on
you, I saw you hadn't made it back yet,
so I thought I'd take the opportunity to watch the sun
come up while I waited for my grandson to come home.
When you were just a tyke, we used to come up to
the roof on clear nights and stargaze all the time.
Do you remember?
Yeah, I guess.
When Martha and I decided to live in Japan, we made
sure to build our house up here in the hills of Miyama
and built it with a large skylight,
so we could easily gain access to the roof.
We dreamed of sitting up here gazing at the beautiful
sky with our grandchildren alongside us,
entranced by the stars as much as we were.
We never thought our wish would
actually come true, though.
In all these years, our real grandchildren never
once came up here to watch the sky with us.
Sadly, whenever I've come up here to
stargaze, I've always been alone until now.
Now, Waver, you really aren't our grandson, are you?
It's very strange, the way Martha
and I were so completely convinced that
you were actually part of our family.
To be honest, you were a bit
too nice to be our grandson.
You really messed up there.
I suppose you're pretty mad.
Well, I guess I probably have every right to be, Waver.
But lately, Martha's been acting so happy
and smiling nearly every moment of every day.
I couldn't have imagined her like that before.
Really, I'm very grateful to the both of you.
It's been quite a blessing.
Besides, it doesn't seem to
me you decided to move in
with Martha and I because you
intended to cause us any harm.
So, what do you think?
If you can, Martha and I would really like
it if you'd stay with us a while longer.
I'm sorry, I can't promise that.
I can't even guarantee I'll make it back here safely.
So, I gather you two are risking your lives?
Yes.
Well, I can't even begin to venture a guess as to
how important whatever it is you're doing is to you,
but when you've had a long life
like me and look back on it all,
you come to realize that there is absolutely nothing
in this world so valuable or so important
that it's really worth risking that life for.
I guess it's been about 40 hours
since I last slept...maybe more.
To win the battle and summon the grail,
one must perform the ritual at the location
of one of the four Fuyuki ley lines.
At two of them, the church and the Tohsaka Estate,
Kirei Kotomine was nowhere to be found,
which leaves the other two:
Here at Mt. Enzo and the Fuyuki Citizens Building.
Given the ley lines' relative power,
this one is more likely.
Even if he's chosen the Citizens Building,
I can launch a frontal assault there.
If Maiya were still alive,
I would have sent her to secure it.
Once again, I'm all alone.
Come to think of it,
I never really figured her into my plans.
Since last night,
I've been searching the whole city for
Irisviel's location, but I found no sign of her.
I am deeply sorry.
Well, then, if you need me,
summon me using the command seal.
Wake up.
Can you hear me, woman?
So, it's you, Kirei.
This building was once the place where
Caster's young master hid,
though it appears that Kiritsugu
Emiya was never able to locate it.
Soon, the Holy Grail War will be over.
It's likely that I'll be the one that will have
the power to grant the wish of the Einzberns.
Are you so unhappy that it would be me?
There is but one man to whom I would entrust the grail,
and it is certainly not you, Inquisitor.
Kiritsugu Emiya has already
seen right through you, Kirei.
He recognizes you as his most dangerous enemy.
You can't escape.
Your words are as the gospel to my ears.
Kiritsugu Emiya is exactly as
I imagined him to be after all.
How laughable.
You couldn't be any further from him if you tried.
What did you say?
Even though Kiritsugu can see through you,
the reverse is impossible.
You have none of the wonderful things
that he carries deep inside his heart.
Why do you speak of me in such a manner, woman?
I freely admit it, I'm a man
who is empty and desolate inside.
So, how do he and I differ?
Devoted himself to one fruitless
war after another for years?
Senseless slaughter,
utter recklessness, wasted effort?!
If he does not doubt or find this life
pointless as I do, then what is he?
Tell me, what is his wish?
What would he ask of the Holy Grail?
What prayer would he entrust
to the wish‐granting device?
Very well, I'll tell you.
Kiritsugu Emiya's wish
is humanity's salvation,
an end to all warfare
and bloodshed and suffering...
forever.
True peace upon the Earth.
What was that?
You can never understand it.
That is the difference between you two;
he has something to believe in.
Conflict is intrinsic to humanity.
To eliminate it completely would mean
the elimination of humanity itself.
As an ideal, it's totally futile,
nonsense that a child would spout.
Yes, and that is why his only
hope is for a true miracle.
Many times, Kiritsugu has been forced to...
to sacrifice the lives of people
he's loved because of his beliefs.
Yes, you see, he's far too kind to chase ideals.
He must love even knowing
it will mean losing that love.
I understand.
I understand well.
So, that is Kiritsugu Emiya.
At last, I see it, my reason for fighting.
Kiritsugu Emiya, I shall grind your
ideals to dust right before you,
along with the Holy
Grail you long for.
Oh, you finally woke up, boy.
I thought I told you to
wake me up at nightfall.
Did you forget?
Oh, sorry, but I thought it might be
good to take our time with preparations.
Tonight, there is no reason to rush.
How come?
I can't say why exactly.
It feels like everything will be concluding tonight.
Uh‐huh.
The night air seems way too still.
Is that because there are fewer
participants still in the fight?
From now on, only the truly
strong remain in the battle.
W‐what was that?
It's a very strange mana surge.
I felt something similar before.
Look at that pattern.
What is it... some kind of secret code, do you think?
Four and seven in different colors.
"Success and victory."
If they're sending up that signal...
...does that mean that someone
got the grail and the war is over?
No, it's coming up from
a completely different
direction than the church is,
which means that the church
didn't send the message.
In essence, somebody is getting way ahead
of themselves and claiming to be victorious.
That says, "If you
object, come and get me!"
It is an obvious challenge.
It looks like the big showdown
is going to happen tonight.
I see, that means this is it, then.
Quite right, boy!
Now that we have our battlefield,
I must go forth and bring honor to the rider
class and ride gloriously into the final fray!
Come now, my steed!
Now then, boy, it may not be as
smooth a ride as by chariot, but... Huh?
Hey, what are you waiting for?
Come on!
From this point,
only the truly strong can continue, right?
My servant, Rider, by his command
seal, Waver Velvet orders you...
fight until you attain the victory you seek.
And by my command seal, I further order that
you, Rider, go now and win the Holy Grail.
And by command seal, I further order, Rider,
take the world for your own.
I will not tolerate failure.
There, it's all over.
I'm no longer your master.
Go, go wherever you wish.
I don't even wanna see you.
I'll certainly be on my way in a moment,
but after all those annoying orders you just gave,
surely you're prepared to see this though to the end?
You total idiot, listen to me!
I used the command seals and quit being your master!
Why would you still wanna take me, dammit?!
I'm not your...
Master or not, boy, you are still my friend
and always will be.
Huh?
I'm...you mean...
you're really okay with me?
You want someone like me by your side?
What are you saying?
After all the battles you and I have seen
together, you have to ask that?
Idiot.
Up until now, have you not faced
the same enemies as I have?
That means you're my friend.
So, be proud and consider yourself
my equal.
All right, I shall begin by
obeying the first of your orders.
Now, boy, keep your eyes open to the end!
Well, let's see what she can do.
Right before my open eyes!
He chose the place least suited to the required
ritual only to gain the early initiative in battle.
In other words, his plan is not to obtain the grail,
but rather to use it as bait
to lure me and the other masters into a
trap, then kill us all.
That simplifies things.
If he's going to be this incompetent,
I'll just outmaneuver and eliminate him quickly.
Kirei Kotomine.
Hm, very impressive.
I must say, you look particularly
ferocious tonight, Kirei.
Now what will you do?
Do you wish for me to stay here and wait?
Unleashing all of your power at this close
range could endanger the ceremony itself.
If you want to fight it full strength
you'll have to go out and meet them.
Very well, what if this place
falls under attack while I'm gone?
Will you allow me to utilize the
command seals to save myself?
I will, but I do not guarantee the Holy Grail's safety.
For tonight, I shant be holding back.
That would be the worst outcome,
but if that should happen, it will be fate.
Kirei, you seem to have finally
found your reason to fight,
but have you still no prayer to offer the Holy Grail?
I can think of nothing I want.
My only hope is that nothing will interfere with
the conduct of the battle we're about to enter.
Honestly, Kirei, as I suspected, the only recourse is
to let the grail reveal what hides within your heart.
Oh, if it appears as if Saber will
be arriving here before I can return,
just have Berserker entertain
her for a little while.
Understood.
Speaking of Saber, what happened to
the doll that was so important to her?
The Holy Grail's vessel is inside of her, is it not?
I took her life.
I had no reason to let her continue living.
Are you crying?
Are you, Mother?
Hey, Mother, I had a scary dream.
I dreamed that I turned into a cup,
and then I dreamed that these seven
gigantic lumps started to come into my body.
It's okay, it's okay.
I would never let that happen.
I promise that will never happen to you, Illya.
I know in my heart that you'll be
released from the shackles of fate.
Where am I?
Inside the Holy Grail?
This shouldn't be happening!
If I'm here...
who am I?
That's right, this is inside the Holy Grail:
The omnipotent wish‐granting device
that will dispel all the world's sadness
and remove all its suffering.
I will have the power to make that happen.
The end is nearly at hand.