My apologies for keeping you waiting.
As you can imagine,
things have been rather hectic this evening.
I'm sure it couldn't be helped
given the extraordinary situation.
It's going to be rather difficult to cover all that up.
Well, perhaps.
What has happened is far too much for
the holy church to handle by herself,
and so we are accepting any and all aid
proffered for assistance in this effort.
Now the, down to business.
Regarding my request, I'm curious
as to what your decision is, Father.
I speak, of course,
of the reward offered for Caster's defeat.
This is wonderful.
Once I receive the command seal for killing Caster,
Diarmuid and I will finally be truly connected forever.
My right hand!
It's gone, it's gone!
I need it or I...
I cannot call Diarmuid,
I won't be able to make him care for me.
My right hand.
My right hand, my right hand,
my right hand, my right hand!
Hand...
my right hand.
Success.
I have secured Sola‐Ui over in New Town.
I removed the command seals in her right arm.
Fine.
Get out of there immediately.
Lancer should be returning any time now.
Roger.
I saved Kariya Matou.
Without doubt, he could threaten my master.
There is no excuse.
This is an act of rebellion.
But what is this I'm feeling?
It is not regret.
Could it be...
that I'm excited about this?
Of course, it's true that in the defeat
of the Servant Caster and his master,
the Servant Lancer played an important
part in the overall conduct of the battle.
A fact varified by a number of
reports from various observers.
Then it's clear.
As master of Lancer, I have the right
to receive one of the command seals.
It's not that simple.
Lord Kayneth Archibald...
I am unsure whether it is at all inappropriate
to consider you a master at this point.
Father, my pact with Lancer
was from the outset executed jointly
by myself and my fiancee, Sola‐Ui.
And is Sola‐Ui not the one currently
supplying mana to the servant?
And is she not also acting as defacto
caretaker for the command seals?
Yes, that's true.
I've temporarily given her
custody of the command seals.
However, the rights accorded by the
pact still legally reside with me.
After all, Father, the petition I submitted
to the church to be considered a master
was filed in my name and did not include Sola‐Ui.
Very well, I agree.
Your rights as a master shall remain intact.
Now, Lord Archibald, extend your hand, please.
Take this and drink from it.
This is my blood, the blood of the everlasting covenant
which will be poured out for you and for all mankind.
Do this in my memory.
I hope you will continue to fight a noble
battle for the Grail as a worthy master.
Yes, of course, Father.
I'm down to a single command seal.
My situation remains dire.
I cannot allow the other masters an
opportunity to acquire an additional seal,
not if I intend to possess the Holy Grail.
Mistress Sola‐Ui.
You complete incompetent!
You useless bumbling fool!
You couldn't even protect a
single woman from being attacked?!
Huh.
I'm sick of all your talk of chivalry.
I am grievously sorry, Master.
She may have been a mere substitute,
but you even failed to protect your
own master from nearly being killed!
What good are you as a servant, I ask you?
I'm amazed you had the unmitigated
nerve to return here alone.
Please understand, my master.
Mistress Sola‐Ui and I never entered
into a proper pact,
and as such we could not sense each other's presence.
That's no excuse.
You should've taken special
care to ensure her safety.
My master, fret not.
Mistress Sola‐Ui yet lives.
She continues to supply me with mana.
That's irrelevant!
You are not her servant.
And therefore you can not discern her location.
So it doesn't matter in the least
whether or not you know if she's alive.
Oh, Sola‐Ui, I should've never
given you those command seals.
I could not dissuade her, Master.
I share in the responsibility.
I really can't believe you
had the nerve to say that.
Don't try fooling me, Lancer.
It was you who encouraged
Sola‐Ui to become ambitious.
I would never do that, Master.
It's just as it was in the legend.
Are you truly incapable of seeing your Lord's
fiancee without attempting to seduce her?
My master...
please retract those words right now.
Have I struck a nerve, Lancer?
You're nothing but a beast who swore an
oath of eternal loyalty to his master.
And then gave into prurient
lust when the moment suited him.
My master.
My lord.
Why will you not understand?
Master, I wished only to defend my honor,
to fight well in noble battle,
and achieve victory on your behalf.
Don't you ever speak to me in that manner, Servant!
Understand your place.
You're nothing but a spectral ghost,
granted form and substance by magic.
You dare to sit there and lecture your master!
It is absurd and unacceptable!
If you are so dissatisfied,
I believe you have but one option available.
Use your precious pride to resist my command seal.
You'll never win.
You servants are mere puppets,
and this seal the string that controls you.
Lord Kayneth.
Master.
What now?
Don't tell me,
you still have something to say to me?
No.
That isn't it.
Something's approaching this building.
Look, Saber, it's just as Kiritsugu said.
There are traces of a magical barrier,
but it's very strange.
It hasn't been properly maintained.
It's already starting to... fall apart.
I did not expect to see you here, Saber.
Well, my...
allies found this place and informed me.
They said that this was your location.
You would not happen to know where my
master's betrothed is, would you, Saber?
My master has not heard from her.
No, I do not.
What of it, Lancer?
Never mind, forget it.
Anyway, are you sure about this?
I am certain you did not come
to engage in idle chit‐chat?
After all, you must be completely exhausted
after employing that technique against Caster.
No more so than all the other servants.
I'm certain.
None of them will be fighting further tonight.
They will focus on defense.
That is why we needn't worry about being interrupted.
Dawn is nearly upon us.
But this may be the best night
for us to finally finish our battle.
What say you, Lancer?
Hm.
Brave Saber.
The only thing in this world
that still grants my heart peace
is your honor and the purity
of your fighting spirit.
Her attacks are too weak.
Saber, why?
You will not use your left hand?
Don't get the wrong idea, Lancer.
If I use my left hand here,
the shame is certain to dull my blade
against your powerful spear.
A dulling such as that would be fatal.
Saber.
Therefore, Diarmuid...
...this is my best strategy,
the path that will allow me to defeat you.
Pride is in the blade of chivalry.
Saber...
I am glad I was able to meet you.
I am first Bure of Fianna,
Diarmuid O'Dyna.
I come for you.
Splendid.
For this night,
Artoria Pendragon accepts your challenge.
Come then.
Why does he not win?
If he has no certain path to victory, should he not
escape with his master instead of risking defeat?
Right now our highest priority should
be to locate and rescue Sola‐Ui.
Why can't he not understand even that
simple concept?! He's a useless servant!
Why him?
Of all people?
This is...
a Self‐Geis Scroll.
A powerful magical item
that has been used throughout the ages
to forge an absolutely unbreakable pact
between one mage and another.
"Binding spell.
Affected party, Kiritsugu Emiya.
The crest of the Emiya family
orders the following actions:
the pledge is to be obeyed by the affected party
upon fulfillment of the terms described herein.
Pledge that Kiritsugu, son of Norikata,
fifth heir to the house of Emiya
will be forever forbidden from
harming Kayneth El‐Melloi Archibald
and Sola‐Ui Nuada‐Re Sophia‐Ri,
or from intending to, by his hand, harm or injure
them or cause them pain in any way whatsoever.
Terms.
In principle, the curse of the Geis cannot be
removed by any means known to the mage world.
Even if you forfeit your life,
as long as the magic crest exists,
it will bind your soul
even in death.
It's true that if I do what's written
on this scroll, he cannot kill me?
But under these terms, my fight, the fight for
which I prepared my entire life... will end here.
The Grail.
And the Archibald family pride.
He asks me to throw it all away?
Sola‐Ui.
Use your remaining command seals to
compel your servant to commit suicide.
The terms of the agreement have been met.
You wanna win!
You wanna win so desperately.
You desire the Grail so desperately,
you have crushed...  you have
crushed my sole remaining wish.
And you just stand there!
Do you not feel any shame at all?!
I will never forgive you.
I will never forgive any of you!
You inhuman monsters who have
ruined the honor of a knight.
Let my blood taint your dreams forever!
May the Grail be cursed!
May the wish it grants bring disaster!
And when you fall into the searing pits of hell,
you'll remember the hateful rate of Diarmuid!
So now the Geis binds you?
Yes, it is sealed.
I can longer kill you or Sola‐Ui.
I can't, but...
Kill me.
Kill me now.
Sorry.
Our pact forbids me to.
Kiritsugu Emiya.
I finally recognize you as
the lowly beast that you are.
I believed that our paths differed,
but we shared a mutual goal.
I was a fool to think this.
Until now, I placed my faith in Irisviel's words,
and thus did not doubt your intentions.
But now...
I can no longer believe that your desire for the Grail
has anything to do with salvation.
Answer me, Kiritsugu!
What is the true reason you desire the Grail?
Even should my sword at the
end of this war win the Grail.
If that means I must yield it to you, I must...
Answer her, Kiritsugu!
After everything that has happened,
you owe her an explanation!
You know, this incident is the very first time
you've seen how I kill, Iris.
If you only eliminate a master, the servant
may enter into a pact with another party.
So I had to eliminate the master
and the servant simultaneously.
No, Kiritsugu.
Not to me.
Talk to Saber.
She's the one who needs to hear your words now.
No.
Honor, glory...
there's really no point in speaking to a killer
who extols the virtue of such things.
You would even insult chivalry to my face, monster!
A knight cannot save the world.
Knights call certain methods of fighting good,
and others evil, acting as if
there were some sacred nobility to the battlefield.
Such illusions created by heroes throughout history
have led countless young
men to their bloody deaths,
all for the sake of this glory
and honor they all extol.
They are not illusions!
Even the taking of a life in battle
as an act as a human being
must have ideals,
otherwise every war would bring the
very fires of hell to this world.
And there you go...
you heard her, Iris.
Our heroic spirit over there considers
a battlefield to be better than hell.
What a joke.
A battlefield is hell itself.
There's no hope to be had on one.
There is nothing but unspeakable despair.
Just a soulless cry we call victory.
Paid for by the pain of the defeated.
But humanity has never recognized this truth.
And the reason is that in every era a dazzling hero
has blinded the people with their legends and kept
them from seeing the evil of bloodshed they bring.
True human nature has not advanced
a step beyond the Stone Age.
Tell me this, Kiritsugu.
Do you force Saber to endure such humiliation
because of your hatred for the heroic spirits?
Of course not.
Personal feelings don't enter into it.
I will win the Holy
Grail and save the world.
And I will wage that war with the most
appropriate weapons I have at my disposal.
Justice and righteousness cannot save the world.
I care nothing for such things.
Kiritsugu, don't you understand?
If you do evil to stop evil,
that rage and hatred will
give rise to new conflict.
Kiritsugu Emiya,
I do not know what betrayed you,
or what has caused you to lose all hope,
but your sorrow and rage are found only in
those who at one time sought for justice.
Kiritsugu, in youth, your true self,
wished to be a hero, did it not?
A hero to save the world.
You believed in that.
You desired it more than life.
Am I wrong?
I will break this endless cycle.
The Grail will make that possible.
I'll ensure that the blood I spill in Fuyuki
is the last that humanity will ever shed.
If that means I must stain my
hands with every evil in the world,
I don't care.
If that will save the world,
then I do it gladly.
Kiritsugu has left, hasn't he?
Irisviel?
Irisviel!