Well, everything went smoothly.
These games of yours are tiresome and tedious
and squander my precious time, Tokiomi.
I am very grateful, Your Highness.
King of all Kings, Gilgamesh.
Your deeds tonight will establish your prowess as king
and they will reveal which of our
foes we must hunt and eliminate.
I ask only that you stay your hand
for just a little while longer.
Very well.
For the time being, I shall amuse myself
with simple reconnaissance.
This age truly fascinates me.
I take that to mean the modern
world is to your liking?
It's unspeakably ugly, but that is fine
in its own way.
The important thing is whether any of the
treasures available here are truly worthy of me.
Of course, if I find there is nothing in
this world that deserves my adoration,
you will pay dearly for summoning me.
Of that, you can be certain, Tokiomi.
Worry not; the Holy Grail is surely an
item fit to please the King of Heroes.
That will be for me to ultimately determine
and me alone.
No matter, I'll play along with
your little schemes for the moment.
Everything of value in this world belongs to me,
so I can assure you, no matter how
precious this grail of yours may be,
I will never let a lowly mongrel
even touch it without my consent.
Tokiomi, I'll leave the details to you.
My, my, honestly,
I'm amazed Gilgamesh materialized
within the archer class
considering their reputation for solo combat skills.
Well, I can let Kirei handle things from here.
For now, everything is
proceeding according to plan.
Assassin was killed?
Hey, Rider, this is big news!
One of the seven is already out!
Hey.
Come on, don't you get it?
Assassin was killed!
Mm‐hmm.
Rider, the Holy Grail War has started!
I've been out gathering information day after
day after day after day, every single damn day!
You sit around eating cookies watching stuff on the VCR!
You're worse than a
familiar, worse than a rat!
And I told you that I always want you to
take spirit form when I don't need you.
I'm giving you all the manna while you're
doing nothing but eating and watching!
Quit your whining.
Nobody cares if Assassin is dead or alive.
The only thing he's good at is
skulking around in the shadows.
He could never pose a threat to me.
Anyway, boy, here, this is what matters!
This, the big black thing they call a B‐2!
It's wonderful!
I'm thinking about buying 10 or so.
What do you think?
For that much money, it'd be faster to
just buy the whole country outright.
Oh, I see.
So, the question is where to procure the money.
Were there some major city nearby, such as Persepolis,
we could simply plunder it and get what we need.
For the moment, I think that the biggest
obstacle for us will be this Clinton guy.
He will prove a more formidable
opponent than Darius III.
Well, regardless of all that, I think it's a pretty good
thing that Assassin was eliminated right off the bat.
I mean, aren't you the type who
prefers to face his enemy head‐on?
So, it's good news for us that the guy who uses sneak
attacks and devious tricks to fight his battles is out.
We could get some good use from
these Tomahawk things, too.
Saber, Lancer, Archer, the three great knight classes,
not to mention the Berserker,
whose sole skill is to break things,
are gonna be toast when you use
that noble phantasm of yours.
That just leaves Caster to worry about.
If we could only find out what
his true identity is, we could...
How was Assassin taken down?
Huh?
Tell me.
Who was it that defeated him?
You saw it, right?
I, uh, I think it was Tohsaka's servant.
It was brutal:
his brilliant appearance, his quick attacks,
everything was golden, bright, and flashy.
It all happened so fast, I couldn't tell what...
You fool!
If I am to fight someone, it will be the victor
of all the other battles between the servants.
Why weren't you paying attention to how he won?
Well, it matters not.
Did anything else strike you about the flashy
gold man or the way he fought the battle?
But...but it was the middle of the
night and it was all over in a second.
Hey, Rider, normally a servant
only has one noble phantasm, right?
Yes, of course, that's the rule.
But how many isn't the correct way
to conceptualize a noble phantasm.
As I'm sure you already know, a noble phantasm is the
physical manifestation of a hero's most indelible legend
or most famous tale.
Sometimes, it may be a specific
ability or a special method of attack.
So, then, is there a noble phantasm that consists
of throwing dozens of swords at an opponent?
A sword that makes copies of itself, really?
Huh, yes, it's possible.
That could still qualify as a single noble phantasm.
But, wait, those swords weren't copies.
Each one of them had a completely different shape.
Ah, forget it, we'll just have to discover each
of our enemies' identities as we encounter them.
Do you really think that would be wise?
Yes, actually it'll be more fun!
Food, sex, sleep, and war!
Whatever you do,
you should always enjoy it to the fullest;
that is the secret of life.
All right now, let's go see if we can find
ourselves some invigorating entertainment outside.
We ride forth, boy!
Prepare yourself!
Uh, we ride forth? To where?
Well, to somewhere.
We can go anywhere!
Oh, come on, now!
Let's face it, you can't have been
the only one who was watching Tohsaka,
which means that news of Assassin's
death is making the rounds.
The others are probably going to
spring into action all at once,
but we shall crush each of them as we come across them.
Go find and crush them all?
It won't be that easy.
I am Rider
and my speed far exceeds that of any
other servant I will face in this war.
Wait, wait, wait, not here!
You'll blow up the whole house!
My servant has been lost.
I have forfeited my rights as a master
and cannot continue the Holy Grail War.
In accordance with the treaty, I, Kirei
Kotomine, ask that the church grant me sanctuary.
Request granted.
In my role as overseer of this war,
I, Risei Kotomine,
guarantee your safety here.
Enter in peace.
Father, isn't this church being watched?
No, this holy place has been
declared a neutral sanctuary.
The Holy Church will censure any
master who dares defy the decree.
Then, you're sure it's safe here?
Mmm.
But still, you should keep watch just in case.
Post a guard here at all times just to be sure.
Yes, understood.
Tell me, who was observing the battle?
Before the battle, I detected the presence
of familiars from four separate masters.
Two days ago, I was able to confirm the
summoning of the final servant, Caster.
All of the Holy Grail War servants should have
now arrived and the fighting will begin shortly.
One unaccounted for.
I had hoped that all the masters would be
watching and taking note of the encounter.
At this point in the war, observing the three families'
estates would be a master's obvious course of action.
That's right, and if they can't even think to do that,
it would never even begin to occur to them
to worry about the existence of us assassins.
We spirits of the shadows shall sneak up behind
those masters who believe Assassin to be dead.
We shall sneak up behind them,
and this time, we shall become
true shadows in the darkness.
The battle for the grail is now at hand.
At last, it's time for the
fourth Holy Grail War to begin.
These tired old eyes of mine will finally
see a wondrous miracle be performed.
Oh, my!
So, this is where Kiritsugu was born?
Well, Saber, how did you enjoy
your journey through the sky?
It was really nothing to speak of.
It was far simpler than I had actually anticipated.
Yes, well, I suppose that flying must be
nothing special to a real hero, right?
No, that's not it.
Upon materialization, all servants
receive knowledge of the modern world.
If required, I could even pilot
this aircraft with relative ease.
You could?
Are you serious?
My riding skill allows me to
command any beast or vehicle,
with the only exception being
phantasmal or divine beasts.
Once I put the saddle between my legs
and take the reins, I'm in control.
The saddle between your legs and take the reins?
What is it?
Did I say something amusing to you?
Uh‐uh.
Still, you must be the only servant who
has flown in an airplane in physical form.
I apologize for that.
If only I could take spirit form.
No, I didn't mean it like that, really.
I never get tired of watching you.
Irisviel, is there something odd about me?
No, no, not at all.
When you laugh like that,
there seems to be some hidden meaning behind it.
What is it?
I want you to be frank with me.
It means that your being stuck in
physical form isn't without its merits.
It's given me many enjoyable
hours of choosing outfits for you.
Irisviel, is this manner of dress
truly common for women of this era?
I choose it for you to balance out my own outfit.
You don't care for it?
No, it is fine.
It is rather easy to move in, and
besides, I'm used to dressing as a man.
This place is so very alive!
Kiritsugu was supposed to have arrived
here in Japan already, wasn't he?
That's right, 12 hours before us.
But, don't worry, he'll find us as
soon as he's certain the time is right.
For the moment, we'll just have to keep an eye
on things so that we can act when the time comes.
We've come all this way, I'd like to
enjoy the city before the fighting starts.
That's dangerous.
We should first concentrate on securing a base
of operations and discuss plans with Kiritsugu.
Well, yes, I suppose you're right about that.
But it's such a waste; we've come all
this way to such an exciting place!
That, and...
it's my very first time travelling.
Oh?
This is the first time I've ever ventured out
into the world outside the confines of my home.
Are you telling me that you spent
your entire life inside that castle?
You see, I was a puppet created
specifically for the Holy Grail War.
Of course, it isn't as though I'm wholly ignorant;
Kiritsugu brought me movies and videos and pictures,
and he's tried in every way to teach me
everything he could about the outside world.
But this is the first time that I've actually
been able to see it with my own eyes,
and so, please, forgive me!
I got overly excited.
Please stop the car.
Walking through the city will be a
brand new experience for me as well.
It is a knight's duty to serve as escort;
I shall do my very best.
Come with me.
The equipment you requested arrived a little while ago.
Madam Irisviel and Saber have just
arrived here in Fuyuki as well.
All the other masters will likely assume that
she is Saber's master and act accordingly.
Understood.
There was an incident last night at the Tohsaka Estate.
I recorded this footage.
What's your analysis of this?
It seems too good to be true.
There seem to be insufficient time
between Assassin's infiltration
and the Tohsaka servants' attack.
Assassin has a skill that masks his presence,
making it improbable he was detected in advance.
It is my opinion that Tohsaka was expecting an intruder.
In a battle amongst servants,
learning their identities is quite critical.
Why would Tohsaka expose his servant like he did?
He must have had a very good reason.
I suppose he had to.
Tell me, what became of Assassin's master?
He took refuge in a church last night.
The overseer declared him to be under his protection.
Assassin's master is Kirei Kotomine.
Maiya, send a familiar to watch the Fuyuki church.
Are you certain of that?
Masters are forbidding to take
action inside the neutral zone.
That's been established around the church.
Place it just far enough away
that the priest won't be able to spot it.
Very well, understood.
The item I left you, where is it?
Right here.
Approximately two seconds.
I'm surprised.
Indeed.
I was just thinking,
Illya weighs a lot less than that Walther.
She's...eight years old already.
Focus on the matter at
hand, just empty your mind.
Think of nothing else except your plan.
It's wonderful!
Almost like a mirror that reflects the night sky.
It's fun to walk around a strange and wondrous
new town accompanied by a gallant gentleman.
Did I really make an acceptable gentleman escort?
You were absolutely perfect, Saber.
You really were the most wonderful
knight a girl could ever hope for.
You honor me, Your Highness.
Saber, do you like the sea?
I suppose; I don't really know.
In my country, and way back in my time,
the sea was a source of attacks
by barbarians from the mainland.
I never felt any affection
for it and often hated it.
I feel kind of bad.
You're a girl, just as I am,
but when you were King Arthur, you never had the
luxury of enjoying simple things like this, did you?
So, what about your desires?
Surely, you would have much preferred to have
Kiritsugu escort you around town today, right?
Of course I would, but he couldn't.
It would only cause him pain and suffering.
Does Kiritsugu not enjoy the time he spends with you?
When he's happy, for some reason,
it seems to cause him pain.
An enemy servant?
Yes, making its presence known from the
shadows, 100 meters ahead.
It appears to be inviting us over to go and see it.
How thoughtful; it wishes
to decide on a battlefield.
Shall we take it up on its invitation?
I'd like nothing better.
Come on, Rider,
let's get down from here right now!
Take me down!
But why?
This is a nearly perfect vantage
point to survey the whole land.
I'm leaving!
No, wait!
Take me back down, I can't handle this!
Oh, calm yourself.
Waiting is a large part of war.
I wanna go... I wanna go back to England.
I told you not to be in such a damn hurry.
You see, things have finally begun to unfold out there.
This is going to be a lot of fun!
Welcome.
I have spent the entire day
searching the city for a worthy foe.
Everyone just slinks away, hiding in their little holes.
You, alone, have accepted my offer.
That pure energy surrounding you;
you are the servant called Saber, I presume?
Indeed, I am, and I presume that you
are the one that's called Lancer?
Being unable to honorably name myself to my opponent
in combat troubles me more than I can describe.
I harbor an enormous dislike of these rules.
Saber, please...be careful.
I can use my healing magic to
act as combat support for you.
But, more than that, Saber...
Just leave Lancer to me.
It troubles me that his master is in
hiding and has not yet shown himself.
Perhaps they plot something.
Watch yourself.
And, Irisviel, from this point on,
I entrust you to watch my back.
Very well, I will, Saber.
Grant me victory in this fight.
I will, without fail.