Rider, over there.
Are you scared, boy?
Yeah, I'm scared.
I'm wondering if this is what you mean
when you say that your heart is dancing.
Hm, it seems you're finally starting to understand.
The enemy is inside.
Berserker?
Are they having a party here?
Where is that little chariot of yours?
Well, the thing is,
I'm embarrassed to say I lost it to Saber in a battle.
Did you forget my decision?
I believe I told you that I would fight and
defeat you when you were at full strength.
True, the weapons at my disposal are somewhat depleted.
However, Iskandar tonight is less than perfect,
and thus, is far greater than perfection itself.
So I see.
Indeed the aura that is emanating from you
is unusually potent.
It appears you have come before me actually
believing that you have a chance of victory.
Hm.
King of Babylonia, a final word.
Our banquet's last question.
I shall allow it, speak.
Well, this is purely hypothetical of course,
but were my Ionioi Hetairoi
armed with your Gate of Babylon,
it would create the most powerful army imaginable.
Hm, so?
Why would you not ally yourself with me?
The two of us together could conquer the
universe and beyond if we desired it.
You never cease to amuse me, mongrel.
It has been ages since I laughed so hard at
gibberish spouted by one who is not a fool.
But unfortunately, I have had one comrade
and he is all I ever intend to have.
Furthermore, there is no need for there to be two kings.
The lonely path of kingship, eh?
With all respect due to a king,
I shall challenge your strong unwavering spirit.
Very well, show me what you think you can do,
King of Conquerors.
You are a usurper truly worthy of my judgment.
Are you guys actually friends with each other?
I could hardly be unfriendly to him.
After all, he may very well
be the last person I ever see.
Don't be stupid, you're not gonna be killed here today.
I won't allow it!
Have you forgotten my command seal?
You are right, ha.
You are exactly right.
Gather here, my glorious comrades!
Tonight we shall become the
greatest legends in all of eternity!
Our enemy is the mighty King of Heroes,
a most worthy opponent.
My warriors, let us show the first heroic spirit
our noble path of ultimate conquest!
Come to me, Lord of Conquering armies.
Now you will be privileged to
behold the sight of a true king.
Why are you suffering so much?
Because of Berserker.
He must fight a battle right now,
and needs mana.
Why?
Because that priest said so.
That priest?
Yeah.
He made a promise to me that he'd
give me the Grail once he got it.
If I have the Grail, I can save you, Sakura.
You're going to save me?
Yeah, of course.
Remember, I promised that we would all play together
like we used to with your mom and sister.
Then I'll be able to see Mother again?
See your mother.
Ahhh!
Now.
No good.
Can he see it?
He knows the lengths of my blade.
Could he be some knight I once knew?
From your skill I assume you
to be a knight of some renown,
and so I ask, if you know me to be Arturia Pendragon,
King of Britain and founder of Camelot...
...name yourself right now as a knight's pride demands.
Challenging me with your identity
concealed is tantamount to using deceit.
Who are you?
Impossible.
That's Arondight.
It can't be you.
Sir Lancelot.
But why, my friend?
You were esteemed as the greatest of
all the Knights of the Round Table.
How can you be Berserker?
Stop!
Lancelot.
You may indeed have saved them,
but you never led them.
Because I never really led them.
Enraptured by a false idol of a humble king
who always serves others.
My ideals, my kingship.
You're just a little girl.
Did how I rule drive you to this?
Please stop, Lancelot.
Uniting dreams beneath a banner of conquest.
I praise your efforts at least.
But foolish warriors, have you not learned?
Dreams disappear when the dreamer wakes,
every last one of them with no exception.
Therefore, it was inevitable that I
would be the one to stand in your way.
King of Conquerors,
now know the end of your eternal dream.
I shall show you the stark reality.
Here it comes!
Now, awaken Ea!
A stage worthy of you has been set!
Look up and behold, at my liege!
Hang on, boy!
What?
That sword is the Anti‐Universe Noble
Phantasm that can destroy all creation?
Hm.
Rider.
I just remembered, there is something important
that I must ask you.
Master Waver Velvet,
would you be willing to serve as my retainer?
You...
...you are my king, sire.
I will serve you with devotion.
Do me the honor of leading me.
Let me dream what you dream.
Ah, very well.
As king, my duty is to inspire others to dream,
and as my retainer, it is your sacred duty to see my
dream to the end and share it with future generations.
Now live, Waver.
See all of this through.
Live long and tell everyone you meet
of how your king comported himself,
of the last charge of Iskandar.
All right, it is time to go, Bucephalus!
Rider!
Glory lies beyond the horizon.
Challenge the unattainable.
Speak of conquest and make it real
for my men and for those who watch behind me.
Hm.
I swear to the gods, it is just one strange
toy after another with you, isn't it?
Have you awakened from your dream, King of Conquerors?
I suppose I have.
However, once again, during this glorious campaign,
my heart was able to dance a good deal.
Feel free to challenge me again as
often as you like, King of Conquerors.
This entire world is my garden
until the very end of time.
Thus, I guarantee you this,
it will never bore you.
It will always be entertaining.
That sounds very good.
Now I see.
It was the beating of my heart
that was the sound of Oceanus' waves.
Child, are you Rider's master?
No, I'm not.
I am his retainer.
Hm?
I see.
But child, if you are truly a loyal subject to him,
your duty now is to avenge your fallen sovereign.
If I challenge you, I'll die.
Yes, of course you will.
I can't do that.
I was ordered by him to survive.
Your loyalty is splendid.
Never allow anything to tarnish it.
He restoreth my soul.
He leadeth me in paths of righteousness
for his name's sake.
Yea, though I walk through the
valley of the shadow of death,
I will fear no evil,
for thou art with me.
Thy rod and thy staff,
they comfort me.
Thou preparest a table before me.
Thou anointest my head with oil.
My cup runneth over.
Surely goodness and mercy shall
follow me all the days of my life.
My cup runneth over.
Surely goodness and mercy shall
follow me all the days of my life.