By my third command seal, I order you again.
Stop!
Now, Saber, destroy
the Holy Grail.
How could I possibly hope to know a man
from merely three commands alone?
I, I never even knew the hearts of those
who served me well,
and were closest to me.
Perhaps all this was a punishment meted out to a king
who cannot understand others.
That can't...
It can't be.
It's impossible!
Daddy?
Ilyasviel, what's wrong?
I had a really scary dream.
A dream where,
where I become a really big cup...
...and then I dreamed that these seven
gigantic lumps started to come into my body.
It felt like they were gonna tear me apart.
It's really scary,
but I can't run away.
And then I hear the
voice of Lord Justice.
After that, a big black hole opens up above my
head, and then the world burns.
Daddy looks at it all
and just begins to cry.
Mother, is Daddy okay?
Is he scared and alone?
Is he in trouble?
It's okay.
Daddy's doing the best he can for you.
He'll make certain that our prayers are realized
so you'll never have to be scared again, Ilyasviel.
That's right.
I know he will.
Daddy always works very hard.
He'll finish all of his important work,
and he'll come home as soon as he possibly can.
Hey, Sakura.
Come on.
Uncle?
I'm here to save you.
It's okay now.
Let's go.
It's Sakura!
Sakura, Sakura, Sakura!
Kariya.
Hi, Aoi.
Thank you, Uncle Kariya.
Thank you so much.
Daddy Kariya!
You're such a fool.
Never disobey Grandfather.
Where am I?
You're a difficult man to look after.
Digging you out from underneath all of this
rubble was quite a troublesome endeavor.
Gilgamesh, what happened?
Who can say?
That mud spit me out and here I am.
I imagine it to be an obvious message from heaven
that I should return to this age to rule the world.
Are you saying you have achieved incarnation?
Infuriatingly enough.
I can't believe we struggled over that ridiculous
thing as if it were actually a wish‐granter.
This ill‐conceived and disappointing play remained
a meaningless farce right to the very end.
But I was shot.
I don't get it.
I have no heartbeat.
Did you somehow heal me and
bring me back to life, Gilgamesh?
The fact is I really have no idea.
To my eyes, you still seem quite dead,
but the two of us were connected by our pact.
When I regained flesh within that mud,
perhaps you were trapped in some
sort of magical nonsense of your own.
Impossible, you're saying that thing granted me life?
All the other servants are gone,
so I suppose we must be the ones who have won the Grail.
Kirei, behold the result of our victory.
If it is true that the Grail
grants the victor's heartfelt wish,
what you see before you,
Kirei Kotomine, is your wish.
It is exactly what you most desired.
Hm?
This is it, what the hell does this make me?
What manner of dark evil?
What manner of cruelty?
This, this is my wish?
This horrible
destruction and tragedy?
This is the joy I sought?
Could something so twisted, so corrupt,
have truly sprung forth from the
seed of Father Risei Kotomine?
No way, it is impossible!
Did my father sire a soulless demon
more evil than the devil himself?
Are you satisfied now, Kirei?
No, no, not yet.
This isn't nearly enough.
Yes, it is true that my life of questions
has finally found its answer.
However, the problem solving
process itself was skipped over,
and the solution was just simply handed to me.
How is it that I'm supposed to
accept all this at face value?
The formula that yielded this strange,
unsettling answer should exist somewhere
as a greater, clearer principle
one can understand.
No, not should, it must.
I must question, I must search.
I must dedicate the remainder of my life
to fully understanding it.
You know, you never fail to bore me.
As you like, your questions
would slay the very gods.
I shall watch you seek out your answer.
Angra Mainyu.
I will reach it again, and next time,
I will see it to the end.
Its birth and the proof of its existence.
Kiritsugu Emiya.
I accept your challenge.
What's the matter, Kirei?
Nothing.
I remember the look on his face,
the tears in his eyes
over finding someone alive in the rubble.
A man filled with joy
from the bottom of his heart.
He looked so happy to me.
It was almost as though it had been him
who had been saved that day, and not me.
He's alive, he's alive!
He's alive!
And then, so fervently that even as I teetered
on the brink of death, I felt jealous of him.
He said, "Thank you,"
that he was glad he'd found someone,
that by saving even one person
he had saved himself.
And now for our next story,
the explosion that occurred...
I hope that Alexey made it back
to his home in England safely.
He called me this morning from Heathrow Airport.
That idiot forgot all about the time difference.
Oh, he called?
I didn't hear the phone ring,
but then, it's just like him to do that.
Hey, Grandpa and Grandma,
I have a favor to ask, if it's okay.
What is it, Waver, speak your mind.
Actually, I'm thinking of taking
some time off from school.
Of course I'll talk to Dad in Toronto about it first.
There's something that I wanna spend
my time on more than studies at school.
Oh?
My goodness.
But what brought all this on, dear?
Is it school, you aren't fed up with it, are you?
No, it's not that.
You see, so far I haven't really been
interested in anything besides studying.
I'm regretting that a little.
And so...
I'd like to do some traveling.
Oh my, did you hear that, Glen, my dear?
Waver just said something that sounded
exactly like something Alexey would say.
Anyway, there's a lot I'd have to do first,
and I'll need money to do it too.
For starters, I was thinking of finding a part‐time job.
And so, um,
to make a long story a lot shorter,
if you wouldn't mind too much,
could I possibly stay here until
I get everything worked out?
Of course you can, Waver, dear.
It will be so wonderful to have you
live here with us for a while longer.
We'll have to celebrate today.
Oh, look at this.
He was just a spirit, so I don't get how he
could've possibly left such a mess behind.
I really did want him to take me with him.
I guess it basically means that I'm just not there yet.
I'm not ready.
He never even got the chance to open this.
Too bad.
A limited edition with an original t‐shirt.
Does anyone even want stuff like this?
What an idiot.
I know that my redeemer lives,
and that in the end,
he will stand upon the earth.
And though, after my skin worms destroy this body,
yet in my flesh shall I see God.
I myself will see him
with mine own eyes.
I am not another.
How my heart yearns within me.
Amen.
Rin, it was an excellent debut for the
young new head of the Tohsaka family.
Your late father would've been
very pleased with you today.
Well done.
You haven't quite grown fully
accustomed to your crest yet I see.
Does it hurt?
It's nothing, I'm fine.
It seems that Tokiomi's
preparations for you were flawless.
I imagine that all the magic the
Tohsaka family has accumulated, Rin,
will pass to you without incident.
Well, why don't you go and fetch your mother now?
Yes, I'll do that.
Come on, Mother, let's say our last goodbye to Father.
Rin, is it someone's funeral today?
That's right, Mother, Father died.
Oh dear.
Then I should take out Tokiomi's black suit.
Oh, and Rin, help Sakura get changed, will you?
My, what should I do?
I have to get myself ready to go too.
Goodness, dear, your necktie isn't on straight.
You need to look good.
After all, you're the father of Sakura and Rin.
I have to go away,
I'll be leaving Japan again for a while.
Do you have any immediate concerns?
None at all, I don't need your help for anything.
We will next meet six months from now.
At that time, I will conduct the
second crest transplantation.
Take care that you are in peak
physical condition when I return.
I know, you don't need to tell me.
Rin, you are now the head of the
Tohsaka family both in name and reality,
and to commemorate this day,
I'd like to offer you a very special gift.
An Azoth dagger.
When my master acknowledged the results of
my training and declared it finally complete,
he presented this to me.
But given the circumstances,
I think you should have it.
This was my father's?
I'm here again.
Everyone...
Lance... Lancelot.
Because I could not stop
myself from loving Guinevere,
I was never able to forgive myself.
But, King Arthur,
you never once spoke of my many sins.
You never sought atonement from me.
You simply continued to stand
before us in your righteousness.
But deep in my heart
I desired judgment at your hands.
Had your anger judged me,
had your righteousness condemned me,
I might not have fallen onto the path of madness,
and my quest to atone and save my immortal soul.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I...
I am unworthy.
But this much I can say with certainty.
King Arthur.
One day, friend,
I will claim the Grail.
You were the greatest of all kings who ever lived.
All of those at the Round Table who served you...
It was not I.
Felt the same as I did.
I shouldn't have been king.
After that day,
I visited the Einzberns many times.
But as I had not returned with the Grail,
Jubstacheit never opened the forest's barrier for me.
And so, I never saw Ilya again.
However, I swore
that Ilyasviel would be the
final person I would ever lose.
My life was meant to be one solely of loss.
But everyone is still here,
just like when we met.
Once I was able, I adopted my son Shirou,
the little boy I saved that day.
Hey.
Hey, old man!
Hm?
If you're so tired you're gonna fall asleep, go to bed!
Huh?
Right, I'm fine.
When I was little,
I really wanted to be a hero.
What are you talking about?
You don't want to anymore?
Did you just give up?
Yeah, unfortunately.
Seems that wish has an expiration date.
When you grow up, it's hard to call yourself one.
I wish I'd realized that sooner.
I see, well, guess there's nothing you can do about it.
Yeah, right.
I guess not.
It really is a nice moon tonight.
Fine, since you can't do it,
I'm gonna be a hero for you.
Hm?
You're an adult now,
so you can't do it anymore, but I still can.
Just leave it to me.
I'll make it happen.
All right.
You do that.
I can rest easy now.
Tell me, Kerry, what do you wanna grow up to be?
Well...
what I wanna be
is a hero.