Irisviel.
Have I lost them?
If I can't see them anymore, then I'll sense them.
A chariot?
I have you now, Rider.
Hey, Rider, check it out!
Doesn't it seem like she's following us?
Well, well, if it isn't Saber herself.
This saves us having to search for her.
Hey, boy, tell me something.
Motorcycles don't usually travel that fast, do they?
A motorcycle, that thing?
No, no way, that's impossible!
Of course, with Saber's skill at riding,
we don't really know what it can do.
This will be fun!
Well, I will also have to do my part to
make this exchange with her interesting.
Huh... we're going down?
Change of plans.
I shall use an ordinary race
to settle things with the girl.
Yah!
Whoa!
I'm okay, but just try and be careful, okay?
Don't worry!
Nothing in heaven or on Earth can
stop me from being victorious!
Yah!
This is bad.
I'm reaching the machine's limits.
At this rate...
and I'm so close.
Invisible Air!
No way.
She's closing the gap!
She's gonna catch up to us!
Ha... a mechanical contraption like
that going so fast is splendid!
But this is a battle chariot we are riding.
It's a fair race, but it needn't be polite!
This is what you get if you want to chase Iskander!
Excellent!
You really are the proud King of Knights.
Truly the beautiful flower of the battlefield!
Do not underestimate me!
Rider!
Prepare yourself!
Irisviel isn't here?
Impossible.
That was definitely Rider.
So then where is she?
Did you really think you could
trick me by imitating a servant?
Rider's master lacks the intel‐gathering
skills to have found that place.
Tohsaka could not possibly have attacked in his state.
And so, by process of elimination,
only the Matous could have abducted Irisviel.
Answer me, where is Irisviel?
I don't know!
I don't know anything!
Then where is Kariya Matou?
Kariya?
I have no idea where that fool is!
I don't know... I really don't know anything!
He left this morning with some guy
who said he was the overseer from the church!
Did you see Overseer?
Hmm.
Kirei Kotomine.
I didn't expect the real Rider to suddenly appear there.
Truly a fortuitous development.
You seem to have been blessed by good luck.
It favors you on the battlefield, Kariya Matou.
Father, was this deception
really worth the use of two of my three command seals?
You don't need to worry about that, Kariya.
Now, hold out your hand.
As long as you work with me,
you may use your command seals
without the slightest hesitation.
Hmm, very impressive.
A transformation ability of all things.
His Noble Phantasm is far too good
for someone of the Berserker class.
There are lots of stories of
him succeeding
by disguising himself as another
knight in pursuit of some heroic deed.
Even with the command seals, this is the best result?
Your servant's obsessive fixation
on Saber is awe‐inspiring.
Enough, be gone Berserker!
This woman, is she really the vessel for the Holy Grail?
More accurately, her insides are.
Don't worry about a thing, Kariya.
As promised, I shall gladly give you the Holy Grail.
But before that, there is the other
promise you made to me, Father.
Oh, that...  everything is arranged.
At midnight tonight, go to the Fuyuki Church.
You will find Tokiomi Tohsaka there.
Don't forget, now, Kariya.
Tonight at midnight, your wish will be fulfilled.
Now then, I've sent Kariya away.
I don't know who you are,
but I suggest you show yourself now.
Ah, you sensed me.
You are indeed a veteran inquisitor.
So you're Zouken Matou.
That's correct.
Rider, are you sure?
We're really going to attack from right here?
From this range?
Straight ahead?
The sword of light we saw her use against Caster
has a delay before activation.
We'll strike then.
Why would you do something so crazy?
Precisely because it is, boy.
If she loses after all this,
her defeat will be bitterly devastating and complete.
She may even change her mind and
decide to be my vassal after all.
You wanna win her that badly.
Right now, on the battlefield,
she is like a star fallen down to Earth.
Only as a part of my glorious army will she
truly be able to shine in her full brilliance!
In all his campaigns, he was never
interested in his opponent's power or wealth.
Without destroying or degrading them,
he sought to rule their very souls,
thus was he the King of Conquerors.
Very well, Rider.
Win by whatever means you wish.
Boy, it seems you are finally beginning
to understand the meaning of conquest.
Glory lies beyond the horizon!
Let us go now!
Via Expugnatio
Wind!
Ex...
...calibur!
What is it you want, Zouken Matou?
Well, to tell you the truth,
I was quite interested to see what sort of clever
deception you would employ to destroy Kariya.
You would let the Matous's chance at victory slip away?
Actually, the sheer pleasure
of watching Kariya suffer...
is something I shall never tire of.
Victory for the Matous or a miserable end for him,
it's a difficult choice.
Hmm.
So, you enjoy watching your own
flesh and blood suffer like that.
Indeed.
I would've thought that you of all
people would understand that sentiment.
How so?
Well, you give off exactly the same scent as I do.
That of a hungry, wiggling little maggot
irresistibly attracted by the rotting meat of Kariya.
Oh, scary, scary!
You are truly a dog of the church.
I tease you at my own peril, eh?
I can assure you that we shall
see each other again, young one.
By the next time we meet,
see to it that you've allowed your true nature
to fully ripen, so that you and I
might fight on an equal footing.
Hmm.
Rider?
I'm sorry, boy.
I screwed up.
Rider, use Ionian Hetairoi!
The chariot is all I will use against Saber.
I understand, but still.
Wait, she left.
A motorcycle... hmm.
It's magnificent.
What the hell?
Those are your first words after she's defeated you?
By the way...
Huh?
...how are we supposed to get back to town?
Well, I suppose we'll have to walk.
I was afraid of that.
How many more days do I have?
How many more times can I fight?
But I can't die now.
Not yet.
Tokiomi Tohsaka!
So did you think you killed me, Tokiomi?
Well, you blew it.
Until I make you pay for that,
I'll keep coming back to...
Tohsaka!
What?
Kariya?
Aoi?
No, wait, it wasn't me!
He was...
Are you satisfied now, Kariya?
Now that Matous are sure to win the Holy Grail War?
But I... I didn't.
Why?
Ripping Sakura completely out of my life wasn't enough?
Of all the cruel things you could've done,
you had to kill him right in front of me?
Why?
But he... it was all his fault!
If it weren't for what he did,
no one would've ever had to suffer!
You, Aoi, or Sakura!
You could've had a happy life!
You shut your mouth!
What could you...
what could you possibly know about it?
You...
you've never...
You've never loved anyone in your entire life!
There was someone I loved.
She was warm and kind.
I wanted her to be happier than anyone else.
For her, I would lay down my life.
That's why I've endured this pain until now.
Endured, endured, endured, endured,
endured, endured, endured it all!
I can't let her deny everything I've been through.
A lie, a lie, a lie, I do have someone...
there is someone in this world that I love!
Who did I do this for?
Whose fault is it?
If I'm going to die, I may as well!
Hmm, it was trite and full of clichés,
but still, I have to say, not bad for your first script.
Well, Kirei?
What are your impressions?
It seems the taste of wine changes
far more than I ever expected.
Well, then I believe that you're finally beginning
to know what it means to expand your horizons.
If it will taste as wonderful as this has,
then I would dearly love
to sample it once again.