What of Rider's Noble Phantasm?
Equal to that of Gilgamesh's Gate of Babylon.
In other words,
too powerful to be given a rank.
Hmm.
It all ended exactly as we planned.
If we'd gone against Rider without
this new knowledge and unprepared,
we would not have been able to
defend ourselves against him.
This will begin the second stage.
We will use the information Assassin gathered for us
to have Archer defeat our enemies
and in the process,
discover the means to defeat Rider.
Yes.
Thank you for your fine work as a Master.
It is my belief that last night's attack
involved all of the existing Assassins.
Understood.
By the way, Maiya,
where are we with our new base of operations?
Tomorrow morning.
I will take Saber and madam there.
Good, thank you.
Of course, goodbye.
No sign of movement at the Tohsaka residence.
Since Assassin's attack on the very first day,
Tokiomi hasn't left the building.
An unsettling silence.
Matou Master appears undefended,
an easy target.
But...
Berserker's strange special ability
suggests that he should be left alive
to distract Archer and Tohsaka.
Lord El‐Melloi should have been
removed from battle already.
But Lancer still remains.
We must discover his new Master's identity
as soon as humanly possible.
Caster's location remains unknown.
But last night several children
vanished from this city again.
They continue their atrocities
with no apparent plan whatsoever.
Rider and his Master are constantly on the move.
Tracking him is difficult.
However large‐hearted he may seem,
he is a dangerous foe.
Furthermore, I'm quite concerned about
the Ionioin Hetairoi that Maiya reported.
But more importantly...
Is it safe to assume that Assassin
has been completely destroyed?
In that case, his Master...
If his plan was to work with Tohsaka,
using Assassin to spy on the others,
then he should have never been
able to leave Fuyuki Church.
But that isn't what happened.
His ambush at the Fuyuki Hyatt,
his attack in the Einzbern Forest,
both actions defy explanation.
Of course it all fits assuming he was after me.
But why, why pursue me?
Two days ago, he should have had no way of
knowing for certain that I am Saber's Master.
Kirei Kotomine, who are you?
You seem to be in rather fine sprits today, Archer.
I still see little value to this Grail.
But even if it is trash, that's fine.
It seems I found another form of pleasure.
Here in this world that you've constantly
mocked for being vile and full of imposters.
That remains unchanged.
However, I am now curious to see this
Holy Grail War through to its end.
I am fond of lives full of hubris.
Those who harbor grand ambitions
but are unequal to the task.
The mere sight of such people
gives me great enjoyment.
There are two kinds of arrogance,
one where you are unequal to the task
and one where your dreams are too big.
The former is just commonplace stupidity.
But the latter is a rare
species, difficult to find.
But they are identical in that
both kinds are fools, are they not?
Isn't the foolishness of the few a more precious
commodity than the wisdom of the masses?
There are those that are born human,
but harbor wishes that man was not meant for
and have renounced their humanity in its pursuit.
I simply never grow weary
of watching their grief and despair.
Kirei, what of you today?
For once, you seem almost strangely pleased.
I'm simply relieved.
I've finally been freed from a most unpleasant burden.
What becomes of the Command Seals once they disappear?
According to theory,
Command Seals ultimately return to the Grail.
And the Holy Grail repossesses the unused Command
Seals from any Master who has lost his Servant
and has withdrawn from the war.
Also, if for whatever reason a Servant loses its Master,
the Grail will give those
seals to a newly chosen Master,
assuming one can be found
before the war is over.
The Command Seals stay a part
of this world until their use.
At the end, any remaining seals are
given to the overseer for safe keeping.
So, depending on what happens now,
a new Master may yet appear and
enter the fight for the Grail.
Possibly.
But the Holy Grail does not deem many
on this Earth to be worthy of that role.
Thus, when a replacement Master is sought,
the Grail tends to select one of those
whom it had previously considered
and deemed suitable for participation.
What's the matter, continue with your talk.
Go on.
There is an unspoken reason that the Holy church
gives asylum and protection to those Masters
who have left the war.
In the event a place should open
among the remaining Masters,
there's a high probability that any unpaired
Masters will receive the Command Seals left behind.
This is why Grail War Masters try to kill
rather than injure or temporarily
incapacitate enemy Masters.
Well, then from that perspective,
is there not a good chance that the
Command Seals will be given to you again?
Impossible.
If as Tokiomi has always suggested,
the Holy Grail only chose me
as a support mage to the Tohsaka team.
I have fulfilled that duty and am finished.
Tokiomi already possesses a winning strategy for
dealing with the remaining Masters and their Servants.
There is simply nothing more for me to do.
If I may opine,
Tokiomi's hypotheses have been dubious from the start.
He has never struck me as a man truly fit to be
backed by the power and prestige of the Grail.
I must say, I am surprised that you have such
harsh words to offer regarding your own Master.
Kirei, you seem to be mistaken as to who
serves whom in my relationship with Tokiomi.
He is treated civilly as my vassal.
And he supplies me with mana as an offering.
I answered his summons precisely because
those were the terms of our pact.
I'm curious, what do you make of the Command Seals then?
I hate them, but if a vassal is
trying to become a better vassal,
I don't mind listening to a differing
opinion or two from time to time.
By the way, Kirei, you mentioned earlier that Assassin
had fulfilled all his missions before he was destroyed.
What of the matter we discussed?
You mean your interest in learning the
motives of each Master for desiring the Grail?
Yes, they completed that investigation.
I should have had an Assassin present
the report to you in person last night.
That would have saved me the trouble of having to...
No, this is better.
I'm not interested in what
that walking shade has to say.
Kirei, this report is meaningless to me
unless it comes directly from your lips.
Hmm.
How does it feel to drive a car, Saber?
Do you like it?
Yes, I think this is a splendid vehicle.
I can not help but wonder what would have
happened had these existed back in my time.
Irisviel, are you certain it is all
right with you that I drive this vehicle?
You seemed to thoroughly enjoy the act of
driving when we were out the other night.
No, this is fine.
If you're happy driving the
car then I'm happy, too.
I have to say, the skills of a
Servant are absolutely amazing.
This is your first time touching this machine,
yet you're driving it perfectly.
Oh, thank you, but I'm finding
the sensation somewhat odd.
It's like I'm employing skills I was taught a long
time ago that were buried deep within my memory.
Rather than understanding it intellectually,
my body instinctively knows what to do next.
Still, do you really think this is a wise idea?
The estate that is to be our new base of operations
lies precisely in the heart of the main battlefield.
Don't you worry about that.
Because secrecy is the hallmark of the Grail War,
the Tohsakas and Matous have openly
established fortifications in the city.
The Einzberns are unusual for building
that castle in such a distant location.
On the contrary, this new base that Kiritsugu
has secured might be more advantageous
than the castle we'd been using because
its location is unknown to the others.
It's another very unusual building.
From now on, this place will be your base of operations.
Ah, if you can take those for me, Saber.
Yes, of course I can, Irisviel.
Maiya, what does this key open?
It appears quite different from the others.
It's for the storehouse in the yard.
It's fairly old, but I've
confirmed that is is solidly built.
There was really no time for preparations,
so this may be somewhat lacking as a proper residence.
That's fine... for now so long as it keeps
us out of the rain, that's sufficient.
Now then, come on, Saber,
let's go and explore our new place.
Yes, let's.
I think this is like one of
this country's haunted houses.
I'm sure all the hallways have wooden
floors and the room's floors are woven grass
with nice partitions made of paper.
I told him once I wanted to see a Japanese mansion.
Maybe Kiritsugu remembered I said that.
Is our new base of operations not what you expected?
No, it's not that, I like it well enough,
but this isn't really an ideal base for a mage.
There are a few things that could be better.
The magical barriers are well laid
out, but for a workshop it's...
well, when it's this open to the outside,
the magic has lots of ways to leak out.
I would have preferred a more secure
room walled off with stone or clay.
Ah, this is ideal!
It's a bit small,
but I'm sure I can craft my spells in here
just as well as I did back at the castle.
Perfect.
Inscribing the magic circle here should
be good enough to make it my own.
All right then, let's get started, shall we?
There's a lot of work to do.
Will you help me, Saber?
We'll draw a magic circle right
there, six feet in diameter.
Right.
I'll need your help most once
we start to craft the mercury.
And don't worry,
I'll tell you exactly how to do it.
Will you do me a favor?
Could you bring in the ingredients
we left out in the trunk?
Irisviel, I must ask you something.
It seems all day today, you've acted as if
you've been carefully avoiding touching anything.
Have I been imagining this?
Driving the car, holding the keys.
Those matters by themselves would
not have caused me to worry,
but now it is beginning to appear as if you're
not even going to handle your own magic.
If you were not feeling well today,
it is important that you tell me about it.
It is my duty to ensure your
safety whenever it is necessary.
So I must know if anything is wrong.
You're absolutely right, I'm sorry.
I couldn't keep this hidden
for very long anyway.
Your hand?
Saber, I'm going to squeeze your hand as hard
as I can using all the strength I can, okay?
All right, go ahead.
Irisviel?
Are you sure you are not pretending.
I know it's weak, but this is all I can do right now.
Just touching your fingers is the most I can manage.
Grasping something or
picking it up is beyond me.
Dressing this morning was so difficult.
But, but what is the matter with you?
Have you been injured?
No, I'm just not feeling too well.
So I've disabled my sense of touch.
Just shutting down one of my senses
allows me to control my power quite a bit
and it means that I can continue
to do everything else I must.
Being able to do things like this
is the specialty of a homunculus.
But Irisviel, that simply can not be all there is to it.
What exactly is wrong with you?
Should you not go see a doctor?
What if it's serious?
Perhaps you may have forgotten, Saber,
but I am not in any way a normal human being.
If I happen to catch a cold,
I can't even go to the clinic like everyone else does.
I suppose you could say my condition stems
from an inherent flaw in my creation.
Don't worry about it.
Of course what this means is I'm going to
need for you to do a few things for me.
From now on, I'll need you to
drive the car like you did today.
And you'll have to help me set up
and perform my magical rituals.
I'm sorry, but I'll be depending on you,
my brave and gallant knight.
Yes, I'll help.
I apologize for prying into the
details of your private life.
Forgive me.
It's really okay.
Now, why don't we get started on
that circle before it gets too late.
If I rest in a magic circle that's
connected to local lay lines,
my condition will improve.
At least it should start to a little bit.
Understood.
Then I shall retrieve the materials right away.
With regards to Lancer's Master and Ryder's
Master, they appear to have no wish in particular
that they plan to ask for should
they happen to win the Holy Grail.
They simply seek victory as a
means to win glory as mages.
Now then, as for Caster's Master,
he seems to have no real
understanding as to what the Grail is.
He is only taking part in the Holy Grail War
as an extension of his interest in killing for fun.
Regarding Berserker's Master, he is immature and
seeks a measure of absolution above all else.
For a time, he had severed all
ties with the Matou family,
yet he is now demanding that the family set free
the younger Tohsaka daughter whom they adopted.
She is currently being groomed to be the
next head of the Matou family in his place.
He has been given the assignment of winning the Holy
Grail to secure his end of a bargain for her release.
In addition, he appears to have a
past relationship with Tohsaka's wife.
In a sense, it might be said that between
all of the five competing Masters,
he has the most unrefined and
banal motives of them all.
What is it?
Continue, Kirei.
It's Saber's Master.
Hmm.
He is merely a hired mercenary
retained by the Einzberns to achieve their
long‐held dream of attaining the Grail.
I was a fool to expect more from him, hmm.
What an utter disappointment.
It seems he turned out to be just another mongrel.
With dull and stupid reasons for
seeking out and stealing my treasure.
Exactly like all the rest of them.
You cause me to go to all that trouble
investigating and that is all you have to say?
Think of those whose effort has been wasted on you.
Wasted effort?
What wasted effort?
The work put in by you and Assassin
has paid off rather handsomely.
Are you mocking me, King of Heroes?
Is that it?
You don't understand.
That's to be expected.
You are an obtuse man who can
not even recognize his own joy.
Regardless of its self awareness of this fact,
a soul instinctively seeks out joy in its life.
This expression of the soul appears in
the form of interest or appreciation.
Thus, Kirei, having you tell me what you've seen and
heard was of great interest and importance to me.
And was very instructive, indeed.
What you spoke about at the greatest length
was what actually interested you the most.
For now, let us just set aside the man
you've deliberately avoided speaking about.
A conscious interest is no more than a simple obsession.
That being the case,
of the remaining four Masters in the war,
of which one did you
speak about most passionately?
Berserker's Master.
Kariya, was it?
Kirei, when you told me about him you
spoke of his motivations in great detail.
His circumstances are complicated.
Thus they required the most detailed
explanation out of all of them.
Hmm, you are wrong.
He was the only one you ordered Assassin to
investigate to a thorough enough degree such that
you can understand
those circumstances.
And this was due to your unconscious interest in him.
I accept that I made an error in judgment.
It's true that in the long term,
Kariya Matou poses no threat.
He was not worth the attention.
My overestimation of his abilities has invited
your unnecessary speculations about me.
Is that so?
Then imagine for me a scenario
in which chance and fortune
ensure that Berserker and his Master survive the
many battles and lasted until the end of the war.
Can you imagine what would happen then?
What do you think?
Listen, Kirei.
Is it not time that you finally understood
the actual question that I am asking you?
Tell me, Archer, what could possibly be the
point in imagining Kariya Matou's victory?
No point.
There is no point at all.
Come now, don't be so angry with me.
Think about it for a moment.
The fact that Kirei Kotomine never recognized
the futility in such a speculation.
Do you not agree there is a
clear, unshakable meaning here?
Explain for me, Archer.
It is like this.
If you had been given the same question
but regarding the other Masters,
you would have perceived that there is no point to
it and you would have rejected it as a waste of time.
However, that was not how it went with Kariya.
For him, you abandoned your usual sharp wits
and wasted your time in pointless thought.
You ignored the futility
and the waste of effort,
you found enjoyment in the exercise.
Celebrate, Kirei, you have finally
understood what pleasure is at long last.
Pleasure, are you talking about joy?
Indeed.
There is nothing in Kariya Matou's
fate that could bring a man any joy.
His tortured life is nothing but an
endless string of suffering and tragedy.
For him, a quick and unexpected
death would actually be a blessing.
Kirei, why must you define joy so narrowly?
Where is the paradox in finding suffering
and tragedy simply other forms of joy?
There is no one fixed type of joy.
You are confused because
you fail to understand that.
This is something that can not be allowed!
King of Heroes,
a sick and human monster such as yourself
may find joy in some small
amount of another's pain.
But that is the soul of a Godless sinner!
An evil that must be punished!
Thus, I have sworn to follow the
path of pure faith in my life.
And so you have defined joy itself as a sin.
It's astonishing to see how far you've twisted it.
You never cease to be a source of fascination.
Delightful.
This pain.
Aarrgh.
Ah, exactly as I expected.
I must admit that did not take very long at all.
Impossible.
This can't be, no Servant has
been freed from their pact.
Why has the Holy Grail chosen a new Master?
It appears that the Holy Grail
still expects much more from Kirei Kotomine in this war.
Kirei, you should go and heed the Grail's summons.
Without a doubt, you have some hidden
reason to seek this mystical wish granter.
I have a reason to seek the Grail?
If this wish granting device is truly omnipotent,
then it can give shape and substance to the wish
that lies within the darkest depths of your heart.
A wish of which even you remain unaware.
So you claim that since I do not know my desire,
I should use the wish granting device
as a means to learn what it is?
That can only happen
if I enter the war as an independent mage
and systematically crush six other wishes.
If I selfishly seek possession
of the Grail for my own desires,
that means that I will have ruthlessly
betrayed my own teacher and mentor.
Then you will need to have a strong
Servant on your side to fight for you.
If you would seek to do battle against me.
Of course before any of that,
you must steal a new Servant for yourself.
One already summoned and controlled
by one of the other Masters.
In that case...  no, I won't say it.
Everything from this point forward is up to you.
Do it all exactly as you desire.
That is the true meaning of pleasure.
Pleasure leads to the experience of joy.
And joy will lead you to happiness.
Your path is now clear, Kirei.
So clear there is no longer any need to hesitate.