Madam?
Huh?
Please hurry.
Madam?
Another intruder has just arrived.
They're waiting for us in the direction we're headed.
We'll run into them if we go this way.
Understood.
Let's circle around to the north side then.
Madam?
The one who is coming is...
Kirei Kotomine.
Maiya, the orders that were given to you by Kiritsugu
were to protect me from harm, right?
Yes.
‐But... ‐But what?
We mustn't let him get to Kiritsugu,
no matter what we have to do to stop him.
Isn't that what you're thinking?
Madam, how did you...
What a coincidence.
I was thinking the very same thing.
Maiya, Kirei Kotomine
represents the most dangerous threat
that Kiritsugu has ever had to face.
You and I are going to hold him off here.
Understood, Maiya?
I apologize.
But, please prepare yourself, madam.
I will.
Please don't worry about me.
Do whatever you think you have to do,
what you believe to be necessary to win,
and not what Kiritsugu ordered you to do.
Right.
What's funny?
Isn't the human heart a funny thing?
Hmm, you repeat an attack you
know to be absolutely futile.
Scalp!
He was somehow able to breach Volumen
Hydragyrum's autonomous defense?
He couldn't have.
His ineffective childish attack simply
rolled me into lowering my guard!
I shall take steps to provide for a much
swifter, more efficient defense from now on.
You're disgrace to mages everywhere,
you piece of lowborn trash!
For spilling my blood,
you will pay with your life.
He knows exactly how powerful this is now.
It's not going to work on him twice.
Next time, he'll channel all his mana into his defense.
Yes, that exactly what I need him to do.
Huh?
An illusion?
Maiya, no!
Madam, please don't.
Woman, this may come as a surprise to you,
but I haven't come here to this
place in order to defeat you.
I'm well aware of that, Kirei Kotomine.
I know what you desire, but I will not allow it.
You will never reach Kiritsugu Emiya tonight or ever!
We will stop you...
...right here.
Madam!
He's a skilled executioner!
An expert at hunting mages!
Regular magic won't be enough to stop him!
Kiritsugu taught me a lot more than how to drive a car!
He taught me to live and to survive!
Shape ist Leben!
Look out!
Not so fast!
Maiya!
Finish him!
It can't be.
Hm.
You bastard... ah!
I'm honestly stunned
that we've made so little progress with these things.
It's that grimoire, Lancer.
As long as he holds that Noble Phantasm,
our situation will not improve.
I see, so that's his secret.
Of course, if you plan to go over and knock the book
from that pale freak's hands, you've got a problem.
You'll need to get pass his big wall of monsters first.
Well, then, what say you to taking in
all‐or‐nothing gamble?
It feels a bit shameful, but there's no glory
in simply fighting these ugly things.
Very well, count me in, Saber.
I shall clear a path for you.
We will have but one chance at this.
Lancer, can you run on the wind?
I understand.
It's child's play.
How delightful!
Have you two said your prayers?
Tremble down to your soul!
Sink into despair!
Superior skill can only defeat so many before
being completely overwhelmed by sheer numbers.
It must be humiliating!
You will die!
Suffocated under a horde of monsters
that know nothing of honor or glory!
There can be no greater disgrace for a hero!
Oh, that beautiful face of yours.
Make it twist and contort in pain for me, Jeanne!
Strike Air!
Ah!
Prepare to die!
Strike him, Gae Dearg!
Ahh!
Damn you.
Damn you, damn you, damn you, damn you, damn you!
Damn you!
Did you like that?
Had Saber had the use of her left hand,
well, you would've experienced the same.
Prepare to die...
...monster.
Pathetic.
I didn't come here and join the Holy Grail War
only to fight in this ridiculous sort of battle!
Where is he?
Find him.
There you are...
...you skulking little rat.
Surely you don't expect the same trick to work
on me a second time, do you, lowborn scum?
The fact that you succeeded in landing a single
blow wasn't due to any great strategy of yours.
It was a fluke.
A stroke of luck, plain and simple.
Now I'm going to teach you the difference.
I shan't let you die easily.
I shall use healing magic to
regenerate your heart and lungs
while I rend every millimeter
of your lowborn flesh.
In excruciating pain and despair,
you will die as you suffer.
And while you die, you will curse them,
you will curse the cowardice of those who hired you.
You will curse the Einzbern for
making a mockery of the Grail War!
Insolent fool!
Fervor, mei sanguis!
Hm.
I knew you'd do that, scum.
Ah!
You struggle in vain!
Disgusting.
He is nothing but a sniveling coward!
Lancer.
Is something wrong?
It's my master.
He's in danger.
It seems, he left me here and
breached the castle himself.
I'm certain that the danger comes from my own master.
Lancer, hurry to his side.
Go to your master as aid.
King of Knights, you have my thanks.
Think nothing of it.
You and I have sworn to settle matters
in a manner befitting two knights.
Let us keep our pride intact.
That must mean that all went
according to Kiritsugu's plan.
Your origin is based on cutting and tying, kid.
To cut and tie.
The nuance is a little different
than destruction and regeneration.
If you cut a thread and then retie it,
it will always be thicker where you cut it.
Isn't that right?
In that sense,
it carries a connotation of irreversible change.
I've powdered some of your ribs,
and also put a very special part inside of here.
Your origin will materialize
in anything shot by these bullets.
It's especially powerful against mages.
If they attempt to use any magic against it,
your origin will interfere with and destroy their
magic circuits which will reconnect improperly.
The more powerful the mage, the more their
magic circuits will run haywire and short out.
Naturally, they will never be able to recover
either as a mage or human.
These will be your ace in the hole.
"Origin Rounds".
I've made 66 in total.
Don't waste them.
I'm sure you must know how easy it would
be for me to skewer you right now, correct?
Master of Saber.
So that's it, is it?
I shall not let you kill my master,
nor will I kill Saber's master.
Neither of us wish for our duel to be ended that way.
Never forget this.
The reason you survived our encounter
is the nobility demonstrated by the King of Knights.
Woman, I have one question.
It appears to me that the two
of you came here to challenge me
with the intention of
protecting Kiritsugu Emiya.
By whose order do you dare attack?
You do not possess Command Seals,
so you are not the Einzbern Master.
Most likely, you are a homunculus
charged with protecting the Grail vessel.
There's no way that someone like that
would ever be stupid enough to risk
going to the front lines of the battle.
So I ask again.
Tell me now.
Who ordered you to fight me?
Hm.
Master Kirei.
Caster, as well as Lancer and his master,
have left the forest.
Saber will arrive shortly.
My lord, it is dangerous here.
Hm.
Fascinating.
So it's red after all.
Impossible.
Could these women have challenged me of their
own accord without being ordered to do so?
No.
Kiritsugu Emiya is like me.
He is alone and empty inside,
understood by no one.
He must be.
Irisviel!
Can you hear me?
Saber.
Stay awake.
You must stay awake.
I'm going to call Kiritsugu.
Be strong until then.
Where is Kirei,
the enemy who was here just a minute ago?
He escaped.
Had I been only a second faster,
this would never have happened to you.
What happened to Maiya?
Her wounds are grave, but not life‐threatening.
I'm more concerned about you.
You've lost so much blood.
Huh?
Irisviel, how...
How can this be?
I want you to carry Avalon, Iri.
What?
But, this is a Noble Phantasm
that heals its bearer's wounds.
I think you should keep it.
No, Iri, unless its original owner,
Saber, is nearby to supply it with mana,
the scabbard won't function at all.
You will be the one who'll be
working with Saber from now on.
So you should have it.
Keep it within you as a conceptual weapon.
Additionally, tell no one of this,
not even Saber herself.
From the moment you touched me, I felt Avalon's power.
Thank you, Saber.
Kirei Kotomine.
That inquisitor is as dangerous
as I imagined he'd be.
No, even more so.
We were lucky today.
But there's no telling what will happen next time.
All I know for certain is that I can't
let him get to Kiritsugu no matter what.
But, I'm not the only one here who is protecting him.
Isn't that right, Maiya?
Next time, we'll win for sure.
We'll both protect Kiritsugu, okay?