[KAZUMA] If that doesn't
happen very soon.
Then Yato will die.
[DAIKOKU]
So Yato was right.
You did steal it.
[KAZUMA] Why is he even
using such a Regalia?
[YATO]
Sekki!
I will re-forge you!
[faucet squeaks]
[HIYORI]
It'll be okay, though...
Won't it?
[chime rings]
[HIYORI grunts]
[YATO moaning]
Ow.
Well, how 'bout
that? Hello, there!
[YATO yells]
[HIYORI shrieking]
[YATO yelling]
Wait! I'm not spying
on you, I swear!
[HIYORI shrieking]
[YATO groaning]
[YUKINE]
Seriously.
He's telling
the truth.
[HIYORI yelling]
[HIYORI] Now, would you like
to explain why you're here?
[YATO]
It's for work.
I was trying
to tell you.
[YUKINE] By the way,
what part of the job includes
graffiti-ing the girls'
bathroom?
[YATO groans]
You see,
young one.
I long for the worship of all
people, regardless of age.
[YATO] Thus, I must
be prepared
to enter even a high
school bathroom
if that's where
the request leads.
[HIYORI] I'm
not buying it!
What kind of client would ask
you to come here, you perv?--
[YATO] Allow me
to introduce...
[YATO] ...our client!
[door slams]
[MANABU whimpering]
I didn't mean to--
Don't hurt me!
[MANABU screaming]
[MANABU]
Sorry.
Very sorry.
But I'm not being dirty
or anything, though, honest.
I just had to get away
from those jerks.
[HIYORI gasps]
[MANABU]
It's true.
My name's Manabu Ogiwara.
I'm in Class 2-A.
[MANABU] There are these
guys in my class.
They mess with me whenever
we have a break.
So I hid.
I figured this was one place
they'd never find me.
I'm sorry!
It was a stupid plan!
[HIYORI]
I had no idea.
Now I'm sorry.
I should've let you
explain all this, first.
[YATO] Yeah,
I had a feeling
it was gonna be
something like this.
[YATO]
That's usually the case
when I get called
out to a school.
[HIYORI] You've seen this sort
of thing before?
[YATO] Bullying
is real common.
And I happen to be just
the type of guy
victims call when
they want some help.
[HIYORI]
I can see why.
They're desperate enough
to clutch at straws.
[YATO]
Or at gods.
[MANABU sniffling]
What did I ever do to them?
[YUKINE growls]
I hate this stupid
school so much.
I wish I could go anywhere else!
[YATO] You're
getting angry
because you can see
yourself in him.
[YUKINE grunts]
I get it,
really.
It's not fair.
But being pissed at him
won't help anything.
[YUKINE] Don't
give me that!
What the hell
do you know about me?
[HIYORI gasps]
[YUKINE] I'm nothing
like that whiny loser!
And I'm sick and tired
of tagging along
on these useless
jobs of yours!
[HIYORI]
Wait! Don't go!
[door slams]
[MANABU whimpers]
[YATO] Not exactly
a sweet-tempered kinda kid, huh?
[MANABU whimpering]
[YATO] You could
learn from him.
In your case, it might
actually be helpful
to let it all
out like that.
Huh?
Here. You can
use this.
[HIYORI gasps]
I-I don't.
Remember this.
If you decide
to fight.
[MANABU gasps]
[HIYORI] I can't believe
you gave him that!
I hope you have some
kind of plan in mind!
[YATO] Just adding some
fuel to the fire.
[YATO] I want Manabu to try
defending himself for once.
How he chooses
to do that is up to him.
I guess so,
but couldn't you and
Yukine handle it somehow?
By severing his ties
to the bullies, maybe?
[YATO moans]
What's
the matter?
[YATO chuckles]
You know...
...you did just
give me a beating.
I think I'll...
go lie down.
Was this
a bad idea?
Being here could
push Yukine too far.
Maybe to his
breaking point.
Huh?
Hold on a second!
What do you mean
"breaking point"?
[YUKINE] So he thinks
I'm like that other kid?
What a joke.
I'm not even alive.
As long as I've got this,
I can't go anywhere.
I'm stuck with the least
popular god ever!
This really sucks!
[footsteps tapping]
[door rolling]
[YUKINE] "Day Duty"
"The class field trip"
"This month's goals"
"Guidance counseling"
[YUKINE gasps]
[clothes rustling]
Everyone wears
the same thing.
Is this how I used to dress?
[YUKINE]
All rise.
Attention.
Bow.
Be seated.
[pen scratching]
I solved it!
[BOYS laughing]
[BOY A]
So what do we have next?
[BOY B]
Uh... Language Arts.
[YUKINE gasping]
[BOY A] Lemme see
your homework!
[BOY B] Man, do you
ever do yours?
[BOY C] My folks
are really pissing me off.
They seriously want
me to quit judo.
[BOY D] The big tournament's
coming up, though.
[YUKINE]
Oh, man.
So many kids,
and they're all my age.
[GIRL grunts]
[YUKINE gasps]
[GIRL A] I can't believe you
brought that with you again.
You know they're
gonna take it up.
[BOY E]
Don't be a narc.
[BOY F] That's it!
Get 'im good!
[buttons tapping]
[YUKINE]
Get him!
[BOTH]
Awesome!
[BOY F] When did you
level up, dude?
[BOY E laughing]
Sweet, huh?
I had my brother help me.
[BOY F]
Hey!
Can we all come
to your house today?
[BOY E]
Well... I dunno.
I'm busy.
[BOY F]
C'mon!
We're your friends!
[YUKINE]
Friends, huh?
That must be nice.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[YUKINE]
They're so lucky.
[MANABU whimpering]
[STUDENTS chattering]
[MANABU]
It's those jerks again.
[BOYS cackling]
[MANABU] Why do they
hate me so much?
[YUKINE]
Why am I so alone?
Why, dammit?
[PHANTOM] Let their
bodies hit the floor.
[MANABU gasps]
[PHANTOM] If you don't like
them you should kill them,
or else you could
just die instead.
[MANABU gasps]
[PHANTOM] Say goodbye
to the cruel, cruel world!
[PHANTOM cackling]
[mechanical clicks]
♪ [KOFUKU humming] What makes
a garden grow, grow, grow? ♪
[DAIKOKU grumbling]
Great. These are bruised, too.
I keep telling her to be
careful, but does she listen?
[knocking]
[DAIKOKU]
Hm?
Yeah?
[DAIKOKU sputters]
[DAIKOKU]
Bishamon?
I mean, Lady?
[KOFUKU humming]
Bisha!
[DAIKOKU sputtering]
[KOFUKU] Yay! Bisha's here!
[KOFUKU]
Bisha's here!
So, why
are you here?
And so heavily
armed, too?
[BISHAMON] Sorry,
I'm being rude.
[BISHAMON]
Kura.
Aki.
Kinu.
Tsugu.
Kazu.
[KURAHA]
I'm Kuraha.
[AKIHA]
My name's Akiha.
[KINUHA]
Hi, I'm Kinuha.
[TSUGUHA]
I'm Tsuguha.
[KAZUMA]
And I'm Kazuma.
[BISHAMON]
There you go.
You've met all my weapons.
[KAZUMA]
Good afternoon.
We've come today in hopes
of getting an augury.
We dealt with the Phantoms
that escaped the Vent,
but we'd like
to take precautions.
Will you help?
[marker squeaking]
[KOFUKU]
In this area here, and...
let me think.
[TSUGUHA]
I don't get it.
What're they doing?
What's an augury?
[KURAHA]
Oh, that's right.
I keep forgetting
you're still new here
so there are things
you don't know.
Every once in a while,
our lady comes here
to consult Lady Kofuku about
where more Vents will open.
[KOFUKU]
Eenie, meenie, miney, moe...
[KURAHA]
Vents almost always open
at locations she
divines like this.
[KINUHA] Of course,
one could always argue
that they open because
she points them out.
[AKIHA] Now, now,
that's not kind to say.
[KURAHA]
Vents are tricky.
They open when
you least expect 'em,
but doing this can help a bit.
It's not surefire, but it's the
best thing we've got right now.
[KAZUMA]
Another one?
There are a lot.
[KOFUKU giggling] Your
work's not over yet, Bisha.
It looks like you've still got
a lot of Phantom hunting to do!
[BISHAMON]
So it seems.
Lady Kofuku, I didn't realize
that you and Yato
were acquaintances.
Do you see him often?
[kettle clacks]
Once in a while, sure.
[cups clatter]
These Vents...
You wouldn't be opening them
intentionally, would you?
As a means of keeping me busy,
and thus away
from Yato, perhaps?
[KOFUKU giggling] Now you're
just being silly, Bisha!
No...
Despite what you might
think about my lady,
not even she would do that.
[BISHAMON] I assume you're
aware of my history with Yato.
[KOFUKU]
Yep!
[glasses clacking]
[KOFUKU] Of course, it's not
really any of my business.
Still, if something
were to happen to Yatty.
Well, then, there'd be a Storm.
[DAIKOKU sputtering]
[BISHAMON huffs]
I should be going.
[DAIKOKU] My Lady Kofuku!
[KOFUKU squealing] What?
[DAIKOKU] Threatening
the Bishamon like that!
And I thought I couldn't fall
for you any harder!
[KOFUKU]
That was fun.
I have a feeling the worst
of it's not over yet, though.
You think those two are going
to keep fighting, then?
[KOFUKU grunts]
That's not what I'm
worried about now.
Yatty was blighted, remember?
[KOFUKU]
I wonder how he's doing.
[phone ringing]
[HIYORI]
No answer.
He should still be at the school
[phone beeps]
[HIYORI]
It's strange, though.
I can't smell him.
I wonder what's going on.
He seemed really
worn down, too.
[door rolls]
Hello? Is there anybody in here?
[HIYORI]
A-ha! I found you!
[KAZUMA] If left untreated,
the pain will intensify.
The blight will spread
throughout the body.
[clothes rustling]
[YATO groaning]
[HIYORI]
Hello.
I know what
you're thinking!
[HIYORI] Don't get
any dirty ideas!
It was innocent.
I was just checking
something, that's all!
[YATO] You know
you're crazy, right?
So, Yukine still
hasn't shown back up?
To be near
me? No.
[YATO] He's at an age
that can be difficult
and dangerous for anyone.
And Yukine is stuck there.
Who knows what
he's up to?
A Storm's brewing.
[HIYORI gasps]
[YATO] So which tortured youth
does it belong to?
Manabu, I think.
[HASHIMOTO] I know,
right? It was my idea.
[HASHIMOTO chuckling]
That's awesome!
Did you see the look
on his face?
[YATO]
Or maybe not.
[STUDENTS murmuring]
[fence creaks]
[YATO groans]
[HASHIMOTO]
Later, man.
[phone beeps]
Oh, it is you.
I thought I got
a whiff of garbage.
[mechanical clicks]
What's your problem?
You got something to say to me?
[HASHIMOTO] Really, dude.
You're actin' kinda freaky.
[mechanical clicks]
[PHANTOM]
You should kill him.
[mechanical clicks]
[PHANTOM] Kill him now.
Kill him now.
[mechanical clicks]
[HASHIMOTO stuttering]
Come on.
We were havin' some fun, is all.
I mean, can't you take a joke?
Having some fun?
That was fun?
[mechanical clicks]
[HASHIMOTO grunts]
[HASHIMOTO whimpers]
[YATO]
Remember this.
If you decide
to fight.
[mechanical clicks]
[YATO AND MANABU] It's only fair
to arm your opponent, too.
[HASHIMOTO whimpering]
[HASHIMOTO] You're
messin' with me, right?
[PHANTOM]
Cut him now.
Cut him deep.
Cut him deep now,
and you'll be free for good.
[HASHIMOTO whimpering]
[PHANTOM]
Cross over the line, now
[MANABU]
Over the line.
[PHANTOM]
Cross over the line.
It'll feel so good.
Hurry.
Cross it.
Cross.
[HASHIMOTO whimpering]
[PHANTOM]
Cross it.
Cross.
[MANABU]
Cross it.
[PHANTOM]
Cross over the...
[MANABU]
The line.
[PHANTOM]
Cross over.
[MANABU] The line.
[PHANTOM A] Cross the line.
It will feel so good.
It will set you free
from them all!
[YATO] All it'll cost
is your humanity.
[MANABU gasps]
[PHANTOM grunts]
[blade shatters]
[HASHIMOTO whimpering]
[MANABU sighs]
[HIYORI]
Manabu!
Are you okay?
[YATO]
Wow.
That's some impressive
self-restraint.
I like to be prepared.
If things'd gone south, I had
purification water ready.
[MANABU]
I remembered what you said.
That's how I held back.
[MANABU] I couldn't use
that thing to hurt someone.
I really wouldn't belong
anywhere if I did that,
'cause I wouldn't
be human anymore.
It's up to me.
Whatever they do,
I have to stay strong.
You did
a good job.
[MANABU] Well, I guess they'll
go back to just ignoring me.
[YATO]
Man, I tell ya.
Kids these days.
They think life's a competition
to see who can make
the most friends.
Really, one is enough.
Find that one unique
person and you're all set.
[MANABU grunts]
[HIYORI] Do you think
he'll be all right?
I mean, can you
be sure those jerks
won't try to get back at
him for today?
[YATO] Didn't you see?
The other kid peed his pants.
He won't be telling anyone.
I hope things work out and
he finds a good friend,
like you said.
I think he's gonna find
what he needs soon;
which is something
I'd like to do.
[HIYORI]
Huh?
[YATO groans]
Find somebody
who's completely...
[YATO]
... unique.
[YUKINE sobbing]
Why.
Why?
Why is this all that I get?
[STUDENTS laughing]
[YUKINE]
Come back!
[bat clattering]
[YUKINE] Why are you
leaving me behind?
Can't you just take me with you?
Please!
[YATO]
So, then.
Figured it out at last.
You can't go back
over to that side.
This is your existence.
You'll never belong where
you used to anymore.
Why are you ignoring me?
Hey!
[YATO] Now you can finally see
what it is you really want,
but you also know that
it can never be yours again.
But don't do it, Yukine.
No matter how you feel.
[bat scuffs]
[YUKINE]
Damn it.
[YATO]
You can't, okay?
You can't cross that line!
[YUKINE]
Damn it.
[NORA]
Poor, lonely little boy.
[YUKINE grunts]
[YUKINE shrieks]
[glass shatters]
[YATO gasps]
[HIYORI]
A crash?
What was that?
[YATO thuds]
[HIYORI]
Yato!
[YUKINE yelling]
[glass shattering]
[STUDENTS shouting]
[MALE TEACHER]
Everyone! Get down!
Hurry!
[YUKINE panting]
[YUKINE yelling]
[glass shattering]
[YUKINE grunting]
[YUKINE panting]
[YUKINE grunts]
[glass shatters]
[HIYORI]
What's wrong with you?
[HIYORI gasping]
Oh no!
[YATO moaning]
The blight.
It's spreading everywhere!
[YATO moaning]
[HIYORI]
Yato!
Say something! Please!
What now?
What should I do?
[HIYORI gasps]
[YATO] If anything
happens to me...
I want you to go
straight to those two.
[HIYORI groans]
This is how
the blight feels?
And he's been enduring
it for all this time?
[glass shattering]
[YUKINE sobbing]
[YUKINE sniffling]
[HIYORI]
Feel better?
[YUKINE grunts]
[YUKINE] Hey what
happened to him?
You happened
to him, Yukine.
Huh?
Every time you do something
bad, you hurt him.
He suffers the
consequences for you.
[YUKINE gasps]
He's in so
much pain.
And has been,
but he's endured it.
No!
But I--
I should've
listened to him
and tried to get you
to stop acting out.
It's my fault.
I'm sorry.
[HIYORI grunts]
[HIYORI shouting]
What are you waiting for?
[pan sizzling]
Don't snack too much!
I'll have dinner
on the table soon enough.
'Kay!
[knocking]
Huh?
Hm?
[DAIKOKU] We sure
are popular today, huh?
[KOFUKU]
Huh?
[YUKINE panting]
[HIYORI]
Help us!
Please! Yato needs you!
Ya--
[DAIKOKU grunts]
Border!
[HIYORI shrieks]
A Borderline?
[HIYORI]
Take it down!
Please let us in!
Daikoku!
Kofuku!
Don't just stand there!
Can't you see?
[HIYROI]
Yato is going to die!
[TENJIN]
When the east wind blows--
[TSUYU] My lord,
perhaps you could recite
a new poem every now and then.
[TENJIN]
Oh, Tsuyu.
The young are so impulsive!
[TSUYU]
Next time, on Noragami: "Name."
Well, my lord? The poem?
[TENJIN] Yes, yes.
Just a moment.
You can't rush divine
inspiration.