[clock ticking]
[HIYORI]
Hey, Yukine?
You awake?
[clock ticking]
[HIYORI] I baked some
cookies for you.
I'll just leave them
by the door with some cocoa.
[plate clinks]
[footsteps scuffing]
[door clicks]
[YUKINE gasps]
[wood crashing]
[plates clattering]
[HIYORI gasps]
[YUKINE panting]
[HIYORI]
Hey, Yukine?
[SHOPPERS murmuring]
Dammit.
[PHANTOM grunts]
[YUKINE gasps]
Border!
[PHANTOM shrieking]
[YUKINE panting]
[YUKINE] Why am I
freaking out so much?
It's Yato's fault.
Forcing me to kill that girl.
[chime rings]
[YUKINE]
Stop!
[PHANTOM moaning]
[YATO]
Rend!
[YUKINE gasps]
What you're doing's no
different than stealing!
[YUKINE]
Damn!
They won't get
off of my ass!
Even Hiyori!
[EMPLOYEE]
What the hell?
Hm? Hmph.
[YUKINE sighs]
[YATO groaning]
Damn kid.
[BOYS murmuring]
[HIYORI]
Not in there, either.
Yukine's been so down
since that last encounter.
And Yato hasn't even
spoken to him.
I guess it's only natural
for him to feel this way
after what happened.
[AMI]
Oh, hey! Hiyori!
[HIYORI]
Hey!
Ami! Yama!
[YAMA] Don't you think that you
should be at home studying
instead of wandering around?
[HIYORI]
What about you?
We all have to take the exam.
[AMI] Yeah, but we don't sleep
through class all the time,
so we're pretty sure
we'll be moving on
to the next grade
with everybody else.
[YAMA giggles] But we're
starting to worry about you.
I'm doing plenty of studying,
thank you very much.
Oh, hey. Have either of you seen
a boy wearing a green
parka around anywhere?
He comes up to about here.
[BOTH]
A boy, huh?
[HIYORI]
Yeah!
He's kinda young.
[BOTH]
Hm.
Oh, hello, Mrs. Iki?
Your daughter is in
a torrid relationship!
[YAMA] And we're smack dab
in the middle of exam season!
Ahh! No, don't
listen to them, Mom!
It's not like that,
I promise you!
And you got a thing
for ugly guys!
I bet he's hideous!
Just look at your beloved
Tono after he lost!
Don't show me that!
I haven't gotten
to that fight yet!
[HIYORI moaning]
You better introduce
us to your boyfriend!
Here's hopin' he looks
like just like Tono!
[HIYORI] Seriously,
it's not like that!
[YAMA]
Oh, man!
I don't even know
if the gods can help her now.
[HIYORI] I actually would
like to introduce them
to Yato and Yukine sometime.
Of course,
there's not much point.
They'd probably forget they met
them as soon as it happened.
And then...
I can't really pretend
like I know Yato
all that well myself.
[HIYORI grunts]
[skateboard rattling]
Man, that was
too easy! Heh, hah!
[skateboard rattling]
Ha, ha! I can pretty much
do anything I want!
[foot thuds]
[YUKINE yells]
What the hell's
your problem?!
[YUKINE gasps]
[YUKINE]
Yato!
[YATO sighs]
[YATO] Wanna tell me
where you got this?
[YUKINE gasps]
Um, well, Hiyori
bought it for me.
[YATO sarcastically]
Uh-huh.
[HIYORI]
Yukine!
You've been
with Yato?
Oh, man,
that's a relief.
[YUKINE gasps]
[YATO] Hiyori, that was real
nice of you to buy this for him.
Huh?
[HIYORI grunts]
Uh. Oh, sure.
I'm nice like that.
[YUKINE gasps]
[YATO sighs]
Man, I really
can't stand kids.
That's one deep
crimson sky.
[YUKINE AND HIYORI gasp]
[YATO] Twilight serves as the
boundary between day and night.
The people of this world,
they fear the darkness,
and hide from it.
[BISHAMON] While the
inhabitants of the other world
blend into the darkness
and run wild.
[YATO]
With its reddish hue,
the setting sun blurs the
distinction between the worlds.
[BISHAMON] As the evening
shadows grow deeper
and harden into
pervasive darkness.
[YATO] This is the time when
those lost in the divide
can most easily
cross the boundary.
[BISHAMON] People once referred
to this as the time of day
when the monsters emerged
from their slumber.
[YUKINE gasping]
[YATO] Yukine, this time
is known as...
[BOTH]
The Fiendish Hour.
[YATO gasps]
[YUKINE grunting]
[metal clinking]
[YUKINE thudding]
[YATO grunting]
[YUKINE]
Oww.
[HIYORI gasping]
[YATO]
Shh.
The hell?
[YATO] Ya see what happens
when I explain things to you?
I'm blaming you for the trouble
that just landed on us.
[BISHAMON] I've found you
at last god of calamity.
Hi, Bishamon.
[YUKINE]
Bishamon?
[YATO]
That's right.
The strongest war god
that I wish I never met.
She's a god?
Well, aren't you
on the same side, then?
[YUKINE]
Why is she attacking us?
[YATO] We tangled once
a long time ago.
And she's been trying
to kill me ever since.
[BOTH]
Huh?
[BISHAMON exhales]
Then count me out
of this one!
You can fight her on your own.
[YATO]
I dunno.
I doubt she's gonna just
let you walk away.
[YUKINE gasps]
[YATO] This is a matter
of revenge for her.
She wants me and my Regalia.
Well thanks a lot!
[BISHAMON] My grudge may
drive me to slay you both.
But the punishment
of evil will make it just.
[YATO grunts]
Come, Sekki!
Huh?
Wait!
[YATO grunts]
[BISHAMON]
You won't escape me!
[lion roars]
[HIYORI shrieks]
[HIYORI sighs]
Wait. The Bishamon,
the god that punishes evildoers?
[HIYORI]
Revenge against Yato?
She even wants
to kill his Regalia?
[YATO] If anything
happens to me.
I want you to go
straight to those two.
Do you understand?
[HIYORI grunts]
[YATO panting]
Kazuma, I need
you to track him.
[KAZUMA]
Understood.
[KAZUMA] Target currently
moving north-northeast.
Distance:
2.1...
1.9...
The area is lightly crowded,
but I suggest restraint
in your attacks.
Only one Regalia,
abilities unknown.
Well, killing is the only
thing Yato's skilled at.
Kuraha, deploy your
pincer attack.
[KURAHA]
As you wish, milady.
[BISHAMON grunts]
[lion roars]
[BISHAMON] You will die
at my feet today.
[YATO panting]
[YUKINE] Why the hell
did you stop?
She's gonna catch us!
[YATO]
Get off my ass.
You're part of the reason
I'm so exhausted right now.
[YUKINE]
Huh?
[YATO]
Quit bein' such a pansy.
What? I am not a pansy.
[YATO]
I can feel it!
[YUKINE gasps]
[YATO] You've been stinging
me nonstop with your crap!
How many times I gotta tell you
that your volatile emotional
state affects me too!
Get it together!
But that woman.
She's a god just like you.
Are you seriously
gonna fight another god?
She's the one
attacking us, okay?
And you're... gonna use me?
[YATO]
Obviously!
It's your job to kill
what I want dead!
[YATO sighs]
[YATO] Everything Bishamon has
with her, all of her weapons,
even her clothes and that beast.
They're all Regalias.
[YUKINE] You're saying
that lion's a Regalia?
[YATO]
You got it.
On top of that,
she's got Kazuma,
who handles her navigation and
coordinates the other Regalias.
His all-seeing guidance
makes Bishamon the mightiest
war god of them all.
[YUKINE]
Hey!
Why aren't you hiding?
She'll see us!
[YATO] She'll find
us no matter what!
I'm making a stand right here.
While I've still
got some strength.
[YUKINE]
What?
But I don't wanna fight her!
[YATO gasps]
[YUKINE]
It's her!
[BISHAMON grunts]
[YATO grunts]
[YATO groaning]
So heavy!
A full hit will snap
the Sekki in two!
Catch him, Kinuha!
[whip whirling]
[YATO grunting]
It grabbed you!
It's a Regalia?
[YATO]
I told you that!
Now shut up and focus, Yukine!
[YATO grunts]
Gaiki!
[KAZUMA]
Locking on.
Targeting cervical vertebrae
and left humerus.
Zero point in:
2...
1...
Fire!
[YATO grunts]
[metal clinking]
[BISHAMON gasps]
[KAZUMA]
Impressive.
[KAZUMA stuttering]
Sorry.
[YATO grunts]
[KINUHA yells]
Kinuha!
[YUKINE gasps]
[YATO grunts]
[BISHAMON]
You evil scum!
How dare you!
[metal clanging]
[BOTH grunt]
I swear I'll never let
you kill another Regalia!
[YUKINE gasps]
Hold on.
You've killed a Regalia?
Didn't I tell you
to shut up, Yukine?
[YUKINE gasps]
Get over it!
You've been stalking
me for years now!
Haven't ya got anything
better to be doing?
Ya crazy
half-naked tramp!
Your existence is an
obscenity to nature!
I will
eradicate you!
Suki!
[YATO grunts]
[metal clangs]
[YATO yells]
[KAZUMA]
The blade's dulled!
[YATO grunting]
C'mon!
Pull yourself
together!
Damn!
[BISHAMON]
Tch.
Kofuku!
Oh, hey, Hiyori.
What's going on?
[KOFUKU]
Hi, Yori!
Talk about perfect timing!
Which kind of daifuku bun
do you like better?
We have the kind with--
[HIYORI panting]
It's Yato!
Bishamon's attacking
him and Yukine!
[DAIKOKU]
Bishamon, huh?
Oh, jeez.
I can't believe Bisha's still
trying to kill poor Yatty
after all this time.
[HIYORI gasps]
She called him...
What was it?
A "god of calamity" I think?
What does that mean?
[KOFUKU]
Just another way of saying
a god that causes disaster.
[HIYORI]
Huh?
Yatty's a scary war god.
You haven't already forgotten
I told you that have you?
[KOFUKU]
It was a long time ago,
but Yatty did kill
a Regalia once.
[HIYORI]
Wait a minute.
The Regalia Yato killed--
Does this mean that it was
Bishamon's Regalia?
[HIYORI grunts]
This is only between
Yato and Bishamon.
It's none of our business
and I'm stayin' out of it.
[HIYORI]
Uh.
But, Yato told me to
come to you for help.
You just have to help him!
Please! What will
he do without you?
You really are desperate
to help him, huh?
I know, you've got a thing
for Yatty, don't you?
Huh?!
No, I don't!
Honestly!
[DAIKOKU] So he's blackmailing
you then, isn't he?
Extortion?
That's just awful!
[HIYORI] There's not
a single person who trusts him.
[HIYORI sighing]
None of that.
I still need his help
with my body problem.
Don't you
worry, Yori!
I'm more than
happy to help you!
Wow! Thanks!
[KOFUKU] You can just pay
me your money offering later!
[HIYORI]
Huh?
Just remember
you asked for this,
and don't blame
me for the fallout.
So, where is Yato?
'm actually not sure.
Oh, wait!
Maybe I can find him!
[KOFUKU]
Whoa! She has a cord!
She's a half phantom?
[HIYORI] I've noticed
that all of the gods
have a pleasant smell to them.
But that smell is
slightly different
for each one of them.
[HIYORI sighs]
[HIYORI grunting]
[HIYORI gasps]
He's that way!
[BOTH grunt]
[YATO sighs]
[YUKINE]
Yato.
Huh?
That lady,
the one that's
chasing us.
Did you really
kill her Regalia?
Yeah.
Then it's only natural
she wants revenge on you.
[YUKINE]
Why'd you do it?
Because I wanted
to, alright?
Nothing more.
[twigs cracking]
[YUKINE] So it's that easy
for you then, huh?
Is what
that easy?
And me?
Are you gonna kill
me if I screw up?
Or if you just don't
need me anymore?
[YUKINE]
Not that I matter to him.
Even without me.
He's still got that
other Regalia, Nora.
[YATO groans]
You're stinging
me again, dammit.
Seriously.
Man up and get
your head straight!
What?
[YATO] Your fear
is killing me here!
It's put me
in a real slump!
Freakin' wimp!
Hey, you're just
as scared as I am!
[YATO]
What?!
Your hands are five times
sweatier than usual, Old Drippy!
Who the hell you
callin' old Drippy?
I'm talkin' to you,
aren't I, you moron!
Well it takes a moron
to recognize a moron!
You freakin'
moron!
[trees crashing]
[BOTH grunting]
[YUKINE yelling]
Se- Seki!
[twigs crunching]
[tree crashing]
You're like
a walking armory.
And c'mon.
Did you hav'ta take
out all those trees?
Did the forest kill one
of your Regalia's as well?
[BISHAMON] I can overlook some
immoral collateral damage
to purge evil.
[YATO] Well it's a
good thing you've got
the power of righteousness
on your side then.
Make you feel all warm
and fuzzy inside?
Those will be
your final words.
Whoa!
We can't fight that!
That monster will
tear me in half!
[YATO grunting]
[chains clanging]
[YATO grunts]
[KOFUKU]
Yatty!
Found you!
Kofuku?
Lady Kofuku?
Come to me, Kokki!
Now pay attention
to me, you two!
Is she?
Are you insane?
No more fighting!
[YATO yelling]
[YUKINE]
What's happening?
[YATO]
She blasted open a vent!
She can barely
control that thing!
She's always causing
Storms with her Kokki.
[KAZUMA] Phantoms are
pouring from the underworld!
Lady Bishamon!
We should retreat!
[BISHAMON growling]
Stay the course!
Kuraha!
[lion roaring]
[YATO yelling]
Yato!
[NORA]
Kuraha.
[KURAHA grunts]
[chimes ringing]
[NORA]
Restraint.
[KURAHA groaning]
[YATO grunting]
Kinki!
[BISHAMON] Kazuma!
[KURAHA groaning]
[BISHAMON]
Help Kuraha.
Bastard!
Lady Bishamon.
We need to
retreat for now.
He's right there!
Just forget
about the Vent!
I demand
justice!
Veena!
[BISHAMON gasps]
If you personally wish
to be eaten by Phantoms,
then go
right ahead.
But tell me.
Do you wish the same
for Kuraha and the others?
[BISHAMON scoffs]
Whoa, what in
the world is that?
[YATO] Dammit, Hiyori,
why'd you bring them here?
But wait, you told
me to go to them
if you were
ever in trouble!
Oh. But I didn't
mean this time!
I just never really expected
I'd run into Bishamon.
[KOFUKU shrieking]
Oh, no!
Well, regardless,
you should hide.
Huh?
And don't say
my name.
Bishamon can't find out you
have any connection to me.
Oh, right!
[YATO grunts]
Out of respect
for Lady Kofuku,
I'll let you live for today.
But I will kill you
the next time we meet
with my own hands.
So try not to get
any more blight.
[YATO grunts]
Let's go, Kazuma.
[HIYORI sighs]
[DAIKOKU]
Hiyori!
It's dangerous
here, we've gotta go!
[HIYORI]
Right!
[YATO] Nice work
back there, Kofuku.
[KOFUKU giggling]
Pretty impressive, huh?
[YATO]
I'm being sarcastic!
You screwed everything up!
[DAIKOKU]
You ingrate!
She saved your sorry ass
from death! [punch lands]
[YATO]
Ow, jeez!
That hurt, Daikoku!
[DAIKOKU]
It was supposed to!
[HIYORI'S MOM] There were
some really high-force winds
blowing through
the city at sundown.
I heard a whole
patch of trees
in the woods were knocked down.
How frightening.
[YATO moaning]
No good.
It just won't cleanse.
Yukine,
is this just not gonna work?
[water drips]
[NORA]
Yato.
Try not to look so down.
[chimes ringing]
Don't forget that you
can always use me.
[YATO]
Nora.
That's a deep crimson sky.
Hiyori.
The word crimson--
[HIYORI] "Crimson" originally
denoted the color of a dye
made from Kermes
vermilio, right?
[YATO]
Uh, yeah, sure.
[HIYORI] Next time on Noragami:
"Uncertainty and Destiny."
[YATO]
You sure do know a lot.
[HIYORI]
Well, this is exam season.