[GIRLS laughing, shouting]
[FANGIRL]
Here, Lord Yato!
Will you say it? Please?
Ha! It is done. May
our fates intertwine.
[GIRLS shouting]
[YATO gulping]
Woo! Man, nothin'
beats a cup of saké
after a long day of work!
All these people.
You have so many
worshippers, my lord!
[MAIDEN] The streets are
just filled with Yatoites!
Hm. About time.
I knew the world would catch
up with me eventually.
[YATO] Still, there
is a certain emptiness
to having your
ambition fulfilled.
The top is a lonely place to be.
Nobody understands!
How it chills my heart!
[ALL]
Oh, Lord Yato.
I am so very cold.
Won't someone come along to warm
this frozen heart of mine?
I will! Let me!
No! Me, Lord Yato!
[MAIDENS clamoring]
[YATO laughing]
[YATO]
Hey, take it easy, now.
There's plenty of Lord Yato
to go around, la--
[YUKINE]
Oh, just shut up!
[YATO grunting]
[YATO groaning]
[YATO]
Hooray!
This looks great, thanks!
Eat all you want.
But in exchange, I expect
you to stop dodging me
and finally listen
to my request!
This is my favorite! Score!
Are you even listening?
You aren't, are you?
[YUKINE yawning] I'm tired.
I barely got any rest,
thanks to mister
talks-in-his-sleep over here.
Is that a normal thing for you?
Ah. that dream was
something special!
Please! Like there'll
ever be "Yatoites."
Yeah, you'll never get any
followers dressing like that.
No one wants to worship a slob.
Especially girls. No girl
would ever think that's cool.
Excuse me?
I mean, I wouldn't even give
you so much as a handshake.
You know, right? His
hands are always sweaty.
It's really gross!
[YATO groaning]
[YATO] I think it's time
for me to show you
what a god is capable of.
[BOTH gasp]
It is fated to happen.
My dream will become real,
and do you know why?
[BOTH grunt]
'Cause I bought this baby!
[BOTH] What's some
old pot gonna do?
It's not just any pot!
I got it from a lady in town
who read my palm
and declared she would sell
it to me and no one else!
All I have to do is chant
"happy-happy, cool-cool,
happy-happy, cool-cool"
every day while I rub
it back and forth, see?
[BOTH]
And you believed her?
And this'll make me
rich if I place it
on a west-facing wall.
And this bracelet will help
me build the home of my dreams.
And this pyramid is guaranteed
to boost my test scores!
With all these charms,
wishes I didn't even
know I had will come true!
I'll be happy-happy, cool-.
[BOTH growling]
Heads up, Hiyori!
[YUKINE grunts]
[HIYORI grunts]
[HIYORI]
Jungle Tornado!
[YATO moaning]
Try doing some work instead!
It's not my fault
things have been slow.
I want to work, but I'm not
getting any job calls.
No calls, no work.
You know, I've been thinking
about what you said.
How gods and Regalias are
together in mind and body.
[HIYORI] You were lucky
to find such a great Regalia.
Don't you think it's time
to clean up your act a little?
Pull yourself together.
Yukine's counting on you now.
[YATO sighs]
[YATO] Get up, Hiyori.
Go get your body.
[HIYORI]
Huh?
There's somebody I want
to introduce you to.
[HIYORI]
Uh...
[birds chirping]
Why'd we come here?
[YATO]
Kofuku!
Anyone here? Hey!
[YATO] Huh?
[footsteps pattering]
[KOFUKU squealing]
[YATO grunts]
[KOFUKU]
Yatty!
[BOTH laughing]
[YATO]
Hey, long time no see, huh?
[YUKINE] So, who do you
think she is, anyway?
From the way they're greeting
each other, you'd think that...
No way. That'd be impossible.
Guys, this is Kofuku.
She's my girlfriend!
Nice, huh?
Yatty and I go way, way back.
Nice to meet you!
Girlfriend? No way!
But she's a hottie!
Anyway, I've got a favor
to ask you, my dear.
I'll do anything you
want. You know that.
Here's the deal.
I recently made this
kid into a Regalia.
[YATO]
Which is great,
but work's kinda scarce
lately, you know?
Breaks my heart.
I'd like to get him a hot
meal in this weather.
But how can I when I
haven't even been able
to provide shelter for him yet?
I think that's the saddest
story I've ever heard!
Don't worry! I'll help you out.
Let me see what I have here.
[KOFUKU]
There.
Do you think this
will be enough?
You're a life-saver!
A real sweetheart,
that's what you are, baby!
Aw, do you really mean it?
I love it when you
talk to me that way.
[YATO] All right! Time
to hit the pachinko parlor!
[KOFUKU]
I'll come with you!
What a grade-A scumbag.
[DAIKOKU]
You dirty bastard!
[YATO groaning]
[YATO grunts]
[DAIKOKU]
What have I told you, huh?
Keep your hands off
my lady or I will end you!
[BOTH]
Whoa! It's an affair?
You hear me, ya rotten,
stinkin', little punk?
[KOFUKU]
Now! You gentlemen
don't need to fight
over little ol' me!
I'm Kofuku Ebisu's Regalia.
In weapon form the name's Koku.
As a person, I'm Daikoku.
[DAIKOKU sputtering]
This is cool. Ebisu's
a pretty big name, right?
Yeah, one of the
Seven Gods of Fortune.
[HIYORI] Sure looks different
in person, doesn't she?
What are you talking
about over there?
[BOTH gasp]
[HIYORI]
Oh, nothing, really! Just about
how cute of a couple
you are. That's all!
[DAIKOKU]
Couple?
Well, yeah. I mean, the two
of you are married, aren't you?
'Course not.
[HIYORI]
Huh?
But what you called
Goddess Ebisu earlier...
We're casual here.
Kofuku's fine.
[HIYORI grunts]
It's just that before, you
called Kofuku your lady.
My lady, like a title.
As in, she's my goddess.
Aren't you?
[KOFUKU]
Mm-hmm!
[DAIKOKU] I wonder what
my tea leaves will say.
[KOFUKU] Reading tea leaves
is a bogus practice.
What are you staring at?
Was there something
you wanted to say to me?
No! No, there's nothing
at all we'd like to say, sir!
[YATO] Be careful. Don't
look that guy in the eyes.
[BOTH]
Huh?
Doing that can
be dangerous.
You might never get away.
Despite his tough exterior...
He has a thing
for kids like you!
[BOTH whimpering]
Don't say it like that!
You make me sound sick!
[YATO yelling]
[BOTH whimpering]
[KOFUKU giggling] Don't get
the wrong idea, okay?
My Daikoku loves kids!
That's all Yatty meant.
Daikoku cares about children.
He could do nothing but sit and
watch them play all day long!
You see what ya did there?
Now I'm starting
to sound creepy again.
[DAIKOKU]
Now. Let's talk, kid.
[BOTH gasping]
[DAIKOKU] Quit it.
Don't be ridiculous.
All right, boy.
You're a Regalia?
What's your name?
Y-Yukine.
[DAIKOKU]
Been a Regalia long?
No, sir. Not long at all.
I just started, actually.
Hm. I see.
Young for such a responsibility.
Do you think he's too young?
[KOFUKU] What about you?
[HIYORI] Uh, sorry?
[KOFUKU]
Do you have a name?
Yes, I'm Hiyori Iki.
Oh! I'll just call
you Yori, okay?
That's fine.
You seem like you're just
a regular human girl, Yori.
What's your
relationship to Yatty?
[HIYORI]
What? Relationship?
I don't even care
about the jerk.
[KOFUKU]
Come on, now!
Why do you look so upset, huh?
[KOFUKU] What's wrong?
Tell me, tell me!
[DAIKOKU] I'm very sorry.
My lady can be crazy sometimes.
[KOFUKU] You're a B-cup,
aren't you? I can tell.
She looks so happy
like that, doesn't she?
She just loves
meeting new people.
So anyway.
Life good with Yato?
[YUKINE grunting]
Sounds about right.
He's not much
of a people person, huh?
I really want to change jobs.
Well, do it, then.
Could I work here?
My lady doesn't need
anybody's help but mine.
[YUKINE]
Of course not!
[KOFUKU] Hey, would you
like some advice, Yuki?
[YUKINE]
"Yuki"?
[KOFUKU] You should
really be careful.
Yatty and I are close and all,
but I've heard some nasty
rumors about him before.
Rumors? Like what?
Trust me. Despite how he might
look, he's a scary god!
[DAIKOKU] Oh, stop that.
There's no need to frighten him.
[HIYORI gasps]
Time to go!
I got a call for some
work! Come on, Yukine!
We're busy men!
[HIYORI] Hey! Aren't
you going to wait for me?
Thanks for having us. Sorry!
[KOFUKU]
Aw!
Leaving already?
But you just got here!
[DAIKOKU]
Yato...
What were you up to,
bringing those two here?
[URASAWA]
Mom, I'm sorry.
I hope you'll
forgive me someday.
[YATO] Thanks for calling
the Delivery God!
Yato, at your service!
[URASAWA groaning]
You pushed him, Yato!
My bad!
[URASAWA]
Hey, I didn't jump...
I fell?
Incredible. Everything
goes wrong for me. Even this.
[YATO]
No need to despair!
Hello, sir.
Are you sick of the daily grind?
Depressed about your love life?
Hi there, ma'am!
Having trouble balancing your
career and your family?
What's that, kids? There
are some bullies in your class
that need to be taken
down a notch or two?
Well, good news! I can solve
any problem, big or small!
That's right, I'm fast
and affordable!
I am the Delivery God Yato.
Call anytime, ladies and gen--
[BOTH screaming]
[YATO]
What was that for?
[HIYORI] Skip the self-promotion
and save him already!
[YUKINE]
Hand-written, huh?
Oh, I'm sorry. I should
introduce myself, as well.
Here's my card. Or
what used to be my card.
Is everyone here crazy?
Ah. Let me see, here.
So it looks like you work
at an ad agency? Or did.
[URASAWA]
That's right.
However, the company
recently went bankrupt.
That's why I'm here now. I
didn't know what else to do.
[URASAWA]
I wanted to call my parents
to apologize for doing this.
but I guess I accidentally
dialed your number instead.
[YATO] That explains
the hang up, then.
I mean, anyway.
The hand of fate
is clear in this.
Start from the beginning.
How did this happen?
Maybe you should start
by saving him!
Well, I suppose it all
began last winter.
[HIYORI]
You're doing this now?
[URASAWA] I happened to come
across a young woman.
I couldn't take
my eyes off of her.
[HIYORI] Hey, why are we
using my face for this?
[URASAWA] You just popped
into my head. I guess because
you're right here. Sorry.
[YATO] Stripes, huh?
I wouldn't have guessed that.
[HIYORI] Don't look!
[YATO groaning]
[URASAWA] Thinking she
might be a runaway,
I offered to take her
to find some help.
[stomach growling]
You must be really
hungry, huh.
You want something to eat?
We can take care of that.
[GIRL] No, thanks. I'm
not allowed to go out to eat.
It's a strict rule. I'd
be scared to break it.
Although I do sometimes
sneak out into town anyway.
I can't help it.
[URASAWA]
The poor girl.
I could tell she was living
in a very controlling household.
She was barely even
allowed outside.
Like a lovely bird
trapped in a cage.
[GIRL gasps]
You could stand
a change of pace.
So where would you like to go?
[GIRL laughing]
[URASAWA] And that's it. That's
how we first started dating.
It was the happiest
time of my life.
[YATO]
I'm gonna vomit!
This guy takes advantage
of vulnerable young women.
Someone call the police!
It wasn't like that!
I cared deeply for her!
I never did anything indecent,
I swear on my life!
I don't believe
you, you perv.
[URASAWA] Anyway.
I came to enjoy spoiling her.
[GIRL giggling]
What do you think?
It looks fantastic on you!
[GIRL]
Promise?
You really don't mind
buying all this for me?
Well, everything looked
so good on you.
[URASAWA] Of course, I'm
broke until I get paid again,
but oh well.
[GIRL] Thank you
so much, Yusuke!
I love you!
Yep, gonna puke.
Stop picturing me. It's creepy!
How long have we
been falling now?
[URASAWA]
Wait. This is for me?
[GIRL]
Just a little present.
[URASAWA]
Oh, do you like Capypas?
They're my favorite! I've never
been to Capypa land, though.
It's called the
"Kingdom of Dreams and Hopes,"
so of course I'm
not allowed to go.
[URASAWA sobbing]
What a sad life!
I'll take you! We'll
see it together.
You mean it?
[URASAWA] It was around then
that things started to go wrong.
I don't know how
else to explain it.
[KIDS sobbing]
[MOTHER]
It's okay, boys.
[URASAWA]
Huh?
[MAN panting]
[YATO shouting]
What's with that place?
Middle-aged men walking around
wearing Capypa skins?
That's twisted and
jus-just plain wrong!
[URASAWA] They're
just suits, it's okay!
Here, you see,
there's a Capypa fairy
coming along to make
everything all better!
[HIYORI] Enough with
this stuff already!
[URASAWA] I don't
know what happened.
but we started to run into
all sorts of bad luck.
As things got worse, my job
performance steadily dropped.
I never got bonuses anymore,
and my meager savings dried up
almost before I knew it.
But I just couldn't imagine
not being with her anymore.
[URASAWA]
I was desperate.
[phone vibrating]
[REPO MAN]
I know you're in there!
[URASAWA] One thing led
to another and I went bankrupt.
I just wanted to be with her.
but with the hole
I had dug for myself,
I knew I would only
become a burden.
I wanted to spend our
lives together.
I had been planning
to propose to her.
Not now! I don't
deserve her anymore!
[YATO]
Hey, uh.
You got a pic of this girl
I could take a look at?
A picture?
There's something
familiar about this story.
[URASAWA]
Here she is.
[HIYORI]
That's Kofuku!
[URASAWA]
Huh? How do you know her name?
Shoulda guessed it sooner.
What? Why? How
could you possibly know?
Guess I didn't tell you
everything earlier.
Kofuku is the god of poverty.
[BOTH]
Huh?
The god of poverty?
Well, she doesn't go by
her title most of the time,
and I can't say that
I blame her, really.
It's not exactly the kind of
thing that makes you popular.
Take my advice on this one, man.
Forget about that girl.
Seriously. Ditch her.
Huh?
[YATO] The god of poverty
only brings disaster.
Spend time with her
and you're basically
asking to have your life ruined.
Oh, and there's one more thing.
She has a guy in her life
you don't want to cross.
[URASAWA sputtering]
And if it helps at all,
she's not nearly
as young as she looks.
We're talkin' way older
than your grandma.
Way older than your grandma's,
grandma's, grandma,
for that matter.
[URASAWA groans]
All right, then!
We'll sever your ties to her
and then you'll be good.
[URASAWA]
Huh?
Sever his ties to her?
But doesn't that mean.
He'll forget everything
having to do with Kofuku.
I don't want to forget her,
though! No, I refuse!
You can't make me agree
to this, can you?
I strongly recommend
you do this.
If you don't, you'll
die very soon.
Well, I'll die then!
You don't understand!
I love her with my whole heart!
How stupid are you?
[URASAWA grunting]
[YATO] Someone who would
end his own life like this
doesn't know a damn
thing about love!
[URASAWA gasps]
[HIYORI] Think we could
hurry this up, please?
It just keeps getting
more and more insane.
[YATO]
All right!
Yukine! You're up, kid.
Huh?
[YUKINE]
Wait! Hold on!
I've never severed
anyone's ties before.
It'll be fine, don't worry.
I know you can do it.
Have a little faith, okay?
[YATO]
Come, Sekki!
[YATO] Anything you want
me to tell Kofuku?
Just this, please.
"I wish you the best.
Have a happy life."
Very well. I've heard
your wish loud and clear.
Hear me.
I am the god Yato.
I hereby sever ties.
Sekki!
Sunder!
Uh-Huh?
[KOFUKU]
Oh, wow! Are you serious?
He was really going to do
that just because of me?
I mean, it's not like
I was trying to hurt him.
I wanted to have
a little fun, that's all!
[ALL]
A little fun?
[DAIKOKU sobbing]
I'm hurt, Kofuku!
I can't believe you would
do that behind my back!
It's your own fault, you know.
I was so sick of you always
telling me where I couldn't
go and what I couldn't do.
[DAIKOKU]
Well, somebody has to!
Or else you'll spread
disaster everywhere!
[DAIKOKU sighing]
I'm too old for this.
Well, anyway,
you got skills, kid.
Severing ties while
you're still a rookie!
Oh. I didn't realize
it was a big deal.
Well, it is.
Severing a bond
is much more difficult
than making one.
And a Regalia's abilities
play a big part
in how well it works, too.
[YUKINE gasps]
It was so easy. I'm really
surprised to hear that.
[DAIKOKU chuckling]
That's the right attitude!
Yato! Looks like you found
yourself a good Regalia.
Yeah, I know.
When I picked him,
I had a feeling he was more
than a pretty face.
Isn't that right, Yukine?
Get off 'a me! Stop, you freak!
[YATO] Aw, no need
to be bashful!
[YUKINE] Quit it!
Leave me alone, sweaty hands!
Sorry about all this.
Thanks a lot for cleaning
up Kofuku's mess.
It was my pleasure!
Later!
[KOFUKU muffled]
Bye for now!
I hope you come back
and visit, Yori!
Sure!
And, um, about what
you said earlier.
[KOFUKU]
Hmm?
When you said Yato
was a scary god.
That was all just a joke, right?
Oh, no. It's true.
[KOFUKU]
It was a long time ago,
but Yatty did kill
a Regalia once.
Before I met him, I'd
only ever heard rumors.
And they weren't exactly
very nice ones.
[KOFUKU] I mean, you gotta keep
in mind Yatty is a god of war.
He kills people, too, sometimes.
[HIYORI]
He kills... people?
[DAIKOKU]
Quit it.
That was a long time ago.
Things were different
then, you know?
It was basically
kill or be killed.
Sorry, I don't understand.
What are you talking about?
The way things work for a god.
People's wishes are what give
gods the ability to exist.
[DAIKOKU] Powerful gods enjoy
constant worship and wishes.
That isn't true for
the obscure gods, though.
They have a hard enough
time even being remembered.
So, what do you do to keep
from being forgotten?
You grant any wish
that comes your way.
No matter what it is.
No matter who it came from.
[HIYORI]
Whatever it is? Really?
[YATO]
You were there a long time.
What were you chatting about?
[HIYORI]
Yato.
Why did you bring
me to meet Kofuku?
I know you had a reason.
[YATO]
Listen.
If anything happens to me.
I want you to go
straight to those two.
Do you understand?
Yeah. Got it!
[HIYORI]
Oh, wow.
Why does he smell so nice?
[water drips]
[YATO]
When I picked him,
I had a feeling he was more
than a pretty face.
[YUKINE gasps]
[NORA]
Hi.
You know, you have
really pretty eyes.
[YATO]
That's enough, Nora.
What do you want?
[NORA] For starters, you
could call me by my name.
Please, Yato.
It isn't so much to ask,
is it? I love that name.
[HIYORI]
Wait, is this girl...
Is she a Regalia of yours, too?
[YUKINE gasps]
Remember, whenever you
need me, I'll be waiting.
[water drips]
[NORA] Just waiting for
you to call my name.
That's all you have to do.
[YATO] Say "Yato"
ten times, really fast.
[KOFUKU] Yato, Yato, Yato, Yato,
Yato, Yato, Yato, Yato, Yato!
[YATO] Now, who's
the coolest guy ever?
[KOFUKU]
Daikoku!
[YATO] Who's the best
god in the world?
[KOFUKU]
Kofuku!
[YATO]
Tch!
[KOFUKU] Next time on
Noragami: "Borderline."