See! Here we have
a little Phantom.
[PHANTOM squealing]
[BOTH gasp]
What are you
doing, Yato?
[YATO] Good! We want
that reaction.
Hate and fear will help
you draw a borderline.
[YUKINE]
And what's that?
[YATO] A borderline is what
serves as a Regalia's shield.
It's also his
only weapon.
Now, then.
You did some pretty nice
work the other day.
I think you're
ready for this.
Humph!
Flattery won't get
you anywhere.
[HIYORI giggles]
It's real simple.
Make your fingers
into a halberd.
Then use them to draw a line
like this between you and it.
[PHANTOM squealing]
Uh, okay.
[YUKINE]
Here goes!
[PHANTOM shrieking]
Amazing!
So that's what you
were talking about?
[YATO]
Yep. Useful stuff.
Phantoms can't cross it.
It acts as a boundary between
"self" and "other."
[HIYORI] Is it something
you can do, too?
Or-or even me?
No. You and I
can't do this.
Borderlines are
a Regalia power.
Any Regalia should
be able to make one.
But creating one that's this
strong without practice...
[YATO] I've never known
a Regalia who could do that.
It's a first.
[YUKINE gasps]
[HIYORI] Speaking of
the Regalias that he knows...
[water drips]
So, um.
That girl we ran into
down by the water. Nora?
She's a Regalia, too?
Oh, Nora, huh?
[YATO]
How to put it...
I guess you could call
her a friend with benefits.
Eh...
I've decided that I'm
going to look after Yukine.
[BOTH] Huh?
[YATO] You are?
That's crazy.
He can't stay with you.
It would never work.
[HIYORI] It makes
more sense
for him to stay with
me than with you.
You don't have
a place to live
or what even resembles
any sort of stable life.
It's all ex-girlfriends,
affairs,
and friends
with benefits.
You're depraved,
irresponsible,
and unfit to be
anyone's guardian!
[YATO groaning]
Yukine is obviously
better off in my care.
You'll just corrupt him!
[YUKINE gasps]
Get away
from her!
Stop that!
What are you doing
to the poor thing?
[YUKINE gasps]
[YATO]
Ahh! Come on!
I'm getting stung
like crazy here!
[HIYORI] Quit it! Can't you
see you're hurting him?
You're gonna pull his arm
out of the socket!
[YATO] You think he's
hurting, look at me!
I'm getting seriously stung!
[BOTH panting]
Jeez!
Are you crazy?
What's your problem?
I told you!
When he has naughty thoughts,
I'm the one who pays for it.
Every one of
'em stings me!
What do you mean
naughty thoughts?
Ugh, please!
You were just talking
about him living with you.
At his age, that's
basically guaranteeing
a whole crap ton
of dirty thoughts!
The answer is no!
He'll be staying
with me!
You know, I think
it's really someone else
who has his mind
in the gutter.
[HIYORI] Unlike you,
he's a good boy.
There's nothing to worry about.
Now, come with
me, Yukine.
No, Yukine!
Don't you dare!
[HIYORI humming]
[YATO sobbing]
[YUKINE] Your house
is freakin' huge!
You must be really rich
or something, huh?
[HIYORI] Don't be silly. I'm
just an ordinary teenager.
[YUKINE] Yeah, well,
this doesn't look
very ordinary to me.
Are your parents around
here somewhere?
[HIYORI giggling]
We got lucky.
[HIYORI] It looks like they're
actually out late tonight.
Huh?
You mean it's just you and me?
We have the whole place to our--
Oh, no! Sh!
[SASAKI] Ah, I thought
I heard you, Hiyori.
Yeah, it's me, Sasaki.
Nice evening, isn't it?
I have a bath drawn for you.
Feel free to hop in whenever
you're ready, dear!
[door creaking]
[BOTH giggling]
[YUKINE]
Whoa!
This is awesome!
[HIYORI] Go ahead
and make yourself at home
you can stay
in here.
Huh? Really?
Isn't this your
room, though?
No. It's my
big brother's.
Your brother?
[HIYORI] Yeah. He's
a lot older than me.
He doesn't live here anymore,
so the room's all yours.
Oh, okay.
It's great.
If you're sure.
I'm not far. My
room's next door.
Let me know if you
need anything.
[HIYORI]
Well, see you in a bit!
[door creaking]
[YUKINE sighs]
Looks like Hiyori's really
living a dream life, isn't she?
[HIYORI]
Everything went as planned.
We made a stealthy entrance,
unnoticed by our housekeeper
or my parents.
Oh! Hi, you guys!
Surprise!
We're early!
Lookie!
We brought home
a tasty snack!
Well. I think I'll
have a nightcap
if it's okay with you, dear.
Oh! You're absolutely
incorrigible!
[BOTH gulping]
[BOTH grunting]
This is the best
part of my day!
[HIYORI'S DAD]
And now for a little snack.
[HIYORI'S MOM]
Don't eat too much, now.
Have you washed
your hands, dear?
What are you doing?
[HIYORI'S MOM]
You know you're
supposed to be watching
your cholesterol!
[HIYORI'S DAD] But I
was just having a little.
[YATO muffled] Your mom sure
doesn't miss much, does she?
[HIYORI] What are you doing
here? This is my house!
[YATO] Jeez what's the big deal?
It's not like they're gonna
notice that I'm here.
[HIYORI]
The whole point
was to separate Yukine
from your bad influence!
[HIYORI sighs]
[YATO] Speaking of,
how's he taking it so far?
How do you think?
He's thrilled, of course!
Do you think he really
enjoys sleeping
in a different, random shrine
every night with you?
[YATO]
Unlike this house,
shrine grounds and buildings
are sacred territory.
Which means they keep
us safe from Phantom attacks.
[HIYORI]
Even so.
[YATO]
Haven't you ever heard
that things go bump
in the night?
That's the Phantoms'
favorite time.
Poor kid. I doubt
he'll be able to handle it.
Huh?
[YATO]
The thing about him...
You see,
Is he's afraid of the dark.
[water splashing]
Aw, man, I don't even
know how long it's been
since I've had a hot bath.
[YUKINE sighs]
What now?
I wonder what Yato'll do if
I decide not to go back to him.
Maybe he'll switch.
Start using that girl instead.
[YUKINE] But if he does,
what happens to me?
[YUKINE sniffing]
[YUKINE]
Huh?
Why do I feel like
I know that smell?
[YUKINE] Ah!
[water splashing]
[YUKINE] Hold on,
is it, is it because.
[YUKINE] D-d-d-d-d-d-d--
Did Hiyori just take
a bath in this water, too?
[door rolling]
[YUKINE gasping]
[HIYORI'S DAD]
Ah!
Here you are. I've
been looking for you.
Hey, Hiyori!
I found what I needed!
Don't worry about it!
[HIYORI groggy]
Gotta train harder.
Build stronger quads.
Gotta master the Jungle.
[knocking]
[door creaking]
[HIYORI] You need
something, Yukine?
I woke you up. I'm sorry.
[HIYORI]
It's okay. Is something wrong?
[YUKINE] Well, um.
It's going to sound stupid,
but your dad turned off
the lights in my room,
and I, well, y'know.
I don't like the dark much.
[HIYORI]
Oh...
I get it.
Well, want to sleep with me?
Huh?
It's okay, see? Come on in.
Oh no I can't really--
[HIYORI] Hurry up already,
it's getting cold.
[YUKINE]
B-b-b-b-but I!
[YUKINE shrieking]
[HIYORI giggling]
Yeah, it's been a while
since I slept with someone, too.
[HIYORI]
You don't smell like a boy.
You smell nice.
I like this.
Lying next to someone.
It's soothing.
[HIYORI] It's kinda nice not
to be alone at night, you know?
[clock ticking]
[heart beating]
[YUKINE panting]
[YATO] Young man, just what
do you think you're doing?
[YUKINE muffled grunting]
[door creaking]
[YUKINE]
You jerk!
What are you doing here?
[YATO] Don't give me that,
you little punk!
What were you about to do?
No, I--
Listen, Hiyori said
I could be there!
[YATO grunts] You're not ready
to have girls in your life yet.
So behave. For now,
I'm all you need.
[YUKINE] When you say stuff like
that, it makes me wanna puke.
[YATO sputters]
And anyway,
you've got a girl.
A Regalia like me,
but she's a chick.
[YUKINE] So what do you
even need me for?
[door creaks]
[YATO] Gonna be another
stormy night.
[PHANTOM groaning]
[twinkling]
[KAZUMA]
Closing in on downtown.
Location reached.
[lion roaring]
[KAZUMA]
Incoming: six o'clock!
[PHANTOM groaning]
[PHANTOM groans]
[twinkling]
We're done here.
[HIYORI] I'm glad
you came. This is fun.
[YUKINE grunts] Didn't have
anything else to do, so.
Those look nice.
You want a pair?
Uhh...
[HIYORI] It is getting
colder outside.
Let's see how much I have.
[YUKINE] No! It's okay. I don't
need anything, I promise.
[HIYORI] Oh, come on.
I want to get them for you.
But I'm fine, really!
I mean, it's not like anyone
can see me, right?
So, if I want something,
I can just borrow it.
[YUKINE laughing]
[HIYORI]
Hey!
You should know
better than that!
What you're doing's
no different than stealing!
What? I said I'm
just borrowing it.
I'll give it right back.
[HIYORI]
Well, it's still wrong.
Here, give it to me.
[HIYORI] The next time
you want something like this,
just tell me okay?
[HIYORI]
Where did he go?
[YATO]
Hey.
[HIYORI]
Yato? What are you doing here?
[YATO] Getting a little R and R.
I'm not feeling so good today.
[YATO] You are looking after
him like you said, aren't you?
'Cause it seems like he's
been gettin' in trouble.
[HIYORI] How could you
possibly know that?
[YATO]
Like I said before.
Master and Regalia
share mind and body.
I feel it when Yukine gives in
to the temptation
to behave badly.
[YATO] That's just how things
work for us.
We're closely connected.
[HIYORI] In that case,
is the opposite true?
Did Yukine get stung
when you swiped some of my
dad's drinks from the fridge?
[YATO]
No, it's not like that.
The pain only goes in one
direction, you see.
From Regalia to master, which
actually makes sense,
if you think about it.
[YATO] After all, Regalias
used to be people.
And people sin.
Some more than others.
[YUKINE gasps]
[kids murmuring]
[YATO] Resentment, fear, envy,
desperation, sadness, greed.
Those emotions tempt Regalias
to do what they
otherwise might not.
Acting on them brings pain.
We gods feel that pain,
and from it we learn something
of what it is to be human.
Listen, Hiyori.
I think there are some things
I ought to clear up for you.
People decide what's
right and wrong,
but those concepts
don't apply to gods.
To put it in simple terms,
Gods get to do
whatever they want.
Even if that includes hurting
someone, or taking a life.
[HIYORI gasps]
[YATO] Someday, Yukine
may need punishment.
Divine punishment.
Yato.
[KOFUKU] But Yatty
did kill a Regalia once.
He kills people, too, sometimes.
I-I have to go.
I need to find Yukine!
Again?
Of all the things
to leave behind.
[YUKINE]
I screwed up.
I wonder if she's
still mad at me.
[bells ringing]
Crap! It's that late?
[YUKINE panting]
[YUKINE]
Damn it!
Hurry!
[YUKINE panting]
Faster!
I hate the dark!
[GIRL]
I'm scared.
[YUKINE gasps]
[GIRL]
It's dark.
I don't like the dark.
Mommy.
Please come and get me!
You stopped walking.
You can see me?
[YUKINE gasps]
Oh no.
You can see me!
[GIRL sobbing] Everybody else
out here just ignores me!
Well, these eyeball
things try to talk to me,
but they're weird and scary.
[YUKINE]
This girl...
[GIRL] I'm waiting for my mommy,
just like I'm supposed to.
She comes to pick me up after
my tutoring session is over.
[YUKINE]
Oh, she does, huh?
She shouldn't be much longer.
Will you please
wait here with me?
[GIRL]
Just 'til six o'clock.
[YUKINE]
Sure.
[HIYORI grunts]
[HIYORI]
Where is he?
[GIRL]
I'm really sorry.
I guess my mommy's running late.
Your family's probably worried
about you, too, huh?
[YUKINE]
Family?
I don't really
have one of those.
[BOTH gasp]
Hey, I know!
When my mommy gets here, you can
come home with us too, okay?
Don't worry.
[GIRL] I'm sure
she'll get here soon.
Really.
[YUKINE]
No, she won't.
[YUKINE] Hey! Come back here!
[GIRL sobbing]
[HIYORI]
There you are!
I've been looking
everywhere for you!
Wait, don't go that way!
Huh?
[PHANTOMS]
You must be so scared.
[YUKINE gasps]
[PHANTOMS]
Poor little girl...
All lost and alone...
[PHANTOMS]...in the dark.
[GIRL sobbing]
[PHANTOMS] But don't worry.
[PHANTOMS]
It'll be okay.
Your mommy is over here.
My mommy?
[PHANTOMS]
Come this way.
Come to us.
Yukine!
[HIYORI]
Use that thing Yato taught you!
First I have to make
my hand into a halberd.
[YUKINE]
Damn!
Border!
[PHANTOMS shrieking]
[YUKINE panting]
[YUKINE]
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have said
your mom's not coming.
[GIRL whimpers]
[YUKINE]
It's okay now.
They'll stay back.
They can't cross that line.
[PHANTOMS chanting]
Smells nice.
[GIRL] Smells nice.
[YUKINE gasps]
[GIRL]
I just noticed.
You actually smell really nice.
[YUKINE yells]
[PHANTOMS] Smells nice.
[PHANTOMS]
Come here.
[GIRL]
You smell really nice.
Want to smell more.
Yukine!
[HIYORI shrieks]
[PHANTOM growling]
More smell, please. More.
Can I have?
[YUKINE whimpering]
[PHANTOMS shrieking]
More smell, please--
[YUKINE whimpering]
[YUKINE screaming]
[PHANTOM moaning]
[PHANTOM grunting]
[PHANTOMS]
Boy smells nice.
Mommy? Where?
[HIYORI grunts]
Yato!
[YATO]
Yukine, you all right?
[YUKINE softly]
That big Phantom...
A girl, went into it.
[YUKINE] Help Her!
[PHANTOMS] Boy smells nice!
[YUKINE] You have
to help her, Yato!
Please help her!
[YATO]
Very well.
Come Sekki!
This is the land
of the rising sun.
Your desecrations
shall not be allowed.
Hear me.
I am the god Yato.
I now lay thee
waste with the Sekki
and expel thy vast defilement.
I cleanse thee.
[PHANTOM grunts]
No!
Yato!
[YUKINE gasps]
[YUKINE]
Stop!
[YATO]
Rend!
[PHANTOM groaning]
[YUKINE] What the hell
are you doing?
You were supposed to save her!
[YATO groaning]
[YATO]
It's too late for that.
Can't you see? She's
been completely possessed!
[YUKINE]
What are you saying?
Killing her is the only
choice we have now.
[YATO grunting]
[YATO]
Yukine.
[YUKINE gasps]
[YATO]
Once it has been corrupted
and consumed by a Phantom,
a soul is utterly lost.
Its existence can be nothing
but a living hell!
[YUKINE whimpers]
[YATO]
You must do this.
Show her mercy and free her!
[YUKINE whimpering]
Yukine!
[sword rattling]
Rend!
[YUKINE whimpering]
[YUKINE gasps]
[twinkling]
[YATO panting]
[YATO groaning]
[HIYORI gasps]
[KAZUMA] We've received
word from Kuraha,
who's patrolling the city.
[water rushing]
[KAZUMA] It seems that he saw
Yato, slaying a Phantom.
He appears to have
obtained a new Regalia.
[BISHAMON]
I see.
[water splashing]
[HIYORI] How was
your bath, Yukine?
Nice and relaxing?
[YUKINE]
Yeah.
Oh, and I used some shampoo.
I think it was rose-scented
or something.
I'm guessing it
was yours, right?
[HIYORI] Actually, it's my
dad's hair-growth cream.
[YUKINE]
Your dad's?
[HIYORI] Next time on
Noragami: "Scary Person."