[HIYORI thinking]
Things have changed.
I'm not the same
as I used to be.
I'm a different girl, and
I have been ever since the day
I met that guy
who insists he's a god.
Ugh.
[HIYORI sighs]
I can still touch things
even without my body.
That's cool.
[HIYORI gasps]
[HIYORI giggles]
[FEMALE TEACHER]
Hiyori.
Hiyori!
Are you with us, Hiyori?
Yes?
Whoops.
Was I asleep again?
Yes, you were.
If you're not feeling well,
you should go to
the nurse's office.
I'll be fine, I swear.
I'm really sorry.
[STUDENTS chuckle]
[bell chiming]
[HIYORI yawns]
[HIYORI thinking]
I'm so sleepy all the time.
I hate it.
I've been feeling like this
ever since the
incident with the bus.
And it's more than
just drowsy spells.
[FEMALE STUDENT A] The forecast
says it's gonna snow today.
[PHANTOM]
Cold snow.
[FEMALE STUDENT B]
Aw, man.
That's no fun.
Snow. Cold snow.
[YAMA] Well,
come on. Let's go!
[AMI] You're
gonna be late.
Oh right!
[HIYORI thinking]
Nobody else can see what I see.
It's a being that dwells
beyond normal people's sight.
A Phantom.
[PHANTOM]
White snow.
What's so special about me
that I can see them now?
[YAMA]
Hello!
Wake up, Sleeping Beauty!
[HIYORI yells]
[AMI] Wow, again?
This is crazy!
[YAMA]
Totally.
I bet this Insta-Snooze
trick of hers
comes in handy
sometimes, though.
[AMI] So she's a closet
martial arts nerd
and a narcoleptic.
That's a combination
you don't see every day, huh?
No kidding.
We should warn her her
panties show when this happens.
Yeah, that way she can wear
something appropriate.
Something non-descript
would work best.
Nah, something
that's super cute.
This is all so strange.
Even so...
[HIYORI laughing]
It does have its moments!
Whee!
♪ I'm a bird! I'm a bird! ♪
♪ I'm a pretty, flying bird! ♪
♪ Look at me! ♪
♪ I'm a bird! ♪
[YATO] Phantoms can
be found everywhere.
Lurking in
the shadows of an alley.
Soaring through the sky.
Sitting on people's shoulders.
[HIYORI yelps]
[YATO]
They're not the same.
They come in
different shapes and sizes.
But they are all denizens
of the Far Shore.
Devoid of life.
[BABY crying]
[YATO]
They're mostly invisible.
The only ones who can see them
are young children, animals.
And, of course,
those of us who roam
the divide between
the Near and Far Shores.
[BABY laughing]
[HIYORI]
A black haze in the distance.
So that's a "Storm."
An area thick with despair
that attracts all
kinds of Phantoms.
It gives me the creeps.
Yato told me
a little about Phantoms.
They possess people
and then those people
lose all hope and
spiral out of control.
That's what I'm dealing with,
and Yato still
hasn't contacted me?
[YATO]
Ah, hello, there.
Nice to talk to you again.
What can I do for ya?
[HIYORI]
Don't give me that!
You said you'd help
with the Phantoms
and the tail
and everything.
Yeah, yeah.
I know, I know.
I'll get to it eventually.
Could you be
more specific?
Exactly how long
is "eventually"?
It's been two weeks!
Look, some unexpected
stuff came up recently.
Stuff I have to deal with
before I can even think
about doing anything else.
So I can't get
to you quite yet.
[HIYORI]
Be straight with me.
Are you really
a god or not?
You doubt me?
Don't.
I'm the real deal.
Do you know any humans
who can do that trick?
You should be in awe
of my magnificence!
You're wearing
a tracksuit
and a weird bib
around your neck.
That isn't really
an awe-inspiring outfit.
You shouldn't judge people
by the clothing they wear.
Didn't your parents
ever teach you that lesson?
And it's not a bib,
it's a fluffy-fluff scarf.
Fluffy fluff scarf?
[WOMAN whispers] Did you
see that girl over there?
She's talking to herself.
[MAN whispers]
Don't stare.
She probably isn't
right in the head.
Explain something to me.
What's the difference
between you and Phantoms?
Huh?
I mean, you have
things in common.
You're invisible
to most people,
and the same thing goes
for Phantoms, doesn't it?
Unlike them, I'm actually
from the Far Shore.
I wasn't born
from a human being.
I'm a god of war,
born from a wish.
Yeah?
Yeah, between
the two of us,
I'd say you're
more like a Phantom.
Huh?
Not again!
I didn't even
notice it happening!
Hey! You're a ghost!
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
This isn't
a joke, you jerk!
In all seriousness.
This bare form of yours
isn't safe at all.
You should be careful.
A living Phantom makes
a very tempting target.
They will come for you.
They'll come, eager to corrupt
your soul and consume it,
and once you're possessed by
a Phantom you lose who you are.
You'll cross lines
that shouldn't be crossed,
and you won't even hesitate.
Because what you'll find
beyond may be a living hell,
but it's a pleasurable one.
Well, when you
put it that way,
would you fix me already?
I remember our contract,
don't worry.
You paid your 5 yen piece.
And it's non-refundable!
Yeah it's my money now.
I'm saving up for a shrine
that's nice and big!
By the station with a wife
and a separate bathroom.
Yes, a shrine just for me!
How is this, Lord Yato?
[FEMALE A] Am I massaging
your right leg to your liking?
[FEMALE B] What about
your left leg, Lord Yato?
[YATO sighs]
Ah most agreeable.
I am Yato!
An almighty god of war!
Now, then go forth
and pick out the peanuts
from a bag of
mixed nuts for me!
[ALL FEMALES]
Yes!
As you wish, sir!
[YATO giggles]
Oh, yeah, I like that!
So, anyway, when
will you get to my job?
Huh?
Soon enough.
I told you to
sit tight, didn't I?
You've been telling me
that since last week.
I'm sick of waiting!
Oh, last week, huh?
Well here's
a proposition, then.
Call me "Lord Yato."
It'll show some respect.
Do that for
an entire week
and I'll consider
starting your job.
I mean, seriously,
who calls a god
by his first
name, anyway?
I could call you
something else.
Fine the truth is I'm
not at 100 % right now.
I can't take on a big job.
Not until I find a Regalia.
[HIYORI] Okay, and what
exactly is a Regalia?
[YATO]
Regalias are tools.
They serve as
weapons for gods.
When I have a Regalia
I can cut down anything.
[YATO gasps]
Did you lose it?
Lose a Regalia?
No, she qui--
I fired her.
Regalias are people?
Well, they're spirits.
Oh.
Really?
Hello!
Thank you for calling
Delivery God Yato.
I'm fast and affordable!
Need help, you say?
I'll be right there!
Wait!
I do not like that guy.
I got everything I need.
Why should I bother
getting some dumb job?
I don't need work.
My parents support me.
[HIYORI'S MOM]
Do you see them, Hiyori?
Those are "lazy bums".
Scary, aren't they?
Working is for losers
who don't have
anything better to do.
I mean, it's not
like I can't get a job,
it's just that I don't want to.
Besides, by not working,
I'm leaving a job free
for somebody else out there
who needs it more.
That's it!
He's one of those lazy bums
Mother was always
warning me about.
But what now?
It's not like I have
anybody else to turn to.
[TONO]
Your fists will guide you!
Pave your own way!
That's it!
I'll listen to the great Tono!
He's right!
I can't rely on others
for everything!
I gotta take matters
into my own hands!
I've got it!
If he needs a Regalia,
I'll find him one!
Excuse me!
What would you think
about being a Regalia
for a guy named Yato?
Excuse me! Hello there!
A Storm.
There are a ton
of spirits in there.
I bet at least one
will hear me out!
[OFFICE DRONE]
Wow.
Never seen
that trick before.
You using toilet paper?
Yep.
If you stick it on
the wall like this,
you can get all the mold off
without having
it drip everywhere.
To be really thorough,
I'd leave it for half
a day before rinsing it off.
[OFFICE DRONE] Man, you
really are a pro, aren't ya?
A pro?
I appreciate ya comin'
over so quickly, too.
Maybe I'll become
a repeat customer.
Please!
That would be great!
Well, I'll leave ya to it.
Oh, by the way.
Do you have an old
toothbrush I could use?
Say what?
It's what you need for mold
that's particularly thick,
like it is here.
You did a great job, kid!
I just called you
in for a leaky faucet.
But, this place
has never been cleaner!
Thanks.
I feel bad payin' just 5 yen.
I know!
Here's a tip.
Ah, man, some god of war I am.
How pathetic.
I spent my day
repairing a leaky pipe
and cleaning up mold
for chump change.
Now that's tasty!
At least I got
a drink out of it, huh?
Well, I'm already here.
I might as well crash
at ol' Tenjin's place.
Looks like business
is boomin' for him!
How's it go again?
"You can check out
any time you want,
but you can never leave."
Or something.
Looks like it's especially
stormy out tonight, huh?
So that Hiyori
girl's job request.
What am I gonna do abou--.
Who's calling now?
Oh, great.
Her again.
This is really getting old.
Yeah, hello.
What can I do for ya, Hiyori?
Hey!
Sorry to bother you
this late, but, uh...
I've got something.
I-I think I found
a Regalia for you, actually.
Huh?
What are you talking about?
Well... here he is!
What do you think of him?
Lia- Regalia.
Run away!
You thought that
could be a Regalia?
Sure, why wouldn't I?
You did tell me that
Regalias were spirits!
That's an ordinary ol' Phantom!
A twisted ball
of emotions and curses!
Can't you tell that much?
Well, yes!
Actually, that's what I thought
when I first spotted it, too.
Smells nice!
But then I remembered
what you said earlier
about not making judgments based
on how things first appear.
This is how you chose
to apply that lesson?
You've got awesome timing!
And there's one more thing, too.
I got separated
from my body again!
Your timing seriously sucks.
Hiyori!
Oh yeah, that's right!
I forgot.
I'm actually a halfway
decent fighter in this form!
It's okay! I'm fine!
I can take care
of this guy myself.
Hey, there, ugly.
Come and get me!
Here I go!
Jungle Savate!
Come on!
[BOTH panting]
Hey, what happened?
Your hand really
isn't looking so good.
Are you o--
I'm fine.
Don't touch me.
Or it will
blight you, too.
What do you mean?
A blight is
a kind of defilement.
One that can spread.
Unless you exorcise,
or cleanse, it,
it'll stay there
and eat away at you.
[SPIDER PHANTOM]
Smells nice.
Also, we need to talk
about your backside.
What?
That thing ain't a tail.
It connects your physical
and ethereal forms.
Like a lifeline.
[SPIDER PHANTOM]
Nice smell!
If something
happens to sever it.
Then you'll die!
No way!
You mean
I'm not wireless?
That's not cool!
That's your worry?
Listen, human!
You're out of your league
trying to fight that Phantom.
Don't do anything
like that again!
But you said
yourself that you can't do
anything without
a Regalia, right?
Back off!
I've been trying
to find one, okay?
I have to--
A young boy.
Not so young... looks to
be in his teens, I'd say.
A difficult enough
age for anybody.
Smells nice!
Uh, Yato.
I think he'll do.
Smells nice!
Spirit, you are lost and adrift.
You have nowhere to go
and nowhere to return to.
Thus, I grant you
a place to belong.
My name is Yato.
Bearing two names,
you shall remain here.
With these names,
I make thee my servant.
With these names I use my life
to make thee a Regalia,
fit to be wielded by a god.
Thou art Yuki!
As Regalia, Sekki!
Come Sekki!
A sword?
Yato!
No! Yato!
[YATO] This is the land
of the rising sun.
Your desecrations
shall not be allowed.
Hear me.
I am the god Yato.
I now lay thee
waste with the Sekki
and expel thy vast defilement!
I cleanse thee!
Rend!
That's so...
Wait, was he just crying?
[HIYORI] I found my body
and brought it back!
It's so cold!
What are you doing?
I have to cleanse
the blight from my hand.
So all it takes
is a little water?
This day wasn't
a total waste, after all.
It's a lucky thing we ran
into an uncorrupted spirit.
Really lucky.
The blade's
the perfect length.
Wow!
So that's a Regalia!
Cool!
It's looks sharp
and shiny.
Which I'm guessing is good.
Sure is. Name's Yuki.
Or, less formally, Yukine.
Whoa!
It became a boy!
Yukine.
I am Yato.
I'm your master now.
I summoned you here from
the Far Shore to be my Regalia.
You will remain by my side.
You need not return
from whence you came.
Take this.
Go on.
You've nothing to fear.
[YUKINE] I don't
want a stinky tracksuit.
Um, well, take this.
It's cold out here.
Can we get
inside, already?
Hey. You hear me?
[YATO]
Are you cold?
You can put on my
fluffy-fluff scarf.
[HIYORI] Thanks for
the offer, really.
But I think I'm okay.
Next time, on Noragami:
"Bidden Calamity."
Oh, go on, just
take the scarf.
I'm gonna pass.