&gt;&gt; HMM!
THERE YOU GO! ALL DONE.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YOU'RE THE BEST, LIZ.
THANKS.
[ COINS CLINK ]
&gt;&gt; SURE! ANYTIME.
HEY, AREN'T YOU SUPPOSED TO BE
OUT HUNTING WITH THE GUILD
TODAY?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ SIGHS ]
YEAH.
I HAD TO TAKE THE DAY OFF,
'CAUSE I SORT OF HAVE THIS
LITTLE MEETING WITH SOMEONE.
&gt;&gt; OH.
[ LAUGHS MISCHIEVOUSLY ]
I BET YOU HAVE A LITTLE MEETING!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: NO!
IT'S NOT LIKE THAT!
[ BELL CHIMING ]
[ GASPS ]
UH, I HAVE TO GET GOING!
&gt;&gt; I BET HE MUST BE PRETTY
SPECIAL, WHOEVER HE IS.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HUH?
DID YOU SAY SOMETHING?
&gt;&gt; MM. GET GOING!
IT'S RUDE TO KEEP YOUR DATE
WAITING!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: IT'S NOT LIKE THAT!
I -- UH, WHATEVER! SEE YOU!
&gt;&gt; I WONDER IF I'LL EVER FIND
SOMEONE SPECIAL.
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ METAL CLANGING ]
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS ]
HMM.
GOOD ENOUGH, I GUESS.
[ DOOR OPENS, BELL RINGS ]
I BETTER GET READY FOR THE
CUSTOMERS!
PERFECT!
WELCOME TO LISBETH'S BLACKSMITH
SHOP!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH. HI.
UH, I WAS WONDERING IF YOU DO
CUSTOM ORDERS.
&gt;&gt; [ GROANING SOFTLY ]
[ Thinking ] HMM.
HE DOESN'T LOOK LIKE HE HAS THAT
MUCH MONEY.
I CAN.
THE THING IS, METAL PRICES ARE
KIND OF HIGH THESE DAYS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH.
WELL, I'M NOT WORRIED ABOUT THE
COST.
I JUST WANT THE BEST SWORD YOU
CAN MAKE AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
&gt;&gt; WELL, I MAKE A LOT OF
DIFFERENT SWORDS.
BUT IF YOU HAVE ANY IDEA OF THE
QUALITY OF SWORD YOU WANT, I CAN
MAKE IT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH, SURE. ONE SEC.
&gt;&gt; HMM?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SO, I'M LOOKING FOR
SOMETHING EITHER THE SAME
QUALITY OR BETTER THAN THIS.
&gt;&gt; OH.
[ YELPS ]
AN ELUCIDATOR!
THIS IS THE GNARLIEST MAGIC
SWORD A PERSON CAN GET FROM A
MONSTER DROP!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT DO YOU THINK?
&gt;&gt; MM.
[ METAL CLANKING ]
HOW ABOUT THIS?
IT'S THE BEST SWORD I EVER
FORGED.
I CALL IT MY MASTERPIECE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S A LITTLE LIGHT.
&gt;&gt; IT SHOULD BE.
I USED A SPEED-TYPE METAL TO
FORGE IT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'D LIKE TO TEST IT,
IF IT'S COOL.
&gt;&gt; TEST IT HOW?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU KNOW, ITS
DURABILITY.
[ METAL SCRAPING ]
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
WHAT THE HECK ARE YOU DOING?!
IF YOU BREAK YOUR SWORD, I'M NOT
RESPONSIBLE!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IF IT BREAKS, THEN
THAT'S TOO BAD!
&gt;&gt; [ SCREAMS ]
[ GASPING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH...
&gt;&gt; YOU BROKE MY MASTERPIECE.
[ WHIMPERS ]
[ CRYING ]
WHAT THE HELL WERE YOU
THINKING?!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'M SORRY!
I DIDN'T THINK YOURS WAS GONNA
BREAK SO EASY, HONEST!
&gt;&gt; ARE YOU SAYING MY SWORD, MY
MASTERPIECE OF A SWORD, WAS
LAMER THAN YOU THOUGHT?!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH...SOMETHING LIKE
THAT.
&gt;&gt; [ GROWLS ]
FOR YOUR INFORMATION, IF I HAD
THE RIGHT MATERIALS, I COULD
MAKE A BUTT-LOAD OF SWORDS THAT
WOULD SHATTER YOURS INTO A
MILLION TINY, LITTLE PIECES!
YOU GOT THAT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH, YEAH?
THAT SOUNDS LIKE THE KIND OF
SWORD I'M LOOKING FOR, AS LONG
AS IT CAN SHATTER MINE, THOUGH.
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
OKAY, SMARTY PANTS!
BUT YOU HAVE TO HELP ME MAKE IT
EVERY STEP OF THE WAY!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SERIOUSLY?
&gt;&gt; ABSOLUTELY.
AND WE'LL START BY GETTING THE
METAL FOR IT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I THINK I CAN HANDLE
THAT MYSELF.
I'D RATHER NOT HAVE YOU SLOWING
ME DOWN.
&gt;&gt; DON'T YOU DARE INSULT ME!
BELIEVE IT OR NOT, I'M AN EXPERT
MACE-USER.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SUIT YOURSELF.
SO, WHERE DO WE FIND THE METAL?
&gt;&gt; FLOOR 55 ON THE WESTERN
MOUNTAIN.
THERE'S A DRAGON THERE THAT EATS
CRYSTALS.
ACCORDING TO THE LEGENDS, IT'S
SUPPOSED TO STORE A RARE METAL
IN ITS BODY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: FLOOR 55, HUH?
YEAH, I SHOULD GO ALONE.
>>ANDTHEY SAY THAT IN ORDER TO
GET THE METAL, YOU NEED TO BRING
A MASTER SMITH ALONG.
STILL THINK GOING ALONE'S A GOOD
IDEA?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I --
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: FINE.
JUST KEEP QUIET AND STAY OUT OF
THE WAY.
&gt;&gt; WHA-- KEEP QUIET AND --
&gt;&gt; Kirito: BY THE WAY, MY NAME'S
KIRITO.
LOOKS LIKE WE'RE A PARTY UNTIL
WE MAKE THAT SWORD.
>> YEAH, WHATEVER, KIRITO!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WELL, IF YOU'RE GONNA
BE LIKE THAT, I CAN ROLL WITH
IT...
LIS-S-S-S-BETH!
&gt;&gt; [ GROANS ]
&gt;&gt; [ SHIVERING ]
[ SNEEZES ]
[ SNIFFLES ]
IT'S COLD!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WELL, YOU SHOULD'VE
BROUGHT A COAT OR SOMETHING.
&gt;&gt; I DIDN'T KNOW FLOOR 55 WAS
GOING TO BE THIS FREAKING COLD!
[ SHIVERING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
HUH?
ARE YOU GOING TO BE OKAY WITHOUT
THIS?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU DON'T FEEL COLD
IF YOU'RE DISCIPLINED.
&gt;&gt; IF YOU'RE TRYING TO PISS ME
OFF, IT'S WORKING.
IT'S WARM, THOUGH.
[ Thinking ] I CAN'T BELIEVE I'M
OUT HERE ALL ALONE WITH THIS
GUY.
THIS IS GETTING WEIRD.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT'S WRONG,
LISBETH?
GIVING UP ALREADY?
&gt;&gt; NOT ON YOUR LIFE!
AND IF YOU'RE GONNA BE A JERK
ABOUT IT, YOU MIGHT AS WELL CALL
ME LIZ.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY, OKAY!
GOT IT, LIZ.
&gt;&gt; YEAH, WELL, DON'T WEAR IT
OUT!
[ GASPS ]
[ GIGGLES ]
[ GASPING ]
IT'S BEAUTIFUL!
[ LAUGHING ]
[ GRUNTS ]
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU SHOULD GET YOUR
TELEPORT CRYSTAL READY.
&gt;&gt; I KNOW, I KNOW.
I'M DOING IT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: AND I'M HANDLING THIS
PART ON MY OWN.
ONCE THE DRAGON APPEARS, YOU'RE
GONNA HIDE UNDER ONE OF THOSE
CRYSTALS OVER THERE.
DON'T COME OUT NO MATTER WHAT.
&gt;&gt; OH, COME ON!
I'M NOT A NOOB!
IF I WANT HELP YOU, I'LL DARN
WELL --
&gt;&gt; Kirito: DO WHAT I SAY!
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
MM-HMM.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: GOOD.
OKAY. LET'S GET GOING.
[ ECHOING GROWL ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HURRY UP AND TAKE
COVER!
&gt;&gt; OKAY!
&gt;&gt; [ ROARS ]
[ GROWLING ]
&gt;&gt; WATCH OUT!
IT'S A BREATH ATTACK!
[ Thinking ] WOW.
AND WITH THAT SKINNY SWORD!
WHO IS HE?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ YELLING ]
&gt;&gt; COME ON!
STOP PLAYING WITH IT AND FINISH
IT OFF ALREADY!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: DAMN IT!
DON'T COME OUT YET!
&gt;&gt; [ ROARS ]
&gt;&gt; WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
YOU'VE GOT IT RIGHT WHERE YOU --
[ GASPING ]
[ SCREAMS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: LIZ!
&gt;&gt; [ SCREAMING ]
[ GASPING ]
[ SCREAMING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HANG ON TO ME, LIZ!
&gt;&gt; [ CONTINUES SCREAMING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: ARE WE STILL ALIVE?
&gt;&gt; YEAH. LOOKS LIKE IT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTING ]
[ CLINKING ]
DRINK ONE OF THESE JUST IN CASE.
&gt;&gt; MM.
[ BEEPING ]
THANK YOU, YOU KNOW, FOR -- FOR
SAVING ME.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IT'S A LITTLE EARLY
TO BE THANKING ANYONE.
WE HAVE TO FIND A WAY TO GET OUT
OF HERE FIRST.
&gt;&gt; HUH?
CAN'T WE JUST TELEPORT OUT?
[ CLINK ]
TELEPORT -- LINDAS!
NO WAY!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WELL, IF WE CAN'T USE
CRYSTALS, THAT MEANS THERE
SHOULD BE ANOTHER WAY OUT.
&gt;&gt; HOW CAN YOU BE SO SURE THERE
IS?!
I MEAN, MAYBE THIS IS SOME KIND
OF TRAP RIGGED TO KILL ANYONE
WHO FALLS INTO IT!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: GOOD POINT.
MAYBE IT IS.
&gt;&gt; WOULD IT KILL YOU TO AT LEAST
TRY TO CHEER ME UP?!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I THINK I HAVE AN
IDEA.
&gt;&gt; REALLY?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH.
WE COULD TRY RUNNING UP THE
WALL.
&gt;&gt; UH --
YOU'RE INSANE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: MAYBE.
BUT THAT'S ALL I GOT FOR IDEAS
RIGHT NOW.
&gt;&gt; NO WAY!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS ]
[ SCREAMING ]
[ CRASH ]
[ GRUNTS WEAKLY ]
IF I HAD MORE OF A RUNNING
START, I PROBABLY WOULD'VE MADE
&gt;&gt; YEAH, I DON'T THINK SO.
&gt;&gt; THIS IS KIND OF WEIRD, ISN'T
THIS WOULDN'T HAPPEN IN REAL
LIFE -- YOU KNOW, GOING TO
STRANGE PLACES, MEETING A TOTAL
STRANGER, AND THEN SLEEPING NEXT
TO THEM!
I MEAN, YOU ACTUALLY TRIED
RUNNING UP THAT WALL!
[ Laughing ] YOU REALLY ARE A
WEIRDO!
YOU KNOW THAT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WELL, EXCUSE ME.
&gt;&gt; [ GIGGLES ]
KIRITO, CAN I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: ASK AWAY.
I'M ALL EARS.
&gt;&gt; WHY DID YOU RISK YOUR LIFE
LIKE THAT TO SAVE ME?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I CAN'T JUST SIT BACK
AND WATCH SOMEONE DIE.
I'D RATHER DIE ALONGSIDE THEM
THAN DO NOTHING...
ESPECIALLY IF THAT SOMEONE'S A
GIRL LIKE YOU, LIZ.
&gt;&gt; WOW, YOU REALLY ARE AN IDIOT.
YOU'RE THE ONLY PERSON WHO'D
THINK LIKE THAT.
[ RUSTLING ]
HEY.
HOLD MY HAND?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH --
OKAY.
&gt;&gt; IT'S SO WARM.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HUH?
&gt;&gt; EVEN THOUGH YOU AND ME ARE
JUST THESE 1's AND 0's IN A
VIRTUAL WORLD.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I KNOW.
[ RUSTLING ]
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTING ]
[ SIGHS ]
WHAT THE...
[ WHIMPERING ]
WHATCHA DOING?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HMM? HERE. LOOK.
&gt;&gt; IS THIS...WHAT I THINK IT IS?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH-HUH.
IT'S THAT SPECIAL METAL WE CAME
ALL THIS WAY FOR.
LIKE YOU SAID, THE DRAGON EATS
CRYSTALS, AND THEY TURN TO THIS
IN ITS STOMACH.
[ CHUCKLES ]
NO WONDER IT'S HARD TO FIND.
&gt;&gt; YEAH, BUT YOU FOUND IT.
WHAT'S IT DOING DOWN HERE,
THOUGH?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THIS HOLE ISN'T A
TRAP LIKE WE THOUGHT.
IT'S THE DRAGON'S NEST.
&gt;&gt; RE-REALLY?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH-HUH.
AND THAT'S NOT JUST AN INGOT.
THAT'S DRAGON EXCREMENT.
YOU KNOW, POOP?
&gt;&gt; HUH
[ GROANS, SCREAMS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WELL, I GUESS THIS
MEANS WE GOT WHAT WE CAME HERE
FOR.
STILL STUCK, THOUGH.
&gt;&gt; [ WHIMPERING ]
WAIT.
THIS IS SUPPOSED TO BE A
DRAGON'S NEST, RIGHT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEP.
&gt;&gt; 'CAUSE DRAGONS ARE NOCTURNAL,
SO IT WON'T BE LONG BEFORE IT
COMES...HOME?
IT'S HERE!
&gt;&gt; [ ROARS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; WHA-- WHA-- WHA-WHAT ARE YOU
DOING?!
[ SCREAMS ]
[ GASPING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HANG ON TO ME, LIZ!
&gt;&gt; [ ROARS ]
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; [ SCREAMING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: ALMOST THERE!
[ BOTH SCREAMING ]
&gt;&gt; WOW.
LOOK AT THAT!
[ WIND RUSHING ]
[ Shouting ] KIRITO!
YOU KNOW WHAT?!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ Shouting ] NO,
WHAT?!
&gt;&gt; DON'T FREAK OUT, BUT I'M
FALLING IN LOVE WITH YOU!
[ GIGGLES ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I CAN'T HEAR A THING!
WHAT DID YOU JUST SAY?!
[ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; [ LAUGHS ]
NEVER MIND!
[ LAUGHING ]
A ONE-HANDED LONGSWORD, RIGHT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEP.
MAKE IT AWESOME.
&gt;&gt; [ Thinking ] I DIDN'T IMAGINE
THE WARMTH OF KIRITO'S HANDS...
THE WAY I FEEL?
AS SOON AS I'VE MADE THE BEST
SWORD I CAN...
I'LL TELL HIM.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHOA.
&gt;&gt; THE SWORD IS CALLED
DARK REPULSOR.
ONE OF A KIND.
AND IT'S NOT EVEN IN THE
INFO BROKERS' DIRECTORY.
GO ON. TRY IT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY.
GOOD? BAD?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IT'S REAL HEAVY.
IT'S A GOOD SWORD!
&gt;&gt; YAY!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IT FEELS LIKE YOU
FORGED YOUR SOUL INTO IT.
OKAY.
YOU HELD UP YOUR END OF THE
DEAL.
IT'S TIME FOR ME TO PAY UP.
SO HOW MUCH?
&gt;&gt; UM...WELL...
I DON'T REALLY NEED ANY MONEY.
INSTEAD...
I'D LIKE TO BE YOUR EXCLUSIVE
BLACKSMITH FROM NOW ON.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
EXCLUSIVE?
WHAT'S WRONG?
&gt;&gt; I MEAN ANY TIME YOU GET BACK
FROM THE FIELD, STOP BY AND LET
ME DO MAINTENANCE ON YOUR GEAR,
EVERY DAY, FROM NOW TILL THE
END!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH --
LIZ, I --
&gt;&gt; KIRITO...
I JUST --
I --
[ DOOR OPENS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: LIZ! I WAS SO WORRIED!
&gt;&gt; ASUNA?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: LIZ!
WHERE WERE YOU LAST NIGHT?!
I TRIED MESSAGING YOU, BUT YOU
DIDN'T ANSWER, AND I COULDN'T
TRACK YOU ON THE MAP!
&gt;&gt; UH, SORRY.
I KIND OF GOT STUCK IN A
DUNGEON.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: A DUNGEON?!
YOU WENT ALL BY YOURSELF?!
&gt;&gt; UNH-UNH. I WENT WITH HIM.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HUH?
K-KIRITO?!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH, HEY, ASUNA!
LONG TIME, NO SEE!
IT'S BEEN, WHAT, LIKE TWO DAYS?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WELL, THIS IS A
SURPRISE!
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU WANTED TO
CHECK THIS PLACE OUT!
I WISH YOU WOULD'VE TOLD ME!
I COULD'VE COME WITH YOU!
&gt;&gt; I'M SORT OF CONFUSED.
YOU KNOW EACH OTHER?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH.
BOTH OF US ARE ON THE ASSAULT
TEAM, SO...
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HE SAID HE WAS LOOKING
TO GET A MORE POWERFUL SWORD, SO
I TOLD HIM ABOUT YOU AND YOUR
SHOP.
&gt;&gt; OH.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WHY IS SHE ACTING LIKE
THAT?
I SWEAR, IF YOU DID ANYTHING
WEIRD TO HER --
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I-I DIDN'T DO
ANYTHING!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: THEN WHY'D YOU STUTTER
JUST NOW, HUH?
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS SOFTLY ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU KNOW, YOU COULD
TRY TO SHOW A LITTLE MORE
COMPASSION.
I ALMOST GOT KILLED!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: LIKE THAT'S MY FAULT!
DON'T I ALWAYS TELL YOU NOT TO
FIGHT SOLO?!
&gt;&gt; RIGHT.
I GET IT NOW.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: IF THIS GUY SAID
ANYTHING RUDE, YOU'D TELL ME,
RIGHT?
LIZ?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH --
&gt;&gt; YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT RUDE,
TRY THIS!
FIRST THING HE DOES WHEN HE
COMES IN IS SHATTER MY BEST
SWORD!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WHAT?! I'M SORRY!
&gt;&gt; OH, COME ON.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO APOLOGIZE FOR
ANYTHING!
HE MIGHT BE A LITTLE WEIRD, BUT
HE'S NOT SUCH A BAD GUY.
DON'T SCREW THIS UP, ASUNA!
HE'S A KEEPER.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ WHIMPERS ]
BUT I TOLD YOU!
IT'S NOT LIKE THAT!
LIZ?
&gt;&gt; SORRY.
I HAVE TO GO PICK UP SOME
SUPPLIES!
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: BUT Y-YOU'RE GONNA
LEAVE THE STORE?
&gt;&gt; HOLD DOWN THE FORT FOR ME.
LATER!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WHAT?! NO, WAIT!
LI-- [ GROANS ]
[ FOOTSTEPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: LISBETH.
&gt;&gt; I ALMOST GOT AWAY WITH IT.
A COUPLE MORE MINUTES, AND I
WOULD'VE GONE BACK TO MY USUAL,
CHEERFUL SELF.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: LIZ, I --
&gt;&gt; HOW'D YOU KNOW I WAS HERE?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I SCANNED THE WHOLE
TOWN FOR YOU FROM UP THERE.
&gt;&gt; FIGURES YOU'D DO SOMETHING
CRAZY LIKE THAT.
SORRY IF I WORRIED YOU.
I'M FINE NOW.
MUST BE ALL THE EXCITEMENT.
I'M NOT USED TO HAVING
ADVENTURES.
ANYWAY --
OH, JUST FORGET EVERYTHING...
I SAID.
OKAY?
[ CRYING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: LIZ, I --
I JUST WANTED TO THANK YOU.
SEE, I --
I DON'T KNOW.
I ALWAYS THOUGHT DYING WAS
BETTER THAN SURVIVING DAY AFTER
DAY...
LIVING WITH THE GUILT.
&gt;&gt; KIRITO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: BUT THEN WE GOT STUCK
IN THAT HOLE, AND I WAS REALLY
HAPPY WE WERE STILL ALIVE!
I REALIZED THAT EVEN HERE, OUR
LIVES ARE REAL AND HAVE MEANING.
THANK YOU FOR HELPING ME SEE
THAT, LIZ.
I GUESS IT'S WHAT I'VE BEEN
LOOKING FOR THIS WHOLE TIME.
&gt;&gt; YEAH. ME, TOO.
I KNOW WHAT YOU MEAN!
I WAS ALSO LOOKING FOR
SOMETHING -- SOMETHING REAL,
HOPING I'D FIND IT.
THE WARMTH OF YOUR HAND --
FOR ME...
THAT WAS REAL.
DO ME A FAVOR, OKAY?
TELL ASUNA WHAT YOU TOLD ME.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: LIZ --
&gt;&gt; I'M FINE, REALLY!
THE GETTING-OVER-IT PART --
THAT'S GONNA TAKE A WHILE.
UNTIL I DO, PROMISE ME --
PROMISE ME YOU'LL PUT AN END TO
THIS WORLD.
TILL THEN...
I'LL KEEP DOING WHAT I DO BEST.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I PROMISE I WILL.
I SWEAR I'LL BEAT THE GAME.
&gt;&gt; [ EXHALES ]
IF YOU EVER NEED YOUR WEAPONS OR
GEAR REPAIRED, MY DOOR IS ALWAYS
OPEN.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SURE.
&gt;&gt; DON'T FORGET, NOW!
YOU'LL ALWAYS BE WELCOME AT MY
SHOP.
[ GIGGLES ]
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]