&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY, ARE YOU READY?
THERE'S NOTHING IN HERE.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HEY, WAIT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'LL BE OKAY.
I'M NOT GOING IN TOO FAR.
BESIDES, WE SHOULD FIND OUT WHAT
KIND OF BOSS WE'RE DEALING WITH.
HOW ELSE WE GONNA FIGURE OUT HOW
TO BEAT IT?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YEAH, I KNOW.
IT'S JUST --
[ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; [ ROARS ]
[ BOTH SCREAM ]
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ BOTH PANTING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: THAT ONE'S GONNA BE
TOUGH TO BEAT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU'RE RIGHT.
I SAW HE ONLY HAD THAT ONE BIG
SWORD, AND I'M PRETTY SURE IT'S
GOT SPECIAL ATTACKS, TOO.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO
PUT TANKS IN THE FRONT ROW AND
KEEP SWITCHING OUT, JUST TO WEAR
IT DOWN.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, AND IT WOULDN'T
HURT TO HAVE ABOUT 10 SHIELD
USERS.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: SHIELD USERS, HUH?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT? WHAT'S WRONG?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YOU ARE.
YOU'RE HIDING SOMETHING, AREN'T
YOU?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I JUST REALIZED
SOMETHING.
THE BIGGEST ADVANTAGE OF USING A
ONE-HANDED SWORD IS YOU CAN ALSO
USE A SHIELD.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
I DON'T THINK I'VE EVER SEEN YOU
USING ONE.
I DON'T USE A SHIELD BECAUSE
IT'LL SLOW DOWN MY RAPIER.
OTHERS DON'T BECAUSE THEY THINK
IT LOOKS DUMB.
AND HOW COME YOU'RE NOT USING
THE SWORD YOU COMMISSIONED FROM
LIZ?
VERY SUSPICIOUS.
MM-HMM.
HMM.
OH, NEVER MIND!
IT'S RUDE TO ASK PEOPLE TO
JUSTIFY THEIR SKILLS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: SINCE IT'S GOTTEN SO
LATE, MIGHT AS WELL HAVE LUNCH
HERE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: REALLY?
D-DID YOU MAKE IT YOURSELF?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YEP.
BUT YOU BETTER TAKE YOUR GLOVES
OFF BEFORE YOU EAT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH. SURE!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HERE YOU GO!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THIS IS GOOD!
HOW'D YOU GET IT TO TASTE SO
AMAZING?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: CHALK IT UP TO A WHOLE
YEAR OF TRAINING AND STUDY.
AINCRAD HAS EVERYTHING YOU NEED.
THERE'S ABOUT A HUNDRED
DIFFERENT SEASONINGS.
I MADE EVERYTHING JUST BY
CALCULATING ALL THE PARAMETERS
USED BY THE FLAVOR-RECREATION
ENGINE.
THIS WAS MADE WITH GROGUA SEED,
SHUGRA LEAF, AND CALIM WATER.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IT'S MAYONNAISE.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: AND I MADE THIS, USING
ABILBA SEED, SAG LEAVES, AND
ULAFISH BONE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHOA!
THAT TASTES EXACTLY LIKE...
SOY SAUCE!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GIGGLES ]
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I MADE THE SAUCE FOR THE
SANDWICH OUT OF THAT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: AMAZING!
IT'S PERFECT!
HAVE YOU THOUGHT ABOUT SELLING
THIS, CAUSE YOU'D MAKE A
FORTUNE!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YOU THINK IT'S THAT
GOOD?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WAIT.
YOU CAN'T SELL IT.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: BUT WHY NOT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: CAUSE THERE WOULDN'T
BE ANY LEFT FOR ME.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ SIGHS ]
MY GOD. YOU'RE SO GREEDY.
IF YOU LIKE IT THAT MUCH, I
COULD ALWAYS MAKE MORE.
[ ALL GRUMBLING ]
&gt;&gt; Klein: HEY, KIRITO!
HOW YOU DOING, BUDDY?!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HEY, KLEIN.
STILL ALIVE, HUH?
&gt;&gt; Klein: GEEZ!
YOU'RE THE SAME AS EVER.
WAIT. WHOA!
YOU'RE A SOLO PLAYER.
WHAT THE HECK ARE YOU DOING WITH
A...GIRL?
[ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UM, I COULD HAVE
SWORN YOU GUYS MET BEFORE AT ONE
OF THE BOSS FIGHTS.
I'LL INTRODUCE YOU.
THIS IS KLEIN, OF THE
FUURIN KAZAN GUILD.
AND THIS IS ASUNA, OF THE
KNIGHTS OF THE BLOOD OATH.
HEY. COME ON. SAY SOMETHING.
WHAT'S WRONG? YOU LAGGING?
&gt;&gt; Klein: HI! I'M K-KLEIN.
I'M 24 AND SINGLE AND LOOKING
FOR A [GRUNTS]
&gt;&gt; All: BOSS!
WHOA! ARE YOU REALLY THATASUNA!
[ ALL CHATTERING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: DON'T WORRY.
IT'S COOL.
THESE GUYS ARE OKAY.
YEAH, BUT I DON'T KNOW ABOUT
KLEIN.
WHAT THE HELL?
&gt;&gt; Klein: THAT'S PAYBACK, YOU
WEASEL.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: COME ON, KLEIN!
&gt;&gt; Klein: WHAT ARE YOU DOING
WITH A GIRL, HOLDING OUT ON ME?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GIGGLES ]
&gt;&gt; Klein: WHAT'S THE DEAL, MAN?
SPILL IT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH, WELL...
&gt;&gt; Asuna: EXCUSE ME?
KIRITO AND I ARE TOGETHER
BECAUSE WE'RE SORT OF IN A
PARTY.
&gt;&gt; All: HUH?!
&gt;&gt; Klein: KIRITO, YOU SON OF
A --
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WAIT!
IT'S NOT WHAT YOU THINK!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: KIRITO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT THE HELL?
IT'S AN ARMY.
&gt;&gt; Klein: IT'S THE BIG GUILD
THAT RUNS FLOOR ONE.
WHAT ARE THEY DOING UP HERE?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: THEY WERE ALMOST
SLAUGHTERED ON FLOOR 25.
INSTEAD OF CLEARING LEVELS,
THEY'VE BEEN TRYING TO BUILD UP
THEIR NUMBERS.
I HAVEN'T SEEN THEM ON THE FRONT
LINES IN AWHILE.
&gt;&gt; AT EASE!
I'M WITH THE AINCRAD LIBERATION
ARMY.
LIEUTENANT COLONEL CORVATZ.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'M KIRITO. SOLO.
&gt;&gt; SURE YOU ARE.
HAVE YOU CLEARED THE AREA UP
AHEAD?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH.
WE ALSO GOT A MAP WITH
DIRECTIONS TO THE BOSS ROOM.
&gt;&gt; HMM. RIGHT.
THEN HAND OVER THAT MAP AND
WE'LL BE ON OUR WAY.
&gt;&gt; Klein: [ GASPS ]
YOU WANT US TO JUST GIVE IT TO
YOU?!
DO YOU EVEN KNOW HOW MUCH OF A
PAIN IN THE ASS MAPPING IS?!
&gt;&gt; WE SHARE OUR INFORMATION AND
RESOURCES WITH CIVILIAN PLAYERS
ALL THE TIME!
AND WE DON'T CHARGE A THING FOR
WE MAINTAIN ORDER IN THE CHAOS
OF BATTLE SO THAT ALL PLAYERS
CAN LEAVE THIS WORLD AS QUICKLY
AS POSSIBLE!
THEREFORE, IT'S YOUR DUTY TO
COOPERATE WITH US, SO HAND OVER
THAT MAP!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: LISTEN, YOU!
&gt;&gt; Klein: YOU BASTARD.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: EASY.
WHEN WE GOT BACK TO TOWN, I WAS
GONNA GO PUBLIC WITH THE MAP,
ANYWAY.
IT'S COOL.
&gt;&gt; Klein: OH, NOW, WAIT!
COME ON, MAN.
YOU'RE BEING WAY TOO NICE TO
HIM.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I DON'T CARE ABOUT
MAKING MONEY OFF MAP DATA.
&gt;&gt; HMM. THANKS FOR COOPERATING.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: BY THE WAY, IF YOU'RE
PLANNING TO HIT THE BOSS, I
WOULDN'T RECOMMEND IT.
>> THAT IS MYDECISION TO MAKE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HEY, I JUST TOOK A
LOOK INSIDE THAT ROOM, PAL.
AND YOU CAN'T BEAT THAT BOSS IF
YOUR TROOPS ARE HALF-DEAD!
LOOK AT THEM! THEY'RE EXHAUSTED!
&gt;&gt; NONSENSE!
MY MEN ARE TOUGHER THAN THAT!
THEY WON'T QUIT UNTIL I SAY SO!
ON YOUR FEET! COME ON, MOVE!
&gt;&gt; Klein: OH, MAN.
ARE THOSE GUYS GONNA BE OKAY?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I'M SURE THEY KNOW
WHAT THEY'RE DOING.
THEY WON'T RUSH THE BOSS WITHOUT
CHECKING IT OUT FIRST, RIGHT?
>> Kirito: MAYBE WE SHOULDKEEP
AN EYE ON THEM, ANYWAY.
[ ALL CHUCKLE ]
I DON'T KNOW WHO'S NICER --
YOU OR ME.
&gt;&gt; Klein: SO...ANYWAY...ASUNA.
I GOT A FAVOR TO ASK.
HE CAN BE HARD TO TALK TO, AND
HE'S A LONER AND ADDICTED TO
COMBAT.
BUT HE'S A GOOD GUY.
TAKE CARE OF HIM, WILL YOU?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: OKAY.
I PROMISE. HE'S IN GOOD HANDS.
[ SWORDS CLANKING ]
&gt;&gt; [ HISSES ]
&gt;&gt; Klein: THAT'S THE LAST ONE.
ONLY THING LEFT'S THE BOSS'S
ROOM.
MAYBE THOSE GUYS USED SOME KIND
OF TELEPORTATION THINGY TO GO
BACK.
[ SCREAM IN DISTANCE ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: ASUNA!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: MM-HMM.
&gt;&gt; Klein: HEY!
[ SCREAM IN DISTANCE ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: IDIOTS!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HEY! YOU GUYS OKAY?!
&gt;&gt; [ GROWLS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: DON'T JUST STAND
THERE!
USE YOUR TELEPORT CRYSTALS!
&gt;&gt; WE CAN'T!
TH-THE CRYSTALS AREN'T WORKING!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I'VE NEVER HEARD OF A
TRAP LIKE THIS BEING IN A BOSS
ROOM BEFORE.
&gt;&gt; THE AINCRAD LIBERATION ARMY
DOESN'T KNOW THE WORD "RETREAT"!
COME ON! KEEP FIGHTING!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THEY'RE INSANE.
&gt;&gt; Klein: HEY, THE HELL'S GOING
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THEY CAN'T USE THEIR
TELEPORTATION CRYSTALS.
WE COULD DISTRACT THE BOSS, BUT
GOING IN THERE'S TOO RISKY.
&gt;&gt; Klein: BUT ISN'T THERE
SOMETHINGWE CAN DO?
&gt;&gt; READY?!
CHA-A-A-A-RGE!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: DON'T DO IT!
&gt;&gt; [ SNARLS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HEY!
HANG ON, CORVATZ!
&gt;&gt; [ GASPING ]
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: NO.
&gt;&gt; [ SCREAMS, WHIMPERS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: NO. I CAN'T...
NO...
&gt;&gt; [ SCREAMS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: ASUNA!
&gt;&gt; Klein: OH, WHAT THE HELL!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: GET OUT!
&gt;&gt; Klein: I GOT YOU, BUDDY.
&gt;&gt; [ Weakly ] THANKS.
>> Kirito: THIS'LL TAKE FOREVER!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: GET OUT OF THERE!
&gt;&gt; Klein: KIRITO!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THE ONLY WAY TO END
THIS IS IF I USE IT!
BUT THEN...
DAMN IT, JUST USE IT ALREADY!
HEY, KLEIN! ASUNA!
LISTEN, I NEED 10 SECONDS!
KEEP HIM OFF ME!
&gt;&gt; Klein: YEAH, YOU GOT IT.
AAH!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY, I'M READY!
SWITCH OUT!
OKAY, HERE GOES.
STARBURST STREAM!
&gt;&gt; Klein: WHAT THE HELL KIND OF
SKILL'S THAT?
>> Kirito: FASTER!
GOT TO GO FASTER!
AAAAAAAAAAAAH!
IS IT...OVER?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: KIRITO!
WAKE UP, KIRITO!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ BREATHING WEAKLY ]
OH, MAN. MY HEAD.
THAT WAS TOO CLOSE.
HOW LONG WAS I OUT FOR?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: JUST A FEW SECONDS.
YOU RECKLESS...IDIOT!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: GEEZ, DON'T HUG ME SO
HARD.
I'LL LOSE THE LAST OF MY HP.
&gt;&gt; Klein: CORVATZ AND TWO OF HIS
MEN ARE THE ONLY ONES WHO DIDN'T
MAKE IT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WE HAVEN'T LOST A
PLAYER IN A BOSS FIGHT SINCE
FLOOR 67.
&gt;&gt; Klein: THAT WASN'T A BOSS
FIGHT, THAT WAS SUICIDE.
CORVATZ WAS A DAMN FOOL.
THERE'S NO POINT TO ANY OF THIS
IF YOU DIE!
YOU'RE NOT OFF THE HOOK, EITHER.
WHAT THE HELL DID YOU DO JUST
NOW?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I DON'T THINK YOU
WANT TO KNOW.
&gt;&gt; Klein: OH, COME ON!
I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYTHING LIKE
THAT BEFORE!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IT'S AN EXTRA SKILL I
PICKED UP -- DUAL-WIELDING.
[ ALL GASP ]
&gt;&gt; Klein: DUDE, ARE THERE
PREREQUISITES?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IF I KNEW THAT, I'D
HAVE SHARED IT BY NOW.
&gt;&gt; Klein: IT'S NOT ON THE INFO
BROKER'S SKILL LIST.
GUESS IT'S EXCLUSIVE TO YOU.
HEY, YOU GOT A UNIQUE SKILL.
WAY TO STAY ON THE DOWN-LOW,
KIRITO.
HOW CAN YOU KEEP AN AWESOME
SECRET LIKE THIS FROM YOUR
BUDDIES?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: ABOUT SIX MONTHS AGO,
I WAS SCROLLING THROUGH MY SKILL
MENU.
AND IT WAS JUST...THERE.
"DUAL-WIELDING."
BUT IF ANYONE ELSE FOUND OUT I
HAD A SKILL LIKE THIS --
&gt;&gt; Klein: THEY'D GET PISSED,
CAUSE YOU HAD SOMETHING THEY
DIDN'T.
SOME GAMERS ARE LIKE THAT, BUT
NOT ME.
YOU'RE RIGHT, THOUGH.
PEOPLE WOULD DEFINITELY BE
JEALOUS YOU HAD THAT.
AND THAT.
WELL, THEY SAY YOUR CHARACTER'S
BUILT BY LIFE'S CHALLENGES, SO
KEEP SOLDIERING ON, YOUNG MAN.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: EASIER SAID THAN
DONE.
&gt;&gt; Klein: WE'RE GONNA GO TRIGGER
THE WARP GATE.
YOU COMING?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO, I'LL CATCH UP
WITH YOU LATER.
NEED TO REST FOR A BIT.
&gt;&gt; Klein: I HEARD THAT.
HAVE A SAFE TRIP BACK.
OH, AND, BY THE WAY.
YOU KNOW HOW YOU RAN IN THERE
TO RESCUE THOSE ARMY GUYS LIKE
YOU DID?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH?
&gt;&gt; Klein: WELL, YOU KNOW, GLAD
YOU DID.
ANYWAY. I'LL SEE YOU.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT'S WRONG, ASUNA?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I WAS SO SCARED.
IF YOU DIED, I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT
I'D DO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT ARE YOU TALKING
ABOUT?
HEY, YOU'RE THE ONE WHO JUMPED
IN FIRST, REMEMBER?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I'M TAKING A LEAVE OF
ABSENCE FROM THE GUILD.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHY?
AND DO WHAT, SLEEP IN ALL DAY?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: DID YOU FORGET
ALREADY?
I SAID I WAS TEAMING UP WITH
YOU.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY.
&gt;&gt; Agil: "A BLUE DEMON THAT
ANNIHILATED A BIG SQUAD OF ARMY
GUYS, AND A 50-HIT COMBO FROM A
DUAL-WIELDER WHO TOOK OUT THE
BOSS BY HIMSELF."
I CAN'T BELIEVE WHAT A BIG DEAL
THEY'RE MAKING OUT OF THIS
THING.
[ LAUGHS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, IT'S BLOWING UP
RIGHT IN MY FACE.
A BUTT-LOAD OF SWORDSMEN AND
INFO BROKERS SHOWED UP AT MY
PLACE THIS MORNING.
NOW I NEED A NEW PAD, CAUSE THEY
KNOW WHERE I LIVE.
&gt;&gt; YEAH, WELL, THAT'S SORT OF,
KIND OF YOUR OWN FAULT.
&gt;&gt; YOU SAID IT WAS GONNA BE OUR
LITTLE SECRET, BUT YOU WENT AND
BLABBED IT TO EVERYONE.
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ FOOTSTEPS APPROACH ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ PANTING ]
WHAT ARE WE GONNA DO, KIRITO?
WE'VE GOT OURSELVES A HUGE
PROBLEM!
&gt;&gt; OUTSIDE OF BOSS FIGHTS, I
DON'T BELIEVE WE'VE EVER
ACTUALLY MET, KIRITO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WELL, THERE WAS THAT
CONFERENCE ON FLOOR 67.
WE TALKED A LITTLE BIT THERE,
COMMANDER HEATHCLIFF.
>> YES, THAT WASA DIFFICULT
BATTLE, WASN'T IT?
WE ALMOST LOST A FEW PLAYERS
THERE, TOO.
WE MAY BE THE TOP GUILD, BUT WE
BARELY GET BY WITH THE AMOUNT OF
TROOPS WE HAVE.
AND NOW HERE YOU ARE, TRYING TO
POACH ONE OF OUR BEST PLAYERS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IF SHE'S THAT
IMPORTANT, MAYBE YOU SHOULD DO A
BETTER JOB PICKING HER
BODYGUARD.
&gt;&gt; YOU HAVE MY SINCEREST
APOLOGIES FOR ANY TROUBLE YOU
MIGHT HAVE HAD WITH KURADEEL.
BUT YOU MUST UNDERSTAND THAT WE
SIMPLY CANNOT ALLOW OUR
SECOND-IN-COMMAND TO LEAVE THE
GUILD JUST LIKE THAT.
IF YOU WANT HER, YOU'LL HAVE TO
USE YOUR DUAL BLADES TO TAKE HER
FROM US.
IF YOU CAN DEFEAT ME IN COMBAT,
YOU'LL BE FREE TO TAKE ASUNA
WITH YOU.
ON THE OTHER HAND, IF YOU LOSE,
YOU WILL JOIN
THE KNIGHTS OF THE BLOOD OATH.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, OKAY.
IF YOU WANT TO SETTLE THIS WITH
SWORDS, THAT'S FINE BY ME.
WE'LL HAVE OURSELVES A DUEL,
THEN.
[ JAPANESE WOMAN SINGING ]