[ KNIFE PLUNGES ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS ]
YORUKO!
[ BREATHES RAGGEDLY ]
KEEP AN EYE ON HIM!
[ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: NO! WAIT!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
DAMN!
WHERE THE HELL DOES HE THINK
HE'S GOING?!
[ BELL TOLLING ]
[ GASPS ]
[BLEEP]
[ TOLLING CONTINUES ]
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
[ SWORD UNSHEATHES ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YOU IDIOT!
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH...
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ SIGHS ]
WELL, WHAT HAPPENED?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I LOST HIM.
HE TELEPORTED OFF SOMEWHERE.
THE SYSTEM'S SUPPOSED TO PROTECT
PLAYERS INSIDE THE INNS.
I THOUGHT, IF ANYWHERE, SHE'D BE
SAFE IN HERE.
DAMN IT!
&gt;&gt; THAT ROBE WAS GRISELDA'S.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS FEARFULLY ]
THAT WAS GRISELDA'S GHOST!
SHE'S COME BACK TO GET REVENGE
ON US!
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
THINK ABOUT IT -- ONLY A GHOST
CAN P.K. SOMEONE IN A SAFE ZONE.
[ LAUGHS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THAT WASN'T A GHOST.
SOMEONE'S USING THE SYSTEM TO
KILL.
THAT'S THE ONLY WAY THESE
MURDERS COULD HAVE HAPPENED IN A
SAFE ZONE.
I KNOW IT!
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO THINK.
WAS THAT BLACK-ROBED FIGURE
GRISELDA'S GHOST?
AFTER SEEING TWO PEOPLE DIE
MYSTERIOUSLY, I'M STARTING TO
THINK IT'S POSSIBLE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO.
THAT DEFINITELY WASN'T A GHOST.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HMM.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'D BET MY LIFE ON
WHY WOULD A GHOST NEED A
TELEPORT CRYSTAL?
TELEPORT CRYSTAL.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WHAT IS IT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NAH. IT'S NOTHING.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HMM.
HERE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH.
WHAT? IS THAT FOR ME?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WELL, WHAT DO YOU
THINK I'M DOING -- SHOWING IT
OFF?
ARE YOU GONNA TAKE IT, OR WHAT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH, OKAY. THANKS.
THANK YOU.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: BETTER EAT IT FAST
BEFORE IT DISAPPEARS.
ITS DURABILITY IS ALMOST DOWN TO
ZERO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH, UH, RIGHT.
IT'S DELICIOUS.
WHEN IN THE HECK YOU FIND TIME
TO PICK THIS UP?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I HAD A FEELING WE
WOULDN'T HAVE TIME FOR LUNCH
TODAY, SO THIS MORNING, I PACKED
ONE FOR US.
HURRY UP AND EAT IT, OKAY?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: GOT TO HAND IT TO
YOU -- FOR A SECOND-IN-COMMAND
OF THE
KNIGHTS OF THE BLOOD OATH, YOU
ROCK.
WHERE'D YOU BUY THESE, ANYWAY?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I DIDN'T.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HUH?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I MADE IT.
YES, I CAN COOK. SO WHAT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH.
[ GULPS ]
WOW.
I-I DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
I MEAN, IF YOU'RE LOOKING FOR A
SECOND CAREER, YOU'D MAKE A
KILLING SELLING THESE.
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ GASPING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: SHOULD HAVE BEEN
EATING INSTEAD OF TALKING.
ARE YOU CRYING?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SHH!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: MM.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO WAY!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THAT'S RIGHT!
THAT'S IT!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WHAT'S IT?
WHAT DID YOU JUST FIGURE OUT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I --
NO, WAIT --WENEVER SAW A
THING.
WE JUST THOUGHT WE DID, BUT WE
WERE SEEING SOMETHING ELSE.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HUH?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I WAS RIGHT.
THE GAME DOESN'TALLOW KILLING
INSIDE A SAFE ZONE.
THERE IS NO WEAPON OR SYSTEM
EXPLOIT!
&gt;&gt; GRISELDA.
THE ONLY WAY I CAN BE SAVED NOW
IS IF YOU FORGIVE ME.
[ ARMOR CLANKING ]
[ CRIES ]
I'M SORRY. I'M SO SORRY!
PLEASE FORGIVE ME, GRISELDA!
I SWEAR I NEVER THOUGHT THIS WAS
GOING TO HAPPEN!
YOU HAVE TO BELIEVE ME!
&gt;&gt; [ Ghostly voice ] OH, REALLY?
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
[ EERIE MUSIC PLAYS ]
&gt;&gt; OH, REALLY?
OH, REALLY?
&gt;&gt; [ GASPING ]
[ GASPS ]
[ SIGHS ]
[ GASPING ]
&gt;&gt; WHAT DID YOU DO TO ME?
TELL ME, SCHMIDT.
TELL ME WHAT YOU DID.
TELL ME NOW.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
OKAY! OKAY!
THE DAY WE VOTED TO SELL THE
RING, I-I-I LOOKED AT MY BELT
POUCH, AND THERE WAS A CRYSTAL
AND A NOTE WITH INSTRUCTIONS.
&gt;&gt; WHO WERE THEY FROM?
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; WHO GAVE YOU THEM?
GRIMLOCK?
YOU'RE DEAD, TOO?
&gt;&gt; TELL ME.
I WANT TO KNOW WHO GAVE YOU
THOSE INSTRUCTIONS.
&gt;&gt; I DON'T KNOW!
I SWEAR I DON'T KNOW!
THE NOTE SAID FOR ME TO BIND THE
CRYSTAL TO GRISELDA'S ROOM AT
THE INN SHE WAS STAYING AT SO
WHOEVER IT WAS COULD GET IN.
THEN I HAD TO PUT THE CRYSTAL IN
THE GUILD'S SHARED STORAGE.
&gt;&gt; THEN WHAT?
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
THAT'S ALL I DID! I SWEAR!
I DIDN'T WANT HER TO DIE.
I DIDN'T WANT TO BE PART OF
THAT!
PLEASE, BELIEVE ME!
[ CRIES ]
&gt;&gt; WE RECORDED EVERYTHING YOU
SAID, SCHMIDT.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
[ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WAIT. THEY'RE ALIVE?!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEP, THEY'RE ALIVE --
BOTH KAINS AND YORUKO.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: B-BUT...
&gt;&gt; Kirito: INSIDE SAFE ZONES, A
PLAYER'S H.P. DOESN'T DEPLETE ON
ITS OWN, BUT THE DURABILITY OF
AN OBJECT DOES-- JUST LIKE THAT
SANDWICH YOU GAVE ME.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WHAT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THAT DAY, THE SPEAR
WAS STICKING OUT OF KAIN'S
ARMOR.
IT WASN'T DRAINING HIS H.P.,
THOUGH.
IT WAS DRAINING THE DURABILITY
OF HIS ARMOR.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: BUT THEN H-HIS BODY
DIDN'T DISINTEGRATE.
IT WAS --
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEP, JUST HIS
ARMOR -- NOTHING ELSE.
AND AT THE PRECISE SECOND WHEN
HIS ARMOR'S DURABILITY
EXPIRED -- POOF -- KAINS USED A
CRYSTAL TO TELEPORT OUT OF HIS
ARMOR.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SURE, IT LOOKS A LOT
LIKE WHAT HAPPENS WHEN A PLAYER
DIES IN THE GAME -- ONLY HE
DIDN'T DIE.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
T-THEN WHAT HAPPENED TO YORUKO?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I BET THE DAGGER WAS
RIGGED TO HER BACK THE WHOLE
TIME.
SHE HAD IT ALL PLANNED OUT.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: BUT WE WOULD HAVE
SEEN.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: ONLY IF SHE TURNED
AROUND, THOUGH.
REMEMBER, SHE NEVER TURNED HER
BACK TO US, NOT EVEN ONCE.
SHE KEPT AN EYE ON HER
EQUIPMENT'S DURABILITY LEVEL
WHILE SHE WAS TALKING.
WHEN IT GOT DOWN TO ZERO, ALL
SHE HAD TO DO WAS ACT LIKE SHE
WAS HIT BY A DAGGER THROWN FROM
OUTSIDE THE WINDOW.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WHO WAS THE PERSON IN
THE BLACK ROBE YOU CHASED?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IT WASN'T GRIMLOCK.
I'M PRETTY SURE OF THAT.
BUT KAINS -- HE AND YORUKO WERE
IN IT TOGETHER.
THEY FIGURED OUT HOW THEY COULD
USE THIS METHOD TO FAKE THEIR
OWN DEATHS.
GETTING PEOPLE TO THINK THEY
WERE MURDERED IN A SAFE ZONE
WAS A CALCULATED TWIST.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: EVERYTHING THEY DID
WAS DESIGNED TO DRAW OUT THE
PERSON BEHIND GRISELDA'S MURDER
AND EXPOSE HIM.
THE ONLY WAY TO FIND OUT FOR
SURE WAS BY FAKING THEIR DEATHS
AND CREATING AN ILLUSIONARY
AVENGER.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: AND SCHMIDT WAS THE
PERSON THEY HAD PEGGED FOR IT,
PROBABLY SINCE THE BEGINNING.
HEY.
YOU STILL HAVE YORUKO ON YOUR
FRIEND LIST, DON'T YOU?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: OH.
[ MONITOR BEEPING, WHIRRING ]
RIGHT NOW SHE'S IN THE FIELD ON
FLOOR 19.
IT LOOKS LIKE SHE'S ON A SMALL
HILL JUST OUTSIDE OF TOWN.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I SEE.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: MM.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THAT'S IT THEN.
I GUESS THEY CAN HANDLE IT FROM
HERE.
I MEAN, OUR JOB'S PRETTY MUCH
DONE NOW.
WOULDN'T YOU SAY?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: MM-HMM.
&gt;&gt; YOU WERE...RECORDING?
[ GASPS ]
[ CRYSTAL WHIRRING ]
SO...THAT'S HOW IT IS, HUH?
YOU CARED ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED TO
GRISELDA AFTER ALL.
&gt;&gt; OF COURSE WE DID.
BUT YOU DIDN'T BETRAY HER
BECAUSE YOU HATED HER, DID YOU?
&gt;&gt; N-NO!
I DIDN'T HATE HER, HONEST.
I MEAN, SURE, I FEEL GUILTY
GETTING MONEY FROM MY PART OF
IT, BUT THE RARE WEAPON I BOUGHT
HELPED ME GET INTO THE
HOLY DRAGON ALLIANCE, SO...
[ SWORD SLASHES ]
[ GROANING, GASPING ]
[ THUDS ]
[ GROANING ]
[ WHIRRING ]
PARALYSIS?
&gt;&gt; ONE DOWN!
[ BOTH GASP ]
&gt;&gt; [ Strained ] NO...WAY!
&gt;&gt; THAT'S A HELL OF A CATCH -- A
BIG SHOT FROM THE
HOLY DRAGON ALLIANCE.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
THE LAUGHING COFFIN -- THE
MURDER GUILD.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPING ]
&gt;&gt; ALL RIGHT.
WHAT GAME SHOULD WE PLAY WITH
THESE THREE?
&gt;&gt; OH, I KNOW! I KNOW!
LET'S PLAY THE ONE WHERE THEY
HAVE TO KILL EACH OTHER -- LAST
ONE STANDING WINS!
&gt;&gt; I KNOW IT'S YOUR FAVORITE,
BUT LAST TIME WE DID THAT, YOU
KILLED THE WINNER ANYWAY.
&gt;&gt; OH, COME ON!
YOU SPOILED IT!
IT'S NO FUN IF THEY KNOW THEY'RE
GONNA DIE!
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; ALL RIGHT.
LET'S GET THIS SHOW ON THE ROAD.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
[ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; HUH?!
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS ]
[ HOOFBEATS ]
[ HORSE NEIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GROANS ] DAMN.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: LOOKS LIKE I MADE IT
JUST IN TIME.
[ GRUNTS ]
[ HORSE NEIGHS ]
SO, NOW WHAT?
I GOT 30 PLAYERS FROM THE
ASSAULT TEAM COMING.
YOU GUYS WANT TO STAY AND FIGHT
THEM?
&gt;&gt; [ GROWLS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; COME ON.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SIGHS ]
NICE TO SEE YOU ALIVE AGAIN...
YORUKO.
&gt;&gt; YOU WON'T BELIEVE ME, BUT
AFTER IT WAS OVER, I WAS GOING
TO TELL YOU THE TRUTH.
I AM SORRY WE HAD TO TRICK YOU
TO HELP US OUT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HMM.
&gt;&gt; KIRITO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: MM.
&gt;&gt; THANK YOU FOR SAVING ME,
BUT...HOW DID YOU FIGURE IT OUT?
HOW DID YOU KNOW THOSE THREE
WOULD ATTACK US HERE?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I DIDN'T FIGURE
ANYTHING OUT.
I WAS ACTING ON A HUNCH IS ALL.
HEY, YORUKO, KAINS, LEVEL WITH
ME -- YOU GUYS ASKED GRIMLOCK TO
MAKE THE SPEAR AND THE KNIFE,
DIDN'T YOU?
&gt;&gt; WE DID, BUT HE WAS AGAINST
OUR PLAN FROM THE BEGINNING.
ALL HE WANTED WAS TO LET
GRISELDA REST IN PEACE.
&gt;&gt; HE DID FORGE THE WEAPONS FOR
US, BUT ONLY AFTER WE GOT DOWN
ON OUR KNEES AND BEGGED HIM.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SORRY, BUT HE HAD A
DIFFERENT REASON FOR NOT LIKING
YOUR PLAN.
GRISELDA HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH
[ BOTH GASP ]
HE WAS WORRIED FAKING P.K.s IN A
SAFE ZONE WAS GONNA DRAW A LOT
OF ATTENTION.
HE DIDN'T WANT TO TAKE THE RISK
OF SOMEONE SNOOPING AROUND FOR
ANSWERS.
WE FIGURED THE WHOLE THING OUT
ABOUT HALF AN HOUR AGO.
WE ENDED UP PLAYING RIGHT INTO
YORUKO'S HANDS, DIDN'T WE?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I DON'T REALLY MIND.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YEAH, ME NEITHER.
HEY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: MM.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: IF YOU WERE IN THEIR
GUILD AND A SUPER-RARE ITEM LIKE
THAT DROPPED, WHAT WOULD YOU
HAVE DONE?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH, I DON'T KNOW.
I PLAY SOLO.
PART OF WHY I DO IS SO I CAN
AVOID SITUATIONS LIKE THAT.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: IN MY GUILD, THE ONE
WHO GOT THE KILL GETS IT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: THOSE ARE THE RULES WE
HAVE TO PLAY BY.
YOU KNOW HOW IN SAO IF A PLAYER
GETS A DROP, NO ONE KNOWS UNLESS
THAT PERSON REPORTS IT?
OUR WAY, NO ONE CAN HOARD STUFF,
BECAUSE WE WORKED OUT WHO GETS
WHAT AHEAD OF TIME.
ALSO, THE RULES MY GUILD PLAY BY
GIVES THE CONCEPT OF MARRIAGE IN
THIS WORLD REAL MEETING.
THINK ABOUT IT -- IF YOU MARRY,
YOU HAVE TO SHARE YOUR ITEM
STORAGE.
IF YOU'RE SINGLE, YOU CAN HIDE
WHATEVER YOU WANT, BUT, YOU
KNOW, WHEN YOU'RE MARRIED, YOU
CAN'T HIDE IT ANYMORE.
I THINK SHARING STORAGE WITH THE
PERSON YOU'RE MARRIED TO IS
WONDERFULLY PRAGMATIC.
AT THE SAME TIME, I THINK IT'S
ALSO VERY ROMANTIC.
[ DISHES CLATTERING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SIGHS ]
HEY.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YEAH? WHAT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SO, UH, HOW MANY
TIMES YOU BEEN MARRIED, ANYWAY?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WAIT!
I DIDN'T MEAN IT!
THAT DIDN'T COME OUT RIGHT!
YOU WERE TALKING ABOUT HOW IT'S
ROMANTIC AND PLASTIC AND --
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I DID NOT SAY THAT,
YOU ASS!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: AAH!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WHAT I SAID IS, "IT'S
ROMANTIC AND PRAGMATIC."
FOR YOUR INFORMATION, THE WORD
"PRAGMATIC" MEANS "PRACTICAL"!
MY GOD!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU THINK MARRIAGE IN
SAO IS...PRACTICAL?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: OF COURSE.
IF YOU'RE MARRIED, EVERYTHING'S
OUT IN THE OPEN, YOU KNOW,
'CAUSE OF COMMON STORAGE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WHAT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THAT'S IT -- COMMON
STORAGE.
OKAY, SAY YOUR SPOUSE DIES --
WHAT HAPPENS TO THE ITEMS?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HUH?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: ITEM STORAGE IS
SHARED, RIGHT?
SO WHEN ONE PERSON DIES, WHAT
HAPPENS TO THEIR STUFF?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: IF YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT GRISELDA AND GRIMLOCK --
HMM.
IF ONE OF THEM DIED...
&gt;&gt; Kirito: EVERYTHING WOULD GO
TO THE SURVIVING SPOUSE, RIGHT?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
AND IF EVERYTHING GOES TO THE
SPOUSE, THEN THE RING IN
GRISELDA'S STORAGE...
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SHOULD BE SITTING IN
GRIMLOCK'S STORAGE, NOTTHE
KILLER'S.
IT'S BEEN SITTING THERE THIS
WHOLE TIME.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: IT WAS NEVER STOLEN IN
THE FIRST PLACE.
>> Kirito: NO, IT WASSTOLEN.
IT DOESN'T MATTER IT'S STILL
THERE.
GRIMLOCK WAS BASICALLY STEALING
IT THE MINUTE HE PUT HIS PLAN
INTO ACTION.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; IT WAS GRIMLOCK?
THEN THOSE WERE HIS
INSTRUCTIONS.
THEN HE KILLED GRISELDA, TOO!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO, I DOUBT HE WAS
THE ONE WHO ACTUALLY KILLED HER.
ALTHOUGH, I'M PRETTY SURE HE
WENT AND FOUND HIMSELF A
RED PLAYER TO DO IT FOR HIM.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; MY GOD!
BUT THEN IF HE REALLY DID HAVE
HER KILLED, WHY WOULD HE GO TO
ALL THAT TROUBLE JUST TO HELP US
OUT?!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU EXPLAINED YOUR
PLAN TO HIM IN DETAIL, DIDN'T
YOU?
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOUR PLAN WAS THE
PERFECT CHANCE FOR HIM TO BURY
THE RING INCIDENT AND ANY
WITNESSES, ONCE AND FOR ALL.
ALL HE'D HAVE TO DO IS SIT BACK
AND WAIT FOR YOU, SCHMIDT, AND
KAINS TO GET TOGETHER.
YOU'D BE SITTING DUCKS.
&gt;&gt; THAT'S IT. THAT'S WHY.
THEY KNEW WE'D BE HERE BECAUSE
HE HIRED THEM.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH.
MY GUESS IS IT WAS PROBABLY THE
SAME BUNCH HE HIRED TO KILL
GRISELDA.
&gt;&gt; OH, MY GOD.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: FOUND HIM.
[ ALL GASP ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IF YOU WANT TO KNOW
MORE, YOU CAN ASK THE MAN
YOURSELF.
&gt;&gt; HELLO.
LONG TIME, NO SEE, COMRADES.
&gt;&gt; I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
DID YOU -- DID YOU REALLY PLAN
THIS?
HOW COULD YOU, GRIMLOCK?!
ANSWER ME!
WHY DID YOU KILL GRISELDA?!
WAS IT THE MONEY?!
WAS THE MONEY SO IMPORTANT TO
YOU THAT YOU'D KILL YOUR OWN
WIFE FOR IT?!
&gt;&gt; HMM.
&gt;&gt; [ CRYING ]
&gt;&gt; MONEY?
DID YOU SAY MONEY?
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
IT WASN'T FOR THE MONEY.
I HAD TO.
NO MATTER WHAT, I HAD TO KILL
HER WHILE WE WERE STUCK IN THIS
WORLD.
I HAD TO KILL HER WHILE SHE WAS
STILL MY WIFE...
AND BECAUSE SHE WAS ALSO MY WIFE
IN THE REAL WORLD.
[ BOTH GASP ]
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; IN A WAY, SHE WAS THE PERFECT
WIFE, IDEAL -- SO PRETTY, SO
SUBMISSIVE.
THE WHOLE TIME WE WERE TOGETHER,
WE NEVER HAD A SINGLE FIGHT.
BUT WHEN WE WERE TRAPPED IN
HERE -- IN THIS WORLD -- SHE
CHANGED.
IN HERE, I WAS THE ONE WHO WAS
AFRAID, TERRIFIED OF PLAYING
THIS DEATH GAME.
BUT SHE LOOKED SO MUCH HAPPIER
HERE, MORE ALIVE THAN SHE EVER
DID IN THE REAL WORLD.
THERE WAS NOTHING I COULD DO
ABOUT IT -- SHE CHANGED.
THE YUUKO I LOVED WAS GONE.
GONE!
BUT THEN I REALIZED I DIDN'T
HAVETO LIVE WITH THE WAY SHE
WAS.
MURDER ISPART OF THIS GAME!
IF I COULDN'T HAVE THE YUUKO I
LOVED BACK, I'D SETTLE FOR THE
MEMORY OF HER, AND WHO COULD
BLAME ME?!
[ BOTH GASP ]
>> Kirito: THAT'SWHY DID IT?
THAT'STHE REASON YOU KILLED
YOUR WIFE?
&gt;&gt; IT'S REASON ENOUGH.
AND, SOMEDAY, YOU'LL UNDERSTAND,
TOO.
ONCE YOU'VE FOUND LOVE, BELIEVE
ME, YOU'LL DO ANYTHINGTO KEEP
&gt;&gt; Kirito: MM.
[ SWORD CLINKS ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: YOU'RE WRONG,
GRIMLOCK.
YOU'VE GOT IT ALL WRONG.
YOU DIDN'T LOVE GRISELDA.
THAT'S NOT WHAT YOU FELT.
YOU STOPPED LOVING HER WHEN YOU
BECAME SELFISH AND POSSESSIVE!
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
[ DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ CRYING SOFTLY ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH...
&gt;&gt; KIRITO, WE APPRECIATE YOUR
HELP, BUT I THINK THIS IS OUR
PROBLEM TO DEAL WITH NOW.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OKAY.
[ YAWNING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HEY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HMM.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: SAY IT WAS YOU AND YOU
MARRIED SOMEONE AND LATER ON,
YOU FOUND OUT SHE HAD A SIDE TO
HER YOU DIDN'T KNOW ABOUT.
HOW WOULD YOU FEEL?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
I GUESS THAT I WAS LUCKY?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: MM.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH, BECAUSE, I MEAN,
IF YOU MARRY SOMEONE, THAT MEANS
YOU ALREADY LIKE WHATEVER YOU
KNOW ABOUT THEM, DOESN'T IT?
AND IF YOU DISCOVERED SOMETHING
YOU DIDN'T KNOW ABOUT THEM
BEFORE AND FELL IN LOVE WITH
THAT, TOO, THEN, UH, THAT WOULD
BE AWESOME?
&gt;&gt; Asuna: RIGHT. GOOD ANSWER.
ANYWAY, I'M HUNGRY AFTER ALL
THIS.
I DIDN'T REALLY GET TO FINISH MY
DINNER.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: OH. YEAH, YOU DIDN'T.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: WE SHOULD GET BACK TO
WORK TOMORROW.
WE'VE BEEN OFF THE FRONT LINES
FOR TWO DAYS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH.
I WAS HOPING TO HAVE THIS FLOOR
TOTALLY CLEARED BY THE END OF
THIS WEEK.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
NOW WHAT?
MM?
[ GASPS ]
HEY, KIRITO, DO YOU WANT TO
"FRIEND" ME?
IT'S KIND OF SILLY NOT TO.
IT'S CONVENIENT.
WE AREIN THE SAME ASSAULT TEAM,
AFTER ALL.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: BUT I'M A SOLO
PLAYER.
&gt;&gt; Asuna: HEY, I DIDN'T SAY YOU
HAD TO FORM A PARTY WITH ME.
YOU SHOULD TRY TO MAKE SOME
FRIENDS WHILE YOU'RE HERE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S NOT THAT I DON'T WANT --
HEY!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: THINK ABOUT IT WHILE
WE EAT -- NO PRESSURE.
COME ON.
LET'S GO BACK AND FIND A GOOD
RESTAURANT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH...OKAY.