&gt;&gt; MOMMY!
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; IT'S MOMMY!
SHE'S HERE!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: ARE YOU SURE?
&gt;&gt; YES, I'M POSITIVE!
&gt;&gt; HEY, I --
&gt;&gt; I SCANNED AGAIN, AND IT'S
MOMMY'S PLAYER I.D.!
HER COORDINATES ARE ABOVE US IN
THE TREE!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; KIRITO!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
WAIT!
KIRITO!
WHY ARE YOU ACTING LIKE THIS,
KIRITO?
IS THIS PERSON THAT IMPORTANT?
ARE THEY WORTH ALL THIS
TROUBLE?
[ GASPS ]
WATCH OUT, KIRITO!
YOU'RE GONNA HIT THE BARRIER!
[ CRASH ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: AAH!
&gt;&gt; AAH!
&gt;&gt; KIRITO!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; NO!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: AAH!
[ GRUNTING ]
&gt;&gt; STOP IT, KIRITO!
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
YOU CAN'T GET ANY HIGHER FROM
HERE!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I HAVE TO.
[ GRUNTS ]
DAMN IT, I HAVE TO TRY!
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; MOMMY!
I'M HERE, MOMMY!
[ CRYING ]
MOMM-Y-Y-Y-Y-Y!
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ] MOMMY!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: OHH.
[ GASPS SOFTLY ]
&gt;&gt; MOMMY!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: [ GASPS ]
Y-YUI! IS THAT YOU?!
&gt;&gt; MOMMY! MOMMY! I'M HERE!
&gt;&gt; Asuna: I'M UP HERE!
WHERE ARE YOU?!
YUI, I'M UP HERE!
[ CRYING ]
KIRITO!
COME ON -- THINK.
THERE'S GOT TO BE SOMETHING I
CAN DROP TO LET THEM KNOW I'M
HERE.
[ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS ]
[ CRASH ]
WHY CAN'T I BUST THROUGH IT?!
&gt;&gt; I USED WARNING MODE TO
CONTACT HER, BUT I DON'T KNOW IF
IT WORKED.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS ]
WHAT'S THAT?
A CARD?
LEAFA, DO YOU KNOW WHAT THIS
THING DOES?
&gt;&gt; UNH-UNH.
I'VE NEVER SEEN AN ITEM LIKE
THAT BEFORE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I CAN'T ACCESS THE
MENU ON IT.
&gt;&gt; LET'S SEE.
[ GASPS ] I GOT IT!
THIS IS A SYSTEM ADMIN ACCESS
CODE!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: REALLY?
DO YOU THINK WE CAN ACCESS THE
G.M. CONTROLS WITH IT?
&gt;&gt; NO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS SOFTLY ]
&gt;&gt; YOU NEED THE RIGHT CONSOLE TO
ACCESS THE CONTROLS, AND THE WAY
TO FIND IT IS THROUGH THE SYSTEM
MENU, AND EVEN I CAN'T BRING
THAT UP.
NO ONE CAN.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I SEE.
ALTHOUGH...I DOUBT SOMETHING
LIKE THIS WOULD JUST FALL OUT OF
THE SKY.
I WONDER...
&gt;&gt; YES! IT'S FROM MOMMY!
SHE MUST HAVE HEARD US AND
DROPPED IT!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: ASUNA.
LEAFA, I GOT A PLAN.
I NEED TO KNOW WHERE THE GATE IS
THAT WILL GET ME INSIDE THE
WORLD TREE.
&gt;&gt; WELL, THE GATE'S IN THE DOME
AT THE BASE OF THE TREE, BUT --
AHH! YOU'RE NOT THINKING ABOUT
GOING IN THERE!
THE BIGGEST RAIDING PARTIES
COULDN'T EVEN GET THROUGH!
THE WHOLE THING'S PROTECTED BY
GUARDIANS!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IT DOESN'T MATTER.
I HAVE TO TRY.
IT'S OKAY.
THANK YOU FOR EVERYTHING.
I'LL BE GOING ON MY OWN FROM
HERE ON.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ] OHH.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SIGHS SOFTLY ]
&gt;&gt; KIRITO.
&gt;&gt; SHOULD WE GET GOING NOW?
&gt;&gt; YEAH, SURE.
&gt;&gt; Both: AAH!
&gt;&gt; WHAT THE HELL?
&gt;&gt; IS THIS AN EVENT?
&gt;&gt; [ GROANS SOFTLY ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YUI, DO YOU KNOW HOW
TO GET TO THE DOME?
&gt;&gt; YES. JUST GO UP THOSE STAIRS
AND THEN G-- YAH!
A-ARE YOU SURE ABOUT THIS,
DADDY?
I'M ONLY ASKING BECAUSE, BASED
ON EVERYTHING WE'VE BEEN TOLD
ABOUT THE GATE, BREAKING IN
SOUNDS LIKE IT'S GOING TO BE
REALLY HARD.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WE DON'T HAVE ANY
OTHER CHOICE.
BESIDES, IT'S NOT LIKE WE'LL DIE
IF WE FAIL.
&gt;&gt; YEAH, I GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: IF I HAVE TO SPEND
ANOTHER SECOND WAITING AROUND,
DOING NOTHING, I'M GONNA LOSE MY
MIND.
AND I KNOW YOU WANT TO SEE
MOMMY, TOO, JUST AS BAD AS I DO.
&gt;&gt; I DO.
&gt;&gt; THOU KNOWEST NOT THE HEIGHTS
OF HEAVEN ABOVE.
DOST THOU SEEK ENTRY TO THE
CASTLE OF THE KING?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'M COMING, ASUNA.
I'M ALMOST THERE.
&gt;&gt; GO, THEN.
PROVE THOU ART WORTHY OF THY
WINGS.
PROVE THOU ART WORTHY OF FLIGHT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HERE WE GO, YUI.
KEEP YOUR HEAD DOWN, OKAY?
&gt;&gt; OKAY. GOOD LUCK.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GROWLS ]
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
GET OUT OF MY WA-A-A-A-A-Y!
I CAN DO THIS.
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
[ MID-TEMPO OPERATIC MUSIC
PLAYING ]
DIE!
[ GRUNTS ]
DIE, DAMN YOU!
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
[ CHUCKLES ]
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
UGH!
[ Crying ] ASUNA.
ASUNA.
ASUNA!
ASU--
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
ALMOST THERE.
I'M ALMOST THERE!
AAAH!
[ GASPS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
JUST A...LITTLE FURTHER.
[ GRUNTS ]
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
>> Kirito: I...
I...
I DIED?
I ALWAYS BELIEVED THAT, DEEP
DOWN, THIS WORLD WAS JUST A
GAME.
IS THIS MY PUNISHMENT FOR
THINKING THAT?
MY STRENGTH IN THE GAME IS A
LIE -- NOTHING MORE THAN A
BUNCH OF SKILLS AND STATS.
I DIDN'T GIVE A DAMN ABOUT ITS
RULES OR ITS LIMITS.
I THOUGHT I COULD DO ANYTHING.
[ SLOW MUSIC PLAYING ]
A GAME WHERE IT'S OKAY TO DIE
SHOULDN'T BE THAT BIG A DEAL.
ASUNA.
HUH?
[ GRUNTS SOFTLY, GASPS ]
GET AWAY! STAY BACK!
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
[ GASPS ]
KIRITO!
AAAH!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
[ BREATHING HEAVILY ]
KIRITO.
MM.
[ GASPS ] KIRITO!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THANK YOU, LEAFA.
&gt;&gt; I-I DIDN'T --
&gt;&gt; Kirito: PROMISE ME YOU WON'T
DO THAT AGAIN.
I CAN DO THIS ON MY OWN.
BUT I DON'T WANT TO CAUSE YOU
ANY MORE TROUBLE.
&gt;&gt; TROUBLE?! BUT IT'S NOT!
I WAS JUST --
HOLD ON. WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
WAIT!
YOU CAN'T DO THIS ALONE, KIRITO!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH.
MAYBE YOU'RE RIGHT.
&gt;&gt; YOU KNOW I'M RIGHT! LISTEN!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'M GOING ANYWAY.
&gt;&gt; [ GROANS SOFTLY ]
PLEASE...STOP.
JUST GO BACK TO HOW YOU WERE.
I-I JUST -- YOU MEAN SO MUCH
TO ME.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS SOFTLY ]
LEAFA...
SORRY.
IF I DON'T GET UP THERE, NOTHING
WILL END.
NOTHING WILL BEGIN.
I HAVE TO SEE HER AGAIN, JUST
ONCE.
I HAVE TO SEE ASUNA.
&gt;&gt; WHAT -- WHAT DID YOU JUST
SAY?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HER NAME'S ASUNA.
SHE'S THE ONE I'VE BEEN LOOKING
FOR.
&gt;&gt; BUT -- BUT THEN...
THEN YOU'RE...
OH, MY GOD.
[ GASPS ]
IS THAT YOU...
KAZUTO?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HUH?
SUGU?
SUGUHA?
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
[ Crying ] IT'S NOT FAIR!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: S-SUGU.
SUGU!
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
[ CRYING ]
[ KNOCK ON DOOR ]
[ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; SUGU, IT'S ME.
&gt;&gt; GO AWAY!
JUST GO!
LEAVE ME ALONE!
&gt;&gt; I WANT TO KNOW WHAT'S WRONG,
SUGU.
I MEAN, IT WAS KIND OF A SHOCK
FOR ME, TOO.
AND IF YOU'RE MAD BECAUSE I'M
USING THE NerveGear AGAIN, I'M
SORRY.
I JUST -- I DIDN'T HAVE A
CHOICE.
&gt;&gt; YOU'RE WRONG.
THAT'S NOT WHY.
IT'S NOT.
[ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; SUGU?
&gt;&gt; I...
I...
I BETRAYED THE FEELINGS I HAD!
I BETRAYED THE LOVE I FELT FOR
YOU.
WHEN I MET KIRITO, I THOUGHT
FINALLY I COULD GIVE UP ON ALL
THESE FEELINGS I HAVE FOR YOU.
WHAT THE HELL?
I ALREADY HAD!
BUT...I THINK NOW I...
[ CRYING ]
&gt;&gt; WELL, I MEAN, LOVE?
BUT YOU AND ME -- WE'RE --
&gt;&gt; NO, WE'RE NOT.
&gt;&gt; HUH?
&gt;&gt; I SAID, "NO, WE'RE NOT!"
I KNOW YOU'RE NOT REALLY MY
BROTHER AND I'M NOT YOUR SISTER!
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; I'VE KNOWN ALL ALONG -- FOR
THE LAST TWO YEARS, ANYWAY.
THAT'S WHY YOU QUIT KENDO, ISN'T
IT, AND WHY YOU STARTED AVOIDING
IT'S BECAUSE YOU KNEW THE WHOLE
TIME, DIDN'T YOU?
YOU PUSHED ME AWAY 'CAUSE I'M
NOT YOUR REAL SISTER, DIDN'T
YOU?!
YOU DID.
WELL, IF THAT'S HOW IT IS, WHY
DO YOU CARE ABOUT ME NOW?!
I JUST -- I WAS SO...HAPPY YOU
CAME BACK FROM S.A.O.
I WAS HAPPY 'CAUSE YOU WERE
BEING NICE TO ME AGAIN, JUST
LIKE WHEN WE WERE LITTLE.
IT FELT LIKE YOU WERE FINALLY
GIVING ME A CHANCE.
THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
BUT NOW, IF THIS IS HOW IT IS, I
WISH YOU'D KEPT ON BEING A JERK
TO ME.
IF YOU HAD, I WOULDN'T HAVE
REALIZED HOW I FELT ABOUT YOU.
I WOULDN'T HAVE FELT SAD AND
JEALOUS WHEN I FOUND OUT ABOUT
HER, AND I WOULDN'T HAVE TRIED
FORGETTING ABOUT YOU AND FALLING
IN LOVE WITH KIRITO INSTEAD!
[ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; I'M SORRY.
&gt;&gt; [ WHIMPERS ]
[ SNIFFLES ]
GO ON.
LEAVE ME ALONE.
[ CRYING ]
&gt;&gt; SUGU.
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]