&gt;&gt; [ SCREAMING ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THERE'S THE EXIT!
[ SIGHS ]
[ MONSTERS GROWLING ]
ARE YOU TRYING TO KILL ME?!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ CHUCKLES ]
NO, JUST TRYING TO SAVE US SOME
TIME.
&gt;&gt; YOU AND YOUR SHORTCUTS.
[ GASPS SOFTLY ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: UH, WAIT A SEC.
DO YOU EVEN KNOW WHERE THIS
MEETING'S HAPPENING?
&gt;&gt; YEAH, I'LL CHECK.
MM...
NORTHWEST -- INSIDE THAT
MOUNTAIN.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: HOW MUCH TIME WE GOT?
&gt;&gt; 20 MINUTES.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THEN WE'RE NOT GOING
FAST ENOUGH.
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I WISH WE COULD GO
FASTER, 'CAUSE AT THIS RATE,
WE'RE NOT GONNA MAKE IT BEFORE
THE SALAMANDERS.
&gt;&gt; I KNOW.
EVEN IF WE CANWARN THEM, IT
DOESN'T MEAN WE'LL GET THE
COMMANDERS OUT IN TIME.
WE JUST MIGHT END UP DYING WITH
THEM ALL IN BATTLE.
&gt;&gt; I'VE GOT PLAYER READINGS --
68 OF THEM FLYING IN FORMATION.
FROM WHAT I CAN TELL, IT COULD
BE THE SALAMANDER ATTACK SQUAD.
THERE ARE 14 MORE PLAYERS ON THE
PLATEAU.
MOST LIKELY, THEY'RE THE
DIPLOMATS FROM THE SYLPHS AND
CAIT SITHS.
THE TWO GROUPS OF PLAYERS WILL
MAKE CONTACT IN 50 SECONDS.
&gt;&gt; WE DIDN'T MAKE IT AFTER ALL.
THANKS FOR TRYING, KIRITO, BUT
THIS IS FAR ENOUGH.
I'M GONNA TRY AND SAVE SAKUYA.
GET OUT OF HERE AND HEAD FOR THE
WORLD TREE.
WE DIDN'T GET TO HANG OUT FOR
LONG, BUT IT WAS FUN.
HOPE WE MEET AGAIN SOMEDAY.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SORRY, BUT RUNNING
AWAY FROM A FIGHT'S NOT REALLY
MY STYLE.
[ PEOPLE MURMURING ]
&gt;&gt; WHY ARE THE SALAMANDERS HERE?
[ BOTH GASP ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: SALAMANDERS, STAND
DOWN!
&gt;&gt; WHO'S THAT?
&gt;&gt; SAKUYA!
&gt;&gt; LEAFA?
W-WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
&gt;&gt; IT'S TOO COMPLICATED TO GET
INTO NOW, BUT YOU SEE THAT
GUY OUT THERE?
BELIEVE IT OR NOT, THE FATES
OF OUR RACES DEPEND ON HIS NEXT
MOVE.
&gt;&gt; YOU HAVE GOT TO BE KIDDING.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I WANT TO TALK TO
YOUR COMMANDER!
&gt;&gt; WHAT THE HELL IS A SPRIGGAN
LIKE YOU DOING HERE?
I'M GONNA KILL YOU NO MATTER
WHAT YOUR ANSWER, BUT SINCE
YOU'RE BRAVE ENOUGH TO FACE ME,
I MIGHT AS WELL HEAR YOU OUT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: MY NAME IS KIRITO.
I'M AN AMBASSADOR FOR THE
SPRIGGAN/UNDINE ALLIANCE.
SINCE YOU'RE ON THE OFFENSIVE
TODAY, I'M ASSUMING YOU WANT TO
WAGE A FULL-ON WAR BETWEEN ALL
OUR RACES.
&gt;&gt; HUH?
&gt;&gt; UH...
MNH-MNH! MNH-MNH!
&gt;&gt; THE UNDINES ARE ALLIED WITH
THE SPRIGGANS, HUH?
AND YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE THEIR
AMBASSADOR, BUT YOU'VE COME HERE
WITHOUT A GUARD?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
SO WHAT?
I WAS SENT HERE TO NEGOTIATE
TRADE TERMS WITH THE SYLPHS AND
CAIT SITH, BUT IF YOU INTERRUPT
OUR TALKS, YOU'RE GONNA GET TO
FEEL SOME SERIOUS HURT.
ALL OF OUR RACES ARE GONNA TEAM
UP, AND WE'LL BRING THE FIGHT
STRAIGHT TO THE SALAMANDERS.
&gt;&gt; YOU'RE KIDDING ME, RIGHT?
YOU'RE ALL ALONE AND YOU'VE GOT
CRAPPY GEAR, SO THERE'S NO WAY
YOU COULD BE ANYONE'S
AMBASSADOR.
IF YOU CAN SURVIVE MY ATTACKS
FOR 30 SECONDS, THEN I'LL
BELIEVE YOU ARE WHO YOU SAY YOU
ARE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: GEE, THANKS.
THAT'S MIGHTY GENEROUS.
&gt;&gt; THIS IS BAD.
&gt;&gt; WHY?
&gt;&gt; DO YOU SEE THAT SALAMANDER'S
SWORD?
IT'S THE DEMON SWORD GRAM.
YOU NEED A TWO-HANDED SWORD
SKILL OF 950 TO EQUIP IT.
&gt;&gt; 950?!
&gt;&gt; YES.
AND THERE'S ONLY ONE PERSON I
KNOW WHO CAN USE IT --
GENERAL EUGENE.
HAVE YOU HEARD OF HIM?
&gt;&gt; YEAH, I KNOW THE NAME.
&gt;&gt; HE'S THE YOUNGER BROTHER OF
MORTIMER, THE LEADER OF THE
SALAMANDERS.
THEY'RE BROTHERS IN REAL LIFE,
TOO.
MORTIMER'S A BRILLIANT
STRATEGIST, BUT IN TERMS OF
SHEER POWER, THEY SAY EUGENE IS
THE GAME'S STRONGEST PLAYER.
&gt;&gt; OH, NO.
HE'S THE STRONGEST PLAYER?
KIRITO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: MNGH!
&gt;&gt; [ SHOUTS ]
&gt;&gt; OH! WHAT WAS THAT?!
&gt;&gt; THE ETHEREAL SHIFT -- THE
SWORD'S BONUS SKILL.
WHENEVER SOMEONE TRIES TO BLOCK
IT WITH A SHIELD OR A SWORD, THE
DEMONIC SWORD GRAM CAN PHASE
RIGHT THROUGH IT!
&gt;&gt; REALLY?! NO WAY!
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE NOT DEAD.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT THE HELL KIND OF
ATTACK WAS THAT?!
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: DAMN, HE'S GOOD.
HEY, BIG RED, I THINK YOUR 30
SECONDS ARE UP BY NOW.
&gt;&gt; I'VE CHANGED MY MIND.
I'VE DECIDED TO KILL YOU ANYWAY.
NOW YOU HAVE TO SURVIVE UNTIL I
DO.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, THAT FIGURES.
BUT I WON'T GO DOWN THAT EASY!
&gt;&gt; THIS WON'T END WELL.
THEY BOTH SEEM LIKE EQUALLY
SKILLED FIGHTERS, BUT EUGENE'S
WEAPON IS FAR SUPERIOR.
&gt;&gt; HE CAN DO IT.
KIRITO CAN BEAT HIM. I KNOW IT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SHOUTS ]
&gt;&gt; WHAT THE --
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I NEED TO BORROW THIS
FOR A SEC.
[ CLANK ]
&gt;&gt; K-KIRITO?
[ WHIMPERS ]
AAH!
&gt;&gt; A FEW SECONDS -- THAT'S ALL
YOU BOUGHT!
[ WARRIORS MURMURING ]
&gt;&gt; HEY, WHERE'D HE GO?
&gt;&gt; DO YOU THINK HE...RAN AWAY?
&gt;&gt; OF COURSE HE DIDN'T!
>> Kirito: AS LONG AS I'M
ALIVE, I'M NOT GONNA LET ANYONE
IN MY PARTY DIE.
I WON'T LET THAT HAPPEN AGAIN.
>>KIRITO WOULD NEVER RUN AWAY
AND LEAVE US.
[ WIND GUSTING ]
[ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; HUH?
&gt;&gt; KIRITO!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SHOUTS ]
[ SHOUTING ]
&gt;&gt; AAAAAAAAAH!
DIE!
YAAAAAH!
YAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ SHOUTS ]
&gt;&gt; AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAH!
&gt;&gt; SPLENDID! MARVELOUS!
&gt;&gt; THAT WAS THE MOST AMAZING
FIGHT EVER!
&gt;&gt; NICELY DONE, SPRIGGAN!
&gt;&gt; YEAH! WHOO-HOO!
[ CROWD CHEERING ]
&gt;&gt; THAT WAS GOOD!
&gt;&gt; YEAH, SERIOUSLY!
&gt;&gt; [ LAUGHS ]
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTING ]
YOU'RE AN EXCELLENT FIGHTER.
IN FACT, YOU'RE THE MOST
POWERFUL PLAYER I'VE EVER SEEN.
WELL DONE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YOU'RE NOT SO BAD
YOURSELF.
&gt;&gt; I DIDN'T KNOW THE SPRIGGANS
HAD SOMEONE LIKE YOU IN THEIR
RANKS.
THIS WORLD'S A BIGGER PLACE
THAN I THOUGHT.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: ARE WE COOL, THEN?
WILL YOU WITHDRAW?
&gt;&gt; MM.
&gt;&gt; EUGENE, MAY I HAVE A WORD?
&gt;&gt; KAGEMUNE, WHAT IS IT?
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ] HIM AGAIN.
>>OH.
THE NEXT TIME, I'LL MAKE SURE
TO BRING MORE FRIENDS ALONG.
YOU MIGHT FIND THIS INTERESTING.
YOU KNOW HOW MY PARTY WAS WIPED
OUT YESTERDAY?
&gt;&gt; SO?
&gt;&gt; WELL, THIS SPRIGGAN -- HE'S
THE SAME GUY WHO TOOK EVERYONE
OUT.
AND HE WASTRAVELING WITH AN
UNDINE.
&gt;&gt; HMM.
INTERESTING.
THEN I GUESS I HAVE TO BELIEVE
YOU.
BUT JUST FOR THE RECORD, THE
LAST THING OUR LEADER AND I WANT
IS TO GO TO WAR WITH THE
SPRIGGANS AND UNDINES.
WE'LL WITHDRAW FOR NOW, BUT I'M
GONNA BE LOOKING FORWARD TO
FIGHTING YOU AGAIN.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: THEN THAT MAKES TWO
OF US.
I GUESS SOMESALAMANDERS CAN BE
COOL AFTER ALL.
WHO KNEW?
&gt;&gt; YOU REALLY ARE INSANE, YOU
KNOW THAT?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, I GET THAT A
LOT.
&gt;&gt; [ LAUGHS ]
&gt;&gt; [ CLEARS THROAT ]
EXCUSE ME, BUT COULD EITHER OF
YOU EXPLAIN WHAT'S GOING ON?
I SEE.
I COULD TELL THERE WAS SOMETHING
OFF ABOUT SIGURD'S ATTITUDE
RECENTLY.
HE SEEMED SO IRRITATED.
&gt;&gt; IRRITATED?
ABOUT WHAT?
&gt;&gt; MY GUESS -- HE WAS
DISSATISFIED ABOUT THE STATE OF
THINGS, THAT IN TERMS OF POWER,
HE COULDN'T ACCEPT WE'D FALLEN
BEHIND THE SALAMANDERS.
POWER IS VERY IMPORTANT TO A MAN
LIKE SIGURD -- AND NOT JUST FOR
HIS ABILITIES AND CHARACTER
STATS, BUT ALSO AS A PLAYER.
HE CRAVES POWER.
&gt;&gt; YEAH, BUT EVEN SO, WHY WOULD
HE TURN SPY FOR THE SALAMANDERS?
&gt;&gt; IT MUST HAVE SOMETHING TO DO
WITH THE 5.0 UPDATE THAT'S GOING
TO BE RELEASED SOON.
I HEARD A RUMOR THAT THEY'LL BE
PUTTING IN A REINCARNATION
SYSTEM.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ] NO WAY!
&gt;&gt; I'M SURE MORTIMER MADE HIM AN
OFFER.
"BRING ME THE HEAD OF YOUR
LEADER, AND I'LL REINCARNATE YOU
AS A SALAMANDER."
&gt;&gt; SO, NOW WHAT?
WHAT'LL YOUDO, SAKUYA?
&gt;&gt; RU, HAVE YOU RAISED YOUR
DARK-MAGIC SKILL YET?
&gt;&gt; MM-HMM.
&gt;&gt; OPEN A MOONLIGHT MIRROR TO
SIGURD.
&gt;&gt; HMM.
[ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; SIGURD.
[ GLASS THUDS ]
&gt;&gt; S-SAKUYA!
&gt;&gt; NICE TO SEE YOU, TOO.
UNFORTUNATELY, I'M STILL ALIVE.
&gt;&gt; HOW -- I-I MEAN...
WHAT HAPPENED AT THE MEETING?
&gt;&gt; IT WENT VERY WELL.
THERE'S STILL THE MATTER OF
SIGNING THE TREATY, THOUGH.
BY THE WAY, WE HAD AN UNEXPECTED
GUEST.
&gt;&gt; W-WHAT GUEST?
&gt;&gt; HIS NAME IS GENERAL EUGENE,
AND HE SENDS HIS REGARDS.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
LEAFA.
SO THAT'SIT.
OH, THOSE INCOMPETENT LIZARDS.
WELL, IT'S YOURMOVE NOW,
SAKUYA.
ARE YOU GONNA FINE ME?
OR MAYBE YOU WANT TO TAKE AWAY
MY COMMAND.
IF SO, REMEMBER -- WITHOUT ME
RUNNING YOUR MILITARY, YOUR RULE
WON'T LAST VERY LONG.
&gt;&gt; ACTUALLY, I WAS THINKING OF
GRANTING THE REQUEST YOU MADE
THEM.
SINCE YOU CAN'T STAND BEING A
SYLPH, YOU'RE FREE TO GO.
&gt;&gt; WAIT -- WHAT?!
[ WARBLE ]
HOLD ON.
ARE YOU CRAZY?!
ME?! YOU-- YOU'RE BANISHING ME?!
&gt;&gt; I'M LETTING YOU LIVE TO
WANDER THE NEUTRAL TERRITORY AS
A RENEGADE.
WITH ANY LUCK, YOU'LL FIND
SOMETHING THERE THAT'LL OCCUPY
YOUR PRECIOUS TIME.
&gt;&gt; [ GROWLS ]
YOU BIT--
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; SAKUYA?
&gt;&gt; THANK YOU FOR SAVING US,
LEAFA.
YOU'VE NO IDEA HOW GRATEFUL I AM
HAVING YOU AROUND.
&gt;&gt; OH, WELL...I DIDN'T REALLY DO
ANYTHING.
IF YOU WANT TO THANK SOMEONE,
THANK KIRITO.
&gt;&gt; SHE'S RIGHT.
WHOEVER YOU ARE, YOU HAVE MY
THANKS.
&gt;&gt; HEY, HANDSOME, ABOUT THIS
SPRIGGAN/UNDINE AMBASSADOR
BUSINESS -- YOU AREN'T ,ARE YOU?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: MM...
&gt;&gt; UH...
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, THAT WAS A BIG,
FAT LIE.
I WAS BLUFFING, CONNING -- YOU
KNOW, NEGOTIATING.
[ BOTH GASP ]
&gt;&gt; OH, GOD. YOU MUST BE INSANE.
YOU HAVE TO BE, TO MAKE ALL THAT
STUFF UP AT THE LAST MINUTE.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH, BUT IT WORKED,
DIDN'T IT?
WHENEVER I'M DEALT A BAD HAND, I
ALWAYS RAISE THE POT.
&gt;&gt; YOU KNOW, FOR A BIG, FAT
LIAR, YOU'RE PRETTY FREAKIN'
STRONG, HANDSOME.
YOU'RE LIKE THE MVP OF
SPRIGGANS.
ARE YOU THEIR SECRET WEAPON?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NAH, OF COURSE NOT.
ALL I AM IS YOUR FRIENDLY
NEIGHBORHOOD MERCENARY.
&gt;&gt; [ SNORTS, LAUGHS ]
I LIKE THE WANDERING TYPE.
HAVE YOU EVER THOUGHT ABOUT
BEING A MERC FOR THE CAIT SITH?
YOU GET THREE MEALS A DAY, PLUS
SNACKS AND A NAP.
&gt;&gt; [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; SO, KIRITO, I WAS THINKING --
HOW ABOUT WE GET TO KNOW EACH
OTHER A LITTLE BETTER?
I KNOW A CUTE LITTLE PUB IN
SYLVAIN -- MY TREAT.
&gt;&gt; WAIT --
AW, COME ON, SAKUYA.
THAT'S NOT FAIR.
YOU'RE TOTALLY SEDUCING HIM WITH
THOSE THINGS.
>>I'MSEDUCING HIM?
IF YOUWERE ANY CLOSER TO HIM,
HE'D BE WEARING YOU.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GRUNTS SOFTLY ]
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
&gt;&gt; WOULD YOU GUYS CHILL OUT?!
FOR YOUR INFORMATION, HE'S MY --
[ SIGHS ]
I MEAN, HE'S...
[ GRUNTS SOFTLY ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: WHAT?
&gt;&gt; HE'S MY...
UH...NEVER MIND.
[ WHIMPERS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: LOOK, I APPRECIATE
THE OFFERS, REALLY.
BUT THE THING IS, SHE PROMISED
TO TAKE ME TO THE WORLD TREE,
SO...SORRY.
&gt;&gt; REALLY?
OH, WELL.
THAT ISA SHAME.
ARE YOU GOING THERE FOR A LITTLE
SIGHTSEEING, LEAFA?
OR...WHAT?
&gt;&gt; I'M LEAVING THE SYLPHS.
OR PLANNING ON IT, ANYWAY.
BUT I WANT TO RETURN TO SYLVAIN
AT SOME POINT.
I JUST DON'T KNOW WHEN THAT'S
GONNA BE.
&gt;&gt; NOT A PROBLEM. I UNDERSTAND.
JUST MAKE SURE YOU COME BACK,
OKAY?
AND BRING YOUR FRIEND.
&gt;&gt; ON THE WAY BACK, STOP BY MY
PLACE.
WE'LL THROW YOU A PARTY.
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
&gt;&gt; THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR COMING
TODAY, LEAFA, KIRITO.
IF YOU HADN'T BEEN HERE TO STOP
THEM, THE SALAMANDERS WOULD HAVE
BECOME EVEN MORE POWERFUL THAN
EVER.
I'D LIKE TO PAY YOU BACK
SOMEHOW.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ Chuckling ] OH, NO.
IT WAS NOTHING.
&gt;&gt; HEY, SAKUYA, ALICIA...
WASN'T THE POINT OF YOU GUYS
GETTING TOGETHER TO MAKE A TRIBE
FOR THE WORLD TREE?
>> ULTIMATELY, YES, THAT WASOUR
GOAL.
&gt;&gt; IF YOU'RE OKAY WITH IT AND
IT'S NO TROUBLE, WE'D LIKE TO GO
WITH YOU.
WE'RE KIND OF IN A HURRY TO GET
THERE, THOUGH.
&gt;&gt; Both: HMM.
&gt;&gt; HMM.
&gt;&gt; WELL, I CAN'T SEE WHY NOT.
IN FACT, THE TRUTH IS, WE'D BE
GRATEFUL TO HAVE YOU ALONG.
BUT WHY ARE YOU IN SUCH A HURRY
TO GET THERE?
&gt;&gt; [ SIGHS ]
>> Kirito: SHE'SNOT IN A HURRY.
I'MTHE ONE WHO HAS TO GET TO
THE TOP OF THE TREE.
I THINK SOMEONE I KNOW IS UP
THERE, WAITING FOR ME.
&gt;&gt; HMM.
IS IT OBERON, THE FAIRY KING?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO. IT'S NOT HIM.
IT'S SOMEONE I CAN'T REACH IN
REAL LIFE.
BUT IN HERE, I MIGHT BE ABLE TO.
&gt;&gt; WE WANT TO HELP, BUT STORMING
THE TREE'S GONNA TAKE SOME TIME
TO SET UP.
WE GOT TO GEAR UP THE RAIDING
PARTY AND STUFF, AND THAT'LL
TAKE US WAY MORE THAN A FEW
DAYS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I SEE.
NEVER MIND, THEN.
I DON'T WANT TO RAID THE TREE,
LIKE YOU.
I JUST WANT TO GET TO THE BASE
OF IT AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
SO IT'S COOL.
WE'LL FIGURE IT OUT.
BY THE WAY...
MAYBE THIS WILL HELP YOU GUYS
GET SOME NEW GEAR FOR YOUR RAID.
&gt;&gt; MM.
[ THUD, COINS JINGLE ]
[ GASPS ]
[ GRUNTS ]
WHOA! SAKUYA, LOOK!
CHECK IT OUT!
&gt;&gt; [ CHUCKLES ]
$100,000 PIECES OF
MITHRIL YULD?!
YOU DON'T WANT IT?
YOU COULD BUILD A CASTLE ON
PRIME LAND WITH THIS.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NAH, IT'S YOURS.
I DON'T NEED IT ANYMORE.
&gt;&gt; YOU ARE SO AWESOME.
WITH THIS BAG OF LOOT, WE'VE GOT
JUST ABOUT ENOUGH FOR NEW GEAR.
&gt;&gt; WE'LL GET READY AS FAST AS WE
CAN.
WHEN WE'RE SET TO GO, WE'LL
MESSAGE YOU, OKAY?
&gt;&gt; Kirito: YEAH. YOU GOT IT.
&gt;&gt; THANKS, GUYS!
WE'LL BE SEEIN' YA!
>> I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU,BUT I
CAN'T BELIEVE YOU PULLED THAT
OFF.
[ SIGHS ]
&gt;&gt; OH, HONESTLY!
I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU -- NO MORE
FLIRTING, DADDY!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: [ GASPS ]
&gt;&gt; [ GRUNTS ]
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I WASN'T FLIRTING
WITH ANYONE.
&gt;&gt; WHEN THOSE GIRLS WERE
CLINGING TO YOU, I NOTICED THAT
YOUR HEARTBEAT INCREASED.
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I'M A GUY.
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENS WHEN GIRLS
GET TOO CLOSE.
&gt;&gt; SERIOUSLY.
>> WHAT ABOUT ME? I'M A GIRL.
ISN'T THAT A PROBLEM?
&gt;&gt; NO, YOU SEEM PRETTY SAFE TO
ME, LEAFA.
&gt;&gt; WHAT DO YOU MEAN, "SAFE"?!
&gt;&gt; Both: MM...
&gt;&gt; Kirito: I THINK WHAT SHE
MEANS IS, MOST OF THE TIME, YOU
DON'T REALLY SEEM MUCH LIKE A
GIRL.
&gt;&gt; OKAY, WHOA!
SAY THAT AGAIN! I DARE YOU!
&gt;&gt; Kirito: NO, LIKE -- LIKE,
YOU'RE EASY TO GET ALONG WITH.
I MEANT IT IN A GOODWAY.
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ] YEAH.
COME ON.
WE STILL GOT A WAYS TO GO BEFORE
WE GET TO ARUN.
THE SUN'S STARTING TO GO DOWN.
&gt;&gt; OKAY, I'M COMING!
WAIT UP!
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ BIRDS CHIRPING ]
&gt;&gt; Asuna: 8, 1, 1...
[ BEEPING ]
3, 2, 3, 2, 9.
KIRITO, I PROMISE YOU --
I WON'T GIVE UP.
[ SIGHS ]
[ WOMAN SINGING IN JAPANESE ]