[KONATA]
Okay, let's do this.
[MIYUKI]
Sure, let's go!
[TSUKASA grunts]
[KAGAMI] Quit screwing
around and start!
[singing in Japanese]
Today's the warmest it's
been all autumn, and all over
the country school athletic
festivals are what's happening.
Yeah, I just came
to cheer my daughter on,
but who knew it'd
be this exciting?
I mean, the trip
was well worth it!
Let me tell you, some of
these pictures are amazing!
Oh, Dad.
I wonder whose daughter
you're talking about.
I don't know. Maybe I should
cut my hair for the festival.
Just chop it all
off really short.
Ah! Why do you want
to cut your hair?
It's taken you forever
to grow it out!
Uh, I wasn't serious,
I was just thinking.
Such a profound
response must mean...
It's about a guy, isn't it?
Don't relate
everything to that!
And don't talk so much, Tsukasa!
But if Kagami did
go and cut her hair...
[TSUKASA] Isn't the
super slim Pocky the same
as regular Pocky?
Don't do it!
Pigtails are the classic
tsundere hairstyle!
[KAGAMI]
Sorry, my face is so boring!
[KONATA] Oh, yeah, the
athletic festivals' coming up.
What a drag.
[KAGAMI] I never thought
I'd hear a teenager say that.
You're good at sports,
Kona-chan, so you'll do great,
but someone like me?
I'll just get in the way.
--[KAGAMI] Aww!
--[KONATA] You're gonna be fine.
Hey, sis, which event
are you gonna sign up for?
I totally know what
Kagami's gonna pick.
The bread-eating race!
If I didn't know better,
I'd say you're trying
to pick a fight with me.
All righty then, what event
are you going to sign up for?
Uhh.
Was I right? I was, wasn't I?
Pissing me off!
I guess you could
say I've been doing
some training for the festival.
Autumn is the season
for sports, you know.
Really?
The question is, are you really
doing it for the festival,
or are you doing it
for the event thing
that happens after it?
What event thing?
You want me to say it?
Really pissing me off!
So, Miyuki's gonna be running
in the relay race, huh?
That's understandable.
You're tellin' me.
But get this,
at first, she was gonna do
the obstacle course!
Okay, does anybody else
feel like volunteering?
Though I've never done
that before,I'll do my best!
But you can't, Miyuki-san!
Huh?
With those curvy curves,
you shouldn't be doing
the obstacle course.
You'll have to squeeze through
things and go over stuff.
[student laughs]
After that, she got
switched to the relay.
That sounds like something
a middle aged guy would say.
Do you remember
back in junior high?
Did your school ever
have any scavenger hunts?
Yeah, we did those.
One time a guy
who was doing it
came up to me with his list.
[KONATA] Me?
The weird thing is, he was
too embarrassed to tell me
what he wanted to scavenge.
I wonder what it was.
There are so many unspeakable
things it could be.
Well, I could ask Miyuki-san.
She might have an idea.
Leave her out of it,
there's no easy answer
for a question like that.
She asked her anyway!
Something about you
that's hard to mention
that might be the item
in a scavenger hunt?
Mm-hmm.
It's only speculation,
but perhaps
it's the mole on your face.
One could consider that
a sensitive subject.
Figures, she's a master
at dodging difficult questions.
But I'm sure she's wrong
[bell chimes]
I do enjoy
the athletic festivals,
but after that we
still have exams.
I think it's kinda sad 'cause
after the festivals' over
we run out of things to do.
The midterm proficiency
and finals exams
are all we have left!
And you always wear yourself
out in the second trimester
'cause of the arts
and athletic festivals.
Yeah.
The midterm is going to
be especially difficult!
[all sigh]
I heard that Autumn's
a good time for reading,
so maybe I'll read some books.
The climate this
time of year is also
excellent for studying.
And right before
Christmas is when they
bust out all the new games!
Although we have
final exams before that.
[all groan]
[BOTH]
Oh, yeah, and then there's--
Hold it! How about
the two of you
stop avoiding the inevitable?
That's right! It's almost
time for the athletic festival.
Do you know that pistol
that starts the events?
I always thought
that was a real gun!
I never figured it out
--till junior high.
--You've gotta be kidding.
No, I think seeing
that is what made me
want to become a cop
in the first place.
You chose your career
because of a misunderstanding?
Oh, by the way, Konata,
when's the school athletics
festival happening?
Here, it's this Sunday.
Augh! This Sunday?
How come you didn't
say anything?
Why didn't you tell
me this before?
But, Dad, we just
got the flyer today.
I'd better get ready.
What's up with your dad?
All right, people,
today's the real deal.
You're gonna get out
there and show 'em all
the fruits of your labor!
Yeah, ma'am? I haven't labored
that much but don't worry,
this stuff's gonna
be a piece of cake.
Don't get cocky!
The cavalier race is where I
want you to give 'em all hell!
Attack the enemy
from all sides
and pound 'em till they holler!
Wouldn't it be better if
we found their weak spot
and pounded that
until they holler?
But all we need
to do is take their hats,
I don't know about pounding.
Relax, don't sweat
the small stuff.
That's one of the mistakes
you make when you're a kid.
'Cause you're just a kid.
We're rooting for you, sis!
Do your best out there!
Hey, do either of you know
how they get the red bean buns
to stay on the strings?
Most likely the
buns are attached by
some sort of clip or something.
Oh. I guess it'll make it
harder to pull them off then.
Just remember you're a girl!
And as a girl you
must win elegantly!
There's nothing elegant
about a bread eating race!
-Get set!
-[gun fires]
[screams]
Aah!
She did it!
[muffled grunting]
[gasps]
Yup, that's our Kagami.
That man's camera
is really amazing.
[camera shutter clicking]
My dad. He's so easy to get.
Hey, aren't you running
the 100 meter dash?
It's coming up.
Yeah. I guess.
Kona-chan, can you teach
me how to run fast like you?
Just imagine yourself winning.
It's all about visualization.
[MAN]
On your mark!
Get set!
[gun fires]
[KONATA] That's some
old school visualization
you got going on.
[joystick toggles]
[gunshot]
[KONATA] Goal!
Kinda like that.
You're kidding.
Three meters, 25 centimeters.
[KONATA] If you fall
back they only measure up
to where your hands hit.
[grunts]
-[gasping]
-Oh, yeah!
[thuds]
That's Kagami.
The sand's not even
safe from her jabs.
[TSUKASA]
One two three, one two three.
I heard that to run
the hurdles you have to
time the number of your steps.
I don't get it.
One, two, and three and jump!
Oh, now I get it!
One, two, three,
one, two, three.
[MAN] Get set!
[gunshot]
Three, two, three,
one, three, huh?
Wait, I started off
with my right foot so that's
two, three, one!
[crash]
I'm not getting it!
I'm on my left foot now, so--
[crash]
Wait! What is it?
Three, two, one, augh!
Stunning. She's plowing
through every single
one of those things.
She's got a knack for it.
I guess I suck, huh?
No, listen, I thought
my daughter was in that race.
I didn't know, honest!
Same old, same old.
Time for the last relay race.
Yuki-chan,
do your best out there!
You've got it all wrong,
my daughter goes to this school!
Hang on, I haven't
done anything!
[gunshot]
Yeah, way to go,
you can do it, run!
All right,
we're in second place!
We're doing pretty good then.
Over here, Sachi!
Here! Got it!
We're in third place now.
Now this is what
I call a race!
[crowd cheering]
They're putting
up a good fight!
It's getting interesting.
I wonder if Yuki-chan's
going to be all right.
Got it.
Whoa!
[panting]
Go, Miyuki!
[camera shutter clicks]
[gasping]
All right, Yuki-chan,
you're so awesome!
That's our Miyuki-san.
She even remembers to give
the audience fan service.
[ALL]
Lucky Star.
Hmm. Okay.
[recorder playing off-key]
Is that Tsukasa?
Oh, man.
Happy Henry likes beer,
but could not obtain food.
[recorder continues playing]
[whimpering]
Hey, uh, could you do
something about that noise?
Sorry about that!
I'm playing the alto recorder
in music class,
but every time I play a note,
it feels like I'm
gonna pull a muscle!
Why did you choose
the alto part?
Well I sort of thought
the lower parts
would be easier to play.
Oh. Well, how about you
get your fingers used to
the recorder by
playing a simpler song?
Oh!
[playing "Twinkle, Twinkle,
Little Star"]
You're missing
most of the notes.
Just try to follow
what I do, okay?
Ready, and...
[playing]
Whoa, hang on, Tsukasa,
try it by yourself.
[playing]
That doesn't seem right somehow.
When you're playing,
try relaxing a bit more.
Maybe you'll play better if
you're not as tense, you know?
Okay, just relax.
Yep.
I'll give it a shot. Here we go.
[inhales]
[plays "Joy to the World"]
[sharp inhale]
[sharp inhaling]
She's sucking in more air
than she's blowing out.
I'd eat in the cafeteria more,
but every time
I come here,
it's always super packed.
[KONATA] If I don't get
some food, I'm gonna faint!
Standing in line
always makes me tired.
Man, this blows.
Aren't you used
to this kinda stuff
from all the cons you go to?
Yeah, but if there's nothing
exciting at the other end,
waiting in line sucks!
Well, at least you stay true
to the things you like.
That reminds me, the other day
I went to an amusement park.
I thought I was in line
for one of the attractions,
but I was actually
in line for the restroom.
[KONATA] You're always
supposed to check what you're
lining up
for before you line up!
I was standing
in line for hours.
Oh, you know, when I get
stuck standing in a line,
the person in front of me
ends up buying the last
of the thing I wanted to buy.
Actually,
that happens to me a lot!
You're just unlucky, Tsukasa.
Do you all know what you're
getting for lunch today?
[KONATA] How tragic. Oh well,
I guess curry's good enough.
[KAGAMI] I think I'm
gonna go with ramen.
[TSUKASA] Ooh, me too!
I was craving some miso
ramen today with lots
of corn and seaweed.
That's what I'm gonna get.
You also gonna get
the eclair and the flan pudding?
Only if I have
room for dessert.
You always have
[TSUKASA]
What are you getting?
I think I'd like
to have a sandwich today
with some strawberries.
[KONATA] That totally sounds
like something you'd have.
-[TSUKASA] Yeah.
-[KONATA] Hang on.
Just throwin' this
out there, but isn't
a strawberry sandwich dessert,
or can you even call
something like that lunch?
You do have a point there.
You get picky about
the weirdest things.
Oh, what about the choco cornets
you're always eating?
Wouldn't they be
considered a dessert?
[KONATA] How dare you
question my choco cornets?
Well, now that that's settled,
I've got some bad news
for Miyuki-san.
The line for the sandwiches
is over there.
That's typical of her.
That girl is moe incarnate.
Oh, look, Kona-chan,
you're up next.
I'd like some curry
please, with extra sauce.
[SERVER] You got it!
I admire your cunning!
Hey, I'll take
whatever I can get.
[SERVER] Okay, next?
The soy ramen please,
with sort of firm noodles.
Okay, it'll just take me
a minute.
Sorry about the wait.
Here you go.
I'll go ahead and grab
us some seats, okay, guys?
-Okay, thanks!
-Okay, thanks a lot!
[SERVER]
Okay, folks, who's next?
I'm next, may I please
have the miso ramen?
[SERVER] Oh, I'm sorry,
the person ahead of you
just got the last
of the noodles.
We're all out of
ramen for today.
If you don't mind
having soy flavored ramen,
you can have mine.
I can always get
the kitsune udon.
Thanks sis, you're the best.
[cicadas chirping]
I just thought of something.
[KAGAMI] Hmm?
You get to be the older
sister because
you were the one
to pop out first, right?
That's right.
I'm so glad I get
to be the younger sister!
Okay, why's that?
'Cause its kinda sad
if the older sister is
asking the younger one
for help with homework
or if she's asking to copy it.
[KAGAMI] When it comes to
copying homework, I don't think
any of that matters anyway.
Look, we're twins,
so I don't think there's
any difference
as far as age goes.
Don't worry about it.
Just hurry up
and finish your homework.
Okay!
I wonder how it would be
if I were the older sister
and I was all reliable
and stuff like her.
Oh, please, sis,
could you show me your homework?
Again? Come on, Kagami,
do I even have a choice?
-You gonna be okay over there?
-You're so amazing!
You're spazzin' out.
Ta-da!
New Type has published
my very own postcard!
It's gonna be in the May issue!
"Konata Izumi from Saitama."
Wow, that is pretty cool.
Can't believe they printed it.
Huh? [groans]
I mean awesome, girl, amazing!
It's a once in a lifetime thing!
I know, isn't it?
Now I got another reason
to pick up a copy!
A bunch of copies!
Don't worry,
I'll still be your friend.
This one's 1,260 yen,
and this one's 567.
If I get another book,
I'll get another point.
I'll just pick one of these,
and then I'm good.
No, it's a trap.
That's what they want you to do.
But I'm way too smart to
let 'em do me like that.
Making me buy something
I don't want just so
I get an extra point?
I'm so on to their little game.
Ha ha ha. What do they
think I am, stupid?
There's no way I'm gonna
fall for that old trick.
Whoa!
I totally forgot
volume five was out!
Yes, please, this'll do.
[electronic clicking]
That'll be 2,587 yen, please!
Eh, whatever.
[metal clinking]
-[BOY] They're stuck,
-Oh, I'm so sorry!
Looks like they
wanna stay together, huh?
I always stuff
like that only ever
happened in manga and games.
Looks like they happen
in real life too.
Yeah, you think?
You know what?
Those two totally
triggered flags back there!
Konata, fantasy isn't
reality, it's illusion.
Try not to mix them up, okay?
[ALL]
Lucky Star.
[AKIRA]
Lucky Channel!
Hiya, luckies!
Delivering tons of love
with a dream-colored heart!
I'm your navigator Akira Kogami.
Welcome to Lucky Channel!
Hi there, I'm Minoru Shiraishi,
the assistant!
Wow, it's already
the eighth episode!
Isn't it crazy how
time just flies by?
I heard that!
We should start thinking about
getting some new material
or folks'll start saying
we're stuck in a rut!
What was that?
What am I gonna do,
what am I gonna do?
No, I was thinking about
trying some new stuff is all.
-You said it.
-You know, yeah.
Oh, by the way, when I was
walking around the other day,
someone called me over!
Was it a survey for a day spa?
Oh, come on now, Shiraishi-san,
do you know what you're saying?
Of course you don't
know, see, it was a fan.
But you don't know about fans
because you don't have any!
Right?
Ah! No, I don't have any fans!
No, of course you don't!
You're just an assistant, right?
Keep up the hard work,
assistant! [cackles]
But I do have a couple
of fans, look! You see?
Augh! What the--
What the hell, Edo,
where's my fan letters?
Why you...
Just one freakin' letter?
"Your membership is about
to expire, please respond by"--
This is junk mail
from the video store!
This is a shout out
to all of you guys
sitting in front of the TV!
Please send me some fan mail
or I'm gonna cry!
I want want want
your letters, okay?
[snickering]
Shouldn't we be starting
the show now, Akira-sama?
Don't be so damn conceited.
It'd be easy
to replace you, feel me?
Sorry, ma'am.
Tada! We have
an announcement!
We're gonna be taking
characters from the show
and making super cool
figures out of them!
[MINORU] Akira-sama, the board!
It's upside down!
Oh, ha! You're doing it
on purpose. You're so funny!
Let me tell you guys how it's
gonna work this time around!
Peel, peel, peel.
Don't touch me.
Heh, this is totally weird.
So, here's how it's gonna
work this time around!
Don't touch me.
This damn time around!
Peel, p-peel, peel! Ugh.
Hey! What the hell, you guys?
Hey, what the-- You're blocking
my close-up, Joe!
Get the hell out of my shot!
Get your ass out of the way!
This is all your
fault, isn't it?
[MINORU] No, it's not!
Oh, hi! So about this
figure project thingy,
we're gonna need you
guys to vote on it to see
which character's gonna be
turned into a figure, okay?
We're waiting for your opinions
so don't disappoint us,
you got it? [punches]
[MINORU groans] Make sure you
guys vote for your favorite!
Whoa! It looks like we're
all out of show for today!
I hope we see each
other again next time!
Bye-bye, me.
It's obvious someone
from the main segment
is gonna get this one too.
What am I, some kind of freak,
a friggin' clown?
[MINORU] Nothing has
been decided yet.
Actually, they are making
a figure out of me.
The hell you talkin' about?
Who said you wer--
[clapping]
[TSUKASA]
Miyuki-chan, that was amazing!
[MIYUKI]
I'm sorry it wasn't better.
[KAGAMI] That's a side of
you I never thought I'd see!
[MIYUKI] Oh, please,
you're embarrassing me.
[TSUKASA] Oh! Yuki-chan,
let's sing something together.
[MIYUKI]
I'd love to!
[KAGAMI]
Yeah, go for it guys!
Sing a duet!
[TSUKASA]
What do you wanna sing?
[MIYUKI] Let me see...
[KONATA] While you
decide, I'm gonna rock the mic!
[KAGAMI] You're
gonna sing again?
[KONATA] Yeah, Kagami,
and you should sing more too!
-[techno music]
-[KAGAMI] What's this?
[KONATA] Saiyuki! Masaaki's
Son Goku was the best!
[TSUKASA] Didn't
Shingo-chan play that character?
[KONATA] Yeah, like
the third time they did it.
This is the theme song from
the original 52-episode series
that ran from 1978 to 1980.
Yes, did you feel that?
[KAGAMI]
How old are you?
This is a long intro.
[KONATA] This is the
part where Octogawa-sensei
goes into his awesome narration!
[KAGAMI]
I don't know who that is!
[KONATA]
Oh, here it comes!
Ataaaaaa!
[KAGAMI]
More shouting?
[KONATA singing]
What the-- that's
not even English, I'm out.
[KAGAMI] You got us
all worked up for nothing.
[ANNOUNCER] On the next
episode of "Lucky Star"...
Miyuki here.
When one is attempting
to illustrate the size
of something that
is incredibly large,
they'll use the term
super D class to describe it.
The "D" stands
for the "HMS Dreadnought,"
a battleship of the English Navy
that was activated
into service in 1906.
Now then,
the term super D class,
or super Dreadnought class,
originally referred to anything
that was larger than
the HMS Dreadnought.
Well, that was the original
meaning behind the term.
These days, however, the term
is used mostly in the context
that I described to you earlier.
Next time, "That Feeling."
[ANNOUNCER]
Look forward to it!