[KONATA]
Okay, let's do this!
[MIYUKI]
Sure, let's go!
[TSUKASA]
Grr!
[KAGAMI]
Quit screwin' around and start!
["Motteke! Sailor
Fuku!" Lucky Star Theme]
[groaning softly]
Anyone wanna
tackle this problem?
Shiraishi?
Aww, you made me
do the last one.
Really?
Then, Izumi.
Izumi!
[gasping]
No, I wasn't sleeping.
I didn't say you were,
you have a good nap?
[yawning]
[clicking]
[gasping]
Oh no, I forgot
my English textbook!
Then just go borrow Kagami's.
She already had English
today, didn't she?
Jeez, what's with you?
How could you be so careless?
Yeah, I know.
Check your bag before
coming to school.
Tsukasa forgets stuff
all the time, doesn't she?
All the time.
But now that you mention it,
you never forget stuff
like textbooks, do you?
I have to say, when it
comes to things like that,
I'm pretty reliable.
I never take my textbooks
home, so there's no worries.
Yeah, see what I'm saying?
That's not being
reliable at all.
If you leave your books here,
then you can't study the stuff
you learned in class that day.
But I never study at
home, so what's the point?
Yeah, you take your
books home to study
the night before a
test, blah, blah, blah.
But Kona-chan's really good
at pulling the all nighters.
That's it, I bet
that's the reason
I always forget
to do my homework!
Hello, it's not
that you forget
to do your homework, you
lack the motivation to do it.
Speaking of homework,
can I see today's stuff
for Japanese class?
See what I mean?
I just thought of something.
If you're in the
same class as Miyuki,
why don't you ask
to see her homework?
Yeah, how do I put it?
Miyuki-san's such a good person,
that it just doesn't
feel right asking her.
It feels kinda weird, you know?
You sorta get what I'm saying?
Yeah kind of, that's
a pretty weak excuse,
if you ask me.
Izumi. Izumi?
What, is she late again?
No, stop, hold it!
I'm here, I'm not late!
I'm late, but I'm late cuz
I was helping someone out!
Oh.
It's someone I hang
out with all the time,
but today I couldn't just get up
and leave 'em like that
'cause it's not right!
Kay.
So then he said
no worries I'm cool,
let's disband, but I can't,
cuz if the other five
get what they want,
and that one guy's the only one
who couldn't get it, that sucks,
and I kinda feel guilty, cuz
that's not cool, you know?
I mean when you've been
hangin' out with people
this long you're
supposed to back 'em up.
Yeah, havin' friends is
a good thing, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
So I guess you spent all
night gaming it up online,
is that it?
[springy twang]
Kept playing after
I logged off, huh?
Izumi, Izumi?
What, is she late again?
No, stop, hold it!
I'm here, I'm not late!
I was walking
past the strip mall
on my way here and this
girl bumps into me,
and all of a sudden
she grabs my hand,
and starts running.
She tells me that she
stole a piece of taiyaki
and is on the run!
I'm running and
listening to her,
and I'm thinking she's nuts!
So we're running,
and I'm thinking,
"Why me?"
But she's holding on
to me and I'm stuck,
and we duck into
this cafe to hide
from the owner of
the taiyaki shop.
There's so many places
in that story to nitpick!
But I can't do it!
As a teacher, as a human being.
Oh, I caught a summer cold.
Hey, Izumi, is
something wrong with you?
[Izumi] Yeah, I'm
really sorry, ma'am.
But I need to take
a sick day today.
[KUROI] Haha, you were
up all night gaming, huh?
Used the sick excuse before,
so it ain't gonna work.
No, I really am
sick this time--
[shrill laughter]
[KUROI]
Don't tell me,
"I got a summer cold."
The rainy season's over now,
and the weather's great.
So get out of bed
and get to class!
[hangs up, dial tone]
[springy twang]
She didn't even believe me,
she treated me like I'm the boy
who cried wolf or somethin'.
Well, you reap what you sow.
You feeling any
better today, Kona-chan?
I think my fever's gone down,
but my throat still kinda hurts.
Oh, I know why that is,
it's cause you breathe
through your mouth.
[BOTH]
Huh?
Huh what?
Well yeah, everyone
breathes through their mouth,
but you mostly breathe
through your nose, don't you?
Yeah, but Kona-chan probably
breathes through her mouth
way more than her nose.
Hmm?
I mean, you know how
when you got a throat cold,
it's cuz the cold virus
got in through your mouth?
And if you get a sinus cold,
it's cuz it got in
through your nose.
So you figure anyone
who gets a throat cold
is a mouth-breather cuz
that's how the virus
got in their throat, get it?
[metallic thud]
How about we let Miyuki-san
handle stuff like this?
-Yeah.
-Okay.
It's hot.
And I don't feel
like doin' anything.
[phone rings]
Hello, Kagami.
How about we have
your birthday party
over at my place today?
It's so hot right now
I can't move a muscle.
[KAGAMI]
Aww, that sucks,
I was just baking
some cookies too.
Coming.
Cool, see you in a bit.
Come on in.
Happy birthday, Tsukasa,
and the other one
with the longer hair.
I have a name!
Happy birthday,
Kagami-san and Tsukasa-san,
I hope you like the
flowers we brought.
Ohh, thank you.
Thanks a lot.
You're welcome.
I know it's not much,
but I saw these and
thought you'd like them.
What is it?
Oh please, open it!
[gasping happily]
Oh, they're matching earrings!
I couldn't decide
on what to get,
but I thought those
might look great on you!
You two are gonna flip,
when you see the
presents I got you.
What is it?
Go on, open it.
[crinkling]
What's this?
A brigade leader armband.
I knew you'd love it.
Jeez, Konata,
why do you think I'd
wear something like this?
Aww, come on,
Kagami, just put it on!
I think it'd look
perfect on you.
It's more your style.
[TSUKASA]
Um, what's this?
To Heart?!
It was really expensive, too.
Take care of it
when you wear it.
Hey, stop trying make
both of us cosplay!
Oh, it's not that different
from our school uniforms.
[giggles]
That could be a problem.
Well, if it's too big.
[TSUKASA] I know, and
what if it's stinky too?
You know, it's our birthday.
You think you could ease
up on the cookie-eating?
I can't help it, Tsukasa
makes the best cookies ever.
Oh, glad you like 'em.
Actually, I helped her
bake those this morning.
Yeah, she taught me a lot.
So what's wrong with you?
I dunno, but
suddenly I'm thinkin'
that a few of these cookies
aren't as tasty as some
of the other cookies are.
What was that?!
Is this one of
your cookies, Kagami?
[KAGAMI] Is anyone ready for
a slice of this yummy cake?
That's our Kagami,
a hard worker.
But only on her birthday.
Shut up.
[groaning]
By the way, when
you guys cut the cake,
do you end up arguing about it?
Huh? 'Bout what?
The cake, I mean you're
cutting all those slices.
How do you decide who gets
the strawberry on top?
And which one of you gets to eat
the little chocolate thingy?
You've always loved
eating the chocolate sign,
right, sis?
[giggles]
My slicing's off today.
[robotic cascading]
It's not moe
when she's clumsy.
Wha'd you say?!
Thank you for the food.
[forks clinking]
[disappointed murmuring]
What's wrong?
[internal] My
strawberry's so small.
[chewing quietly]
[KONATA giggling awkwardly]
What's the matter?
Do I have cake on my
face or something?
I think I just found another
charming quality
about Kagami is all.
Stop talking like him, okay?
Can you believe summer
vacation's almost here again?
You're right, it is.
The beach, the pool,
summer festivals.
Anything else that we
absolutely have to do?
Screech.
There's only one festival
that matters during summer:
The War Zone in Ariake!
No matter what, it's
gotta be Comiket!
No, no, no, no no, no no.
That stuff's only for you!
War Zone?
Well, I guess there's
something for everyone to do.
Some people like to visit
their relatives, right?
Good morning, everyone.
Hi, Miyuki.
Hey, what do you do
every summer vacation?
Well, let me see.
There was talk about
vacationing overseas again,
we'll probably do that.
Again? Did you say again?
Damn bourgeois!
Isn't that yogurt?
When you said you started
working at the Cosplay Cafe,
I was kinda surprised.
Don't those places only hire
girls with amazing figures?
Yeah.
I know, my lack of breastiness
is something that's
always really bugged me.
But in this game, they were
saying that a flat chest
was a status symbol, and
how it's considered rare.
[gear grinding]
And when you think about it,
there's probably a demand
for that kind of thing.
I'm quite the
valuable commodity.
I wanna know how
a line from a game
can make you so confident.
Then maybe I'm valuable too?
Finals are coming up,
and here you are playing
games all the time.
You should be
studying, you know?
[groans]
If only you could somehow
channel your passion
for gaming into studying more,
your grades would
be so much better.
[gasps]
If a game could
influence her that much,
maybe if there was a game
that promoted studying,
it would turn her into a genius.
There are those moe quiz games.
What's wrong?
Hasn't there been an awful
lot of teenage crime lately?
I know, and when it happens,
they always ask the
neighbors about it,
and they say something like:
"He always seemed
to be a nice boy,
"he didn't seem to be the
type that could do that."
Well, then that's all the
more reason to be careful.
You can't tell what
someone's capable of,
until they snap.
Although if you ever
did something horrible:
[garbled] "I always
knew deep down,
"she'd do something like this,"
is exactly what
I'd tell everyone.
[gasping]
[drum marching beat]
It's so hot.
[gasping]
It's so hot, I don't feel
like doing anything anymore.
I know what you mean.
It has been hot lately.
Then again, you've always
got one reason or another
for not doing anything, doncha?
[giggles nervously]
[ALL] Lucky Star!
[clock ticking]
[groans]
[phone ringing]
Hello there, Kagami.
Hey, so how's the
studying coming along, huh?
Yeah well, I was just
cleaning up my room.
[KAGAMI]
Huh?
You know how when
you've got somethin'
important you have to do,
but you get this urge
to clean up instead?
[KAGAMI]
Yeah, I get it.
Go study.
All right, time to
get some studying done.
[determined grunt]
[groaning]
[huffs]
I think I'd better
take a 30 minute break.
I'm starting to lose
my concentration.
[clock ticks]
[giggling]
Aww, time's up already?
[groans]
30 more minutes,
just 30 more minutes.
[clock ticks]
Oh.
Oh yeah, it's almost
time for Haruhi to start.
[beeps]
Click.
Talk about cutting corners,
Nagato just sat
there the whole time.
Man, that [beep] guy's not
really doing it for me anymore.
Whoa, that's right guys.
Let the flaming begin.
It's two A.M.
I'd better stop for today.
I'll just sleep a bit
and wake up early.
If I get up at five, I'll
get three hours of sleep.
Then I've got the
whole morning to study.
[fly buzzing]
[twitches]
[alarm rings]
After all of that, I
ended up watching anime,
and reading my manga
all night long.
Oh, that's just like you.
That's one thing
about you Konata,
you've got strange tastes,
when it comes to
anime and manga.
You only read the
stuff guys like,
and you play those dating sims.
Well yeah, it's probably cuz
my dad likes that kinda stuff.
So, go figure, it's
rubbed off on me.
When I was little,
I'd sit next to him,
and watch him read
and play his games.
I get the manga part,
but what kind of father
plays adult-oriented
dating sims with his
daughter sitting there?
Ew.
If both you and your dad
are into that kinda stuff,
what does your mother
think about it all?
Oh, my mom's been gone
for a long time now.
[bell dings, girls gasp]
Yeah, I never told you,
but my mom died when
I was really young.
I'm so sorry.
I guess it means I can
do the household chores
better than anyone,
even you, Kagami.
How can you go off
on a tangent like that,
after you've brought
the mood down?
I bet you're a really
good cook, Tsukasa.
I dunno if I'm all that good,
but I do love to cook.
I wonder how good
Miyuki-san is at cooking.
I bet because she's rich,
she's probably awful
at doing the housework.
Oh, do I know how to cook?
[metallic sparkling]
Actually, I only help
out around the house
every now and then.
So I'm afraid I'm not very
good at chores and things.
I'm ashamed to say it.
[KONATA]
See, told ya.
Yeah, but Miyuki's so
good at everything else,
you can't possibly
compare her to any of us.
She's just being
modest when she says
she's not good at
something, that's all.
Hmm, I guess you're right.
[gasping]
That's not true.
I just thought
of someone else.
How about our teacher?
She says she lives alone,
and I always got
the impression that
she'd be a total slob.
[laughter]
What are you talking about?
These days, anybody can get by,
without knowing how to cook.
You've heard of
convenience stores, right?
[disappointed groaning]
I'm kidding, I do all my chores!
I cook and clean
as good as anyone!
[KAGAMI]
Please don't joke,
when your joke doesn't
sound like a joke!
[guitar twang]
[bell ding]
Tsukasa hasn't given
my dictionary back yet.
Tsukasa?
Sorry, but can I have
my dictionary back?
[door slides]
[giggles bashfully]
I was just cleaning up,
cuz I figured, I would?
You too, huh?
[humming thoughtfully]
Hey, whacha thinkin' about?
They want everybody
who's workin'
at the Cosplay Cafe to
come up with new stuff
for the summer menu.
Really, they make
you guys do that?
Wait, you haven't stopped
studying for the exams, right?
That's it, since it's hot out,
how about we have
somethin' hot and spicy,
like an ultra-spicy ramen?
[groans]
How about coming
up with something
that you'd actually
order in a cafe?
An ultra-spicy parfait!
Do you think you could
stop and think for a second,
before you answer a question?
[gasping]
[water running]
[drum beat]
I can't stand up.
[groaning]
Could somebody tell
my why our school
doesn't have a swimming class?
We have a pool, don't we?
I hate to admit it,
but I'm glad we don't
have a swimming class.
Huh, why is that?
Remember how I told
you I couldn't open
my eyes under water?
I can't swim very
far because of that.
It's so embarrassing.
Your weaknesses are
your greatest strength,
it's so unfair!
[page flips]
That's right, this
summer's ComFest
is just right around the corner!
Oh yeah, the only
reason I went out
and got myself a
job was for ComFest.
A festival, and with
it, so many memories.
Why'd you pull out an old
reference like that one?
Well, when you're excited,
and everyone around
you's getting excited,
don't you get the feeling
you make each other
that much more excited
for the festival?
If you could only
focus a tiny bit
of that passion on
your schoolwork.
[birds singing]
[crickets chirping]
I can't get to sleep.
I guess I'll read a
book, maybe that'll help.
I just bought this, it'll do.
[crickets]
[sighs]
I didn't get any sleep,
and it's already morning.
And now I'm tired and
ready to go to sleep.
Figures.
[train clattering]
Stare.
I know I'm supposed to
turn off my cell phone
when I'm next to
the priority seats,
cuz it's got somethin' to do
with pacemakers and stuff.
Mm hmm.
But I don't get
why we're not allowed
to talk on our phones
anywhere else on the train.
Well isn't it because
when you do that,
you're bothering
everyone around you
with your conversation?
Hmm, I guess.
But aren't trains
filled with people
that talk too loud, even when
they're not on the phone?
I'm talkin' both men and women.
[giggles nervously]
Well yeah, I
guess that's true.
[crickets]
Do you guys do your New
Year's priestess thing
at the shrine during summer too?
Nah, we don't do that
kinda stuff in the summer.
And you know, I
still can't believe
that it's already
that time of year.
I know, what are you eating?
Aren't you supposed
to be on a diet?
[KAGAMI]
Yeah, that.
Well, I guess with all the
studying I've been doing,
I got on the scale yesterday,
and I'd lost a little weight.
So I figure, why not, you know?
Woah, don't tell
me you gave up.
[KONATA]
Good morning.
Good morning, Kona-chan.
Hey, what's the
matter, Kagami?
Konata!
It's my weight again,
I gained it all back
in like the blink of an eye!
That's cuz you
let your guard down,
and ate too many snacks.
Hey, wasn't that a Senryu?
[harp strum]
You're making such
a big deal out of it,
you don't look any different,
if you gain a kilo or two.
Why bother getting
excited or freaked out
about each kilogram anyway?
[sighs]
This is one of the
reasons why girls are so--
Hello, you're supposed
to be a girl too, arencha?
[ALL] Lucky Star.
[rabbit snoring]
Lucky Channel!
Hi Luckies!
Lucky Channel's back,
and I'm so glad to
see you guys again.
So have all of you
been doing well?
I'm Akira Kogami,
and I'll be giving you 120%.
This week I'll be--
Just kidding, I'm
Minoru Shiraishi,
the assistant.
Hey.
Don't you ever cut me off again!
I'm so sorry!
This isn't kid's play,
so learn how to handle yourself.
Like a professional.
Or maybe you don't
want this job anymore.
No, no!
I'm really very sorry.
I promise you, I'll do my best!
Okay, today we've got, ta da!
Really super important news
for all the Lucky
Channel fans out there!
If you picked up the
November issue of
Comptiq, you'll know
all about Akira's
fashion project.
You were supposed to
send me a postcard,
and you did!
A whole lot of postcards!
Uh, you know, I think
there was someone else
involved in that project
with you, wasn't there?
Thank you so much for
sending in your entries!
I am mammoth happy!
I don't think I
know that reference,
is it from the 80s?
Now I'm gonna single-handedly
pick the one idea out
of all the amazing
entries you sent in.
[muttering] This'll do.
Let's see, this is
from a Miss Cherry,
who lives in Saita
City, Saitama.
Akira Fashion Project!
[dramatic music]
On Lucky Star, Kagami-san
looks super cute,
in her pigtails,
why don't you try
putting your hair in
pigtails too, Akira-san?
Oh, pigtails, huh?
[groaning excitedly]
Oh, yeah!
You're right, Cherry!
A girl loves long hair
more than anything!
And if she puts her
hair in pigtails,
maybe if I did that it
would look cute too.
I dunno if that's a good idea.
Your hair's kinda short.
Pigtails'll make you--
[screams]
Yeah well, it's not
like having long hair
is better or anything, right?
Don't sit like that.
Long hair weighs you down.
It takes forever to
shampoo, you know that?
That looks passe
these days anyway.
You guys are always
goin' off about how much
you like the long hair,
but if you think about it,
hell, you don't
know a damn thing.
If you could just
come back to topic?
You don't know how much time,
how much money, how much
effort goes into maintaining--
-Hello?
-Nobody notices.
[cooing]
It's time to say
goodbye, isn't it?
Oh well, if you
guys are wondering
how I'm gonna look in
pigtails, don't worry!
Go to my website
and take a peek!
And don't forget my radio show!
I hope you guys tune in, kay?
Please keep sending
those letters!
Yeah, please look forward
to the next episode.
[crashing]
[AKIRA]
So what's up with the attitude?
[MINORU]
What attitude?
[AKIRA] You kept snapping
at me, what's that?
Did I piss you off when I
corrected you or something?
[MINORU] No! I didn't think
they'd recognize
Nouri peace speak from the 80s!
[AKIRA] Huh?
[MINORU] Eh?
[AKIRA]
Huh.
[MINORU]
Look, I'm really sorry.
Let's just forget
about the whole thing.
[AKIRA] You know--
[MINORU] Yes?
[AKIRA] They're auditioning
for Minoru Shiraishi.
[MINORU] You're kidding?!
[AKIRA] Nope.
[MINORU]
When'd this happen?!
[AKIRA] You should try out.
[MINORU] What are
you talking about?!
[AKIRA]
Break a leg.
[MINORU]
But I'm the real guy!
[AKIRA]
Huh? The real what?
[MINORU]
Whuh?
[TV tubes buzz]
[tapping]
[TSUKASA]
Kona-chan, you're amazing,
you can sing anything!
[KONATA] As long as
it's an anime song.
[MIYUKI] I think
you sing wonderfully,
and in different voices too.
[KONATA] It's the
number one rule,
that when you sing
a song from anime,
you have to do it exactly
like the original singer.
[MIYUKI]
Really?
[KAGAMI]
All right, my turn now.
[TSUKASA] What are
you gonna sing, sis?
[MIYUKI] Her title came
up a little while ago.
But I don't know the song.
[KAGAMI] Miyuki, you
don't know this song?
[MIYUKI]
No.
[KONATA] Practice what
you preach, right Kagami?
[KAGAMI]
Eh.
[TSUKASA]
Oh, I heard this one before.
[KAGAMI] Well yeah, we've
been watching the show together.
[TSUKASA]
Oh, I forgot.
[KAGAMI] I like the movie
better than the series.
[KONATA]
Yeah, whatever, old man!
[TSUKASA singing]
[KONATA]
Hey, she's good.
[TSUKASA] Yeah, out of all
our sisters, she's the best.
[WOMAN]
On the next episode
of Lucky Star:
Hello, it's Miyuki.
Did you know that Golden Week
is a term the motion picture
industry came up with?
Apparently around this time,
there's an increase
in movie-goers.
Next time, The Famous Shooter.
[WOMAN]
Look forward to it.