[MISS KUROI]
Senior year, Class B!
[ALL]
Miss Kuroi!
[KAGAMI]
Yeah, Yeah.
[singing in Japanese]
[KONATA]
Guess what?
I'm raising a pet dog
in a game I'm playing,
and the little guy's so cute
I can't help talking to him.
[GIRLS]
Wow!
Yeah, I know, and even
though it's in a game,
I notice that I talk to
it like it's a real animal,
like all cutesy and stuff.
Yeah, I totally know
what you mean.
When I talk to my goldfish,
my voice gets all high-pitched
and sweet sounding.
I can see talking to dogs
and cats that way, but a fish?
That's something only a lonely,
desperate person would do.
What'd you say?
That sounds like
prejudice, damn you!
I see your face!
Don't you pity me!
Talking about
doggies reminds me
of this question I've had.
There's this one command I
heard where the trainer says,
"Chin, chin," so do you
guys know what that means?
Oh, oh, uh, if I
start explaining it,
we could be here
for quite a while.
Oh, let's just say
the term is Chinese
and leave it at that, shall we?
Okay, all those who just
thought of something X-rated
raise your hands.
It's weird how "Gun [beeping]"
still really popular
with lots and lots of people.
I know, I get [whistle tweets]
when I watch it.
And [beeping] come in lots
of different varieties, too.
You know,
like "V," and "W," and "X."
Yep, I've been watching
it since the beginning
so I know 'em all by heart.
You could say it's
my duty as a fan.
Okay, then, if a show called
"Gun [beeping] Serial Murders"
was on, would you watch it?
Or a show like
"Detective Gun [beeping],"
would you watch that?
Yes, if you really love
"Gun [beeping]," then it's
your [chimes] to
watch those shows.
[chimes]?
Although it's not [rattle]
if you can't refer to it
using a letter.
All this talking about
[beeping] made me realize
something, I know I'm kind
of small for my age and
everything but I'm
[beeping] years older
than [horn honking].
Time sure [whistling],
doesn't it?
[KONATA]
Can you believe that
in two years I'm going to be
the same age as [beeping]?
Isn't that crazy?
[SOUJIRO] Well, you
know, [beeping] a really
[beeping] character even in
the world of "Gun [beeping]."
Same goes for [rattle].
The thing is, you can't compare
your [whistling] to them.
I mean, you're awfully
[crackling] for your age.
Shock! It would have been
better if you said that
I looked [rattle] for my age.
Whatever, you're
still a cutie pie.
[video game noises]
-[doorbell rings]
-[BOTH] Hmm?
Look at what the neighbors
got us from their vacation.
I bet it's a valuable souvenir.
What is it, a vase?
I can't believe how
awesome you turned out!
You're so damn cute,
you're my kind of girl.
It's too hot for hugs,
Dad, and what you just said
sounded really pervy.
[snoring]
Oh, it's morning.
I got so hammered last night,
I figured I'd be passed out
for most of the day.
Oh well, I guess
I'm still young.
[ANCHORMAN] Up next is
the morning news for today,
Monday, July the 2nd.
Wait, what happened to Sunday?
Where'd my weekend go?
Whenever I've got an exam,
I always make it a point to
stay up the night before to
study for it but I don't get
far 'cause I get sleepy.
I asked sis for
advice and she said.
You don't like
scary movies, right?
What if you watch one
before you start studying
and maybe it'll keep
you up for the night.
Remember last time?
You jumped into my
bed and wouldn't leave.
So I watched a horror movie
and I stayed awake all night.
Your sister always knows
what to do, doesn't she?
[TSUKASA]
Yeah, but now when it gets dark
and I hear a noise,
I start thinking
that there's something
sneaking up behind me.
Now it's even harder
for me to concentrate
on studying than before.
Anyway, I haven't slept
too good since then
so now I'm tired in class.
But for someone who claims
she doesn't like horror movies,
you seem to watch a
lot of them regardless.
Believe me, if I had
a choice, I wouldn't.
Come to think of it,
my mother's the same way.
Hey, Miyuki, would you
like to watch this movie
with me tonight?
I'm too scared to
watch it alone.
I heard that people who
scare easily tend to watch lots
of movies of that sort,
perhaps they secretly like it.
No, Yuki-chan, you're wrong.
I really, really hate
horror movies, really!
Do you understand this
problem, Iwasaki-san?
I'm stuck on that one, too,
and I was gonna keep at it.
If I couldn't figure it out,
I was gonna ask Miyuki-san to
help me with it.
Oh, yeah, hey, aren't
we lucky that both of us
know people who are seniors?
They'll totally help
us if we ask 'em.
And that's what
Iwasaki-san and me were
talking about at school today.
[KONATA thinks] No way,
she's got too much faith in me!
[YUI thinks]
She's gonna find out real quick
just how harsh
reality really is!
Hey, Na-san, before
you and Ki got married,
did you guys ever go
and study together?
No, why?
I always see that set up in
games and stuff but if you're
with a boy you like and you
have to study, there's no way
you'd be able to
concentrate on homework.
And if you can't
concentrate, that's when
your mind wanders and
you start to fantasize.
And that's about the time
the withdrawals set in.
Oneichan, could you
show me how to do this part?
I'm sorta slammed right now so
why don't you ask Yui-neisan?
Gotta study, study, study.
Why you little.
Well, I went to a different
school and they never
really taught us
anything like this, so.
Oh, no!
What a lame excuse.
I'm kinda stuck myself.
Do you understand
any of this stuff?
I bet you don't, Oneisan!
You know,if you already
know I don't know,
don't even ask me.
Didn't you see what just
happened with Yutaka?
Maybe I should just call
Miyuki-san and ask her.
I don't wanna bother her though.
Yeah, it's kinda late.
Maybe you can call
her about it tomorrow?
[SOUJIRO thinks] Why don't you
ever come to me with things
like homework and stuff?
You can trust me, I'm your dad!
C'mon, man, give me a shot!
I'll fix you good!
Morning, wakey, wakey!
Even though corporal
punishment in the classroom's
been banned, you
love hitting people.
Not that I'm
complaining or anything.
That's true but I
don't hit just anybody.
If I don't pick my targets
carefully, I could get
into a lot of trouble, if
you know what I'm saying.
[MINORU] Wow, she even
admits it, she's so amazing.
Banning corporal punishment,
what are they thinking?
That's it for today,
see y'all tomorrow!
Hey, Miyuki-san, sorry to
bug you but I don't get any
of the names of these eras.
Could you show me how to
do this problem, Yuki-chan?
[MISS KUROI thinking]
Why are they always asking her?
How come you guys never
ask me about the
stuff you don't get?
Wait up, Ms. Kuroi!
Hey, Izumi, what's up?
Well, I sorta had a
little question for ya.
Sure, ask me anything you want!
That's what I'm here for!
In this game I'm
playing right now,
there's this rare
item in it and--
woah, ma'am, what's wrong?
That's not what I had in mind.
Why's the day after a
typhoon always so darn hot?
It's called typhoob-ikka but I
hope the mom and dad typhoons
leave the kids at
home next time.
[laughs] Nice word play!
Wait, what do you
mean by word play?
You do know that
what you just said was
a play on words, don't you?
[door opens]
Hmm?
Hey, sis?
I hope I'm not bothering you
but I sorta had a question.
Sure, come on in.
What'd you wanna know?
It's about what
happened this morning.
Did Kona-chan say
something that was weird?
'Cause I sorta didn't
see anything wrong
with what she said either.
[KAGAMI thinks] How can you
be as dense as Konata?
We watch the news together!
[humming]
[doorbell rings]
What the hell?
It's like you guys
have bad timing
on purpose or something.
[BASEBALL BROADCASTER]
Pitcher's eyeballing the runner
on second--
Hey, how much longer's the
baseball game gonna be on?
It sorta looks like it's
gonna be running long again.
[KONATA]
Again? jeez!
Now I gotta reset the
timer on the recorder.
Oh man, why can't they
just block off more time
to begin with?
You know, dad?
That's the problem
with pro ball.
The players always drag
out every little move.
I mean, would it kill
anyone to pick up the pace?
'Cause if the players did that,
they might actually be able
to finish a game on
time for once.
[SOUJIRO]
Yeah, well,
I think the pacing is
one of the things people
like about it and besides,
the players need time to
concentrate, so.
Well, have you gotten used
to everything at school yet?
Yeah, but there's lots of
homework so it's kind of hard.
[laughs] You'll live.
Since you're all focusing on
your college entrance exams,
I bet you guys don't have much
homework to do these days.
Huh?
Okay, Konata.
What, I don't know
where she got that.
Man, is it hot out or what?
What are you doing?
Put some clothes
on or something.
What if Yu-chan starts
walking around like that?
C'mon, it's been
really hot lately.
Besides, what's that thing
politicians are doing?
[SOUJIRO]
Cool biz?
Yeah, that!
[SOUJIRO]
No, that's different.
[sighs]
What the heck are you
doing down there?
Just waiting for
someone to text me back.
Don't you hate that?
While I was reading my book,
I missed my station again.
I don't think I'll ever
get sick of your klutziness,
Miyuki-san, it's so cute!
I dunno about cute, sounds
more like a hassle to me.
You gotta be kidding, the
way she gets all embarrassed
about it afterwards, hello, moe!
It's super cute when you got a
couple flaws you can exploit.
Oh yeah, so when you're
at work, you're all,
"Oh no, I tripped, I'm
so terribly sorry, sir!"
or something lame like that?
Kagami, when you did
that thing just now,
you looked pretty stupid.
I was just giving an example!
You're the one who brought
it up in the first place!
Whatever, go on, tell us
about how you act all clumsy
just to score points
with your customers.
No way, not me, you'd
think something like that
would happen in
my cafe but if it did,
the manager'd chew
my butt out for it.
Really, 'cause I thought
you'd be tripping on your feet
every five minutes, saying
it's all moe and stuff.
Uh-uh, it's true that
clumsy girls are cute
and there's tons of moe there
but the fact is it's only fun
to see that stuff happening
in games and anime.
If your always breakin'
stuff in real life,
it'd be irritating.
You otaku types are really
harsh, for geeks that is.
[HOST] So if we have
a contestant with a perfect
score today, [beeping] TV will
be giving one lucky viewer
a month-long trip
across the tundra.
On variety shows and
quiz shows on TV,
you see 'em giving out
all kinds of prizes.
You know, like trips
and lots of cash.
Maybe they get more contestants
when they do it that way.
I bet their ratings go up
a lot when they get someone
really popular to appear
on the show, huh, sis?
I dunno, I guess so.
Ooh, here's a thought.
What if these shows let the
whole audience participate
and gave them
the prizes instead?
Don't you think that
would make their ratings
go up even more?
Maybe but I don't think
a TV game show would be
that straight forward.
Good mornin', ladies.
[KAGAMI]
Hey, you!
Anyway, I was playin'
this game yesterday
and I got to thinking.
Do either of you know who the
school idol at our school is?
Okay, what the heck's
a school idol anyway?
Is it like
a Miss Ryouou or something?
Yeah, I guess that's sorta
what I'm talkin' about.
But if it's anything like how
it's supposed to be in a game,
you get to have
groupies and stuff.
[footsteps]
Oh, man, was that a
grueling day or what?
Whew, that feels good!
Wait, I gotta wake up
early tomorrow.
It's better I stay off the
computer and just hit the sack.
I don't wanna be late for class.
[thinks] I can't believe
I'm making sleep a priority!
Hell, when I was
still in school,
I was too busy
having fun to sleep.
I'm getting old.
[GROUP]
"Lucky Star."
[humming]
Uh, Tamura-san, you've
been making all those faces.
Are you okay?
Yeah, you know how when you
draw, you make the same faces
as the characters
you're drawing?
Yeah, I get it, you were
drawing something, huh?
I didn't know you drew manga,
Tamura-san, that's cool.
Yeah, well, it's
only doujin, so.
What kind of stories
do you like to draw?
Well, just your
typical four panel stuff.
And some romance-y
type manga between
my favorite characters, too.
[thinks]
Tough question.
I bought this lottery
ticket the other day
and I won 3,000 yen with it.
So there I was
thinking how awesome
the rest of my day's gonna be.
Woah, you're so lucky!
But on the way to school, my
bike got a flat and my lunch
exploded all over the sidewalk
so I used some of the money
to fix the flat and the
rest to buy some lunch
from a convenience store.
And that's pretty much
all the money I won.
They say that truth is
stranger than fiction, I guess.
[sighs] Whatever.
I guess in the end it'll
make a good story for a manga
someday so it's all good.
[BOTH think]
She's so tough.
[screams]
[BOTH gasp]
[loud thud]
An artists' drawing
hand is her life. [coughs]
I'd give my life to save it.
[BOTH think]
She's really tough.
Wow, you're super
talented, Tamura-san!
I don't know what's
going on with me.
That drawing's
pretty darn awful.
Oh, but here's a little
something I just finished
that I think rocks super hard.
[loud thud]
Whatever, I shouldn't
expect most people to get
where an artist is coming
from or pick up on all
the subtle details in the lines.
I should know better than that.
Holy crap, I forgot it!
What happened, are you okay?
Oh, it's my favorite
mechanical pencil.
I was drawing yesterday and I
left it home back on my desk.
Wanna borrow mine?
No, man, it's gotta be her,
I'm used to the way she feels.
The way she just flows
across the page, I--
[loud thud]
Yeah, you're right, mechanical
pencils are all the same.
Uh-huh, yes they are.
Yeah, I knew you guys
would react like that.
I totally knew
that, I knew that.
The sucky-ist thing about
it's that I got totally lost
in there, I couldn't get
out for three hours. [gasps]
Is anything wrong, Tamura-san?
How embarrassing!
What are they thinking
dressing like that in public?
[MINAMI]
Is it the coat?
[YUTAKA]
Wow, it's summer
and they're dressed like that.
They must be hot.
This kind of pain's reserved
for the ones who know about it.
Hang on a second, I gotta
send these to someone.
[HOST]
Welcome, ladies.
Wow, it's super crowded.
I'll go put my name
on the sheet.
It was fun, 'cause oneichan
and me stayed up late again
playing a video game.
[HOST] Suzaka-sama,
Suzaka-sama, part of three?
Oh, hey, that's us.
But I didn't hear
them call your name.
That was someone else's.
Any time I have to put
my name on a waiting list,
I write down the name of one
of my favorite characters.
It kinda makes me feel
a little closer to 'em.
Know what I'm saying?
Awesome, you can find
my people everywhere.
Oh, thanks a lot!
If there's one
thing I'd wish for,
I'd wish I could be as
slender and tall as you are.
I think that'd be so cool.
I want you to know, Minami-chan,
that I admire you so
very much and I--
Yutaka.
Well, I'm sure you're not done
growing yet so don't worry.
You never can tell.
Perhaps you'll even be
taller than me someday.
[laughs] You really think so?
Minami-chan.
Minami-chan!
Woah, hold it, stop!
That totally goes against
the laws of nature
and that last shot
is so wrong it's insane
and I need to calm down!
Are you feeling okay,
Tamura-san?
You're looking really pale,
wanna go to the nurse's?
[laughs] I was up all
night drawing my brains out,
trying to make the deadline
for this contest I'm in,
and even though
I didn't get any sleep,
I still made it to
the courier's in time.
It's okay, when I work
really hard on something,
I feel all shiny inside,
like I'm dissolving into
little tiny blobs of light.
[BOTH think]
She's really super tough.
Oh, Tamura-san!
What does "yaoi" mean?
That depends on
which one you mean.
[GROUP]
"Lucky Star."
[AKIRA]
"Lucky Channel"!
Hiya, luckies!
Are you guys ready for the
19th episode of "Lucky Channel"?
We're almost at the
end of the season.
Can you guys believe it?
I'm Akira Kogami, your guide!
And I'm her assistant,
Minoru Shiraishi.
I hope everyone's
having a good day today.
Wow, you look like you're
in a good mood, Akira-sama!
You must have done
something fun last night.
I wonder what it could've been.
Go on, take a guess!
Well, I think I'll
pass, I just ate.
Man, this TV gig's really
getting on my nerves these days.
I'm tellin' ya, after 19
episodes, I'm startin' to feel
like I need a vacation,
do some unwinding.
Maybe soak in a hot spring.
I'd be nice if I can win
something like that trip they
were talking about in
the main segment today.
Hang on, if you want
to win a trip like that,
you're gonna have to become a
contestant on that quiz show
that was playing
in the background.
[sighs]
Vacations are cool, aren't they?
I'd like to go on one!
Traveling through foreign lands.
They say it's good for the
soul, don't ya know? [laughs]
Are you saying
you like to travel?
I'll say I do, I love it!
Traveling's the best
and I should know,
'cause I've done a lot of it!
I climbed to the top of Mount
Takao and I went to Jogashima.
I'm what you might call
the outdoorsy type.
Huh, so your outdoorsy.
Nothing calms your
jangling nerves like
a walk in the woods surrounded
by Mother Nature's splendor.
It's the best in the world!
Sure, Mother Nature, walking
in the woods while you're
jangling your nerves, sounds
like a real blast, man.
Yeah, doesn't it?
Leaving all the noise
of the city behind,
letting nature take
you in her hands,
soothing your mind and body.
Mm-mm-mm, yeah, that Mother
Nature sure does sound hot.
I know, isn't she awesome?
You wanna go for a
walk in the woods?
Are you serious, can I go?
If you're serious, I'll totally
go, I'll go right now, yes!
Then you're going on
Minoru's Mother Nature Tour.
Have fun.
They've got everything you want.
So, where am I going
on tour exactly?
Fuji.
Huh, oh.
Well I've already climbed
a mountain before so, uh--
[giggles] You're not
going up to the mountain.
I want you to go
up to Fuji Forest.
Oh, I get it, the forest, okay.
Fuji Forest.
Me, seriously?
Mm-hmm.
Okay, so once I
get to the forest,
is there anything in
particular I should be--
Go and bring me back some water.
Water?
Yeah, the famous Fuji water!
And I want it straight
from the source.
[screams] Are you kidding?
You can just buy a bottle
of it at the store!
[groans] I like my water fresh!
I'm not going alone,
am I, am I, am I?
Someone's coming with me, right?
It's okay, you'll be fine.
The director and producer
have agreed to sacrifice
themselves along with
you, isn't that nice?
[DIRECTOR]
Let's the lady her water!
Don't get yourselves
killed out there.
Oh no, is that it?
I guess it is, oh well.
Just make sure you
guys tune in next time,
'cause "Lucky Channel's" gonna
have a super special guest
coming by the studio!
See you guys later, okay?
Bye-ni!
Wasn't there an easier
way to get rid of him?
I mean, we could've
just shot him out of a--
[yelling in Japanese]
[singing in Japanese]
On the next episode
of "Lucky Star"...
I'm Nanako!
And I'm Yui-chan!
[NANAKO]
I don't know if you're like me,
but right before summer starts
don't you get all excited
about it, sure you do!
But then before you know
it, the summer's over
and nothing exciting's
happened to you.
[YUI]
Hmm, I guess.
What's so special
about summer anyway?
[NANAKO] Yeah, well, it's
not like you're going to find
true love with anyone
you meet during summer
so whatever, right?
[YUI]
Hmm, yeah, I wouldn't know.
[NANAKO]
Who cares, we're still young!
Let's get out there
and get some!
[YUI]
Yeah, wait, what?
No comment.
Next time,
"Ways to Spend Summer."
[NANAKO]
I'm gonna get me some!