[MISS KUROI]
Senior year, Class B!
[GIRLS]
Miss Kuroi!
[KAGAMI]
Yeah, yeah.
[singing in Japanese]
Good morning, guys, what's up?
Hey, you.
Good morning.
Wow, you remembered to
wear your winter uniform.
Yeah, who'd you
think I am, Tsukasa?
Ahh?
But it's still so darn hot out.
I wish we could stay in our
summer uniforms a little longer.
I wish they'd let us
pick when to switch
'cause it's still cold
when they make us
change back to our
summer uniforms.
Yeah.
I think the point of it is to
get us to change gears mentally.
Otherwise there'd be nothing
but slackers like you guys.
So have you guys
heard the stories about
how parents are
checking their daughters'
cell phones and computers
for sketchy emails?
Right, I've heard about
that happening.
Does your dad check
up on you that way?
Hmmm.
I doubt he'd do
anything like that.
Yeah, I guess not.
Your dad loves you
so much I bet
he'd never do
anything to upset you.
Hmm, yeah, of
course he does, but
don't forget, my dad
uses a computer, too.
And he knows how
embarrassing it is when
someone's been
peeking in to his D: drive.
His D-- forget it.
Man, this summer
was all filled up with
taking classes and
homework and stuff.
The fireworks and Ariake
were the only fun I had.
So you went to
Comiket after all?
Comiket?
Yeah, you know it!
That's the reason why
my wallet's all sad now.
Whenever you go,
you hemorrhage cash.
How much did
you spend this time?
If issues cost
1,000 yen each, then...
[register dings]
somewhere around
40,000 to 50,000 yen.
What the?
You know, you've got really
warped ideas about money.
I hear what you're
sayin' but there's a thing
in this world called
fair market value.
Anything self-published
is bound to be expensive.
I'm not not talking about that!
I'm talking about how you can
even spend that kinda money!
[sighs] What's up
with the weather?
It's September but
it's still so hot out.
Yeah, you're right, it is.
And it feels especially
hot this year doesn't it?
Global warming is
on everybody's mind.
Yu-chan gets heat
stroke real easy
so she usually goes and
hangs out in the living room
or wherever we
got the AC crankin'.
Yeah, Tsukasa does
the exact same thing,
but only because she's lazy.
Ahh!
You know, sometimes me and
dad join her for a snooze.
And we end up lying on the floor
lookin' like the kanji
for the word "small."
Wait, you mean you guys
look like the kanji for "river"?
No, 'cause dad always plops
himself down
between us like this.
That figures, looks
like Yutaka-chan's
gotten used to
living at your place.
[tires squeal]
Yoo-hoo, I'm here
to hang out again!
What's up, Yutaka?
Doin' good?
Oh, hey, oneichan.
Hello, what's your name?
This is my friend,
Minami Iwasaki.
[YUI] Right on, you're
Minami-chan, huh?
Yutaka's told me all about you!
Oneichan!
[YUI laughs]
[MINAMI thinks]
Knowing these two share
the same DNA makes
me a little... envious.
Hmm?
Wow, I guess all those
rumors I heard about
how pretty you are
aren't rumors after all.
You're a little cutie pie, girl.
Want something to drink?
Yeah, beer!
But you can't,
you drove over here.
No, I'm just kidding.
Barley tea please.
[thinks] Of course, one sister
absorbs the traits of the other.
Absorbs.
[clock ticks]
[sighs]
[loud bang]
Woah, it's Yasai Mosai!
Do you know what I can
do to stay awake longer?
I get so sleepy when it's night.
Instead of forcing
yourself to stay up late,
how about getting to bed
early and waking up early?
You'd feel better.
Good idea, sis, I'll try it out.
[clock clicks]
I'll wake up early
tomorrow and do my best.
[birds chirp]
How come I woke up the
same time I always do?
I think I remember
turning something off.
Even if I get up
early I just end up
falling right back to
sleep again out of habit.
You have to want
to wake up early.
Maybe it's better
if I just tried harder
to stay up late
and kept studying.
I seriously doubt you're
gonna get a whole lot done
if you're constantly rubbing
sleep out of your eyes.
I got it, everyone else
gets up early around here,
maybe you could ask
mom to wake you up.
How 'bout it Mom?
Okay, I'll make sure to
wake you up tomorrow morning.
This is totally gonna
work and it's
all thanks to my
super smart sis.
[TSUKASA] Mom, you were
supposed to wake me up!
[MIKI] I did wake you
up, you even answered me.
[TSUKASA]
Wait, I did?
[MIKI]
Don't you remember?
[TSUKASA]
Oooh.
Huh, oh no, Konata
forgot to take her lunch.
Ah, thank you.
It's kinda weird
walking through the halls
of the senior class when
you're just a freshman.
It feels like
everybody's watching me.
Yeah, I know what you mean.
[thinks] Uh-huh, I bet everybody
was checkin' Yui-chan out.
-I mean, just look at her.
-Huh?
It doesn't matter if it's
the senior's hall
or the freshman's.
If you're someplace
you've never been before,
you get this weird
vibe, kinda like
you're the center
of attention or somethin'.
I'm gonna stand out no matter
what 'cause I'm so short,
but I totally feel the pressure
when a bunch
of seniors are staring.
[KONATA] You know
what, I always like it
when I get that kinda attention.
Really? You're lucky.
Yeah, but nobody blinks an eye
when I go walkin' through
the freshman halls.
They don't even realize
I'm older than they are.
Hi, Patty-chan.
Oh, hey, guys, what's up?
Are you headin' off
to work right now?
You know it.
I signed on for way too
many shifts this week.
Are you guys still working
together at the cafe?
Yep, believe it or not, we're
startin' to get pretty popular.
Yeah, the "A" boys get
all moe-moe for us.
Hmm, what the heck's an "A" boy?
It's what you call
boys who look like
they belong in Hakuba,
you know the type.
Although Narimiya-kun wasn't who
I had in mind for that part.
That girl has definitely
gotten used to Japan.
Oh come on, because of that?
[heavy sigh]
Woah, I just had
a really cool idea!
I think I'll finish my bath
first, then I'll sketch it up.
[heavy sigh]
[blows bubbles]
Uh.
Wait, what was it?
This always happens when
I don't jot down my ideas
right away,
and it was so funny!
[sighs] What a day, what
a day. I'm so tired.
[drum beat]
[fast-paced dinging]
[giggles]
[thinks] That sounds
like it could be funny.
I'll sketch it out when
I get up in the morning.
It's so funny!
[birds chirp]
Oh, this sucks.
I wish I wrote it down
instead of being so lazy.
It was such a good idea, too.
What was it?
[sighs and giggles]
Ha!
[moans]
Ah! I woke up this
time, but I still forgot.
Why can't I remember my dreams?
It was such an awesome idea.
[GROUP]
"Lucky Star."
[birds chirp]
Okay, everybody, I'm
leaving it up to you guys
to figure out who's
staying with who.
We're going to
Kyoto and Nara, so I want
you guys to research
all the cool places.
[KONATA] But isn't the
bus gonna be stopping
at all the cool places anyway?
[chuckles] Nah, the
bus is gonna be stopping
at all the typical
touristy spots. Dream on.
[KONATA thinks]
And there goes my comeback.
[phone rings]
Woah!
Iris crashed through here.
About 1,300 years ago, Nara
was the capital of Japan.
But then, in the year
710, the capital was
relocated to Heijo-kyo.
So please sit back,
relax, and enjoy the ride
as I Nara-row down
Nara's history for you.
[register dings]
[MINORU laughs hysterically]
"Nara-row down Nara"!
[KONATA]
Is that supposed to be funny?
Thanks for waiting.
Hmm, if this dude's
the main one,
then the little ones around
him are all the options.
You ever hear of
divine punishment?
[crunches]
[giggles]
[gasps]
[crunches]
[giggles and gasps]
[screams]
[roars]
[crunches]
Aw.
It's really sticky.
Ew, I'm all stinky now, too.
Come on girl, cookie.
Keep it up, shorty.
Please to snap-snap, okay?
Oh, what?
I bet he wants you to take a
picture of him and his buddies.
Oh, uh, okay, uh,
click-click, okay?
Here's where you find out
just how good a person studies.
Yeah, look who's talkin'.
Um, hey sis, do you know
how people from
India say cheese?
Huh, cheese in Hindi.
Uh,
cheese in Hindi?
Ah ha, we're not so
smart after all, are we?
Isn't English understood by the
majority of the
population in India?
That's right, if you say cheese,
they'll know what
you're talking about.
Okay, say cheese, everyone.
[KAGAMI] I heard that
whenever there's a field trip
it's guaranteed that people
are gonna start hookin' up.
That's probably why these things
are so popular with everyone.
Hmm, perhaps the fact that
we're off campus together
creates an atmosphere where we
can feel more open
to such things.
[KAGAMI]
They think, "It's now or never."
It's kind of
embarrassing, but if I don't
have my pillow, it's hard
for me to get to sleep.
It's kind of
embarrassing, but if I don't
have my clock, it's hard
for me to get to sleep.
It's kind of
embarrassing, but if I don't
fire this bad boy up
at least once a day,
I can't get to sleep at night.
[GUIDE] Okay, everyone,
we'll be arriving
at Kiyomizu Temple
any minute now.
Here's something you
might find interesting,
the hill leading up to the
temple is called Sannen-zaka.
And if you trip and fall here,
it's said you'll die in
three years time.
The Sannen-zaka becomes
the Zannen-zaka, get it?
-[register dings]
-[MINORU laughs]
[KONATA]
What if you die laughing?
Okay, people, we're
gonna split up
into groups and go look around.
Have fun, but be
careful of the traffic.
We're gonna meet
up at 12:30 in front of
Chionin Temple, so make
sure you're on time.
Or be late and when we get back
you'll have a 20 page
report waiting for you.
[KAGAMI]
I don't think we should.
Hey, come on guys,
let's give it a shot.
[moans and groans]
I wonder if this is as
heavy as Dragon Slayer.
[ALL]
Woah!
[MIYUKI]
It's so high up.
They say do it like your
willing to jump off the
Kiyomizu stage, so
does that mean
that you shouldn't worry
about the consequences?
'Cause if you really jumped
off this thing you'd die.
Kagami, you're
way too realistic.
[TSUKASA]
Oh look, it's a god of romance.
[MIYUKI]
Apparently this spot is
famous for bringing
lovers together.
[KONATA]
Yeah, I can see why.
[MIYUKI] Look, they're
selling love fortunes!
Hey, let's all pick one.
[KONATA]
Yeah, come on, let's do it.
Darn it, I can't see
anything through the wrapper.
I think they do that on purpose.
This one!
Yes, a great blessing!
Good for you, Kona-chan,
that's awesome.
Oh, mine just says fortunate.
A fortunate fortune's
good enough.
I wonder what mine's gonna be.
What the heck is
a half blessing?
Maybe it means that
you're half-blessed.
Or maybe it means
you're half-cursed.
Nobody takes these love
fortunes seriously anyway.
[TSUKASA]
Oh, how cute!
Ah, you picked a good one.
I don't know, Kagami,
that's more your style.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Well, I guess I will
buy this little guy.
[KONATA]
Don't forget this, nom-nom-nom.
[KAGAMI] I'm not buying that.
[KONATA]
How about this flavor?
No!
Watch out, you're gonna trip.
[ALL]
Hm.
[KONATA] This one
says, "Konata's my wife."
'Kay, if y'all are
ready, we'll get going.
And when we get back to the
hotel, we can all have lunch.
Buckle up guys, we're off.
Ready when you are.
And, I heard Koizumi's
song was sung the way IZAM--
ah, hey, Teach,
someone's chasing us!
[NANAKO]
What?
This is just like what
happened to me in Hokkaido!
Hey, sing "Maetel" for me!
That idiot's gonna give
me 50 pages for this.
Hey, driver, could you please
stop the bus for a second?
Later.
-Hmm?
-[bell chimes]
[gasps]
[giggles]
[BOY]
Yeah, right, hurry up.
[KONATA]
How come Kinkaku temple is gold,
but Ginkaku temple isn't silver?
Apparently they wanted
it to be mentioned
right along with
Kinkaku, so they
named it "Gin"
to complement "Kin."
It was never actually meant
to be a silver temple.
I wonder if it's
anything like how
they got Ruby and
Sapphire Pokemon.
[thinks]
Didn't she hear me?
Nice shot.
I forgot to tell you our
shrine was in the news.
Can you believe we
only have one day left?
And it's our day off, so
we're gonna have lots of fun.
Get ready, 'cause the real
field trip begins tomorrow!
We're off to the Holy Land!
[KAGAMI]
Yeah.
Huh?
[busy traffic]
[KAGAMI]
Your note said in front of
the hotel so I
figured this was okay.
[BOY]
I, I hope you
weren't waiting too long.
[KAGAMI] So, what'd you
want to talk to me about?
Well, I, I don't know
how to say this,
but I...
[car horn blows]
I was wondering if I
could have that doll.
You want a doll?
Yeah, you know, it's
the one that you bought
back at that shop
in Kiyomizu temple.
The little Yatsuhashi doll.
[KAGAMI]
Yatsuhashi-kun?
Right, that's him!
I'd love that little guy
and I really want one but--
but I was afraid of
what the guys would say
if they saw me buy it,
so can I have yours?
Please!
Oh, sure.
Thanks a lot, Hiiragi!
I owe you one, man, ha-ha!
Don't tell anyone
about this, 'kay?
Later.
It won't open.
When the steam inside the bowl
cools down it creates a vacuum.
You just give the edge of
the lid a little squeeze
to let some air in and
voila, the lid comes off.
Oh.
Okay.
Wha!
I'm sorry!
Uh-huh, she's showin' off again.
I figured out the
directions to get there.
And you're sure it's okay to go?
Oh, yeah, besides, we're just
looking at the building
from the street.
I don't see why we have to go
to all this trouble just
'cause we're in Kyoto.
Tisk, tisk, tisk.
You still don't get the
adventur-ious ways of the otaku.
And I don't ever wanna get it.
[train slowly chugs]
There's nothing even here.
That's a good thing, 'cause they
need to concentrate
on their work.
[camera shutters]
Their building looks
pretty normal.
It's perfect 'cause they keep
their focus on a
small number of titles.
Did you have to come all the
way to Kyoto to buy that stuff?
No, that's embarrassing!
[KONATA] Come on, it'll be
an awesome memory of today.
[TSUKASA] Yeah sis, I
want a picture with you.
[MIYUKI]
She's right, it'll be fun.
[camera shutters]
This is cool 'cause
we got it in Kyoto.
But there's nothing
Kyoto about it.
[crow caws]
[KAGAMI] Yeah,
we made it back safe and sound,
pretty fast too.
Tsukasa went right
to sleep though.
[KONATA]
I thought you'd be in bed too.
Ya know, sulking or something.
What makes you think I've
got anything to sulk about?
Did you put that picture
we took anywhere special?
[KAGAMI]
No, it's totally embarrassing.
Totally embarrassing.
[yawns]
I worked my butt off this week,
and now that the
class field trip's over
I got time to do some relaxing.
I'll just fire up my
computer and spend
the weekend playin'
games 'til my eyes bleed.
[sniffles]
[GROUP]
"Lucky Star."
[AKIRA]
"Lucky Channel"!
Hiya, Luckies!
"Lucky Channel's" filling
up your lives with
another episode!
And I'm your
navigator, Akira Kogami.
And I'm her assistant,
Daisuke Ono, at your service.
Can you believe it's
our 21st episode?
That's true, we're getting
close to the final episode.
So without further ado,
our segment today is called
"This Week's Maggare."
[bang]
Ugh! Is that...?
I brought back your water.
Sniff, sniff.
Blah!
What the hell is this?
It's warm, I'm not
drinking that piss!
I'd rather get something
from a vending machine.
Ahhh!
Do not mess with me!
Come here, you rotten--
I've been takin'
your crap for too long! No more!
You think everything's
about you, don't ya?
[loud crash]
[AKIRA]
Mi-- Minoru!
Well, today it's my turn, missy!
You got any idea what it's
like for me workin' part-time
in CoCo Ichi, then coming
here to do this thing?
Hell, least I make more there
than I do as a voice actor.
I've been workin' there so
long they wanna promote me.
Before I come here to kiss
your ass, I'm fryin' cutlets.
Well, maybe that's
what you should
be doing instead of acting.
You son of a-- all right,
Ono, get out of my chair!
That's my spot and I
want it back right now.
I'm sorry, didn't
anyone tell you?
The producer and director
said you were out.
Ahh!
Those guys didn't
even give me a chance.
Well, I'll show them,
I'm a late bloomer!
I bet I could turn into a
star [rattle] if I wanted!
You think you could, huh?
Someone like you?
Wha, how dare you mock me.
I don't have to take this crap.
Not from [rattle] and
not from [rattle, tweet]!
-[sighs]
-Fine, I quit.
I'm quitting this desk!
Ahh!
-"Luck Channel" my ass!
-[MEN shout]
Get the hell off of me!
What, you see
something that you like?
You like that "Misoji Misaki"
junk? You think it's funny?
Oh, I'm gonna be 30 soon, man.
Yeah, take it.
[maniacally laughs]
I see you standing there.
Come here you!
[MAN]
Welcome to Idaho!
[laughter]
[BOTH speaking Japanese]
[MAN singing in Japanese]
[WOMAN speaks]
[DAISUKE] On the next
episode of "Lucky Star"...
[AKIRA]
Akira Kogami here!
[DAISUKE]
Daisuke Ono here.
[BOTH imitating animals]
[AKIRA] Okay,
enough with the animal talk.
[DAISUKE]
Oh, those were animals?
[AKIRA]
Next time, "The Yonder Here."
[DAISUKE] I can cross
the finish line, right?
[AKIRA imitates animal]
[DAISUKE]
Ramen set!