[MISS KUROI]
Senior year, Class B!
[GIRLS]
Miss Kuroi!
[KAGAMI]
Yeah, yeah.
[singing in Japanese]
[KONATA]
Thanks for that awesome meal.
You got it, I should take
you guys out more often.
That was really, real good.
Yeah, I know.
I get happy inside when the eggs
are yummy like that.
-Ah!
-[GIRLS] Huh?
Gas is two yen more today
than it was yesterday.
I should have filled up
when I had the chance.
[KONATA thinks] Why do
people who are generous
with their money care about gas
prices going up a yen or two?
So, you know that
book I let you borrow
the other day?
I heard they're turning
it into a game now.
What do you think about that?
Geez, Kagami, that's old news.
I went and pre-ordered
the limited edition
the second they announced it.
Then I bought the box
set of the anime
and a bunch of
other related stuff.
[KAGAMI] Wow, you got
more hooked than me.
If someone recommends something,
the person they recommend it to
usually becomes a
bigger fan than
the person doing
the recommending.
That's how Yui-neisan
bought her car.
No way.
Yup, right after I
loaned her a manga
with a car racing theme.
When I found out,
I was like, "Whoa."
Having a hobby can
be a scary thing.
I guess last night
makes three in a row, huh?
Yeah, talk about
a miracle, right?
If they keep up
this winning streak--
What's she talking about?
I think she's talking
about professional baseball.
Apparently she's a fan.
And speaking of baseball,
I seem recall that the
famous poet, Shiki Masaoka,
was quite fond of it.
In fact, I heard he played
on the team as catcher
until tuberculosis
forced him to stop.
He loved the game
so much he took
his childhood
nickname of Noboru
and changed it to "No-boru"
which means "no ball."
Anyway, you said
Japan Series just now
and I realized something.
In Major League Baseball,
don't they call the winning
team world champions?
Yeah, well that's
something that only applies
to North American teams.
I mean, if they wanna start
talking world anything,
they should come
over here and beat
our team sometime, you know.
She's really into
baseball, isn't she?
It was totally stinky.
It was, wasn't it?
Oh, hey, I was looking
all over for you guys.
Hey, Konata.
Can either of you show me how
to do this problem?
I can't believe you're
asking about your studies.
Sure you don't
wanna just copy it?
You know, looking
at these problems,
some of them
look very difficult.
Huh?
Oh, yeah, that's 'cause they're
for this quiz game I'm
playing at the arcade.
I'm not too good at
figuring out basic
academic questions.
Oh, boy, here we go again.
Maybe you should
try studying some time.
Entrance exams are
right around the corner.
[laughs] This is the way I am
when I'm at school,
but at the arcade
they call me a sage.
Well then, go enroll yourself
in that whatever
academy game of yours.
I wish I got more
sleep last night.
Playing games all night, huh?
Hey, Miyuki-san,
is it true that
you always go to sleep by 11:00?
Yes.
That's way too early.
Whoa!
Oh, I get it.
That's what flashed
in my head when
I was looking at Miyuki-san,
but you get lots of sleep
and you're still teeny-tiny.
Oh, can you believe
she said that to me?
Like I needed that.
[phone rings]
Hello, is this the
Iwasaki residence?
Sorry to call so late,
my name's Yutaka Kobayakawa.
I'd like to speak
with Minami-chan.
Oh, she's in bed already?
[thinks] Does she always
go to sleep this early?
♪ Pittan ♪
♪ La, la, mojipittan. ♪
Okay, that sounds like
a happy little song.
[KAGAMI]
Oh, yeah, absolutely.
No, it's okay.
Uh-huh,
right, I'll make sure my
father knows about it.
I'll tell him right after
the ground-breaking
ceremony, okay?
Yes, right after.
Oh, no, it's nothing
like that, really.
Besides, I'm not even
old enough yet,
so there's no way he'd let me.
Well, that's not how it is,
but thanks for saying so.
Okay, I'll let my dad know.
Okay, bye.
-You're funny.
-Hmm?
They can't see those
gestures you're making.
I know, I know, I can't help it.
So, what?
Whenever I'm on the
phone talking to someone,
I have to stop playing my game
'cause I can't concentrate
on the conversation.
But then my other hand
starts getting lonely
'cause it's got nothing to do.
[KAGAMI]
Yeah, I know what you mean.
[KONATA] Anyway, I was on
the phone the other day,
cleaning the floor with
one of those roller thingys
that picks up lint and stuff,
and I just kept
rolling and rolling.
[KAGAMI] And isn't it weird how
if you're doing something
like that or if
you're doodling,
you just keep doing
it over and over?
[KONATA]
Yeah, I guess so.
But the second you
get off the phone,
you lose your
motivation to keep cleaning.
And then you look around
and you get all sad,
'cause the floor's only
clean where you were sitting
and rollering.
You could just keep rollering.
My passion to keep cleaning
ends with the conversation.
So you just give up.
That guy's super
stinky, isn't he?
It's fine once in a while but--
Ha, ha, look, it's a pocky,
get it?
Come on, we used
to do that back
in elementary school.
Seriously, that's a little
kid thing you're doing there.
Ah, cute.
Anyway, do you guys
remember some of the stuff
you used to do
when you were young?
Like when you'd stir up
your yogurt and yell,
"Bread factory."
"Bread factory"?
-Yeah, didn't you?
-Hm-mmm.
So, yeah,
"bread factory," huh?
Go on, say it,
come on, don't be shy.
Shut up, okay!
You know that game you
borrowed a while ago?
I need it back
'cause someone else
wants to play it now.
Is that someone someone
Shorty McBlue-Hair?
Yup, actually, I loaned
a couple games to her too.
I should probably
get those back.
You're something else,
Hiiragi, you know that?
What do you mean?
I think it's cool you
remember that stuff.
The other day, I found
some games I borrowed
from someone, but
now I can't remember
who it was.
[KAGAMI]
You're kidding.
And there's a couple
of games I loaned out
but I can't remember
who's got 'em.
Sounds pretty careless.
Nuh-uh, it's a universal truth.
In fact, they call it
the law of forgetting
the lender or something.
You made that up.
[phone rings]
Hello, this is Kagami.
[MISAO]
Hey, Hiiragi, it's me, Misao.
Oh, hey, how's it going?
[MISAO]
Oh!
Dammit, I dropped it.
What the heck
are you doing,
you okay?
[MISAO] Huh? Oh, yeah,
I'm fine, no worries.
So, what's up, why'd you call?
[MISAO]
Oh, yeah,
why did I call you?
How should I know?
[MISAO] It was something
really important too.
Then don't forget it.
I just looked at the
winning numbers
for the autumn jumbo lottery,
but I didn't win.
Guess getting the winning
ticket's pretty rare.
I sent in a ton of
postcards for something,
and I didn't win
anything either.
I guess it sucks for
both of us, huh?
But if it's this hard to win,
maybe its because the people
who run these lotteries
and giveaways are cheating
and don't want anyone to win.
It isn't nice to say
things like that
about people, Konata.
[thinks]
I can't do this.
I should go to sleep.
I better go to the
bathroom first.
They say I talk to
myself too much,
but that doesn't matter at all.
Why did saying a dumb
joke like that wake me up?
I was so sleepy before.
Oh, I'm done.
I don't have to use the bathroom
so I better hop into
bed while I'm sleepy.
Cold!
I was so sleepy too.
Why does my futon
have to be so cold
when I get in?
It totally woke me up.
Maybe 'cause it's warm tonight
I'll get to sleep faster.
Now my feet are hot and
I can't get to sleep.
Why, why?
Does this stuff only
happen to me?
[GROUP]
Lucky Star.
Roasted sweet potatoes
taste the best
this time of year.
Yeah, but you know, Kagami--
I already know what
you're gonna say,
so don't say it, all right?
Here, you want some?
Thanks but no thanks,
that stuff makes you fat.
And she says it anyway.
Look, I couldn't help it, okay.
I made eye contact
with the vendor.
I mean, you can't
just walk away
without buying
anything after that.
He looked at me like I was
gonna hurt his feelings
if I didn't buy something.
Yeah, I know exactly
what you mean.
At Comiket, it's hard
to put the book down
after eye contact.
No one understands
what you're talking about
and you don't really
care, do you?
What do you mean?
That's what it's like
when you're checking
out the tables in
the artist alley.
If you pick up a
book and the seller's
standing right in front of you,
you feel bad about
going to another table
without buying it.
But in the end you
don't buy it, do you?
They're turning a
lot a light novels
into anime lately, aren't they?
Yeah, I noticed.
The one I let you
borrow the other day
has been turned into an
anime three times so far.
They're also gonna
release a new volume soon.
Yeah, I saw the
anime version of it,
but I still haven't gotten
around to the book yet.
All those words
kinda wear me out.
Here we go again.
Look, those games you
play have way more words
in them, don't they?
Yeah, I guess so.
But wouldn't it be
really awesome
if they released all those
books as dating sims?
Now, that's what
I'm talking about.
Hey!
Yeah, I know.
Anyway, I wonder when
season four is gonna start.
[KAGAMI]
Wait, what?
Is that like product
placement or something?
Hey, Yu-chan,
you okay over there?
You need some help?
It's this lid.
Every time I try to close it
it ends up crooked.
Oh, it's okay.
It's no big deal.
This kind of stuff
happens to everybody.
But I keep doing it.
Here you go.
I think it's cute how
you and Miyuki-san
have the whole
clumsy thing going on.
You're so awesome, oneichan,
thanks a bunch for
helping me out.
Oh, no, what do I do?
It won't open.
Uh, oh, my bad.
I'm always doing
stuff like that.
I guess I don't know
my own strength.
Is that bag giving you trouble?
Come on, hand it over.
Thanks, oneichan,
you're the best.
Hey, what the--
open!
Rotten bag.
Why don't you try tearing from
the jaggedy edge of the bag?
Hang on, I'm gonna open
this thing up proper or else!
Fire.
Hey, oneichan,
maybe you should use a
pair of scissors on it.
No!
If I use scissors, it'd be like
I let this thing beat
me or something!
Is that a mosquito?
Yup.
Even if it hasn't
launched a full on attack,
it pisses me off just knowing
it's around here somewhere.
But now that I know it's here,
I'm gonna make sure
it goes down hard.
Look out, my hunter
instinct's about to kick in.
Hey, Dad, wanna know
what I was just thinking?
If Yu-chan was asked out
by a guy from her class
and I was asked out by
a guy from my class,
does that mean those guys
have lolita complexes?
Oh, boy.
I guess if the guy's in
the same grade as you,
it's safe to say
he doesn't have one.
Then again, both
you girls look younger
than you really are,
so I guess there's that.
Hmm. If a girl's 30 years old,
but she looks like she's
in elementary school,
if that's the case,
you could say the
guy prefers older women.
That's a good question, hun.
I don't know if there's an
easy answer for it, though.
It's so cool I can
ask you stuff like that.
If I ask Kagami, she'd
say something like,
"I don't care."
How about you, Dad,
-are you like that?
-Hmm?
Well, you loved Mom and
she looked young,
and I know you love
having me for a daughter.
Does that mean you
have a lolita complex?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
that's not exactly what
your old man's about.
I also have a lolita complex
is a better way of putting it.
I mean, sure I like young girls,
but I also like normal girls,
I don't discriminate.
Either way, that's
still pretty creepy, Dad.
Look, you've always been
super clingy with me,
but I was wondering
if I was a boy
instead of a girl,
would you still be
all clingy with me?
Yeah, sure, of course I would.
I totally get where
you're coming from.
I bet you're glad I
turned out to be a girl.
Yeah, I guess.
Hey, Yu-chan, I know you
wanted to take a bath,
so how about you go first, okay?
[YUTAKA]
Thanks, I won't take long.
[KONATA thinks] He's feeling
weird about her hearing this.
-Hey, Dad, you know what?
-Hmm?
I've been thinking about Mom,
how she knew you all her life
and how she was
petite and stuff,
she was kinda like a
character in a dating sim.
When she was a
little kid, Kanata sure
was a cutie pie.
I know you were always head
over heels in love with her,
but I was wondering,
why did she wanna marry you?
Well, I made her feel guilty.
I told her it was
her fault I turned into
a dating sim-loving maniac
'cause she always ignored me.
I'm being serious, Dad.
But it's the truth.
You guilted her
into marrying you?
No, of course not,
I'm kidding, honey,
you know that.
But when you were
born, your mom and me
were the happiest
people in the world.
Her little mole
looks just like yours.
[SOUJIRO] Yeah, but she's
got your eyes, Kanata,
no doubt about it.
She's our daughter.
I'm worried, though.
I hope she doesn't
grow up to be like
either of us.
I don't want her
to be short like me
or a raving geek like you.
Thanks a lot, honey.
What got your thinking about
your mom all of a sudden?
Well, I guess
I just don't know
all that much
about her, that's all.
Konata,
are you lonely 'cause
your mother's not around?
No, not really.
I mean, Yu-chan's here now
and you can be such a spaz,
it's almost like having
two people around.
I guess.
[thinks]
You see her, Kanata,
she turned out
pretty good, hasn't she?
She might not be as
normal as you wanted,
but she's a good girl.
-Hey, Konata?
-Hmm?
You gotta promise me
something, honey bunny,
don't die before I do, okay?
Okay, I wasn't really
planning on it or anything.
Thanks, kid.
Kanata was really young
when she passed away.
She was laughing and
talking about how happy
she was right up to the end,
I get sad sometimes
thinking about her.
But when my time comes,
I hope I go out like that.
What are you
talking about, Dad?
You wanna die laughing?
Mmm, I wanna get moed to death.
Come on, be serious, Dad,
or you're never
gonna die a proper death.
[laughs]
I'm kidding.
Anyway, I bought a new
camera for work today.
You wanna help me test it out?
[KANATA]
Ah.
It's been so long
since I was here.
[KONATA]
No, Dad, stop.
[KANATA thinking]
I wonder what they're up to.
Sounds like they're having fun.
[SOUJIRO]
Say cheese!
[KONATA]
Dad, you said... [groans]
Cool, get ready for another.
Come on, dad, you
got enough shots
and you're hanging all over me.
Aw, come on, honey,
what's the big deal?
I just wanna get
a few pictures of us
with my new camera.
I thought you said
you got it for work.
Aw, come on, don't--
[KANATA thinking]
You're the same as always.
You still like making
people do everything
you wanna do,
even if they don't.
Why are you being
so mean to me, Konata?
-Hyah!
-Whoa!
[chuckles]
[thinking]
He hasn't changed a bit, has he?
You know something,
whenever I hug you,
you feel just like
how Kanata felt,
and I really like it.
[BOTH think]
You shouldn't say
creepy things like that, ever!
[KONATA] I bet Mom had
her hands full with you.
[SOUJIRO]
What do you mean?
[KANATA thinks]
Yeah, sort of.
But your dad's a good person,
so listen to what he says, okay?
Oh, you know that
game you were playing
the other day?
After you figure it out,
you think you could tell
me how to finish it?
Sure, you got it.
That thing is way
harder than I thought
it was gonna be.
[thinks] It's nice to see that
they play games together.
I guess they're doing
okay after all.
I can't get to the sex
scene of this one character--
[KANATA]
Whoa!
What kind of
games are you playing
with our daughter anyway?
Oh, boy, I hope she's okay.
You better not be teaching
her anything bad, So-kun.
Hey,
why do you think Mom
chose to marry you anyway?
[both] Huh?
[KONATA]
I mean, you're a pervy old geek
with a lolita complex,
why would anyone pick you?
[BOTH]
I can't believe you said that.
I think pervy old geek
is a little bit harsh.
[KANATA]
Super harsh.
Anyway, let's get
back to your mom.
[thinks]
She's right, though.
You were always like this.
And sometimes I almost forget
why you were the one...
And I was a loser.
...I wanted to be with.
There was one thing I
was absolutely sure of.
[KANATA]
Huh?
[KONATA]
Why'd you stop?
What was it?
What were you so sure of?
Hmm?
I was sure that no one
else could ever love Kanata
as much as I did.
[gasps]
Oh,
there it is.
Yeah, that's it.
You can't beat that.
[KANATA]
He accepts all the good in me,
along with all the bad.
He shares everything with me,
the good,
and the bad.
I felt so safe and
happy with you.
It was the only place
I ever felt so safe and happy.
Know what I mean?
[laughs]
Since we're in such
a good mood now,
I think this calls
for a picture.
[KANATA]
I feel kind of sad I can't
be there with the
two of you right now.
Well, yeah.
Geez, Dad, that camera's
not for work, is it?
Man.
[SOUJIRO]
What?
I'm just trying to
get used to it.
I don't wanna be
figuring this out
when I'm on assignment.
[KANATA]
But,
you and Konata are
always with me.
And as long as the
two of you keep
me alive inside your hearts,
we'll always be together.
Look, it's flashing,
it's flashing.
[KANATA]
You gave me so much happiness.
-May your lives be blessed...
-Here it comes!
...with as much joy as mine was.
Cheese.
[KANATA giggles]
I wonder what they'll say.
Ah! Dad, look at
-this picture!
-Hmm?
Ah!
Whose shadow is that
in the background?
I think it's a ghost.
[KANATA]
Huh, what?
Okay, I'm all done.
-[BOTH] Yu-chan!
-[KANATA] Wait!
[KONATA]
Look at this picture!
[YUTAKA]
What-- what's wrong?
[KONATA]
We gotta delete it,
it's cursed.
Quick delete it!
[KANATA]
No, stop, don't delete it!
[SOUJIRO]
No deleting it won't work,
we have to burn
it in a holy bonfire!
[KANATA]
Don't you dare burn that camera!
After talking to her
a bit more and stuff,
I can see she's not the person
I thought she was.
But Minamin is still
pretty darn scary.
She's not scary, she's sweet.
Oh, look there she is.
Hi, Minami-chan.
Hi, Yutaka.
[HIYORI thinks]
Wow, those two sure are close.
Yeah, close.
Yutaka, your tie is crooked.
Oh, onee-sama.
[HIYORI thinks] Ah!
I'm fantasizing
about my friends again.
Oh, God, I'm all pent up!
[BOTH]
Hmm?
[GROUP]
"Lucky Star."
[DIRECTOR] In three,
two, one, we're live.
[PRODUCER]
Well, where are they?
What do you mean they're gone?
Where the hell are they?
Call their managers!
Whatever, they're
all getting fired.
Never liked that
stupid show anyway.
[DIRECTOR]
We're live.
[PRODUCER] I knew something
like this would happen.
[DIRECTOR]
Hey!
[PRODUCER] You know
I turned this gig down.
Yeah, turned it down.
But I had to do it anyway.
Politics, man,
gotta be grown up about it.
[DIRECTOR]
Hey!
We're rolling.
[PRODUCER]
Huh, what's rolling?
Me, you, the Earth?
[laughs]
[DIRECTOR]
No, we're rolling!
The camera's rolling!
[PRODUCER]
Holy crap!
Cut, cut!
[speaking Japanese]
One, two, three, four.
-[singing in Japanese]
-[whistle tweets]
-[WOMAN speaks Japanese]
-[laughter]
[man speaks Japanese]
[KANATA] On the next
episode of Lucky Star.
[SOUJIRO]
Soujiro here.
[KANATA]
Kanata here.
Well, So-kun,
I better get going.
-[SOUJIRO] You're leaving now?
-Mm-hmm.
[SOUJIRO]
Take me with you.
I know I can't separate
my spirit from my body,
but I can learn.
[KANATA]
So-kun, if you're going to talk
about anime and
manga, I'm leaving.
Bye.
[SOUJIRO]
No, Kanata!
Next time, "Delicate Line."
[KANATA]
So-kun, I can't fly well
in all this turbulence!
[SOUJIRO]
Oh, brother.