[KONATA]
Okay, let's do this!
-[MIYUKI] Sure, let's go.
-[TSUKASA] Grr!
[KAGAMI]
Quit screwin' around and start!
[singing in Japanese]
[chattering]
♪ Miyuki-san! ♪
Are you gonna be doing
anything fun on New Year's Eve?
Oh, why do you ask?
There's a super cool festival
going on.
Want to come with me?
What do you say?
A festival for the new year?
That does sound
like a lot of fun.
[chuckles]
Oh yeah, it's gonna be fun.
Oh, I wonder if it's anything
like the Snow Festival.
Unfortunately, I'm going
to visit with my family.
-Ah, perfect timing.
-[groans]
I couldn't help but overhear,
but didn't I get the same invite
from you last summer?
Did you, Kagami-san?
Here's a translation
of Konata's jibber-jabber.
She wants you
to run around and buy stuff
at that Comiket thing.
When I went this past
summer, it blew my mind.
I wasn't lying, though.
I mean, a festival's
a festival, right?
Besides, going alone is no fun.
It's a lot of work.
[phone rings]
[KONATA on phone]
Hello? Izumi residence.
Hey, what's up?
I was just doing
my New Years cards,
and I wasn't sure if you
were still in mourning.
I didn't get a decline note
from you yet.
Hm? We're not in mourning.
What made you think that?
[KAGAMI]
What are you talking about?
You took a couple days
off from school this year
'cause you were
in mourning, weren't you?
[chuckles] Oh, that.
Yeah, I remember.
We're doing much better now.
I cannot believe you'd
use such a cheap trick!
[SOJIRO]
Shiny, happy.
I'm kind of right in the middle
of our big
house cleaning now, so--
[KAGAMI]
Yeah, yeah, I got it.
I'd hate to keep you away
from all that dusting
you got going on.
-But--
-[KAGAMI] Later!
-Yeah.
-[hangs up]
[dial tone beeps]
[sighs]
This sucks.
Ah! Why is it that whenever
you got stuff to do
that you don't want to do
you go into cleaning mode?
And why is it
that when you do start cleaning,
you realize that you'd rather
be doing something else?
Hey, Konata, less breaks,
more cleaning, okay?
[whistle tweets]
Why is it called Comiket, huh?
I know
it's a big festival and all,
but don't you think it starts
too early in the morning?
I can't wait to see it!
You have no idea what
you're getting into, do you?
I pity you.
Ah, she'll get used to it
in no time.
Tsukasa, I gotta warn you
that this thing's
gonna wear you out,
like in all kinds of ways.
You okay with that?
Mm. Mm-hmm!
Don't worry, I'm good.
Something tells me you
don't really understand.
[KAGAMI whimpers]
[KAGAMI sighs]
[thinking] Unbelievable.
The train's
being overrun by otaku.
Be patient! The light
will turn green momentarily.
Hey, sis,
I'm getting really scared.
I hate to say I told you so.
Okay, here's the part
where I give
the two of you
your assignments for today.
[BOTH] Assignments?
Assignments, here are
your shopping lists.
When we get in there,
we're gonna split up.
Then we're gonna hit
all the tables
in the order shown on this map.
You guys take sections one
to three in the east hall,
I'll take four to six.
But, you have to be careful.
I've indicated your route
in red ink on the map.
If you don't stick to the route,
you're going to get
caught between the lines
for the tables
that are along the walls,
like right here and here.
If the two of you get stuck
in the crowds in this area,
you're going to lose
at least 30 minutes.
I dunno,
this looks sketchy to me.
Can't we just hang out?
Oh, come on, you'll be fine.
Look, the tables marked in green
are the ones you can
leave until the afternoon.
These guys won't sell
out of stuff that quick
'cause they usually have
a lot of stock on hand, okay?
Concentrate on getting
to all the tables
marked in red
before the morning's over.
"S" is for new, "K" is for
previously published.
If you're not sure, just buy
one of everything they have.
Doesn't matter
if it's new or not.
-Here's your ammo, men.
-[BOTH] Huh?
It's cash,
'cause you don't want
to be fiddling with your
wallets during checkout.
The cafe au lait is to
keep your sugar level up.
Take a drink every 30 minutes.
-This is our rally point.
-[BOTH] Huh?
Meet me here
at exactly 1300 hours.
-[whimpers]
-[grumbles]
I'll wait for you
for 15 minutes.
If you don't show,
then I'll know
to go look for you in first aid.
That's it. Any questions?
I got a question.
How come your passion
and intellect
only pop out when you're
being a total fangirl?
-[rumbling]
-[MAN] Please, don't run!
Climax from the get go!
The new issue is limited
to four per person.
That's four copies per person!
Behave yourselves!
Um, excuse me.
Hi, I was wondering
if this was A92?
Indeed it is.
Hi, you're getting one each
of the new issues?
1,000 yen please.
You were saying?
Oh right, sorry.
I was looking
for your new issues.
Perfect, the new issues
are this one
and that one,
and they're both 500 yen.
Ah, thanks for the help today.
You like the cookies I made?
You loved them, didn't you?
Oh, that's awesome.
Can I have three copies of each?
Absolutely!
"Slippery Brigade Leader"
and "The Naughty Captain."
-Enjoy! 3,000 yen please.
-Ah!
[grunting]
I'll take all of these, please.
Sure, that'll be
4,500 yen, please.
Here you go.
Thanks for you business,
hope you like 'em.
Tango down, proceeding
to the next target.
I wonder
if I'm in the east hall now.
If I am, that means north
is that way so then-- oh boy.
Ah! No, no, wait a minute!
Please! Oh no!
Um, excuse me, but I
need to go that way! Ah!
All right,
I guess I've covered
pretty much all the big ones.
Let's see,
where should I go to next?
Huh?
[grunts] Oh.
[straining]
[mutters]
A little peek won't hurt.
Wah!
Gauron's really sticking it
to Sousuke.
[screams]
No way!
[WOMAN] You like it?
You can take it home
for 500 yen.
Um, ah... it's too stimulating.
Huh?
[yells] No way, it's her!
The legendary girl "A."
[BLUE-HAIRED MAN]
Relax!
She'll think something's up
if you start freaking out.
Right. You're right, I know.
But I heard that whenever
she comes here
and buys stuff,
whoever she buys from,
their books
suddenly get popular!
How could I not
be excited about her?
Dude, I know!
I want her to buy one
as bad as you do!
We worked our butts off
on this issue.
Yeah, we did, didn't we?
We took time off
of work and everything
just to make this issue
rock like a mother.
This is our year.
-Can you feel it?
-Can I check it out?
[MEN] Yeah, sure!
Hm.
[MEN grunting]
What do you think? How is it?
It's pretty cool, isn't it?
We put a lot of work into
the scene with the live show.
Hm, needs work.
-[MEN gag]
-Thanks anyway, guys.
[whimpering]
[crying] Don't cry,
there's always next summer.
'Scuse me, can you help me?
Sure, what can I do for you?
I'm kinda lost and
I'm looking for Pu-61.
Which way is it?
Oh, I think you'll find the
Pu section in the east hall.
How do I get to the east hall?
[BOY] This is the west hall.
You need to get in that line
over there, and head upstairs.
That'll take you right
over to the east hall.
How long do you think it'll
take for me to get there?
[BOY] Hm, right now?
I think it'll take
about an hour.
[screams]
[whimpering]
Okay, that's all.
I'm sorry, Kona-chan.
I got lost
and then I had to escape
from this place
called the west hall.
I wasn't paying attention
and I got
washed away by the crowd.
What kind of place is this?
I had to stand in line
for the bathroom
and it took an hour.
I figured the little
shopping list I gave you
was gonna be too much
for a first timer.
It's all good.
Let's take it easy
and look around
for the rest of the day.
[KAGAMI thinks]
She hasn't had enough?
I have to say though,
since they moved
the festival to Ariake,
it's gotten better.
You should've seen it before.
Back in the day when it
was held in Harumi Hall
there were only two
convenience stores in the area.
Oh, back in the day, huh?
Mm-hmm, I think
the last time they held it
in Harumi Hall
was like 12 years ago?
-Huh?
-Whoa! Hold on a sec.
-How old were you?
-Hm?
I was about five.
It was great, my dad always
used to take me there.
We'd spend a couple nights
in this place
called the Hotel Urashima.
The first time he took me
was a Summer Comiket.
The second floor of the new
hall was totally awesome!
The sweat from all the
people in there evaporated
-and rose to the ceiling.
-[BOTH gasp]
Then it turned into this
huge cloud of steam!
-[whimpers]
-Yeah, too much information.
Ever since they started
having this thing in Ariake,
it's gotten better and better.
But because it's gotten so
big, all the younger people
who come here act like this
is some kind of supermarket.
That breaks my heart 'cause they
totally miss the point of it!
This event was supposed
to be something
the fans all did together.
Sorry to interrupt
your nostalgia,
but I don't get
any of it, at all.
Huh?
I didn't see this last summer.
Do they always have
something like this?
Mm-hmm, although by now
most of the good stuff's
all sold out.
Hm.
-Look, you guys, it's Nagato!
-[BOTH] Huh?
It's the real Nagamon,
and she's selling stuff!
[KAGAMI] Who?
What are you talking about?
What do you mean you sold out
of Haruhi stuff?
You're pissing me off, kid!
Give me my Nagato phone card!
Geez. What an ass.
As I was saying before,
there's a lot more
of that type coming here
these days.
I'm sorry to have to
be the one to tell you
but the limited edition
items we had for sale
have completely sold out!
What?
You gotta be kidding me!
[sizzling]
I am not kidding.
[MAN] That's what happens
when you get here late.
-Who's that?
-Sorry, kid, but you have
to line up in the morning
if you want to get--
You idiot!
[grunting] Asia.
[grunts]
Hey, what the hell?
You will do your best
to make the customers happy,
even if they show up late.
You're showing
a complete lack of spirit!
But-- but we sold out
of the limited-edition things.
We've only got leftovers
and old stock!
[energy humming]
Did you just say leftovers?
There's no such thing
as leftovers!
[yells]
Don't let the flashy trends
and cheap moe urges fool you!
Comiket is here
to show you the true value
of your so-called leftovers!
And now,
after all the limited edition
thingies have been sold,
the real battle between
corporate booths
is about to begin!
I-- I didn't know.
Well, don't you have a
suggestion for this customer?
The best you have, sir,
and be quick about it!
Something.
Isn't there a weapon?
Well, how about
something like this?
No, this is more like it!
You see?
Nagato sold out.
Everyone sold out,
but do you see this?
Even Koizumi sold out.
Silence,
how do you think I feel?
This is three years old.
The Captain card
sold out the first day.
Well, kid,
you want to buy a Kyun card?
No, Sousuke's the one for you!
[CUSTOMER] I was looking
for the Coco Saikube card.
You idiots!
[BOTH grunting]
It's the company president...
[BOTH] Mr. Takahashi!
Right, I am the company
president, Mr. Takahashi.
And I overheard what you
two were telling this kid.
[chattering]
That booth's always got
something crazy going on.
[BOTH, hesitantly]
R-really?
[TAKAHASHI]
...unsuspecting customers,
well, I can't allow that.
[BOTH] But, sir, both of them
are main characters.
[yawning]
[GIRLS]
Lucky Star!
[chattering]
[rattling]
[TSUKASA]
I'm so tired.
[KAGAMI]
I know, I'm tired too.
I wish we didn't have to come
here right after Comiket.
How can they have
an event like that
right on New Year's Eve?
Kagami, Tsukasa,
Happy New Year!
-Hey.
-Hi, Kona-chan.
Happy New Year to you, too.
I can't believe
you're still standing
after a crazy day like today.
Besides, it's so cold I
figured you'd stay home.
Yeah, well,
you got a point there.
But it's a new year and you
have to start it off right!
The idea's to visit the
shrine and get yourself
charged up
for the coming year.
Wow, that's admirable.
-I know, my dad said it.
-Hello.
[KAGAMI thinks] Suddenly,
I'm feeling weird about it.
And your outfit's looking hot!
Oh yeah.
[BOTH] Stuff like this,
stuff like that.
Okay, I'm all done praying.
Oh, well great, good for you.
Have you guys finished
with all your prayers
and stuff for the night?
Hey, sis, what were you
so feverishly praying for
a little while ago?
What? You don't have to
broadcast it to everyone.
And I wasn't
that feverish about it.
I-- I was just thinking
how nice it would be
if I could be in the same class
as you and Miyuki,
that's all it was.
Hm?
Don't forget
Kona-chan's there too.
That's so adorable!
I never knew
you had a cute side, Kagami.
Shut up, you!
I didn't say anything
'cause I knew
you'd tease me about it!
And the way you resist
your cuteness is also cute!
-What about it?
-You've always been
in a different class
than the rest of us.
[sighs]
Maybe it's because Ms. Kuroi
doesn't like me or something.
I know!
I'm gonna go say a prayer
so that the two of us can be
in the same class together.
Really, Tsukasa?
I wouldn't do that
if I were you.
Kagami needs to be
in a different class.
-Huh, but why?
-Elementary!
We need you there
so we can borrow your stuff
and copy your homework
without getting caught!
Besides, if you're
in the same class as me,
my ranking's gonna drop.
Maybe you should be
in a different class, weirdo.
-Yeah right.
-Anyway, we saw Sebas--
[thinks] Schoolgirls are
the best! The best!
Will you and your dad be
buying fortunes this year?
Yeah, you know it.
That's why we're here.
[BOTH] Oh!
Your new year is looking
good right from the get-go.
I'll say.
Everywhere I look it's good.
This is gonna be
a great year, I know it.
-Oh, it'll be all right.
-[crying]
Even though the fortune
you picked is horrible,
it can only get better,
you know?
Good things will happen.
Sure, yeah,
whatever you say.
I guess it's
how you look at it.
Thanks a lot!
If you're worried about it,
you could tie it to a branch
to lift the curse.
Hm, yeah, I'll do that.
Whoa! You gotta be kidding!
Whoa! More of 'em!
Ah, I found a spot!
I guess this is what
they call being cursed.
Yeah.
Look, whether good things
happen or not,
it all depends
on you in the end.
A fortune is nothing
more than a game of luck.
Yeah, I guess,
but you're a shrine maiden.
I didn't know you could
say something like that.
[TSUKASA whimpers]
I know, I can collect
all the fortunes,
from great curses
to great blessings.
Those things
are not trading cards.
Maybe I could even find
a secret fortune, too.
Oh, come on,
secret fortunes?
What the heck
is a secret fortune?
Maybe an ultra great curse!
It's a curse. Who'd want to
collect something like that?
I beg to differ.
You want to collect 'em all,
'cause if you do,
you get a limited edition prize.
There is nothing like that.
I've been wanting to ask you
something ever since
I saw that huge Kagami-mochi.
That really big one?
I was wondering if that's where
the name Kagami came from?
Well, yeah, I guess
you can say it does.
Kagami-mochi is round,
the same shape
as an old-fashioned mirror.
And for a long time now,
people have believed
that mirrors were
where the gods lived.
See, that's why
my parents named me Kagami,
because they
hoped that my life
would be blessed
by the gods.
By the way, its shape symbolizes
a well-rounded family, too.
[THINKS] Her name's got
all these mystical origins,
so can someone
please tell me how
she grew up to be
such a hardcore realist?
Hmm. [chuckles]
-Ah!
-You want one?
-Mmm.
-They're nice!
[panting]
[KONATA] There sure
are a lot of worshipers.
Yeah, well,
it is New Year's Eve.
This is nothing compared
to other shrines.
[chuckles]
I bet most of 'em are here
for the same reason as Dad.
They just want to check
out all the shrine maidens.
[KAGAMI thinks]
Oh, come on!
There aren't
that many pervs here.
I guess.
[birds chirping]
[motorbike approaches]
I guess it's that time again.
It's the first day
of the new year
and time
to start things off right.
Have a Happy New Year, Dad.
I hope you have
the best year ever.
Happy New Year, hon.
[MAN on TV]
Yeah, Happy New Year!
How's it going, everybody?
I'm Du! How about this
beautiful location, huh?
Isn't it great?
It's fantastic!
Ooh, look at
that pretty flower!
-There's so many flowers.
-[ALL laughing]
I made some tea, Dad.
Do you want some?
Sure, I'll have a cup.
-Here you go.
-Oh, thanks a lot, kiddo.
[sipping, sighs]
Dad, do you want to
play this game with me?
Dad, do you want
a bowl of rice cake soup?
Hey, Dad, how about--
Yeah, well, I guess
Dad thought it was cute,
the way I was bugging him.
Can you believe that?
I got my New Year's
allowance, though.
He sure wore me out.
Ah, yeah, I bet.
You guys are totally weird
for each other, aren't you?
And now that
my New Year's allowance
has been secured,
I think I'm gonna
head over to Gamers
right now and spend it.
[KAGAMI]
Right.
Oh, it's a pain
stores like that
aren't open out here
in the sticks.
I mean, I'm a little strapped
for cash these days.
And the train ride isn't cheap.
I wish there was a store
like that around here.
Don't most stores have websites
you can order stuff from?
Ever think of doing that?
I mean these days you can pretty
much order anything online.
You just don't get it, do you?
Yeah, shopping online's okay
'cause you can get
points and stuff,
but looking around's the best
part of going into the store.
There's always a chance you'll
find something unexpected that--
What is wrong with you?
All you want to do
is spend your money!
[MAN on TV] Daikon radish
gets all nice and done.
I wonder why people call
these things "Pochi Bukuro."
I know. "Pochitto" means
"a tiny amount,"
and "koreppocchi"
means "a bit."
It's a bag you put
your loose change in.
Oh.
Western Japan
calls it "pochitto,"
and "koreppocchi" is how
you say it in eastern Japan.
[phone buzzes]
Best wishes for a safe
and happy New Year.
Miyuki speaking.
Hi, Miyuki-san, happy
New Year to you, too.
So anyway,
I want to know about these
Pochi Bukuro things, like
why they're called that.
Ah, come on.
Why can't you trust your
old man just a little bit?
Or at least you could do
your fact-checking
when I'm not around.
Alrighty then.
Time for me to log on and give
all my gaming buddies
a Happy New Year greeting.
Oh, teach logged on.
[keys clacking]
Oh.
[thinks] This is so sad.
It's like the poor woman doesn't
have anything better to do.
I mean,
she's always online, always!
No wonder
she doesn't have a boyfriend.
[snoring]
[GIRLS]
Lucky Star!
[MAN]
Lucky Channel!
Hiya, luckies!
I'm Akira-sama's assistant,
Minoru Shiraishi.
Can you guys say,
"time flies"?
'Cause we're
on episode 12, baby!
-[coughs]
-Uh...
[MINORU thinks]
This ocean is hell.
Okay, so, uh,
Akira-sama was
supposed to show up
in today's episode
of "Lucky Star,"
but as you can see,
she fell ill
at the last minute and
couldn't quite make it.
-[coughs]
-Huh?
[speaks indiscernibly]
That's right,
it's a nasty cold.
But we had a standy of you
there with a sign on it,
so if folks were
watching the show,
they'd see something that sort
of looked like you.
[speaks indiscernibly]
-[coughs]
-Huh?
Wait, Akira-sama.
-[grunts]
-[gasps]
Okay, I guess everyone can tell
Akira-sama's
wiped out for today.
So how about we wrap this up?
See you guys later! Bye-ni!
Huh, why do you keep
saying that?
I am not getting a big head!
-[AKIRA speaks indiscernibly]
-[MINORU] What?
"I'm gonna make you listen
to the full version
of 'Take It!
The Sailor Suit'"?
-[AKIRA moans]
-[MINORU] "Look forward"-- what?
"If you don't watch
the next episode,
I'm going to lecture you
in the name of Mars."
[AKIRA]
Fumoffu.
[applause]
[KAGAMI]
Way to tear it up, you guys!
[TSUKASA]
That was so much fun!
[MIYUKI]
It was!
[KONATA]
No one entered a song.
[KAGAMI] What's with you?
You're next in the lineup.
Why didn't you pick a song yet?
[KONATA]
Oh, I couldn't decide.
What song should I pick?
[KAGAMI]
I'll help you look for one.
[MIYUKI]
Oh, I found a menu.
Ooh, I didn't know
they served food here.
[KONATA] Mm-hmm.
I sang this one already.
Now my flow's off.
Oh, I should've
saved it for later.
[KAGAMI]
What do you mean, "flow"?
[KONATA] You know, getting
your groove on, your flow?
How you work yourself up
to sing a song?
[KAGAMI]
I don't get it.
[KONATA]
Ooh, how about this one?
[clears throat]
♪ Hey, Godman ♪
♪ Can you hear me? ♪
[MIYUKI] Look, they
also have tambourines.
Yeah, so you can
really have some fun.
Here, Miyuki-chan,
let's use these.
[MIYUKI]
How fun!
[KONATA]
Yes, I'll do this one.
[KAGAMI sighs] I don't care!
Just pick something already!
[KONATA]
Here's a song I know
will get everybody moving!
[KONATA]
Oh! You know this one!
[TSUKASA]
I know it too!
[MIYUKI]
Well, I know of it.
[KONATA]
♪ Makenai... ♪
Oh, I blew it.
-[GIRLS giggling]
-[KONATA vocalizes music]
[GIRLS singing in Japanese]
[MAN] On the next
episode of "Lucky Star"...
[MIYUKI]
Miyuki here. If you'd like
to describe something as
being at the top of its class
or standing head and shoulders
above everything else,
you'd use the term "dan-totsu."
Apparently ,this is the
abbreviation of "danzen top."
According to record,
the very first time this term
was used in print was when
you-know-who won the election
to become governor of Tokyo.
And, yes,
he did win by a landslide.
Next time, "Delicious Day."
[MAN]
Look forward to it.