[KONATA]
Senior Year Class B.
[GIRLS]
Ms. Kuroi!
[KAGAMI]
Yeah, yeah.
[theme music playing]
Hey, guys.
Oh, hi-ya, sis.
How'd your exams go?
[giggles] Same as ever.
A disaster as usual.
It's funny how during
these exam periods,
you seem to have more
free time than usual,
but then all that free time
you thought you had's gone
and you end up
cramming the night before.
You know what I'm saying?
You've got your college
entrance exams coming up,
so accept it and start
acting like you care.
[MAN ON TV]
Raided the suspects room
where authorities confiscated
thousands of manga
and video games.
Apparently...
[KONATA]
It's happened again.
[YUTAKA]
No way!
There was a story
on the news again
about another geek like you.
Yeah, I know. I can't
stop thinking about it.
It's totally unfair. I mean,
they're always so quick to put
the hate on manga like that.
But there's a lot of
good manga out there, too,
and it really sucks that
they never talk about that.
[sighs]
Yeah, I guess.
It bums me out, too.
Wow, you really are a good
person, aren't you Kagami?
If I say stuff like that
around normal people,
they mock me and say that
Otaku are desperate freaks.
Ugh.
If I look around
at the people I know,
I notice that sisters
tend to absorb
certain characteristics
from one another.
Like how it is with
you and Yui Na-san
or Kagami and Tsukasa.
Hm? [chuckles]
Mm-hmm.
That's what Konata and I were
talking about this morning.
[WOMAN]
You're quite attached
to Miyuki-chan, aren't you?
Why you're so close,
you could be sisters.
Absorbing.
Here you go, Kona-chan.
Happy birthday!
Wow. Huh?
If Tsukasa hadn't
reminded me about it,
I would've forgotten.
[chuckles]
Happy Birthday, Konata.
Hmm. Thanks a lot you guys.
Yeah, I guess it's nice if
people remember your birthday,
but at this age, I don't
really feel too happy
about getting another
year older.
Yeah, whatever.
I'm super happy
I'm a year older.
Huh, why's that?
Do you wanna get a drivers
license or something?
I'm old enough to play
games with a mature rating.
So what, you've been
playing those games
this whole time, anyway.
[KONATA] He ha.
[KAGAMI] Ugh.
Who me?
[sighs]
You're a year older, and you
still haven't changed a bit,
either inside or outside.
Let me go.
Hey Miyuki, do people
ever think you're older
than you really are?
You do look really mature,
Yuki-chan.
Yes, I suppose so.
When I go out
in my normal clothes,
I sometimes get mistaken
for an office lady.
Wow, you get to skip past
college and everything.
But in your case,
when you're out
wearing your street clothes,
everyone thinks you're
back in grade school.
Hm, it doesn't matter
what you say
'cause starting today,
I'm officially an adult.
Ugh, give me a break.
Look, for starters,
if you're such an adult now,
you can't be getting all weird
about games and manga anymore.
Wha-- But it's important to
have a childlike heart
filled with dreams and passion!
Oh, I don't care.
Do what you want.
Mmm?
Hmm? Oh this thing?
Uh-huh.
I'm making it for
Konata's birthday party.
We're gonna be secretly
getting ready for it
while she's at work tonight.
[chuckles]
Did I make it home in time?
Yup, are you ready
to do some decorating?
Yeah!
[drums beating a la "24"]
[phone rings]
[SOUJIRO]
Oh, that's gotta be her.
I wonder if she's gonna
be coming home soon.
Hey, kiddo.
[KONATA]
Hey, Dad,
I totally forgot to tell you
everyone at work is
throwing me a birthday party,
so I'm gonna have dinner
with these guys,
and I'll be coming home late.
Sorry, bye.
This is really good, Yutaka.
Oh, thanks a lot.
You can take the stache off now.
[sighs]
Future aspirations?
There's lots of careers
I dream about having,
but choosing is hard to do.
That's so true. If you're
going to continue on to college,
your plans for
a career might depend
on what subject you
end up majoring in.
You put down number one, a
career in nutritional science,
number two, fashion designer
and number three, marketing?
Yeah, you know me,
I've always liked to
cook and sew and stuff.
Oh, you just wrote down
all your dreams, huh?
How about you, Miyuki-san?
Since I want to become a doctor,
I have to take courses
in pre-med
for this list,
what I've done is to select
three different schools
which I'd like to attend.
That's our Miyuki-san.
You know what you want
and how to get it.
How about you, Kagami?
Okay, for my first
choice I put down pre-law,
my second choice is economics
and my third choice
is literature.
Jeez, that doesn't sound
very interesting at all.
Does it have to be interesting?
What'd you put down?
[chuckles]
I should've known you
wouldn't take it seriously.
Don't you have
some kind of special talent
besides making faces?
Special talent?
Hmm.
Oh! Poke-[beep]-mon!
I memorized the names of
each and every one of them.
I guess that's a special talent,
but it doesn't address
the future goals thing.
[shoppers talking]
Oh, there it is.
This is the one I wanted.
When you buy your
manga and magazines,
do you always pick from
the bottom of the stack?
Well yeah, the top copies
have already been handled,
and you wanna get the
cleanest one you can, right?
Yeah, I guess I know
what you mean.
It's like when you go to one
of those revolving sushi places
and you put your order in
instead of picking
a ready made plate,
'cause the fish
on the conveyor belt's
always dry and crusty.
Whoa! I can't believe
you do that Kagami,
you horrible customer!
What, you don't?
You're so cheap.
It still blows my mind, Kagami,
that you actually read books
that are only filled with
words, don't you get sleepy?
Oh come on,
this is a light novel.
It's not that different
from a manga.
It's got the same vibe, right?
You really think so?
Well yeah,
it's got illustrations
and the writing's simple enough.
Here, just give it a shot.
Oh, they already turned
that one into an anime,
so yeah, I'll just watch that.
If this were a manga,
you'd be saying
it's cool, because
it's the original.
You'd read it
and watch the anime.
So come on, just try it.
Yeah, I'm gonna have to pass.
The thing about you, Kagami,
is that you read
a ton of other books
besides those light novels.
Well, how do I explain it.
When you read,
it's like you're loading up
on all this knowledge,
so I guess in a way,
you're enriching your soul.
Yeah, it's nutrition
for the soul.
Uh huh, I get it.
Get what?
Your reasoning.
You load up on sweets,
'cause you think you're
enriching your body.
Isn't that right?
Ugh! Bite me.
So, here's a question?
Doesn't that magazine
you're reading
have any serialized novels
in it?
You know, besides the comics?
I wouldn't know. I just
sort of look at the pictures.
[sighs]
Well, I guess despite
everything you say
about how you love
all things geeky,
you don't really
love that stuff at all.
You just skim right past it.
All right, all right. Fine.
I'll read it.
Oh no, don't bother.
It doesn't count if you have
to force yourself to read it.
I was only skimming,
'cause I had a lot of
other stuff to read, okay.
Hey, don't worry. It's fine.
Just forget I even
said anything, okay?
Oh, darn it!
I can't believe I forgot
my world history book.
I bet I left it sitting on my
desk after doing my homework.
Hey, can I borrow your
world history textbook?
You left it here, didn't you?
Yeah, I did.
What, did you forget yours?
Uh-huh.
Huh, that's weird.
Here.
Ah!
Whoa, you've got one heck of a
fun looking textbook
there, don't you, Hiiragi?
No, it's not really mine.
[chuckles]
[sighs]
I feel like
I'm hitting the wall.
Guess I'll go downstairs
and get something to drink.
Great!
What the?
Yay, I just bought
that stuff yesterday,
and it's already gone.
Whatever, a walk'll
do me some good.
Huh? They're closed?
Ugh, it's like a conspiracy.
320 yen, please.
Uh-oh.
[grumbling]
Hiya sis, what's wrong?
Well, you know how
when you get irritated,
you make a bunch of
little mistakes
and get even more irritated?
Oh yeah, no matter what you do,
nothing seems to go right.
Yeah, it's like a negative
spiral or something.
Oh yeah, I forgot to tell you,
I baked a cake! Want some?
Yeah!
Studying for these
entrance exams is tough,
so we've got to change
gears every now and then.
I know! Tomorrow
I'll bake cookies.
Oh, now that's what
I call stress relief.
I can't wait!
[sighs]
And now I'm stressed out
about this.
No way! You think so, too,
Iwasaki-san?
Yeah, I know, I guess the two
of them are always so busy
that they keep on missing each
other or something like that.
[chuckles]
Yeah, I know what you mean.
[YUTAKA]
Uh-oh, Konata's studying
for her entrance exams
I better keep it down
so I don't disturb her.
Hey, sorry about this but
I'm gonna have to talk quietly.
[gasps]
Hey, after you're done,
you wanna go head to head
on this game with me? You wanna?
Say what?
[meows]
[GIRLS]
Lucky Star.
Can't believe this is the
last year I'll be wearing this.
Whenever I think about it,
I start getting all emotional.
Oh, there's something
in my pocket.
My favorite handkerchief.
I thought I lost it,
but it was in my pocket
the whole time.
Huh.
Where's the octopus and wasabi?
Oh. Wonder what this is.
[screams]
I have no idea what that is.
It's changed so much
I can't tell.
[KONATA]
Sure rains a lot
during the rainy season.
[TSUKASA]
I know.
Just when you think
it's getting too hot,
all of a sudden it gets cold,
and it totally sucks,
'cause we just switched
over Summer uniforms.
Hey, what are you guys
still doing here?
You're so lucky, ma'am,
you know?
You can wear whatever you
want, whenever you want.
[laughs] Are you kidding?
Wearing a uniform's better,
'cause you don't
waste time in the morning
thinking about what to put on.
Wow, ma'am, that's just so...
I mean you're really...
[screaming]
[chuckles]
Yoohoo, the rainy season's
back and so is the humidity!
[KONATA] Hey, Onee-san.
[YUTAKA] Hey, Onee-chan.
Man, all this rain's
so darn depressing.
Would you like some tea?
Sure, sounds awesome.
You've got something coming up
that you can look forward to.
You're gonna be celebrating
your first wedding anniversary.
Oh, that's right.
Wow, time flies.
During the rainy season,
the skies look--
They look a lot like
Yui Na-san's heart
when her husband's
away on business,
even though their
one year anniversary's
right around the corner.
This totally sucks!
[crying]
I'm sorry, I shouldn't
have said anything.
It's okay.
I've gotten used to living
with a giant wad
of emotional pain.
Here, maybe if you have
some tea it'll cheer you up.
[sighs] Thanks.
I doubt it's gonna help, though.
Mmm. Wow, that's good.
Glad you like it.
[YUI sighs]
Jeez, my love life
is gonna get all rusty
if things keep up like this.
Well, if you took your love
life to a car repair shop
they'd have it lubed up and
ready to go in 45 minutes.
Couldn't you at least
try to comfort me a little?
Couldn't help it, sorry.
[phone rings]
Hello?
Huh, you'll be coming
back home soon?
Wow, that didn't take
45 minutes at all,
more like 45 seconds.
I know.
[KAGAMI]
You're kidding, Tsukasa.
You mean, Matsuri still hasn't
given you that outfit back?
Mm-mmm.
That's not good.
You know how she is,
if you don't tell her
to give it back,
she's gonna keep it
and say it's hers.
Oh no. She can't.
I really like that outfit.
[sighs]
[chuckles]
I think it's just wonderful
how Kagami-san and Tsukasa-san
get to have two older sisters.
I guess.
Oh, really?
That's funny, because I
think being an only child
like you and Miyuki
is way better
than our situation, right?
Yeah, I guess
I see what you mean.
I don't know. You get
to do a whole lot more
when you're part
of a bigger cast.
You could be like
that story of the mother
and her four daughters
who are all waiting
for the father to return,
'cause he went away to battle
during the American Civil War.
Or maybe you could be like
that gang of
dynamic female art thieves.
One, two.
Uh.
Ha.
What the?
[KONATA]
Wait, there's one too many.
Man, when you talk to her,
she always has to turn it
into something about
games or anime.
Hold up Kagami, you get
those things for dinner
I asked you to get?
Huh?
Don't tell me
you forgot to tell her.
I'm sorry.
Could someone tell me
what's going on?
What do you mean,
Mom and Dad started their
vacation today, remember?
Oh yeah,
they're not gonna be home.
It's all my fault.
We were supposed to go
shopping for ingredients.
Sorry, I totally
forgot about it.
I called your cell, Kagami,
and even left you a
message. Didn't you get it?
Oh, come on Matsuri,
we can make dinner
with whatever's
left in the fridge.
Ah, but I was totally set
on making something
yummy tonight!
You can make it tomorrow night.
Well, fine but it's all
your fault. You guys suck.
I'm sorry.
[groans]
Fine, whatever.
I'll go get your ingredients.
[ALL sighing]
Well, you could've handled
that a little better.
I know.
Uh oh, does she even know
what kind of stuff
I need her to buy?
Uh.
Gimme a break.
She doesn't even like
to cook that much, anyway.
Man, she can be such an ass.
[TSUKASA]
Kagami!
Huh?
Tsukasa?
[breathing heavily]
You forgot this.
It's the shopping list
with the ingredients.
Ugh.
They're really late.
If you're that worried about it,
maybe you should've gone
to get that stuff yourself.
Oh.
Took you guys long enough.
Hmm.
What happened?
Matsuri was really getting
worried about you guys.
The store we usually go
to didn't have any saffron,
so I said we could
probably get by
using some curry powder instead,
but sis said we might as well
look for it since we were out.
So we went to that supermarket
that's way down there.
Jeez, you know you guys
didn't have to go that far.
Yeah, well whatever!
Hmm.
[sighs]
Okay, let's make some dinner.
I'm so hungry,
I'm gonna pass out.
There, sorry for the wait.
All that's left is
Matsuri's special dish.
[MATSURI]
It's done!
Yummy, it looks amazing.
Yeah, it's got a wonderful
golden brown color.
Hey, Matsuri, when did you learn
how to cook something
as amazing as this, huh?
Oh, well the other day, me
and some girls from college
went drinking
and we ordered this dish.
It was so good
I wanted you guys to try it,
so I walked back to the kitchen
and asked the chef there
how to make it.
[INORI]
Really? I'm surprised
they gave you the recipe.
[MATSURI]
Uh, no big deal, let's eat.
[TSUKASA]
Yay.
[moans]
Uh oh.
What happened to you?
You won't believe it.
Your dad made a mistake
about the date for our trip.
Oh.
When's it supposed to be?
Well, I actually made the
reservation for next week.
It sounds like a bad joke.
Oh, having dinner?
Yeah, you guys hungry?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, is that paella?
Yeah and guess what?
Matsuri made it.
Oh? It looks amazing.
Thanks. Kagami totally
helped me out
by getting all of
the ingredients.
She went all the way out
to the supermarket
just to get them.
[chuckles]
Well, wanna dine in
tonight, Hun?
Okay.
[everyone laughs]
[KAGAMI]
This is pretty good.
[MATSURI]
Hey, who took all the mussels?
[TSUKASA]
Mussels?
[KAGAMI]
I wasn't supposed to take any?
[MATSURI]
I can't believe it.
I was saving them
to eat for last. Oh, man.
[KAGAMI]
Then write your name
on them next time!
[INORI]
Jeez, you guys, stop fighting.
Hey, is it cool if
I take a little detour
into town with you today?
Oh yeah, sure.
You wanna buy something?
Uh-huh. It's the new book
by Shin-[pops]-yamara.
I don't know when I'll
have time to read it, though,
'cause of all the assignments
they're giving us these days.
Yeah, I've got this
totally huge pile of manga
I still haven't read
next to my pillow.
And then before I know it,
I'm out buying more new manga.
I know. I do that, too.
Then read the stuff you've got
instead of buying something new.
Well, if you buy it now,
then you don't have to
worry about buying it later,
and if you don't, you feel
like you're missing out, right?
What are you asking me for?
[GIRLS]
Lucky Star.
[AKIRA]
Lucky Channel!
Hi-ya, Luckies!
Yay, you guys ready to
have a super exciting time!
Do you realize that this is the
17th episode of Lucky Channel?
That's so amazing,
and I'm your navigator!
Who's the red rose
with all the thorns?
Who's the platypus
of the idol industry?
It's Akira Kogami!
Okay!
[MINORU] Hello!
So we invited
a super big name guest
to come on the show today.
Um--
How long are you people
gonna make me wait!
[screaming]
Oh, crap I'm in the shot. Sorry!
He's in the shot again.
[MINORU] I know.
[screaming]
Oh, okay, today's special guest
is the anime manager,
Meito Anizawa. Yay!
This program's totally weak!
Ugh. Well you see, Lucky Star
is an anime that's a peek
into the lives of a group of
ordinary high school girls.
It's supposed to have a very
slow paced and casual feel,
but then with our segment,
Lucky Channel,
even though we've also got
that laid back vibe going on,
we're really
quite different than--
Unacceptable!
[MINORU]
Whoa, where'd he go?
[screaming]
Holy cow, he's fast.
[MEITO]
There are three things that
every successful
anime has in common.
Quickly, tell me what they are!
Three things? Let's see,
the voice actors,
animation styles, and the story?
No!
Ah, my uniform's burning red!
Hot, hot, hot!
They are...
Go on!
It's the love the staff and
the cast pour into the show.
It's also the time
they're given to do it
and the budget of the thing.
Although, we don't have control
over the production
schedule or the budget.
[screams]
Wow.
I don't care how great
the original work was.
If the script's a piece of crap,
what's the point? So what
if the VA's work hard.
If the characters aren't
colored in, the show's a goner.
You see what
I'm saying, Shiraishi?
Shiroshi?
Everybody on the
production puts everything
they've got into what they do.
They pour all their love
and passion into the show
grinding their bodies into dust.
That's the stuff you need
to make a successful anime!
[crying]
Yeah, so that's everything,
is it?
Right now, you're playing
someone called Akira Kogami.
Right now, huh?
Sorry to be the one
to have to tell you,
but I've always been Akira.
What about Lorou-[beeps],
Gaor-[beeps]-nger,
[beeps]-tato, or Mai-[beeps]-ai?
You loved them didn't you?
You had to!
What the hell
are you talking about?
Well if you didn't feel
anything in your heart for them.
No, not a thi--
Burn yourself out
as Akira Kogami!
You're twisting my bra.
Okay, I promise I'll burn
out as Minoru Shiraishi.
Right on, Shiraishi!
And I know just where
to start with you, sir.
Hosting a concert!
[AKIRA] So that's it, right.
You MC'd something
recently, did you not?
[AKIRA] Bye-nee.
[MEITO] You did.
[MINORU]
You were watching?
[MEITO]
Of course, part of my job.
[AKIRA] Thanks for the hard work
today, now go home.
[MINORU] I can't believe they
let me do it, I was so nervous.
[MEITO] I bet, now then.
[AKIRA] What? Oh,
Shiraishi can handle the rest.
[MEITO] Your ad libs are weak
and don't let Sugita
push you arou--
[MAN speaking in Japanese]
[singing in Japanese]
[BOTH talking in Japanese]
[sped up singing in Japanese]
[MAN 1]
On the next epis--
[MAN 2]
Boring!
Would you stop with the
cookie cutter preview?
[MAN 1]
Heil Blayking, boss!
[MALE 2]
Right, now listen up!
The first rule to becoming
a big-time voice actor is...
[MAN 1]
Rule number one is?
[MAN 2]
If you can't beat them,
join them!
[MAN 1]
Well said, sir!
Next time, "To Each Her Own."
And that's it for Anizawa.
[MAN 2]
Finger!