[MISS KUROI]
Senior year, class B!
[GIRLS]
Miss Kuroi!
[KAGAMI]
Yeah, Yeah.
[singing in Japanese]
[growls]
Those boxes all look the same,
and you've been
at it for a while.
Isn't there a better way to
figure out what's inside?
It's common sense to
do it this way, or else
I'd spend lots and lots of
money and never get what I want.
What you call common sense
doesn't apply to everyone.
And if we're talking
about normal people,
it definitely doesn't apply.
It's not just for
figures, you can also
use that method to find
the cards you want, too.
Okay, but how can you
tell which card is which?
Don't they all weigh the same?
Actually, there are
all kinds of legends
and rumors about
finding this stuff,
like how there's a special
mark on the box somewhere,
or that the boxes form a
pattern inside the case.
If it's the type of
packaging with candy in it,
I can pretty much always
get the card I want.
If they just open the case,
finding the pattern's easy.
[thinks]
Okay, that's pretty awesome,
but there's no way
I'm telling her that.
[KAGAMI]
If anyone can figure it out,
don't the rare things get
snapped up right away?
Yeah, it totally sucks,
and if you live someplace
where there's an expert
or two, the rare cards
and secret figures are usually
gone before you know it.
When I go to a store and I see
a bunch of cases with
all these gaps in them,
I wanna curl up in
a little ball and cry.
And the worst thing is that
you stand there and think
"There still a chance,
there's a few left."
Sounds like you could
use some therapy.
Anyway, I heard somewhere
that collectors can just
buy everything by
the case, is that true?
Ahh, that's a true collector.
If you buy stuff by the case,
you can complete
the set quicker,
and you can figure out the
patterns in distribution.
Really?
Yep, it's called the
grown-up shopping method,
'cause you need a
job to support it.
That's why I work part-time.
Grown-up shopping method, huh?
If you ask me, only possessive
and selfish people act that way.
You might call it grown-up
and everything,
but it's incredibly
childish behavior.
Maybe big-kid shopping
method's a better name.
You know, putting a little
bit of that kind of effort
into something else
would be more productive.
Maybe you should try it.
Anyway, have you
noticed all the attention
Akihabara's been getting
from the media lately?
I know, but most of
it's painful to watch.
I mean, the specials are
okay, but most of the stuff
they're putting together
isn't very realistic.
Maybe they blow stuff
out of proportion
'cause the culture of
otaku is so extreme.
If it's so extreme, then how
come TV shows and songs that
the otaku liked first are
suddenly popular with everyone?
I mean come on, even the
news and tabloid shows
use music from anime and games.
Well, maybe they use
it 'cause they know
normal people won't recognize
where the music came from.
Speaking of otaku, you
can find forums online
where the otaku guys talk about
wanting to date otaku girls.
They want someone who's into
the same shows and stuff.
But you never see any
posts from the otaku girls
talking about wanting
to date the otaku guys.
Why is that?
Is it because a girl's obsession
with 2D is bigger than a guy's?
Maybe girl otaku worry about
the future more than boys,
that's probably why they can
go out and find proper jobs.
Why are you asking me this?
[buzzing]
I hate how when it gets
hot the flies show up.
They make all this noise, and
run away before I slap 'em.
Rotten fly.
Remember Musashi Miyamoto?
The story goes he could catch
flies with his chopsticks.
Ew, you're kidding.
That's disgusting, why
would anyone try to grab
a dirty old fly with
their eating utensils?
That's not the point, but I
get where you're coming from.
[buzzing]
[slap]
[menacing laughter]
Oh wow, I could never
ever smack a mosquito.
Why? They suck.
Don't you think it's gross how
when you smoosh 'em
you get blood all over?
Yeah, you're right.
But it's just my blood.
If you don't smash mosquitoes,
then what do you do if one
of them lands on your arm?
I go "shoo, shoo"
and flap my arm,
or I go "whoo" and blow 'em off.
[buzzing]
[SOUJIRO] If a mosquito bites
your arm, and you flex it
hard enough, it won't be
able to pull its straw out.
[KONATA]
No way!
[SOUJIRO]
Check it out.
Wow.
[menacing laughter]
You are already dead.
And you're already bitten, Dad.
[SOUJIRO] And if you
flex your arm harder,
the mosquito explodes.
No, stop it, don't do it!
Oh, itchy itchy.
[thinks]
Maybe it would have been better
to whack it after all.
So, Miyuki-san, are you gonna
go overseas again for
summer vacation?
Oh no, we're not
going this year.
I'm visiting my relatives
in the country instead.
And then I usually attend
the summer festival with my
neighbor, you know, she's the
one who goes to school here.
She's just like a little sister.
Yeah?
Yeah, you're gonna go
to a summer festival?
I bet you look
great in a yukata.
Not really.
[thinks] I know
she's giving me a compliment,
but still, I'm not
happy about it.
It's like she's saying
that I have a flat.
[doorbell rings]
[KONATA moans]
Come on in.
Hey, guys, good morning.
So, lazy pants finally wakes up.
Lazy?
I don't know if that's it,
but something else
has been bugging me.
What?
Like trying to remember
whether the alarm went off
this morning, or if someone
came in and turned it off.
Oh, I totally know
what you mean,
like it was turned off
and you didn't even know.
Well, the good thing
is that by noon time
it's so hot you can't
stay asleep any longer.
It is way past noon.
[MAN in game] It's morning,
Kona-chan, rise and shine.
Would you like to
have lunch with me, Izumi-kun?
I thought we could
walk home together
today, Konata-kun.
Hey, Konata.
What's the deal with
that game you're playing?
How come the main
character is so popular?
I don't know, maybe
it wouldn't be
much of a game if he
wasn't that popular.
[MAN in game]
Oh come on,
you have to do all
your homework first?
Look, it's not like I'm
worried about you or anything.
If that's what
you want, Konata, I'll do it.
-Hey, Konata.
-Hmm?
How come the heroines
in games like that
never have boyfriends?
They're always cute,
have great personalities,
and could pretty much
pick any guy they want.
I don't know, maybe it wouldn't
be much of a game if they did.
Hey, Konata, I'm here
to hang out again,
after I see what's up
with Yutaka, that is.
Hey there, neisan,
how's it going?
Konata, didn't you
hear your dad calling?
Oh yeah.
Yutaka's studying, so hook
me up with some manga, girl.
Hey, shouldn't you be studying?
I mean, like you've been
messing around this whole time.
I have not! It's just
that you keep coming in
when I'm taking a break, is all!
Okay, so I guess that
means you've been taking
a heck of a lot of
breaks today, huh?
Like, I feel I've gotta act
responsible and stuff now,
but every time I sit
down at my desk,
I end up taking another break.
I swear, it's like
that 'cause you've never
been serious about
doing your homework.
Anyway, I guess I know
where you're coming from.
Wait, you saying this kinda
stuff happens to you, too?
Well, if I take a break
and crack open a book
I've been wanting to read,
when I go back to studying,
I sorta wanna take
another break.
I know, you just
can't put something
like that down in the middle.
It's the same with manga,
you think you're gonna
stop after one volume, but
then before you know it,
you end up plowing through
all the other volumes
-in the series.
-Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Like when you miss a
couple episodes of something,
and you rent the DVDs and
then watch them all in one go.
Just to find out the rest of
the episodes are totally lame.
Oneichan, may I please
change the channel?
Go for it, I just had
it on a random channel.
Is there something else
you wanted to watch?
Uh huh, it's a special show
about desserts
from all over Japan.
Cool, I know how much you like
desserts and sweets and stuff.
Bet you Kagami's watching it.
Wow, that looks good.
Yeah, but with a
show like this, whenever
you see a dessert that
looks good, the bakery
that makes it is
always really far away.
Like they'll say the
shop's in Nagoya,
but we live in Saitama.
I know, but I just can't
help watching it though.
Oh well.
[sigh]
Hi, Yuki-chan, good morning.
Hey, are you okay?
Unfortunately, I had to
go to the dentist yesterday.
Oh my gosh, you're still going?
Halfway through the procedure,
I got up and ran away.
[DENTIST]
You'll be sure to tell me
if this hurts, won't you?
[MIYUKI]
It hurts, it hurts!
[DENTIST]
It'll be over soon, I promise.
[MIYUKI]
Okay.
And that's how
my appointment went.
Just hearing you talk
about it makes my teeth hurt.
And he just kept drilling away?
This sucks, not only do
we have to go to classes
during summer break, but
they give us homework too.
It's supposed to
be summer vacation.
Well, it's not like
you actually
do any of your
homework yourself.
For one thing, it's not
like elementary school
or junior high,
there aren't any
research projects
or book reports.
You see, it's easier, you
just have to solve problems.
Oh, remember we had all those
posters and art projects to do?
And with stuff like
that, you could always
get your parents to help
you out when you needed it.
They'd get all gung-ho
about it and
take it over and
finish the thing for ya.
I remember one
time I got an award
for something like
that, a poster I think.
Oh yeah, I think I
remember that one.
And then I told Dad
I won 'cause of him,
and how I thought
he was amazing now,
and that made him happy.
[KAGAMI thinks] If I was him,
I would have been pissed.
[meow]
[GROUP]
"Lucky star."
[laughter]
The next time you're at
the store, pick up a case.
Every time I see
that commercial,
it sort of reminds
me of when I was a kid.
I would read these fairy
tales about candy houses
and gingerbread stuff,
and the one thing I wanted
was to go there and eat
all the candy I could.
I know exactly what you mean,
but it's always like that
when you suddenly get
a lot of something you want,
you get sick of it fast.
No way.
Oh yes way, I'm telling
you it's stinky all year.
Hey, I just
thought of something.
Summer vacation
homework's a total drag
'cause you end up putting
it off until the end,
and then you gotta cram
to get it all done.
[KAGAMI]
New topic, huh?
Yeah it sucks, but
that's how it is.
[KONATA] Right, so
I thought that if
I worked on it a
little bit every day,
I wouldn't have to scramble
to get it all done.
And you're just
now realizing that?
Look, you're a senior,
so whatever you do,
just try to keep
your focus, okay?
[KONATA] No sweat, I'm coming
over tomorrow to copy stuff.
I'm bringing a present.
[KAGAMI]
A little bit every day, huh?
So you're gonna come over here
every day all summer long?
[KONATA] Well, how
'bout every other week?
Oh shut up!
It's so hot, I wanna die.
Hey you, don't die yet,
I got the AC blasting
hot and heavy.
Ah, wake me up when it's over.
Make yourself at home,
why don't ya?
Man, summer's the same
every year, isn't it?
I mean I never wanna
do anything, and then
before you know it, summer
vacation's just passed me by.
Listen, you need to
get up off your butt
and set some goals, you know?
Like being more proactive
about doing your homework.
Yeah, well every year
before vacation starts,
I get to thinking about how
I'm gonna do things different.
You're kidding.
In manga, the "I haven't
done my homework yet" storyline
happens during
summer, isn't that right?
I guess.
Well, when you see
that, doesn't that
make you not wanna
do your homework?
I mean, if everyone else isn't
doing their homework,
why should you?
Because you have to.
If that's what you think,
don't come over to copy.
Is anyone else thirsty?
I'll bring us some
cold barley tea.
Oh, sis, sorry, will
you do me a favor
and bring my math
book from my room?
I'll love you forever.
Okay.
Gah, it's hot.
No one wants to leave
an air conditioned room,
so you wait for
someone else to leave,
and then ask them
to get you stuff.
The only problem
is, it takes a while
before someone
actually decides to leave.
And in winter you
don't wanna get out
from under the
kotatsu, so you ask
whoever stands up
to get you things.
Hey!
Wow, can you believe
how hot it is?
Hi, guys.
Since I'm not gonna
be much help
with the homework
homework today, I figured
I'd pick up some ice
cream for everyone.
There's three different flavors,
so take whichever you want.
All right!
In the marimokkori.
[thinks] How come
it's always at times like this
that you start wanting the
flavors that everyone else got.
I'm reading this manga about
getting into Tokyo University.
Oh I know that one.
It's like when
you're reading it,
you're thinking,
"Yeah, I could probably
get into Tokyo U, if you
work hard like they do."
You're too simple
for your own good.
Even if that method
gets you into Tokyo U,
you need things like, "A,"
friends who will drop
all their classes to join
you, "B," teachers who are
gonna teach classes like
that, and "C," someone to be
in charge, not to mention
all the other elements
you're gonna need
to make it work.
You're right, I guess
it ain't easy after all.
[KAGAMI thinks]
There are too many people
in the world who think
self-improvement is as easy as
it is in manga and TV shows.
Yeah, every time I
plan on making an effort
to study hard, I always end
up getting sleepy instead.
Do either of you guys have any
good tips on how I
could stay awake?
I heard that it's
better if you take
short naps instead of staying
up all night studying.
Yeah, you know, I heard
that from somewhere too,
so I've pretty much
been doing that.
But my naps all go
into overtime, get it?
You have no willpower.
Hey, everyone.
Hi, Yutaka-chan,
how's it going?
Um, can I ask you something?
Go ahead, ask away, Yu-chan.
Don't be shy, ask us
anything you want.
There's this friend
of mine from junior high
who just got a boyfriend
for the first time.
His birthday's coming
up, so she asked me
what I thought she
should get him.
But I don't know what
guys want, do you?
[GIRLS gasp]
[YUTAKA thinks]
Uh-oh, it's an awkward pause.
Well, you could always
try going online, I'm sure
they got a bunch of websites
that can give you advice.
Yeah, why don't you try that?
Or, you could hit up a
couple of threads for advice.
I'll even lend you my computer.
[YUTAKA]
Oh, okay.
I know about that train man guy,
but do lots of people go online
and ask about this stuff?
Yeah, you see it pretty
much everywhere these days.
Wow, I guess it's
anything goes, then.
You know it.
In fact, I bet they
even have the answers
for math tests
floating around online.
Can you believe
how lucky elementary
and junior high school kids are?
[KAGAMI thinks] As technology
and community evolve,
I can't help feeling
that the mind and will
of the users are wasting
away, for example.
Hmm?
[thinks] This is so weird.
I'm just copying homework,
but now that I've got
someone watching me,
suddenly I'm feeling... pride?
Hey, Kagami, when's that
festival of yours happening?
Festival?
What are you talking about?
It's over, it was the
same thing as last year.
No way, why didn't
you say anything?
With college entrance
exams coming up,
we didn't say anything 'cause
we knew you'd wanna go.
Don't be mad,
we didn't go either.
It doesn't always
have to be over here.
You could always
go to the festival
in your own neighborhood
instead, couldn't you?
Oh yeah, when was that
supposed to be happening again?
That figures, some people
go to other festivals,
but they won't be
caught dead in the ones
happening in their own backyard.
What is it, are you
afraid you'll bump into
someone you know
or something, huh?
Man, I don't care if we've got
college entrance
exams, I need a break.
Well, if you'd like
to go, they're having
a firework show near my
house tomorrow evening.
Right on! We're finally gonna
have some fun this summer.
Hm, okay, it'll probably
do us all some good.
Come to think of it,
Minami-chan,
aren't there supposed
to be some fireworks near
-your house tomorrow night?
-Mm-hmm.
Wow, a real Japanese
firework show!
Hey, Minami, let's all
go see the fireworks.
Well, what do
you say, Minami-chan?
[MINAMI] Okay.
Cool, then it's all set, Minami.
Can't wait, Iwasaki-san.
[MINAMI] Yeah.
[thinks]
Wait, "Iwasaki-san"?
It's supposed to be a
pretty famous firework show,
right, Mi-- Iwasaki-san?
[thinks] Aw, it's hard to change
how you say someone's name
after you've gotten used to it.
Wait, I just realized
that it's kinda far,
and it can get really crowded.
Are you gonna be
okay if you go, Yu-chan?
I mean, didn't you
just get over a cold?
And I heard it's supposed
to be really hot tomorrow.
You wanna wait for the next one?
Oh no, you guys don't
have to worry about me,
I'll be fine, this
happens all the time.
I'm class rep for the school
nurse, and I'll be there.
I'll make sure
you're okay, Yutaka.
Oh that's right,
yeah, that's right.
Oh thank you, Minami-chan!
So anyway, it looks
like we're all gonna
go see the fireworks,
and after that it's
right back to the
homework and the studying,
which takes up all my play
time and royally sucks.
Why is everyone so serious?
I sorta see where
they're coming from.
But you know what,
just do what you want.
Back in the day, I used to
drag Kanata all over the place,
and we had a lot of
good times together.
I'd get scolded, but you're only
young once, so I didn't care.
I think I'm gonna
go out and find
a boyfriend and have
some good times too.
I absolutely forbid it!
Boyfriends are off limits!
You don't know what you're
saying, Dad. Calm down, okay?
So do you wanna come see the
fireworks with us, Yu-chan?
Actually, I'm already going.
We're all going to be
meeting up Minami-chan's.
Cool, it's gonna be fun.
Well, see ya later.
Okay, guys, have fun.
The train just pulled in.
[KAGAMI]
Late as usual.
Yeah, sorry.
Neato, you brought Yutaka-chan.
Oh, umm.
Hey! Hey, guys, we're here.
Hey, what's up?
Hey, how's it going?
Oh hey there, Patricia-san.
Did you guys all come
to see the fireworks too?
You look good in a yukata.
Doh.
[thud]
I'm trapped, oh no!
[embarrassed laughter]
[KONATA, YUTAKA]
You're kidding.
Mmm! Ah!
How trippy, Miyuki-san.
I didn't know
Minami-chan was your neighbor.
It is a coincidence.
-Yeah, I'm really surprised.
-[MINAMI] Mm-hmm.
Okay, everyone, bon appetit.
[ALL]
Thank you!
Uh-oh, am I short?
I think I counted right.
But, Mom, were you
counting yourself
along with all the rest of us?
One, and two, and
three, and four,
and five, and six, and
seven, and eight.
Nine.
Oh, silly me, you're right.
[laughter]
[KONATA thinks]
Awesome.
[GIRLS]
Thanks for having us over!
So this is Minami-chan's house?
Whoa, big scary dog!
No, it's okay, it's
a good doggy.
It's not gonna hurt you.
Oh yeah?
Aren't you a big cutie pie?
A big, fat, hairy,
squishy cutie.
Whoa! What'd I do?
Why is it growling?
[YUTAKA thinks]
I guess she's the type
who makes doggies growl.
[boom]
[ALL]
Wow.
Check it out, when
I was a little kid,
I always wondered if
you looked at fireworks
sideways, if they'd
look round that way too.
Oh really?
But I always thought
they looked flat.
Here we go.
You see fireworks on
TV all the time,
but coming out to watch
them live is really cool,
'cause everyone's
having so much fun.
Yeah, you're right.
Something's bugging me, though.
Every time they light
up a big one,
they announce the
name of some store.
They're all, "This one was
brought to you by so and so."
I mean, you know, doesn't
that kinda kill the mood?
Yes, I suppose so.
Whoa, you okay?
You look kinda pale, Yu-chan.
I'll be okay.
I'm just gonna sit for a
while. I'll be fine, really.
Yeah, but...
Don't worry, I'll
stay here with her.
[thinks]
Minami-chan.
Wow.
[laughter]
[MIYUKI]
That was wonderful.
I know, this totally
felt like summer vacation.
[KONATA]
Yeah, but...
How come it can't
be like in manga
where everyone leaves
with beautiful memories?
These mosquitoes chewed me up.
So itchy.
If you scratch, it's
just gonna itch more.
And when you get home
and take off your yukata,
it itches where the sash was.
Yeah, I know.
Pretty.
It really was
pretty, wasn't it?
Thanks for staying.
Sorry about that.
Look, there they are.
Hey, guys!
Are you okay? Did the
skeeters nail you too?
Huh? Oh, no, we were okay,
we didn't get bitten.
Well, I guess there's
people who get bit
by mosquitoes, and
there's people who don't.
You're so lucky.
Maybe the skeeters didn't
wanna ruin the mood over here.
[GROUP]
"Lucky Star."
[AKIRA]
"Lucky Channel"!
Hiya, luckies, and
I'm your navigator,
Akira Kogami,
at your service!
And I'm her assistant,
Daisuke Ono, at your service.
Did you know that today is
"Lucky Channel's" 20th episode?
So I guess you're
not a crow today.
And it looks like
you're not a dog today.
Okay, let's go to
Fuji, see if he's alive.
Ow, I wonder where
our intrepid adventurer,
Shiraishi-kun, is
right about now.
Wow, Mt. Fuji's so pretty!
Well, guess that's a wrap.
Okay, goodbye.
Bye-ni.
[DAISUKE]
Uh, Shiraishi-kun?
Shiraishi-kun!
[MAN speaking Japanese]
One, two, three, four.
[vocalizing tune]
[singing in Japanese]
[laughter]
[AYANO] On the next
episode of "Lucky Star"...
[MISAO]
Misao here.
[AYANO]
Ayano here.
[MISAO] Ayano,
Hiiragi's so cold-hearted.
She's always over
at the midget's class.
[AYANO]
Now, now.
[MISAO]
Aren't we cool enough?
Why does Hiiragi forsake us?
[AYANO]
Next time, "Pandora's Box."
[MISAO]
Now Ayano's ignoring me.