[KONATA]
Okay, let's do this.
[MIYUKI]
Sure, let's go.
[TSUKASA]
Grr!
[KAGAMI]
Quit screwin' and start!
[theme music playing]
[KAGAMI]
Oh, that's right.
It's time to wear
the summer uniform.
I bet Konata's gonna show
up in her winter uniform.
There's always
someone in every class
who forgets the switch.
[door opens]
[TSUKASA]
Good morning, Sis!
And that someone is my sister.
Oh, darn it!
I forgot to send my
entry into The Tele
for that giveaway of theirs.
I was kinda hopin' to win that
apron from Love Apron too,
darn it.
It sounds like you
don't have enough love.
Huh?
You forgot about it because
you don't have enough love
for the show.
Whatever, I've been really busy
with all my committee stuff.
Besides, I also had
to study for exams.
No, no, no, no, no.
Those are excuses.
I've never forgotten
to send mine in.
Stop comparing yourself to me!
You got time 'cause
you goof off all day!
Besides, the way you
said that ticks me off!
Ah ha!
How does anyone win
a contest like that, anyway?
One word, and that's love.
Whatever,
I'm a woman with no love!
There it is!
Well, if you send in
a normal-looking postcard,
you're never gonna win anything.
[TSUKASA]
What do you mean, Kona-chan?
[KONATA]
I design it so it'd get picked!
Design how?
The first basic step
is neat penmanship.
Then you have to make a postcard
that attracts the attention of
the person who's picking 'em.
For example?
For example, take a highlighter
and draw a border
around the edges
of the postcard.
Ahh, that makes it stand out!
Then draw a picture on it
that's got something to do
with the prize
you're trying to win.
A picture, huh?
Hmm.
But I can't draw too good.
Not to worry, Tsukasa.
Send in a bunch of postcards
and overwhelm 'em with volume!
[giggles]
I know I can do that.
Although, if you
do it that way,
you can't use a computer
and you can't just make one
and make a bunch of copies.
You have to write
each entry by hand.
And it's gotta be
at least 100.
100?
Sure, it's normal to
send 100 postcards.
That's gonna cost a fortune!
But winning takes
lots of time and money.
Winning is all about
how bad you want it.
Okay, but at this point,
wouldn't it just be
cheaper to buy it?
You can't buy the feeling
you get when you win something.
[sighs]
Can 100 postcards
fit in a mailbox?
No, don't put all of
them in the same mailbox.
You put a few in this one.
You put a few in that one.
Just do that
every day for a week.
Really?
Yeah, 'cause if you send in
a stack of cards all at once,
whoever is choosing will
notice and shove yours aside.
It's a sign of desperation,
so it's not a good
idea to do that.
But sometimes it
really pays off.
Then what do you
think I should do?
Like I said, you need love!
Yeah, yeah.
Anyway, if you
really wanna win stuff,
there's always
those free handouts
or those flyers in newspapers.
Just keep your eyes open for
the drawings that don't have
too big a following
and you're set.
Then your chances of
winning are pretty high.
[giggles]
I'm gonna try that.
[KAGAMI]
Where's the love in that?
[KONATA]
Hmm.
I just noticed something.
You guys look different,
for twins, that is.
Of course. We're fraternal
twins, not identical twins.
You can tell us apart just
like ordinary sisters.
Identical twins look
the same but fraternal twins
come from two different eggs,
so they differ in
appearance and personality.
Oh, I get it.
That explains why
Tsukasa's really laid-back,
and you're so vicious.
What'd you say?
[laughs] You see?
Maybe if you do your
hair the same way,
you'll look more alike
than you'd think.
[KAGAMI]
Kona-chan!
[KONATA]
No way, Kagami can't do cute.
Oh, shut up!
And keep your kooky fantasies
and comments to yourself!
Hey, are you guys telepathic?
Huh?
[KONATA]
I heard that even if twins
are raised separately,
they end up having
similar lives.
If they get married,
they'll pick the same type
of people to marry.
I even heard sometimes
twins marry other twins.
Weird, huh?
It's even weirder when
one twin's in danger,
and the other one gets a feeling
something's wrong, even though
the other twin's far away.
That's a whole lot of
phenomena, isn't it?
So you guys have
to be telepathic.
Come on, let's try it out.
Hokey-pokey--
Okay, you read
way too much manga.
There is ManaKana.
ManaKana?
Yeah, them.
They said there were things
about them that were different.
Like how Mana's the one
who's really cautious,
and Kana's the one
who's optimistic.
And they said that when
they sing they can tell
their voices are different.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
ManaKana always thought
they're from different eggs,
you know, fraternal.
But a little while ago,
they found out they're
twins from the same egg.
What? They're identical?
Yeah, why are you so
surprised about that?
I heard the
definition of identical
and fraternal twins had
been changed recently.
You think it's possible
that you and Tsukasa came from
the same egg?
Let's see, how're you
guys are the same?
I got it, both of you
like sweets, right?
Yeah, I do.
Sure.
Both of you are
also left-handed.
Yeah.
That's right.
What's your favorite color?
I like white.
Mine's black.
That would be
the color of your souls.
What was that?
[stomach growling]
I guess all this talk
about eggs and sausages
and stuff got me hungry.
[KAGAMI]
We weren't talking about food.
Ugh, it's so muggy in here.
It's not even that crowded
in here and we're sweating!
Guess it's that
time of year again.
Hot!
I wish someone would
turn on the air conditioning.
[KONATA moans]
Ah!
Don't do that!
[KONATA]
So hot!
Ladybug Samba,
punk rock version.
So I just found out
that a cousin of mine's
gonna be getting
married this month.
Wow, she's gonna
be a June Bride!
That's nice!
[KONATA]
Tell me something.
How did such a wet and
gloomy month ever become
synonymous with
weddings and happiness?
Uh. [giggles]
You're wondering why
the month of June is
synonymous with
weddings and happiness?
[BOTH]
Uh-huh.
In Roman mythology,
the goddess Juno,
where the word June comes from,
was regarded as the protector
of women and marriage.
The Greek's version of Juno,
Hera, was the goddess
of anything related to
marriage and childbirth.
That's why it's said
that whoever gets married
in June will be blessed by
the goddess and have a marriage
filled with happiness.
Oh.
Yeah, but isn't Hera
supposed to be Zeus' wife?
Yes, that's right, she is.
[KONATA]
I always pictured Hera
to be the jealous type,
'cause Zeus was always
foolin' around on her,
so I'm not feeling
the happy here.
[sighs]
When you get married,
do you wanna wear
a dress or a kimono?
I'd really like
to wear a dress.
It's what I've dreamed of
since I was a little girl.
Hmm, maybe I'd
like to wear a dress.
But I also think
a kimono would be nice.
Hmm, I wish I could wear both.
They have miniskirts now
and all kinds
of colorful wedding dresses too.
Wow, miniskirt
wedding dresses.
That could be really cute if
it had some kind of frilly
design on the hem.
So many dreams
and so many frills.
Oh my.
Tsukasa's like Angel Salvia.
No, actually your hair makes
you look more like Daisy.
So you should be
wearing a miniskirt
and your top should be yellow.
[BOTH]
Huh?
I think Tsukasa-san would
look good in a miniskirt.
You do?
Sure, the outfit's important,
but the kind of person you
end up marrying is too.
It could be a childhood friend,
or some girl from a rich family.
That's a tough
decision to make 'cause
one's got the money
and the ability
to cast magic spells
like [beep] and [beep],
which always come in handy.
But if you're after true love--
Then, Bianca is the one!
Whoa, Kagami, when
did you get so pure?
I thought you'd go for
the girl with the money.
I'm out of comebacks.
Hiya, Konata!
[KONATA]
Hm?
You know that game I borrowed?
I need help getting
past this one level.
Whoa, not so fast
there, Kagamin.
Don't you think it's more
fun when you figure things
out like that on your own?
Hmm, yeah, you have a point.
You know it.
It's fun to figure things
out on your own, uh-huh.
So I guess you won't be
copying my homework anymore,
will you?
[KONATA groans]
Hm.
You know those detectives
in manga and TV shows?
Isn't it weird how they
keep coming across murders
all the time?
Guys like Conan &amp; Kindaichi.
If they didn't,
they wouldn't have
any mysteries to solve,
would they?
Really?
'Cause they could go
after normal cases too.
Normal, how?
They could have a case
where they run all over Japan
looking for a missing person.
Tracking someone down's
got a lot of
game-like aspects to it.
It's got thrills.
It's got suspense.
Yeah, I guess.
A case where a husband
wants his wife tailed
'cause he thinks she's cheating.
Looking for a lost pet
could be a case.
Yeah, right?
Yeah, but do you think it'd
be any fun to watch that?
Well no, I guess it
wouldn't be any fun at all.
You see?
You're right.
Real-life cases don't
have the clever tricks,
bizarre situations
or show-stopping finales
that the crimes in manga
and anime have.
Hmm.
You're right, they don't.
Like faking fingerprints,
or scrubbing a crime scene
so luminol won't
pick up anything.
Huh?
Making it so the forensics
team can't solve it.
Well, the police don't
want someone copying
the perfect crime,
so they censor that
stuff from manga and TV.
Yeah, or maybe
perfect crimes happen all the
time but they don't tell us.
Maybe they're never solved.
Ever!
Careful talking like that!
Someone might hear you.
[TSUKASA]
Don'tcha hate how
there's been so
much rain lately?
Yeah, I know. [sighs]
I remember when I was
little I used to like
rainy days a lot.
I never liked them 'cause
if you go out, you get wet,
and then you can't hang
your clothes out to dry.
How come you liked
rainy days so much?
[KONATA]
Because if it rained,
there wouldn't be
any baseball on TV,
and I'd get to
watch all my anime.
[TSUKASA]
I should have known
you'd say something like that.
[KONATA]
Yeah, but now they've got
stadiums with domes.
[GIRLS]
Lucky Star.
[groaning]
What's the matter?
You know how in
manga and anime,
they've got really
smart characters
and really stupid characters
and they're both going
to the same school?
I've had enough outta you!
Shut up!
If you don't like it, why
don't you get lost, you dork!
I always thought that was
kinda strange, don't you?
I noticed something too.
The other day I watched
this anime where the teacher
and the students all
looked the same age,
and it was totally weird.
Heck, the teacher
looked younger!
Uh, ma'am...
Yes, Tachina-san?
That's not surprising
'cause the world's always
had a fascination
with stuff like that.
People who look
young and act old,
or people who look
old and act young. You know?
[KAGAMI]
Uh, no.
You never question it.
You just go with the flow.
It's a lot weirder
to have students
with different test scores
in the same class,
don't you think?
[KAGAMI]
You're right.
I couldn't agree with you more.
And since you brought it up,
Konata, I was always surprised
that you got accepted
to this school.
You're so good at
pulling all-nighters,
maybe that's how you
passed the entrance exam.
[laughing]
[darkly chuckles]
[gasps] Wait!
Is that how she did it?
Nah, just kidding.
That's way too much
work for an all-nighter.
Oh, thanks goodness.
I'm surprised you
actually studied for it.
Did a new quiz game come
out for the DS or something?
No, but my dad did give
me a couple of conditions.
For a D rank school,
I'd get a Pippin,
a C rank, a 3DO,
and a B rank's a PS2.
[KAGAMI]
Man, Izumi's dad sure knows
what buttons to push.
I just thought of something.
Huh?
Huh.
[sighs]
[KONATA]
I'm surprised Tsukasa's
in the same school as us.
I can't believe you'd
be so blunt about it!
[MAN]
K.O.
All right!
Uh, damn!
I can't beat her
in a fighting game.
She spends too much
time playing these.
Pick another game.
Even if it isn't a fighter,
I'll take you on!
Oho, sure about that?
Then how about we
play a quiz game next!
Ugh, you're kidding!
It's a lousy quiz game
and she totally beat me!
No way.
[chuckles]
[KAGAMI]
Maybe she went and memorized
all the questions and answers.
Her memory's sharp as a tack
when it comes to games!
So what are we
gonna play next?
You in a hurry or something?
Hey, that's weird,
where is it?
Didn't you used to
have an easy party game
that you liked to play?
Hey, how do you know
so much about what games
I've got in my house, huh?
Well, I just thought
it was something
even you could beat me at.
[groans]
Really stinky!
[giggles]
Hey, Kagami,
how come you're not eating
any of these snacks?
Usually, you gobble 'em all up.
No reason, I just
don't want any.
Oh, I get it.
You're on a summer
diet, aren't ya?
No, I'm not.
It's nothing like that.
No one to show your
bathing suit to anyway.
Shut up!
You don't need to go there!
Oh, that's right.
You guys were born
on the Star Festival.
It's almost your
birthday, isn't it?
Yeah, so what?
Oh, Kona-chan, you
remembered our birthday!
Mm-hmm.
We're gonna be seventeen.
Seventeen's the year
before the unlucky one.
What do you mean?
What's gonna happen?
Seventeen's when unlucky
things start happening
and it's right before
the real unlucky year.
Uh-huh.
So now, with my seventeenth
birthday coming up,
I'm getting a little worried.
I ended up buying power
stones and talismans
to ward off evil
and other stuff.
Well, at least you're
having fun, right?
Yeah, right.
I bought so much,
I got to the point--
Yeah, now that we have one
of those reckless charms,
I mean, one of those
cautious charms.
[KONATA]
She said reckless charm.
[chuckles]
She's all, "That's enough.
"Safe childbirth!
Safe driving!
"Be careful now!"
Heh heh heh.
[KAGAMI] Yeah, yeah.
Oh, that's right.
Did you guys know that
your birthday happens
to be on Ponytail Day?
Uh-uh, I didn't know.
Why is July seventh
Ponytail Day?
'Cause in the legend
of the Star Festival,
Vega had a ponytail.
That's why.
Boy, that's stretching it.
And did you know that
there's this thing called
the Japan Ponytail Association?
And that every year they pick
a celebrity who they think
would look good in a ponytail
and give 'em an award for it?
Wow, I didn't know.
That's silly.
I mean, doesn't everybody
look good in a ponytail?
Oh, you think so, huh?
[chuckles]
Oh, I didn't think it
would work with my hair.
How is it?
[KONATA]
Great!
A small ponytail is
really cute on you.
Kona-chan, you look great!
I think you totally
pull off that look.
Yeah, you think so?
Mm, I really do.
[laughing]
Wow, you look so--
Yeah, you look so--
Okay! Fine.
It doesn't work on me.
I get it.
You look manly like a samurai!
Drop it already!
You know how drunks go
around with their neckties
wrapped around their heads?
You guys have any
idea why they do that?
Yeah, I do.
See, when a drunk
loosens his tie,
he's gotta pull it over
his head to take it off.
The tie gets stuck,
and there you have it.
[KONATA]
Oh.
What's even weirder are the
drunks that stagger around
carrying take-out boxes.
What's up with that?
Take-out boxes?
You know, Kato-chan
carries 'em in The Drifters.
I still don't get it.
That's the visual
of the typical drunk.
They've always got the
necktie around their heads
and they're carrying take-out.
I don't know why that is.
[KAGAMI]
You see?
Vega and Altair.
I hope they meet this year.
[TSUKASA]
Twinkle, twinkle, twinkle.
[KONATA]
I'm just hopin' that
your reckless charm works.
[KAGAMI]
Yeah, whatever.
The Comp-Fest is in
the middle of a huge
Quo card giveaway.
You know, you've been collecting
those Quo cards forever,
but I don't think I've
ever seen you use them.
Hm? Oh, I don't use 'em.
But, why do you
collect them, then?
When something comes out
that's related to
a show or manga you like,
don't you wanna have it,
as a collector and as a fan?
Okay, but you're supposed to
use those things, aren't you?
You can't use them, ever!
You have to store
them someplace safe.
It really pisses me off
when I see all those people
using those cards
like common money.
These are sacred things.
They're meant to be bought
and carefully archived.
You're not supposed to use 'em,
and it's out of the question
to go and auction 'em!
If you do, you'll fail both
as a fan and as a collector!
Okay.
Didn't think you get
so worked up about it.
Here's how I do it.
I always get three cards
for the collection.
First off, I pull
the most pristine one
and lock it away for
eternity in a special case.
The second card's for me to keep
so I can look at it
every now and then.
And the third one?
It's a loaner.
You're kidding.
Kagami, isn't it human
nature to want two or three of
something that you
really, really like?
Come on, aren't
you the same way?
Huh?
Uhh.
Fine, whatever. So you don't.
I'm an otaku.
I'm totally weird.
I'm a weirdo.
No, I, I didn't say that.
I think I sort of know what
you're saying, I guess.
Tsukasa,
you seem like the type
who'd be popular with boys,
but I never hear
'em talk about you.
[TSUKASA gasps]
She's kinda on the plain side,
so she doesn't really stand out.
Mm.
I think it's 'cause she's got
a scary sister guarding her!
You say something?
[laughs]
Maybe it's not
because I'm plain.
Maybe it's because you guys
and Yuki-chan are more unique.
Yeah, that Miyuki-san, she
sure is smart and pretty.
She's got an awesome figure!
She wears glasses,
she hates the dentist,
and she's clumsy in a cute way--
[KAGAMI]
Hey, you're getting
weird on us again.
You know I've never heard any
rumors about Miyuki either.
Maybe guys are
scared to talk to her
'cause she's so pretty.
Oh, I doubt that.
She's totally nice and
gets along with everyone.
I guess you're right.
Hey, maybe she gets
asked out all the time.
And then she turns
all of them down?
I don't know, maybe she does.
Maybe she doesn't even
know she's being asked out
when they ask her.
Oh, that might be it.
You know, Yuki-chan's
sort of clueless,
so maybe guys need
to be more direct
when they ask her out.
I swear!
Your class has gotta be
filled with a bunch of
scared little boys.
You're telling me that there's
not one of them with the guts
or passion to go up to Miyuki
and ask her out on a date?
I don't think so.
Maybe what the school needs
are more maniacs in class.
[BOTH]
Huh?
Oh, yeah, girls
like Miyuki-san
are much more appealing
to the maniacs.
Maniacs, huh?
[laughing]
[MIYUKI]
Oh no!
I didn't realize it
was already this late.
Sorry, but I think
I have to go now.
[KAGAMI]
Oh, already?
[MIYUKI]
Yes, I'm sorry,
but don't mind me.
I'll see you later, okay?
Well, I'm off then.
[TSUKASA]
Have a good rest of the day!
[KONATA]
Later!
Where was I?
Oh, yeah.
So here's the end of the story.
This guy got up and then he--
[ALL]
Huh?
Oh no.
Excuse me!
[BOTH]
Yeah!
I'm so sorry.
Eh, don't worry about it.
Yeah, that always happens!
It's no big deal.
Even I've done it before.
I've done it too.
See, it happens to
everybody at least once.
You've done it too, right?
Never.
[KAGAMI] Uh.
And that, Kagami, was
an example of moe-ism.
Miyuki-san, good job, girl!
[GIRLS] Lucky Star.
[snoring]
[AKIRA]
Lucky channel!
Hiya, Luckies!
Yeah!
It's time for more super
fun on Lucky Channel!
[giggles]
And I'm your navigator,
Akira Kogami, and--
Oh, and I'm Minoru Shiraishi,
Akira-sama's assistant.
How's it going?
Yeah, sure.
You know,
today's a really special day
because it's officially...
Ta-da!
Our third episode together!
What do you think,
Shiraishi-san?
Are you getting the hang of it?
Yeah, no, not really.
I'm sorry.
Aww.
Looks like Shiraishi-san's
having a hard time opening
up to me, and that
makes me really sad!
You're even sitting further
away from me than usual.
Huh?
Guess this means you
don't like me anymore.
Sob!
Whoa! Hey, that's not true!
Look!
Scoot.
Hi! I wanna start this episode
with a twinkle today!
You see, we're gonna
start doing something
that'll make all you
fans out there happy!
That's right!
Today's our first
installment of Lucky Star
featured character
introductions!
Bom bom bom bom!
Yes, today, we'd like
to introduce you to
Miss Miyuki Takara.
Let's see.
She's a class committee-chair.
She's beautiful.
She's gentle and kind.
She's kanullabul?
[SHIRAISHI]
Knowledgeable.
Knowledgeable, good at
sports and super human, too.
Shiraishi-san, you know a lot
about Miyuki-san, don't you?
That's right,
I know all about her.
She's a really nice person.
Besides that,
she wears glasses,
which makes her even more
pretty, as you can see.
You know, when someone's
as beautiful as she is,
you feel like you can't
really approach her.
However, she's actually
very easy-going
and will talk to any--
[AKIRA]
Wow, it would be nice
if you were that talkative
on my radio show.
Uh.
Ugh, you just can't stop talking
about that girl, can you?
Well, uhh, I know her, and
I was just telling everyone--
Sure you were.
Miyuki-san was it?
Miyuki with the pretty face,
Miyuki with the big boobs.
Every fault's an aspect of moe.
Ohh, I'm so jealous.
Come to think of it, don't
the maniacs go for her type?
Sure, she's got the maniacs,
but I've still got my
pedophiles so take that.
Oh no!
It's time to say
goodbye, isn't it?
I hope you had
a super happy fun time!
We wanna know what you
think about the show,
and I wanna know what
you think about me.
So, send those cards
and letters, please?
Yeah, well, we hope to
see you again next time!
See ya later!
Okay, so what's she really like?
[SHIRAISHI]
Well, like I described her.
[AKIRA]
Oh, please.
You mean she's not
backstage burning through
a pack of smokes
every 15 minutes?
[SHIRAISHI]
Oh, no,
she's not like you, she's--
[AKIRA]
Uh-huh.
[screams]
[TSUKASA]
That was so cool.
[MIYUKI]
It certainly was a unique song.
[KAGAMI]
I'd like to hear a song
that normal people know.
[KONATA]
Oh, you'll know
the next one, Kagami.
Promise.
[KAGAMI]
Huh?
[KONATA]
Intro's comin' up!
Try to guess it.
[KAGAMI]
It's not gonna be
another weird song, is it?
[MIYUKI]
Hmm, what is this?
[TSUKASA]
I don't know.
[KONATA]
Kagamin, your answer please.
[KAGAMI]
Oh, FMP, Full Metal Panic!
[TSUKASA]
Oh.
[KONATA]
And it's your
favorite version, Kagamin.
Fumoffu!
[KAGAMI]
Oh, really?
[KONATA]
No, I just read the book
and got a little.
[female singing in Japanese]
[TSUKASA]
Kona-chan, you're good!
[MIYUKI]
She has such
a mature singing voice!
[KAGAMI]
She's just
impersonating the singer.
So, how about you guys?
What are you gonna sing?
[MIYUKI]
I'm not sure if
there's anything I can sing.
[TSUKASA]
I don't think
I know any of these songs.
[KAGAMI]
Like it matters!
Come on, Konata's gonna
be singing this stuff
all night if we
don't pick anything.
Pick something!
[MIYUKI]
Okay, I'll try.
I'm not confident about
my singing though.
[KAGAMI]
It's all right.
We're the only ones listening,
so just pick a song
and have some fun!
[MIYUKI]
Really?
Okay.
[MAN]
On the next episode
of Lucky Star...
Tsukasa here!
So, um, the other day
I laughed so hard
I couldn't breathe. [giggles]
I thought I was gonna pass out.
And the next morning at school
[screams] I'm out of time?!
Next time,
A Question of Motivation!
[MAN]
Look forward to it!