[KONATA]
Okay, let's do this!
[MIYUKI]
Sure. Let's go!
[TSUKASA]
Grr!
[KAGAMI]
Quit screwin' around and start!
[MAN]
On your mark, get set...
Wow! Kona-chan,
that was so amazing!
You're so good at sports,
and I always wondered,
how come you don't
join a team or anything?
'Cause if I got on a team
and started playing sports,
I'd miss all of my
prime-time anime shows.
Hey, Tsukasa, which end of
a choco-cornet do you eat first?
Huh? Um...
I think I start at the head.
Really?
So which side of this
thing's the head anyway?
The fat part,
or the skinny?
[TSUKASA] I always thought
that this end of it,
the thin one was the head.
[KONATA]
Oh!
See, I always thought the
fatter end was the head.
So, why do you think the
thinner end's the head?
Doesn't it look like a seashell?
Why do you think
it's the fatter end?
I always thought, it looked
more like a caterpillar.
[TSUKASA]
A caterpillar?
Yeah, but when you
think about it,
I guess a seashell's
a much better image.
Um, you know...
There's another way to eat it.
Tear off the thin end
and dip it in the chocolate
cream on the fat end.
[TSUKASA giggles]
Good idea!
Ah! It figures you'd know that.
You're so smart, Miyuki-san!
Well, not really. Everyone has
their own way of eating one.
How about cream puffs?
How do you eat them?
Huh? How do I eat a cream puff?
That's easy. I split it
in half horizontally,
then I take the top half
and dip it into the cream
in the bottom part.
Then, after most of
the cream is gone,
I start eating the bottom.
I find that if I
eat it that way,
it keeps the cream
from spurting out,
and I have equal amounts of
cream and pastry in each bite.
Huh...
What do you do about the ones
that have both
custard and cream?
Do you have a system
to eat those?
Do you mix the flavors together?
No, I don't have a system
for those per se...
Wait, how exactly does
one mix the flavors?
Uh, just asking.
When do you eat the strawberry
on a strawberry shortcake,
or a chestnut on top
of a Mont Blanc?
Let's see now...
It depends on the amount
of strawberries
that are sandwiched between
the layers of sponge cake.
With the strawberries,
the whipped cream,
and the sponge cake,
I pace it so that I can get a
bit in each and every bite.
So getting to the strawberry
on top of the cake
is always different for me.
Hmm. That's a solid move.
When I eat it, I always save
the strawberry on top for last.
Sometimes I get so full
that I can't eat it.
And other times,
someone in my family comes
along and takes it away.
And that's why you should always
eat your favorite part first.
Come to think, I've
never seen anyone take
Kagami's strawberry
away from her.
That's Kagami for ya.
She's sharp.
Here's one. Can you eat the
very last bite of an ice pop
without dropping it?
Wait, you drop it?
If you don't eat it
the right way...
...it falls off, doesn't it?
Yes.
How you do it,
Kona-chan?
I suck it off the stick.
Oh...
Or maybe you could
just turn it around
while you eat it, like this.
Oh, that's a good idea.
And then there's
soft-serve ice cream,
which I'm not very fond of.
Huh? Whats wrong with it?
I hate how you're always left
with an empty cone
at the end of it.
You're right! There's never any
ice cream left, just the cone.
[KONATA] I always try
to push the ice cream
further and further down
into the cone as I eat.
But how in the world
do you do that?
While I eat, l do a
push and shove thing.
A push and shove thing?
You try to balance
everything out, don't you?
I suppose.
Oh, here's another one.
How do you eat curried rice?
Do you mix the curry
with the rice?
No, but I do try to
have equal amounts
of curry and rice left
over for my last bite.
I like mixing it up.
How do you eat it?
It all depends on the curry.
If I pour some sauce on it,
or drop a raw egg on top,
then I mix it up.
You put sauce on curry?
Oh, yeah, it's tasty.
[MIYUKI] Do you put
sauce on fried eggs too?
Nope, I put soy
sauce on fried eggs.
Oh! See, when I use that,
I use mayonnaise.
Mayonnaise on fried eggs
but not on hard-boiled eggs?
Mh-hm.
You know mayonnaise is good
with pretty much every egg dish.
You put it on curry too?
Mh-hm.
I put mayo on white
rice and on beef bowls.
It goes good with
that sweet broth.
Oh! And on
parent-child bowls too!
You know how the chicken's the
parent and the egg's the child?
And how mayonnaise is
made from eggs too?
I just put a little
blob of it on top
and I call that
the Relative Bowl.
[KONATA]
Hmm.
And I used to really
hate natto beans,
but if I put some mayonnaise
on 'em, I can eat 'em.
Ach, I can't imagine that.
Oh, but the tastiest
thing has to be
when you put mayonnaise right
on top of some soft-boiled eggs.
Even the fried eggs are
half-cooked at my house.
Really?
Yep. That's just how
my dad likes his eggs.
I guess it's because he always
liked to suck on the yolk.
So, if you fry the egg too much,
then the yolk gets too hard
and my dad can't
suck the yolk out.
So, how do you eat
chicken skewers?
What do you mean "how"?
Do you eat it
right off the skewer?
Or do you pull it
off with chopsticks?
Let me see.
When I'm alone, I'll
eat it off the skewer.
but when I'm eating in
public, or with company,
I'll use chopsticks
to pull it off.
Yeah! And don't you feel weird
when there's only one
piece left on the plate?
Yes, the last bite
certainly makes things
awkward at the table.
And then it gets later and
later and no one eats it.
It gets all dry and stale
and it's not lookin' so tasty,
and no one really
wants to eat it,
but they don't want
to say anything,
and then the waiter comes
over to take the plate
and you're like, "Woah,
we're still eating that!"
In the end, we all go home
without eating that last bite.
Oh, that's such a waste.
I feel sorry for it...
Oh! With Korean barbecue,
I feel sorry for the meat
that's left on the grill
that turns to charcoal.
Well, at a Korean barbecue,
you're always eating and
chatting at the same time,
so you get a little distracted.
And when you're grilling beef
tongue with green onions,
that cooks really fast.
Oh, you're so right.
It's already done cooking
by the time you flip
it over, isn't it?
Wait, you flip it over?
Huh?
You flip it over?
You should never flip beef
tongue with green onions.
Why shouldn't I flip it?
'Cause if you flip it over,
all the green onions on top
will fall into the grill!
Yeah, I guess you're right.
You don't need to
flip it over at all
You roast it on one side,
and the heat cooks
it all the way through.
I get it. I guess I'll
do that from now on.
You absolutely,
positively never flip it.
Never flip it.
Ever.
Ohh...
Oh, which end of a
choco-cornet is the head?
The fat end or the skinny end?
[gasps]
[KAGAMI]
Such a bad boy!
What's with all the
kidnappings lately?
I mean, these guys
imprison girls
and force them to call
them "Master" and stuff.
It's sick.
Oh...
I think it's about guys
playing way too many
dating sims and erotic games.
The master/slave thing
is a pretty common
scenario, ya know.
Oh yeah, like you'd
know all about that.
Wait, you're in the
eleventh grade.
How do you know about
erotic game scenarios?!
[gasps]
[ALL]
Lucky Star!
[KONATA]
You're amazing.
You're always at
the top of the class.
[MIYUKI]
Huh?
[KONATA] Don't you have
any faults, Miyuki-san?
It's a little embarrassing,
but I guess I tend to think
about things too much.
So much that I end
up spacing out.
I Sometimes cut my finger
using the veggie slicer,
Sometimes, I'll trip on
my feet and fall down.
Or a corner of my tote bag will
get caught in the train's door.
Wow.
Woah, hold it. Miyuki-san,
those aren't called faults,
People call those moe points!
Huh? Moe points?
Clumsy is sexy.
[TSUKASA]
Kona-chan,
what have you been
thinking this whole time?
How come you wear glasses?
I mean, you're really pretty,
but you can only appeal to a
tiny section of the fan base.
Ha. Appeal to.
Besides the whole
popularity thing,
don't glasses actually
make your vision worse?
How come you never switch
to wearing contacts?
Well, it's a little
embarrasing to admit
now that I'm in high school,
but I suppose you could say...
...I'm afraid of contact lenses!
Actually, I'm pretty scared
to put anything into my eyes.
I can't even open
my eyes underwater.
[KONATA]
Damn, she's a natural airhead.
A total cutie pie!
Hey, isn't that
Miyuki-san over there?
Huh?
[KONATA]
I wonder if she broke down
and decided to
get some contacts.
[gasps]
[KONATA] I guess
she's probably better off
with the glasses after all.
[TSUKASA]
That must've hurt.
[KONATA]
And she's like that naturally.
Kagami's staying home 'cause
she's got a cold, huh?
Mh-hm.
But at least she's only got a
cold and not the flu, you know?
Thankfully, I'm stupid,
so I dont have to worry
about catchin' flus and stuff.
[chuckles] I heard that
works with a cold
but I didn't know it was
the same for the flu.
[KONATA] I thought the flu was
the deluxe version of the cold.
You saying that colds and
flus are two different things?
[TSUKASA] I-I guess I think
they're different things.
Or maybe the aren't.
I dont know anymore.
I'm kinda confused now.
Oh! The difference between
influenza and a cold?
Mm, mm.
Let's me see now...
Influenza is a viral illness,
with many symptoms such
as fever and muscle aches.
If it's not treated,
there's a risk of more
serious complications.
On the other hand,
the symptoms of a cold
are sore throat
and a runny nose,
and the fever
doesn't run as high.
Those are just a few
of the symptoms
that differ from the flus.
Huh...
So, to answer your question,
yes, they are
different illnesses.
Oh, really...
Oh, but then again,
colds and flus do share
many common traits.
I guess one could say a flu
is sort of a scaled-up version
of a cold, after all.
I knew it!
Hmm...
Why are you looking so
serious, huh, Kona-chan?
Ah, it's nothin', just somethin'
that's been bugging me
since our conversation
this morning.
Huh? The one about
colds and flus?
You didn't disagree with me
when I said I was stupid,
did you Tsukasa--?
Wait, It's not like that!
I didn't mean--
[MRS. HIIRAGI]
Hello, Konata-chan. Come in.
[TSUKASA]
She came by to visit Sis.
[MRS. HIIRAGI] Oh, thanks
for coming to see her.
[KONATA] No worries,
I'll just go up. Thanks!
[door opens]
[KONATA] Haha, Kagami sure
is cute when she's sleeping,
isnt she?
How'd you get into my room? What
are you doing here? Get out!
Huh? You came
by for a visit?
All the way out here to see me?
Yup, that's right.
Oh, no. I appreciate the thought
but I'd feel terrible
if you caught this thing.
[KAGAMI]
Oh, this makes me so happy.
She's all worried about me
because of that new virus
that's going around.
I thought the only things
she cared about
were games and anime.
But now, this is so touching.
[KAGAMI]
Hm?
'Kay, so, uh, I'm gonna
copy that homework
we got the other day.
But you don't have to get up,
you cute little
sleepy face, you.
[KAGAMI]
Out!
[MRS. HIIRAGI]
Kagami!
Miyuki-chan's come
over to visit you!
[sighs] Okay.
May I come in?
Oh, I hope this isn't
too much trouble.
Not at all, you should
be resting though.
-Here's a little something.
--Thank you.
I'm feeling a lot better now.
I took some medicine,
so my fever's down.
--Here.
--Wow!
You brought me flowers and
fruit! You shouldn't have!
Come on, sit down.
Oh.Thank you. I will.
I had thought of coming by
to visit you with Izumi-san.
Unfortunately, I just couldn't
seem to find any time.
I'm sorry.
No, really, it's fine.
Ah! I almost forgot,
I brought you the minutes from
the last committee meeting.
Oh. Well, thank you!
Have a look at it when you can,
but only when you're feeling
up to it. There's no rush.
[KAGAMI]
Mm.
There's that,
and I have the budget
requests for each club here.
What else was there?
Let me see now...
Let's see...
Oh, but you're not
feeling well right now!
I should go home
so you can rest.
Now this is what a
visit should be like!
What do you mean? What happened?
Well, you know how
Konata came by yesterday?
That's what happened.
Maybe that was just
Izumi-san's funny little way
of showing you she cared.
Perhaps the bit with the
homework was her attempt
at cheering you up, Kagami-san.
And maybe she was trying
not to wake you up,
but couldn't help
noticing you as you slept.
And that would certainly explain
how she saw you sleeping.
[KAGAMI] I never would've
thought of it that way!
Is this girl a saint
or something?
Oh, I just realized,
I haven't seen
Tsukasa-san today.
Morning.
Are you feeling any better
today, Sis? You need anything?
Look at that.
My sister isn't even sick and
she's more relaxed than I am.
Well, it's not like I'm
always sleeping in this late.
Really! Today's like "spring
sleep dawn" something or other.
Oh! By the way, good morning!
Oh, I know how that is.
Lately, even I'm having trouble
waking up in the morning.
Yeah, I know, and I've
been so sleepy lately.
Me too. It's especially
warm out today,
so that doesn't help either.
Isn't it though?
You really can't help it.
Wasn't it warm a couple
days ago during our break?
It was
When I woke up, it was
just starting to get dark.
I spent the whole day sleeping.
Can you believe it?
It's a good thing
if you can rest up
when you have the day off.
Yeah, but the thing is,
I was in my pajamas all day!
Oh! Like today.
[chuckles]
I had no idea those
were your pajamas?
Oh, yeah, there my jammies!
I think they're adorable!
Why, they don't even
look like pajamas.
--You think so?
--Yes.
Do you think it's okay
if I wore them all day?
I think you could even
go outside in them.
[KAGAMI] Jeez, would someone
get to the punch line already?
[KAGAMI]
It's gone up a little.
No, wait!
The bra that I'm wearing has
underwires and extra padding!
That's why I'm heavier today!
Yeah, that's it. Yeah.
I wonder how much
that is in grams.
If I just subtract...
[sighs]
[TSUKASA]
It's over. I totally screwed up!
I forgot I had a
physical exam today,
so I wore my
character-print underwear.
I'm so embarrassed now!
[KONATA]
I'm still short.
[giggles]
How dare you look happier
than the rest of us! Damn you!
Hey! I'm here, now.
Oh, hiya' Sis.
I Just thought of something.
You always come
here to hang out.
What's the deal?
Don't you have any friends
from your own class?
Unlike you, I have friends.
Are you picking a fight?
No, I just thought they were
avoiding you, is all.
Why don't you worry about
yourself for a change
and get to work on
those social skills?
Social skills?
What're you talking about?
See, even though
I look like this,
I've got about a
hundred friends.
Both my social and my bargaining
skills are actually pretty high.
Oh, and I go to
parties every night.
Huh?
And with my allies,
I strive to restore the
light to the crystals,
rescue the kidnapped princess,
and save the world from ruin!
Wait, you're talking
about a game!
Oh yeah, I haven't seen
that guy in while.
What guy?
She's talking about one
of her game buddies.
Mm. He's a warrior
class character,
who wanted to improve his
hand-to-hand combat skills.
He left to train somewhere else
where's there lots of monsters,
but hasn't come back yet.
I heard from someone else
that he's camping out
in one of the
underground caverns.
I wonder if he's
all right though,
being all cooped up
down there like that.
Everyone's worried about 'im.
How do you get
cooped up in a game?
Trust me, it happens.
I don't know, but by the
looks of his login info,
he's been playing the game
non-stop for days.
Cooped up in the
real world too, huh?
Whatever, its the same
guy in both worlds.
I always wanted to
ask you guys this,
how'd the two of you
become friends, anyway?
[KONATA] Tsukasa was
about to be kidnapped
by some big suspicious
foreign dude.
I just happened along, saw what
was going down and jumped in!
I unloaded a front punch,
whirlwind kick
combo attack on him
and rescued her
from that creep.
[KAGAMI] Why does
everything you talk about
revert back to gaming?
Hey, I was just doin'
what any other
skilled martial artist
would've done, you know?
I don't approve the
use of hasty violence,
but you did save her.
The thing is that the foreigner
was just asking
me for directions,
I couldn't understand what
he was saying though
and that's when
Kona-chan came by.
Wait, that's no good! How can
you be so smug about it?!
Oh, that's right. It's that time
of the year again, isn't it?
What are you talking about?
I just remembered that
baseball season's starting soon.
Oh, do you not like watching
sports and stuff, Kona-chan?
I sorta figured you'd
love watching sports
because you're so athletic.
If a game goes into extra
innings, it's guaranteed
to totally screw up
the late-night programming
schedule for anime.
Or even worse,
they could end up cancelling
the broadcast for that night.
It sucks when something you
like disappears, doesn't it?
When do you
eat the strawberry
on top of a strawberry
shortcake?
Why do you want to know?
I was just wondering
if you liked to save
your favorites for last?
I guess I save my favorite
stuff for the last bite.
Although with strawberries,
it depends.
Beef tongue with green onions,
you cook both sides?
Beef tongue with green onions?
Hmm. It cooks pretty fast,
but i guess if you
roast it on both sides,
it'll get done quicker.
You can't! The green
onions fall off.
But you put the
green onions on it
after the meat's been cooked.
But if you do that, the
onions won't get roasted.
But the green onions are
just a topping, aren't they?
Man, you just don't
get it at all.
Wait, maybe you can
cook it both ways.
Oh!
Which end of a choco-cornet
is the head?
Is it the fat end,
or the skinny end?
Hmm. The fat end?
Wow. Guess we agree on that.
You're kidding.
Okay, so which end
do you eat first?
Hm. Don't you tear
off the thin end
and dip it in the
chocolate in the fat end?
Do you have any other friends,
besides us and the ones that
you have in video games?
Oh, yeah, I used to have
this really good friend
back in junior high school.
[TSUKASA]
Oh, you actually had one.
Yeah, but I haven't
talked her in a while.
I wonder what she's
up to these days?
You know, I remember in
our junior high year book,
she wrote that her big dream
in life was to become a mage--
So, she was a geek too!
[ALL]
Lucky Star!
[AKIRA]
Lucky Channel!
Hiya, Luckies!
It's time for the first ever
episode of Lucky Channel!
So throw your hands up
in the air and say "yay!"
And a big hello to all
the viewers tunning in!
I'm Akira Kogami, and
I'll be your navigator!
And... I'm Shiraishi.
Who's that?
Just kidding!
Allow me to introduce
Minoru Shiraishi.
He's going to be my
number one assisstant!
Ta-da-da-da!
Yeah, well, I am
Minoru Shiraishi,
and I will be Akria-sama's
assistant from now on.
Howdy.
My, my, my! You're so
tense, Shiraishi-san!
Come on now, you're
finally on TV!
Loosen up you big
stick in the mud, you!
Sorry, I'm just
not used to this.
I know it's only our first show,
but we've already got
bunches of letters from
viewers just like you!
Okay! We got a letter
here from a viewer
in Osaka calling themselves
"I Love Berry-Kou."
"Dear, Lucky Channel,
congratulations
--on your first ever episode."
--Thank you, Thank you!
"By the way, I've got a
question for Akira-san.
You are referred to as a
Super Idol by everyone,
including yourself.
How much money do you make
as an idol? Please tell me."
What I'm paid?
Yes.
You know, this question's
kinda personal,
so maybe we should move one.
Yeah, you know,
what are you thinking
asking a question like that?
A-Akira-sama?
Well, it totally
depends on the job.
You know, some gigs are cheap.
Some are really cheap,
Either way, I get paid a flat
fee from the production company.
So, who knows how much money
those guys are
skimming off the top.
I've been in this business
since I was three-years-old,
and every cent of my pay
still gets direct deposited
into my parent's bank account.
So, all I get is
a small allowance,
and, believe me, it's tiny.
Uh. Come to think of it,
Mama's been buying a lot
of brand-name bags lately.
She couldn't be spending the
money from this show already.
You vampire!
Just because Dad stopped
sending money after the divorce,
you're going to suck
me dry now, huh?!
What do you think I am?!
Some kind of Cinderella,
or something?!
Huh? Oh, no, it's time
for us to say goodbye!
I'm so sad now!
Please send us your
questions and comments.
If you guys have idea or
opinions about the show,
or if you want to tell me
how much you love me,
start sending
those letters, 'kay'?
Is there anything you want
to add, Shiraishi-san?
Uh, right. So, I hope you guys
tune in to see us next episode.
See ya!
[AKIRA] I heard they're
giving you a part in the show.
Is that right?
[MINORU]
Huh? Where'd you hear that?
[MIYUKI] We don't
karaoke together enough.
[KAGAMI]
To tell you the truth,
I hardly ever go to
places like this.
[KONATA]Come on,
we've only got two hours,
so start singing, people!
[KAGAMI]
Stop being so pushy!
Two hours is plenty of time.
[MIYUKI]I have to say,
this sure is exciting.
[TSUKASA]
It's so fun!
I like how after you sing,
you feel really good.
[KONATA]
Anyone see the catalog?
[MIYUKI]
Catalog?
[KONATA]
Yeah, the catalog.
[TSUKASA]
The catalog?
[KONATA]You know, the thing
with all the song numbers in it.
[MIYUKI]
You mean this?
[KONATA]
Right on! I'm going first!
[KAGAMI] Hang on... Wait,
you just entered three songs?!
[KONATA] Yeah! It's way
better if you load it up!
[KONATA singing]
[KAGAMI]
What song is this?
[KONATA]
Space Iron-Men Kyoudain!
Ohh! We gotta start
with this one.
[KAGAMI]
I don't know this one.
[MIYUKI]
Go for it, Kona-chan!
[KAGAMI]
Konata-chan, this is too loud!
Turn down the volume!
How the hell does she
know a song like this?
[MAN] On the next
episode of Lucky Star.
[KONATA]
Konata here. I'm so sleepy.
How come on nights
when you slept a lot,
you wake up even sleepier
the next morning?
Kinda defeats the purpose
of gettin' a good night's
sleep, doesn't it?
Next time:
"Efforts and Results."
[MAN]
Look forward to it!