[evil laugh]
How does it
feel to be powerless
against these flames
which consume you?
[ASHIYA] King Satan?
[MAOU] Your flesh,
your entrails.
I shall nourish my ambition,
and devour you until
nothing remains but memory!
Sire. Could you listen
to me for a moment?
Now, let the feast
of feasts begin.
The time for the
first sacrificial offering
has finally come!
You're mine!
[ASHIYA] Your Majesty!
Jeez, Ashiya,
what's your problem?
[ASHIYA] Please feast
a bit more quietly, Sire.
You're disturbing
the people around us.
Whoops. Sorry, I'm
just really excited.
Look at this! Beef
intestines are so good!
For the first time,
I totally get those demons
who love eating entrails.
That's certainly
wonderful to hear, Sire.
But vegetables are just as
important as vital organs.
A proper diet is balanced.
Will you lighten
up for once; c'mon,
we're celebrating
my promotion tonight.
Oh, hey. You think
we should buy dinner
for Urushihara
before we leave?
I bet we can grab
something to-go.
Hardly necessary.
Apparently, he learned the
"online shopping" recently.
That cretin is utterly
demolishing our budget.
I implore you to bring
the hammer down on him, Sire.
[ROBERTIO in Ente Islan]
[SUZUNO in Ente Islan]
[HIGH PRIEST A in Ente Islan]
[HIGH PRIEST B in Ente Islan]
[SUZUNO in Ente Islan]
[ROBERTIO in Ente Islan]
[CERVANTES in Ente Islan]
[MAOU] We're home!
Good. I'm starving!
Try to be polite
and welcome our Master
back home properly?
Without His Majesty's
benevolence,
you would be
homeless right now.
Lookie. We brought
a present for you.
[URUSHIHARA] You guys
get to go out to eat
but all I get is
a crappy pork bowl?
From a cheap convenience store?
[ASHIYA] We obtained
that computing device
and internet
environment for you.
How much do you think that cost?
You've no right to complain.
Yeah, but I can't
eat the computer, can I?
[ASHIYA] Then do what
you're supposed to do,
and gather information
on existing magic
in this world for His Majesty.
Depending on your success,
you can get a large
pork bowl instead.
Or maybe even a jumbo one.
[URUSHIHARA] Jumbo pork?
That's all?
About this
computer stuff,
are you seriously good at it
because I don't get it at all.
[URUSHIHARA] Well,
if you don't believe me,
I'll show you some of
what I can do right now.
Boo. I wish today
would hurry up.
[EMI] Thank you for
calling the Docodemo
Customer Service Center.
My name is Emi Yusa,
how may I help you today?
[MAOU] Whoa, you got through!
Nice one dude; you are good!
[EMI] What?
[MAOU] Hey, Emi,
can you hear us?
Oh. Maou.
[EMI] I'm working right now,
and you know it!
What do you think you're doing?
[MAOU] Aw, don't be mad.
This is a hacking experiment.
Urushihara said he
could do all kinds of stuff
if he had a computer,
so I made my first big
credit card purchase
and got one for him.
[EMI] I have several
questions for you,
but first of all,
who's Urushihara?
[MAOU] Oh, that's Lucifer.
[EMI] What?
What do you mean, Lucifer?
Don't tell me he's
staying with you!
[MAOU] Bye!
Sorry for interrupting!
[MAOU] Thank you very much.
Mister Maou,
you are like so cool!
I mean, you already made shift
manager after less than a year!
You should be proud.
You think?
I feel like I'm just
a cheap substitute
for the boss when
she's not around.
Wait. Doesn't
this mean--
Well, even if it's only
a couple people,
for not that long o' time,
you're technically ruling
over humans, right?
[EMI] Wrong. I won't allow it.
[MAOU] Emi?
[CHIHO] Welcome
to MgRonald's!
[EMI] I need to talk to you.
I'm working right now,
and you know it.
What do you think
you're doing?
You started it
while I was--shut up,
I see what you did just there!
Excuse me. Might
I uh, interest you
in a delicious order
of jalapeño fries?
They're our
featured item today!
[URUSHIHARA] Aw, suck.
It can't handle online gaming.
That was the whole
point of this thing.
[URUSHIHARA] I know you.
[ASHIYA] Cappadoshia.
Given all the evidence
I've amassed,
it is not impossible this
site is the former home
of a lower-level demon
who was banished to Earth.
And if that's
indeed the case,
there's a chance we may be able
to replenish our magic there.
Although there's no telling
how many months worth
of His Majesty's wages
it would take to
fund a trip to Turkey.
[ASHIYA] The landlady?
[FEMALE PART-TIMER A]
Thank you! Good night!
[MAOU] So, what do
you want from me now?
Oh, like you don't know!
What was with that
phone call yesterday?
I already told you;
Urushihara did it.
And why is Lucifer
randomly "Urushihara"?
Well, with the
police arresting Olba,
he's trying to lay low.
To answer your next
pressing question.
Yes, for the lack of
a better option,
I'm letting him stay
at my place for a while.
[EMI] Three men in
that tiny apartment?
[MAOU] I know.
It's not like
I have a choice.
At this point, I'm
basically all out of magic.
We couldn't go back to
Ente Isla even if we wanted.
Oh!
Sucks for you; I can go back
there anytime I want to.
I don't have
to slave away
looking for a
source for my power.
Controlling the Gate
is hardly anything
I need to worry about.
Then, why don't
you leave me alone
and hurry on out of here?
Because I am a hero!
As long as you
stay in this world.
I have a duty to
keep my eye on you!
Why's she
always such a pain?
Hey, guys, I'm home.
[MAOU] Urushihara?
Hang in there!
Who did this to you?
[toilet flushes]
Sire, you mustn't look at that.
Please. It's not worth it.
[ASHIYA pukes]
You saw the
landlady in a swimsuit?
Correct.
She said she
was visiting Hawaii,
and for some reason
included a photo of herself
frolicking in the waves
at Waikiki Beach.
Yeah, it's unbelievable.
Why would she show
us something so awful?
Isn't vulgarity supposed
to be censored?
Really, guys?
What kind of demons freak
out over a simple picture?
[URUSHIHARA] Fine!
You look at it, then!
[MAOU] Enough of this
swimsuit business;
have you gathered info
on this world's magic?
Dude! No fair!
You're trying to pull
a fast one on us!
[ASHIYA] His Majesty is
not pulling a fast one.
Sometimes, a valiant retreat
is simply the best option.
[URUSHIHARA] Valiant retreat,
my butt. Whatever.
I just found some very
interesting magical info,
if you care.
How exactly
does this qualify
as information about magic?
You can find magical
spots here all over.
There's a lot more
to this world
than just the pyramids
and Stonehenge.
If you look,
you can find a whole
bunch close to us.
That info's not
necessarily available
at the library, though.
[URUSHIHARA] This might be
the best candidate in the area.
[MAOU] A sealed-off classroom?
[URUSHIHARA] Yep.
There's an old room
in this school
that's been
completely abandoned.
Supposedly, you can
hear stuff every night.
Whispers and laughter
and footsteps.
[URUSHIHARA]
Freaky stuff like that.
Y' ask me, there's prob'ly a
demon involved in that story.
[MAOU] Guess this is the place.
You know, I'm surprised
it looks so cheery.
Do you really think
there's a magical spot
and a possible demon here?
I don't know; I'm not
sensing anything so far.
[ASHIYA] Well, Sire,
one does not simply walk
into a high school
one does not attend
and start exploring
the place.
[CHIHO] Mister Maou!
[ASHIYA] Miss Sasaki?
Oh yeah.
I knew the name of this
school sounded familiar
for some reason; must
be 'cause Chi's talked
about it before.
[KAORI] Hey, Chi. Is that
the boy you work with?
Yeah, it's Mister Maou.
[KAORI laughs]
[KAORI] Who's that
guy with him?
[CHIHO] That's his
roommate, Mister Ashiya.
[KAORI] His
roommate? No way!
Are you're telling me two men
are sharing an apartment?
Oh my gosh, do they
share a bed, too?
I bet it's a twin, huh?
[laughs fanatically]
[CHIHO] No, you
got the wrong idea!
Quit imagining things; it's
not dirty like that at all!
[CHIHO] Seriously,
you need to calm down...
[ASHIYA] She certainly seems
to be enjoying her conversation.
I wonder what it's about.
[CHIHO] A sealed-off classroom?
Yeah. From what
I've been told,
it's supposed to be one of
your school's "seven wonders";
do you know what
any of that means?
Yeah, those stories are
pretty famous actually.
People've said they can
hear monsters groaning
and other mysterious
voices whispering.
Some have seen reflections
of demons in the windows.
[CHIHO] Wait a minute!
That wasn't you,
by chance, was it?
No. Certainly not.
But it still might have
something to do with Ente Isla,
so I was thinking
I should, you know--
I should probably check it out.
That makes
perfect sense to me!
I can set the whole
adventure up for you, too!
The old part of
the building is this way.
[ASHIYA] Why was the room
sealed off in the first place?
It happened
before I was even born.
Now, this is only a rumor,
but apparently, a student
disappeared from that room,
almost like he
was spirited away,
so they closed off the room
and never used it again.
So, how would you guys
like to take a break
and have a little snack?
[ASHIYA] You do realize
this is not a field trip.
Seems like you're having
a good time with this.
[CHIHO] Well, yeah.
Because no matter where we are,
I'm always the one who
ends up needing you
to help me out.
It feels pretty good to be
on the other side for once!
[MAOU] You're not scared?
No, I'm fine
as long as I'm with you.
Cool. So, if there
are seven wonders,
what are the other
six supposed to be?
[CHIHO] Um.
Lemme see here.
The north stairway with a
different number of steps
going up than going down.
The statue that walks
around covered in blood.
The sculpture
in the art room
that gets a fold in its
eyelid at three in the morning.
The dictionary in the
library where the words
for "curse" are stained red.
And, the piano
in the music room
where one of the notes
sometimes won't play.
With the
sealed-off classroom,
that only makes
six wonders, though.
[CHIHO] Nobody knows
the seventh one.
It is said that if
someone learns all seven.
If they learn
all seven, what?
Yeah. What happens then?
[CHIHO] They get a
call on their cell phone
from the netherworld, and
their soul is totally stolen!
That doesn't
make sense at all!
I mean, why would just finding
out get your soul stolen?
What if it was
like a coincidence,
and it wasn't even your
fault that you found out?
[ASHIYA] Sire, please
calm down for a moment
and think about it rationally.
Why would the story
about this room,
which existed well before
Miss Sasaki was born,
involve a cellular telephone?
[MAOU] Good point.
[phone rings]
[MAOU] What the
crap, Urushihara?
Try'nna gimme--?
Dude, what are you
shouting at me for?
Where are you?
D'ja make it to the sealed room?
No, not yet. So?
What are you calling for?
I'm trying to help you,
jeez; listen.
The room in question
is most likely an area
where the Gate has opened
at some point before.
The Gate?
Yep.
Once the Gate has
opened someplace,
magnetic fields at that
particular location destabilize,
and it's easier for it
to open there again.
Then, that story
about the student
who was spirited away
could actually be true?
Could be.
I bet the poor kid got
sucked into the Gate.
Anyway, if we can manage to
be there next time it opens,
or at least figure
out when that is,
maybe we can get
some magic from it.
You never know.
Just holler at me when
you get there. Lates.
Urushihara and
his inter-whatever.
I don't understand
how he could find out
so much so quickly.
It's like a series
of magic tubes.
[door opens]
[MAOU] You guys heard
that too, right?
[ASHIYA] Maybe it's
a security guard?
No, the guards
should've all left by now.
So, we might see a
demon who came through
the Gate from another world.
Knowing that ahead of time means
there's nothing to be scared of.
Bring it on!
But do you have
an adequate amount
of magic left
to fight, Sire?
If not, you can use this.
[MAOU] What is it?
[ASHIYA] A potent talisman.
It has already proven effective
against demons like us.
[MAOU] The
landlady's letter?
[footsteps]
I hear footsteps.
[WOMAN] What are you
idiots thinking bringing
a teenage girl
here after dark?
[MAOU] Emi!
[EMI] Oh, I get it.
Your goal was to find
some way to get magic
from the sealed-off
classroom, is that right?
First of all,
I don't have to tell you,
and second of all,
what are you doing here?
The great hero
is trespassing?
Um. I'm sorry,
but uh--
We're not allowed to
wear shoes inside.
Would you mind
changing into these?
Look, I was following
you guys around
as usual and I saw you
sneaking into a school
after it was closed,
so I came in to find
out what was going on.
I'm still not sure what
you weirdoes are up to,
so just deal.
I'm here,
I'm going with you,
and there's absolutely
nothing you can do about it.
[EMI screams]
Maou! Get back here!
[CHIHO] I feel guilty.
Is it really okay to ditch her?
You bet it is.
She's annoying and nothing
but trouble; keep on walking.
[EMI screams] Hold it right
there, you jerks!
[MAOU] She's such
a freakin' pain.
[EMI] I'm serious!
Stop right there or else!
If you keep running away
from me, I will cut you!
Hey, what's wrong?
Is everything okay?
I-- No, I'm fine;
it's nothing.
[EMI] You'll pay
for this, demon!
[EMI] Nailed it!
No, you didn't, psycho!
[CHIHO] Miss Yusa, that's
called an "anatomical model."
It's like a doll.
[EMI] What?
Brave Emilia:
the only hero in the history
of the universe ever to
slice up an anatomical model
with a sacred sword.
Makes me question
how well
she'd do against
an actual opponent.
You need
to do something
about this mess, woman.
Man, these things've
gotta be expensive.
And I ain't
payin' for it.
Well.
They won't have to know
if we don't say anything.
But that's prob'ly out
of the question, huh?
[EMI] Yeah, well, technically,
it's all your fault
because you're the
ones who left me behind
and made me chase after you!
Learn how to take some
personal responsibility.
[EMI] Come on;
use your magic to fix it.
[MAOU] Why should
I use my precious magic
to cover up something you did?
[ASHIYA gasps]
[ASHIYA] This model!
It only had one heart!
[CHIHO] Mister Ashiya,
I don't know how demons work,
but humans only
come with one heart.
[EMI] So, it's across
this passageway, huh?
Would ya please quit
wavin' that thing around?
S'like you're compensating
for somethin'.
Nice try, Bucko, but
I don't take orders from you.
[CHIHO] That's the old
part of the building there.
The room we're looking for
should be on the third floor.
All the way up the stairs.
[MAOU] Okay, let's go!
[EMI] Yeah, I'm gonna
say this is it.
[CHIHO] I don't remember there
being any actual boards, though.
[MAOU] What did I just say
about waving that around?
[CHIHO] Mister Ashiya?
What was that noise for?
[ASHIYA] Look. Someone has
clearly used this door recently.
[MAOU] They're
not even attached.
[EMI] So, the door isn't
even actually sealed?
[MAOU] Is it me, or has
someone been living here?
[ASHIYA] Agreed.
Based on the trash,
I would hardly say
this place has been
sealed shut for years.
[EMI] What's that?
Isn't it a
game system?
[phone rings]
What now, Urushihara?
[URUSHIHARA] Don't be rude.
Are you there, yet?
[MAOU] Just walked in.
What's with you?
Stop calling every five seconds!
It's really annoying.
[URUSHIHARA] Do you
see anything on the floor?
Like, say, a game system?
[MAOU] Yep, it's here.
We have it right now.
Yeah.
I knew it; I had a feeling
that's where it got left.
[MAOU] Where it what?
[URUSHIHARA] Huh?
Oh, nothing; never mind.
Why don't you just go ahead
and bring that on home with you?
Just tell me one thing.
Do I have to punch you
when I get home?
[URUSHIHARA] What? Why?
[MAOU] You said this was an easy
place for the Gate to open.
Is this where you
and Olba came through
when you got to this world?
Yeah, that's the place.
Did I not say that?
[MAOU] What do you think?
[URUSHIHARA] Oh, well, huh.
We sorta lived
there for a while,
and I accidentally
forgot to grab the game
I was playing before we left.
[MAOU] Urushihara.
You better not've
sent us out here just
to bring back a stupid game.
[URUSHIHARA] Don't be silly!
Give me some credit.
I thought, you know,
maybe the Gate opened again
and someone else
came through, obviously.
Did you find anything?
If not, get back here already.
I'm starving.
I'd even be fine with a
pork bowl at this point.
[MAOU] Who does
that little jack wagon
of a demon think he is?
[ASHIYA] If you ask me, Sire,
we should just sell it
at the used game store.
We could certainly stand
to have the extra cash.
Your cheapness
never ceases to amaze.
[CHIHO] Udon?
[MAOU sighs]
Dang it; yesterday was
a complete waste of time.
Oh, hi, Mister Maou!
[strangled gasp]
I found that envelope on
the floor of the science room.
[CHIHO] Mister Maou?
What's wrong? Mister Maou!
[URUSHIHARA] Give that back!
It's my game, jeez!
You only get one hour
of gaming per day!
And you should be
grateful we didn't sell it
for cash like I wanted.
[door opens]
[MAOU] Looks like...
we have a new neighbor?
Hey, watch out!
[MAOU] Are you okay, Miss?
Majesty! Are
you all right?
Yeah.
But uh-- This girl just sorta
fell on me out of nowhere.
Carelessness,
the greatest enemy.
What?