[doorbell]
Why would someone
come by so early?
Not sure.
It does seem a rather unusual
time for a salesperson.
[doorbell]
Salutations.
Salutations?
Perhaps that
girl from yesterday?
You mean that girl who
fell down the stairs?
[ASHIYA] Yes, Sire.
[doorbell]
[GIRL] Salutations!
[MAOU] Yeah. Coming!
Good morning.
Forgive the early hour.
My name is Suzuno
Kama-zuki, and,
as of yesterday,
I am your new neighbor.
I'm afraid I've already been
rude and caused trouble,
so I must humbly apologize
for my wretchedness.
Your wretchedness?
Um. Thanks,
that's very courteous.
I'm pleased to
formally meet you.
My name is Sadao Maou.
This is but a small
gift of my thanks
and good wishes,
as your new neighbor.
I have been told that
noodles are the best gift
for someone to give
their new neighbor.
New neighbor, got it.
That's very nice of you.
Sire. Do you
need assistance?
That looks heavy.
[MAOU] That's because it is!
Oh. G'd morning, Miss.
My name is Ashiya,
I'm an old friend of Maou's;
it is a pleasure to meet you.
Likewise; I actually
know who you two are.
I have never met the landlady
of this fine
establishment before.
But I received a
letter from a person
whom I believe to be her,
and it instructed me
to come to you if
I had any issues.
Oh? Does it now?
Yes, there was
a photo enclosed,
[slow-motion talking]
if you would like to see it.
No, no, that's fine;
I'm sure it's her!
[toilet flushes]
At any rate.
I'm relieved to have such
helpful new neighbors.
I wonder if you
would be kind enough
to instruct me in the
"lower class living"?
[URUSHIHARA]
Heh, the lower class living?
Is there
another person here?
[MAOU] Yeah, we inherited
a third roommate recently.
I'm Urushihara.
Nice to meet you.
[MAOU, mockingly]
"And I'm a lazy bum!"
Well, that's not
my choice, is it?
[MAOU] And why is that exactly?
'Cause--you-- Shut up.
[SUZUNO] I see. I understand.
You understand what?
I shall excuse
myself for now.
Salutations, again.
[MAOU and ASHIYA]
Yeah. Salutations.
[phone rings]
[EMERALDA] Hello! You're
speaking to Emeralda Etuva!
[EMI] Yeah, I actually know
who I'm speaking to
because I called you.
This is Emilia.
I just got a package,
and the label says
it came from you.
Did you send something?
[EMERALDA] I can't believe
it already arrived!
How amazing; I only put it
out for delivery yesterday.
That is surprisingly fast!
I sent you a gift--
celestial force!
What? Celestial force?
That's right.
I tried to process
it into a form
that wouldn't seem out
of the ordinary there.
Oh, I do hope you like it!
Interesting. So, it's
called "Holyvitan B"?
[EMERALDA] That's not a
"b," silly! It's a "beta!"
Right, beta, whatever.
Anyway, you're saying downing
this energy drink will
replenish my force?
[EMERALDA] Yep.
But let me be
absolutely clear here,
be very careful with the dosage!
Wait, how careful?
Are you saying I can
drink too much of it?
[EMERALDA] Uh-huh.
Under no circumstances
are you to drink
more than two
bottles in one day.
You can have
one bottle in the morning
and another in the afternoon.
That said, if you
skip your first dose,
you can't simply
double up on them later
in the day to
make up for it, okay?
Yeah. Seems easy
enough; I think I got it.
[EMERALDA] Wonderful!
And, please follow the
instructions to the letter.
I know how you can get.
Talk to you later!
[disconnects]
Weird. Where is
that girl, anyway?
Nothing ventured,
nothing gained.
[EMI] Why does it always
seem to be so hot outside?
And it's not like those
guys are up to much.
I feel like I'm sweating
out here for nothing.
It's all about perspective!
The fact that
they're just working
and eating like normal people
is a good thing, right?
They're behaving.
I guess another
way of looking at this,
could make me seem
like a weirdo stalking
a nice group of boys who all
live together. Whatever.
[SUZUNO] Honestly!
Can you not adequately
hang one piece of laundry?
You truly know
nothing of chores,
do you, good Hanzo?
Dude, lay off me. Ugh.
[SUZUNO] You cannot allow
clothes to dry wrinkled...
[EMI] Who is that?
Yeah, yeah, I'm
sorry, I'm sorry.
Jeez, you're like
the ghost of Ashiya
haunting me before
he's even dead.
[EMI] Okay. What's
going on? Think, Emi.
Could she possibly
be a new demon?
Ah, this might
be a little risky,
but what choice do I have?
[SUZUNO] You need to
get your act together
in times of crisis like this.
Pay attention.
Chop the Welsh onions,
grate the ginger,
and dilute the
broth with cold water.
Now, all you
have to do is boil
some udon noodles,
and you've got a
delicious meal in a flash.
Once the noodles are done,
give them a quick rinse,
and you'll have a very
respectable cold udon.
If we had a raw egg,
it would be even better.
[URUSHIHARA] Ugh.
How can you stand to boil
anything when it's this hot out?
Good Shiro does this
for three meals every day.
Do you feel no filial piety?
Thank you,
Miss Kamazuki,
and please keep
trying with the boy.
That creature refuses to
listen to his own family.
[SUZUNO] Go on.
Grate some ginger.
Surely you can handle
a simple grater.
[URUSHIHARA]
Don't call me Shirley.
Uh-oh.
Ashiya, it looks like
we're out of ginger.
[ASHIYA] Oh right, I finished
the last of it yesterday.
I beg your pardon,
Miss Kamazuki,
but let's just add
Welsh onions this time.
[EMI] What are they even doing?
[SUZUNO] I shall fetch
ginger from my room
and return forthwith.
Crap!
[EMI screams]
[crash]
[MAOU] I don't think you
actually know how to use stairs.
[EMI] Wha--? Maou?
[MAOU] Seriously.
You need to, like,
practice or something.
[URUSHIHARA] What's
going on? Who fell?
[EMI groans]
[SUZUNO] I apologize.
This is because I opened
the door so suddenly.
No, so not your fault.
I'm the one who's sorry;
I should have been
paying better attention
to what I was doing.
Yep, totally.
Yet she claims to be a hero.
So yeah!
You're welcome, Emi;
I picked up all the crap
you dropped outside.
Oh, good.
I suppose you can just
put it over there, then.
[URUSHIHARA] And I
suppose you can just
cut the stupid
pretentious tone.
What is this?
Never pegged you as
an energy drink fan.
Give that back!
Stuff'll give you heat stroke
like Our Lady Ashiya
of the Floorboards.
For real?
You're suffering
from heat stroke?
No, I just get sick
every once in awhile
like most human beings do.
I'm afraid my gift
was the culprit for
your current state.
I should have chosen
something more thoughtful
and nutritious.
Oh no.
You're hardly responsible,
Miss Kamazuki.
[SUZUNO] Sorry, I haven't
introduced myself!
I moved in next door to these
kind gentlemen last week.
Nice to meet you;
I'm Suzuno Kamazuki.
As I hail
from an ancient
and old-fashioned
family in another land,
I am still fairly unaccustomed
to this particular area.
I would be most happy
if you could instruct
me in "city life."
[EMI] Sounds a lot like me.
[SUZUNO]
Pardon?
Nothing! My name's
Emi Yusa. It's a pleasure.
Yum. Thanks
for the grub.
[MAOU] There's too much
to do and memorize.
I am exhausted.
[EMI] Because your part-time
job is just so hard?
I'll have you know
while you spend your days
dilly-dallying through
your little life
on your little telephone,
I've been greatly
maturing as a human.
In what way?
Also you don't
really count as "human."
Did you forget, Emi?
A mere two days
from now, this Sunday,
I will be the new shift manager
at the MgRonald's over
by the train station!
I will be the assistant boss!
[EMI] Whoopee.
Hey, don't act
like it's not a big deal.
Shift managers get paid more
and have a major position of
responsibility, so there!
Yes, I'm sure
it's a big deal to you;
but the point you
seem to be missing
is that I couldn't care less.
Fine, be that way.
But don't act surprised
when I eventually climb
past heights you
can't even imagine!
[EMI] Are you an idiot?
[ASHIYA] No, ma'am!
I cannot allow you
to speak to the head
of our household in such
a disrespectful manner.
[EMI] What?
[SUZUNO] Good Emi,
do you perchance
have an intimate relationship
with Good Sadao?
Not funny, Suzuno!
Well.
I have noticed your
conversations seem
to flow back and
forth quite easily.
It is rather as though there is
no restraint between you two.
H'yeah, like an old married
couple or somethin'.
Shut up, twerp,
nobody asked you!
No, there's no
restraint between us.
But more importantly,
there's no trust,
or friendship,
or anything positive!
In fact, I pretty seriously
want him to drop dead,
so don't get it twisted;
we will never be "intimate."
Oh. I see.
[EMI] I'm gettin' some
serious deja vu right now.
Look, I'm sure
I'm reading this wrong,
but are you maybe
crushing on Maou?
Gah. Emi.
That was so loud; what if
he heard what you said?
Oh. No--I'm sorry.
I didn't actually think
you were, so uh--
Well, be that as it may,
I'm very impressed.
How did you figure it out?
I dunno, I can't
really explain it.
[EMI] Probably shouldn't
mention I've been
through this before
with another girl.
You know, I guess it's
just our ladies' intuition.
Of course.
How remarkable.
[EMI] At first, I thought
she was an assassin
from Ente Isla, or
possibly another demon.
But assassins don't normally
stay still for a whole week.
And as far as demons go,
she's way too polite.
Maybe I should
give her a warning.
[EMI] Hey, um, Suzuno.
I'm sure you'll think
this is none of my business,
but I need to
tell you something.
[SUZUNO] You do?
[EMI] Yeah, you shouldn't get
too close to those guys.
It'll only end badly for you.
What do you mean badly?
[EMI] Maou's not the kind of
boy a normal girl can handle.
I just think it's best
to steer clear of him.
No, I'll be fine!
I know I may not look
it at the moment,
but I'm a seasoned warrior!
Still, though.
Since this warning
is coming from you,
I'll be careful.
I doubt you'd mention this
to me if you didn't have
a reason to believe it.
Nevertheless, it's too
late for me to leave.
I'm sorry if this
is impertinent,
but would you lend me
your aid should I need it?
Sure.
I'll do whatever I can to help.
You will?
Wonderful, I can
rest easier, now.
I have an idea;
wait here a sec.
You guys didn't go
and do anything stupid
while I was out there, did you?
What, n' incur the wrath
o' the daring hero?
Here ya go, I've written
down my cell number,
my email, and my address.
If these buttheads
are rude or make you
feel uncomfortable at all,
just let me know, okay?
Thank you.
I am in your debt.
Come on.
Quit freaking out;
what do you think we are?
Bloodthirsty demons
who are more despicable
than cockroaches?
I'm sure I don't
have to say this,
but if you pull
anything with that girl,
I'll cut off your
head and display it
on your filthy windowsill.
Jeez, what are you now?
The evil police?
All righty then, I think
that should take care of that.
Don't worry, though.
They're actually
a lot better behaved
than I generally
give them credit for.
See you later!
[EMI falls down the steps]
I'm fine! I am OK
this time; I'm good!
Nothing to see here.
[MAOU] She
make it okay?
[SUZUNO] No, but she only
fell half-way this time.
Baby steps, Emi,
baby steps.
[EMI whines]
[MAOU] Awright, I'm out.
May the tides of war
be with you, Sire.
[MAOU] Don't worry about seeing
me off, just stay in bed.
Ugh, dealing with Emi
saps my energy every time.
[SUZUNO] Good Sadao.
[MAOU] Oh, Miss Kamazuki.
Sorry about Emi earlier.
She can be kind
of a handful;
I hope she didn't say
anything rude to you.
No, she didn't say
anything rude at all.
Oh good; that's
a relief.
Well, I've gotta head to
work, so I'll see ya later.
Um, here. It's for you.
What is it?
[EMERALDA] So, how's it
going over there, Emilia?
Is the Holyvitan Beta
working out so far?
[EMI] Well, I've been
drinking it regularly,
but I haven't
really had a chance
to see if it's
doing much quite yet.
We haven't
been in any fights,
so I haven't needed
celestial force.
[EMERALDA] Wow, really?
Does that mean you're
getting along better
with the Devil and his
demon friends these days?
[EMI] I wouldn't say that.
We bicker pretty much
whenever we see each other.
And we're both so busy
working, neither of us
has the energy to actually
go out and get a life.
[EMERALDA] You
know what's funny?
That sounds like the
quintessential complaint
of couples who
don't get to spend
enough time together.
Whoa. Wha-- What?
Where did that come from?
I'm Ente Isla's hero and
he's the freaking Devil!
Maou's my enemy no matter
what situation we're in.
Couple? Seriously?
That makes me furious
just thinking about it!
I've been literally
stalking him
to make sure he's behaving.
How could you say
something like that?
[EMERALDA] You're right.
I'm sorry.
But, please, don't do
anything to make things
more difficult than
they need to be, okay?
With everything
else that's going on,
we can't afford to start
fighting demons, too.
Why would I do that?
I am the hero.
If it makes you feel better,
I swear on my parents' names
I won't screw anything up.
Now. How are things
progressing on your side?
[EMERALDA] I suppose
they're better
than we thought
they'd be at the moment.
None of the countries have made
any obvious moves, per se.
[EMI] "No obvious moves"
is a good thing?
[EMERALDA] Well, it's
the best we can hope for.
I'm getting information from
a lot of sources right now,
but so far it's all just
whispers and rumors. Also...
[EMI] Also what?
[EMERALDA] I heard the
Church's Missionary Division
is trying to uncover the truth
behind Olba's disappearance.
It's possible some people
are setting their sights
on finding you
hoping it might help them
figure out what happened.
Bottom line is,
under no circumstances
are you to let your guard down.
From what I've been told,
some of these interested
parties may not be above
taking out Japan if it
gets them faster answers.
I guess catching a break
is too much for a hero
to ask for. Lucky me.
[EMERALDA] Seems
that way. Well, then.
This bill will be
out of control
if we stay on the
phone much longer,
so I'm going to hang up now.
Be safe; talk to you later.
Sure. You be safe, too.
[KISAKI] As you know, Sentucky
Fried Chicken across the road,
which is expected to
pose a huge threat to us,
will finally be open tomorrow.
Unfortunately,
I'll be out of town,
so I'm counting on
you to run the ship.
This is a big
deal for you, Maou;
think you'll be
able to handle it?
Yes!
[KISAKI] Of course, in
case there's an emergency,
I'll let you know where
you can reach me at any time.
But, unless it's
"someone-died" serious,
I want you to try and
handle things on your own.
This is a chance for major
personal development.
I understand, ma'am!
Tonight, you're
low on staff,
so stay out of the weeds.
In case you couldn't tell,
your new job as shift manager
is starting right now.
[KISAKI] You might
as well take a break now
since you won't be
getting one later.
If you can get
back here by six,
you can run and
grab some dinner.
Or, if you'd rather,
you can eat here no charge.
I brought food today,
but thanks anyway.
Hi Mister Maou! Are
you taking a break?
[MAOU] Yep. Gotta
refuel and all.
Excuse me. What's that?
[MAOU] What? My bento box?
Your bento box?
Because it looks pretty
darn fancy to me.
Did Mister Ashiya
splurge on that for you?
[MAOU] No. It's not
really my bento box.
A new neighbor moved in next
door, and let me borrow it.
New neighbor, huh?
Living right next door to you?
Yeah, she's cool;
I think you'd like her.
Your neighbor is a she?
Why are you yelling?
There's no
reason for yelling!
Wrong! A she moved
next door to you.
She's already loaned you her
personal fancy bento box.
Something's going
on! What is it?
Please stop shaking me;
it feels not good!
What you're telling me
here is the new girl
who moved in next door lent you
her personal bento box,
is that correct?
Yes, Chi.
That is correct.
Now Mister Maou,
I'm sure my fears are
completely unfounded.
I'm sure it could not
possibly be the case.
But I have to ask.
Is the meal homemade?
Uh. Yeah?
I'm fairly certain
she put it together herself.
I'm sorry, I need to see
the food now, please!
Sure, do whatever
you want!
Just stop shaking me!
Please, I'm begging you!
[CHIHO] A New Year's meal?
[MAOU] What's that mean?
You wanna see
what's on the bottom?
No wait; just
hold on a sec;
I'm not mentally
prepared for that yet!
Um. Okay.
[CHIHO] I've got
a bad feeling about this.
Something's wrong.
I know the adrenaline
has gotten me this far,
but if this is
my chance to turn back,
I should probably take it.
But, on the other hand,
after coming this far,
how can I just quit?
Now, Mister Maou.
Show me the bottom!
Right. Yes, Ma'am!
[CHIHO screams]
[door alarm]
[MALE CLERK]
Good evening sir, welcome.
[EMI] Great.
Yet another uneventful
day stalking demons.
I swear, I buy
the same meal every night.
[MALE CLERK]
Thank you very much.
I'm sure we'll see
you again tomorrow.
[MALE CLERK] Hey.
What just happened?
[MALE CLERK] Ah, jeez.
Sir! Are you okay?
[EMI] Stay back!
[EMI] Don't leave this store!
And call the police immediately!
I'm not scared of you.
And whether you're
a demon or a human being,
you should be ashamed for
attacking me out in the open
when other people are around.
It's one thing
coming after me,
but if you so much
as think of hurting anyone
in this world,
I will show you no mercy!
What did you do?
Heh.
[MALE CLERK] Hey!
[ATTACKER running away]
Take this!
Miss! Please tell
me you're okay!
[EMI] Are you all right?
I'm sorry for
pushing you, by the way.
[MALE CLERK] Oh, I'm fine.
I just hit my
forehead, s'no biggie.
Did you call
the police like I asked?
I'm pretty
sure tripping the alarm
called the security company,
so they should have
contacted the cops for me.
By the way, I have to tell you.
Yeah, what?
[MALE CLERK] I know this
sucks, but the emergency manual
states that we're to have
the customers remain
in the store until
the police arrive.
So uh, would you mind
waiting until they show up?
I'm sorry. I hate to even ask.
Fine.
[EMI] It is working.
The Better Half that
I activated this time,
it contained a heck
of a lot more power
than back when I fought
Lucifer two months ago.
With this power,
I might even be able
to use the Evil-Crushing Robe.
But, that just makes it
harder to figure out
what that purple
light might have been.
I've never
encountered an enemy
who nullified a sacred sword
and celestial force.
[MALE CLERK]
'Scuse me, Miss!
I picked these up;
they're yours, right?
Oh, yeah. Thank you
for grabbing them.
[phone rings loudly]
Crap, I have that
turned up loud!
Wow, that scared me; I seem to
still be a little jumpy, huh?
[MALE CLERK] Me too.
[CHIHO] Miss Yusa?
Yeah? Chiho?
[CHIHO] Yes, it's me.
And there's trouble!
[EMI] Chiho, what is it?
What happened?
[CHIHO] It's Mister Maou.
Mister Maou.
What about Maou?
What did he do?
[CHIHO] Maou um--Today
he brought-- he brought.
He brought what?
[CHIHO] He-- He brought
the heart with the bento
in the rice!
And the homemade New Year's,
and the two layers and the she!
What?