[ASHIYA moans]
[MAOU] You gonna be okay?
[ASHIYA] I apologize, Sire.
I've failed you.
I'm so debilitated, I can't
even manage to go shopping.
[MAOU] Yeah.
Just stay here.
I'll take care
of dinner tonight.
Sire.
Yet again you shower me
with your kindness.
Such a hopeless servant
does not deserve you.
[MAOU] We've got
some rice left.
Maybe I can mix
that with an egg.
[doorbell]
[MAOU] Great.
Emi again?
[DELIVERYMAN]
Special delivery!
Son of a bastard.
Did you go behind my back and
place more orders online?
No, I did not.
And if I did, I'da had 'em
delivered while you were gone.
[DELIVERYMAN]
Have a nice day!
[MAOU] "I've found lots of
wonderful things in Hawaii.
So would you sell them for me
at the Neighborhood
Association's Summer Bazaar?"
[coughs]
[URUSHIHARA]
One-two-three, not it!
[ASHIYA] You!
[ASHIYA coughs]
[URUSHIHARA] Hey, either
complain or cough, but pick one!
[ASHIYA coughs]
[SUZUNO] It's you.
[MAN] Yes, I remember
you from the church.
You are Crestia Bel,
the Deathscythe.
I'm starting
to get worried.
I haven't seen Tom at his
shop for several days now.
Do you know if
he's been sick?
[MAN B] I haven't heard
anything, but you know,
that guy was always defying
the Grand Hoshin Church.
An' rumor has it, he
even gave the Federation
of Knights priority when he
passed out food and supplies.
You think he'll have to
face the Inquisition?
Keep it down,
you fool!
What if they're
listening to us?
[CADRE A] I've received
intelligence that Lucifer's army
is invading Porridge Village.
Most unfortunate for
the platoon of Church knights
who are stationed there;
they don't stand a chance.
Why don't we
send in reinforcements,
and then they
can owe us one?
[CADRE D] No, it wouldn't
make much difference.
The enemy force is too large.
The most intelligent
course of action is
to just pretend we never heard
about it in the first place.
[CADRE B] Following such
a strategy will let the world
know the Church failed
to protect the village,
allowing doubt to set in.
Our federation will then be able
to take advantage of the mess
and proceed with our plans
to subdue Satan.
Right.
And we will lose only one
minor village in the process.
A sacrifice well worth it if
we can win back the people.
[door creaks]
[CADRE B] Who goes there?
[gasps, chokes]
Wait, what?
Poison!
No!
It's in the wine!
[chokes]
[CADRE A] You wench!
You are with the
Inquisition, are you not?
Damn you!
[chokes]
[CADRE A] Church lapdog.
You will pay!
No!
Spare me!
[halted scream]
[OLBA] Well done.
Your work was as
efficient as always.
I'm impressed.
Now wipe off all that blood.
A portion of the blame
for the knights' inability
to band together against Satan's
army lies with the Church.
Why does no one
try to compromise?
We should not be at
war with each other.
Do not think
above your pay grade, dear.
Your only concern
is your duty as
the Bailiff of the Inquisition.
A questioning spirit
is a prideful one.
[OLBA] Here is the
next list of heretics.
[SUZUNO] In the end, it was the
Hero who saved the world.
We were just
part of the problem.
[RIKA] What?
The amusement park?
Did you go
with Maou?
Why would you jump
to that conclusion?
[RIKA] You mean
you didn't?
Okay, well I guess technically
I did see him there,
but I went with Chiho
and Suzuno, not him.
[RIKA] You can keep
denying it all you want,
but I still think Maou the
Shift Manager is on your mind.
Amirite?
If you want the truth,
Suzuno's the one most
on my mind at the moment.
Sorry to burst your bubble.
[CHIHO] Good afternoon!...?
[MAOU] Oh, Chi, we've
been waiting for you!
[CHIHO] Um, Mister Maou,
what's going on?
Our landlady sent all
this junk from Hawaii.
She said to sell it
in the summer bazaar
at the shopping arcade.
[ASHIYA] Apologies,
Miss Sasaki.
I'm afraid we had to
bother you because of me.
I'm still rather ill.
[ASHIYA grunts]
[URUSHIHARA] Watch it, yo!
[MAOU] Be careful
with those boxes!
Oh.
Are you all right,
Mister Ashiya?
Having help is
fine, I get it,
but are you sure we're even
gonna have enough room in here?
You know, with Emi
comin' over, too?
What?
How do you know she's coming?
Because I planted
a tracker in her purse.
Like, forever ago.
[MAOU] Yeah,
she's gonna kill you.
[MAOU] What on Earth
is wrong with her, anyway?
We're busy, whacko--!
Huh?
[MAOU] Oh, you're
at that door.
Why should I have to help
you out with this weird sale;
it's not like I live here!
I only came over
to check on Suzuno!
Speaking of weird Emi,
I don't understand why you feel
I need to be checked on.
[URUSHIHARA] I'monna
go back to our place.
I'm a hermit, remember?
I have a strict rule...
[MAOU] You're helping!
You'll be fine so long as
you don't leave the building.
I didn't think our
landlady could freak me out
more than she already has,
but what's she doing with
a bikini top like this?
Well, I actually think
this one's kind of cute.
Yeah, it
kind of is.
Maybe I should
buy it!
Doubt it'll fit.
[EMI] Shut it, hermit!
[MAOU] There's food, too.
[CHIHO] Pineapples.
Macadamia chocolates.
Ew, Sp'Ham.
Oh, and there's juice!
This note says
she wants us all
to eat the
food together.
Ugh.
Lame.
[SUZUNO] What's Gu-a-va juice?
[MAOU] Why don't
we try it?
[CHIHO] I'll go get cups.
Y'know where
they are, right?
[CHIHO] I think so.
[SUZUNO] I don't believe
that's how you open it.
Watch your eyes, everyone.
That cork's about to fly.
[cork pops, MAOU screams]
[MAOU] Oops.
[EMI] What is your problem?
Here, this'll help some.
What's wrong?
Oh.
Um.
It's uh, nothing.
[MAOU] I really am sorry.
I could only find
five, Mister Maou.
Well, none for
Urushihara then.
Dude, why not?
There are exactly five of us!
[MAOU] Me, Emi, Suzuno, Chi,
and Ashiya's not dead yet.
[EMI] How about
you stick to water.
[CHIHO] I might have
seen a used to-go cup.
[URUSHIHARA] Gah!
What the crap?
Why do you keep treating me
like the plague?
What did I do to deserve this?
You guys suck so hard!
[MAOU exhales]
Thanks, you all were
a massive help today.
Oh, no worries;
it was fun!
Feels like the day before
my school's culture fest.
Yeah, it seems the prep
for stuff like this always
gets people more excited than
the actual event, you know?
[CHIHO] Something wrong?
Not at all.
I was just thinking.
It's been years since
I've had the time to enjoy
a proper festival.
Well in that case we have
to hang out and enjoy it!
We'll do the prep first, and
then go check out the rest!
I would love to,
but I gotta head out.
I work tonight,
so I've gotta get ready.
[CHIHO] Okay,
have a good shift.
We can finish up
what's left for you.
[EMI] Jeez, Chiho, you don't
have to spoil the poor idiot.
[MAN] Why do you waste time
with silly festival
preparations?
You need to carry out
the objective.
If the Devil regains his magic,
it will be too late.
[SUZUNO] I know, but--
[MAN] I believe
we're past hesitation.
Your hands have been thoroughly
stained with blood already,
have they not?
[ROBERTIO] Curse Saint Aire.
Always so self-righteous
the moment there's peace.
[HIGH PRIEST A] Their
current goal is to prevent us
our rightful access to the
rebuilding of the central lands.
They will exploit any
weakness to come after us.
How did they acquire
the assassinated
nobleman's corpse?
Not to mention the transcript
of the trial proceedings
from the cathedral.
What has the
Prince-Bishopric of Bel
been doing?
It may seem wise to
let our lead bailiff
take the fall, but I don't
think handing her over
would change the situation.
After all, the Inquisition
conducts a number of unfair
trials without her.
What do you
suggest we do?
The Hero Emilia
is a former knight
of the church who defeated
the Devil's army with the
assistance of by the
high priest Olba.
I would imagine that means the
people owe this peacetime
to the Church.
Not so fast.
You are still the ones who made
the trials severe and unfair
to begin with, and those actions
will not be left unpunished!
One of us should
most assuredly
take the blame.
Nonsense, why should
we be blamed when
the high priest Olba was
in charge of the trials.
And now that he's conveniently
disappeared on us,
we have no reason
to take responsibility.
Exactly.
[CERVANTES] To avoid delays
in trying the heretics while
the Grand Inquisitor is absent.
Father Robertio will establish a
"Doctrinal Correction Council"
and transfer all officers
of the Inquisition to it.
The Inquisition will be
suspended until the return
of Father Olba.
Under this new leadership,
the council shall
conduct fairer trials.
That should be a sufficient
story to feed the kingdoms.
[SUZUNO] It is always this way.
They refuse to
discipline themselves,
out of shame and fear of
damage to the institution.
They keep their hands
from getting dirty,
while stealing their
glory from others.
I-- I never wanted
to execute anyone.
[MAN] For the last time, Bel.
You have a job to finish.
Kill the Devil.
[SUZUNO] He shall die.
I swear it.
[ASHIYA moans]
No way.
[URUSHIHARA] Look, dude.
If you're that sick,
why not go to the hospital?
I'll even call an ambulance!
No, that's way
too much to pay.
Tough nuts.
I'm calling for help, and
you're going to the hospital.
[ASHIYA] Wait!
Do you know how much
an ambulance costs?
I don't know if
insurance will cover it!
[emergency sirens]
[EMI] Oh, there she is.
[CHIHO] Miss Suzuno!
Where have you been?
[EMI] Is everything okay?
[SUZUNO] Yes, fine.
I was just doing some thinking.
[CHIHO] So, uh.
I've been wonderin,
how's your job search?
'Cause, if you
haven't found one yet,
I'm sure we could get you
hired at MgRonald's with us!
Can you imagine
how much fun
we'd all have
working together?
[SUZUNO] Good Chiho.
Yeah?
You should not associate
with Maou any longer.
What the
crap, Suzuno?
[SUZUNO] Emilia,
please stay out of this.
"Emilia"?
Miss Yusa, how does
she know your real name?
So you do know
about King Satan.
My instincts were correct.
Something has been
telling me you knew
the awful truth already.
[EMI] Suzuno.
[SUZUNO] Emilia.
Believe me, I know you
have your own agenda here.
But you must understand
I do as well.
It was my mistake.
I should have
killed him immediately.
[CHIHO] Miss Suzuno.
Please, where is
all this coming from?
How could you
want to kill him?
Listen to me.
Don't you remember how as
soon as the Devil decorated
those trees for the festival,
your MgRonald's was suddenly
flooded with customers?
What do you
think that means?
That he's good?
It means he used magic.
Those slips of paper were
filled with human desires,
and then tied to bamboo to
exorcise the bad energy.
Satan subconsciously used
that whole thing as a medium
for casting a spell.
He only wanted customers
to come in so the store
would do well!
I mean, yes, I guess cheating
isn't exactly fair, but still.
Not so bad
if that were all.
But there's no guarantee
he won't start making more
dangerous magic and hurting
people in the process.
No!
Mister Maou would
never do that!
Remember those
alligators in the pool?
What do you think
will happen if the Devil
works his way up
in this world?
What if everybody ends up
trusting and respecting him
like you do?
It'll be the perfect
opportunity for him
to betray us all.
I don't think so.
You don't?
No offense, but uh--
do you really think getting
a promotion at a fast food
joint means he's capable
of taking over
an entire world?
[SUZUNO] Demons
live a long time.
We have no idea how
elaborate his plans are.
We should kill him now,
while we still can.
No, please!
I realize this
must be painful,
but we are from an entirely
different world, Good Chiho.
You and Satan should
never even have met.
The best course now
is to erase your memory,
and eliminate all traces
of Ente Isla from this land.
[bag drops]
[EMI] Chiho?
Erase my memory?
Why?
Why would you
do something like that?
I don't want to forget
about all of you.
Not Mister Maou, or Miss Yusa.
Or Mister Ashiya, or you.
Or-- even Mister Urushihara.
[CHIHO] We were lucky
enough to become friends.
And we've gone through
so much together.
But now you want to make
me forget part of my life
because of your
precious Ente Isla?
That's not fair;
what about me?
[SUZUNO] This situation
is not about you, Chiho.
That being said, taking
advantage of your feelings
may actually be
part of his plan.
He might be trying to sow
seeds of doubt and confusion.
[CHIHO] I'm telling you
he's just not like that!
Why would you say
such horrible things?
He's worked hard, and he's
been so nice to everyone!
So how can you do this?
How can you defend him?
The Devil has killed
thousands in Ente Isla!
He's the ruler of demons!
Fine, since you know so
much, tell me something:
did you ever meet him
before he came to this world
and turned into my
friend Sadao Maou?
[SUZUNO] I--
[CHIHO] You only
fought with his army.
You never even met him
in person, so how would
you know anything about him?
False logic!
Every commander bears
full responsibility
for the actions
of his troops.
If he was evil
and plotting to do
all the things you think he's
doing, then why would he bother
saving people and fixing the
expressway after it collapsed?
[SUZUNO] There must have
been an ulterior motive.
Something to do with
his nefarious plans!
[CHIHO] What reason is
there other than just being
an actual nice guy?
When a good person
causes someone else problems,
they apologize and then
try to fix the situation.
Maou did what good people do.
Did you know?
I learned everything
about my job from him.
He has taught me so much.
When I screwed up,
which I did a lot,
he always made me feel better.
He's kept
his promises, too.
Even when he turned
back into a demon.
I wanted to learn how to
use the ice cream machine,
and he remembered!
If you still think he wants
to take over the world
with his army, well--
I'm sure he must have a
pretty good reason to do it!
So you believe we should
just forgive and forget
all the atrocities and horrible
things he's done to us?
Just pretend it never happened?
Is that what you want us to do?
[EMI] Calm down, both of you.
Crestia Bel.
To be perfectly honest,
I agree with you.
[SUZUNO] Then join me--
[EMI] However, I don't
agree with all of it.
I hope for a peace
that will allow
every person to be happy,
not just a select few.
And that peace is what I've been
fighting for all this time.
Looking the other way while
we make our friends cry
is not acceptable.
Believe me.
The means don't
always justify the end,
and I won't allow you
to behave as though they do.
You cannot
truly be serious.
[EMI] I am.
Then, you're dreaming.
There's no way we can win this
without someone getting hurt.
[EMI] I'll find one.
Sacrifices will
have to be made!
This is war!
[EMI] No one needs to suffer.
I'll figure it out.
I am a hero, after all.
It's what I do.
Thank you.
Fine.
So right now you have no
intention of defeating
the Devil?
[EMI] Nope.
Not right now.
[SUZUNO] Understood.
[CHIHO] Miss Suzuno!
[CHIHO] I think I went too far.
I don't know anything
about Ente Isla,
so how can I understand
where she's coming from?
I wish I hadn't've
been so mean.
Don't worry.
Suzuno realizes we don't
always get to choose
who we fall in love with.
You think so?
[CHIHO screams]
[EMI] You again!
[chuckle]
[EMI] And just like last time.
It's like you have a thing for
attacking me out in the open.
I suppose it doesn't
really matter, though.
This won't take long.
Careful, things
might get rough!
No!
I gotta call for help.
[EMI] Who are you?
[MAN chuckles]
I tried to warn you.
Men will always take
advantage of vulnerable women.
Chicken creep?
Please oh please,
pick up!
No!
[SARUE] It's no use.
The power of my gaze makes
angels fall from grace.
It subdues all who use Celestial
Force; and belongs to me alone.
Angels?
Hold on.
Does that mean--?
Yes, that's right.
You're welcome, Emilia;
I'm here to release you
from your painful mission.
Since you don't need the
Better Half anymore,
I'll be taking it back.
Miss Yusa!
Not you, too.
You're just like that
awful man Olba, aren't you?
She's in your way, so you think
it's okay to get rid of her.
How can you do this?
Mister Maou may be
a demon, but you're the one
who's got no problem
betraying the only person
who fought for your world!
So what does that make you?
Good Chiho.
I'm sorry.
[MAOU] Oh.
Chi called, huh?
[phone rings]
Yeah.
Hello?
[WOMAN] Hi, this is
Chiho Sasaki's mom.
I just wanted to thank you for
taking such good care of her.
Oh, yeah, uh--
You're welcome.
[CHIHO'S MOM] So,
Chiho's not home yet.
Is she with you, by chance?
Have I seen Chiho?
Sorry dude.
No, she hasn't been by here.
While I've got you, I
investigated that SFC place.
For a chicken joint,
it smells fishy.
[MAOU] What does that mean?
[URUSHIHARA] Well,
you said the manager's name
was Mitsuki Sarue, right?
That name is not on their
employee list anywhere.
Seriously?
Yeah, the data's
been manipulated.
[MAOU] You planted
that tracker on Emi.
Is it still on her?
Can you tell me
where she is right now?
Gimme just a sec.
That's creepy.
She's moving in a straight line,
through buildings!
Wait, I'm wrong,
it's not Emilia; it's Suzuno.
[MAOU] Where's she headed?
[URUSHIHARA] Looks like
government building?
[KAWA-CCHI] Whoa,
Maou, where are you going?
On my way, Chi!