Yesterday sure
was rough, huh?
Yeah.
But we can't stop
busting our humps now,
otherwise Sentucky Fried
Chicken might steal
all our customers again.
[KISAKI] I have to go
tell Corporate about
our eighty percent sales drop.
No way we wanna freeze our
butts off in Greenland, right?
[MAOU shivers]
[KISAKI] Hey, Maa.
[MAOU yelps]
I want you to help out
another restaurant.
No!
Please don't do this to me, I
made our sales goal plus some,
just like you said!
What?
It's a fun place.
Besides, you're
not in trouble.
My friend manages the Hushimaen
store and wants to borrow
one of my best workers.
Oh, that makes sense.
Don't thank me just yet,
that joint's gonna be
out of control busy.
The park is opening a bunch of
new rides and attractions, so,
we'll cover all your expenses
and give you a small bonus
for your trouble.
So yeah-- Think you're
up for the job?
Of course, ma'am.
[CHIHO] Oh oh!
Can I go with?
That's all right.
They can manage
without you.
[CHIHO] Aw.
But I wanna.
[KISAKI] I'm counting on you,
Maa, you're my top crewmember...
[CHIHO] Hushimaen, huh?
[MAOU] You got it!
[ASHIYA] Oh?
Tomorrow you say?
[MAOU] Yep.
[slurp]
You're eating
too much too fast,
and you're not
fully recovered.
Ease up, or you'll
make yourself worse.
[ASHIYA] Sire...
[swallows]
The noodles will expire any
day now, we have to consume
as many of them
as we possibly can.
But thank you very
much for your concern.
[URUSHIHARA] She's right.
The amusement park
near that other MgRonald's
is reopening tomorrow, and
they're rolling out a bunch
of cool attractions, so it
looks like they're expecting
a big crowd.
Quit surfing on the interwebs
and start helping us...
--...slurp down some noodles!
--[URUSHIHARA] Whoa.
They got a wicked new
reptile exhibit there!
Dude!
Over three hundred
different species.
Sounds like you'll
be busy, Sire.
Yeah.
[URUSHIHARA] Whoa!
The new Haunted House
is supposed to be scarier
than Labyrinth of Shocks!
And everyone says that's the
scariest one they've ever seen.
[URUSHIHARA] So if a whole
bunch of people are going to
a crazy-scary Haunted House,
that means there's probably
gonna be a butt load
of concentrated fear
ripe for the taking.
[URUSHIHARA] You
could get some magic.
[ASHIYA] Then I
shall assist you.
I will be there to watch
over you with true zeal.
Don't worry, Sire.
With me by your side,
nothing can go wrong.
[URUSHIHARA] Wait.
You're going, too?
[ASHIYA] Yes.
It's my duty.
You stay at home and
try not to burn the place
to the ground.
[ASHIYA] Now what?
[URUSHIHARA]
Want pizza.
Gimme money.
[ASHIYA]
Absolutely not.
Such extravagance is not
allowed in this house.
You will eat these noodles,
and that is the end of it.
You will then
wash the dishes.
[URUSHIHARA] Dude, no.
How old are those noodles?
They have got to be turning
a little south by now.
Taste perfectly
fine to me.
Do not waste them;
there are starving
children somewhere.
Yeah whatever, Mom.
[ASHIYA] Fine!
I'll have to
finish them myself!
[MAOU] Will you two stop
fighting and hurry up and eat?
We gotta get this done!
[symphonic ringtone]
[EMI] Hello?
Hey, Chiho; what's up?
Oh.
Yeah.
An amusement park, huh?
Sure, why not?
I've got the day free tomorrow.
Awesome.
It should be a lot of fun.
And thank you so much.
I'm glad you're
coming along, Miss Yusa.
Going by myself might
have been kinda weird.
Cool!
I'll meet you there, then!
I wish I coulda gone with
Mister Maou, but oh well.
[CHIHO giggles]
[symphonic ringtone]
Hello?
[SUZUNO] The Devil is traveling
to Hushimaen tomorrow;
I'm certain he plans
to collect magic.
What?
I thought he was helping
at another MgRonald's?
I see word has already
reached you then, Emilia.
Yeah, Chiho told me.
I'm going to take the train
up there tomorrow, too.
She wanted some company.
And that doesn't make any
sense, how can he collect magic
at an amusement park?
What do you think he's up to?
You're too trusting,
you know.
A healthy amount of suspicion
might do you some good.
It would be prudent if
I joined you at this park.
Yeah, whatever.
And I'll let Chiho know
you're tagging along,
so she isn't caught off guard.
[SUZUNO] The Hero trusts him.
But why?
[MAOU] Hi, my name's
Sadao Maou!
I'm from the Hatagaya store,
and I'm here to help out today.
Good to meet you all!
Kisaki's told me
quite a bit about you.
Says you're one
of her best.
I'll do everything
I can to live up to
your expectations, ma'am!
Great.
Today's gonna be a
super busy day people,
so bring your 'A games!'
[MAOU] Yes, Ma'am!
[CHIHO] Miss Yusa!
[EMI] We're late, I'm sorry!
Oh. No big deal.
How are you,
Miss Suzuno?
I've no complaints
to speak of.
Thank you for asking.
Though I am a bit concerned;
this is my first time
at an amusement park.
I do hope you will teach
me the ways of "fun."
Of course,
I'd be happy to!
[CHIHO] All right
girls, let's go!
Two Special
One-Pound burgers with
secret sauce ready to go!
[CHIHO] Whoa!
Miss Yusa, you look like
such a grown-up in that suit!
Two small burgers,
piping hot and ready!
So, I've
got to ask.
Ask what?
It's just--
You're sixteen.
Aren't you?
[CHIHO]
I sure am!
[EMI] Life's
not fair.
[CHIHO] Was it
something I said?
[EMI] No!
You're just so
huge-- Cute.
I meant to say
'cute', 'cute.'
Wow, thanks a lot.
[CHIHO] I just hope
Mister Maou will think so, too.
[SUZUNO] I am prepared.
So let the
fun commence.
What ails you two?
[MAOU] Thanks,
have a wonderful day.
Next customer, please.
What would you like?
Two orders of nuggets,
extra barbeque.
Add a side of mustard!
One iced latte.
One hot mocha.
Two small burgers,
one all the way.
One no pickles,
no lettuce, please!
Thank you, come again.
Nice job Maou.
All righty,
who's up next?
Hey!
Chi!
Hi, Mister Maou,
how's it goin'?
Um, I'd like to order three
Big Mig meals, if that's okay.
Of course, here at
MgRonald's we aim to please.
[CHIHO] Thanks.
[MAOU] Three
Big Mig combos!
I came to hang out
at the park.
[MAOU] Oh cool.
Good luck with the crowd;
you're gonna do amazing!
Yeah, thanks.
So um.
Do you like it?
Like what?
Ahhh...
Well, this store's
definitely a lot busier
than the one
we work at.
The customers
never stop coming.
So it's been good
practice for me.
Uh yes, of course.
[MAOU] What doesn't
kill you, amiright?
[CHIHO] Uh yes, of course.
I shoulda seen this one coming.
[EMI] You really are clueless.
[MAOU] What are
you two doing here?
Well, last time I checked
we hardworking office ladies
are free to do whatever we
want to on our days off.
Yeah, great.
I have not come here
seeking pleasure.
I'm here to learn
how people have fun.
Yeah, great.
[toilet flushes]
[ASHIYA groans]
[URUSHIHARA]
Are you gonna croak?
Not gonna lie,
you look like dookie.
No, I'm fine.
Nothing I
can't handle.
[URUSHIHARA] If I were
you, I'd take some meds.
It's just a
stomach ache.
I don't need
alchemy.
[ASHIYA] I'm so ashamed.
I intended to assist King Satan
in his collection of magic
and now look at me.
I'm such a disgrace.
Truly pathetic.
[URUSHIHARA] Take it
easy, stressin' out
only makes it worse.
Seriously, you're already
stuck at home anyway.
Either just stay in
there, or stay in bed.
[ASHIYA cries out]
[toilet flushes]
[URUSHIHARA] Dude.
Don't die, 'kay?
Wow, this place
is like crazy crowded.
I know, it's like everyone
and their mom's here
to check out all
the new stuff opening.
You mean like that
haunted house over there?
[CHIHO] Yep!
I hear it's pretty intense!
[EMI] So.
Should we go get in line?
[SUZUNO] Yes, let's.
[URUSHIHARA] You
could get some magic.
[SUZUNO] I have several
reasons to be interested.
[GIRL screams]
Let's go, girls.
Wait.
Awww...
[CHIHO shivers]
[CHIHO screams]
--[EMI] Chiho?
--[SUZUNO] Good Chiho?
[CHIHO screams]
[EMI] Wow, she
really took off.
Wimp.
I suppose we should
venture on without her then.
[EMI gasps]
[shivers]
[grumbles]
--[SUZUNO] Chiho, is that--?
--[crying]
--[SUZUNO] No, not her...
--It appears to be someone else.
[SUZUNO] Hello?
Are you all right?
Child?
Why are you crying?
[GIRL] She's gone.
[SUZUNO] "Gone"?
Who's gone?
[GIRL] My momma.
[SUZUNO] Where is she?
[GIRL] She's gone.
All right.
Would you like
to come with us then?
[GIRL] She's gone.
My momma.
She's gone. She's--she's gone.
She's gone, my momma.
She's gone, gone...
Hey.
Wait.
[distorted voice]
It's-- It's Momma.
[SUZUNO and EMI scream]
[GIRLS sobbing]
[EMI] What sicko
thought that up?
[SUZUNO] This did not fit
with my understanding
of what you call 'fun.'
[SUZUNO] Shall we
give this a chance?
Uh.
Hey Chiho?
It's not too late
to turn back.
Uh... No.
I'll go in if
you guys will!
Kay.
Though I really
don't mind not going.
No.
We've come too far
to chicken out now.
Yeah, right.
Perhaps you're the one
who's a bit afraid, Emi.
Me? Please!
I just don' like
reptiles, that's all!
I'm not a big
fan, either.
[CHIHO] Huh?
[squirms]
It's so gross how they
come creepin' in outta nowhere.
Yeah gross is right.
[EMI breathes heavily]
[growls]
I hate 'em with
a fiery passion.
Totally.
[SUZUNO] Still--it appears they
have a rather large variety.
I do hope they're edible.
Wait.
You said edible.
You like to
eat reptiles?
Yes.
They're delicious.
What?
When have you
done that?
[SUZUNO] Oh, many times.
But my first was on
a journey to the South.
[CHIHO] South of where?
[SUZUNO] A persuasive
acquaintance of mine told me
I would deeply regret it if I
did not sample the lizard so
I was left with no alternative.
[CHIHO] I woulda said 'no!'
[SUZUNO] I did protest at first,
but she was so adamant
about how tasty it was.
[CHIHO] Oh, yuk!
I can't even.
[SUZUNO] The inn prided itself
on serving every single part
of the lizard, from the
head all the way down
to the tip of the tail.
I have to admit, the Lizard Tail
Soup was truly wonderful.
[CHIHO gags]
[SUZUNO] The broth was salty and
rich, and the chunks of tail
were quite delectable.
Grotesque to look at,
but honestly I think
it's Ente Isla's finest dish.
So remarkable!
[screams]
Why are you telling
her about Ente Isla?
Have you lost your mind?
I've misstepped.
[MIZUSHIMA] Hey, Maou?
Ma'am?
When you're
finished with those,
can you make some
in-park deliveries?
Ma'am!
[WORKER] Whup!
[WORKER] Oh.
I'm sorry.
No.
It's completely my fault.
Please,
not at all.
What's up?
You're cute,
Miss Yusa.
Oh you!
[MAOU] MgRonald's delivery!
I have your order!
Great, we've been
waiting for you!
Would you mind bringing
that inside please?
[MAOU] Just give us a call if
you need anything else, okay?
[CHIHO] This is way cool,
I had no idea there were
so many different
types of reptiles.
Neither did I!
Well?
Do you recognize anything
you've eaten for dinner?
Quiet.
I prefer not to think of them as
food while they're still alive.
Look, it's
a monkey.
Perhaps
it's lost.
Why is it
wearing clothes?
Hey there.
Don't be afraid; come on out.
[CHIHO gasps]
[EMI] Yeah.
I don't think
I like this monkey.
[MAOU] Thank you
for choosing MgRonald's;
we'll see you next time!
[MONKEY TRAINER] Wait.
Sadao!
Sadao?
[MONKEY TRAINER]
Yeah, he's my monkey!
A monkey, huh?
Sadao!
Stupid monkey.
Come on!
[MONKEY TRAINER]
Hey, Sadao!
Here, boy!
Where'd you go?
[MAOU] Uh.
Here Sadao!
So, what do you think
we should do with him?
Could we take him to the
Lost Children Center?
[MONKEY TRAINER] Sadao!
Sadao!
You know it's not safe for
you to run off on your own
like that, buddy!
[MAOU] Oh, you
found him, great!
Yeah!
[CHIHO] Mister Maou!
Chi!
What's up?
Thanks, Miss,
you're a lifesaver!
So this little guy's
name is Sadao, huh?
[MONKEY TRAINER] Yep!
[SUZUNO] Were you lost, Sadao?
[CHIHO] I tell ya what, you sure
are one lucky monkey, Sadao.
[MONKEY TRAINER]
My Sadao has a real weakness
for the ladies.
He's a full-blown problem child!
[EMI] Yeah.
And clearly your Sadao
is a fan of "big'uns."
[CHIHO]
"Big'uns"?
[EMI] Never mind.
That's enough!
Just let it go already!
[EMI] Bump!
[CHIHO] Set!
[SUZUNO] Spike.
[WOMAN yelps]
[WOMAN screams]
[EMI] What's that?
[CROWD screams]
[PARK ANNOUNCER]
I have an urgent message
for all guests.
Alligators have escaped
from the reptile exhibit hall...
Chiho!
Everyone please try
to remain calm!
Don't get separated
from your children!
Oh gosh, you okay?
Yeah.
[PARK ANNOUNCER]
Everyone, please follow...
Suzuno?
[MAOU in Ente Islan]
[CHIHO] Emi...
Mister Maou's using
his powers, isn't he?
[EMI] Apparently.
[MAOU in Ente Islan]
[SUZUNO] I don't understand.
He could've taken advantage of
the chaos and absorbed its power
for personal gain.
But instead he's being selfless;
using what he collected
to help the humans.
King Satan, Ruler of Demons.
What is going on in your head?
I gotta say, Maou,
you did even better than
Kisaki said you would.
Thank you, ma'am.
Just doing my job.
Well, then.
I've still got clean up duty
so I'd better go.
Bye, Chi.
I'll catch you later on.
[CHIHO] See you
at work tomorrow!
[EMI] Well, Maou
conveniently bailed.
Yeah kinda.
I was worried today
might be a disaster,
but it turned out alright.
It was worth it seeing
Mister Maou like that!
I guess so.
Plus, I got to spend a
gorgeous day having a blast
with two really
amazing people.
I'm so lucky to have
friends like you!
Yeah.
Pretty good times,
all things considered.
Right?
Yes.
This was fun.
[CHIHO] Miss Suzuno?
[URUSHIHARA] So what's up?
Did you get any magic yesterday?
Hm.
Hard to say whether I got
some or just used some up.
[URUSHIHARA] Huh?
[ASHIYA] Urushihara
is a fool.
Nothing he says is to be relied
upon under any circumstances.
Oh, Sire.
I am so very sorry for
interrupting your meal.
I'm so rude.
I kinda hurt just
lookin' at you.
[ASHIYA] I am in pain,
true, but I shall recover.
[URUSHIHARA] Oh,
he just ate too much!
Silence, rogue!
Do not mock me!
[doorbell]
[DELIVERYMAN]
Special delivery!
[URUSHIHARA] Yes!...
--[MAOU] Yeah!
--...Uh no, I'll get it--
[URUSHIHARA] Crap!
Stupid legs fell asleep!
--[MAOU] One second.
--[URUSHIHARA] Wait.
--[MAOU] I'll be right there!
--[URUSHIHARA] No. Come on...!
[DELIVERYMAN]
I got a delivery
for Mister Hanzo Urushihara.
What, really?
[ASHIYA] "Jungle dot-co."
[URUSHIHARA] Uh. Well you see.
This is uh--
This is what?
Cough it up!
What did you do while I was
in the bathroom, you little--
[MAOU] Maybe you
should see a doctor?
[ASHIYA] No.
No need.
It's only a bug.
[URUSHIHARA]
You sure about that?
[ASHIYA] Quiet, you!
[ASHIYA] Wretched
little twerp.
You worrying
makes me feel worse!
[ASHIYA groans]