[EMI] Weird.
Seems a lot more
crowded than normal.
I was told today
was the first day
of a local star festival.
Perhaps that is the reason
all these people are here.
Yeah, okay,
there's this huge crowd,
but something's kinda odd.
Look at the MgRonald's
we came all the way to see.
I mean, it's
practically deserted.
What is going on?
This is no place
for proper drama.
Without a busy restaurant,
how are we gonna make things
super awkward?
On top of that,
with no one around,
this jerk might get wise to
what's about to happen to him,
which would defeat
the whole purpose.
[EMI groans]
Luckily,
the perfect place is
standing right over there!
SFC!
That's where we can
convene our council of war!
Rika's maybe enjoying
this a little too much.
[RIKA] First, you're gonna
have to confess everything
you might know, think, or
feel about this "Maou" guy.
That way, we can plan
the best course of action
in order to get
this battle finished!
[EMI] Given he's
the Devil and I'm a Hero.
I doubt our battle
will ever finish.
Also,
I'm still wondering how
Suzuno's gonna handle
Rika's misunderstanding.
Guess I'll just
have an iced coffee, please.
How 'bout you two?
I would like to order the
number eight combination:
a maple biscuit
with an iced tea.
Milk in the tea, please.
Iced coffee for me.
You got it, and consider
this my treat, ladies.
Um, so that's all.
Thank you kindly.
Allow me to present you with
a special Grand Opening coupon
for our guests
who come in today.
Oh, thank you.
[SARUE] And now, I shall
lovingly prepare your order.
Surely, your food and drinks
will appreciate being consumed
by such lovely maidens.
Your change, m'lady; don't
spend it all in one place.
[gasps]
Order up.
[SARUE] Apologies for the wait.
I have your order
for you right here, Miss.
And it was indeed a crime to
keep such a lovely lady waiting.
[RIKA] Yeah.
He's like one of those guys you
figure might be a good catch,
but then he's way more creepy
than even he realizes.
I mean, what are
those glasses about,
and all that cologne?
[EMI] You're not
making sense.
Sorry.
[RIKA] Never mind.
Let's go find a table.
Okay.
I think the best
place for us to start
is at the very
beginning, girls!
His name is
Sadao Maou, right?
Come on, don't hold
anything back, either of you.
I wanna know it all!
[EMI grumbles]
To me, he's my neighbor
at my new boarding house.
I can safely say he
is a good neighbor.
[EMI] Oy, this girl.
I want for you to
join me in my quest
to eliminate King Satan,
and then return home with me.
[EMI] All that, and now
he's a "good neighbor"?
Well, she's cool as a cucumber,
I'll give her that much.
[RIKA] And you, Emi?
Oh, I'd happily kill
him first chance I got
if that gives you a clue.
[RIKA] Conflicting opinions.
But you do have that tendency
to put up a front, Emi. Lots.
Look, Rika, I'm gonna
be perfectly frank;
there is nothing between Maou
and me and there never will be.
I have completely different
reasons for not wanting him
and Suzuno to be together,
so get it straight
and get it out of your
thick skull: we are not
fighting over him,
understood?
Perfectly.
See, this is that front I
was just telling you about.
Why are you so set
on the two of us
being some sort
of item to begin with?
It seriously pisses me off!
That man is cruel, cagey,
greedy and insensitive.
He's beyond broke and acts
like you owe him for some
random umbrella and has no
common sense whatsoever!
[loud growl]
[ASHIYA] I would not say
such things if I were you!
Ashiya?
What are you doing here?
[MAOU] Ashiya sure is taking his
sweet time with his mission.
[ASHIYA] You want me
to exhaustively consume
all the fried chicken options
at this new "Sentucky" place?
Technically, it's not
just about eating.
[ASHIYA] It would be
one thing if you wanted me
to exhaustively consume
all the offerings of
the fried-food flash sale at the
supermarket near the station
where I can get
it for half off.
But, unfortunately,
our army does not have
the financial reserves
to contribute to the sales
of your present nemesis.
We cannot waste money on SFC!
[MAOU] Will you
just listen to me?
These methods are being
employed for a good reason.
To win the battle,
we must know our enemy.
Are you telling me my top
advisor has forgotten that?
I have not, Sire.
[MAOU] I'm not saying
to simply eat.
I want you to eat in an
exhaustive investigation
of their strengths, weaknesses,
and everything in between!
The expense is necessary
for my rise to power.
Help me.
Since you feel that
strongly about it, Sire,
far be it from me to refuse you,
or buckets and buckets
of fried chicken.
However!
I, Shiro Ashiya,
will make certain
my thoroughgoing
investigation employs
the minimum possible
expenditure.
[MAOU sobs] Ashiya!
[ASHIYA sobs] Sire!
You can count on me!
[MAOU sobs] Ashiya!
[URUSHIHARA] Gag me.
[MAOU] I know
I said "exhaustive,"
but he's taking too long!
[CHIHO] Mister Maou?
[MAOU] Hey, Chi.
What's up?
I just finished up all
of the chores on my list
for the day.
What next?
Oh. Yeah, right.
Let me think.
[MAOU] Wow; everyone
seems really bummed.
Well, I guess that's
not a huge surprise.
There's a pretty decent-sized
crowd having fun outside
thanks to the Star Festival.
But look how empty
our restaurant is compared
to that stupid SFC.
What do I do?
I can't just keep
twiddling my thumbs!
So, y'think maybe we
should stand outside
and invite people to
eat over here instead?
[MAOU] Soliciting customers.
Could work.
But it might be better
to wait on intel from Ashiya.
The critical delivery
isn't here yet,
so how can we get
the public's attention?
Should I make a move now?
No.
I mustn't make a move now!
I can't predict
this battle at all.
I'm on the front lines
of a fast food war.
Why is it so complicated?
You okay, Maou?
We know you're Shift
Manager tonight,
but you don't have to take
care of everything yourself.
We can help.
[MAOU] That's right!
I command an entire army again!
If I show fear, unrest will
spread amongst my men!
Now is not
the time to act!
At the moment, the tides
are merely in their favor.
But worry not, those tides will
turn again, so we shall wait!
And in the meantime,
we will prepare for
our moment to shine.
[MAOU screams]
Polish the windows!
--[GROUP] Yes, sir!
--[KAWA-CCHI] What?! All that...
[MAOU] Please tides,
move quickly!
[EMI] You are the last person I
expected to see in this place.
And also, why the heck
were you hiding from us?
I wasn't hiding; I noticed
you when you came in,
and hoped to avoid
making a scene.
That said, I cannot allow you
to abuse the master of my house
in such a disrespectful manner.
It would stain my honor!
Yeah, yeah.
Oh, wait, you being here
is a perfect opportunity.
Ashiya, I need your
help real quick.
It's a matter of dignity--
yours and Maou's.
You what?
Why should I help you
with anything ever?
Like ever ever?
Okay, I'm sure you're here
to research this place.
You have to be.
You can get whatever
you want; on me.
[ASHIYA] Well,
if you insist.
[EMI] I swear, you must
be the greediest,
cheapest creature
in existence.
Don't get the
wrong idea, Hero;
I have a responsibility
to prioritize
the household budget
above all else.
And for that duty,
I shall bear any indignity;
I shall suffer any disgrace.
[EMI] You "shall" be an idiot.
[ASHIYA] At any rate,
due to budget constraints,
I was unable to research
salads and desserts.
With your help, I
shall be able to order
each one of them.
[RIKA] Um.
Help me out, Emi;
I'm a little lost.
Is he your friend?
--[ASHIYA] Absolutely not!
--[EMI] Absolutely not!
I don't know
who you are, Miss,
but in terms of this
group's relationships,
I am Miss Kamazuki's neighbor
and Emi Yusa's nothing.
Pleased to meet you,
I'm Shiro Ashiya.
[RIKA] Oh, nice
to meet you.
I'm one of
Emi's co-workers.
My name is
Rika Suzuki.
Hold on a sec, if you're
Suzuno's neighbor,
that means you live
with Sadao Maou, right?
Yes, that's right.
You have the pleasure of
knowing him, Miss Suzuki?
[RIKA] No; but I do wanna
know everything about him.
From the beginning?
No.
Not the sort of everything you
might be worried about, Ashiya.
It's fine.
Basically, this is about
a man Emi doesn't want
other girls getting close
to, so I wanna know why
and what makes him
such a bad catch.
[ASHIYA] I'm sorry, what is
she talking about exactly?
[EMI] I'm honestly not
so sure myself anymore.
[ASHIYA] So he's a man she
doesn't want other girls
getting close to, huh?
Interesting.
A matter of dignity indeed.
It seems you have let
the cat out of the bag, Hero.
Nice.
Well, the truth is, and
apologies, Miss Kamazuki,
I haven't told you this yet,
either, but Maou and I once ran
a very successful
company together.
[RIKA] What?
A company?
Um.
Ashiya?
You don't know what he's
talking about, do you?
That doesn't make sense,
you look a little young
to have run a business;
how old are you, anyway?
The main focus
of our company
was Real Estate Management,
with occasional forays
into Construction
and Odd Jobs.
But we discovered
our true passion was
in Personnel Placement.
We had such
a great name.
The Maou Syndicate.
[SUZUNO] Maou Syndicate?
[EMI] Personnel
placement, my butt.
[ASHIYA] And Miss Yusa?
She worked for a rival company.
Emi.
You had an actual career
in construction before?
So, then how old are you?
Um. It's kind of a
long story, I guess.
If I recall correctly,
you were just a temp
at the time.
Wha--?
I see.
So you're saying the
Hero is a temp worker.
Yeah, you are
not helping.
[ASHIYA] Though we had
our fingers in many pies,
we were still fairly small,
so management had to command
our teams on-site.
But Yusa had both skill and
the support of her own company.
More often than not,
she was the one competing
with us for clients.
We were all so young,
and all with the same
level of experience.
That was smack in the
middle of the recession, too.
Thus, with a major
firm taking business
out from under us.
Our little company went down
like a house of cards.
The last person to ever
battle us for a job was her.
We lost; and the
company went bankrupt.
We drifted; eventually
winding up in our small,
nondescript apartment.
Then, almost a year later,
we saw Miss Yusa again.
[EMI] It's them.
[ASHIYA] And that's it.
I imagine she has
complex feelings, too.
Her failed competitors
from the past.
She still manages to check in
on us every now and again.
I see.
But!
Maou has not given up
on his dream of running
a successful business.
Currently, he is working
intensely at MgRonald's
to learn all he can about
management from the ground up.
It only took him a year to
be appointed shift manager.
And now.
I am forced to play
housewife all day long.
Oh, how far I have fallen.
Yet still!
We intend to start
a brand new business
with Maou as Chairman very soon.
And I shall to do all in my
power to support our dream!
Entrepreneurship,
however, is a gamble.
Knowing that kind of
risk is a part of our lives,
I can understand why Yusa did
not want Miss Kamazuki to get
too close to us, lest she
become unexpectedly dragged into
that gamble as well.
It's far too late for
that; I'm more dragged in
than you know.
...He sees Yusa as an
enemy, and thus hates her
on a fundamental level.
Sorry to burst your bubble,
but I doubt the sort of thing
you're imagining about
them would ever happen.
Wow, that is
very impressive.
I can't get over how
we're all around the same age.
Now, I'm the jerk for having
such a nutty idea and blowing it
all out of proportion.
[RIKA] What the heck, Emi?
Why didn't you
mention any of this?
Well, it's not like you
ever would have listened.
My family actually
runs a small factory,
and whenever times get really
tough, which believe me they do,
we pull through it
by working together.
I know you said you feel
fallen, but the truth is
Maou needs you so he can work;
he eats all the meals you make,
sleeps on the futon you air
out, and wears the underwear
you've washed
for him, right?
Yes.
Then you're
the foundation
of this whole operation!
And I think you need
to be prouder of yourself.
I dunno; I just have this
feeling that since you guys
are so supportive of each other,
things are going to work out
for you.
It's funny; you're the
first person who's ever said
something like that to me.
Thank you for
the encouragement.
I feel a bit stronger for it.
[EMI] Rika?
What? What? What?
Yeah, "what, what,
what" is right.
What in the world
has come over you?
Oh, uh, nothing, nothing,
nothing, nothing, nothing!
She said "nothing"
five times.
[RIKA] I mean, wow.
Everybody's got a past, huh?
Anyway, this should clear
up all your misunderstandings,
so why don't we go home?
No way; now I'm
personally invested
in sizin' up Maou.
For starters, if
he's really that gifted,
I should probably go ahead
and network with the guy,
just in case.
Network?
You're a nutcase.
So, Ashiya.
You have to report
on the enemy, yeah?
Let's go over together!
Yeah, how about no?
All of us.
Together, Yusa.
But not before I obtain one
of those maple biscuits,
as well as a salad
with an extra side
of Thousand-Island dressing.
To go please.
[EMI] Hey, wait.
An extra side?
[ASHIYA] ...Miss Kamazuki,
thank you for your help.
Allow me to treat
you to dessert.
I hate this day so much.
Just when I think today
couldn't possibly suck any more,
it totally does.
[SARUE] Why so serious, Miss?
You cannot allow things
in life to trouble you,
or you won't be able
to enjoy your delicious
Sentucky Fried Chicken!
Yeah, thanks, I guess.
No matter how much one
worries, whether we like it
or not, things
change over time.
Whatever it is you've got going
on right now will end up
completely out
of your control.
So the sooner you accept
that, the better it'll be
for everyone.
This is the first
time I've been given
unsolicited advice on life
by a fast-food worker.
[SARUE] Oh, I apologize
for being presumptuous.
But if I might share
just one more thing.
Men have a tendency to
take advantage of women
who appear vulnerable.
You should be on your
guard at all times.
What is that
supposed to mean?
[SARUE] Oh, nothing.
Nothing at all.
Thank you so much for
visiting today.
Please come back
and see us again soon.
[MAOU] Great, they're giving
out Grand Opening coupons?
That's right, and I
did try their food.
Their trademark fried chicken
is incredibly good.
And depending on the part
of the chicken you order,
you can even eat the bones.
Even bones?
Wait, I don't think
humans normally do that.
[ASHIYA]
There's more, sire.
Evidently, they're
serving organic coffee.
Coffee made
from ogres, why?
[ASHIYA]
"Organic," Sire;
it means "grown with
natural pesticides."
But ogres are already
full of natural pestilence.
Luckily, apart from
those small discrepancies,
there is not
much difference.
Customer service
was fairly average.
I imagine the only reason
they have such a crowd
is that humans are hopelessly
dazzled by new things.
[MAOU] I see.
In any case, we can at least
try putting up a good fight.
Thank you for
the information.
[ASHIYA] Though it is
appreciated, Sire,
I hardly deserve
your thanks.
I know it's not much, but let
me contribute to your sales.
I require two
Big Mig combos.
Both with cheese.
And both with
large soft drinks.
Urushihara will
most surely complain,
but this will be
our dinner tonight.
[MAOU] If he
complains about the food,
you have my permission
to give him a good beating.
[ASHIYA] Will do.
[URUSHIHARA sneezes]
Before I go.
You can expect great things
from those young ladies.
[MAOU] Oh good.
I'm not really sure
what that means.
[ASHIYA] Well, Sire.
I pray for your
success in battle.
Wow, okay, first of all,
they seem really tight,
and then, beyond that,
he's so professional.
You're surrounded
by amazing people.
Oh, can I count myself
among the gifted ones?
Why not?
Knock yourself out.
These seats are much
harder than Sentucky's.
[MAOU] Um.
Excuse me, ladies.
Yeah, what?
We'd appreciate it
if you'd sit down only after
you've placed
an order up front.
[EMI] Ugh.
Okay, how about a small
iced coffee then?
Happy, Maou?
Again, kind miss;
we like customers
to order at the register.
Up front.
While you're at it, I'll
order an apple pie, too,
and you can bring it to the
table to show some gratitude.
Yeah, still not---
[RIKA] So, you're
the Sadou Maou.
Somehow you aren't
as charismatic as I was
hoping you'd be.
Sure didn't expect the
restaurant to be empty
with you in charge.
Why would you say
something like that?
Who do you think you are, lady?
You know, Mister, I don't
really appreciate your tone.
You want me to
complain to corporate?
I don't mind letting 'em
know about you.
[MAOU] Oh, shut it.
Restaurants have rules that
even customers have to follow.
Besides, who are you
to threaten me?
I'm Rika Suzuki, and Emi and
I happen to be co-workers.
I got'cher number.
These two ladies and
your friend, Mister Ashiya,
told me quite a bit about you.
[MAOU] Ashiya?
When?
What did he say?
[ASHIYA sneezes]
Oh, he only had wonderful
things to say, but Emi seems
to find you the complete
opposite of wonderful,
so I decided to check you
out and see for myself.
Since I honestly don't
understand what you're saying
or why you're here, I'm just
gonna go with you being nosy.
Not sure which is worse:
no customers or Emi being here.
Come on, Mister Maou.
You shouldn't talk like that.
Miss Yusa is
a valuable customer.
Here!
I brought you your iced
coffee and a yummy apple pie,
fresh out of the oven.
Thank you, Chiho.
And I'm sorry; you know
how I get around him.
[CHIHO] Don't
worry about it.
I understand.
[SUZUNO] Good Chiho,
it's nice to see you again.
Yeah, you too!
Hope all's well.
Oh, we haven't met;
are you Miss Yusa's friend?
Yes.
We work together.
I'm Rika Suzuki.
Nice to meet you;
I'm Chiho Sasaki.
Miss Yusa has been
nothing but kind to me.
She's adorable.
Pardon?
For real, this little
girl is the cutest thing
I've ever seen!
[EMI] Rika!
Stop being a weirdo!
[RIKA] It's totally not fair
how many awesome people
you have in
your life, Emi!
This precious thing
is so sweet and works
her poor little tushie off.
That's it; I'm
stealing her from you!
[EMI] You're acting like
a drunk old pervert.
Stop it!
Okay, fine.
I'm sorry, Chiho.
I just get a little carried
away; can't help myself.
[CHIHO] Oh.
That's cool,
but it was super confusing.
Well?
What are you gonna do?
Got a plan?
[MAOU] What?
Didn't you just tell
Mister Ashiya that you
would try to put up
a fight or something?
[RIKA] Listen, I'm gonna
be straight with you;
I want to see you work
your magic, so get to it.
[MAOU] You have major
daddy issues, don't you?
[RIKA] Emi has Mister
Ashiya, Chiho, and me;
I mean, this girl has got a lot
of talented people in her life.
I'm sitting here choosing to
believe you're not the idiot
you appear to be;
so prove me right.
Just to be sure
we're on the same page here,
are you implying I look stupid?
Implying's maybe not
a strong enough word.
How dare you?
Fine!
To hell with SFC's coupons!
Time to fight
fliers with fliers!
Come on in and try
some delicious
MgRonald's food!
Come on in!
You know you want to!
It's no good.
[MAOU] What?
Then we advertise
that our food's easier to eat
since it doesn't have any bones!
Chiho! Go!
Come one, come all!
Try a Big Mig burger!
They don't have any bones,
so the eating's easy!
Isn't it fairly
normal for hamburgers
not to have any bones?
That was funny;
you're a silly girl.
[MAN B] Silly and cute!
It didn't work.
[MAOU] I know.
No more Mister
Nice Maou, Kawa-cchi,
it is time for us to begin
Operation: Let People Use
the Restroom Even if
They Don't Buy Anything!
Uh, isn't that
actually still nice?
This is depressing.
Hey, there's
the guy I'm looking for!
Mister Nabe!
Oh good; you finally made it!
[MR. NABE] Well, it was
a request from you, Maou,
so I couldn't refuse; I'm
sorry it took me longer
than I thought.
No problem; you're a life
saver, oh and please,
you have to stay and eat;
whatever you want is on me.
Thanks for the offer,
but my wife said she's
making me dinner, and since
you were my last delivery,
I'm gonna head on home.
See you on the
next cleaning day.
Say "hi" to Miss Kisaki!
[MALE PART-TIMER A] Amazing!
He gave us really nice ones.
[KAWA-CCHI] Let's hurry up
and decorate before
the dinner rush starts!
Yeah, this is awesome!
Maou.
Got some more for you!
I'm not sure if we've
got enough ornaments.
If not, we can
use the flyers.
[FEMALE PART-TIMER B]
Is it really okay to use those
to make more ornaments?
As the current shift
manager, I say you bet it is!
What's going on?
Mister Maou came up
with a super cool idea,
thanks to the Star Festival.
He thought it would be fun to
have our customers write wishes
on strips of paper and
decorate the trees with them.
Then the really smart
part was when he got our manager
to make a request from Regional.
They're letting us give
a complimentary small drink
to any customers who decide
they want to participate.
He got the trees
from that older guy
who came in earlier.
They met a while back,
volunteering for
neighborhood cleanup together.
Mister Maou found out Mister
Nabe grows bamboo in his yard,
so they worked out a deal.
Hang on.
Maou volunteers for
neighborhood cleanup?
Of course, we can't be
sure if this will directly
affect our sales tonight,
but at least everyone here
seems to be in a better mood,
so not a total loss!
[CROWD] Wow! Nice! This
is really coming together!
Okay, that was
pretty good.
Well, I don't
know about "good,"
but I guess he's
a hard worker.
No way.
How pretty!
This is the MgRonald's
with that cute girl
who makes funny quotes!
[MAN C] I saw
her pic on Twitter!
Wait, you
saw me where?
Mommy, I'na write
a wish and put it up, too!
Get out!
Look at what a couple o' bamboo
trees can do for the feng shui.
I gotta redecorate!
Guys.
Assume your battle stations!
War is upon us!
[GROUP] Yeah!
Hi, welcome!
Good evening, all!
As soon as you know your order,
go ahead and get in line!
For two?
I think we have some
empty seats over there.
Sure, just follow me.
Thank you for coming in.