[EMI thinking] Why?
Why would the
Devil rescue humans?
[MALE REPORTER 4A] I'm reporting
now from a helicopter above
the site of a
massive subway collapse.
There are plenty of emergency
vehicles on the scene,
and the atmosphere is grim,
but--and this is
fairly shocking--
Despite the magnitude
of this disaster,
there are no
casualties reported.
I repeat, at this time,
the police are not
reporting any casualties.
Looking at this wreckage--
[YOUNG EMILIA] Daddy!
Almost there, Daddy!
[YOUNG EMILIA]
I brought us some lunch!
Oh great. Thanks, sweetie!
You like it?
Of course.
[MALE FARMER 4A]
Afternoon, Nord. Hi, Emilia.
Wow, that looks good.
Did you make it?
I sure did!
[MALE FARMER 4A]
I bet it's delicious.
Yep!
Here. You have some, too!
[MALE FARMER 4A]
Well, that's very kind of you.
[MALE FARMER 4A] Did you hear?
Both the eastern and northern
lands fell to the Devil's army.
Everyone's saying the
West is bound to be next.
We're protected by the
Grand Hoshin Church
and the Royal Army,
so I have no doubt
we'll be perfectly fine.
There's nothing to worry about.
[MALE FARMER 4A] If y'ask me,
there's a lot to worry about!
Especially if the Demon
General Lucifer attacks.
I certainly hope
you're right, though.
Are the demons coming here?
If they do, I promise
you'll be okay.
The Holy Father's
prayers protect us.
No one will hurt you.
[YOUNG EMILIA]
My daddy's right, you know!
Listen, my daddy
never ever lies!
Tell 'im, Daddy.
Yep. That is true.
You're a smart girl, Emilia.
It's you, Holy Father.
Did you come to save us
from the demons like
my daddy said you would?
Daddy!
[YOUNG EMILIA] Look!
The Holy Father came
to save the village!
Emilia.
He didn't come for the village;
he came here for you.
Me? But why?
[NORD] Sweetheart. I've been
protecting you for this day.
For what day?
I know this is confusing,
but you are an angel's child.
The only human in Ente Isla
with the power
to defeat the Devil.
No. That can't be.
I'm your daughter not
the daughter of an angel.
[NORD] But you are, Emilia.
Your mother was an angel.
That doesn't make sense.
I don't understand what
you're saying to me, Daddy.
You will, sweetheart.
You're coming with me, right?
Don't make me go with
them all by myself, please!
[NORD] I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I pray you lead a
life full of light
in a world you've freed
from any trace of evil.
Emilia, my darling girl,
I love you, with all my heart.
[EMI] And that was the last
time I ever saw my father.
Several days after
I was separated from him,
our village was burned to ashes
by the demon army
sent to crush the West.
General Lucifer led the attack.
[PRIEST 4A] I know
you're in pain, Emilia,
but do not lose heart.
Remember, you have inherited
the power of your mother,
one of the great angels.
[PRIEST 4A] Now, listen.
"Better Half," the
sacred evolving sword,
is a holy weapon
that only children
of both a human and
an angel can wield.
You, my dear, are the
only human in Ente Isla
with the power
to defeat the Devil.
Then, will you please teach
me to fight with that sword?
[EMI] I swear I will
defeat the Devil myself.
Back off!
[MAOU] What?
You were acting like your life
was flashing before your eyes,
so I thought
something was wrong.
I'm fine, and besides,
the Devil isn't allowed
to worry about me!
[EMI] Why are you back
to that craptastic form?
See now that was
just uncalled for.
[CHIHO] Mister Maou!
[MAOU] Chi.
I um-- I wanted...
[MAOU] Hush.
I'm just glad you're okay.
[CHIHO] Eheh! Thanks.
Hey, you kids.
It's dangerous here,
you need to-- Hold on...
You're Inspector Sasaki's
daughter, aren't you?
I'm Chiho.
I mean, yes, that's right,
Senichi Sasaki
at West Shinjuku Station
is my father.
I knew I recognized you.
Gimme a sec; I'll go get him.
[CHIHO] Um. Mister Maou?
[MAOU] Oh hey
I get it; don't worry.
No girl wants to tell
her father she ended up
at a disaster zone,
especially because of a date.
I feel the same way.
I'm sorry.
[MAOU] Please, it's no big deal.
I'll see ya tomorrow.
'Kay! And Miss Yusa,
I should thank you as well!
[MAOU] Sasaki from
West Shinjuku Station.
It's no coincidence, then.
I'm the reason she's
hearing that voice.
The magic I used
when I first got here
must have affected
Chiho somehow.
So, what's your plan?
I think I'll try eating in a
bunch of underground cafes.
Then wait for one to fall on me.
How stupid are you?
[MAOU] Oh, shut up. I'm tired.
I'm gonna go home now
and get some rest.
You're what?
I'm sure you've realized
nothing else will happen today.
I imagine they'll
need to regroup
since their big attack failed.
[EMI] Attack?
[MAOU] Yeah, that
was no natural quake.
We weren't just
coincidentally almost killed
in the same place at
the same time again.
Someone set it up.
[gasps]
[MAOU]
Could have been a sonar pulse
or some kind of
magical interference.
I'm not a hundred
percent, though.
What I can tell you for sure is
that both of our
covers are blown.
Then our enemy--
[MAOU] Has been
standing right next to us.
I wonder if maybe he didn't
try to follow through--
because my magic
started to come back.
But who?
Who could possibly
be after both of us?
And also, who can produce
that kinda power in a world
where we can't even replenish
our own magic
or celestial force?
[RIKA] Emi! Emi!
Hey, Emi;
it's me! Over here!
[EMI] Rika?
Wow, you actually
have a friend?
Didn't see that coming.
Shut up!
Like you can talk!
Oh, go on, she's waiting.
Yeah. I hear her.
Oh, thank
goodness you're okay!
See ya later.
[ASHIYA] Your Majesty!
[MAOU] Great. What now?
Please, please
forgive me, Sire!
Not only did I allow
Emilia near you,
but I failed to notice
the enemy closing in.
Then, I selfishly put you
in a position to
save my pathetic life!
How can I ever be
pardoned for this atrocity?
Quit making a scene, man.
You're not hurt, are you?
You graciously inquire
after my welfare?
Oh, Sire!
[MAOU] Your clinginess
is creeping me out!
Lemme go!
[RIKA] Oh, so your
parents live abroad?
Yeah. You could say that.
I'm sorry for just crashing.
Hey, no problem.
I'm sorry for dragging
you over here.
You didn't drag me here.
[RIKA] Did, too.
'Cause, based on
my own experience--
I dunno, I just--
I figured you probably
shouldn't be alone right now.
So--
Here you go! You missed
out on dinner, right?
[EMI] Yeah. And I'm starving.
Feels like my stomach
is eating itself.
[RIKA] Then by all means,
dig in, sister!
Please, Sire,
punish me harshly!
You cannot dismiss this;
I am unworthy to
stand at your side.
I already told you,
just forget about
the whole damn thing.
Excuse me, could I have
a word with you two?
That was amazing; thank you.
Oh, you're more than welcome;
I'm glad you enjoyed it.
But with an appetite like that,
guess I didn't have to worry.
Truth!
[cellphone ring]
'Scuse me for second.
[RIKA] Hello?
Oh good; you got it?
No, it wasn't expensive at all.
Grandpa loves pretty
much any liquor--
couldn't care less
about the brand.
Today's quake?
Oh, yeah; that wasn't
a big deal at all.
It was close, for sure,
but I'm totally fine,
so let everyone know, okay?
All right. Bye!
Moms. Sorry 'bout that.
That her?
Yep. One and only.
Do they live close, or
are they abroad like mine?
Oh no.
They're just in Kobe;
not too far away.
I don't normally talk
about where I'm from
because I always get
awkward questions.
Awkward? Like what?
Well, people wanna know
about that whole
earthquake thing.
What tragedy was like for me.
[gasps]
I was just a kid
when it happened,
but it's not like I have a super
easy time talking about it.
That disaster was the scariest
thing I've been through.
I don't know why,
but everyone always asks
the questions that're
the hardest to answer.
[EMI] Yeah, I can
empathize with you there.
Uh, Rika.
What's with the surprise hug?
You are the first one, Emi.
You are the first
person I've ever met
who didn't ask anything
insensitive as soon as
they found out I was from Kobe.
Once someone's
perspective gets shifted
so dramatically,
you can't tell
which way they'll go,
so it's hard to
have faith in people.
There's always those ones
who take advantage of the chaos
to do bad things, you know?
But then others
are so kind hearted,
they'll do whatever
they can to help you,
even after they've
lost everything.
So I was thinking that,
you know how when
you feel unsure,
it's kind of like
your angel side
and your demon side are arguing
with each other over
what you should do?
It's like, well, it's up
to people make that choice--
They can either
go with the angel
or go with the demon, right?
Yeah maybe they can choose.
[MALE COP 4B] Now, you boys
are with an acting troupe?
I used to wanna be an actor,
so I know exactly
where you're coming from.
But you can't practice lines
on the sidewalk, okay?
[ASHIYA] Uh.
I'm sure it's tough trying
to get a full house,
but there's gotta be a better
way; just don't give up.
Look, it may not mean much
from a man whose
dream never came true.
But the minute
you give up, it's all over.
Right.
[MALE COP 4B]
Oh, and watch your backs.
We've had a lot of
muggings around here lately.
Don't want people
to start accusing you.
[RIKA] You can take
the first bath, Emi.
[EMI] Okay, thanks.
Yet another businessman has had
his briefcase stolen on
the way home from work.
What? Another one?
[EMI] There've been a
lot of muggings lately.
Yeah, it's totally crazy;
makes me wish I had my own,
personal bodyguard.
Maybe one with a nice six pack.
You should consider
yourself lucky, Emi.
Huh?
[RIKA] You know,
you've got that guy
you were talking to before.
Wha--? That guy's a twit!
You two gotta be
close to know that.
Sorry, I'm gonna be a
Nosy Nancy, now dish.
Who is that hot guy anyway?
He--Whatever; he means
absolutely nothing to me!
[RIKA] I'm leaving
some towels here for you.
[EMI] Cool. Thank you, Rika!
[thinking] This feeling.
What could it be?
It's so warm.
Is this the power
of the human heart?
If so, is that what
was affecting him
when he saved those people?
[door being unlocked]
Jeez, what do you want?
It's early.
[EMI] Don't worry.
It's not poison or razorblades
or anything like that.
[MAOU] Funny, 'cause
I can't think of any reason
you'd give me
something not dangerous.
[EMI] Oh, well sweet.
Does that mean I get to
keep the money I owe you?
[EMI] Consider us even.
Huh? Hardly. Or did
you forget your promise
to leave us alone for a while?
Did you forget how
I bailed your asses out?
Like I said, even!
Ya still suck!
Yeah, shut up.
How's Alciel?
Did he make it out
of the collapse okay?
For the most part;
he's not physically injured.
But he seems to have taken
a sizable psychological hit.
[ASHIYA] Please, Your Majesty!
Oh Sire.
Forgive me!
[MAOU] I told him
about I'd gotten some
of my power back.
But he still beat himself
up all night for not being able
to do anything for
his "king in crisis,"
so he's taking the
morning off and sleeping in.
Yeesh.
So what about you?
Have you had the chance to
recover from our little attack?
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but you used some of your
power to put Chi to sleep.
Yeah-- Thank you for asking,
but you don't get
to know everything.
Fine, be that way.
And feel free to skedaddle, too.
[EMI] My pleasure!
It's too early for this.
Oh and be careful with
those shoes on the stairs.
[scream and tumbling sounds]
It's an ambush!
[ASHIYA] I have never!
For the Hero who very nearly
vanquished King Satan--
even in this assumed
form--to sustain
so many injuries falling down
a simple flight of stairs?
Well, you have sullied
His Majesty's reputation!
Oh. We only have bandages.
I thought we
purchased gauze;
did that not happen?
[MAOU] Apparently not.
I know it's a pain,
but would you make a quick run
to the pharmacy
and pick some up?
Medical tape, too.
I really don't wanna have to
hear her whining at me again.
[ASHIYA] As you wish, Sire.
Might I borrow Dullahan
for this journey?
[MAOU] Permission granted.
[MAOU] Guess we can go
ahead and disinfect it.
Here. Use this to--
[EMI] Don't touch me!
I can handle it myself!
[MAOU] Jeez.
Well excuse me, princess.
Have at it.
Stings a bit, huh?
Does this?
Dude, what
was that for? Chill out!
[EMI] Shut up!
What are you doing?
You're the Devil.
So why haven't you been
acting like a demon at all?
Like, not a single atrocity?
I honestly don't understand
where all this is coming from.
[EMI] No?
You're poor, you cook, you're
respected at your lame job,
you charm your way into the
hearts of high school girls.
I have never heard
of a Devil being proud
of some random teenager
havin' a crush on him!
That part seems
a little personal.
[EMI] Because it was personal!
Well, I've never
seen a "hero" who's
so inept that she falls
down stairs, cries,
and has to get put back
together by a couple demons!
[EMI] Why are you
being so courteous?
[MAOU] What?
Why be nice to me?
To people?
Why are you being
nice to this world?
[sniffs]
If you have the
capacity for compassion.
capacity for kindness.
Why didn't you show it
when you killed my father?
The Devil I know
is cruel and vicious.
He murders humans and squashes
them under his feet
like they were bugs.
And you know what
makes that Devil happy?
Death and destruction
and sorrow and blood!
[MAOU] I, uh--
[EMI] You burned our
fields with your fire.
Destroyed our castles
with lightning.
You swept away
our towns with floods!
You're the ruler of demons
and you allow your
monsters any brutality!
I swear, I will
never forgive you!
Our home, our fields,
my father's life.
You took away
everything I've ever loved.
I was happy!
You destroyed it all!
Never. I'll never forgive you!
[MAOU] Wow, okay.
I've never given it
much thought, but--
I'm sorry, ya know.
Back then.
I didn't really understand
what humans were like.
Morning, Mister Maou!
Look who I ran into while
I was at the pharmacy!
I asked her to come by, and--
And I should not have come.
I'm interrupting something.
You-- You two
really are a thing.
[MAOU] Chi? No.
I swear we're not--
It's not how it looks!
Uh-huh! M'sorry.
[MAOU] Chiho!
[EMI] So, that was bad.
[MIKI] My, a lovers' quarrel
with his old flame over
his beautiful new girl.
And without warning,
the newest sweetheart
arrives on the scene,
just in time to
discover her darling love
never truthfully broke
things off with his ex.
Well, this is the variety
of sordid romantic drama
that's syrupy enough
to cause the diabetes.
Yes! I feel the same way!
[MAOU] Of course you do.
[MIKI]
I'm Miki Shiba,
and the landlady of
this fine establishment.
I take it you are
Mister Maou's girlfriend?
Or one of them
at the very least?
I'm not dating this loser!
You're the loser!
Miss Shiba--
Non! "Mikitty," please.
Right. Forgot.
[MIKI] Listen kids.
I'm having some repairs
done to the building.
This is my official
notification to the tenants.
Quite a few disturbing
occurrences these days.
Cave-ins and muggings
and what-have-you.
[EMI] Uh huh.
I wonder if something will
happen again today, don't you?
I uh-- I hope not.
[MIKI] Which reminds me,
that adorable young lady
who was just here seems
to have run off toward
the train station in tears.
[EMI] Another earthquake?
[MIKI] Mister Maou.
[MAOU] Yeah?
If you've involved her,
I hope you're prepared
to take full responsibility.
[MAOU] For what?
Come now; surely
you've realized the truth?
That child took
a direct sonar hit
and received an
idea-link transmission.
An earthquake at this moment
is hardly a coincidence.
A human being's thought
and will have
immense power, right?
I imagine if anyone
knew that to be a fact,
it would be the three of you.
In my opinion,
you should to run
to her rescue
before it's too late.
[MAOU] That was weird.
[ALBERT in Ente Islan]
[EMERALDA in Ente Islan]
[sobbing]
[CHIHO] Why--
Why am I even crying?
[CHIHO] I can't believe it.
I must love
Mister Maou, after all.
[CHIHO] I'm sorry.
[MALE YOUTH] Well, well,
you'll make a nice meal.
[MALE YOUTH]
I've been watching you
since my massive fail earlier.
Y'know, just in case.
But I never figured you'd
get so miserable so easily.
Chiho Sasaki.
[MALE YOUTH] I'm gonna
feed on your bitterness
and despair over the
Devil and the Hero.
With your sad little heart,
I'll materialize right here!
Hey, get out
of the way, bro.
[crashing sounds]
[MALE YOUTH]
It's time for the hunt.
Today I rise above
Satan himself!
This won't go well for us.
[MAOU] It's him.
Him who? Hang on.
Is that who's been
behind all of this?
Isn't it obvious?
I knew it was you.
No. No, it can't be!
[MALE YOUTH] Oh. If it
isn't the great King Satan.
Oh, right. I suppose
I should call you Sadao Maou
from now on, yeah?
Call me whatever you want.
Why are you here?
Aren't you dead?
Demon General Lucifer?