[NARRATOR] In the
great sea of Ignora
lay five islands in
the shape of a cross.
Four point in each
cardinal direction
around a larger central island
to form Ente Isla;
the islands protected
by the gods.
All who lived in
Ente Isla knew of Satan,
ruler of demons.
His very name was synonymous
with the terror and cruelty
that ruled his demon realm,
as well as the creatures
of the night that
thrived in its depravity.
Satan was an
ambitious ruler.
He sought to crush the
humans and their world,
thereby creating a land
of peace and prosperity
for all night's creatures.
Four trusted
generals served the Devil;
Adramelech, Lucifer,
Alciel, and Malacoda.
These four great
demons launched
merciless attacks on
the four continents.
[screams]
[NARRATOR] However, a lone
hero rose up against them,
sacred sword in hand.
[NARRATOR] Along with
a band of comrades,
the hero crushed
Lucifer's army to the west.
They went on to defeat
Adramelech in the north,
and Malacoda in the south.
Then the federation of
knights, led by this hero,
invaded the central continent,
where the Demon Lord
kept his castle.
[ALCIEL in Ente Islan]
[EMERALDA in Ente Islan]
[SATAN in Ente Islan]
[ALCIEL in Ente Islan]
[SASAKI] Hey kids!
Excuse me a sec.
Mind if we talk to you?
Oh. Looks like we got
a couple of foreigners.
Well, that should
make this a good story.
Do you understand the
words I'm saying right now?
[SASAKI] You think
they'd be hot, huh?
Dressed up like that.
[COP 1A] I believe
they're cosplaying, sir.
It's weird, though,
we don't get much of their
kind in this neighborhood.
This is Sasaki out on patrol.
I've got a couple of youths
with minor injuries here.
[ALCIEL in Ente Islan]
[SATAN in Ente Islan]
Now boys, would you mind
joining us in the car?
You're not in trouble, so--
[SASAKI] Okay, you two,
behave yourselves.
Uh. This is
katsudon, okay?
Cot-su-dawn.
Yes, that's right. Yes.
[SATAN] They coated animal
flesh in some sort of grain
and fried it in hot oil.
Then, a mangled bird
embryo was placed on top,
and the whole thing was heated
even further in a fish broth.
[SASAKI] Look. I'm not
supposed to provide food,
but I can't let two
injured kids go hungry.
We'll just call it my treat.
Huh? O' course.
[ALCIEL in Ente Islan]
[COP 1A] Hey, now, son!
You can't just waltz on in here!
[COP 1A] Right.
[ALCIEL in Ente Islan]
[SATAN in Ente Islan]
[SATAN] We find ourselves
in one of Earth's nations.
An archipelago which
they call "Japan."
We stand now in its
capital of "Tokyo."
And this building is someplace
they call a "Police Station."
These "police" are evidently
a state institution
maintaining public order.
I see, Sire.
And what is that substance
on the table they fed me?
[SATAN]
"Cat's Doom."
It is an extremely common
food in this country.
[ALCIEL] "Cat's Doom."
Yes, that name has
a powerful ring to it.
This is of great interest.
Incorrect.
Now, focus.
Food is neither interesting
nor important right now.
In this world we
are only fantasies.
These humans don't consider
things like demons
or even the Devil
to be authentic;
no one believes magic
legitimately exists.
They do not
believe in magic?
How do they survive?
[ALCIEL] I see.
So because there is insufficient
magic in this pathetic realm,
we are unable to retain
our demonic forms?
Yes.
But I never imagined stripping
our magic would cause this.
Our physical change
makes me wonder if humans
might actually be the foundation
for all living creatures.
[ALCIEL] Surely you jest, Sire.
I'm certain 'tis merely
an effect of this world
and the Gate.
[SATAN] I still retain
a fraction of my magic.
But 'tis quite an effort
to stem its outward flow.
How is it with you, Alciel?
[ALCIEL] Looks like
it worked, Sire.
[SATAN] No. I highly
doubt this carriage
was conjured with magic.
[ALCIEL] Alas.
[SATAN] If I adjust the
amount of magic I release,
I won't run out for
a fair amount time.
The undeniable problem is
we currently have no way
to amass more. However,
if the Earth is familiar
with the concept of magic,
even as "imaginary,"
we may have a chance.
The path left to us now,
is to discover that method
and regain our natural strength.
Until then, we have no choice
but to live in this world,
and obey these humans' rules.
[ALCIEL] What a
cruel reality this is.
[SATAN] Indeed. But we might
as well do what we can.
[SATAN] We must obtain
official "Records"
at what is called
a "Ward Office."
Huh? Okay. Here.
[SATAN] Good. Next, we
create accounts at the "bank."
To do so, we use this.
[ALCIEL] What is that paper?
'Tis this country's currency.
I borrowed it from that
police officer human
right before I created
our own personal seal.
I have to say I'm
rather proud of myself.
As am I.
[FEMALE BANK CLERK 1A]
Here you are.
[SATAN] Good. Lastly,
we must secure a base
of operations
from a "ree-la-tore."
[MALE REALTOR 1B]
Sure, what sorta home
did you have in mind, Sir?
[MALE REALTOR 1A]
The landlady at this location
is a very admirable person.
If I may speak frankly,
she says she wants to set an
example by taking on persons
of unknown backgrounds, like
the two of you fine gentlemen.
[ALCIEL in Ente Islan]
[SATAN in Ente Islan]
[MALE REALTOR 1A]
You'd be renting room 201 here.
[SATAN in Ente Islan]
[MIKI] Good afternoon.
[MIKI] You two
adorable creatures
are the new rental
applicants, correct?
[MALE REALTOR 1A] This
woman owns these apartments.
And lives next door.
The name's Miki Shiba.
In kanji, that's with characters
meaning "beauty" and "radiance."
Ah. But please boys,
call me "Mi-kitty" instead.
That's so much more fun, no?
[ALCIEL] Sire.
Are you sure we should
waste our time here?
[SATAN] Remember, in this
world they like the saying,
"Patience is a virtue."
In the end,
this castle might be
a welcome change of pace.
[ALCIEL] Oh, Sire.
[SATAN] We have no other choice,
but we will move
forward from here. We--
King Satan! Sire!
[ALCIEL] King Satan!
[SATAN] I didn't realize this
body was one that required food.
Well, you do have a
human body now, Sire.
That gruesome IV drip
thing will cost us
as much as a full month's
rent on the castle.
You know what that's called?
"Rubbing salt in a wound!" Tis
what the nurse said, at least.
[ALCIEL] That uncanny
landlady spared us
a good deal of trouble, Sire.
She tells me that
Japan requires residents
to carry something
called "health insurance."
[SATAN] Never mind her!
Money is clearly of the
essence in this human society,
so we need to
possess it somehow.
I cannot afford to
expend more of my magic,
so that means we really have
only one option left to us.
And what is that, Sire?
Curses, did it wrong again.
You idiot!
Résumé forms do not
grow on trees, you know!
[MAOU] Okay, my new
name is Sadao Maou.
[ASHIYA] And mine,
Shiro Ashiya.
Do you find this
name strange, Sire?
It's a little late
to ask that now;
we've already
made both our IDs.
[ASHIYA] King Satan.
[MAOU] Yeah?
[ASHIYA] Might I suggest you put
a little more thought
into your spending?
Gimme a break;
I put thought in spending.
Summer's around the corner,
so we need a fridge.
Owning a washing
machine is cheaper
than a Laundromat
in the long run.
And, I have to have
the bike to get to work.
It's not what
you purchased
that concerns me, Sire.
I just think paying in
installments would have been
a better choice than
buying them all at once.
[MAOU] Well, I hate loans, so--
Don't "so" me, Sire.
Nag all you want,
but installment plans
come with interest and fees.
And I ain't gonna
pay for something
I can't touch with
my own two hands.
Impeccably worded, Sire.
But do tell me.
How are we supposed
to make it to payday
on milk, jelly, and--
Oh wait! We have cucumbers, too?
[MAOU] I see your point.
But calm down, it's not like
we don't have any money left.
I have still have some cash.
We'll be fine until payday.
Don't forget, they give me
lots of food at work, too!
[ASHIYA] We're gonna die.
[talks faster and faster] You
propose we eat burgers and fries
three times a day
until you get paid?
What is this, Super Size Me ?
You plan to eat a high-calorie,
high-cholesterol diet
at such a young age?
I'm looking forward
to the next ten years,
but now I'll have to hope
you don't die prematurely
of a lifestyle-related
illness before we get home.
I must apologize for
my cowardice, Sire;
however, you're the one who
argued for biding our time!
You of all people ought to prize
constant diligence
and health maintenance!
[MAOU] Stop freaking out!
I gotta go to work.
[ASHIYA] Wait, Sire!
[MAOU] Lecture me later!
[ASHIYA] That's not it;
you forgot your umbrella.
Let's roll, Dullahan! Hiyaa!
And he's off.
Guess I'll get ready, too.
Here, you can take this.
Please, all yours.
I, um-- okay?
I'm not going that far--just
to the train station.
I work at the
MgRonald's over there.
Thanks.
You can throw it
out for all I care!
Whu-hoa, that is brisk!
[MAOU] This week is key!
Soon, we will know who had
the highest featured
item sales in our district!
I swear, I will be
the one who breaks
the sales record for
black pepper fries!
Hello, and welcome.
Would you like to
try a meal today, sir?
[MALE CUSTOMER 1A] Nah, just a
cheeseburger and a small Spark?
Of course, sir.
Might I also interest you
in some Black Pepper
Fries with that;
it's our featured item?
[MALE CUSTOMER 1A]
Nah; thanks, though.
[MAOU] Yes, these little
continuous efforts are necessary
for my eventual comeback
as lord of demons!
Let me get your change.
[CHIHO] That's one chicken
sandwich, one iced coffee,
and one Happiness Meal.
Will that be cash or card?
Hi, Ma'am.
We hope you're
having a great day.
I'd be happy to let you use
our microwave if you want.
[MAOU] Have you brought any milk
or baby food with you?
I don't mind
heating it up at all.
Uh... You sure that's okay?
Of course; my pleasure.
Mister Maou,
you are like super way cool!
I can't believe you
thought of her baby's food;
that was so sweet!
Oh, no big deal.
Accommodating all of
our customers' needs
when we have the time gives
us a long-term advantage.
I was just doing my thing.
You are beyond
incredible!
You're like a for-real grown up!
Thanks. But hardly.
I'm just a part-timer.
Curses.
I can't believe you
were fired again, Ashiya.
You suck.
I wish you'd keep
calling me Alciel, Sire.
I wish you'd get over it,
but that's not important.
We need to focus on
finding a way home,
not doing awful
day labor, capisce?
[ASHIYA] Right.
And your point, Sire?
[MAOU] You are now
in charge of finding
a way to get our magic back.
I'll work and get money;
you do research.
Magic's at least a concept here,
so if we trace that alleged
fantasy back to its source;
well, maybe we'll be able to
find something that's helpful.
Do you believe
there's a chance
we can recover our powers?
Hopin' so.
I mean, why stop
at just Ente Isla?
Why not rule this world, too?
I like this plan so
much better, don't you?
Yes, Sire! I do!
[MAOU] It's Maou.
[ASHIYA]
As you wish, Sire. Maou.
I, Alciel, vow to discover
the path to your supremacy.
You will rule all worlds!
Thank you,
Alciel; now rise.
You're embarrassing me.
Yet still.
We got nothin'.
Guess what!
I totally got a raise today!
I don't trust
that new guy;
he's too good for my own good.
You're excited to
be the lowest person
on the fast-food
totem pole, Sire.
If the Devil is
considered nothing more
than an underling,
what does that make me?
Though, how can I judge?
I can't even do
research properly.
[ASHIYA] With only books to go
on, all I can do is speculate.
[rumbling]
[ASHIYA] Earthquake?
[CHIHO] Mister Maou,
it's an earthquake.
[MAOU] Mmmm.
So it is.
Hey, Chi.
Yeah?
Everyone
makes mistakes.
[CHIHO] But it's the sixth
time I've dropped fries
on the floor this month!
I'm the klutziest
person in the world!
[MAOU] Yeah, I guess you
do drop 'em every other day.
[CHIHO] All I do is
clean up after myself
while everyone else
waits on customers.
At this rate, potatoes will
start sprouting from the floor!
Hey, I know you
guys are on break,
but I need a quick minute.
I'm not that scary, Chi.
[MAOU] Is everything
okay, Manager?
Wouldja please
call me, Miss Kisaki?
It's getting crowded out there.
When your breaks are over,
I want you both at
a hundred percent.
This is when the fight
for number one gets real.
So, bring it.
Oh, and Chi, sweetie,
try not to plant too many
potatoes, kay? Thank you.
Yes, Ma'am.
[CHIHO] One Big Mig meal
with black pepper fries. Got it.
[MALE PART TIMER 1A]
Will that be cash or card?
Can I take your order?
[MALE STUDENT 1A]
Fries and your phone number?
[snickering]
Yeah not on the
menu, sorry!
[MAOU] If we keep
this up, we'll do it!
We can be number
one in the district!
[MAOU] They're not
cooked all the way?
Don't tell me
the fryer's broken!
[MAOU] Why did it have to
be the black pepper fryer?
Okay, Maou, focus! What now?
If I don't do something,
being number one is
the least of our problems.
[MAOU] Should I use magic?
It is kind of an emergency.
Make sure you
save your magic only
for extreme emergencies, Sire.
[KISAKI] What's wrong?
[MAOU] Life is fail.
[CHIHO] It's not
your fault, Mister Maou.
Everything's fine;
the guys fixing the fryer
will be done by tonight.
Yo-yo-Maa,
you got a sec?
Sure.
[MAOU] What's going on?
Is she gonna blame me for
us not getting number one?
Surely not.
It's not like
I broke the lousy thing.
Maybe she's suspicious
because I was
about to use magic!
[KISAKI] Thanks for
waiting. At ease, kid.
It's not bad. In fact,
I'm gonna make your day.
I was just waiting
to get final approval
from our district office.
[MAOU] Oh. For what?
For your promotion.
Sadao Maou, as of today,
you are A-level staff.
[MAOU] Aw yeah!
I am A-level staff, Ashiya!
I got a raise! I'm a rock star!
[EMILIA] Hey.
[MAOU] Hey, it's you.
I went to your restaurant
after our conversation.
Oh. You did, really?
I'm sorry; I didn't see you.
Next time, just say something,
and I'll come say hi.
[EMILIA] I watched you all day
from the bookstore
across the street.
You look so different.
I thought for a second
I must be wrong,
but then I saw you
start to cast a spell.
A spell? What?
Wait. Who are you?
[EMILIA] First tell me why
you're working part-time
at a MgRonald's!
Why, Satan?
The Hero, Emilia?