[GOKU] Now's your chance!
[NARRATOR] It was a moment
that shook the earth...
When a brave young boy
stepped into his father's shoes,
and put an end to the evil
creation known as Cell.
[CELL yells]
[NARRATOR]
That was several years ago.
[NARRATOR] Thanks to
the sacrifice of a hero
named Goku, and the
great courage of his son,
the Earth's future
has been redirected,
and its people have a new
chance at keeping the peace.
[NARRATOR] And in many ways,
that chance
has not been wasted.
These last few years
have been calm and prosperous,
as the entire world
was reminded
of how precious peace can be.
[NARRATOR] Of course,
it never takes long
for that lesson
to be forgotten.
[ROBBER 1] Let's do this!
[BYSTANDER whimpers]
[GUARD groans]
[chuckling]
--[FEMALE CLERK 1 shrieks]
--[ROBBER 3] Hey, sweetie!
[NARRATOR] Elsewhere,
a young man is flying towards
that same city on
a familiar golden cloud.
The boy who saved
the world has become...
a teenager.
[NARRATOR] With no more
trips across the galaxy
or lethal androids to fight,
Gohan has at last
been free to do his studies
like his mother wanted.
And since his mountain village
was far from any schools,
he did his education at home,
under ChiChi's careful eye.
But now, Gohan has decided
to enroll in high school
with other students,
ready to try his luck
at normal life.
Here we go!
I guess this is Satan City.
Hey, thanks
for the lift, Nimbus!
I'll catch you
after class, okay?
[GOHAN thinking]
Dad, you've got to see this.
I know you'd
have a good laugh.
The whole world thinks Hercule
was the one who beat Cell.
And now they've even
named a city after him!
[GOHAN chuckles]
Probably for the best.
"Goku-And-Gohan Town" would
sound kind of silly. Heh.
[NARRATOR] Hurry, Gohan.
You'd hate to be late to class!
[whimpering]
That's right! Nobody be a hero!
Stay down!
[ROBBER 5] Let's get moving!
[ROBBER 1]
You heard him, lady! Hurry up!
Done! All the bags are filled!
Fine! Let's roll!
And now I'd like to thank you
all for your cooperation!
[yelling, screaming]
Ah, look at the time.
At this rate,
I'll never make it.
[GOHAN] Turbo speed!
[BOTH gasp]
[GOHAN] What's going on here?
[POLICEMAN 1 whimpers]
[ROBBER 4 laughs]
You just try and stop us!
Ooh!
Aw... Another batch of crooks.
It never ends!
I guess if I transform
then no one will recognize me!
[GOHAN grunts]
Is this the best
you pigs can do?!
[chuckles]
Aah!
[gasps, groans]
Huh? Who's that?
[ROBBER 5]
You little--! Eat lead!
[gasps]
I... Uh...!
[ROBBER 5 groans]
He's... a monster!
Let's go!
[yells]
[ROBBER 1 and 3 groan]
Who was that guy?!
Amazing!
Ehhh! Oh dear.
But where'd he go?
[BYSTANDERS murmur]
Hey... did we do that?
You!
Tell me who did this!
It hardly looks
like police work!
[GOHAN] Oh...
I-I guess I wasn't looking...
I can't believe I missed it!
I should've stopped them!
[OLD MAN] Oh... Hey, Videl!
I was wondering
when you'd show up!
Wasn't that
Golden Fighter incredible?
A golden fighter? Explain.
You mean you really
didn't see him?
He was some kind of
freakish superhuman!
Wuuuh--I saw him knock down
a truck by yelling at it!
Actually I assumed
he was a buddy of yours
since he went to
your high school.
Huh?
Yeah, he had a badge just like
that one on his shirt.
All the kids at school
have to wear this thing.
Well if he really goes there...
I will find him!
[school bell chimes]
[commotion]
Hey... Sharpner...
Don't tell me
you're the Golden Fighter!
Oh spare me!
I don't have time
to play superhero.
I spent all morning
working out my arms.
So Videl...
Do you think this guy could
be stronger than your pops?!
What a joke!
We all know Videl's dad
is the strongest there is!
He could knock this gold boy
out by flexing his biceps!
He's strong.
[clears throat]
[MALE TEACHER] Good morning,
my young scholars...
Today we are being graced
with a new class member
who actually
knows how to read.
That's your cue, my boy.
Oh. Good morning.
My name's Gohan.
Nice to meet you.
Oooh! Look at him, Videl!
He's a cutie!
[GLASSES BOY]
What kind of name is Gohan?
Huh?
That's weird.
He looks familiar...
[SHARPNER chuckles]
He was probably
on a TV spelling bee.
[MALE TEACHER]
Gohan here made perfect scores
on all his entry exams.
English, Math, Chemistry...
Uh, many of you could
learn from his example.
[MALE STUDENT] Example this!
Silence! You kids are an
embarrassment to public school!
Well... Gohan, you may sit
wherever you'd like to sit.
Okay.
Uh...
[GIRL] Yoo-hoo! New boy!
Here's one.
Oh! Sure. Thank you.
Huh?
[giggles]
Nice to meet you.
I'm Erasa! With an "E"!
And this is my friend Videl!
[GOHAN gasps]
Please open your textbooks
to the page twenty-four.
Gohan... You wanna know
who Videl's pop is?
You'll be surprised!
She's the daughter
of Mr. Satan!
What?! Mr. Satan?!
[ERASA] Yup! The one and only!
I knew you'd be surprised!
Well that must be neat.
You being a celebrity's
daughter and all.
Our Videl is a special gal.
Of course being the friend
of a daughter of a celebrity
is pretty good too, you know!
So you're the guy!
[GOHAN gasps]
Yeah. You're the guy
who I talked to outside of
the bank this morning!
Yes, I am.
Wow! Right after
the Gold Fighter vanished?
Who? The Gold Fighter?
Is he a celebrity too?
Where are you from?
You're out of the gossip loop!
He's a crime fighter with
super strength and magic powers!
They say he looks
like a teenage boy
except he has
glowing golden hair!
Everyone's talking about it.
[GOHAN thinking]
Uh-oh! It's been five hours
and they've already
made a legend out of me.
[GOHAN gasps]
[VIDEL] Hmph!
[GOHAN thinking] Does she know?!
Now, let's see
if you can find
the unessential clause
in this sentence.
"On the bus I told my friend
who knew me well
a very important secret."
--[FEMALE TEACHER] Well...
--[VIDEL] Gohan!
Huh?
I remembered something.
What the Gold Fighter
was said to be wearing...
It was a white shirt,
a black vest,
and red pants.
Sound familiar?
Uh...
[ERASA] Hey, that's funny!
You and the
Gold Fighter dress alike!
Uh, yeah. Funny...
[FEMALE TEACHER] You three
in the back! Pay attention!
Yes. Yes ma'am.
Good... Now then...
The essential clause
"that" is...
[SHARPNER laughs]
Come on, Videl.
You know he can't
be the Gold Fighter.
Who in the world's ever heard
of a little book nerd
secretly being a superhero?
The guy's gotta be buff.
Ignore him.
I bet you could
fight crime if you wanted.
Oh, I doubt it...
[VIDEL thinking]
Of course it's not him.
His hair's not even right.
But then again...
Those fighters
in the Cell Game videos
turned their hair gold, too.
Although Dad said
it was a cheap trick.
[ERASA] So, uh, did you
just move into the city?
Maybe we could
study at your house.
Well... actually I commute here.
Oh, that's cool. Where from?
The... 439 Mountain Area.
See, it's... pretty small.
What?! Oh, get out of here!
The 439 Area
is like 500 miles away!
Hey! Excuse me, miss!
But I am trying to
teach a class here!
[ERASA gasps] I'm sorry!
How in the world
do you get here?!
That's gotta be close to
a five hour car drive!
Yes, well, uh...
That's how dedicated
I am to my education.
[GOHAN chuckles]
[GOHAN thinking] I can't
believe I just said that.
Now, let's move forward.
Creating the complex sentence.
Can I get a volunteer to read
this sample paragraph?
[GOHAN thinking] That's crazy!
They even talk about Hercule
in the grammar exercises.
Hey! Brains!
Volunteer and show us
how good you read!
[GOHAN] Huh?
Yeah! Do it!
--[ERASA giggles]
--[GOHAN yells nervously]
[FEMALE TEACHER]
Excellent! A volunteer!
Now, I haven't quite
learned your name yet.
This is Gohan,
the perfect test-score boy.
Oh, that's right.
Well, Gohan, now go ahead.
Yes, ma'am...
Now what am I...
doing exactly? Heh heh.
[SHARPNER chuckles]
You're reading the paragraph!
Oh right!
"Mr. Satan went to
the city that was then called
Orange Star City
and started a happy family.
After he beat Cell,
who was very evil,
the city changed its name.
Even though
the world is now safe,
Mr. Satan keeps
his fitness routine,
which includes running laps
and breaking heavy rocks."
[MR. SATAN sneezes]
You guys need to
work a little harder!
Being the greatest fighter in
the world isn't easy you know!
[MR. SATAN laughs]
[birds chirping]
All right, boys and girls.
Today, we'll be battling it out
in the great sport of baseball.
Brains...
You know what baseball is?
Uh, yeah. Well, I've read
a couple books about it.
Oh, have you? [chuckles]
Well then, I'm sure you'll be
the next all-star on your team!
Hey, you can have him.
My team just filled up!
Oh yeah, thanks.
Come on!
Give him a break.
I bet he could
think of a bunch of
really great strategies since
he's such a smarty!
Okay. Fine...
I'm putting you
in right field.
Do you know where that is?
Yeah! On the right! Right?
Right...
Just get on to the field.
[CHICHI] It sure is quiet
around here without Gohan.
I should've gone with him.
I'm so nervous.
I sure hope those
teenagers treat him right!
[metal clangs]
[GOHAN thinking] Mom told me
not to show off my real power,
and I'm really trying not to.
But why should I hide it?
This whole "fitting in"
thing is really weird.
[SHARPNER clears throat]
Hmph! Hope you're
ready for a strike!
[SHARPNER chuckles]
[VIDEL grunts]
[SHARPNER grunts]
Aah!
[cheering]
[BOY] What a hit!
[ALL gasp]
[GOHAN thinking] The runner
on third's left the base.
That means if I throw it
to third, he'll be out!
Okay...
Nice and slow. Not too hard.
[GOHAN grunts]
Aaah...
[grunts, groans]
Like, third and out.
All right!
I think I'm really getting
the hang of this game!
Uh?
[VIDEL gasps]
[GOHAN thinking] Oops...
I guess that was a little much.
[COACH]
That move was beautiful, Gohan!
You must have jumped
twenty-five feet into the air!
Way to go, son!
[GOHAN]
Oh, it was beginner's luck.
I-I just got some...
new shoes. Yeah!
With the air cushions, y'know!
They sure make
a difference, huh?
Right. It's gotta be the shoes.
Hey, man, I think it's
your turn to bat, isn't it?
Huh? Oh! Yeah, I'm up!
Hold on, guys! Here I come!
So, does he swing
as hard as he throws?
You heard him! He said
it was just beginner's luck!
That's the left-handed
batter's box, son...
[GOHAN] Is that bad?
Well, no, just...
most right-handers
bat from the other side.
Oh? How come?
Well... why don't you swing
there and see how it works?
So brain-boy thinks
he can catch my hits?
I'll just have to
give him a good scare.
[GOHAN thinking] I don't want to
show any more of my strength.
I better not swing.
[SHARPNER] I'll have you
ducking for cover like a sissy.
[SHARPNER chuckles]
[SHARPNER grunts]
Watch out!
[GOHAN grunts]
Ngh!
Aah! You idiot!
Why didn't you
duck like a sissy?!
[CATCHER 4 whimpers]
Coach... if I get hit,
that means that I walk, right?
--[COACH] Right.
--[GOHAN chuckles]
[GOHAN thinking]
That worked perfectly!
I got to base and didn't have
to show my strength! Heh heh.
What... the heck... is he?!
Bizarre...
[school bell chimes]
Gohan. What clubs
have you joined?
I haven't... joined any...
Good. You can
join the boxing club.
With a little practice, you just
might become a good fighter.
Thanks. But I don't think
I can join any clubs...
'cause...
'Cause he's got an extra,
extra long drive home
and doesn't have any time
to spend on clubs, right, Gohan?
Yeah, that's it!
[ERASA] Now Gohan...
what's say you give me
a ride home on your way out?
Oh well, uh--
I'm afraid that my ride
is just a one-seater!
I've got room
in my car, Erasa.
Sounds like a plan to me!
Now this is strange.
He says he lives very far away
but now he seems
to be walking home.
[GOHAN] Hmm?
[VIDEL panting]
Huh?
[GOHAN] Whew!
So many close calls!
I need a way
to use my powers...
without letting all of
my classmates know...
[GOHAN] Hmm...
Maybe Bulma can help...
[NARRATOR] So Gohan's first day
of class comes to an end.
But it seems the real
excitement is just starting up.