[NARRATOR] Last time
on DragonBall Z:
He's the ultimate evil,
he's an android,
he's unstoppable!
His name is Cell
and he's loose in the city!
Any unsuspecting
citizens become snacks
if they are unfortunate
enough to cross his path!
[WOMAN A]
[MAN A] No, please! No! No!
[MAN A gurgles]
[NARRATOR] Trunks and Krillin
descended into the depths
of Dr. Gero's ruined lab to
destroy the unfinished Cell,
and came across
something unexpected:
the plans to Android 17!
[TRUNKS] Yes! This could
be our lucky break.
By studying this
we might be able to find
Android 17's weak spot!
[KRILLIN grunts]
[NARRATOR] The boys
blasted what was left
of the evil doctor's lab
and headed back to
decipher Android 17's plans.
But Cell has made plans of his
own for the other androids
and he is intent on
carrying them out.
[NARRATOR] If Cell has his way,
he will absorb
the other androids
and become a complete,
pure-evil entity.
And that's when the
trouble will really begin.
[NARRATOR] Now that's a scene
worthy of a postcard isn't it?
Wrong! Something's not
right about this picture.
It's quiet. Too quiet.
There's an evil in the air
and it has taken over
the whole town.
[music plays]
[NARRATOR] The strangest
thing of all is the people;
Where have they all gone?
It's as if they
never existed at all.
[AEROBICS GIRL] And one,
and two, and one, and two!
Come on, girls! Look alive!
[NARRATOR] What should be a busy
street in the middle of the day
has now become
silent and empty.
There's sure to be a
vacancy at the local hotel
and I guarantee it
won't be a problem
getting a good table
in the restaurant.
Just seat yourself.
Oh! And you'll have to
serve yourself as well.
Everywhere you look
is a disaster area.
[OPERATOR] Hello?
[NARRATOR] It's as
if time has stopped.
How could this have happened?
What could have caused such
widespread devastation?
There can be only one answer:
There's a monster on the loose.
[CROWD screaming]
[machine gun firing]
[screaming continues]
[GUNMAN screams]
[NEWS ANCHOR] At this point,
the most important thing
for anyone listening to this
broadcast to do is remain calm.
Now, we're live with the
latest update on the situation.
[REPORTER 1] I'm standing
here in Nicky Town,
where normally the
street you see behind me
would be alive with the
activities of everyday life.
But today is not like every day.
Today, this once bustling
community stands a ghost town.
Law enforcement officials are at
a loss to explain
the mysterious disappearance
of the town's population.
But it seems that Nicky Town has
suffered the same tragic fate...
[GUNMAN screams]
[CELL chuckles]
All citizens should
remain indoors!
[screaming continues]
[CELL laughs]
Keep your television
tuned to this station
for further reports.
And do not go outdoors
unless you have to!
[gun clicks]
[GUNMAN gasps]
[REPORTER 1] If you encounter
the suspect remain calm.
Smile pleasantly and do not
make any sudden moves!
[GUNMAN screams]
[REPORTER 1] I suggest you
try distracting the intruder
by offering him a drink,
or something to eat
--until the authorities arrive.
--[GUNMAN screams]
Roy, back to you.
Thanks. That was Barry
Walters reporting live.
That ends tonight's broadcast.
I'm John Johnson.
Reminding to stay safe
and be prepared!
[CELL grunts]
[CELL] Heh. "Be prepared."
What's the point?
I will absorb them all,
one by one.
[CELL laughs]
[SISTER whimpers]
Aaahhh...
Anything?
[TIEN growls]
No, I can't sense
Cell anywhere now!
Darn!
We've got to find him before
he finds the other Androids!
[SISTER screams]
[BOTH panting]
[panting continues]
Wait, Sis!
[SISTER gasps]
[BROTHER whimpers]
[SISTER whimpers]
[SISTER gasps]
[CELL grunts]
[SISTER sobs]
[SISTER screams]
[BROTHER grunts]
[CELL yells]
[BOTH scream]
[CELL growls]
[CELL grunts]
[CELL] Hrngh?!
[KRILLIN growls]
Ha! It's Krillin!
How did you know I was here?
[KRILLIN] I could smell
you from a mile away!
[thinking] Just my luck! I try
to take a shortcut to Kame House
and I run into this monster!
[SISTER] Wow...
You're so brave!
[KRILLIN gasps]
Thanks for rescuing us!
[KRILLIN stammers]
Uh! No problem!
Now get out of here!
Right! Come on!
[KRILLIN sighs]
[thinking] Hey,
she's kinda cute!
[CELL laughs
This saves me
a lot of time!
I'm going to very much enjoy
draining you of your energy!
[KRILLIN growls]
[KRILLIN]
[CELL] There's no
need to resist!
[SISTER] Hurry, Tommy.
Come on!
[TOMMY grunts]
[CELL yells]
[KRILLIN gasps]
[KRILLIN grunts]
[CELL growls]
[KRILLIN shouts]
[SISTER] Yeah! Here we go!
[SISTER grunts]
[KRILLIN grunts]
[CELL grunts]
[thinking] I'd better
watch my step.
If I make one wrong move
he'll turn me inside out
and hang me out to dry!
[CELL yells]
Huh?!
Solar Flare!
[CELL yells]
[SISTER screams]
We're safe!
[KRILLIN sighs]
[KRILLIN growls]
He's gone?
Where is he?!
[TOMMY] Gosh, Sis!
That was a close one!
[SISTER screams]
Hang on!
--[CELL] Huh--?!
--[KRILLIN grunts]
[CELL rasps]
[CELL] Now... it's time...
[CELL] ...to die!
--[CELL yells]
--[KRILLIN gasps]
--[CELL growls]
--[KRILLIN screams]
[SISTER screams]
Oh no!
[KRILLIN grunts]
[KRILLIN gasps]
A valiant effort, Krillin.
But all in vain.
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL] We have company!
How rude of them
to interrupt.
This time you're lucky.
[KRILLIN grunts]
[CELL] What a shame we won't
get to know each other today
[KRILLIN] Uh...?
Ah-ah-ah!
[PICCOLO growls]
Now we just missed him!
Krillin, are you alright?
What do you think?
[thinking] I just don't
understand it!
[CELL] Goku is still alive?
[KRILLIN] Yeah, of course he is!
[CELL] Goku's alive...
So, this history is somehow
different from the one I know.
[TRUNKS thinking]
Even Cell knew it!
The timeline in this world is
playing out very differently
from the one we
knew in the future.
Nothing is happening
as I expected it to!
And I can't figure
out what it was
that threw things
so far off course!
[FRIEZA growls]
When I get my hands on-- Huh?!
[TRUNKS yells]
[FRIEZA whimpers]
[TRUNKS] My battle with Frieza
was three years ago now.
With the element of
surprise on my side
I defeated him and
his father easily.
But I knew it
wouldn't end there...
I came from the future to warn
Goku and his friends
of an even greater threat
that was on the way.
It was hard for them to believe,
but Frieza would be the
least of their problems.
[TRUNKS] Goku was unaware that
he would catch a deadly virus.
Of course,
how could he ever know?
But I felt that if I gave him
the antidote to save his life,
he would survive and be strong
enough to help me defeat
Dr. Gero's androids,
both in this world
and in my future world!
When I later came
back to this time,
I found that the
timeline I had expected
was slipping out of control.
Something had changed!
Goku was nowhere to be found.
Neither were the androids
that terrorized my world.
Instead, that strange Android 19
and the maniacal android version
of Dr. Gero had
appeared in their place!
[TRUNKS] At last,
Androids 17 and 18,
the androids I expected
to find did arrive.
But along with them came
yet another new android...
One that may be even more
terrible than the rest!
Why hadn't he been
activated in my time?
How many other evil schemes
had Dr. Gero planned of
which I was unaware?
I guess I learned the answer to
that question soon enough...
[ANDROID 16 sighs]
[TRUNKS] That's when
we discovered that Cell,
Dr. Gero's ultimate
creation had arrived.
That creature...
That terrible creature
from the future!
By my calculations he
must have arrived here
at least a year before I did...
Lying dormant until
the time was right
for him to unite with
Dr. Gero's other androids.
But I don't understand how the
ship he came here in
could be exactly
the same as mine?
In fact, that ship IS mine!
[TRUNKS] By travelling back
and forth through time,
have I unwillingly had
a negative effect
on the future of this world?
Am I responsible for
everything that has happened
up to this point?
Maybe I've had no effect
on anything at all!
Either way there is
no way of stopping
what's been set in motion!
The future is now!
[VEGETA] I am
now a Super Saiyan,
but I will not stop there!
I will ascend!
[TRUNKS] My father is right!
Now I must follow his lead
and find some way to push
myself to the next level.
[thinking] That may be the
only hope we have
of beating the Androids
and saving this world!
And mine...
[KRILLIN] Well, bon voyage...
[PICCOLO] He disappeared again!
I'm getting a little
tired of this routine!
We almost had him
this time, Piccolo.
We're getting closer and
closer to catching him
every time he shows himself!
He can't outrun us forever.
[KRILLIN thinking] Aww man, but
now we have to wait
until Cell attacks again
before we can find him...
How many innocent people is
that monster going to hurt?
[KRILLIN] We have to do
better than this, you guys!
We can't let this happen again!
[TIEN] We know, Krillin...
We're doing everything we can...
We'll find him.
[CELL chuckles]
Tell me again,
why are we off the road?
Come on. Where's your
sense of adventure, 18?
[brakes squeal]
16! Are we getting
close to Goku's house?
Yes. Not far now.
[ANDROID 18] Well... you look
like you're enjoying this too.
Really, the two of
you are hopeless.
[ANDROID 18 yells]
[ANDROID 18] See,
that's more like it!
Well done. Once again
you've managed to destroy
any possibility we
had of having fun.
Oh, stop complaining, 17.
Fun or no fun,
we'll get to Goku's house
much faster this way.
[NEWS ANCHOR] And now,
over to Beverly Jones
for the latest on the
creature crisis!
[REPORTER 2] The creature
continues its path
of relentless destruction,
sparing no one
who happens to
cross it's path.
Reports are coming
in from South City
that the creature has been
sighted all over town.
[PICCOLO] CELL!
[KRILLIN] He's on
the attack again!
What are we doing here
watching television?!
We should be
helping those people!
We out number Cell!
We can beat him!
That's it!
[YAMCHA] So long!
Gohan! Take care now!
[YAMCHA] As long as we
keep our energy levels down,
Cell won't be sense us
coming. Then he's ours!
Yeah, when all of us
jump out of this plane
and go after Cell at the same
time, he won't stand a chance!
Right! Together we'll
take him down!
There's no way he can
handle all of us.
You guys are right! If we
come at him from all sides,
he won't know what hit him!
[PICCOLO] Cell is
much smarter than that!
There's a good chance
he's expecting us
to try something like this.
Don't underestimate him.
--[crashing]
--[CHICHI screams]
What was that?!
Oh no, are the
Androids attacking?!
[ROSHI growls]
[CHICHI screams]
[ROSHI screams]
Will you stop that?!
Why'd you dump a
bucket on my head?!
[crashing]
[CHICHI screams]
[ROSHI screams]
Will you please
stop screaming now?!
If you wanted a
hug... well...
You could've just asked!
[ROSHI chuckles]
[ROSHI yells]
Thank you...
That was nice...
Good night...
[CHICHI gasps]
Goku!
Goku! What...?
[CHICHI] Goku...?
[CHICHI gasps]
[ROSHI] Huh? What's going on?
Huh?
Well, you sure don't
see that everyday...
[CHICHI gasps]
--Goku!
--Hey, Goku!
[CHICHI laughs]
[ROSHI chuckles]
Hey! Wait up!
[GOKU yells]
[ROSHI stammers]
[ROSHI yells]
[CHICHI] Goku!
[CHICHI laughs]
Hey!
Oh, Goku!
[CHICHI sobs]
I'm sorry I
worried you, ChiChi.
Everything's gonna be alright.
I'm all better now.
Are you sure, Goku?
Yeah! Here, see for yourself!
[BOTH laugh]
Oh, Goku!
[CHICHI screams]
Uh-oh...
I've really gotta start
watching my strength.
[CHICHI screams]
Oh my!
Sorry about that.
[GOKU laughs]
[ROSHI] Goku!
Oh, hi!
[ROSHI] So,
you're all better?
Sure! I feel just fine!
In my dreams I could hear
everything that was going on.
We're in deep trouble aren't we?
But... I'm not ready
to fight just yet...
Goku? Why not?
Of course he's not.
You still need to rest.
So just stay put!
Hey, I'm alright.
Just relax now...
It's time for me to start
my training once again!
It's time for me to
move to the next level!
[CHICHI gasps]
What?
[GOKU] Vegeta knows it too.
Through my dreams,
I could hear him speaking
what I had also felt.
That there is a level beyond
that of a Super Saiyan...
And I will rise to claim it!
Huh?!
[NARRATOR] Has Goku
lost his mind?
Maybe he's still
running a fever?
He seems determined to take
his Super Saiyan powers
to the next level. But is it
actually possible for him
to become an
Ascended Saiyan?
Find out on the
next Dragon Ball Z!