[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball Z,
as Trunks and Mr. Satan fought
a "friendly" exhibition match,
the rest of the Z-Fighters
were confronted
by a mysterious stranger.
Although this curious young man
greeted Goku as a friend,
his smile seemed to be masking a
far more ominous intent.
Later, Trunks and Goten did a
little masking of their own!
[NARRATOR] And when
the time finally came
for the sixteen finalists of the
World Martial Arts Tournament
to secure their
places on the fighting board,
one of the competitors,
it seemed,
had developed a particularly,
er, youthful personality.
[NARRATOR] Bulma and ChiChi
watched in suspense
as the final pairings
were posted,
but neither could have expected
this round one shocker:
Vegeta versus Goku!
[GOKU] That figures.
[NARRATOR] The last of the
numbers has been drawn...
[ANNOUNCER]
The champion is number 10!
[NARRATOR] Now with
a full board of fighters,
and eight exciting matches in
the first round,
everyone's ready
for the action...
The fighting starts today!
[KRILLIN] This is so exciting!
I'm gonna totally cut loose!
Now... Let the World Martial
Arts Championship begin!
[CROWD cheers]
[REPORTER #1] Mr. Satan,
now that the pairings
have been decided,
how do you feel
about the tournament?
Well, I think that we've got a
decent lot of competitors
all willing to lay their
strengths on the line...
And for the good
of all the fighters,
I hope they keep
their heads on straight
and save all of their
power for the ring.
'Cause they'll certainly need it
if they come up against me!
[MR. SATAN chuckles]
I have to say, Hercule,
you really are rather confident
for a man who just got
beaten up by a youngster.
Hey! That was just
an exhibition bout...
You got that?
What do you want personally
out of this match?
Well, there's only one thing
that any fighter worth his salt
could ever want.
So, what you're saying
is that your goal today
is to win the grand prize.
No, no, no...
I just want to do my best.
And if it just so happens
that, you know...
I win... Hey!
So what do you think
of today's line up?
Ah, Well I don't know.
Who's my first
unlucky competitor?
I believe it's a
woman named Number 18.
Oh... Really?!
Wow! That'll... be... close!
[MR. SATAN laughs]
[FRIAR #1 thinking] I could have
sworn I told him that already...
[GOHAN] Hmm...
Something's wrong...
Hey, that Piccolo guy looks like
he's really stressed
out over there.
Does he get like this
before every fight?
He's a pretty serious guy.
This is all just part
of his usual routine.
[VIDEL] Hmm...
[GOHAN] Piccolo... What is it
that's eating at you like this?
Are you really
that worried about Shin?
Should I be worried
about Kibito?
Soon Kibito, that which we came
for will be within our grasp...
[GOKU grunting]
You can't seem
to sit still, Goku.
[GOKU] Haha... I'm just excited.
Well, with you fighting
Vegeta right off the bat,
it's kind of like having the
last round first, you know?
[GOKU laughs]
[VEGETA] Hm?
That's why I'm stretching.
Huh?
You alright?
Yeah... Looks like
he's got his game face on!
[SHIN] I think we'll
find them in here...
[KRILLIN] Hey, Piccolo!
Looks like you and I
are gonna be fighting
each other in the second round!
Just try to take it
easy on me, okay?
Gotta try and look good for
the Mrs. Know what I mean, Goku?
Hey, Hon, I've got a great idea.
Let's trade! You take my slot,
and I'll fight Mr. Satan!
Forget it! He's mine...
[CROWD cheering]
I've been waiting
for this forever...
Videl's in the third match.
I'm so nervous!
Stop worrying about
things so much, babe.
Her only competition today
is her father!
Yeah, you're right...
Hey, there's the Great Saiyaman!
Ooh, what if he and
Videl have to fight?
Just think!
The city's two greatest crime
fighters in the ring together!
Isn't it exciting?
Nah... Nobody with an
outfit that stupid looking
could be strong enough
to get past the first round.
[COMMANDER]
Now don't forget the cheer.
"Videl! Videl! You're
the one! Videl!" Got it?!
[POLICMEN cheer]
For you.
Thank you.
Well, you're sure
in a good mood!
Ready for things to start, huh?
I guess I'm still a
little giddy over Trunks' win
in the Junior Division
this morning.
And now, of course,
Vegeta has the best chance of
winning the World Championship!
Father and son winning
on the same day?
You bet I'm in a good mood!
[BULMA laughs]
[CHICHI] I don't think so!
Huh?!
Vegeta's a long way
from winning
especially if he has to fight
my Goku in the first round.
Oh?! Need I remind you, ChiChi?
My Trunks beat your Goten. "Like
father, like son", they say...
They were just little kids
fighting, and besides!
Your boy cheated!
I hate to be the one to
break it to you Bulma,
but my Goku has
never lost a fight.
Oh, so that's why he
wears that halo?!
Now you listen to me!
My husband has done nothing but
train for the last five years!
He's wearing that
championship belt home, sister!
[CHICHI] Goku's fighting so he
can feed his family
and put his children
through school!
He's got heart, you know.
He's not out there for cheap
thrills like your husband...
Vegeta will win!
[CHICHI] No, Goku will win!
[BULMA] Vegeta!
[CHICHI] Goku!
[BOTH snarl]
Please, ladies, don't
you think this is a
little childish--
[YAMCHA yelps
[BOTH] No!
[YAMCHA grunts]
[OOLONG growls,
YAMCHA whimpers]
Yes! Ladies and gentlemen,
I am proud to present to you,
the first match in the
World Martial Arts Tournament!
So... Let's get Krillin and
Pintar out here to the ring!
[GOKU] Break a leg, Krillin.
Just so long as
it's not one of mine!
[KRILLIN grunts]
Hey!
[PINTAR chuckles]
Why don't you
save it for the ring?!
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't see you down there.
I'm surprised that you've
stayed this long, little man.
I was worried that I'd end up
beating myself into a pulp.
But now that you're here,
I guess you'll do just fine.
[PINTAR grunts]
You know, I asked my assistant
to call and reserve you
a private room at the hospital.
[PINTAR laughs]
You'll thank me.
[KRILLIN growls,
PINTAR giggles]
[ANNOUNCER] We now have both
fighters for the first match
entering the ring!
[ANNOUNCER] Krillin is quite
the accomplished fighter,
but this is his first tournament
appearance in many years.
It's a pleasure to
see him back in the ring.
Pintar's fierce fighting
at the last championship
proved he had stamina.
He may have lost
in the semi-finals,
but he's back today
ready to change his luck!
[PINTAR chuckles]
[PINTAR yells]
[CROWD cheers]
The man that Daddy's
fighting looks really scary.
I hope he doesn't hurt him.
Oh, Maron, I wouldn't worry
about anything like that.
Your dad's one of the
strongest fighters around.
Is that true?
Well, I'll tell you one thing...
[YAMCHA laughs]
I certainly wouldn't
want to fight with him!
[MAN A] Look how much
bigger Pintar is!
[MAN B] There's no way
this'll be a fair fight.
[MAN A] I feel bad
for Krillin...
[ANNOUNCER] There's a lot of
talk down here on the floor
about fairness in regards
to the size difference
of our competitors.
Let me just say that
this is a competition
where size truly
does not matter, folks!
You can believe...
what he's saying...
if you want to...
But I tell ya this...
You're gonna definitely think
size matters when
I'm done with you!
[KRILLIN] Hmph.
[KRILLIN] I'm gonna have to
take it easy on this guy.
I don't want to cause him
any more brain damage!
[KILLA talks incoherently]
[KILLA mumbles incoherently]
[PINTAR growls]
[FIGHTER screams]
[PINTAR laughs]
[ANNOUNCER] Now,
let the battle begin!
[PINTAR yells]
[KRILLIN] Huh?
[PINTAR grunting]
[PINTAR laughs]
I told you
size matters, boy.
I guess you see
what I'm talking about.
You must be ready
to forfeit the match, right?
Run home like a little girl?!
[KRILLIN sighs]
You are so lame...
[PINTAR laughs]
Sticks and stones may
break my bones,
but you can never hurt me!
And just to prove to you
that I'm right,
I'm gonna give you
a little something.
[KRILLIN sighs]
I'll give you the
first punch, shorty!
Right here in the gut.
C'mon! Now!
[KRILLIN growls
'Kay!
[KRILLIN yells]
[PINTAR screams]
[CROWD gasps]
[KRILLIN yells]
[PINTAR screams]
[KILLA screams]
[ANNOUNCER yells]
[PINTAR grunts]
[PINTAR whimpers]
[ANNOUNCER] Out of the ring!
Pintar has landed
out of the ring,
which makes Krillin the winner!
[CROWD cheers]
[BOTH] Yes! Yes! Yes!
Daddy, you're the best!
That's right!
[ANNOUNCER] Now, that's the
kinda fighting
I'm talking about!
That is entertainment!
Hey, nice going, Krillin.
[KRILLIN laughs]
That was nothing.
Sorry, Piccolo, but it
looks like they want
the next victim out in the ring,
so you better put
your fighting gloves on.
Hey, why are you getting
all bent out of shape,
I'm just fooling around.
This match should be
a piece of cake for you!
[KRILLIN] What's the matter
with you guys?
Man... All of you, loosen up!
[GOTEN] Trunks, give me a sip.
It's really hot down here.
If I give you some, then they'll
find out what we're doing--
[GOTEN] You don't get it!
I'm burning up,
and I want a sip of juice!
You better give me some
or I promise I'll knock you
right off my shoulders!
Here!
[GOTEN] Wow! That was great!
Could you get me another?
Now, for match number 2...
And I guarantee you that this
will be another colossal brawl!
Majunior versus Shin!
[CROWD cheers]
Well then...
This should be interesting.
Don't you think, Piccolo?
[ANNOUNCER] This is the first
year Shin has participated
in the tournament.
He's a man of few words, so
we know very little about him.
And that could spell trouble for
our other competitor Majunior!
Someone who,
if I remember correctly,
came close to turning
this arena into rubble
the last time he was here!
[ANNOUNCER] Uh... this time,
try to leave the stadium intact.
Okay?
Am I right to say that
the big green fellow
was one of the guys who jumped
up between Cell and Mr. Satan
when they were fighting?
I think so.
I saw him on the tele.
[PICCOLO thinking] What is this
strange energy I sense?
[KRILLIN] I don't understand...
Is this guy really getting
under your skin that much?
Yeah...
If you say so...
He just doesn't seem to be
all that powerful to me.
[VEGETA thinking]
Come on, Shin...
Why don't you show us
why you have the little
Namek all worried?
[ANNOUNCER] Fighters...
let the second match begin!
[PICCOLO thinking]
Why can't I focus my power?
[PICCOLO growls]
[PICCOLO thinking] Why am I
holding back like this?!
I've never even met him
before today!
And yet, there's
something about him...
C'mon, guys, would one of you
throw a punch already?!
This is bogus, man!
The match has already started so
you guys can fight anytime now!
[MAN A] Can't you hear him?!
He said the fight's
already started!
[MAN B] Stop staring at each
other already and do something!
This is boring!
Well, folks, it looks
like we've got ourselves
an old-fashioned stand off!
[PICCOLO thinking] I've sensed
this kind of energy before.
But where?
[SHIN laughs]
[PICCOLO thinking] No...
It couldn't be...
[GOKU gasps]
What's wrong with Piccolo?
Why won't he fight?
[VEGETA thinking] He's afraid!
[PICCOLO thinking] It can't be
him... Why would he be here?!
I promise you'll know soon.
[PICCOLO gasps]
[SHIN] You'll know soon...
But for now, let's enjoy
our little match.
[PICCOLO gasps]
[GOKU thinking] Piccolo!
[ANNOUNCER] So, is this
gonna happen or what?
[PICCOLO] I'm sorry.
[ANNOUNCER gasps]
I can't.
[SHIN gasps]
[ALL gasp]
Quitting?!
Does this mean... you're
withdrawing from the match?!
[PICCOLO] Yes, it does.
[SHIN thinking] Interesting...
Yes, that Namek was the
guardian of this planet
at one time.
Perhaps he knows more
about me than I thought.
Well, you heard it! Majunior
has withdrawn from the match.
That makes Shin
the winner by default!
[CROWD yells]
What's going on?
I paid good money to see
some serious action!
Oh yeah? You made me
pay for the tickets.
[GOHAN] Hey, Piccolo.
[KRILLIN]
What went down out there?
Is he that strong, Piccolo?
Yes...
Stronger than you can imagine.
[gasping]
[KRILLIN] Uh...
Please tell me you just got
a headache or something...
'Cause I'm getting edgy,
I'm the one that has to go out
there and fight him next!
[PICCOLO growls]
Not wasting any more time...
let's get on
with the third match!
Videl versus Spopovich!
♪
Videl! Go Videl!
Vi-del! Vi-del! Vi-del!
[GOHAN] They really
like you, don't they?
I guess we've got
a pretty smart crowd.
Thanks.
Hey...
They called your name, buddy.
It's your turn in the ring.
Hello?
[KILLA talks incoherently]
[KILLA yelps]
[KILLA gasps]
It's time.
Gohan...
Yeah?
I wanna see you in the
second round, okay?
[ANNOUNCER] I'm sure that
most of you know Videl
is the daughter of our
champion Mr. Satan.
Seven years ago, she succeeded
in becoming champion
of the Junior Division.
And since then, she has
put her best foot forward
to help our
brave boys in blue
capture evil villains
across the city.
As for her rival today,
Spopovich is here
to redeem himself
for a loss he suffered
in the first round
of the last tournament.
He's trained hard
and buffed up...
I'm sure he'll be
a mighty challenge
for our city's daughter!
[NARRATOR] As Videl
prepares to take her place
in the center ring,
the mysterious Shin has
set his sights on Spopovich.
But what secrets lie hidden
in that penetrating stare?
What is the link between
Spopovich and Shin?
The questions continue to mount,
and the answers
are sure to follow!
Stay tuned for scenes from the
next episode of Dragon Ball Z!