[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Gohan trained with
his little brother
for the World Martial
Arts Tournament,
which begins in one month.
And a strong arm proved to be
the least of Goten's talents!
[GOTEN] Since... Mom's not here,
is it okay if I be like you?
You know, a Super Saiyan?
[NARRATOR] Those green eyes and
gold spikes of hair
can only mean one thing:
Somehow, Goten
has already mastered
the switch to Super Saiyan!
An amazing jump indeed for the
half-Saiyan half-pint,
considering he doesn't
even know how to fly.
[GOTEN] Funny?! Well, you
better teach me how to fly,
because I don't like
being laughed at!
You hear me?!
[GOHAN] Whoa, whoa,
easy there...
[NARRATOR] And from there,
the next step was a shoe-in.
Gohan would have to hold
some flying lessons.
[GOTEN] Wow! You will?!
[NARRATOR] But Goten
wasn't the only student
enrolling in Gohan's course!
[VIDEL] Well,
I've got news for you,
you're going to teach me to fly!
That's fine!
I gave you my word and
that's all there is to it!
[NARRATOR] Flying class begins,
today on Dragon Ball Z!
[GOTEN laughs]
I've... never done
this before...
Ah... Uh... But teaching
can't be that hard right?!
Right... anyway...
So to fly, you basically take
control of your energy.
Then you sort of
put it underneath you,
and your energy holds you up!
Really, a toddler could do it!
[VIDEL growls]
I, mean an extremely
talented toddler
who's put years of hard
work into it, of course.
This energy business...
What are you talking about?
Well... It's uh...
Guess... they call it something
different where you're from...
Well, it's like that power you
can feel inside of your body,
--and--
--What?!
Who are YOU to be talking
about MY body?!
[GOTEN laughs]
[GOHAN groans]
I don't think I'll ever find
the right words for this...
[VIDEL growls]
It's like this!
Yeah... It's... like that!
I see...
So if you guys don't
call that energy,
what do you call it, Videl?
[VIDEL] Huh...?
Well, it's a trick.
No, that can't be right.
It's all real!
We're not trying to
trick anybody!
Well, if it's not a trick,
then I've never seen it
in my whole life, okay?!
Okay... I hear you.
This is... gonna be
harder than I thought...
[VIDEL] So... I can't fly
if I don't have the energy?
Don't worry! Every living
person has it inside them!
You just... have to find it!
I will.
Alright then.
Goten, can you
hang tight for a while?
Before we move
any farther along,
I need to show Videl
how to use her energy.
Alright... But...
If you ask me,
it's a waste of time!
Hey! I'll learn it!
Ahhh... Go on, Goten!
Go play somewhere else.
[GOTEN] Okay! I'll go play!
But I'll be back!
And you better be ready!
[GOHAN] Alright, Goten!
We will be!
[GOTEN laughs]
[GOHAN] I'll do it slowly...
That way...
You can watch me better.
The first thing
that you have to do
is make yourself
completely calm.
Then you listen...
Listen to the center
of your body...
Until you start to feel a pull.
Then...
[VIDEL gasps]
[GOHAN] You just bring it out!
There! You see?
Cool isn't it?
Uhhh... Videl?
[GOHAN laughs]
Right. Now you try!
[VIDEL] Huh...?
Remember: From the center!
Uhh...
[VIDEL] Okay...
[VIDEL grunting softly]
Ah?
You've got to relax
your muscles!
You're never going
to bring it out
if you're all tensed
up like that, Videl.
[GOHAN gasps]
[VIDEL] I have to
make this work...
[GOHAN] Food looks great, Mom!
[GOTEN] Ooh! Yummie!
[VIDEL] Thank you very much
for lunch, ChiChi.
[CHICHI] You're welcome.
I'm just glad Gohan's
making some nice lady friends.
You know, it's never
too early to settle down...
[GOHAN] Mom!
Delicious! I should give
this recipe to our cook!
What? Your cook?
Is your family in the
restaurant business?
[VIDEL] Oh no. I meant the
cook we have at our house.
You have your own cook?!
Your family must be
pretty loaded!
About how many rooms do
you have in your house?
Ten? Twenty?!
[VIDEL] Mmm...
That's a good question...
I guess about fifty?
Fifty?! That's like
a small village!
I can hardly imagine it!
[CHICHI screams]
This is SO good!
And you're planning
to marry this girl?!
[GOTEN] Hey... Hey!
[GOHAN whimpers]
So, does this mean Videl's
gonna be my new sister?!
I have no idea what you
guys are talking about!
[GOTEN] I got you now, mister!
[GOTEN grunts]
Aah--!
[GOTEN] Ha-ha!
Come back, you villain!
[VIDEL growls softly]
You're close! I can feel it!
Ah, yeah! You got it!
I guess since you've been doing
martial arts all your life,
it was easier to tap into
your power! Very good!
Ahh?
[VIDEL laughs]
So! Do you think
I can fly now, Gohan?
Whoa! Slow down there!
Didn't I mention you
have to learn to control
that energy first?
--[VIDEL growls]
--[GOHAN laughs]
[VIDEL] Then don't
just sit there!
Let's learn this thing!
[GOKU grunting]
[KING KAI laughs]
[SOUTH KAI] Sort of an outdated
way to train, don't you think?
[KING KAI] South Kai!
Thought you were still
hiding under a rock.
Please, it's been years
since I lost that tournament
and you'll find that many
things have changed.
You thought you were so swift
with your little new-boy.
Well, now I've got
one of my own!
Fresh from the living world!
Ooh, how exciting!
Hey, let's throw a party.
Hmph.
[GOKU grunting]
[SOUTH KAI] So, how much
weight does he put on?
It's nothing, really.
Just two tons a piece.
Two... tons?!
That wasn't surprise
in your voice, was it?
Uhh... No, of course it wasn't.
Why would I be surprised?
I have my own fighter!
His name's Papoy,
and he saved the South Quadrant
from something very nasty!
[KING KAI] What, like boredom?
[SOUTH KAI] Joke all you want,
but the fact remains
that my fighter is much
stronger than Goku!
I only wish he could have been
there to win that tournament!
Really? Well, it just so happens
that another championship
is being held
on planet Earth!
Goku's going to
be fighting in it,
so why don't you have
your Papoy fight in it too?
What d'ya say, huh?
[PAPOY grunts]
Well, you heard him folks!
Papoy's in!
Hey, Goku!
Why don't you try using
some heavier weights?
[GOKU] Hmmm?
Alright... How much do you think
I should put on, King Kai?
Let's say... Eight
more tons! On each one.
Oh, don't be foolish!
That would be...
Ten tons a piece!
Ten tons?! Uuhh...
Don't you think
that's a little much?
I won't be able to move!
[SOUTH KAI laughs]
Just as I thought! North
Kai's attempt to show off
was just another one
of his pathetic jokes!
[SOUTH KAI laughs]
[PAPOY guffaws]
Goku! Just make yourself
a Super Saiyan!
[SOUTH KAI] Huh?
[GOKU] Oh, okay! But that
almost makes it too easy!
Huuh?!
Hey! Since you're here...
You think you might
want to do the honors
and change his weights?
Why, I'd love to.
Now you do realize that
ten tons each is forty
tons in all, right?!
Uh-huh!
[SOUTH KAI] Huh?
[GOKU laughs]
Are you sure you
understand?!
Just change it!
Now don't blame me
when you get hurt!
[SOUTH KAI grunts]
[SOUTH KAI yells]
[SOUTH KAI] Ten tons!
[GOKU screams]
[GOKU Ooh-whooa!
[SOUTH KAI laughs]
[GOKU growls]
[KING KAI laughs]
Check it...
[GOKU yelling]
[SOUTH KAI &amp; PAPOY whimpering]
The Tournament will take place
in 28 Earth days from now.
I bet Papoy can't wait
to fight Goku there!
[PAPOY grunts]
Actually, I just remembered
Papoy has other plans!
Dinner dates, yeah!
And we all know you
can't break dinner dates, so...
Besides, it'll probably be
a boring tournament anyways.
Maybe next time, North Kai!
Thanks for the invite!
[KING KAI giggles]
Okay!
It's finally time to
try our first flight!
Just use your energy!
And be careful!
[GOTEN grunting]
[VIDEL growling]
Uhh...
[GOTEN grunting]
No, no, Goten!
Flying and hopping are
two different things!
Huh?
Use your energy!
Ohh!
Hm...?
[GOTEN grunts]
You mean... like... this?!
Yeah! That's it! Wow!
--Good job!
--[GOTEN laughs]
Look at me, Gohan!
I'm a little birdie!
[GOTEN laughs]
That's really great, Goten!
[VIDEL growls]
Not so high!
Aw, don't worry, Gohan!
[GOTEN shouts]
[GOHAN] Goten! Are you okay?!
[VIDEL growls]
[GOHAN] Goten! See?! You
should have listened to me!
But don't worry!
At this rate, you'll be
flying high in no time!
[GOTEN sniffs]
But when can we have
our real training?
Shhh! Just as soon
as Videl leaves.
I promise we'll train
extra hard after that, okay?
Okay!
[VIDEL growls]
Gohan! Have you
forgotten about me?!
[GOHAN] Oh, uh no! I'm coming!
It's getting late
in the afternoon.
You think you should
go call your dad
and tell him where you are?
[VIDEL] I'm not moving an inch
unless it's through the air!
[GOHAN] Okay. Fair enough...
Then let's start
from the beginning.
[GOHAN] Feel the energy
from your stomach,
and slowly bring it out.
Relax your muscles...
[VIDEL growls]
That's the energy!
Now push it up!
[growling continues]
Yeah, you got it! Ha, ha!
Look! You're floating!
Gohan, I'm trying
to concentrate!
[GOHAN gasps]
[VIDEL] Hm?!
That's incredible, Videl!
No one learns how to fly
on their first day!
Is that a fact?
[GOTEN] A birdie! A
birdie! A birdie!
Goten is a birdie!
[GOTEN laughs]
Of course, Goten
is an exception!
He's been controlling his
energy for a long time, you see,
and besides it's in his blood,
and well, what can I say?
Kids learn so fast!
Don't you think?
[GOHAN laughs nervously]
[GOHAN gasps]
I'll be back tomorrow.
What?! But I already
taught you how to fly!
All you really need now is a
little bit of private practice!
I wanna learn
more about this.
Or is my presence
a burden on you?!
[GOHAN] No! No! No-no!
Of course not!
I just didn't think--
Good. It's settled.
[VIDEL] See you tomorrow!
Yeah... See ya!
Oh! Videl?!
Yes?
I... was thinking...
about your hair...
Huh?
It might...
be... better short!
So, you mean you
like short hair...
on girls, Gohan?
Uuh?! I've never
really thought about it!
I just meant that
if you get it cut
it won't get in your eyes
when you're fighting.
And, plus, your opponents won't
be able to grab it
--during a match!
--[VIDEL growls]
--and also it--
Why don't you just stay
out of my hair
and leave me alone,
you big jerk!
[GOHAN gasps]
[engine roars]
[GOTEN] What was
she all upset about?
I... don't... know!
[GOHAN whimpers]
[VEGETA yells]
[TRUNKS grunts]
[VEGETA grunting]
[TRUNKS grunting]
[VEGETA grunts]
Perhaps you should
rest, Son.
One hundred and
fifty times gravity
is a man's training level.
You're clearly still a child...
[TRUNKS grunts]
Goten called me last night.
He said he's going to
be in the tournament...
Now I... want to...
[VEGETA grunts]
So, what are you going
to do about it?
[TRUNKS pants]
Guess I'll go...
Super!
Huh?!
[TRUNKS yells]
[TRUNKS laughs]
[VEGETA gasps]
[laughing continues]
Did... I miss something?!
[TRUNKS grunts]
When was it that the
transformation
to the legendary warrior
of the Saiyan race
was reduced to a
child's plaything?!
[TRUNKS grunts]
Come here, Son.
Huh?
Can the youngest
child of Kakarot
also become a Super Saiyan?
[TRUNKS] Yes.
Yes, naturally! It's a
Super Saiyan bargain sale...
Uhh... Uh-huh?
Try to hit me!
Uhh...?
Why would I do that, Dad?!
You know I'm not strong enough!
You want to play like that?
Fine! Let's deal!
If you can land a
punch in my face
then I'll take you to
the park for an hour!
Wow! You mean it?!
Okay!
[TRUNKS growls]
Now, let's just see
what you can do!
Here comes!
[TRUNKS yells]
[BOTH grunting]
[VEGETA snarls]
--[TRUNKS yelps]
--[VEGETA gasps]
[TRUNKS grunts]
You didn't say
you'd hit back, Dad!
Well, I didn't say I wouldn't
hit you, now did I, Trunks?!
No, but...!
[TRUNKS whimpers]
Dry your tears!
We're going to the park now!
[TRUNKS laughs]
But before you go, you must
tell me who is stronger!
You or Kakarot's boy?
I'm a little bit
stronger than him,
because Goten's a
year younger than I am
and he hasn't
learned to fly yet.
Only a bit, eh?
Well, we'll have to do
something about that...
[GOHAN] So, is this the kind of
training you wanted, Goten?
Just the two of us?
[GOTEN] Ha-ha! Yeah!
[BOTH yell]
[GOHAN] Guess...
our time's up...
Hey, Gohan. Who's the new girl?
It's time to continue
my lessons.
Oh, I give up.
This girl business
is so complicated.
[NARRATOR] As fighters across
the globe struggle to train,
it looks like Gohan
has some different kind
of lessons to learn!
But he better do it fast,
because The World Martial Arts
Tournament is drawing near!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z!