[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Goku and Pikkon fired up
as the final bout of the Other
World Tournament began.
[NARRATOR] The mighty warriors
cut right to the chase,
quickly tagging one another
with heat-seeking energy blasts!
[NARRATOR] And
narrowly escaped...
[NARRATOR] Back on the ground,
the two locked arms for an
electrifying test of strength.
[NARRATOR] And to
Pikkon's great surprise,
Goku was able to
take the lead
pushing Pikkon just
inches away from defeat.
[NARRATOR] But the true
struggle had not yet begun.
[PIKKON yells]
[GOKU yells]
[NARRATOR] Without a word,
Pikkon removed his outer robes,
revealing that he'd been wearing
weighted training clothes
all along. And with the
heavy burden now removed,
his strength would
dramatically increase.
[NARRATOR] But of course,
Goku had been doing a little
holding back of his own.
[GOKU yells]
[NARRATOR] The second
half is kicking off...
and Goku is a Super Saiyan!
[CROWD gasping, murmuring]
[PIKKON gasps]
[PIKKON thinking] What is he?
I've never seen such
a transformation...
[CROWD gasping]
[GRAND KAI laughs]
Well! This is unexpected!
The rookie fighter Goku
has just changed
into some sort of
shining golden thing!
[SOUTH KAI] Buh...?
Shiny gold thing?
Maybe it's a disease!
He could be contagious!
[KING KAI giggles]
Oh, it's nothing.
He just transformed
into a Super Saiyan.
Super...?
What's that mean?
Not much.
Just that his speed,
strength and ability
have become several
times more sensational
than before!
There's... no way!
Oh, but I'm afraid
there is, West Kai!
And by our bet, your home
planet will soon be mine!
You just wait!
Because Pikkon hasn't used
his full power yet either!
[thunder crashes]
The entire sky itself
seems to be shaking
from their awesome power!
This bout is gonna be insane!
Heh!
I might as well start it big.
Ka--Me--Ha--Me...
Haaaa!
Got you!
[GOKU yells]
Haah!
Yaah! Haah! Haah!
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU screams]
Hm?!
[CROWD roars]
[PIKKON] Goku...
Look above you...
Huh?!
[thinking] Darn it!
I just couldn't
keep up with him!
[PIKKON] Your power
is impressive...
But you'll need
more concentration
if you want to follow me.
Hmph.
You've disappointed me, Goku.
--[GOKU growls]
--I'm ending this fight.
[PIKKON yells]
[GOKU gasps]
[yelling continues]
Hyper Tornado Attack!
[GOKU screams]
[slashing,
screaming continues]
[CROWD screams]
[KAIS grunt]
[GRAND KAI grunts]
[GOKU screams]
[GOKU growls]
[CROWD screaming]
[GRAND KAI grunts]
[KAIS whimpering]
[WEST KAI] I hope you're
ready to be my servant!
[KING KAI] Oh, stuff it!
[EAST KAI screams]
[gasping]
[GOKU screams]
Goku...
You must know there's
no point in fighting it.
No!
[GOKU growls]
Huh?!
[growling continues]
What the--?!
[GOKU yells]
Super Kaio-Ken!
[PIKKON grunts]
Ka...
me...
ha...
[GOKU gasps]
[GOKU yells]
[grunting]
--Yaaaaaah!
--[PIKON yells]
[PIKKON growls,
GOKU grunts]
[GOKU shouts,
grunting]
[PIKKON yells]
[GOKU gasps]
[MUSHROOM MC] Oh, man,
I'm getting way too old
for this stuff...
[GRAND KAI laughs]
So close...
Pikkon was so close...
Phew...
They're awesome!
It's no wonder why
my piddling fighters
couldn't stand up against
those powerful guys...
I guess my boys
can count on another
five hundred years
of training.
Heavens, Grand Kai...
You must be very excited to
be giving your private lessons
to either of these
wonderfully skilled fighters!
[GRAND KAI thinking] Oh, darn.
I did make that
little promise, didn't I?
I was hoping they
wouldn't remember.
I've never fought someone quite
as powerful as you are.
It's because you're strong.
I find that my toughest
opponents always bring out
the best in me.
Well, this should
be exciting then
since I'm about to
get much tougher!
Wha--?
Your energy!
It's skyrocketing!
Thunder...
Flash...
Attack!
Thunder Flash...
[GOKU screams]
[CROWD gasping, screaming]
[GOKU grunting]
[thinking] Incredible...
I couldn't block
against any of it!
[CROWD muttering]
[KAIS whimpering]
[GRAND KAI] Hmm?
[GRAND KAI sighs]
[GOKU grunts]
[PIKKON grunting]
[GOKU thinking] I can feel his
energy shooting upward again.
He's doing it!
Thunder Flash...
Attack!
[GOKU grunts]
[CROWD screams]
[MUSHROOM MC screams]
[GRAND KAI grunts]
[KAIS whimpering]
[PIKKON] Hmph.
[PIKKON growls]
[PIKKON grunts]
[GOKU growls]
Wha--?!
[PIKKON snarls]
[EAST KAI groans]
I can feel my
antennae smoking...
They've... turned our ring
into a rock collection...
I told him not to do that...
"Don't use Thunder Flash unless
you're far away," I said...
It's getting harder and harder
to teach these kids...
It's all about
explosions to them!
[PIKKON grunts]
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU screams]
[PIKKON yells]
What's happening up there?
I've lost track of them.
Me too...
Both fighters have
moved out of our sight...
Who knows what kind of crazy
moves are going on up there?
Who is winning? Who is losing?
Who is blowing up stuff?!
It seems these are things none
of us can ever know...
[GOKU screams]
[PIKKON yells]
[growling]
[BOTH grunting]
[grunting continues]
[BOTH growl]
[BOTH yell]
Ka-me-ha-me-Haa!
Hmph.
[GOKU growls]
[thinking] Darn! I've got to
catch him off guard!
[KAIS gasp]
[GOKU grunts]
Ugh... You... got... me...
And I'll finish you!
Using the special attack
you seem so fond of...
[GOKU grunts]
[KING KAI squeals]
[WEST KAI giggles]
[GOKU grunts]
[thinking] This is it, Goku!
This is your chance!
His attack has got to
have a weak point!
[PIKKON grunts]
Thunder...
Flash...
Aaaaa--
[GOKU] There!
[PIKKON]
--ttack!
[GOKU] Ka-me...
[PIKKON gasps]
...ha-meh...
Haaa!
[PIKKON grunts]
--[KAIS gasp]
--[KING KAI laughs]
[FIGHTERS gasp]
[FIGHTER] A... A...
A... A-Astonishing...
[MUSHROOM MC] Uhh...
Oh, uh, Pikkon has landed
outside of the ring!
And that means
Goku is the winner!
And champion of the
Other World Tournament!
[CROWD cheers]
[CROWD (chanting)]
Goku! Goku! Goku! Goku!
[PIKKON grunts]
Huh...?
[PIKKON chuckles]
[PIKKON] You got me...
[GOKU] Well, Pikkon,
it was a mistake to use
your Thunder Flash
move a third time.
By then I had seen
the attack enough times
to find a weakness in it!
Huh?
[PIKKON chuckles]
I see...
Truly, you're a great fighter.
Enjoy your private lesson...
[PIKKON] I'll keep
training and beat you
at the very next chance.
Great! Hey, thanks for
fighting with me.
Goku's the champ! I am his King!
That... means... I... win!
And! That, of course,
means I get your planet!
Please! No talking!
Now... Goku if you could
come over here for a minute
we can give you
your official prize!
[GRAND KAI] Minor problem!
[BOTH] Huh?
[GRAND KAI] Both Goku and
Pikkon have violated the rules
of the tournament,
and therefore...
Both fighters have
been disqualified!
Huh...?
[ALL] Huh?!
Yeah, that's right!
Goku, do you admit that you
and Pikkon touched the ceiling
of this here stadium
during the fight?
The ceiling?
Uhh...
Yeah, we did.
Well, according to Article 3,
Section 9, paragraph 1351
of the official rule book,
the stadium ceiling
is the same as the
stadium floor.
Because if you stand on your
head, the floor is the ceiling
and the ceiling is the floor!
Therefore, it's ring-out!.
Oh, but Grand Kai!
If he's disqualified that
means that nobody wins!
Homeless again!
--[KING KAI groans]
--Yes! What a wise judgement!
Mm-hmm, Mm-hmm!
Goku lost! I agree!
You're right...
We broke the rules so we lose.
But, your fight rocked!
So as a bonus,
I'll allow both you and Pikkon
to take my private lessons
in two to three hundred years!
Two hundred years...
Great! I'll be there!
[thinking] That'll
give me just enough time
to whip back into shape!
I've been too much of a
couch potato to keep up
with those boys now!
[NARRATOR] And so it
was in Other World...
Even after death,
Goku's fighting spirit
could not
be put to rest.
[NARRATOR] As the hero trained,
several years passed
in the living world, on the
humble blue planet called Earth.
[GOHAN] Heading out, Mom!
[CHICHI] Oh, wait a sec, Gohan!
Huh?
[CHICHI] Here. You'll
probably want your lunch!
[GOHAN chuckles]
Oh... You're just
like your dad--
Always jumping the gun...
Thanks, Mom...
Now I'm off!
Well, remember to listen
to your teachers carefully, Son.
'Course!
Nimbus!
Have a wonderful
first day, Gohan!
[NARRATOR] Gohan
has become a teenager...
With no schools near
his mountain village,
he has done most of his
schooling at home,
finally free to study
like his mother wanted.
[NARRATOR] Gohan may have
ventured across the galaxy
and saved the Earth from
destruction,
but there's one great
challenge he has yet to face:
High School...