[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z!
Time ran out
for our heroes,
as Frieza's diabolical
Ginyu Force
descended from
the skies!
Even the mighty Vegeta
could only watch helplessly,
as his hopes for using the
seven magic Dragon Balls
to make a wish
vanished into thin air!
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN whimper]
Now then, if
you'll excuse me,
I have to deliver these
Dragon Balls to Lord Frieza.
[ALL] We are
the Ginyu Force!
[ALL laugh]
[NARRATOR] Captain Ginyu made a
hasty departure with his prize,
but he left behind
his four lieutenants,
with orders to eradicate
Gohan, Krillin, and Vegeta...
Now, these unlikely allies
must stand together
if they hope to survive
the battle ahead...
Say there...
Why don't you go ahead
and take your
turn first, Guldo.
Yeah, why don't I?
[NARRATOR] Gohan and Krillin
fight for their lives... today!
Whoa! Yeah, just
look at 'em go! Ha!
Lotta good
that's gonna do.
Now!
Right!
[BOTH] Haaa!
Buh! 'Kay...
[GULDO screams]
Time Freeze!
[thinking] Ha! Suckers.
[thinking] What?! They're gone!
Why, those little... Try to
sneak up on me, will ya'?
Well, it's not
gonna work!
[thinking] Hey! They're
some quick little buggers,
aren't they? Oh well...
Now I got 'em...
[thinking] Uh-oh...
There's just one problem!
I... can't... hold my...
breath... any longer!
[GOHAN yells]
[GULDO panting]
Have to admit
I'm impressed...
Guess those two are
tougher than we thought!
Oohh...
Now isn't
that something...
Looks like our little
friends have the ability
to increase their power
without changing their shape!
[JEICE] Hey, Vegeta! You got
some real choice mates there!
Incredible...
Their speed and power have
increased exponentially
since I fought
them on Earth.
That was
amazing, Gohan!
If I hadn't seen it, I'd never
believed you had it in you!
Yeah, that makes
two of us!
But thanks to Guru,
I've never felt stronger!
But look! How'd he get
way over there already?
I dunno. Maybe he stopped
time again... Be careful!
[GOHAN] Right!
[GULDO] Yah! Not again!
Uh? Huh?! Ah-ah-ah!
Time Freeze!
[GULDO squeals]
[thinking] Wait a second!
Why am I running away?
They're the ones who are
supposed to be scared of me!
Heh! Prepare to
die, small fry!
[GULDO growling]
[coughs]
[BOTH gasp]
Ugh... Oh, crud!
There he is!
Ka-me-ha-me-HAAA!
[GULDO screams]
[GOHAN growling]
Haaa!
[GULDO screams]
[coughing, gruntiing]
I guess old four-eyes
didn't see that one comin'!
If I were a betting man,
I'd say Guldo's gonna lose.
Oh, obvious.
Thanks for pointing out
the obvious, Burter.
Guldo'll kill 'em
in under a minute!
One chocolate nut
bar says he does!
Ha! You're on!
[GULDO panting]
Knew I should have joined that
Ginyu Fitness Club last year,
but no, I had to go on that
stupid chiliburger diet!
[BULMA] Come on...
Come in, Master
Roshi, this is Bulma!
I need your help!
Krillin and Gohan have
run off and left me again!
And they've taken our
Dragon Ball with them!
What's worse:
They're with Vegeta!
[ROSHI] What? Vegeta?
My, that does sound serious.
But I'm sure they have their
reasons. You just sit tight.
They'll be back
before you know it.
[BULMA] I'm tired of sitting
tight! I can't take it anymore!
I just wanna get off
this stupid planet!
Ah, well, I certainly
do feel your pain...
But there's really
not much you can do
with your spaceship blown
to pieces, now is there?
I wish there was something
I could say to help...
Oh, wait! Hasn't it been
six days since Goku left?
He should be getting
there any minute now!
He'll get'cha home!
[BULMA] What?! The
signal's breaking up!
Hello? Ugh...
Mmm... Agh!
Master Roshi?!
Ooohh! Darn it!
This stupid
satellite phone!
I hate using
outdated technology!
[thinking] Goku, please
hurry. We need you!
[GULDO panting]
Hey, Gohan! Looks like
all this time-stopping's
starting to
wear him down.
Now, let's end this before
he gets his strength back!
Gotcha!
[KRILLIN] Okay, ready?
On my mark... NOW!
[GULDO whimpers]
[GULDO] Time Freeze!
[GULDO giggles]
[GULDO grunting]
[thinking] Aw, hell! Of all
the times to run outta energy!
Well, there's only
one thing left to do...
[thinking] And that's
to run for it!
[thinking] I gotta find
me a place to hide!
[ thinking] There! I can
hide behind that rock
'til I catch my breath!
[GULDO] Bwaah!
[KRILLIN] He did it again!
[KRILLIN] C'mon!
We gotta find him!
[KRILLIN] You sense
anything, Gohan?
Behind that ridge!
[GULDO screams]
[GULDO] Get away!
[GOHAN growls]
[GULDO] No! Wait!
Wait a second!
[GULDO screams]
[GULDO gasps]
Yaah!
C'mon, Guldo, you're
killin' me here!
I dunno, I'm kind of
enjoying watching him
get his flabby
tail whipped!
Hey, Guldo!
Here's the deal:
If you can't beat those two
little punks, and I mean quick,
then you're outta
the Ginyu Force!
Yeah, and not to mention your
spot on the bowling team!
[GULDO yelps]
But, you can't kick
me off the force!
I was just warming
up! That's all!
They're dead!
I promise!
Ha! Now's our chance!
Charge him, full power!
Right!
What do I do?
It's time to pull
out all the stops!
[GULDO screams]
[KRILLIN grunting]
[GOHAN grunting]
Ahh!
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN grunting]
[GOHAN] I... can't move!
[grunting continues]
[GULDO laughs]
How do you like
that trick?
It's a little something I
like to call my Mind-Bind!
[KRILLIN grunting]
[GOHAN grunting]
C'mon, Gohan! We can't
just give up now!
[GOHAN grunting]
Go ahead, fight it! Struggle
all you want! You're mine!
[GULDO laughs]
[grunting]
Looks like what we said really
lit a fire under old Guldo.
He never uses
his "mind bind".
Not unless he's
gettin' desperate.
Yeah, it's a shame
didn't use it sooner.
Sucks for you,
Recoome... Pay up.
Too little,
too late...
It's been more than a
minute. You lose the bet.
Ugh. Yeah,
yeah, whatever...
Here's your stupid
chocolate bar.
[BURTER chuckles]
[BOTH grunting]
Dammit...
Those ignorant fools.
I specifically warned them
not to try a direct assault!
They flew right
into Guldo's trap!
Ha! Get ready, boys!
I'm gonna finish you
off nice and slow!
Raaa...
Haah!
[shouting continues]
[BOTH] Ah!
[KRILLIN grunting in pain]
[GOHAN grunting in pain]
Hey, Guldo!
Just kill 'em!
Yeah, step on it!
C'mon, we don't
have all day!
[GULDO laughs]
[grunting]
[GULDO chuckles]
[GULDO] Whee!
Little baby not so tough
after all! Guchi guchi goo.
[GULDO laughing]
[GULDO] Come on!
[laughing continues]
What's wrong? You don't like
me pulling on your cheeks?
So how 'bout I try
pounding instead?!
[blows landing,
GOHAN grunting]
[grunting continues]
Gohan!
[GULDO] Take that, and that!
And one to grow on!
[GULDO chuckles]
Oh, hey there, Cueball. Don't
think I've forgotten about you!
[GULDO chuckles]
[KRILLIN growls in pain]
[GULDO] Aww, does it hurt?
[blows landing,
GULDO laughing]
[GULDO panting]
[RECOOME] That's enough goofin'
around! Get on with it already!
[JEICE] Do I have to come up
there and kill 'em for you?!
[BURTER] It's still not too late
to kick you off the force!
Uh, uh, right! Huh, huh?
A-ha!
[GULDO chuckles]
Ah... This oughta
do the trick!
[GULDO grunting]
[GULDO] Haah!
[GULDO laughs]
[BOTH gasp]
[GULDO] Shish-kabob, anyone?
[GULDO laughs]
Personally, I prefer
mine well done!
[BOTH grunting]
But to each his own,
boys. The grill is open!
[KRILLIN grunts]
[GOHAN grunts]
Uh-oh! Heh, heh, heh. Almost
there! Time's running out, boys!
Last chance to save yourselves
before I stick it to ya'!
[grunting]
No! I have to...
break free!
I can't
disappoint Piccolo!
[GOHAN grunting]
[PICCOLO] Hm!
[ALL grunting]
[thinking] Gohan's
in trouble!
[thinking] So, Piccolo, you can
also sense the trouble on Namek.
I know how badly you must
want to help your friends,
but from here I'm
afraid there's nothing
we can do
for them!
[PICCOLO growling]
[growling continues]
[CHIAOTZU yells]
Oh?
[YAMCHA] Piccolo...?
Now that's what I'd
call breaking wind!
Heh, heh, heh! Get it?
[KING KAI giggles]
[KING KAI] Ohhh...
[GULDO laughs]
Now, let's see here!
Who dies first?
Bah. Sorry, baldy. That
big shiny head of yours
just gave
you away..
It's way too easy a
target to pass up!
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[grunting]
Gohan, forget about me!
Save yourself!
It's no use! I still
can't move a muscle!
[GULDO laughs]
Ready or not...
Time to die!
[GULDO laughs]
[GULDO] Huh?!
Krillin!
Gohan!
[GULDO coughs]
[BOTH gasp]
[JEICE gasps]
[GULDO whimpering]
No... No...
Fair, Vegeta.
You cheated!
This fight was
supposed to be
just me against those
two! Alone, Vegeta!
There's no such thing as
fair or unfair in battle...
There is only victory.
Or, in your case, defeat.
[GULDO] You...
You dirty Saiyan!
Do you really think
you'll get away with this?
You're nothing!
Just a stupid monkey!
I belong to
the Ginyu Force!
[VEGETA chuckles]
[VEGETA] Not anymore.
[GULDO screams]
Well, I certainly didn't expect
you'd be the one to help us.
Thank you.
[VEGETA] Keep your thanks...
I had my own reasons for
wanting to destroy that freak.
[BOTH gasp]
I saw my moment to
strike, and I acted on it.
That's all. It had nothing to
do with saving your lives.
From now on, you'd
best watch yourselves.
Because next time...
you won't be so lucky.
That's insane! The crazy
bastard actually killed Guldo!
Yeah...
We're in trouble!
I know!
With Guldo gone,
our whole
routine is ruined!
We're gonna have to
come up with a new one!
[ALL] Hmm...
Recoome!
Burter!
Jeice!
Now!
[ALL] Feel the power
of the Ginyu Force!
[RECOOME] Uh, do any of
you guys feel not so fresh?
I'd say Captain Ginyu's
gonna be pissed!
You guys know
how he gets.
He worked real hard on
that choreography...
[JEICE] That's right!
And someone's gotta pay
for it means one of us
has got to teach
these twerps a lesson!
[RECOOME] I still
got dibs on Vegeta.
[BURTER] Then it's
between me and you
for the other two, Jeice!
[JEICE} Let's do it!
And, go!
[BURTER &amp; JEICE] Rock, paper,
scissors! Rock, paper, scissors!
[chanting continues]
Who knows?
Maybe we'll get lucky
and they'll keep
tying forever.
Well, maybe. I guess it
doesn't hurt to have hope.
[BOTH] Rock, paper, scissors!
Rock, paper, scissors!
[chanting continues]
[VEGETA growls]
No... Hope is a luxury
none of us can afford.
[NARRATOR] After his long and
perilous journey through space,
Goku is now in the final
approach to Planet Namek.
But, even after all of his
training at 100-times gravity,
is he prepared to face
the evil might of Frieza,
the most powerful villain
the galaxy has ever known?
And more importantly,
will he be able to put a stop
to the remaining members
of the Ginyu force-
Burter, Jeice, Recoome,
and Captain Ginyu himself-
before they put a permanent
end to all of his friends?
[NARRATOR] A showdown of epic
proportions is about to begin...
and it all starts in the
next exciting episode
of Dragon Ball Z!