[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
warriors from around the
universe came to celebrate
King Kai's death in the only
way they knew how-- by fighting.
Deep within the Grand
Kai's palace, in a room
the size of a
small solar system,
preparations for the Other
World Tournament were made.
[NARRATOR] Four fighters from
each quadrant were allowed
to participate, and the winner's
prize was said to be enormous:
A private lesson from
the Grand Kai himself!
[NARRATOR] So, with a
crash of the Grand Kai's gong,
the competition got off
to a lightning-speed start,
until Goku's competitor Caterpy
took an unexpected time out.
[MUSHROOM MC] Pardon me,
South Kai...
But may I just ask you
how much time
this metamorphosis
of his will take?
[SOUTH KAI coughs]
I'd say in the neighborhood
of twelve hundred years...
[NARRATOR] But Goku
couldn't wait that long!
[GRAND KAI] Yeah...
Well, neither can I.
So Goku wins this
round by default!
[NARRATOR] The first match
has been fought and won,
but it's far from over yet.
Now brace yourself, Goku!
It's time for the second round!
Wow! I don't know about you
guys but I haven't seen
such competition since
I was just a toadstool!
Now let's have a big hand for
our eight advancing contenders!
Fighting for the
South Quadrant...
the amazing Torbie and Froug!
[CROWD cheers]
[MUSHROOM MC]
And in this corner,
pride of the East Quadrant,
the flipper-of-fins Arqua!
[CROWD cheers]
[MUSHROOM MC] From the
North Quadrant...
We have the new sensation Goku
and the heroic Olibu!
And finally, the West Kai's
stellar dream team!
Maraikoh...
Tapkar...
and Pikkon!
[CROWD cheers]
[WEST KAI laughs]
Hey! Three of my
fighters advanced!
I'm incredible!
[KING KAI] Yes, West Kai...
Incredibly lucky!
[WEST KAI] I dare you
to say that again!
Lucky!
[WEST KAI] Oh! You're
brain's slower than
South Kai's fighters!
[SOUTH KAI] Guys!
Guys! Let's not argue!
Let's make fun of East Kai.
She only has one fighter!
[EAST KAI] Quiet!
I only need one of my
fighters to beat you dummies!
[WEST KAI] You want to
try saying that again
without spitting in my ear?
[MUSHROOM MC] And now the
start of the Quarter Finals!
[MUSHROOM MC]
First in the ring!
Torbie from the
South Quadrant.
And Tapkar from the West!
Torbie! Kick that little boy
back to his own galaxy!
[WEST KAI laughs]
South Kai, I sure hope you're
ready to eat your words!
[SOUTH KAI] Hmph!
Tapkar! Show them your footwork!
[TAPKAR giggles]
[TAPKAR growls]
[TORBIE gasps]
[TAPKAR giggles]
[KAIS gasp]
Ah... Oh, wow!
He's so fast, my eyes
can't keep up with him!
[WEST KAI laughs]
This... is bad...
[TAPKAR hisses]
Let's get this party started!
[gong crash]
[TAPKAR yells]
[TORBIE yells]
[TORBIE gasps]
[TAPKAR yells]
[TORBIE yelps]
[TORBIE] Huh...?
[TAPKAR pants]
I'm tired...
[panting continues]
[TAPKAR] I give up...
[TAPKAR pants]
[TORBIE stammers]
That ring is just
designed for big people.
It's biased against
small guys like Tapkar.
You're such a sore loser!
[MUSHROOM MC] Next match!
Froug versus Maraikoh!
--[FROUG grunts]
--[SOUTH KAI gasps]
There we go!
[MARAIKOH laughs]
You think being bigger
than me is funny, huh?
[MARAIKOH growls]
[MARAIKOH] Hmm?
You stopped laughing!
Guess it's not so funny
when you're the small one!
[FROUG laughs]
[MUSHROOM MC] Froug continues to
swell up to unbelievable size!
But what does he plan to
do with this odd ability?
Oh, wow...
This sure is some
wacky competition.
Kinda like a circus...
[FROUG laughs]
[FROUG] That's right...
Keep sliding back...
And before long, there'll
be nowhere to slide back to
except "out of the ring".
My oh my!
With Froug's expanding gullet,
he's giving new meaning
to the phrase "this ring's not
big enough for the both of us."
[MARAIKOH grunts]
[FROUG chuckles]
You won't beat me!
[MARAIKOH growls]
[MARAIOH yells]
Huh...?
[MARAIKOH grunts]
[FROUG whimpers]
[whimpering continues]
[GOKU gasps]
[FROUG yells]
[FROUG grunts]
[CROWD cheers]
[MUSHROOM MC]
And the winner by ring out,
advancing to the semifinals...
is Maraikoh!
The strong arm from
the West Quadrant!
[WEST KAI laughs]
Ah, darn!
Ahh... Now, it's
finally my turn!
Hmph!
I'm ready!
[MUSHROOM MC] The third
exciting match will be between
Arqua from the East Quadrant and
Goku from the North Quadrant!
[KING KAI] He's yours,
Goku, get him!
[EAST KAI] Don't even joke!
Arqua's gonna
tear him to pieces!
Let's see some action!
[gong crash]
Don't just stand there, Arqua!
Go and beat that little rookie!
Everybody's watching!
You're making me look bad!
[ARQUA whimpers]
[GOKU yells]
[ARQUA yells]
Sorry...
I wouldn't have kicked him
so hard if I had known
how... how weak the guy was...
Arqua! Hurry! Use
your special power!!
O--kay...
[ARQUA growls]
[EAST KAI screams]
[GOKU grunts]
[KING KAI gasps]
[CROWD gasps]
[GRAND KAI] Whoa-ho...
Huh...?
[KING KAI gasps]
[CROWD gasps]
Oh dear...
[EAST KAI giggles]
[KING KAI whimpers]
Not so cocky now, are you?
Once Arqua is underwater,
he's absolutely unbeatable!
But... that's just not fair!
Why? There's nothing
in the rule book
against changing
the ring into water.
There should be...
[GOKU grunts]
[ARQUA screams]
I've gotta take this
out of the water!
[ARQUA screams]
Now!
Solar Flare!
[ARQUA grunts]
[GOKU] Ka... me...
ha... me...
Haaa!
[ARQUA] Oh?
[ARQUA screams]
[CROWD murmurs]
[EAST KAI gasps]
[ARQUA grunts]
And that's a ring out!
[MUSHROOM MC laughs]
The winner of this
round is Goku!
[CROWD roars]
Oh yeah! Goku's the winner!
Yeah! Woo-hoo! Yeah, yeah!
[GOKU laughs]
[EAST KAI] Arqua!
You have destroyed
my reputation!
You will run one thousand laps
around the Grand Kai's palace!
[ARQUA stammers]
Now hop to it!
[GOKU] Say, those were some
great moves back there.
One more of those
underwater attacks
and I would have
been out cold.
[ARQUA gasps]
I'll... win next time...
Alright then! We can rematch!
Someday...
Just keep training, okay?
What are you doing?!
One thousand laps!
[EAST KAI growls]
Now! It's the last bout
of the quarter finals!
Olibu from the
North Quadrant...
And from the West Quadrant...
Pikkon!
[CROWD cheering]
Go, Olibu! Hurray, Pikkon!
Give us a good fight!
Finally, the bout we've
all been waiting for!
Both Pikkon and Olibu
are highly expected
to take home the gold this year!
It seems the entire tournament
hinges on this match!
[CROWD &amp; FIGHTERS cheer]
Come on! Olibu!
Hey! North Kai!
Why don't you just
save your breath
and cheer for someone good?!
There's no way
he can beat Pikkon!
What?!
Just wait and see,
you fast-talking half-pint!
Olibu's gonna beat Pikkon
without even trying!
OH! Everyone look at North Kai!
He's just told
another CORNY joke
that no one thinks is funny!
[KING KAI groans]
[gong crash]
[PIKKON yells]
[OLIBU grunts]
[CROWD yells]
[OLIBU yells]
[PIKKON yells]
[OLIBU growls]
[FIGHTERS gasp]
[KING KAI whimpers]
[PIKKON grunts]
[GOKU gasps]
[OLIBU growls]
[PIKKON yells]
[OLIBU yells]
[grunting]
Look at that energy...
And... how polished all their
fighting techniques are...
These guys are true
martial artists...
[grunting]
[PIKON yells]
[OLIBU yells]
[WEST KAI gasps]
[KING KAI gasps]
Ah...
[OLIBU grunts]
[CROWD murmurs]
Aw... man!
I landed out.
So I don't need to say it.
But still, I want... to say...
I concede.
[CROWD gasps]
It's official, people!
Pikkon haaas won!
[CROWD cheers]
[MUSHROOM MC] And that
brings us to the Semifinals!
This should be dynomite!
So, Goku, how do you feel?
I'm... trembling...
It's just indescribable...
Trembling, huh?
Well, of course you're scared.
With you being a rookie and all.
No, I'm trembling...
'cause I'm excited!
What?! But you can't be!
[GRAND KAI laughs]
Well, good for you, Goku!
Gee... Beating Pikkon
is gonna take all I've got...
Huh?
[NARRATOR] The Other World
Tournament is coming to a head!
Will Pikkon clench
the prize as expected?
Or will Goku the underdog
be able to win?
Stay tuned for more
of Dragon Ball Z!