[NARRATOR Last time
on Dragon Ball Z!
Things looked bad
for Gohan and Krillin,
as they fell before the Ginyu
Force's first wave of attack.
But then, at their
darkest moment,
a light arrived to bring hope
to the young warriors...
A light that has traveled
across the galaxy from Earth,
bringing with it a warrior
determined to defend
his friends and
family at any cost.
A hero that has trained
himself in extreme conditions,
and overcome
impossible opposition
to bring himself
to this very place,
ready to face the most
difficult challenge
he has ever
encountered.
[NARRATOR} This Saiyan
fighter's strength and power
are matched only by his
determination and will
to stand up and
face the evil
that threatens to put an end
to everything he believes in.
The last line of defense
for his friends,
his family, and the
planet Earth...
[NARRATOR] A warrior
named... Goku.
[NARRATOR] Armed with training
in one hundred times gravity
and a bag of
Senzu beans,
Goku would soon find
out whether or not
all of his efforts
had been in vain.
[KRILLIN chuckles]
[NARRATOR] The proud father
and friend took a few moments
to revive Gohan and Krillin,
before engaging in battle.
Whaa--?!
[GOKU] Your mom'd kill me if
she saw how dirty you are...
Hah! Yeah, right! You've
gotta be kidding me!
[BURTER] Don't sweat it!
His power level
is only five thousand!
[NARRATOR] Recoome stood ready
to defeat this unknown intruder,
but Goku was
not intimidated.
You'll never even
touch me. Not one finger.
[VEGETA] No... Is
he... C-Could he be?!
[RECOOME] 'Cause I'm about
to send all you little wimps
straight to hell!
Dodge this, punk!
Here it comes!
Full power!
Eraser Gun!
[RECOOME grunts]
[groaning]
[NARRATOR] One swift attack
was all Goku needed
to put an end to the
rampaging Recoome...
But the members of
the Ginyu Force
weren't the only
ones awestruck
by this unprecedented
show of strength!
Vegeta's worst fears
may be coming true!
Has Goku really become the
legendary Super Saiyan?
No... Is he... You do
not deceive my eyes!
[NARRATOR] The battle
continues today!
[RECOOME groans softly]
[GOKU] You two!
I'm warning you!
Leave this planet now
and don't ever come back!
I don't want to fight you,
but I will if I have to.
And if it comes to
that, I promise you
that you'll both be joining
your friend here on the ground.
Understand me?
[JEICE chuckles]
Oy... Did you
hear that, Burter?
This guy gets in
one lucky punch
and he thinks he can
take on the Ginyu Force!
Yeah, Jeice! I think he
must have hit himself
in the head pretty hard
when he landed here.
He caught Recoome by
surprise, that's all.
That doesn't make him
tough, just lucky... Right?
Right... I'm surprised
he got a punch in at all.
This guy's power level
is way too pathetic
to be a challenge...
Man, I don't
like this at all!
We better get
ready, Gohan!
[GOHAN] Right!
C'mon, Dad...
[JEICE] Hmph.
[BURTER] Yeah-ha.
[BOTH grunt]
Now! Say hello to
the Ginyu Force!
Jeice!
I'm your
worst nightmare!
Prepare yourself
for... Burter!
You wanna dance,
or fight?
Do it,
Kakarot...
Ready?! Set! Go!
[BOTH shouting]
[BOTH shout]
[BURTER] Feel it!
[JEICE] Yaaah!
[JEICE gasps]
[JEICE] Burter!
[BURTER] What?!
What's the deal
with this guy?
He won't even
make a move!
I don't
know, Jeice!
I guess he's
scared stiff!
Gotcha! I'll bet the poor
guy is shaking in his boots!
Man! I don't
understand this!
Is Goku just gonna
stand there
and leave himself open
for their attack?
Hey! Yo, Jeice!
This guy's a sitting duck!
Go ahead and
put it to him!
Right! You take
the lead, Burter,
and I'll be right
behind you.
Haah!
[JEICE] Awh yeaah!
Ha, ha, ha! Yeah! Yeah!
Goku! No!
[thinking] Incredible!
If I wasn't seeing
this with my own eyes...
I've had
enough of this!
Think it's time to throw
some pain on the barbie!!
I'm sick of your little
games! We are the Ginyu--
[JEICE screams]
[BURTER gasps]
[JEICE wailing]
How... dare you!
[JEICE whimpers]
Hmm? How dare I what?
Weren't the two of you
just trying to attack me?
Why, you! I'll...
I'll destroy you!!
Haaah!
[gasping]
He's...
...dead meat!
[GOKU yells]
[JEICE screams]
There's... no way!
Where did he get that power?!
He just channeled his power
into some sort of blast!
[FRIEZA laughs]
The audacity of
those foolish Namekians.
Do they truly think they can
outsmart the great Frieza?
Well, we'll just
see about that...
This little snag has only
postponed the inevitable.
Very soon...
I'll beat the secret to
using the Dragon Balls
out of one of
those Namekian pests.
And then nothing will stop
me from making my wish!
[FRIEZA cackles]
[GURU snores softly]
Oh, Guru...
[DENDE thinking] It's been
quite a while since Nail left.
I wonder what's going on?
I feel so helpless...
[thinking] Please, Nail...
They need our help. Hurry!
[GINYU] Gentlemen! You
can't make it as a Ginyu
on brute strength alone!
A Ginyu must be able to
showcase his grandeur
and fabulous strength
in a variety of poses!
Now! It's your turn!
I want to see you men
strike a pose! Watch!
Captain Ginyu!
Got it?!
You look like a bunch
of hood ornaments!
The purpose of
striking a pose
is not to become
like wallpaper!
That's why we chant
loudly when we pose!
To draw attention to
our magnificence!
Hmm... I know! I'll just have to
raise the stakes a little bit.
The best poser gets a
candy... Now do it! Let's go!
Ginyu!
[stammering]
Strock, here!
Captain Strong!
Goose!
Oggers!
Sound off!
[ALL] Now! Feel the power...
[GINYU] ...of The Ginyu Force!
Hrrgh...
So, you're a
captain, too?
[GINYU] There's only one
Captain of the Ginyu Force,
and that's me!
Idiot! You touched
a Dragon Ball!
[HENCHMAN whimpering]
[GINYU] Didn't I specifically
say before starting this try-out
not to touch any of the
Dragon Balls? Well? Didn't I?!
[whimpering]
Y-Yes!
And did you?
Well, uh... Y-Yes...
Okay...
[HENCHMAN screams]
Congratulations,
gentlemen.
You've managed to
survive the first cut.
[sighing]
[GINYU] But...
I'm afraid
try-outs are over.
[ALL whimpering]
You're all tough
guys, that's true,
but, you lack the one thing
that sets all Ginyu's apart...
[GINYU chuckles]
Style!
[GINYU laughs]
[GINYU] Oh, oh, and
gentlemen, one more thing:
Run for your lives!
[ALL whimpering]
[blows landing,
screaming]
[GINYU] Don't feel
ashamed men!
I give the same farewell card
to everyone who tries out
for the Ginyu Force
and doesn't make it!
And remember...
[screaming]
[GINYU] Style!
[GINYU laughs]
[BURTER shouts]
[JEICE shouts]
[JEICE yells]
[thinking] What is
with this guy?
[thinking] Burter and I are
coming at him from every angle,
but he's not dodging!
He's not even lifting a finger!
[thinking] He's really
pissing me off!
You know, Krillin, I just
don't think these guys
are as powerful as we
thought they were.
My Dad hasn't
even fought back.
I'm not
so sure...
[thinking] No one ignores
me like that! No one!
[JEICE yells]
Haaah...
[VEGETA growls]
Hah! Urgh!
Hurgh! Hgh!
No way! They can't
even touch him!
His speed is incredible!
I hardly see him moving!
Those two guys are
about to find out
how powerful Goku
is the hard way.
I... I don't know...
It's two against one and
they're both so strong.
I don't understand!
His power level is only 5000!
I'm sure of it! But my
attacks don't even faze him!
It's obvious
that Kakarot
is raising his power
level so quickly
that they aren't
able to detect it!
He's not even
breaking a sweat!
It's unbelievable! How did he
become so strong so fast?
Those scouters
won't help them.
Even if they knew
his power level,
they still wouldn't
be able to stop him...
But where did
this power come from?!
I must know! If there is a way
to become a Super Saiyan,
I must
find it out!
Argh... That punk... No one
makes a fool of Burter
and lives to tell
about it. Hey, Jeice!
It's time for the
Purple Spiral Flash Attack!
The Purple Spiral Flash,
huh? Hmph. Good idea...
Right, Burter!
Let's do it! Now!
[BURTER] Right!
[BURTER growling]
[JEICE growling]
[BOTH shouting]
Haaaah!
Ah! What's happening?
I've had it!
[BULMA growls]
[BULMA] What do they
think they're doing,
leaving me here alone like
this?! It's inexcusable!
This is not how
to treat a lady!
This place is
ruining my complexion!
The first thing
they're gonna do
when they get back
is take me home!
Don't they have any idea how
weak and defenseless I am?
I'm too
delicate for this!
I miss Earth...
[BULMA screams]
Somebody get
me outta here!
[BURTER growls]
[JEICE] We didn't
even touch him!
[BURTER] Jeice, come in.
Jeice, do you hear me?
[JEICE] Yeah, Burter!
I got you!
I've got a new plan... Use
the Fire Crusher Ball, right?
When you
fire it,
I'm sure he'll jump out
of the way to evade it.
[JEICE] That's your plan?!
[BURTER} I wasn't through!
When he jumps,
I'll sneak in and
crush him from behind.
He might
be fast,
but I'm the fastest
warrior in the universe!
Gotcha, mate...
This is what you get for
messing with the Ginyu.
[JEICE grunts]
Crusher!
Ball!
[grunts]
Dodge, you punk!
Jump, now!
What are you doing?!
[gasping]
He deflected it!
Damn you!
Huh?! Uhh... Hello?
[JEICE gasps]
Hey! Uh... Where did he go?
Look out!
Behind you!
[BURTER screams]
[BURTER] Be merciful...
Hi!
[NARRATOR] Goku certainly
seems to have the upper hand,
but the battle has
only just begun!
Could Vegeta
be right?
Has Goku, through
training and sheer will,
become a thing of legend?
A Super Saiyan?
Find out next time,
on Dragon Ball Z!