[NARRATOR]
Previously, on Dragon Ball Z,
the wicked wizard, Babidi,
resurrected the radically
powerful Majin Buu!
[NARRATOR] Though the misguided
Buu eventually saw the light,
his evil counterpart
destroyed the Earth
and had no intention
of stopping there!
[NARRATOR] With the entire
universe in danger of extinction
the Dragon of Namek was
summoned to bring the Earth
and its inhabitants
back to life!
And in a desperate
bid to stop Buu,
humanity offered up its
collective energy to Goku,
who used it to form
a massive Spirit Bomb!
[NARRATOR] The future of the
universe was now in his hands!
[NARRATOR] At last
the nightmare was over!
Once again Goku
had found a way!
The curse was lifted!
And now the story continues, ten
years since that fateful day!
Huh! That's weird!
She seems to be running
a little sluggish.
Nah, I'd rather fly
the old fashioned way.
[TRUNKS]
It's tune-up time for you!
Much better!
Yeah!
Whoa.
[TRUNKS] It's been so long
since I've been here!
[TRUNKS]
Hello?
Anyone home?
[CHICHI]
We don't want any!
[TRUNKS]
Huh?
Oh! It's you, Trunks!
Welcome to Mount Paoz!
It's great to be out here!
Say ah, is Goten around?
Well, when he wants to be.
Right now he's
out with his father.
They left this morning.
But hey! Go ask Gohan.
I'm sure that he
knows where they are.
Oh that's cool! I actually
wanted to see Gohan anyway!
It's nice to see
you again, ChiChi.
Hey! Knock, knock!
Hello? Gohan?
Huh?
Good afternoon! Welcome!
This is the mid-day
edition of Wether News!
Where we bring you
the latest breaking news...
[GOHAN]
I don't believe it!
Trunks! What are you
doing down there?
Hey! Long time no see!
Yeah! What a great surprise!
Would you mind grabbing
some of these for me?
Sure!
Oh, wow! These books, you're
doing a bit of reading, huh?
[GOHAN]
You could say so!
I'm getting ready
for a big conference!
Oh, hey! Put
those on the table!
Sorry about that.
[TRUNKS]
Whoa!
Dad was right! You're a
bit of a nerd, aren't you?
[GOHAN]
Well maybe, yeah!
Videl come on down and
say hi to an old friend.
[VIDEL] Trunks! Wow, what a
surprise! How've you been?
Oh, pretty good!
It's nice to see ya!
[VIDEL] It's been way
too long! Look at you!
You're a young man now!
[MR. SATAN]
What? Who says I'm too old?
Why my megaton punch is as
strong as ever! Watch this!
[TV] Check your local listings
for tomorrow's tournament!
[sighs]
That's my dad, all right!
He has no shame whatsoever!
Well, he is the World Champion!
Besides, my dad said
that he really helped
him and Goku beat Buu!
I just wish he would stop
taking credit for things
that he really didn't do!
It's like he's a
professional wrestler
and the whole world is his ring!
So, uh, Trunks,
what brings you all the
way out here from west City?
I almost forgot! I came
up here looking for Goten.
Oh! He's out training
with my dad on the south face!
Your folks are on
their way out there as well!
Huh? They didn't
say anything to me!
[GOKU]
Yeah! Hahahaha!
[GOTEN]
Ow!!
[GOHAN]
Ha, ha, ha! Gotcha!
[GOTEN]
Hey! That's not fair!
[GOKU]
Why not?
[GOTEN] You're in
for it now, Dad!
[GOKU]
Oh, yeah?
Now tell me! What's
so important about this?
[pants]
One of these days the shoe's
going to be on the other foot!
[giggles]
Huh?
Hey!
Wow! What a surprise!
How ya doin'?
Now you wouldn't know
that! Would you, Goku?
How could you?
You never call and if we
didn't come to visit you--
we'd probably
never see you again!
Hey! Come on!
You know that's not true!
Didn't we just see each
other not too long ago?
Five years, Goku!
Every time we get
together with everyone,
you say you have to train!
[GOKU]
Well, it's true! I uhh...
Uhhhh... Huh? Heh...
[GOKU] Whoa!
It really has been long!
[BULMA]
What do you mean?
What? Say it!
Well... it's just that
you look middle aged!
Shut your rude mouth!
I'll have you know
that most people think
I look good for my age!
Excuse me for not being an alien
monster that never changes!
We Saiyans evolved
as a warrior race!
We retain our youthfulness
so we can fight longer!
Hmph! I guess your race didn't
evolve with enough brains
to have good manners!
By the way, Kakarot!
Is it true that you
are going to be fighting
in the World Championships?
Yep! Sure am!
And you should compete as well!
You can't beat
those stadium hotdogs!
Hot dogs? Enough already!
Tell me the real
reason you're fighting.
Okay, but I'd really
rather talk about hot dogs!
But if you insist
there's this guy
who signed up
to fight yesterday!
I think he might be really good!
Really?
Hmm...
You'd think I could
sensed a spirit like that.
That's true. If he wasn't
suppressing his energy!
No, I think this
guy is really shrewd!
We may have
ourselves a challenge!
Hmm! I don't believe it!
A real fighter on this planet?
Is he an alien or what?
Uh-uh! This guy's an Earthling!
An Earthling?
Wait, are you talking about
some kind of android, Kakarot?
Nope! This guy
is home grown.
One hundred
percent human being.
[BULMA]
How could that be possible?
You and Vegeta are the best.
There's no way an Earthling
could be on par with you!
Give me a break!
[GOTEN]
Trunks?
I don't believe it!
[TRUNKS]
Hey!
Now, Trunks!
Hay is for horses, son!
[TRUNKS]
Grass too, Mom!
So! Just grazing, huh?
I thought you'd be training!
Are you going to be
fighting in the tournament
or are you chickening out?
Yeah, my dad's
gonna make me fight.
I actually had a
date for tomorrow night.
Until he made me...
cancel, that is!
Aw, come on, Goten!
There's plenty time
after the tournament!
Hm! So your son has the
same slack attitude as mine?
[GOKU chuckles]
Well, it's easy to get a
little soft in times of peace.
Ahh... Excellent!
Now there's a real go-getter!
Well, look who it is!
Grandpa! I just flew around
world again! Good, huh?
Yeah! I think that was
your fastest time yet, Pan!
Think I'll be ready
for tomorrow then?
Wait? No way!
Pan! You're not
really going to fight
in the tournament
tomorrow, are you?
Yeah! Of course I am!
What? But there's not going
to be a junior division
at the tournament
this year, guys!
Don't tell me she's
fighting with adults!
Ah, don't you guys
worry about Pan.
She can hold her own in
just about any division!
She might not
win the championship,
but she'll do just fine.
Pan has the right attitude!
I'm going to enter as well!
And guess what else?
Trunks is entering!
Aren't you, son?
[TRUNKS]
Huh?
[VEGETA] If you don't,
I'll cut your allowance in half!
Ahh...?
[laughs]
[GOTEN]
Trunks is gonna fight!
[ANNOUNCER]
Welcome everyone!
To the World Martial Arts
Championship Tournament!
They never grow up, huh?
I don't know! The jury's
still out on the professor!
[PAN]
Hey! Grandpa!
What's up, Pan?
Let's go have
some fun, Grandpa G!
Hey, Gohan!
How we doing on time?
We're early!
We still have a little bit!
'Kay! Let's go!
Hey! Where are you going?
Grandpa! Hurry! Come on!
[GOKU]
We'll be right back!
[PAN] Do you like
my new teddy, Grandpa?
[GOKU] Yeah!
He seems nice to me!
Here!
[PAN] My name is Pan!
What's yours?
[BUNKO] Hi, my name is Bunko!
You are my best friend!
--[SERVER] There!
--[PAN] Thanks!
[audience laughter]
[BIG BERTHA]
Hey, you! Get back here!
--[KABU] Move it, French Fry!
--[MAN IN BLACK] Huh?
Aw, dude! What a score!
This is the mother lode!
Huh?
[gasps]
Thank you, Sir!
What? Pan?
What's the big deal,
you little runt?
You blind or what?
You killed my cone!
[growls]
Hey, bonehead!
Do you know sign language? Huh?
Huh?
Hey! What are you doing?
Eeeeh! Yikes!
[KABU] What's the deal,
you little psycho?
She's serious!
Put up your dukes!
Pan?
[wails]
He killed my ice cream cone!
Pheeew.
Goodness gracious!
Hey! Pan! Look! You can
have Grandpa's ice cream cone!
Thanks!
Phew!
[BIG BERTHA]
Where ya goin', kid?!
You're mine!
Aaaaahh!
Hey! There they are!
[GOKU] Hey! What's up, guys?
You look great! How are ya?
[KRILLIN] Well, to tell you
the truth, we're a little p-o'd!
How come you never call or
come by? We're your friends!
Training is fine, but
can't you keep in touch?
Ahaha! I'm sorry, guys! Geez!
I got bawled out by Bulma
for the same exact thing!
You do have phones, don't you?
Actually no,
I can't figure mine out.
[GOKU]
I hear ya!
Hey! Are you gonna
enter, Piccolo?
Hmph! And step into the ring
with the likes of you, huh?
No thanks! I'm gonna kick
back and enjoy the show.
I'm too old for this.
You're sandbagging, Piccolo!
You don't look a day older
than you did ten years ago.
Grandpa!
We're gonna be late!
Huh? Yeah! Pan's right!
Bye, you guys!
We'll see you in a little while!
[KRILLIN thinking]
Yeah! Ten years from now!
Oh man, I don't know
what it is about that guy,
but it's impossible to stay
mad at him very long! Hah!
[MR. SATAN] We're going to work
this the way we always do, Buu!
You're going to go out there
and beat all of the challengers
and then of course
lose to me in the finals.
But remember to be very gentle
in those early rounds
so the other
challengers don't withdraw!
One of these days
maybe I'll let you win
and you can be Champion!
Now how does that sound?
Okay!
[MR. SATAN] Buu the Champion!
It has a nice ring to it,
doesn't it, Big Bee?
[knocking on door]
[MR. SATAN]
Hmm?
Now what? Another
fan bearing gifts?
I thought I told them not
to let anyone else through!
Hi!
Hey! Goku!
How ya doing, buddy?
Don't forget about me, Gramps!
Oh, my goodness!
It's my favorite
little girl in the world!
How are you, Pan!
Fine! But your beard hurts!
Oh! Hi, Buu!
[MR. SATAN] Aww!
You came all the way here
just to cheer on Gramps?
Uh-uh! I came out here
to win the tournament!
Huh?!
Yeah! We're all going
to fight! It should be fun!
[MR. SATAN]
Hmm?
Ready to rumble?!
Hey, don't worry about it!
If one of us makes
it to the finals,
we'll let you take
the victory, is that okay?
Wow! Really?
You'd really do that?
Of course we would! Why not?
But that's assuming we make it!
I mean, someone else
might make it to the finals!
You never know!
Oh! Yes! That's true!
But hang tough!
If you try your best,
you just might make it!
[GOTEN]
Excuse me, Champ!
All of our friends
and family just arrived,
but they were told there
weren't any more seats left
in the whole statium!
Oh hoho! Is that so? Hahahaha!
No seats left?
That's a good one!
Not while
I'm World Champion!
[ANDROID 18 thinking]
What a slap in the face.
[KRILLIN thinking] Oh man, talk
about your nosebleed section.
[GOHAN thinking]
We look like ants.
[BULMA thinking]
Unbelievable!
[OOLONG thinking] Ooo,
I hope no one can smell that!
[YAMCHA thinking]
Dude...
I should have entered!
At least then I'd
have a decent view!
How could you
say such a thing?
What? I could'a done it!
Well, I'm not gonna
take this sitting down!
This is absurd!
Wait! Bulma! Please!
Let me go talk to my father!
Look, Mama!
I can see everything!
Wonderful!
Well, sometimes it pays
to know the right people, huh?
Ahh! What a relief!
Yeah! Bulma was about to
go ape on us! Hahahahaha!
Huh?
Ooo! Someone's coming, Mama!
[ANNOUNCER clears throat]
Ladies and Gentlemen,
welcome to the World
Martial Arts Championships!
It's time to introduce
you to our finalists!
Let's hear it for
these great athletes
who have passed
the preliminary rounds!
[ANNOUNCER]
Yes! Yes! Give it up! Yeah!
Hey! Goten! Who was it that won
the last time we fought here?
That was last time!
Yay!
Aa! There he is!
All right! Go! Go! Buu!
Whoa! Check out the Buu!
He's become really
popular with the ladies!
[ANNOUNCER] All right!
All right! Here they are!
The greatest
fighters in the world!
Each vying for the right
to be called World Champion!
Which one will it be, folks?
Your guess is as good as mine!
[ANNOUNCER] And now it's time
for the fighters to draw lots
to see how they'll be matched up
in these exciting first bouts
of the final rounds!
[NARRATOR] The starting gun
for the tournament
is about to be fired!
Who is the mysterious fighter
whom Goku was speaking of?
And which competitor will
be named the new Number One
Under the Sun? Stay tuned!