[CELL chuckles]
[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
an evil android creature
arrived from the future
to take over the world.
And mankind seems
powerless to stop it.
[COUPLE screams]
[NARRATOR] Fortunately,
Goku has fully recovered
from the devastating virus that
had a grip on him for so long.
And now he's ready to
put his plan into action.
[NARRATOR] Goku has to
get into fighting shape,
and he's taking Vegeta, Trunks,
and Gohan to Kami's place
where they can get a year of
intense training in one day.
[VEGETA] All right, I'll go!
[NARRATOR]
The door is open,
all they have to do
is step through...
[MR. POPO] Good luck.
[NARRATOR] Is Trunks
tough enough to survive
being locked in a
room with Vegeta?
If Goku is right,
this training will push
all of their Saiyan powers
to the next level,
transforming them
into Ascended Saiyans.
This plan had better work,
because those three
devious androids are
still hot on his trail.
[ANDROID 17] Hi...
Can Goku come out and play?
Where has Goku gone?
If you don't tell us
where he's hiding,
I'll make you tell us.
Alright... Have it your way.
Over there! That island!
You and me!
Very well...
If you really want to.
[NARRATOR] Piccolo's definitely
got his hands full now.
Locked into a deadly
duel with Android 17.
Since uniting with Kami,
Piccolo has been pumped up
with extra power.
But does he have the strength to
pull the plug on Android 17?
Find out today!
Tell us where Goku is...
or I'll make you.
Last chance.
[PICCOLO] I'm going
to enjoy this.
[ANDROID 17] Hm...
[ANDROID 17] Hm.
I don't think you know
what you're getting into
by challenging me.
Just give up.
Really.
You can't win.
[PICCOLO chuckles]
[ANDROID 17 laughs]
[ANDROID 17] Very well.
Let's see what you've got.
[PICCOLO gasps]
[thinking] Fighting this android
is going to be tough because
I won't be able to keep
an eye on the other two.
I've got to make sure
they won't attack me
--while my back is turned.
--[ANDROID 18 chuckles]
Keep those two
out of this. Alright?
[ANDROID 17]
Don't worry.
Those two are only spectators.
This is between me and you.
[thinking] Perfect!
If it's just him, then
I won't have any problem
shutting him down.
I'll take out Android 17 first
and then I'll get the others.
If I can beat them, then Cell
will have nothing to absorb
and he won't be able
to become complete.
[PICCOLO growls]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[PICCOLO growling]
[growling continues]
[PICCOLO yells]
[ANDROID 16 growls]
[yelling continues]
[ROSHI growls softly]
[KRILLIN] Come on!
Something's happening out there!
I've never felt anything
like this before.
The energy coming from
Piccolo is incredible!
Wow!
It's for real?
But, he's all
alone out there?
No, Kami is with
Piccolo right now!
[ROSHI, TIEN, &amp; YAMCHA]
Huh?!
That's no ordinary
energy level.
It's the combined powers of Kami
and Piccolo working together.
Well whatta ya know?
--[MR. POPO] Oh no.
--[GOHAN whimpers]
[GOKU]
Time's running out.
Piccolo has already
started fighting!
[GOHAN] Who's he
fighting, Daddy?
Is it Cell?
[GOKU] No...
There's no life force...
It must be the androids!
[GOHAN]
What?!
I've got to
help Piccolo!
[GOKU] Come back, Gohan!
We have to complete
our training!
Piccolo will have to hold
them off on his own!
[GOHAN whimpers]
[GOKU] It's no use going
down there, Gohan!
You're just not
strong enough yet!
And besides, you'd only
get in Piccolo's way!
As soon as we
finish our training,
we'll go down and help Piccolo.
You can count on it!
Yes. That's right.
You will be stronger than
you've ever been before.
[GOHAN whimpers]
[thinking] I wonder how
Vegeta and Trunks are doing?
I wonder if they've become
Ascended Saiyans yet?
Their time is almost up!
I don't think Piccolo can handle
those androids on his own...
[PICCOLO yells]
[yelling continues]
I sense two powers.
Piccolo is not alone.
[ANDROID 17]
What was that?
[PICCOLO growls]
[ANDROID 17 gasps]
[ANDROID 17 grunts]
[ANDROID 17]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[blows landing,
BOTH grunting]
[PICCOLO yells]
[ANDROID 17 grunts]
[PICCOLO growls]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[ANDROID 17 chuckles]
[ANDROID 16 growls]
[PICCOLO &amp; ANDROID 17 grunting]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[PICCOLO yells]
[PICCOLO grunting]
Wow. Not bad.
Come back here!
[PICCOLO growls]
[ANDROID 17 gasps]
[PICCOLO growls,
ANDROID 17 grunts]
[PICCOLO yells]
[ANDROID 17 grunts]
[PICCOLO grunts softly]
Well...
[PICCOLO growls]
He beat me.
How? Just how could he beat me?
I must have
miscalculated somewhere.
[PICCOLO]
Stay down!
[PICCOLO grunts]
[ANDROID 17 grunts]
[PICCOLO growls]
[ANDROID 17 gasps]
[PICCOLO yells]
[thinking] His strength
is incredible.
[PICCOLO] What's wrong?
Do you need to recharge
your batteries?
No. I am never going to give up.
[thinking] Good!
'Cause I'm just getting started!
[PICCOLO chuckles]
[DR. BRIEF hums]
Ah... I think
he's asleep!
[BULMA] Great!
Thanks for looking after Trunks
while I work on this, Dad!
[DR. BRIEF] Sure...
Any luck in deciphering
those plans to Android 17?
Yeah... But man,
it's a lot of work!
I'm trying to isolate the
android's main power source,
and then, I can shut it off!
The only problem is
there are thousands of
circuits to sort through!
Don't give up!
I've gone too far
to turn back now!
But I only hope this remote
control I made can zero in
on the frequencies of the
circuits and turn them off!
Huh?
What's wrong?
[alarm sounds]
[BULMA] Huh?
Hey! Stop that!
Why'd Dr. Gero have
to make these androids
so hard to figure out?
[BULMA growls
[BABY TRUNKS wails]
[DR. BRIEF] Uh-oh...
[wailing continues]
I wish...
I could cry.
Heh. Nice shooting.
But not quite nice enough.
[PICCOLO] Hmph.
[PICCOLO growls]
[blows landing,
BOTH grunting]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[ANDROID 17 growls]
[PICCOLO] There you are...
Scatter Shot!
[PICCOLO yells]
[ANDROID 17 laughs]
[ANDROID 17 chuckles]
[PICCOLO growls]
[PICCOLO grunting]
[grunting continues]
[PICCOLO growls]
Makosen... Ha!
[ANDROID 17 yells]
What? He deflected my blast!
Well done.
Impressive light show.
Do you have anymore
tricks to share with me
before I finish you?
[ANDROID 18] 17 is
playing with him.
Why doesn't he just get it over
with? Then we can go find Goku!
[PICCOLO growls]
[PICCOLO yells]
It feels like a fierce
battle is going on,
but I can't tell who's winning,
Is it Piccolo or the android?
I know who's going to win!
There's no way that Android
could have as much power
as Piccolo right now.
[ROSHI] Not so fast!
Piccolo's energy
is incredible, yes,
but we really don't know
how strong the Android is!
For all we know, that Android
is as strong as ten Piccolos.
[ANDROID 17] What a shame.
Is that all you've got for me?
No!
Come on... Let's go!
Finish him off.
If you can't
do it then maybe
you should let someone
who can--like me!
Stay out of this.
Can't you see I'm just
trying to have some fun?
Are you ready to begin again?
Yes, of course.
I have enjoyed
this game.
I'd love to stay, but I must
find Goku and deal with him.
[PICCOLO] Then stop talking
and start fighting!
[PICCOLO growls]
[PICCOLO yells]
[ANDROID 17 grunts]
[PICCOLO] Masenko... Ha!
[ANDROID 17] Again?
You're so predictable.
[PICCOLO grunts]
[ANDROID 17 grunts]
Hmph! He won't give up.
What a fool.
He keeps on shooting hoping
he'll get lucky and hit me.
[PICCOLO grunts]
[PICCOLO growls]
[ANDROID 17] Huh...?
It's time to end this!
[ANDROID 17 gasps]
[ANDROID 17]
What have you done?!
[ANDROID 17] He was
never trying to hit me!
It was a trick all along!
[ANDROID 17 whimpers]
[PICCOLO chuckles]
[PICCOLO] You never expected a
guidance scatter shot, did ya?
It's all over.
There's no escape for you now!
[PICCOLO chuckles]
[PICCOLO] Your reign
of terror ends today!
[PICCOLO] So long, Android!
[PICCOLO yells]
[ANDROID 17 whimpers]
[PICCOLO chuckles]
[GROUP grunts]
[KRILLIN] What's happening?!
[PICCOLO growls]
[PICCOLO gasps]
No! Alive? Still?
[ANDROID 17 chuckles]
Give up!
There's no way to win!
[PICCOLO] Well, it's not
over 'til it's over!
Ya see that island?
Meet me there and we'll
end this little game
once and for all!
Ha! Unless you're
too afraid to go?
[PICCOLO growls]
[OFFICE MAN whimpers]
It's you're lucky day,
little man.
Your worthless life
will be spared...
I have much more important
things to deal with right now!
Hmm... Ah yes, perfect...
Piccolo must be
fighting Android 17!
I can feel his energy signal!
[OFFICE MAN screams]
I'm still alive?!
[CELL grunts]
Complete at last.
Wonderful!
This is going to be far less
difficult than I imagined!
[CELL laughs]
[NARRATOR] Things have
taken a turn for the worse.
Cell is on his way to
absorb the androids,
but Piccolo is completely
unaware of the imminent danger.
There's no room for error!
[NARRATOR] Piccolo put up a good
fight against Android 17.
But even with the power of
Kami surging through him,
he couldn't recycle
that renegade robot!
Now more than ever, the help
of Goku and the other Saiyans
is needed to stop these
machines of madness!
With every second that ticks by,
Cell is closing in!
If he gets to the island
before Goku and Gohan
can finish their training,
then all hope is lost!
Could this be the
beginning of the end?
Find out on the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!