[chuckles]
[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z!
Cell displayed
a most uncanny ability.
It's hard to believe,
but Cell can use
the special attack moves
of all the other fighters!
Yes, even Goku's
mighty Kamehame-Ha Wave
is a part of the Android's
deadly arsenal...
a fact Piccolo
found out the hard way!
[NARRATOR] With this
incredible ability unleashed,
it seemed that the
injured Namek had no choice
but to raise the white flag.
But Piccolo had a plan.
I am Cell.
I am an android
created by the great Dr. Gero.
[NARRATOR] Counting on
Cell's unbridled arrogance,
Piccolo persuaded
the mysterious Android
to divulge the story
of his origin!
It seems Cell has traveled here
from 24 years in the future,
in search of a very
specific energy source.
[CELL] I now require the energy
of Androids 17 and 18.
Once I have
absorbed them I will be
the most powerful being
who has ever lived!
[NARRATOR] But while Cell
was busy telling all,
Piccolo had enough time to
regenerate his injured arm.
[grunts]
Huh?!
[yells]
[NARRATOR] Back in one piece,
Piccolo stands ready
to fight the Android once again.
But will his powers
be enough? Find out today!
[thinking] That's odd!
This storm just
blew up out of nowhere!
And there seems to be
a great energy behind it.
[thinking] It's gonna take
all I've got to help Piccolo.
[thinking]
I just hope I'm not too late.
♪
[PICCOLO] You know Cell,
even with the energy
you took from me,
my power is still
far greater than your own.
And don't think I won't pay
you back for taking my arm.
Maybe I'll take yours.
Very cunning... Feigning
weakness just long enough
to regenerate your arm.
[CELL laughs]
Perhaps my superior mind
came from you.
Don't give me all the credit--
the idea was Kami's.
Kami?
Mmm... Ah, yes... Kami!
So he's the Namek you fused with
to get your new power.
[PICCOLO]
Now you've got it... Ha!
Atleast you're
not as dumb as I am!
[thinking] But Kami was
the guardian of the earth...
That means there are
no Dragon Balls
to revive people after
I've consumed them.
[chuckles]
[CELL thinking]
My, how convenient... for me!
[CELL] Well Namek, I'd say
you've gone to a great deal
of trouble for such a
miniscule power increase.
Hm! I'm afraid you haven't
even come close
to seeing the depths
of my new abilities.
But, you will soon enough.
[grunts]
[growls]
Hm?
[BOTH] Huh?
[KRILLIN] All right! There's
Piccolo--we're not too late!
Hey, Trunks, up there!
[TRUNKS] I see it!
Look at it. Look at its skin.
It must be that creature
that came from my capsule.
[thinking] Trunks is here?!
[CELL thinking] Stupid boy...
As if being killed by me
in his own time wasn't enough.
[CELL thinking] I don't
understand why creatures
so defective are
ever allowed to live.
[CELL thinking] Oh well...
It will soon be corrected.
[CELL chuckles]
He's... freakin' me out!
Uh huh.
[KRILLIN] Is this
the guy who's responsible
for wiping out
everyone in Gingertown?
[PICCOLO]
Yeah. He's the one.
So be careful,
and stay clear of his tail.
What's up with
the energy I'm sensing?
It feels like
Goku and Tien are here!
I'll explain
all of that soon.
Right after we
destroy this thing!
[CELL] So, you really
think you can defeat me?!
[chuckles]
Don't flatter yourself!
Man... he's a freak!
Don't worry guys--
with the three of us here
he doesn't stand a chance
and he knows it.
Namek, once I become complete,
you won't be so cocky.
[grunts] Face it!
[PICCOLO] You're outnumbered
and outmatched!
You can't win!
Especially if that
Kamehame-Ha technique
is the best you can do!
Kamehame-Ha...? The only
way he could know that
is if he studied
under Master Roshi!
Not only do I know
the Kamehame-Ha, Krillin,
but I also know
another little move
called the Spirit Bomb!
[BOTH gasp]
Impossible...
How does he know my name?!
Man, this whole thing is getting
freakier with every minute!
[CELL] Tell me,
how's your friend Goku doing?
[KRILLIN]
You'll see soon enough!
[CELL thinking] So, he's still
alive in this timeline.
I will deal with him later.
[CELL thinking] First I must
attend to these three vagabonds.
[gasps]
You must feel honored--
soon you'll be a part of
the perfect being!
[grunts]
[CELL]
But as anxious as you are,
you will just
have to be patient.
You see... I have a date
with a couple of friends
and it would be rude
of me to make them wait.
[CELL]
But here's a parting gift!
[laughs]
What?!
[BOTH gasp]
Solar Flare!
[grunts]
[BOTH stammer]
[PICCOLO, KRILLIN,
and TRUNKS groan]
[CELL laughs]
[ALL groan]
I can't see! Augh!
He's gone!
[groaning]
[KRILLIN] Ah man!
I wish I had Master Roshi's
sunglasses right about now!
[grunts] Hey, Krillin!
That was Tien's Solar
Flare technique, wasn't it?
Yeah. It's a great
move if you're looking
to make a quick escape.
[KRILLIN]
I've even been known to use it
on more than one occasion...
[PICCOLO] That coward!
[PICCOLO grunts]
[KRILLIN]
I-I don't see him anywhere!
We have to find him quickly!
Or more innocent people
are going to die!
[chuckles]
[laughs]
Those pitiful fools
were no match for my cunning!
And as long as I
keep my energy hidden,
they won't find me
until it's too late!
[CELL laughs]
[CHICHI]
Everyone! Hurry! Come see!
M-Master Roshi!
You have to hurry! It's Goku!
Calm down... What's happening?
Is it Dad? Is he okay?
You've all got to come see!
[CHICHI] Up here!
Move it, you slow-pokes!
[ROSHI]
I'm coming, I'm coming!
What's the big hurry?!
Shhh! Quiet please!
[ALL] Huh?
Everyone! Did you see that?!
Goku actually smiled!
Yeah!
He smiled all right!
He must be
feeling better!
[OOLONG] Oh, gee, Gohan,
you should be a doctor!
[chuckles]
[CHICHI] Oh my, I'm so happy!
[ROSHI] Wait...
[ROSHI]
That's no ordinary smile...
[BOTH] Huh?
I've seen that look on
his face a few times before.
[ROSHI] It's that same
peculiar smile he gets
just before he's about to
engage in a colossal battle.
Yeah, it is. Yeah!
Hm.
[CHICHI grunts]
I bet it's a premonition.
Like he's getting ready
to fight those Androids!
[YAMCHA laughs]
[YAMCHA] Yeah! Even though
he's still recovering,
he's planning
the big battle already!
Boy, Goku sure is
something, huh?
Ah, Yamcha, maybe you should...
Well... what'd ya think?
Am I right?
[ROSHI chuckles] I wouldn't
put it past Goku!
[OOLONG] Yamcha!
Yeah? What?
[CHICHI grunting]
Did... I say "battle"?
No, I meant battling
his condition, that's all!
If you think my Goku's
going to fight any time soon,
you're sadly mistaken!
Yeah, but Mom...
Yamcha just meant
when he gets better. I--
[CHICHI] That's enough, Gohan!
My poor Goku is suffering,
and all you can think about
is how soon he can help you!
Sorry...
So... he will not
be fighting. Is that clear?!
[CHICHI] I can't hear you?!
[ALL] Yes ma'am...
Thank you!
Now please keep quiet!
[CHICHI] Much better!
These flaws in
my body are intolerable.
I can't believe
that Namek actually
exhausted some of my energy...
Really...
[CELL] If I don't
absorb those Androids soon,
these imperfections
will be more than I can bear.
Hmm... Nickeytown.
Devouring these people
should give me
just the pick-me-up I need.
[yells]
[tires screech]
[BUS DRIVER yells]
[BOTH yell]
Hey! Get off the road!
[thinking] I just hope
those Androids can survive
long enough
for me to reach them.
[BUS DRIVER] Last warning,
you moron! Move it!
[thinking] After all, if Piccolo
was able to slow me down,
who knows what he
might be able to do
to those lower-model droids.
[horn honks]
[thinking] I guess I'll just
have to spend less time
playing with my food.
[commotion]
What's up, freak show?
Why you holdin' us up
from our game, bucko?
[PLAYER 2] Maybe he's
a mascot who lost his team!
[PLAYER 3]
Yeah! Go grasshoppers...
Weirdo. Get off the road.
Or we're gonna
throw you off ourselves!
[BOTH grunt]
[PLAYER 1]
So what's it gonna be, huh?!
[CELL chuckles]
Well boys,
after careful consideration,
I think I'll choose option two.
[yells]
[PLAYER 6 gasps]
[PLAYERS gasp]
[commotion]
Blocking formation!
[PLAYERS grunt]
[ALL grunting, yelling]
[PLAYERS groan]
Hey, look!
Hmmm?
[grunts]
[thinking] Vegeta?! I thought
the Androids took care of him!
Hmmm. Perhaps they're in even
more danger than I thought.
[screams]
[PLAYERS groan]
[thinking]
Better hurry this along...
[PLAYERS groan, yell]
[VEGETA] That's strange.
One of the power levels
I was following
seems to have disappeared...
But I can still sense
one of the others.
It can't be Android--
they don't have power levels!
This is absolutely ridiculous!
I have to know who... it is!
[grunts] I can't... stand it!
[grunting]
How could I have
let him escape?!
[quavered exhales]
He's out of control!
[PICCOLO] I'll find you, Cell!
I'll find you!
[yells]
Aaah! The Namek! It can't be!
[grunts]
--[TRUNKS] Huh?
--[KRILLIN] Vegeta!
F-Father!
[VEGETA grunting]
[VEGETA] Namek! I demand
to know what happened here!
All right, I'll tell you,
but let's wait for Tien first.
[PICCOLO]
He should be here shortly.
Well, in the meantime,
answer me this...
[VEGETA]
Who are you... really?
There's no way
the real Piccolo could have
such incredible fighting power!
[PICCOLO scoffs]
[grunts] Answer me, now!
[TRUNKS] I'll tell you...
He needed to get stronger
to fight the Androids,
so he merged with Kami!
Piccolo merged with Kami?
[thinking] It seems
too incredible to imagine!
With that union,
Piccolo has become
more powerful than I am,
even as a Super Saiyan!
But that's impossible!
He is nothing but a mere Namek!
Uh... Huh?
Hey look! I can see Tien!
[KRILLIN] See? There he is!
[thinking]
This situation seems hopeless.
I'm not sure
I'm even powerful enough
to defeat Androids 17 and 18,
never mind 16...
And that still leaves Cell!
Piccolo! Er, I mean, Kami!
Eh. No, uh, I mean--
that is--uh, aaah...! Mmm...
Uh, whoever you are...
I'm trying to say
that Tien is here!
Krillin, just call me Piccolo.
[PICCOLO] Now listen up!
What you're about
to hear may determine
whether we live or die...
[gasps]
Ever since I
arrived in Gingertown
I have been fighting
a creature from the future.
He is, in fact, an android
created by Dr. Gero.
[TIEN, KRILLIN, VEGETA,
and TRUNKS gasp]
[stammers]
[CELL] Next.
[BUS DRIVER yells]
[stammers]
[birds chirpping]
I hope you know
how much I hate this outfit!
I look like a cowgirl!
Do you think
we'll have the time
to find me something better?
I suppose...
Just a brief stop in Nickytown
and then it's off
to find those Androids.
[KRILLIN] Are you serious?!
[VEGETA] You're saying
he possesses cells
from Kakarot and me?!
We have two choices.
We can either track down
and destroy Cell
or find Androids 17 and 18.
Because if we destroy them,
then Cell cannot absorb them
and reach his final form.
[PICCOLO] I say we go for Cell
since he'll be easier to find.
Whatever we do,
we must do it quickly
because there'll be no stopping
Cell once he is complete.
[gasps]
[VEGETA thinking]
This cannot be happening!
Every time I reach
a new level of strength,
a greater power appears
to challenge my authority!
It's as if fate
is laughing at me
with a big stupid grin,
just like Kakarot!
Look at all the savory people...
[chuckles]
It's a pity I won't
be able to stay too long.
[CELL] Wait for me,
Androids 17 and 18.
I'll be ready
for you soon enough!
[NARRATOR] Terror has
descended upon Nickytown!
Can anything save its citizens
from being sucked away
by Cell's deadly tail?
Next time on Dragon Ball Z!