[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
a group of thugs called
the Red Shark Gang
tried to muscle
their way into town
until a concerned citizen
challenged them!
[JIMBO] We're gonna
make an example o' you!
[SLIMJIM]
Let him have it, Jimbo!
--[VIDEL] Ah!
--[GOHAN] You missed me! Huh?
[CROWD gasping]
Hey, Videl! Huh?
[JIMBO grunts]
[NARRATOR]
But when Gohan got hammered
and the big Boss
had Videl against the ropes,
there was only one hope left!
Hey, you! Back off!
[BOSS]
Huh?
[NARRATOR] The Great Saiyaman
arrived and it was time
to put a halt to the
Red Shark Syndicate's actions!
[GOHAN] Here! I think
this belongs to you!
[NARRATOR] With the
mobsters out of the way
the city was safe once again!
But was Saiyaman
safe from Videl?!
[VIDEL]
Tell me who you are!
[GOHAN] Hm?! All right!
I guess I can trust you!
But please don't ever repeat
what you're about to hear!
I'm the Great Saiyaman!
[NARRATOR]
Look out, Saiyaman!
This is one girl
who won't be satisfied
until she unmasks you!
[GOHAN thinking] That's strange.
The nimbus is here!
I'm here! But where'd Chobi go?
Don't you think it's
strange that he's gone?
He's just a baby!
He can't even fly!
Well, hey, you can't fly either,
but you manage to get around!
Besides, Toeto and his wife
would never let anything happen!
Don't worry!
Chobi's fine, Goten!
Let's go home!
[GOTEN]
I'll beat ya!
[GOHAN]
Oh, no you won't!
[FIGHTER groans]
[MR. SATAN laughs]
[MR. SATAN]
Yeah, heah! Ha, ha, ha!
Now that's a real man!
Incredible! What a guy!
[VIDEL]
Dad?
[MR. SATAN]
Hm? Oh, it's you, Videl!
I'm just reviewing
some of my old matches
and studying stategy!
You can never rest
if you want to stay on top!
[VIDEL] You're a
brilliant fighter, Dad!
You could definitely win
at the tournament again
but I heard that the guy
who won before you
is extremely powerful!
Ah! Your dad knows all about
the former champion!
His name is Goku! And he's
a magician, not a fighter!
Uses all kinds of
light tricks and deception
to win his matches, see!
And he doesn't have
the brute strength
that your father does, Videl!
He's a sissy compared to me!
No one can defeat the man
who saved the world!
No one! Do you
hear me, Goku?!
Ha, ha, ha!
[CHICHI humming]
Hope you two boys are hungry!
Well, not for meatloaf!
[CHICHI]
Goten! Shame on you!
You'll eat what
I put on the table!
[NEWSCASTER]
That's right, folks!
The circus is
in town once again!
And thanks to the promoter,
Mister Musuka,
circus goers have
a different attraction
to cheer about this year!
And there he is!
The baby dinosaur
that's winning the hearts
of circus goers everywhere!
Isn't he cu--
Hey! Chobi! Gohan! It's Chobi!
[NEWSCASTER] The little dinosaur
is said to be responsible
for the record-breaking crowds!
Look, the poor little
guy's scared to death!
You boys know him?!
Yeah! His nest is a
couple miles from here!
We've known
his parents for years!
They're not gonna be
very happy about this!
I can tell you that!
This is really awful, Gohan!
Don't worry!
He'll be fine, Squirt!
I'll see to it personally!
And that's a promise!
Here we go!
[ANNOUNCER] Step right up,
folks! See the baby dinosaur!
The one and only, Rocko!
The most adorable
spectacle on Earth!
[GOHAN thinking]
Poor, Chobi!
He's so scared that he's
trembling! This is terrible!
[CROWD cooing]
[GOHAN]
Excuse me, sir?
[MUSUKA]
Huh?
Hi! My name's Gohan!
I'm a little concerned about
the well-being of your dinosaur!
That's great! Now buzz off!
Look, I know you kidnapped
that little guy!
Please let him go!
You've gotta be kiddin' me!
Don't yous remember how
Jack and the Beanstalk
got the goose that
layed the golden eggs?
He stole her, that's how, kid!
But maybe you're right!
Maybe all circus owners should
be arrested for kidnapping!
[MUSUKA laughs]
It's not funny!
Look, that dinosaur has a
mother and a father and a home!
You can't just
take it, Mister! Huh?
Shut up! Where do yous
think circus owners
get their animals from, kid?!
Do you think
the stork brings 'em?!
It's dollars that matter!
Not sentimental rubbish!
[MUSUKA laughs]
[GOHAN thinking] I hope taking
Chobi is the right thing to do!
Of course it is!
What am I thinking?!
Chobi has the right
to be with his parents
just like that girl does!
Just like all children do!
Oh, boy! Speaking of
Chobi's parents,
they're going to be
boiling mad!
If I don't get Chobi
back to them soon,
we're gonna have a real
disaster on our hands!
I can see it now!
Toeto and his wife
combing the art district
for their kid! Oh, man!
[GOHAN]
Chobi!
[CHOBI]
Hm?
What's up there, little guy?!
It's me! Me! Gohan!
[GOHAN grunts]
Yeah! There we go! Great!
Now, let's get outta here!
Whatd'ya say?!
Hold on, boy!
[STRONG MAN] What do you
think you're doing?!
[GOHAN]
I beg your pardon, sir!
I'm returning him
to his rightful home!
That's what you think!
[GOHAN grunting]
[STRONG MAN groans]
Be careful, sir!
Swinging iron poles
can be dangerous!
Man! Who in the world are you?!
[GOHAN] Let's just say
I'm a friend! See ya, buddy!
[MUSUKA]
Oh, yeah! Hundred n' ten...
Hundred n' twenty...
Hundred n' thirty-- Huh?
[TRAINER]
Mr. Musuka, Rocko's gone!
Someone bent the bars
of his cage and stole him!
[MUSUKA]
What?! I want that thief dead!
[TRAINER]
Yes, sir!
[MUSUKA] Well, what are
yous waitin' for? Let's go!
[CHOBI whimpering, crying]
[GOHAN]
Ah, Chobi, no! I can't see!
[CHOBI]
Ahhhh!
[GOHAN]
Gotcha!
Calm down, Chobi!
You've got me dizzy!
I know! You too, huh?
Let's go down!
Man, Chobi! Stay still!
[GOHAN] You know
what I'm talking about!
Now, come on!
I think we'll stick to
the ground this time!
No offense, but I need to
be able to see to fly!
[sirens blaring]
[GOHAN]
Huh?! Uh, oh!
Looks like we've got company!
There! That's my dinosaur!
Run that guy over!
What?! Why, that's
the Great Saiyaman!
Well, I'll tell ya,
now I've seen everything!
[POLICE 2] Stay where you are!
This is the police!
[GOHAN]
Let's boogie!
[CHOBI yelps]
Huh?
[TRUCKER screams]
[GOHAN]
Uh...
[GOHAN] Good! No one's hurt!
This is our chance!
[VIDEL]
Stop, thief! It's all over!
Well, well! Look who it is!
[GOHAN thinking]
Oh no, Videl! This isn't good!
[VIDEL]
It didn't take long for you
to reveal your true colors,
did it, Mr. Saiyaman?!
You should be ashamed!
It's not what it seems!
You're going to have
to believe me, Videl!
If I don't return this guy
to his rightful home,
the people of this city are
going to be in grave danger!
And that's the truth!
[VIDEL]
What do you know about truth?!
You're just a common thief!
Now, give that dinosaur
back or else I'll have to
take him back
by force, Mr. Saiyaman!
Have it your way!
Let's see what you're
really made of, big guy!
I mean, Great Saiyaman!
[VIDEL laughs]
Come on, you idiots!
He's right there!
I don't pay
my taxes for nothin'!
Apprehend that thief!
Please, sir! Wait!
That girl has more power
than all of us combined!
Yous gotta be kiddin'!
[POLICE 1]
No, sir! Her name's Videl!
Mr. Satan's daughter!
You bonehead!
Why didn't you say so?!
Yeah! It's her all right!
Now there's someone
who knows how to catch a thief!
My tax-dollars
should be goin' to her
instead o' you
donut-packin' monkeys!
[POLICE 2]
Please! Stand back! Everyone!
Please! Stand back!
[GOHAN] Please! You know that
I'm a law-abiding citizen!
But this is a
special case! I swear!
[VIDEL]
Oh, I get it!
You hold yourself
above the law! Is that it?!
You obey the law
when it's convenient,
and then when
you wanna break it,
you just call it a special case!
Well you can tell your special
case to the judge, Mister!
I go by the book!
[VIDEL grunts]
[CHOBI whimpers]
[GOHAN grunts]
[GOHAN yelps]
[CHOBI screams]
Serves you right! What a hero!
You know, I'm glad
you finally decided
to show your true colors!
Because, to be honest,
I wanted to kick your butt
ever since I met you!
Gosh, you're mean! Wow!
Don't mock me, you little freak!
[VIDEL yells]
[GOHAN yelps]
[VIDEL]
Mmm!
[VIDEL growls]
[VIDEL yells]
[GOHAN, VIDEL grunting]
[GOHAN thinking]
Oh, man! How can I end this
without embarrassing her
in front of all these people?!
Pardon me, Miss!
You'll regret that!
[GOHAN, VIDEL grunting]
This is my chance!
[MUSUKA]
Gotcha!
How dare yous, you little twerp!
[CHOBI whimpering]
Huh?
The dinosaur is with
it's rightful owner now,
you kidnapper! So there!
Please! Listen!
Tell it to your lawyer, pal!
Look, if we don't
return that baby
to its father and mother,
they're gonna come
looking for him,
and it's not going to be pretty!
You have to believe me!
I believe that you're
trying to cover your tracks!
That's what I believe!
What's your deal?! My gosh!
[CHOBI whimpers]
[VIDEL grunts]
[GOHAN, VIDEL grunt]
[VIDEL]
Come on, jerk!
Let's go! Hey!
Guess what's gonna happen
when they arrest you?!
The first thing they'll do
is take that trash can
off your head and
reveal your true identity!
[CHOBI yelping, crying]
[VIDEL]
Huh?
[CHOBI crying]
Oh, no!
[VIDEL]
What's he doing?!
[GOHAN]
He's calling his parents!
[CHOBI crying]
[MUSUKA]
Quiet, you little monster!
Yous hurtin' my ears!
Yikes! Here we go!
[CROWD screaming]
[SMALL GROUP OF PEOPLE]
Oh, my gosh! They're huge!
[POLICE 2] Clear the area!
Get away from the road!
This street is now
a restricted area!
Open fire!
[POLICE 2]
Hold your line, men!
Don't shoot!
They're just trying to
get their baby back!
You'd do the same thing
if you were them!
See! It's them! Chobi's parents!
They stole him from them!
The circus people came
and robbed their nest!
They want Chobi back!
They're... huge...
Miss Videl! This family
needs our help!
Right! I understand now!
[GOHAN grunts]
[VIDEL]
Hold your fire! Don't shoot!
[POLICEMEN]
Huh?
[VIDEL] Come here,
little guy! It's okay!
You should be ashamed!
Hold on, Toeto! Please!
Chobi is safe now! We want
to give him back to you!
I'm sorry that this
happened, old friends!
Saiyaman! Dinosaurs don't
understand English!
I'm well aware of that,
Miss Videl!
You're very smart! But I've
known these creatures
since I was
a baby myself, see?!
I can't show them who I am,
but they might
recognize my voice!
[VIDEL]
Just show 'em who you are,
I won't tell anybody!
[GOHAN gasps]
[CHOBI whimpering]
[GOHAN]
Look out!
[VIDEL yelps]
Toeto! Please, stop!
I'm your friend! It's Go--
Huh?!
What?! What's up?!
[VIDEL] You know what's up!
Don't act dumb!
You said "Go,"
didn't you?! Go-what?!
That's what I wanna know!
Please! Let go!
There's no time for this!
Sure there is!
It'll only take a second!
Just tell me your name!
It's Gohan! Isn't it?!
Just say it already!
Please, Miss! Here he comes!
Toeto!
[MUSUKA]
Gimme that, you idiot!
Hey! Come back here!
What do you
think you're doing?!
[MUSUKA]
All o' yous, freeze!
Now, gimme back my dinosaur
or I'll blow you away!
I found him! He's mine!
Don't shoot!
[MUSUKA]
Why yous!
Ah!
[GOHAN gasps]
[MUSUKA grunts]
[TOETO shrieks]
[VIDEL screams]
Toeto! Not her! Please!
[TOETO growls]
[VIDEL screams]
Toeto! Don't do it!
[GOHAN grunts]
Don't worry about
your dad, little guy!
He'll be just fine!
Wait and see!
Listen to how precious
he is! Saiyaman I-I, uh...
Goodbye, Miss! I hope
we'll meet again soon!
Bye!
[VIDEL]
Good-bye!
[GOHAN]
Hello there! Special delivery!
Now that was an adventure!
You're a heck of alot braver
than I was at your age, Chobi!
You should be very
proud of him, Ma'am!
[VIDEL]
What a guy!
[MUSUKA] Hey! I know
where their nest is!
I'll be back! Yous hear?!
[VIDEL]
Why don't you think it over
in jail for a few days?! Hm!
What? Jail?
Takin' a dinosaur's no crime,
but steal'n an
officer's handgun is.
[POLICEMAN 1 laughs]
[VIDEL laughs]
[VIDEL thinking]
Saiyaman...
[GOHAN] All right!
That's the way it should be!
One big, happy family!
Yay! Chobi's back!
All right! Ha, ha, ha!
[GOTEN laughing]
[GOTEN]
Welcome back, Chobi!
[GOTEN laughing]
Gohan! You're the greatest!
[GOHAN laughs]
[class tune chimes]
[GOHAN]
Oh, man! Late again!
[VIDEL]
Hey! Good morning, Gohan!
[GOHAN]
Oh! Hey there, Videl!
You're late too, huh? Uh--
Gohan! It's over!
Whatd'ya mean!
Class is just
now starting, Videl!
--[VIDEL] Forget class!
--[GOHAN] Huh?!
[VIDEL]
Hold still! There!
My gosh, isn't
that funny?! Yeah!
I saw Saiyaman get
scratched in the same spot!
And that's exactly who
you are! Mr. Saiyaman!
Yikes! Busted!
I can't believe it!
The secret identity of
Saiyaman is public knowledge!
[GOHAN] Guardian of the city!
I am the Great Saiyaman!
I wouldn't exactly say that
it was public knowledge!
Only I know!
But I do think the public
has a right to know!
Maybe I should schedule
a press conference!
No, please! Don't!
You know the only reason
I keep my identity secret
is to protect my family's
privacy! It's for them!
Please, Videl!
Is that true?!
Yes, of course!
Hey! You're the
Golden Fighter as well!
Aren't you?!
No! Just Saiyaman!
Why should I believe you?!
That guy has blonde hair!
[VIDEL]
You're right about that!
He's more handsome
than you are, too!
I guess I believe you!
Yeah! I do!
Videl, Is there
any way you could
keep my secret between us?
Maybe. But you have to do
something for me in return.
Okay, here's the deal!
If you enter the
World Martial Arts Tournament,
I'll keep your secret!
How's that?
Me? Compete in the Tournament?
That's right! I'm gonna
be competing myself,
but winning the
World Championship
won't mean anything to me,
unless I know that
all of the best fighters in
the country are participating!
My dad was the last
champion and he told me
that a guy named Goku
won the one before that.
Strangely enough,
I did some research
on this Goku fellow
and found out that
he has a son named Gohan.
Then I put two and two together
and realized you're his son!
I'm right about that,
aren't I? Well?
Uhh, no!
I knew it! You're a
terrible liar, Gohan.
You're Goku's son! It's
written all over your face!
Wow! This is gonna be great!
What a terrific match!
The former champion's daughter
fighting the
former champion's son!
Doesn't that sound
exciting to you?
No, not really.
Why don't we do something
really challenging
like go out on a date!
Look, if you're too
chicken to fight me,
then you don't have to compete!
But I'm going to
tell everyone your secret!
What?! You'd do that?!
[VIDEL] Yeah, sure.
The truth is the truth, right?
Your family can adapt
to being in the limelight
just like mine did.
You wouldn't really!
Just try me!
Oh, all right then.
I'll compete in the tournament.
Cheer up! This is
gonna be a blast!
You just wait and see!
It's gonna be a heck of
a lot better than going out
on a silly ol' date,
that's for sure!
Oh, and there's
one more condition!
[GOHAN]
Huh?
It's no big deal!
I just wanna learn
how to fly, that's all!
That shouldn't be too hard
to teach me, should it?
No, it's a cinch.
Great! Well, we'll get
started right away!
See you later!
[GOHAN groans] Blackmailed
again! How do I do it?
[NARRATOR] It looks like
Gohan has gotten himself
into a pickle once again!
Stay tuned for scenes from the
next episode of Dragon Ball Z!