[NARRATOR] Last time,
on Dragon Ball Z!
Fine, here we go...
The rivers,
the trees, the wind...
And all the living
things in nature...
I ask of you...
Please offer me the power
of your
fighting spirit!
[NARRATOR] Goku called
upon the forces of nature
to help him form the only
weapon capable of stopping
the rampaging Vegeta...
The Spirit Bomb.
But before Goku could
deliver the finishing blow,
Vegeta unleashed a
devastating counterattack
that brought our
hero to his knees.
Without the
Spirit Bomb,
Goku had little chance of
defeating the monstrous Vegeta.
But even though all
hope seemed lost,
Goku was determined to
fight to the bitter end.
I have no more power to defend
myself against this monster.
I hope it buys
me more time.
[APE VEGETA growling]
Damn yooouuu!
[NARRATOR] Having exhausted
the last of his strength,
Goku's life is in the hands
of the merciless Vegeta.
And the evil Saiyan
will not be satisfied
until he has squeezed
every last breath
from our hero's body.
Will this be the end for Goku?
The pressure's on...
Today on
Dragon Ball Z!
We're almost
there, Gohan.
Hang on, Dad!
[GOKU screaming]
[YAJIROBE]
Man, that's awful...
I want to help... I mean
I would, it's just...
Against that monster,
what could I do?
[screaming continues]
Sorry about this, Goku,
but you know how it is...
I gotta look out
for number one!
I hope you won't
take it personally.
[APE VEGETA laughing]
I'm going to crush
your puny bones!
[GOKU'S bones breaking]
[GOKU screaming louder]
[YARJIROBE whimpering]
Look, there!
It's just up ahead.
[GOHAN] The sky is so bright,
Krillin... What's going on?
I wish I knew. But
whatever that weird light is,
it's not natural,
that's for sure...
I've got a bad
feeling about this...
Huh?!
What in the
world... is that?!
[APE GOKU roaring]
Aagh!
Gohan! Wait! We better
not go near that thing!
But, what about Dad?
Let's go down
here and hide!
Who is that?
[thinking] He's transformed
into a giant ape...
Just like
Goku used to do!
[GOKU screaming]
[APE VEGETA] What's wrong,
Kakarot?
You don't look like
you're in enough pain...
Have some more!
Goku's in pretty
bad shape. Come on!
We have to
move fast!
[GOHAN] Right!
[YAJIROBE] Stop!
Yajirobe!
Hey! What are
you thinking?
Do you know how strong
that monster is? Do you?
[KRILLIN] We've
gotta help Goku!
And how exactly are you
planning to do that?
It's suicide!
We've got
one chance...
If we cut off his tail,
he'll turn back to normal.
His tail?
But how?
You two go out there
and get his attention,
while I sneak up behind him...
I only need a few seconds.
I know it's risky, but unless
you have any better ideas,
it's our
only choice.
Hurry!
Or Goku's toast!
Let's go!
Give me a break. You two want
me to get his attention?
And what if he does
turn small again?
Face it you guys,
he's still gonna be
way too strong for
us to beat him.
[thinking] Hold on, Dad.
We're coming!
[thinking] Goku has no power.
We've got to hurry.
If we don't move fast,
he could die any second!
Ah, do whatever you want.
I'm out of here.
Somebody's coming...
Who is it?
[APE VEGETA] Show yourself!
I know you're out there!
Where are you?
[GOHAN] Right here!
You put my Dad
down, right now!
Oh, no! It's you!
Please, don't hurt me!
I'll do anything
you say!
I'll put your father
down if you want,
It might be one
piece at a time,
but I'll definitely
put him down!
[APE VEGETA laughing]
Now which piece
would you like first?
[GOHAN] You better
not hurt him!
[APE VEGETA] It's a little
too late for that.
Destructo Disk!
Yeah...
This'll work!
[birds twittering]
Say goodbye to
your father...
You should be
proud of him!
It's rare I have to
transform to win a battle!
[thinking]
Krillin... Hurry!
What a waste!
It's a shame that the two of us
just couldn't see eye to eye!
Hyaah!
Yaargh!
Waaugh!
[KRILLIN] Oh, man!
How did he know?
Did you really think you could
sneak up on me, little man?
Did you really think
that you could fool me
with such a
simple ruse?
Like I'd believe for a
second that Kakarot's son
came back to
face me all alone.
Ha! I knew from
the instant I saw him
that he was merely trying
to distract me from
the real threat.
You'll have to do
better next time.
Except, there won't
be a next time...
You're finished...
As soon as I'm done
squeezing the life from
Kakarot, you're next.
[thinking] Darn it! I really
messed things up big time.
He anticipated us
every step of the way!
I'm sorry, Goku. We tried. But
he's just too strong for us!
I don't know what
else we can do!
[APE VEGETA laughing]
Take a good look!
This is what you have
to look forward to
once I get my
hands on you!
[KRILLIN] No! We can't
let him do this! Goku!
No... Dad, no!
Stop it! Let go!
I said stop it!
[APE VEGETA chuckling]
Sorry, kid. But
you're in no position
to be giving
me orders...
Oh, no. Gohan!
Oh? Ha, ha, ha! No more orders?
What about last requests?
[APE VEGETA laughing]
[APE VEGETA grunting]
[APE VEGETA growling]
Impossible! Who did this to
me? Where did he come from?
You fools! You don't
know what you've done!
[APE VEGETA groaning]
[groaning continuing]
[VEGETA panting]
[KRILLIN] Yajirobe?!
He... did it!
I must be out
of my mind!
I couldn't have picked a worse
time to decide to be brave!
Yeah, alright!
He's gone back to normal!
[GOHAN whimpering]
[VEGETA] Those little pests...
[VEGETA] How could
I be so careless?
[KRILLIN] He never
even saw it coming!
Wow! Who woulda' thought
Yajirobe had it in him!
[thinking] All right. I've
done my good deed for the day.
They can take it
from here.
You're all...
going to... pay!
[KRILLIN whimpering]
You've disgraced me for
the first and final time.
I thought cutting his
tail would stop him...
It just made
him angrier!
You're going to know a new
meaning for the word pain!
You will all suffer!
[YAJIROBE whimpering]
[VEGETA chuckling]
Hrrgh!
Gohan!
Get out of there!
[GOHAN whimpering]
What's wrong?
You seem scared.
Ooh... auugh...
A brave Saiyan like yourself
shouldn't be scared,
it's not becoming!
I guess those powers of yours
are taking a nap. Pity.
Patience, little man.
You'll get your turn.
Oh, man! Great!
We're all doomed!
[VEGETA laughing]
Up, you brat. Get up!
I'm not through with
you just yet...
Come on, boy! Defend yourself!
I thought you were a Saiyan!
So fight me! Show me
what you're made of!
[GOHAN screaming]
You're low-class scum,
just like your father.
[OX KING] Oh, no, look!
He's got Gohan!
I can't...
How could anyone be
so cruel to a child?!
[OX KING] ChiChi?
Are you all right?
Oh, wow... It looks
like she clocked out.
She's just scared. I don't
blame her... Poor thing.
[OOLONG] ChiChi, snap out of it!
Can you hear me?
It's me, Oolong!
[OOLONG grunting]
Ow! That hurts!
[CHICHI] Fight...
Huh?
Fight him, Gohan.
Oh?
Huh?
Uhh...
Fight, fight,
fight, Gohan!
Fight! Don't let him beat
you and your father!
You can do it! Get him!
Fight with everything you have!
Fight! Go for it! Fight!
[BULMA] Look out!
[GOHAN yelling]
I think it's time
I threw you out
with the rest of the trash!
You're all used up!
[VEGETA laughing]
Gohan...
It's Dad...
[VEGETA] Well, Kakarot's
awake again...
He just doesn't know
when to quit, does he?
Gohan, please don't give up.
Listen, my body is shredded.
I can't use it anymore,
so you're going to have
to fight for both of us!
He's got to be hurting
pretty bad, too...
We can't give in!
This is our only chance!
Please, Gohan!
Dad, I don't think
I can do it!
He's just too strong for me!
I'm scared of him!
I hate to say
I told you so...
But you really should
have joined me, Kakarot!
Now, it's too late!
You had your chance!
Now you, your son, and the
bald guy... you're history!
And let's not forget
about the sneaking coward
who cut my tail!
[YAJIROBE whimpering]
Son, don't be
scared of him..
Hey, you're a lot
stronger than you think...
Piccolo trained
you very well.
You have to have faith
in him... You can win!
And look!
You're not alone.
You still have Krillin
to lend you a hand.
I can't move. I don't
think I can do it, Dad!
Yes, you can! I know
it, and so did Piccolo!
He believed in you! That's why
he gave his life to save yours!
[PICCOLO screaming]
I believe in
you, too, son.
Haah!
Waugh!
[VEGETA laughing]
Being a good fiend is like
being a photographer...
You have to wait
for the right moment.
Go-Gohan...
[VEGETA laughing]
[VEGETA] Sorry! Father-son
time is over!
No... Dad, no...
[GOKU screaming]
No... Stop...
[VEGETA laughing]
I said STOP!
Huh?!
You heard me!
Let's go!
Sure, kid.
Why not? I'm game.
[GOHAN growling]
Rrgh!
Little punk!
Krillin, come here, quick...
Gohan needs our help...
Well, there's more to
this kid than I thought...
[KRILIN] I'm sorry, Goku,
but in my condition,
I'm not sure
I can help him.
I wouldn't last a
minute up there!
Right. You don't
have to fight...
It's just a one shot
deal... Come closer.
I have some energy that
I need to give you.
[KRILLIN] Ah, no offense, Goku,
but you don't look like you
have any energy to spare!
I know, but
it's not mine.
I gathered a bunch of energy
earlier, from the Earth.
Most of it got away
but I have a little...
It should be enough to stop him
if you can hit him with it.
Yeah... If...
All right... Let's do
it... Take my hand...
But are you sure
I can handle it?
Yes! You have to!
Well, let's hope
you're right...
Grab hold!
Gotcha...
Rrgh!
Hey, I don't feel
anything, Goku!
You will. Just give
me a few seconds.
Okay! Now relax!
Oh, wow.
That's a lot of power!
Man! Hey, Goku! What...
What do I do with this thing?
First, turn
your palm up.
Then use your will power
to concentrate the energy
and form it
into a ball!
[VEGETA growling]
You little brat!
Uwaah!
Clear your
mind, Krillin...
Don't try to force the energy.
Just let it flow through you...
Wow, I did it!
Um... what'd I do?
It's a Spirit Bomb.
King Kai taught me...
That kid hurt me!
Listen... You can do
this. I know it...
But, you have to
be very careful.
We... We only get one shot
at this. Make it count!
Right. Got it!
I'll do my best.
[NARRATOR] A glimmer of hope
has returned to the battlefield.
With the
Spirit Bomb,
Krillin and Gohan now
have one final chance
to defeat the evil Vegeta.
Can they succeed?
Find out next time
on Dragon Ball Z!