[NARRATOR]
On the last Dragon Ball Z,
Gohan and Cell threw
all their remaining power
into a titanic showdown!
Both fighters struggled,
unable to secure the upper hand.
But in a most unexpected move,
Vegeta jumped to the
young warrior's aide,
distracting Cell
long enough for Gohan
to unleash his
deepest, final power.
[NARRATOR]
A power that eradicated
every trace of the genetically
engineered monster,
down to his wicked core!
Dr. Gero's hateful creation,
after crossing through
space and time
to torment the planet,
has finally been destroyed,
but the cost of
victory was high.
Now, can our heroes
clean up the damage
Cell has left in his wake?
Find out today,
on Dragon Ball Z!
[PICCOLO]
Heh. Look at him.
Guess saving the world
can take it's toll on you.
[KRILLIN] Hey, Gohan.
Let me ask you something.
Were you holding back
your power all that time
just to scare us?
'Cause, boy, it worked.
[GOHAN laughs]
[YAMCHA] Gosh, you guys! I can't
believe we survived that!
[TIEN]
I know.
[KRILLIN] And don't worry
about those bruises, Gohan!
We'll get Dende
to fix you right up!
You'll feel like
a zillion bucks!
[GOHAN laughs]
I gotcha, big guy.
Sorry for the mess.
Gohan!
Don't worry, Krillin.
He's just exhausted, that's all.
What about you, Yamcha? You have
a lot of wounds yourself.
You sure you can fly
as far as the Lookout?
Sure. Compared to Gohan's,
these are nothing but scrapes.
All right, then.
I'll carry Trunks
and follow you, just to
be safe. See ya there.
[KRILLIN] Great!
And, uh, I'll just grab 18!
Well, she is
a victim of Cell,
and, uh, we might as
well bring her along.
[YAMCHA]
Let's hit the sky, Piccolo!
[PICCOLO]
You guys go on.
[YAMCHA]
Oh, right.
That was brave, what you did.
You can save your applause.
Now, go on.
I don't need anybody's help.
Your call.
[VEGETA]
He has beaten me completely.
First, by his own actions.
And then, through his son's. And
what has he left for me here?
How? How could you die
like that? How, Kakarot?
I'll... never...
have the chance...
...to prove my
strength against you!
You died without fear.
What does that make of me?
[VEGETA] I am no warrior,
and I will never fight again.
[MR. SATAN screams]
Where did that canyon come from?
[ANNOUNCER groans]
[MR. SATAN gasps]
It's, so quiet.
[ANNOUNCER] Mr. Satan! What on
this crazy Earth just happened?
What? Well, I, uh...
I do remember Cell
and that little boy
shooting strange
light at each other
and later the ground
started shaking.
I was pretty sure the whole
world had ended after that.
That's funny.
It didn't phase me!
[ANNOUNCER] So where's Cell? Did
you see what happened to him?
Uh, oh. well...
what if I said that...
...I defeated Cell
single-handedly?!
You believe me?
[CAMERAMAN] Hey, some of the
equipment's still running!
[PIIZA] Wow, Hercule! You really
are a great, great man!
You hid your strength
right until the end.
You sure know how to give
people a good show!
So is it true
you really beat him?
Sure, why wouldn't it be?
But, just how did you do it?
Well, piece of cake, really!
I just got so irritated
with the light shows
and the tricks I shouted:
"Hey! I've had enough of your
light shows and tricks!"
And I just walked over there to
Cell and I gave him a good chop!
Chop, yeah!
Oh, Hercule!
But, then what h-happened
to the little boy
and all of his
friends on the cliff?!
Chop! Yeah.
Well, they all thanked me kindly
and went home, of course!
[CAMERAMAN] Hey, guys,
the radio in the relay car
is still working!
Great, now are you
absolutely positive
everything you said is true?
What do you mean, is it true?
Have you totally forgotten
that I am the greatest Martial
Arts Champion of the World?
[ANNOUNCER]
So much to do! So much to do!
[PIIZA]
That's right!
We should be thanking him and
loving him for what he did!
Got it?!
[MR. SATAN laughs]
[ANNOUNCER] Ladies and
gentlemen across the globe!
We apologize for the
break in communication,
but we are now back on line
and with incredible news!
Cell has been defeated!
Yes, the monster has fallen at
the hands of Mr. Satan himself!
All thanks to our
hero, Hercule Satan!
Mr. Satan's the coolest!
Hey, we're alive!
I don't believe
that for a second.
A real hero must have come
to save us again, like Goku.
[CHICHI] It's not fair! They
deserve to know what Gohan did!
I know.
[KING KAI] Guess the Earth
should be happy for a while.
[GOKU]
Yeah! And you helped a lot,
even if it wasn't
your own choice!
[stomach growls]
[GOKU laughs]
Now that I've stopped
worrying, I'm really hungry!
Hey, King Kai, you wouldn't
happen to have any food?
Are you crazy?!
You destroyed my house,
my car, and my entire planet!
How could I possibly have food?!
Oh yeah. But, I have to eat!
I'm starving to death!
But you're already dead.
[GOKU] Well,
that makes it twice as bad!
I guess I could eat these.
[KING KAI] You know, I've
heard of light tasting food,
but this is ridiculous!
[GOKU]
Mm! Fluffy!
Are they here?
[KORIN]
Mm-hm.
Yeah! Way to win
one for the team!
[KRILLIN]
Yarjirobe?
[YAJIROBI] Yeah, I was on
my way to meet you guys,
but my plane broke down.
I really wanted to help!
[YAMCHA]
Ah, such bad luck.
Funny, it always happens to you.
[DENDE]
Gohan!
[YAMCHA] Hey, little guy.
You must be Dende.
[DENDE] Yes, please set
him down right here.
[YAMCHA]
You bet.
Gohan! Hey!
--[GOHAN] Dende!
--Alright!
I mean, I'm really sorry
about your father, Gohan.
[GOHAN]
Don't be sad. He's not.
He told me himself!
When I talked to him!
I felt his energy
all around me
and I swear, for a moment
I could've touched him!
He was right there
with me, by my side,
giving me advice,
and rooting me on!
That's how I was
able to beat Cell!
My dad helped me!
[PICCOLO]
Well, Gohan.
Whatever it was,
you made us all proud.
You sure have
gotten strong, kid.
Awake at last.
[YAMCHA]
Dende! Get away from her, quick!
She'll punch a hole
right through you!
[KRILLIN]
Nobody's gonna kill anybody!
Hey! We can put the past
behind us, can't we?
Now that Gohan's beat Cell,
we can all be friends!
Gohan did?
[YAMCHA]
You bet he did!
Gohan's incredibly strong!
So you can forget about
punching holes in anyone!
[TIEN] Why don't you
come a little closer?
You should thank Krillin, 18.
He stayed at your side the whole
time after Cell spat you out.
Uh well, it was nothing really,
I-I mean I enjoyed it, I mean!
I couldn't leave you there.
I got it!
Krillin, you have a crush
on Android 18, don't you?
Thanks, Mr. Smooth.
What? How could you?
Krillin she's a...
You know she's an
android, right, pal?
Expect me to fall
at your feet now?
Big strong boy rescues me,
so I'm his forever, right?
Not that easy!
I was wrong about you, Krillin.
But... I...
That ungrateful--!
I can't stand that android!
I'm gonna show her!
I'm not so sure
you could do that.
We've wasted enough time here.
Let's hurry up and summon
the dragon so we can start
undoing all the damage
that Cell has done.
Yes, of course.
Yeah! That means Trunks'll
come back! And Dende and me.
You'll have plenty
of friends here,
so you won't
even need a girl!
Leave me alone.
Eternal Dragon, by your
name I summon you forth.
Shenron!
Amazing! What the heck is that?
[YAMCHA] I'll never get
tired of seeing him.
[TIEN]
Tell me about it.
Fabulous work, Dende!
The new Dragon you've
made looks flawless!
Thanks, Mr. Popo!
Choose your words
carefully as you speak.
I will make two
of your wishes true.
Oh wow! It worked!
Dende made it so that the Earth
Dragon will grant us two wishes!
[YAMCHA]
Shenron!
Please revive all those on
Earth who were killed by Cell!
Your wish will be granted.
[MR. SATAN]
Yeah! Yeah!
Hey! Hey, I think you're
gonna wanna here this.
What? For real?
Hey, folks! We've got news!
It seems all the people Cell
killed are somehow waking up!
A miracle!
It's because
Mr. Satan beat Cell!
He's saved us all!
Who loves me? Yeah!
[ANDROID 18]
Is this really happening?
As I feared.
Since Dende created
a new Earth dragon
I was hoping Goku
could be revived.
But this dragon was made from
the same model as the old one,
so their powers must be linked.
I don't sense Goku's energy.
It's a shame.
[DRAGON]
What is your second wish?
I am waiting for it.
Listen! Can't you use our whole
second wish to revive Goku?
All of us really
want him to come back.
How badly you want it
makes no difference to me.
Goku has been revived before
and so it is impossible.
[YAMCHA]
It looks pretty hopeless.
[TIEN] No! There has to
be a way! Just think!
What if we ask him
to turn back time
to just before Goku died?
Then we could prevent
it from happening!
[YAMCHA]
Great idea! Let's do it!
[PICCOLO]
Would you think for a minute?
That would make Cell alive, too!
It would be an endless cycle!
[DENDE]
I have an idea!
All we have to do is ask
Porunga back on Namek!
Dende's right. Because Porunga
is the original dragon,
he can revive a person as
many times as he sees fit.
Oh, of course! That's how
Krillin and Chiaotzu
came back to life!
All we have to do now
is get ourselves to Namek!
Then we all agree, right?
That'll be our second wish!
[GOKU] Hey, don't I
get a say in this?
[GOKU]
Hi, everybody! It's me!
[KRILLIN]
G-Goku?
[GOHAN]
See! I told you guys!
[GOKU] King Kai's letting
me talk to you
from here in the
Other World, so listen up!
Lately I've been thinking about
why the Earth is
always in danger,
and I realized that
most of the guys
who attacked it were after me!
Think about it!
Frieza, Cell, the androids.
[TIEN]
It's an interesting point.
I guess, but where
is he going with this?
[GOKU] Well, I think
it would be better
for the Earth if I didn't
come back this time.
King Kai agrees with me.
Sort of.
As a Saiyan baby I was sent
to Earth to destroy it.
And though all my life,
I've tried to do the opposite,
it's kinda like I've been ful-
filling that mission all along.
So yeah, I'm gonna
stay here now.
I really don't mind.
King Kai says I can get
special treatment 'cause
I saved the Earth and all.
I'll be able to keep my body,
and from what I hear,
there's lots of
interesting people to meet!
It'll be a fun!
Another adventure.
[GOKU] King Kai could ask one
of the Dragons to revive him,
but he's agreed to
show me around here
for a while and keep me company.
I guess what I'm
trying to say is,
I really appreciate your
feelings towards me,
but you'll have to find
something else to wish for.
This is my home now.
Gohan's so strong now--
I've nothing left to teach him!
But that doesn't mean
I don't need you!
[GOKU] You all better take
notes of everything
that happens in your life.
'Cause when they're through,
I'll wanna hear all about them!
Until then, bye!
Goku...
Y'know, even though
he was saying goodbye,
it didn't make me too sad
because he was so
cheery about it.
Yeah, well Goku's been that
way ever since he was little.
[YAMCHA] It's like
nothing ever got to him.
He's always had that
goofy smile on his face.
Guess that's just him.
Yeah, you're right.
And with each new adventure,
we're always left behind.
[PICCOLO] Goku has and
always will be Goku.
He gave me a Senzu Bean when
I was trying to kill him.
Even with a villain like me,
he always assumed the best.
Nothing can take
that from him.
Dad, I know what I'll
remember about you.
I'll remember when we
were up against Frieza
and knew we couldn't win, how
you just walked right up to him.
And whenever things
seem tough for me,
I think of you walking
forward like that,
and it makes me strong.
[GOHAN]
You've given us so much, Dad.
Thank you for it all.
Excuse me.
[NARRATOR] So Goku has decided
to remain in the Other World.
But he will stay
alive in the hearts
of Gohan and of us all.
Listen, you have one more
wish for me to grant.
I'm waiting...