[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Bulma made a shocking discovery.
The maniacal Android
20 is none other
than Dr. Gero himself.
And he's not about to
surrender without a fight.
In a final desperate
attempt to escape,
the diabolical doctor unleashed
a powerful energy blast
that sent Bulma
into a tailspin!
[BULMA screams]
NARRATOR] Much to the relief
of Tien, Gohan, and Krillin,
however, Trunks, the
boy from the future,
was on the scene to
perform a daring rescue.
--[BABY TRUNKS cries]
--[BULMA] Wow! I'm still alive!
--Ah! Where's my baby?!
[NARRATOR] But unlike Bulma,
Vegeta was none too happy
to see Trunks again,
for it seemed
that the young
Saiyan's predictions
had been less than accurate.
[TRUNKS] The timeline as I
know it must have shifted!
[NARRATOR] Vegeta flew off
to challenge the androids
on his own, but Trunks was
determined to stop him.
For although history may
have been slightly altered,
terrible dangers
still lie lay ahead!
[PICCOLO] We're really
going to have to move fast!
[TIEN] Right!
[NARRATOR] Dr. Gero
races to his laboratory
to activate the fearsome
Androids 17 and 18.
And unless our
heroes can stop him,
it could mean the
end of the world.
[TRUNKS thinking]
I can't believe my father
is so stubborn and
self-centered!
If that's the case, then we
might just have a chance
to find this lab and destroy
the other two androids
before Gero even gets there!
I would never do
something that cowardly!
[TRUNKS gasps]
Only one course of action
can possibly satisfy me!
I will fight these
androids face-to-face!
And I will break them
with my bare hands!
You must never
underestimate the power
of the androids!
If you really want
to destroy them,
we have to do this
Piccolo's way!
[VEGETA chuckles]
[thinking]
Unless I can stop him,
his arrogance is going
to get him killed!
[thinking] Don't these
fools understand?
I am one of the Saiyan elite!
And now that I'm a Super Saiyan,
my powers are second to none!
Hmph! "Wait for
Kakarot" indeed!
I will grind these
Androids into dust!
[ANDROID 19 giggles]
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU growls]
[ANDROID 20 yells]
[ANDROID 20 grunts]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU yells]
[ANDROID 20 laughs]
[GOKU gasps]
[ANDROID 20] You
cannot win, Saiyan.
Your destiny has been written.
This world is mine!
[DR. GERO chuckles]
[glass shatters]
[GOKU gasps]
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU thinking] What's going
on?! I've never seen anyone
or any-thing quite
like him before!
[BLOB roars]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU screams]
[CHICHI] Goku...
[CHICHI] Goku!
[screaming continues]
Goku! Wake up! You
were having a nightmare!
--[GOKU screams]
--[YAMCHA] C'mon, Goku!
Hang in there! You've
got to fight the pain!
[CHICHI] Goku!
You've got to hold
on a little longer...
You've just got to... Goku!
Don't worry. Everything
is alright now...
[YAMCHA growls]
Please, Goku! You can't
give up now! You can't!
[GOKU whimpers]
[PICCOLO] Tien!
Can you see it yet?!
[TIEN] Not yet, but we
should be getting really close!
There!
[PICCOLO] Yes!
That's it all right!
North City...
So which one of
these mountains looks
like the best place to
put a lab to you guys?
[VEGETA] Would you
stop following me, boy?!
You're getting on my nerves!
[TRUNKS] Sorry, but there's
no way I'm going to let you
fight the Androids on your own!
And just what are you
planning to do to stop me?
It's going to take more than
that little sword of yours
to stand in my way!
How many times
do I have to tell you
before it sinks into
your thick skull?!
Never underestimate the
power of the androids!
Ha! And never underestimate
a true Super Saiyan
who loves taking
on a challenge.
Well, if you're
going to stay,
you can at least help
me find Dr. Gero's lab!
[TRUNKS growls]
You are
totally impossible!
Could you
hurry up, Gohan?
My arms are getting tired!
Really! Would you stop
your belly-aching already?!
You're just along for the ride!
It's poor Gohan who's
doing all the work!
It's okay, Bulma...
I'm just sick of
Yajirobe's whining!
Trunks, when you grow up,
I hope you turn out to
be just like Gohan!
[BABY TRUNKS giggles]
[GOHAN] Well, you don't
have to worry about him!
From what I've seen, I'd say the
grown-up Trunks is pretty cool!
[BULMA] You're right!
He is cool, isn't he?
He's not that cool...
What'd you say?!
--[YAJIROBE &amp; GOHAN gasp]
--[BULMA] How dare you
say something like
that about my son?!
[GOHAN] I'm losing
control, Bulma!
[BULMA] What're you
saying?! It's my fault?!
[ALL scream]
[grunting]
Gee whiz, Bulma,
do you think you could
freak out any more?
What?!
Well, we'll just tell
Daddy about him!
No, don't! Not Vegeta!
Please! I take it back!
[GOHAN] Heh, heh!
Watch out, Yajirobe!
Little Trunks is going to
be pretty tough himself
one of these days!
He may come after
you if he hears
you were giving his
mom a hard time!
[YAJIROBE] Yeah! I'd
like to see him try...
[BULMA] Oooh, that does it!
I'm going to tell Vegeta
exactly how mean
you're being to his son!
[YAJIROBE whimpers]
No, you can't tell!
I'll do anything!
[GOHAN] What do you have against
Trunks anyway, Yajirobe?
He's the one who warned
us about the Androids,
and he may have
saved my dad's life
by bringing him that
medicine from the future!
[YAJIROBE] Well, I... uh... I--
[BULMA] That's right!
My Trunks is a good boy!
Yes you are!
I just hope that medicine really
works like he said it would...
[BULMA] Don't worry, Gohan!
Your dad's going to be fine!
[GOHAN] Well, I've got to know
for sure! Hang on!
--[BULMA screams]
--[YAJIROBE yells]
[TIEN] You know,
I didn't exactly think
that finding Dr. Gero's
lab would be easy...
But this? This is ridiculous!
I mean, considering the
fact that we can't sense
the androids' power
and the fact that we have
about a million
mountains to choose from,
I'd say it just
might take a while.
I say we split up and
whoever finds the lab first
sends out a signal.
What kind of signal did you
have in mind, Piccolo?
Raise your power level
so we can all sense it.
[KRILLIN whimpers]
Oh man, it's
freezing up here!
I know... But this is
no time to complain!
Just one more reason I'm
glad I'm not an Earthling.
Now we'd better get moving!
We don't have much time!
Okay, let's do it! I'll head
a little further north
and see what I
can find up there.
Hey, wait a sec!
What's the problem now?!
[KRILLIN] Nothing. I just
thought it'd be a good idea
if I gave you some Senzu
Beans before you went!
Oh yeah... Good call!
[KRILLIN] I've got
exactly six beans left.
That means we get two each.
Here's yours...
and here's yours.
[PICCOLO] Thanks, Krillin,
but let's just hope
we don't have to use them.
Just as I had hoped.
Those meddlesome fools are still
searching for my laboratory!
It will take them
hours to find it!
And by then it will be too late.
[beeping]
Ahh, gee whiz! I thought
you were a deer!
A-Are you okay?!
[DR. GERO growls]
[crunching]
[HUNTER screams]
[KRILLIN Huh...?
[HUNTER groans]
What happened to you?
Cra-zy old guy...
Dr. Gero!
Which way did he go?
[HUNTER grunts]
[KRILLIN growls]
[HUNTER] Hey, where
are you going?!
You can't leave me
like this! Hello?!
[thinking] That "Krillin"
may have spotted me.
No matter, he is
easily dealt with.
[beeping]
Huh?!
[DR. GERO yells]
[wolf howls]
Huh?!
[KRILLIN] Gotcha!
[beeping]
[DR. GERO] Hm?!
Aaahhh...
What a mess...
Huh?
[KRILLIN] A-ha!
Dr. Gero's footprint!
And he went this way!
--[DR. GERO grunts]
--[KRILLIN] Whoa!
[DR. GERO growls]
[KRILLIN grunts]
Silly human!
What exactly did you think would
happen when you found me?
[KRILLIN whimpers]
Why... don't I show you...?
Little fool...
You still do not understand!
--[beeping]
--Hm?!
[DR. GERO] Piccolo?!
I must get to my lab
before he finds it!
I will spare your life for now,
but only for a moment.
[DR. GERO laughs]
[DR. GERO] I will return to
dispense with you shortly!
[KRILLIN whimpers]
I've got to...
I've got to let
the others know...!
[KRILLIN grunts]
Huh?!
[thinking] No! First,
I've got to find that lab!
[DR. GERO laughs]
[DR. GERO] It seems I
have won this little race.
[beeping]
[DR. GERO] Hmm?!
[DR. GERO growls]
Yes, I've found it!
But I've got to hurry
and tell the others!
You are too late, human!
There is nothing that you
or your friends can do
to stop me now.
Oh no! I'd better
send out the signal!
[KRILLIN growls]
Piccolo, Tien! I've found it!
[PICCOLO] Huh...?
It's Krillin!
What's going on?!
I had hoped to avoid
activating them again so soon,
but it seems the time to put my
androids to the test has come!
I no longer have a choice.
Ah, yes... Android 17!
Dr. Gero. How are you today?
Good. Good! You remember me!
Of course. You gave
me life, Doctor.
[DR. GERO] Yes!
[thinking] It appears 17
is functioning properly.
And now for 18!
Hello, Doctor.
How have you been?
Good! So you
remember me too, 18!
How could I forget?
[thinking] Excellent!
They both seem to be in
perfect working order!
I see that you have chosen
to become an android...
[DR. GERO] Yes. Now I
have eternal life like you.
But we have pressing
matters at hand.
In the past, the two
of you have displayed
an unacceptable tendency
to disobey my orders.
I blame myself for this,
and the way I programmed you.
I have since modified your
programming, however.
And I will no longer
tolerate insubordination!
Now then, listen closely.
Several of Goku's friends are
presently outside our door.
You are to destroy
them immediately.
Yes.
We understand.
[PICCOLO growls]
[KRILLIN] See, there it is!
That opening in the
mountain is the entrance!
Right! Good job, Krillin!
Ah, thanks, Tien!
You can pat each other
on the back later.
Right now, we've got work to do!
[TIEN] C'mon!
[PICCOLO yells]
[KRILLIN] Hey, guys! Hold on!
[TIEN] What's the
matter now, Krillin?!
[KRILLIN] I... forgot
to mention one thing.
Dr. Gero beat me here...
What?!
I-I'm sorry...
[PICCOLO] You should have
told us before, Krillin!
[PICCOLO yells]
[door clangs]
[DR. GERO] Here they are.
The fools still do not
realize what awaits them.
But they will. Oh, they will...
[door clangs]
[KRILLIN grunts]
[TIEN grunts]
It won't budge an inch...
We need help!
[PICCOLO] Step aside. My turn.
[VEGETA] Oh, I see
you found it.
[KRILLIN &amp; TIEN] Huh?!
[DR. GERO chuckles]
Now go out there
and finish them!
[DR. GERO] Huh?!
Android 17! What are you doing?!
This is the controller you used
to deactivate us last time,
isn't it Dr. Gero?
I think I'd better
hold on to it.
--[DR. GERO whimpers]
--What? You disagree...?
Then let's try
another idea...
[DR. GERO] What?!
What have you done?!
You dare to defy me?!
I created you!
You're not going to put us
to sleep again, old man.
[DR. GERO growls]
[VEGETA] Hurry up, Namek! But
don't destroy those Androids
before I get a chance
to fight them!
[TRUNKS] Picolo,
don't listen to him!
He doesn't know
what he's saying!
Be quiet!
[DR. GERO] Enough
of this nonsense, 17!
I order you to go out there
and exterminate the
intruders at once!
[KRILLIN screams]
What do we do now, you guys?!
He's activated the Androids!
[VEGETA] Get out of
my way, you idiots!
--Huh?!
--Huh?
Don't do it! We can't beat
the androids without Goku!
Stop it!
You don't understand how
powerful they really are!
Too late, kid!
[VEGETA yells]
[DR. GERO] Huh?!
[VEGETA] Well, well...
What have we here that
has you all so nervous?
A boy with long hair and
a scarf around his neck,
and a beautiful young girl.
I take it these are
the scary androids
we've heard so much about?
That's them.
[NARRATOR] Our heroes have
finally come face-to-face
with the Androids of
Trunks' predictions!
But can they really
be as terrible
as the young Saiyan claims?
Find out on the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!