[NARRATOR] Last time
on DragonBall Z,
The Great Saiyaman,
or rather, Gohan,
entered the ring
with his opponent Kibito.
Gohan's true identity
had been revealed
so there was no sense
hiding it anymore.
But he didn't expect
that all his secrets
would be revealed.
[KIBITO] Gohan, I am curious to
see your Super Saiyan powers.
Show them to me!
We may be able to use them!
[NARRATOR]
To everyone's surprise,
Shin stepped forward to
reveal that Gohan
had become a pawn
in a much larger plan.
[SUPREME KAI] You do not
need to worry about Gohan.
He will be fine.
But no matter what happens,
I want all of you to promise me
that you'll stay out
of the ring.
Do you understand?
What? No way!
What do you want with Gohan?
[NARRATOR] This mysterious
message seemed to spell trouble
for Gohan, but when the
Z-Fighters learned that Shin
was none other than
the Supreme Kai himself,
they had no choice
but to obey his request.
Meanwhile, two pairs
of hungry eyes
closely monitor
Gohan's power, but why?
A conspiracy is brewing,
today on Dragon Ball Z!
Wanna see me turn
into a Super Saiyan?
Fine! I'll do it!
Just remember, you asked for it!
Goku, I got a bad
feeling about this...
I think Gohan's in trouble.
Listen, the instant
Gohan transforms,
I'm certain Spopovitch and
Yamu will try to attack him.
[GOKU] Hm?
[SUPREME KAI] But as
I've already told you,
you must not try to help him!
I don't know what you're after,
but Gohan can
take care of himself.
He doesn't need
any help from us.
Yes, of course...
What makes you so sure
that those two are
going to attack Gohan?
[SUPREME KAI] Spopovitch
and Yamu are not yet aware
of it, but Gohan is the one
they are searching for...
Don't worry. They don't want
his life--only his energy.
Energy?
[VEGETA grunts]
[VEGETA Hey!
Last chance for requests!
Do you just want to see
a Super Saiyan,
or should I take it up
to the next level?!
What's that?
There's a level beyond
a Super Saiyan?
[GOHAN grunts]
[GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN growls]
[BOTH gasp]
[GOHAN grunting]
[CROWD gasping]
[GOHAN yells]
[VIDEL gasps]
[CROWD gasping]
Hey, look! Yamu!
[YAMU growls]
All that energy! It's him!
You're kidding!
Is this for real?
Gohan is the Gold Fighter?
Impossible!
Ah! He's the Great Saiyaman
AND the Gold Fighter?!
Boy, he sure is
talented, huh?
[Oh wow, uh... he's strong...
[CHICHI] That's my boy! See?!
Didn't I tell you?! Huh?!
Now come on, you guys!
Let's hear it for Gohan!
Go, Gohan!
There, now you know
what I can do!
Is this good enough for ya?
What happens now?
Should I start fighting?
[KIBITO thinking]
What enormous energy...
He is far stronger
than I expected...
[VEGETA] Bah! Gohan had a lot
more power when he fought Cell.
I think your son has gone soft
in these peaceful times,
Kakarot.
You may be right, but he is
still the strongest fighter
at this tournament.
The only question is,
will it be enough?
[GOKU] Hm?! For what?
What does he mean?
[PICCOLO whimpers]
What's the matter?
C'mon, fight me!
[GOHAN]
What are you waiting for?
A written invitation?
Hey, hold on! Golden Boy, there!
I remember seeing that kid
when Mr. Satan
was fighting Cell!
Yeah, man, I think
you're right. It's gotta be him!
Come on! Let's get him!
Make sure you hold on
to him and don't let go!
Do you understand?
Right!
[SUPREME KAI] There!
Hold on! We've got company!
[SUPREME KAI yells]
[GOKU gasps]
What did you do?!
[GOHAN grunting]
[GOHAN screams]
[SPOPOVITCH &amp; YAMU laugh,
GOHAN screaming]
They're killing him!
Trust me... He'll be fine.
Gohan!
[KRILLIN grunts]
Hey, let me go!
[KRILLIN grunting]
I told you, you must stay back!
[GOHAN screams]
Make sure you get
all of it, Yamu!
[SPOPOVITCH laughs]
[screaming continues]
[KIBITO thinking] It's almost
over, Gohan... Hold on...
Th... Th-That's my head...
[CHICHI] Hey,
stop that you creeps!
What are you doing to my son?!
Leave him alone!
[VIDEL growls]
No! Gohan!
[VIDEL screams]
Let me go! Gohan's
in trouble! He needs help!
Stay here! Gohan
will be fine, Videl.
Goku? Please, help him!
Please!
[SUPREME KAI]
Gohan is in no danger.
Are you sure?
[GOHAN screams,
SPOPOVITCH &amp; YAMU laugh]
[GOHAN screams]
[GOTEN] My brother's in trouble!
How come nobody's
helping him?
And where's your dad?
[GOTEN] We gotta save him!
[TRUNKS yells]
[GOTEN]
Let me outta here, Trunks!
I gotta help him! Gohan!
[YAMU laughs,
GOHAN screams]
Yes! Now we have all the
pure energy we need!
Let's go!
[SPOPOVITCH chuckles]
[SPOPOVTICH laughs]
That was easier than we thought!
[SPOPOVITCH laughs]
[ANNOUNCER whimpers]
[GOHAN whimpers]
[SUPREME KAI] Don't move!
All of you stay where you are!
Kibito will take care
of Gohan now.
He has no need
of your assistance.
At least tell us what
you're gonna do with him?
It's time!
I must follow them and find out
where they are taking
Gohan's power!
You're leaving?!
I could use your help...
I understand if feel you
have to stay here...
But I must go.
Erasa! What in the
heck is going on?
What? I don't know!
I was going to ask you...
[CHICHI whimpers]
My poor boy!
You're going, too?
Are you crazy?!
I don't think
I have much choice!
The Supreme Kai gave us his word
that Gohan would be okay,
and I believe him!
So, unless I go with him,
I'm never going to know
what's going on around here!
[running footsteps]
[GOHAN whimpers]
[VIDEL gasps]
Gohan! Don't move...
You're gonna be okay. Hey!
Get a stretcher over here!
[ERASA]
Am I seeing things again?
Is that Videl down there?!
What's she doing?
She's all fixed!
Sharpner, pinch me so
I know this isn't a dream.
Ow!
I can't say I like it...
But... if you're going,
then I'm going, too.
Oh, I know I'm
gonna regret this...
All right. Let's do it!
[KRILLIN gasps
Oh, I better tell my wife
where I'm going,
or she'll kill me!
[GOKU] Huh?
[KRILLIN]
I'll catch up with you, Goku!
[VEGETA growls]
I know what you're
doing, Kakarot!
You're trying to skip out on
our next match, aren't you?!
Vegeta... Can't you see
that there's something
more important going on here?
You listen!
After the next two matches,
we are scheduled to fight!
And you will fight me!
So if you leave, you had better
make sure you come back!
I only entered this stupid
tournament so I could beat you!
Okay, okay!
Take it easy, Vegeta.
I have to go with the
Supreme Kai, but I promise
I'll put you at the top
of my "things to do" list
when I get back.
Just try and relax, will you?
[VEGETA growls]
You forget!
You can only stay for
one day in this world!
I guess that slipped
my mind, but listen,
why don't you come with me?
[VEGETA growls]
We're wasting time here!
Okay!
Kibito, will you promise to
take care of Gohan for me?
You have my word.
And as soon as he is healed,
I will follow after you.
Gohan, I presume,
will want to do the same...
[VEGETA growls]
I'm right behind you... Kakarot.
[FRIARS] Hup, hup, hup...
[KRILLIN] So you see,
without my help, they're toast!
If your friends
need you, then go.
But I've got a
tournament to win.
Oh yeah! Right!
Good luck with your match and
I'll see you when I get back!
[ANDROID 18] Hmph.
[KRILLIN] So long!
Krillin, you be
careful out there!
[KRILLIN laughs]
[KRILLIN] You got it!
Where did everybody go?
[KIBITO] Quiet.
You must stay still.
[FRIARS] Hup, hup, hup, hup...
[FRIAR A]
We'll take it from here.
[KIBITO] No, you will not.
Ah! What?
But he's been stabbed, sir!
[KIBITO growls]
[FRIARS gasp]
O-Okay, he's all yours!
[KIBITO growls]
[GOHAN grunts]
[growling continues]
[KIBITO thinking] I don't know
how long it will take
for him to regain
his full strength...
He has lost an
enormous amount of energy!
It's hard to believe a single
Earthling can possess
so much pure energy.
It's no wonder they were
so eager to obtain it!
[TRUNKS] What's the deal, Goten?
Did your brother
lose the match or what?
I don't know? He got hurt!
I know... But why did
your dad take off?
[GOTEN] Don't know!
I want to go see!
Get off me, Trunks!
Lemme outta here!
[KIBITO grunting]
[KIBITO sighs]
That should do it, Gohan.
[FRIARS squeal]
Gohan!
Do you feel better now?
I feel even stronger
than I was before.
Hey! What did you do?
If you come with me,
I'll tell you everything.
Hey, tubby. Do you know
where my daughter is?
Yep! I do. She's
right over there, sir!
[MR. SATAN] Oh great!
She's with that
skinny kid again!
Gohan, what's going on?
I'm not sure, Videl.
[MR. SATAN growls]
Darn! I gotta figure out
a way to keep that punk kid
away from my daughter!
[VIDEL] Insane...
I know...
[MR. SATAN snarls]
[MR. SATAN screams]
[grunting]
Is it okay if I come
with you, Gohan?
Uhh...
Please let me come.
I can help you guys out. Okay?
No, you better not.
I have a feeling something
bad's gonna happen.
And I don't want
you to get hurt.
[VIDEL] Oh please, Gohan!
I'll be careful!
If you don't let me go,
I'll just follow you anyway!
[MR. SATAN] Videl!
Get away from that
scrawny punk right now!
If things get tough, you promise
me that you'll get out of there?
[VIDEL giggles]
Alright then. Let's go.
Thanks, Gohan.
[CROWD gasps]
My... Videl is flying?!
C-Come back!
[MR. SATAN whimpers]
[MR. SATAN] Where'd she
learn how to do that?!
So she can fly.
What's the big deal?
I blame myself! I know I
should be more strict with her!
Whoa! It's no wonder
she's flown the coop!
[MR. SATAN growls]
Oh, be careful Gohan.
[ANNOUNCER]
My beautiful tournament...
What am I going to do now?
Majin Buu will be
resurrected with this power...
Babidi will be
very pleased with us!
[SPOPOVITCH] Uh-huh!
[WOMAN A] Is the
competition over?
What happened?
[MAN A] I don't know, dear.
They just keep
showing Mr. Satan!
[TOWNSFOLK scream]
[WOMAN B] Hey, my hat!
[GOKU] Hey! Wait!
I'm glad you decided to come.
And thank you.
Without all of your help,
I would not be able
to defeat them!
You need us? To beat those two?
No, it's not Spopovitch
and Yamu that concern me...
It's the wizard
controlling them.
[PICCOLO] Huh? A wizard?
[SUPREME KAI] Yes.
Long ago, at a time
when the human race
was still in its infancy
here on Earth...
a powerful wizard from the
distant edge of the universe
named Bibidi,
first appeared...
With him, he brought a
terrible monster
of his own creation, whose
sole purpose was to detsroy...
The name of that
monster was Majin Buu.
[GOKU] Buu, huh?
So what did this guy do?
[SUPREME KAI] Majin Buu had
no feelings or conscience.
He was designed as an
instrument of fear and terror.
His single desire was to
eliminate all living things.
And he was very good at it!
[VEGETA chuckles]
[SUPREME KAI] With Majin Buu
under his control,
Bibidi set about the
systematic destruction
of all life in the universe.
Hundreds of planets
were reduced to rubble.
Entire galaxies were
erased from existence.
No force could withstand
his evil power...
[VEGETA thinking]
This Majin Buu sounds like
he would have made
a decent Saiyan...
No, you're wrong Vegeta!
[VEGETA gasps]
There were five Grand
Kais at that time,
each one a thousand times
more powerful
than the one you called Frieza.
When they fought Buu...
only one survived.
[VEGETA growls]
He would have wiped out
your entire Saiyan race
with a breath.
Just like so many others...
Whoa! Not good.
[VEGETA thinking]
Why didn't someone tell me
he could read minds?!
In time, Majin Buu
became so powerful
that even Bibidi had
difficulty controlling him.
[GOKU gasps]
Whenever he needed to rest,
Bibidi used a spell to seal
Majin Buu inside a ball,
where he would lay dormant until
the counter-spell was invoked.
[KIBITO] Bibidi used
this spell to transport
Majin Buu from planet to planet.
The ball was brought here.
The Earth was intended to be
Majin Buu's next target.
No... That's terrible!
Obviously this action
was prevented,
but the ball that
contains Majin Buu
remains here on Earth
to this day...
Yes... The Supreme Kai
could have destroyed him...
He chose to leave him hidden.
[GOHAN] I don't get it.
Why didn't he destroy him
when he had the chance?
Because Majin Buu is no threat
as long as he is
confined to that ball.
And until now, we thought
Bibidi was the only one
who could release him.
Until now?
It would seem that we
have discovered another...
Bibidi had a son...
He's here on Earth.
Huh?!
Bibidi named his son Babidi.
At any cost we must stop him!
But what is he gonna do?
He intends to continue
his father's work.
He's going to
release Majin Buu!!
[NARRATOR] At last, the
source of Spopovitch and Yamu's
inhuman power has been revealed:
the Wizard Babidi!
Who, unless the
Z-Fighters can stop him,
intends to unleash a monster
that will eradicate the Earth!
The Supreme Kai has witnessed
the destructive force
of Majin Buu before...
Can he prevent it from
being released once again?