[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Frieza fired an attack that
seemed to pass by everyone...
[NARRATOR] Everyone
except the one person
who couldn't be
healed by Dende...
[NARRATOR] Dende himself...
Enraged by the loss
of their friend, Gohan...
...Krillin...
...and Piccolo...
...go three-on-one
with the evil Frieza.
A move that almost
lands Gohan in trouble.
[NARRATOR] Surprisingly,
Vegeta stepped in
and saved the young boy.
[NARRATOR} Then launced
an attack of his own.
You're making me mad!
[NARRATOR] Fueled by the idea
of becoming a Super Sayian,
Vegeta tried his hand at
defeating the maniacal Frieza.
Things were looking good, but
Frieza's immense power and speed
were too much to handle,
and left Vegeta puzzled
over his inability to
strike his nemesis.
That's impossible!
I guess you're... not a
"Super Saiyan", are you?
[NARRATOR] Does Vegeta have
the power to destroy Frieza?
Find out today!
[VEGETA thinking]
How can I beat Frieza?!
I've used all of my best moves!
[VEGETA chuckles]
[VEGETA roars]
Here I come!
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA] Hyaah!
Huh?!
Where'd he go?!
[thinking] He's so darn fast!
I don't believe it!
It looks like Frieza's
too much for Vegeta!
I think you're right.
[FRIEZA] Vegeta,
face it, to fight with me
is futile and useless.
Just wake up. You're
blind and delusional.
[VEGETA gasps]
You keep going on about
being a Super Sayian.
But it's just a myth, Vegeta.
I've never seen one.
Have you? You're such a chump.
[FRIEZA giggles]
[VEGETA gasps]
Such an ego...
You really believe all that?
A "Super Saiyan".
I must say, somebody
has some high hopes.
[VEGETA whimpers]
[thinking] Oh no!
What if he's right?!
What if I'm not
a Super Saiyan?!
That would mean I don't stand
a chance against Frieza!
And that means I'm
pretty much... dead!
Blast it! It can't be true!
What's he doing?
No, this just isn't possible!
Huh?
[VEGETA] You're wrong!
I am a Super Saiyan!
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA] Ryaaagh!
[gasping]
[VEGETA giggles]
[FRIEZA] Idiot.
[VEGETA gasps]
Wha--?!
[VEGETA growls]
Haah! Haah! Haah! Haah!
[grunting]
[GOHAN yells]
Go for it, Vegeta!
[GOHAN whimpers]
[GOHAN screams]
[PICCOLO gasps]
[KRILLIN] Hey--! Whoa!
[VEGETA screams]
[VEGETA] Raaagh!
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN grunt]
[PICCOLO thinking]
Vegeta's aim is bang on,
but everytime he shoots, Frieza
anticipates his every move!
[thinking] It's only
a matter of time
before Frieza goes on the
offensive and finishes Vegeta.
[KRILLIN] Piccolo
looks worried...
Hey, Piccolo!
What's going on?
[PICCOLO] Quiet!
[BOTH] Huh...?
Huh! Haah! Haah! Haah!
Huh! Raah! Haah!
Haah! Haah! Rrgh!
[VEGETA gasps]
Hah...
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA] I'm not
done with you!
That's it!
[VEGETA yells]
I'll show you, Frieza!
Feel my Super Saiyan wrath!
[VEGETA yells]
Vegeta! What are you trying
to do, destroy us all?!
[FRIEZA yells]
[ALL gasp]
Huh...? Huh?!
Aah--!
[grunting]
[VEGETA whimpers]
I should go...
I've wasted enough of my time
playing around with you.
Uh... guys...?
I-I don't...
Frieza defended himself with
just one... one simple kick!
[KRILLIN] And that's
not the worst of it.
Looks like Vegeta's power
is pretty much done for!
[GOHAN] This is terrible!
This is all just terrible!
But before I depart... One
final piece du'resistance!
Don't worry... The pain
will subside after a while.
Ready?
[thinking] Oh my! I fear Vegeta
has exhausted all of his power.
He fought a brave battle,
but this is awful...
[KING KAI thinking]
Despite all the attacks,
Frieza isn't even winded!
Poor Vegeta. How sad.
I sense he too realizes
that his fate lies
in the hands of the icy tyrant.
[KING KAI thinking] Now it is
only a matter of time before
the ruthless Saiyan prince
meets his demise.
All things come around,
and Vegeta's treachery is
about to be paid back tenfold.
Well, then... Shall we begin?
[ALL scream]
[VEGETA grunts]
Vegeta!
[FRIEZA giggles]
No! Gohan!
We can't help Vegeta now.
[thinking] Vegeta... No...
[VEGETA grunts]
Vegeta... I must say I'm
very disappointed in you.
After all that "Super Saiyan"
garbage you were spouting.
But I thought I should
give you a sporting chance.
[VEGETA screams]
There you go... I
was just checking
your reflexes and
they seem to be fine.
Let's try it again just
to be sure, shall we?
[VEGETA yells]
While you did put
up a good fight,
the bottom line, Vegeta,
is you are just as stupid
as those other half-wits!
[VEGETA grunts]
But I can help you...
If you were to pledge
your allegiance to me.
[gasping]
[VEGETA grunts]
[blows landing, grunting]
[VEGETA whimpers]
Get up... Vegeta...!
[ALL gasp]
[whimpering]
[PICCOLO growls]
[VEGETA gurgles]
[bones creaking]
[VEGETA gasps]
[VEGETA yells]
[blows landing,
yelling]
[VEGETA gasps]
[VEGETA screams]
Feel free to jump in
anytime, my little friends.
[blows landing]
[KING KAI thinking] Piccolo and
the others are bound by fear,
rendering them helpless
against Frieza's fury.
Now it looks as though all
hope to defeat Frieza is lost...
[thinking] I can sense Vegeta
losing his battle against...
...against some
tremendous dark force!
It must be Frieza!
[thinking] And I fear
the worst for Vegeta...
[beeping]
[buzzing]
[thinking] I'm healed!
[thinking] I can feel
my renewed power!
It's surging
through every vein!
[thinking] I can't believe it!
I can't believe my strength!
This is incredible!
[thinking] I feel so calm,
yet I know I must help Vegeta
and the others.
[thinking] I'm sorry I haven't
been there for you, Gohan.
But I'll make up for lost time.
[thinking] Trust me!
I'm on my way!
[blows landing,
VEGETA grunting]
[NARRATOR] Is Goku truly
strong enough to stop Frieza,
the ultimate fighting machine?
Find out on the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!