[NARRATOR] Last time,
on Dragon Ball Z,
Goku's hidden powers
had at last awakened,
as he transformed into a
legendary Super Saiyan.
Faced with
this new threat,
Frieza launched a
desperate volley of attacks
but to no avail.
[FRIEZA yells]
[NARRATOR] For all of his might,
it seemed the once
invincible Frieza
had finally met his match.
[FRIEZA] You--!
What... What are you?!
I am the hope
of the Universe.
I am the answer to all living
things that cry out for peace.
I am protector
of the innocent.
I am the light
in the darkness.
I am truth.
[NARRATOR] Now, with
Planet Namek set to explode
at any minute, the
final, decisive round
of this epic battle
is about to begin.
Today, on Dragon Ball Z!
[GOKU] Ally to good!
Nightmare to you!
[FRIEZA whimpers]
[FRIEZA growls]
Bah! Super Saiyan.
So, out of that whole barrel of
monkeys, one finally made good.
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[FRIEZA] Vegeta...
He was sure that
he was the one.
Ha, ha! When he was a boy, that
legend was his only comfort.
He tried so hard and failed.
What a dope!
He thought he was a jewel,
but he was just a dirt clod.
[GOHAN] Hmm...
[GOHAN thinking] Gosh,
what a battle!
Krillin, where are you?
We made it so far together...
I can't believe that
you're not with me now...
We were so close!
[FRIEZA growls]
[FRIEZA] Huh...?
What?! No way!
[FRIEZA yells]
[FRIEZA growls]
Nooo!
[FRIEZA thinking] This can't be!
I am lord of the Universe!
How could his power rival mine?
By toying with him
I gave him the chance to
develop his power even more!
[FRIEZA growls]
[thinking] I should have
destroyed this scum
the moment I first
laid eyes on him!
[MELAKKA] Sir, all
check-point communications
from the Ginyu Force
have stopped!
And, Sir, Lord Frieza's
scouter is still offline!
I can't even get a reading
of their power levels!
That means... That
means it's possible
that they've all been
destoyed somehow!
[SOLDIER] Well,
I say good riddance!
[gasping]
That's right! You heard me!
What?! Are you crazy?!
[SOLDIER] Frieza
destroyed my entire race,
so let him get
what's coming to him!
[SOLDIER screams]
You...
...idiots!
Live as slaves if you want to!
[CUI] No one double-crosses
Frieza and lives!
[SOLDIER screams]
[CUI] Take note men, of
what happens to someone
who decides to oppose Frieza!
[MELAKKA] B-But he was
one of your own kind!
That man? My own kind?
Yes, he was!
[CUI] Listen!
Don't you men get it?!
There are no individual
races anymore!
There are only
two kinds of people now:
Those who obey Frieza...
And those who disobey him!
And they never live very long!
So which kind
of people are we?!
Do we support Frieza?
Good! It's
better than dying!
Take my word!
Now, get back
to work, you bums!
[beeping]
[BLUE] There we go!
Picking up a power level
reading from Namek!
Isolated!
Wow, it's him! Frieza!
It's huge!
I'll say! It's
off the scale!
[CUI laughs]
Excellent!
It looks like the boss
is turning up the heat!
Huh?!
What's that?
There's one more,
and it's huge, too!
How big?!
It seems equal in
measure. No, wait!
It's actually a little bigger!
[BLUE] Here we go, sir!
Isolating signal right now!
[MELAKKA] Unbelievable!
[BLUE] Complete system overload!
[grunting]
[SOLDIER 2]
Let's get out of here!
[SOLDIERS screaming]
[MELAKKA] Commander,
she's going to blow!
[screaming]
[FRIEZA growls]
It's over.
You're finished.
[FRIEZA gasps]
[FRIEZA] How dare you?
Me?
Finished?
No one says that to me!
I reign supreme over all!
[FRIEZA growls]
[GOKU] Ka... Me...
Ha...
[FRIEZA growls]
[GOHAN] There it is!
Dad's spaceship!
It looks okay!
Hang on, Piccolo!
We're going home!
[DR. BRIEF hums]
[CHICHI] You sure have
been up here a long time.
Are you sure you know
what you're doing?
[DR. BRIEF] My dear,
in this line of work,
patience is a virtue!
[DR. BRIEF yells]
Who said being a
scientist isn't dangerous!
Just look at the swelling!
[CHICHI growls]
[beeping]
[SCRATCH] Meow!
[DR. BRIEF] Hm?!
Somebody has triggered the
floor sensor in Goku's ship.
[CHICHI] Huh?!
Oh my goodness!
Who do you think it is?
Well, there's only one
way to know for sure...
Now...
Let's hope this works!
[CHICHI] Is that Gohan?
It really is him!
Gosh, it's bad!
Gotta focus; there's
no time to waste!
Huh?
My baby!
[GOHAN] Mom?!
Is that you?!
Gohan, I can't believe it!
It's really you!
You're still alive!
[ROSHI] Ask him
about the others!
Are they okay?!
Krillin's gone...
Krillin?! He's gone?!
How dare you!
Gohan! What's going on?!
Is the fight over?!
No, Dad told us to take off
while he handles Frieza.
Frieza got Krillin...
He's gone now...
[ROSHI] Is Goku winning?
I don't know.
And I'm sorry,
but I don't have time to answer
any more questions right now!
[CHICHI] Where are
your manners, Gohan?
This is your mother speaking!
[CHICHI] Gohan, wait!
You come back here this instant!
Alright then, you're grounded!
Do you hear me, Gohan?!
Hey, just what do you
think you're doing, Gohan?!
Get back here right now!
I'd destroy us both
before I let you live.
Either way, you'll never
make it out of here alive!
We'll see about that.
Guess what?
I just had a brilliant idea.
I've figured out
how to beat you!
Hmm?
Your power is amazing
but there's more to
winning than that!
Sometimes it's the smartest
one who wins, not the strongest!
[FRIEZA laughs]
[GOKU gasps]
Now, say
goodbye to Namek!
[GOKU yells]
Die, planet! Die!
Say goodbye to Namek!
Can't stop it!
[GOKU gasps]
[FRIEZA laughs]
[FRIEZA yells]
[CHICHI] What's happening?!
What's that light?!
It looks like the
planet is exploding!
[DR. BRIEF] Unbelievable!
It can't be!
[ALL scream]
Gosh! Oh, no... No!
I don't want to die!
[BULMA screams]
[GOHAN grunting]
[GOHAN] Whoa!
Dad, hang on!
[KING KAI] Huh...?!
[KING KAI] Oh, my! Dear me!
[CHIAOTZU] What's
the matter, King Kai?
What happened?
[KING KAI] I'm afraid
it's bad, guys...
What?!
Tell us, please!
[KING KAI] Goku was
doing well, extremely well!
But now he's finished...
It's all over...
Huh?
What?! No way!
It looks like Frieza
won this one, my friends.
Goku had Frieza
against the ropes!
With his new power, Goku had
Frieza totally outclassed
in strength
and speed!
Then how?!
What went wrong?!
M-Maybe Goku's
still okay!
No, I wish that were
possible, Chiaotzu...
Frieza got desperate.
He was losing the battle.
So he used his trump card.
He couldn't beat Goku,
so he destroyed Namek!
Destroyed Namek...?
But then... That means...
That means that there was
no longer any atmosphere
or air for them to breath!
I'm afraid it's all over...
[CHIAOTZU gasps]
Gosh! Goodness...
[YAMCHA] But what about Gohan?
And Piccolo?! And Bulma...?
[KING KAI] All gone,
I'm afraid...
[TIEN] It looks like we'll
be sticking around for a while.
[KAME] King Kai!
Can you hear me?
This is Kame.
Kame? Oh!
Yeah, sure. How's
the weather there?
[KAME] Uh, yes, the weather
happens to be very pleasant
right now, King Kai.
But we have other concerns.
Do you remember my
trusty assistant Mr. Popo?
Short guy?
[KAME] Yes, that's him.
Well he's been searching
for the Dragon Balls
and he's doing very
well, bless him.
He already has five of them!
[KING KAI] Hmm...?
Kame... exactly
where are you?
[KAME] Why, I'm
on Earth, of course.
Hey..
That means... Huh?!
Hey! That means that...
you're still alive, Kame!
[KAME] Huh...? Why, yes, I do
have a little indigestion
but I don't think it's
anything that serious.
[KING KAI] Do you know
what this means, Kame?!
Piccolo must still be alive!
Huh?
Yes, I couldn't be
here if he wasn't.
But you know that better than
anyone, don't you, King Kai?
Well, guys,
Piccolo's alive!
Really?!
[CHIAOTZU &amp; YAMCHA gasp]
[KAME] King Kai,
are you still there?
This is Kame.
Hello, is anyone home? H-Hello?
Hey! Be quiet, will ya?!
Ah! Oh...
Hey! He is alive!
Namek's still there!
[BULMA] Oh, man!
This is great! Just great!
[BULMA grunts]
[BULMA] No way...
I'm not giving up now..
I've come too far!
Rrrgh!
Whew...!
[BULMA] Guys, where are you?!
[thinking] You can do it, Dad!
I know you can!
It looks like we're going
into overtime, you guys!
Goku is fine!
And so are Gohan,
Piccolo, and Bulma!
We're back in the saddle!
[ALL gasp]
Yes! We can
still do it!
[CHIAOTZU &amp; TIEN cheer]
Darn.
I held back too much power.
So, you couldn't do it.
You couldn't go through
with it after all, huh?
Hmm?
I don't blame you.
Destroying both of
us to make sure
that I don't win isn't
any way to fight.
It's just another
way of giving up.
You still don't
get it, do you?
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[FRIEZA] I didn't plan
on destroying myself,
just you and the planet!
[GOKU] Hm?
[FRIEZA] I can breathe
in space and you can't.
That means if the planet goes
then you won't have
any more air to live on.
And I shall be victorious!
Five minutes.
That's how
long you have.
This planet is
still going to blow;
the core has been
completely disintigrated.
Hmph.
Five minutes
is all that I need!
It won't take that
long to beat you
and leave with my
friends on my spaceship.
You underestimate me.
The true depth of
my power escapes you.
Well, it's time
that you experience
the ultimate Frieza!
Yes, a very rare
occurrence indeed.
One hundred percent
of my true power!
You never really had
a chance to beat me!
It's over!
Can your body handle the
stress from all that power?
Well, I don't
think that it can!
In any case, I'm not going
to give you the time
you need to power up!
[GOKU growls]
This battle
ends right now!
[NARRATOR] In just
a few minutes time,
Planet Namek is
going to explode!
[NARRATOR] Hurry up, Gohan!
There's no time to lose.
You've got to find Bulma and
bring her back to the ship.
That's right.
Keep a keen lookout, guys.
The decisive moment
has finally arrived
on next
exciting episode...
of Dragon Ball Z!