[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z...
Vegeta unleashed the full
force of his Super Saiyan
powers on the
monster Majin Buu.
He scored a hole in one by
sending a searing blast of
energy right through the
belly of the bloated beast.
[NARRATOR] But Majin Buu
wasn't down for long.
[NARRATOR] He was eager to
fill that empty spot
with a Super Saiyan sandwich.
[NARRATOR] And once this
monster's little mind is made up
there's no stopping him.
[BUU]
Big power!
[BUU yells]
[grunts]
[BUU screams]
[VEGETA grunts]
[NARRATOR] Majin Buu's amazing
demonstration of power
put a canyon sized
crater in the Earth.
It was then Vegeta realized
that a tangle with this
half-witted horror
would not only be dangerous,
it could be lethal!
[VEGETA]
How... can I beat him...
...if he's able to regenerate
himself after every attack?
Darn it!
You no fun.
You go bye-bye!
Bye-bye! Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
[screams]
[NARRATOR]
With Vegeta on the run,
Majin Buu used his own body
to trap the Super Saiyan
and then dropped from the
sky like a ten ton brick.
As his father took the
beating of his life,
Trunks could barely
contain his anger
as he watched from
the sidelines.
[PICCOLO]
Stay where you are, Trunks!
We don't want to lose you, too!
There's nothing you can do now!
[NARRATOR]
Vegeta's only chance of survival
lies in Trunks' hands.
Can Trunks save Vegeta?
Or will Majin Buu turn
the two Super Saiyans
into his very own
father-son picnic?
Trunks! Come back!
I'm coming! Wait up!
No!
Goten! I won't let
you go down there!
You'll just make things worse!
Let me go!
Trunks needs my help!
[growls]
If I were Gohan, I bet you'd
let me go, wouldn't you?!
[gasps]
Stop!
No! Goten!
[laughs]
[yells]
[BABIDI gasps]
Ah! What was that?!
[BUU grunts,
VEGETA yells]
[TRUNKS yelling]
[BUU grunts]
[GOTEN]
Trunks!
[TRUNKS]
Dad!
[grunts]
Oh, Dad!
[BABIDI] Huh?! Who are
those meddling kids?!
So Vegeta still has
a few allies left?
Ha! Well they can
try to save him,
but it won't make
any difference.
[giggles]
[TRUNKS]
Dad?
[GOTEN]
It's all right now! We're here!
Come on, Dad! Wake up!
Please! Wake up!
Dad! Dad! Dad!
Come on! Wake up!
Is he alive?
Of course he is!
My dad's the toughest guy
in the whole world!
Yeah, but... but he
got hurt real bad...
Hey, Goten! Clean out your ears
and listen to me, okay?!
My mom told me. My dad...
He used to be the prince
of every single Saiyan!
[gasps]
He's a prince?!
[TRUNKS] That's right!
He's a prince, Goten, a prince!
And there's no way a prince
could lose to a stupid monster!
That's it! Dad!
[GOTEN]
He's awake!
Trunks, my son...
[BOTH laugh]
Wait! Where is Majin Buu?!
Ha! So he's alive!
That poor fool!
It would've been a lot
less painful for him
if he just rolled over and died!
My Majin Buu is invincible!
And now he's going
to eat them all up!
[laughs]
[PICCOLO]
That's not gonna happen!
What you and that monster
have done is unforgivable!
[BABIDI]
Wh-Who are you?
My, what a lovely shade
of green you are.
Looking good.
Who could blame you.
After all, you've seen
the power of Majin Buu.
It figures you'd
turn green with envy!
No, I always look this way!
So there's no use in
flattering yourself, Babidi!
What? How dare you!
You've got some nerve talking
to me like that, you insect!
Yes! You had better
watch yourself
or I'll sick Majin Buu
on you next!
Yeah, why don't you
call him, wizard.
I'm sure he'd be glad to
see you writhing in agony
like the worm you are.
[BABIDI]
What?! Ooh, that does it!
You're going to regret
every word of that, you!
Call your monster...
so he can watch you die!
[gasps]
[yells]
Barrier!
[laughs]
You see, I'm far too
powerful for you!
Paparapapa!
[laughs]
[PICCOLO growls]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[laughs, gasps]
[growls]
[BABIDI]
Majin Buu! Majin Buu!
Come get him!
Hurry, Majin Buu! Get him!
Haa!
Ha! There's no way that
you're going to get in here!
--[screams]
--[PICCOLO yells]
No, you fool! Don't you know
that if you destroy me,
then no one, no one will be able
to control Buu! He'll run wild!
And there will be no way
to seal him up again!
Listen to me!
If I'm gone, Majin Buu
will destroy everything until
there's nothing left of this
planet. Do you want that?!
That's not gonna happen
even if you are alive
so it doesn't matter anymore!
[PICCOLO growls]
[BABIDI screams]
[BABIDI gasps]
Goodbye!
--[screams]
--[PICCOLO yells]
What have...
What have you done to me...?
Buu mad! Buu make pow, pow, POW!
[VEGETA]
Trunks... listen. You need...
to take good care
of your mother...
[TRUNKS]
Take care of Mom?
But... you can
do that, too, right?
[TRUNKS] You can take care of
Mom too, can't you, Dad? Dad?!
[NARRATOR]
Goku is alive... barely.
The battle he fought with
Vegeta has left him in
an unconscious state that
he may never wake from.
He has no way of knowing
that Vegeta is no longer
under the control
of the wizard Babidi;
he has no way of knowing that
Vegeta is about to fight
his greatest battle... alone.
[NARRATOR] Gohan has suffered a
fate similar to his father's.
The young Super Saiyan clings to
life after being assaulted
by the monster Majin Buu.
[NARRATOR] For these two,
the battle is over.
But for Vegeta, the
real fight is about to begin.
Why would you say that? Dad?
Why do you want me to take of
Mom? Are you going somewhere?
I want you two to leave
and get far away from here.
As for Buu,
I'll fight him alone.
[gasps]
Don't do that!
Goten's right!
We'll fight with you!
You don't wanna
get killed, do you?!
You've got to let us
help you, Dad!
Are you in?!
Yeah!
See? We're with you!
Stop it... It's too
dangerous for you two.
I will finish this by myself.
Come on! It'll be easier to
beat him with me and Trunks!
We'll gang up on him!
He-He won't know what hit him!
Yeah! We're tough!
We could even beat that
big blob without your help!
Right, Trunks?
[TRUNKS]
You bet!
Might do better than you did.
[GOTEN]
Uh-oh...
[VEGETA] Trunks...
You are my only son and yet,
I haven't held you once
since you were a baby, have I?
Come here, Son.
Dad, what's wrong?
Aw, this is embarrassing...
Dad. Come on. Cut it out.
[VEGETA] Trunks, there's
something you must know.
You've made me proud, my son.
[TRUNKS grunts]
What did you do to him?!
Why'd you do that?!
What's wrong with you?!
Why did you do that to Trunks?!
You might have killed him!
Why?! Are you crazy?! Why?!
Why did you do it?! Tell me!
Why did you do that to Trunks?!
Your his dad!
Dads aren't supposed to do
bad things to their sons!
Why did you hit him? Why did you
hurt him like that?! Why? Why?!
[grunts]
[gasps]
[whimpers]
[PICCOLO]
Vegeta, I think I understand.
[PICCOLO] And one day,
so will Trunks.
[BUU humming]
[BUU] Me big mad!
Which guy hit Buu?!
Take the two boys as far away
from here as possible. Go now!
Of course.
It's time... Hurry.
You'll die... You know that.
[VEGETA] There is one thing
I'd like to know.
Tell me. Will I meet that clown
Kakarot in the other world?
I'm not going to lie
to you, Vegeta,
although the answer may be
difficult for you to hear.
This is the truth.
Goku devoted his life to
protecting the lives of others.
Because of his selflessness,
when he died,
he was allowed to keep his body
and travel to King Kai's planet.
[BUU hums]
You, on the other hand,
have spent your life in pursuit
of your own selfish desires.
You've caused too much pain.
When you die, you will not
receive the same reward.
Oh well... So be it...
[BUU hums]
[VEGETA] That will be all.
Get out of here... And hurry!
You stay! You fight Buu!
Yes! That's right!
Huh...?
[VEGETA]
Your fight is with me!
The others are of
no concern to you!
Got it? You big,
bloated balloon freak!
Ohh! [growls]
Me no like you! Buu angry!
[chuckles]
You talk mean to Buu?!
[PICCOLO]
Hurry, Krillin!
You have to get away
from here right now!
Yeah, right.
Me make you hurt bad!
[chuckles]
Buu get big mad now!
Me want fight!
I think I finally
understand you... Let's go!
Oh...?
[KRILLIN]
What's Vegeta up to, Piccolo?
He's crazy!
He won't make it!
That monster is
gonna eat him alive!
For the first time...
...Vegeta is fighting for
someone other than himself!
Controlling his own fate!
Oooh!
You look tasty!
I make you chocolate...
Or maybe make you
cracker and cheese!
[chuckles]
You're a fool...
I'm going to crush you.
And throw you into the wind.
[gasps]
[thinking] Trunks, Bulma,
I do this for you...
...and yes, even
for you, Kakarot.
[gasps]
[growls]
[screaming]
Oh... Vegeta...
Vegeta!
[gasps]
[screaming]
[NARRATOR] And so, one of the
Earth's greatest warriors
has vanished in a
blinding flash of light,
having made the
ultimate sacrifice
for the sake of his loved ones.
His name... was Vegeta.
A proud Saiyan prince...