[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z!
Frieza's elite fighters,
the Ginyu Force,
raced across the galaxy
toward Planet Namek,
equipped with new
scouters to speed
their evil master's search
for the Dragon Balls.
Meanwhile,
Krillin and Gohan
continued their
journey to see Guru.
I guess we can risk
picking up the pace a bit.
We should be far
enough away from Vegeta now
that he won't be
able to sense us.
Yeah, and not
only that,
my dad should be getting
here any minute now!
He'll need
our help!
[KRILLIN]
Let's go!
[NARRATOR] Unfortunately
for our heroes,
Vegeta was much closer
than they realized!
[VEGETA] Ah! I've
found them at last!
[NARRATOR] And with six Dragon
Balls already in his possession,
the Saiyan Prince
was determined
to have the
seventh at any cost!
They'll get no mercy
from me! They're dead!
[NARRATOR] Now, with
Vegeta hot on their trail,
Krillin and Gohan need
Guru's help more than ever.
But even if Guru can unlock
Gohan's hidden power,
are any of these warriors
ready to face the Ginyu Force?
Keep it up, Gohan!
We're getting close!
Guru's house should
be just ahead!
Right!
[thinking]
I don't know...
If Guru can release
Gohan's powers,
there's a chance he'll
be strong enough
that we can
take on Vegeta.
But the more I think about
it, I'm not so sure...
[VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA chuckles]
[thinking] That guy is
like a bottomless pit...
Somehow, he keeps pulling
out more and more power!
[KRILLIN growls]
[KRILLIN thinking] But if we
can just get Gohan powered-up
before Goku
gets here,
maybe the three of us
can beat Vegeta together!
9,999...
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU] Ten thousand!
Wow! All that, and
I'm not even tired!
So much for hundred
times gravity!
[GOKU] I can't turn up
the machine any higher...
Well, all
right, then!
I guess I'm as ready for
Planet Namek as I'll ever be!
In that case, it
might be a good idea
to get used to normal
gravity again...
[alarm beeping]
[GOKU] Huh...?
[beeping continues]
Huh?
Huh...
[GOKU laughs]
I can't believe I've
gotten this much stronger!
Incredible! I don't even
feel this gravity at all!
It's almost like
I'm weightless!
I feel light
as a feather!
Watch my speed!
I feel good!
[GOKU laughs]
Just watch
me now!
This is great!
I bet I could power
up my Kaio-Ken attack
times ten,
no problem!
Huh?
[GOKU] A wise
man once said,
"The harder you train,
then the stronger you smell!"
[GOKU laughs]
That's better. Now,
time for something to eat!
Let's see...
What am I in the mood for?
Ah! Just what I needed!
What's this doing in
here? It's no good...
There! Now that's what
I'm looking for!
A sports drink! It's
much less filling
and tastes great!
[GOKU snoring]
[VEGETA chuckling]
[thinking]
I have them...
They won't be able to
hide from me this time.
[KRILLIN] Gohan!
There it is!
Dead ahead! On top
of that tall peak!
That's
Guru's house!
I can't believe we
actually made it!
[KRILLIN laughs]
Hold it, Gohan!
I think we got
ourselves some company!
[GOHAN whimpers]
It's Vegeta!
I-I know...
What do we do?
Gohan...
I'll stay here and try to
hold him off for a while.
I want you to go on ahead
to Guru's house without me.
But, Krillin...
Don't argue!
Just go! Now!
[KRILLIN growls]
[GOHAN whimpers]
Right!
[KRILLIN] Okay.
Come on, Vegeta.
[KRILLIN] Guh...
[thinking] How can I
compete with that?
Well...
Wh-What do you want, Vegeta?
How did you find us?
What do I want? Oh, I'm
just here to say hello...
Don't play
ignorant with me.
I want the four-star
Dragon Ball.
The one I had
hidden in the lake.
And I know
you've got it.
[KRILLIN] I-I don't know
what you're talking about!
[VEGETA] Hmph... Is that so?
Well, we'll just
see about that.
Ah... Such
great power...
[VEGETA chuckling]
Huh? What's that?
There's a huge power-level
coming from that mountain.
So, that's where
you were headed.
Is that where you've hidden
the Dragon Ball as well?
No! You're wrong!
[KRILLIN]
Vegeta! Nooo!
[GURU coughing]
[GURU] I can feel that you have
truly amazing hidden powers.
The strongest
I've ever felt!
Please! I have to hurry! It's
Vegeta! He's right outside!
Are his
intentions pure?
[GURU] Hmm.
What is
this place?
Hey! Stop
right there!
I'm warning you!
Leave now.
Hmph. I don't think so.
[GOHAN panting]
[panting continues]
[GOHAN whimpering]
[screaming]
Ha-ha!
[thinking] Gohan!
Guru did it!
That power... There's only
one person that could be...
So! You've come to settle
the score at last, have you?
Here I am, Kakarot!
Uhhh...
[VEGETA] Huh?
[VEGETA chuckles]
What?!
[VEGETA] You?! But your...
Your power level...
What is this place?
What have you done?!
[KRILLIN chuckles]
[VEGETA chuckles]
Huh?
[VEGETA laughing]
What? Am I supposed
to be scared now,
just because you've gotten
a little "power boost"?
It changes
nothing!
You're still nowhere
near my level.
So go ahead if you
want! Attack me!
Your move.
What is it, Guru?
[GURU] Dende, my child...
What's wrong?
Please... You must go
and warn the others...
I can sense that
there is an
incredibly powerful force
approaching our planet...
[GURU coughs]
Are you all
right, Guru?
[GURU] Go,
Dende. Quickly!
Right!
Hey... Hey!
Listen!
Guru just told me there's
some kind of powerful force
headed straight for us!
What?
What in the...?
Who's this Guru?
Hey! He's right!
Something is coming!
Yeah! That power
level's huge!
Wait! I know!
It's Goku!
I knew he'd be
here to save us!
Kakarot?!
[GOHAN] I dunno...
Are you sure, Krillin?
It feels like there's
more than one...
No! Not them!
[VEGETA] One... Two...
Three... Four... Five...
It... It has to be...
Damn it all!
Frieza's called in
the Ginyu Force!
You! No more
time for games!
Give me that
Dragon Ball right now!
I... I can't!
I don't have it!
Tell me
where it is!
Tell me, and I promise no
harm will come to you,
or your friends!
But if I don't
make my wish
before they get here,
we're all dead!
[KRILLIN] What do you
think we are? Stupid?
You put him down.
Right now, Vegeta.
Listen to me!
Don't be a fool!
These are no petty
henchman Frieza's called,
it's the Ginyu Force!
Five men each as
strong as I am.
Maybe even
stronger!
And in a few moments,
they'll be here
with their
new scouters.
They'll find us
and kill us all!
No... I-I don't
believe you!
[VEGET] Do you
feel that power?!
None of us are strong
enough to face that!
We only have
one chance.
We have to use the Dragon
Balls to make me immortal!
[NAIL] I fear what the
Saiyan says may be true.
This is an evil presence
that approaches...
Here's the deal:
We use the wish on Gohan!
The boy may
have power,
but he doesn't have the
fighting experience!
It has to be me!
I can't do it!
That would mean...
our entire search
would be in vain!
But you would still
have two more wishes.
[VEGETA growling]
Didn't you know?
The Dragon Balls will
grant you three wishes.
Uh... Three? Are you
sure about that?
Not... just one?
We're wasting time!
The Ginyu Force will
be here any second!
We have to use the Dragon Balls
now, before it's too late!
You're not giving the
orders here, Vegeta!
Nail, are you
absolutely certain
that we'll
get three wishes?
Yes.
Let's go, then.
But, you try
anything funny
and the deal's off,
you got it? Follow me!
[GOHAN] Hey! Wait up!
This is crazy!
Just fly as
fast as you can!
So then,
have they gone?
[NAIL] Yes. But even
if they do get
the Dragon
Balls in time,
I don't much
like their chances.
Can't you
help them?
[GURU] Dende's right.
I think you should join
them in this battle.
It might help their
chance at victory.
But what about--?
[GURU] Don't worry
about me, my son.
I don't plan on leaving
this world just yet.
[GURU chuckles]
[NAIL] I will do
as you wish.
[FRIEZA giggles]
[FRIEZA] At last,
my precious Ginyu Force
has finally arrived.
And right on schedule!
[FRIEZA laughs]
[VEGETA] We're
running out of time!
The Ginyu Force has landed!
[thinking] Just a
little farther...
[BULMA sighs]
I just wish they'd
hurry up and come back...
[BULMA screams]
Hey, what's
the big idea?!
[KRILLIN] Sorry!
No time to explain, Bulma!
I need the
Dragon Ball!
[VEGETA] Quickly, now!
Follow me to the others!
Hey, hang on a second!
Come back!
What's going on?!
Do you have any idea
what I went through
for that stupid
Dragon Ball?!
You could at least
fill me in!
Come on! I'm
going nuts here!
Come back here!
Youuu...!
Krillin and
Vegeta... Ugh!
What the...? What was
Krillin doing with Vegeta?!
[FRIEZA chuckling]
[FRIEZA laughing]
[growling]
I'm Recoome!
[hissing]
Burter!
Oh, yeah!
I'm Jeice!
[growling]
[yells]
Guldo!
Captain Ginyu!
Now! You! See! The! Power!
[ALL] Of the Ginyu Force!
[FRIEZA] Uhh...
Well, that's quite
an entrance, boys.
[ALL] Heh!
[NARRATOR] With the
Ginyu Force by his side,
is Frieza on the verge of
taking over the universe?
Or will Vegeta's new alliance
with Gohan and Krillin prove
to be a sufficient
deterrence?
It's a race for survival,
and every second counts!
Can our heroes get to the
remaining Dragon Balls
in time to summon the Dragon
and make their wish?
There's only one
way to find out...
Tune in for the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!