[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
two young juniors vied for
the title of World Champion!
One of them was Trunks,
son of Vegeta.
The other was Goten,
son of Goku.
The winner could
rightly be called
the strongest boy in the world.
The action paused
for only a moment,
when the confident
Trunks took a time out
to make an
interesting proposition.
[GOTEN] Huh?
Yep! That's right!
Now look, you...
You're cooked!
I'm going to win this thing
without using one of my arms!
Come on, Trunks!
You wouldn't have a chance!
Ahh! You! You can't
beat me with one arm!
[TRUNKS] No left arm!
[TRUNKS growls]
[grunting]
[GOTEN] No fair!
[NARRATOR] The two young
warriors faught passionately
to the end, when Goten
made a head-on attack
that would determine the match.
[GOTEN] Here I come!
[GOTEN yells]
[TRUNKS] What?!
[GOTEN screams]
[NARRATOR] A victor has emerged!
Young Trunks is the new
Junior World Champion!
And now it's time for him to
fight an exhibition match
with the reigning World
Champion himself, Mr. Satan.
[ANNOUNCER] Ladies
and gentlemen,
we are proud to bring
to you an exhibition match
between Trunks, the new
Junior World Champion,
and Mr Satan, the greatest
Martial Arts expert alive!
[CROWD cheers]
Mr. Satan!
[ANNOUNCER] That's right, fans!
Give it up for Mr. Satan!
Let's get him out here!
[MR. SATAN whimpers]
Yeah! What a strong junior
and over three feet tall!
It's going to take
everything you have
to win this one, Mr. Satan!
[ATTENDANT laughs]
Well, the truth is,
I don't have a chance
of beating him!
[ATTENDANT laughs]
Yeah, right!
[MR. SATAN laughs]
No, hey, uh,
I'm totally serious...
[BOTH laugh
[ATTENDANT] That's a good one,
sir! You crack me up! Aw, boy!
Whew!
Hey, kid, do you want to
rest before we begin?
[TRUNKS] Nah, I'm fine.
Alright, then.
Ladies and gentlemen!
Introducing... Mr. Satan!
Don't be too hard on him, sir!
--[MR. SATAN squeals]
--[ATTENDANT laughs]
[MR. SATAN whimpers]
Yeah! Mr. Satan rules!
You're the king!
[MAN 3] Show him
how it's done, Champ!
Yeaah!
Alright, you people!
I hope you're ready to rock,
because Mr. Satan's
gonna raise the roof!
[CROWD] Mis-ter Sa-tan!
Mis-ter Sa-tan! Mis-ter Sa-tan!
[MR. SATAN laughs]
Alright, little man!
Are you ready to go
toe-to-toe with the Champ?!
Yeaaah! Ha, ha, alright!
Well, you better watch it, son!
I'm the greatest
fighter of all time!
And I forgot to
bring my kid gloves!
Yeah! Ahhhhh!
[thinking] Now what
am I going to do?!
This kid has
no fear of anything!
[thinking] I wonder if this guy
is as strong as he says he is?
He looks like a big gorilla!
Looks can be deceiving, though.
Hmm...
Tear him apart, Trunks!
You can do it!
[MR. SATAN squeals]
Quiet there, kid!
Watch your mouth!
Let's not encourage
him too much, okay?!
[GOTEN] Huh?
Man! He's just too
pitiful to watch!
Does, uh, anyone else
wanna get something to eat?
Sure, that sounds
good to me.
--Let's do it!
--[VIDEL] Huh?
Hey, wait you guys!
Don't you want to see the fight
between Trunks and my dad?!
He is the reigning
World Champion, you know?
Don't you want to
study his technique?!
Ha, ha! Yeah! Of course we do!
Whatd'ya say, guys?! Sounds like
a great opportunity, huh?!
[GOKU] Thanks, but I
think we'll pass! See ya!
[MR. SATAN] Ohh yeah...
[MR. SATAN]
That's right, c'mon...
[MR. SATAN growls]
[MR. SATAN yells]
[grunting]
[MR. SATAN growls]
[yelling]
[thinking] What in the
world is he doing?!
He couldn't have
been serious just then!
He must be trying to trick me
into thinking that he's weak!
Well, I'm not buying it!
[MR. SATAN squeals]
Hey, kid! Let's
take it easy, okay?!
This is just an
exhibition match!
Right?! We're not
supposed to be too serious!
Exhibition means
a pretend fight!
See?! Huh?
No way! I'm going
to try my best!
[MR. SATAN gasps]
You little runt!
Don't you get it?!
It's not supposed
to be a real match!
I'm going for the win, jerk!
No, no!! Don't you understand
what I'm trying to say?!
Exhibition matches
are make-believe!
[TRUNKS] Whatever.
--[MR. SATAN growls]
--It looks like they're both
ready to get this
match underway!
Let's hear it for these
two great warriors!
If that were my son,
I wouldn't even let him
in the ring with Mr. Satan!
No way! Sheesh!
I'm with you, friend!
His parents must be insane
to let him in there!
Kick his butt, Trunks! Yeah!
[thinking]
This is like a bad dream!
Huh...?
[MR. SATAN] Yowwrrgghh!
[ANNOUNCER yells]
Oh no! It looks like
Mr. Satan is down!
And he's in some
really serious pain!
Oooh!
Don't worry about me, I'm fine!
Just an old knee injury
from fighting Cell!
[MR. SATAN whimpers]
Whoa! Did you hear that, folks?
A knee injury from Cell!
Really! I'll be just fine!
It pops out of place sometimes!
I... I can fix it!
Just give me a few minutes!
Oh no, you're going to
have to have it looked at!
Bring out the doctor! Emergency!
Got it! It popped
right back into place!
It's painful but it
works like a charm!
Now then, let's get this
ridiculous exhibition
match over with!
Shall we continue then?!
Okay...
[ANNOUNCER] Amazing! It's fixed!
Mr. Satan has popped his knee
back into place and
he's ready to fight!
[thinking]
Wh-What am I going to do?!
Heroes don't get beat up
by small children!
My reputation!
Everything I've worked for!
Gone! All gone!
People are going to laugh at me!
Nooooo!
I'm not going to let it happen!
He's just a kid!
I'll outsmart the little rascal!
Let the match begin!
Whoa-whoa-Whoa!
Wait just a second!
Good luck, kid!
May the best man win!
Hey, let's make real sure not
to hit each other really hard
when we're doing
the Champions' gGreeting
at the beginning of the match!
Champions' Greeting?
That's right!
World Champions
have a special way of
greeting each other
before a match!
It's like a punch, only super
soft, right in the face!
Get it?! Little tiny touch!
Right there on the cheek!
Except with fists! Okay...?
Now remember, kid!
When you think "Champions'
Greeting", think soft!
Am I clear?! Do you understand?
I think so! It sounds
simple enough!
Yeah!
[MR. SATAN] Alright!
We're ready whenever you are!
[MR. SATAN laughs]
[MR. SATAN]
Just discussing strategy!
This one's a real firecracker!
Reminds me of myself
when I was his age!
Wow... Tender moments...
Alrighty then! Here
we go, sports fans!
Our champ has given
the thumbs up!
Without further delay,
let the match begin!
Yeah! Oh yeah! Let's do it!
Egads! Look at that!
In the confident style
of a true champion, Trunks is
being offered a free shot!
Now that's a fighter,
ladies and gentlemen!
What a class act!
--How great!
--Hang in there, kid!
[MR. SATAN] It's time
for the greeting, kid!
[MR. SATAN groans]
[MR. SATAN yells]
[ANNOUNCER whimpers]
But...
One punch, it's, uh...
Father!
Ahh, darn it, Trunks!
Why'd you have to go and
do something like that?!
[TRUNKS] Hmph.
[ANNOUNCER] Wow! Oooh!
[ANNOUNCER gasps]
[GOTEN] Huh?
[ANNOUNCER] Oh, my goodness!
Mr. Satan's out cold!
Oh, Dad!
[MR. SATAN grunts]
[ANNOUNCER] Wait! Wait a minute!
He's getting up!
[MR. SATAN laughs]
What a punch! Man!
Yeah! He beat me up
fair and square! Yep!
What a great little fighter!
Well! That's it! Young Trunks
has defeated Mr. Satan!
Wow! What a guy!
He let the kid win, didn't he?!
Heck yeah! That kid
didn't have a chance!
Now that's what I call
a hero, alright!
[MR. SATAN] Thank you!
Thank you! I love you all!
[TRUNKS] Hm?!
[ATTENDANT laughs]
Satan... You're always
so full of surprises!
Come on.
You didn't really think that
I would fight a kid, did you?
[thinking] I can't
figure that guy out!
Is he super strong
and just lost on purpose?
Or is he just a
stupid weakling?!
[FAN 2] Alright,
Hercule! You rule!
[MR. SATAN sighs]
[MR. SATAN yells]
The pain! The pain!
Oh, I can't stand it!
Oh, I just wanna die!
I hate that kid!
Ahhh! The pain!
Well, congratulations, Trunks!
You're stronger than the
World Champion, kid!
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER] Ladies
and gentlemen...
The main event, the World
Martial Arts Championship,
will begin in just
thirty minutes!
And don't forget to visit one
of our concession stands
during the intermission!
We've got cold drinks,
chili dogs,
and mouth-watering nachos!
I've had those nachos. Yuck!
Yeah, no joke! You've got
one day, you gotta eat well!
Hey, there's the waiting
area for the athletes!
They always have
good food in these places!
Whoa! Hold on!
The general public's
not allowed in here!
This is for qualifiers only!
Heeey, relax man!
We are qualifiers!
We all passed
the qualifying test,
and with flying colors
I might add...
Ohh? We'll see about that!
Names please! You first!
I'm Goku.
The name is Krillin.
Number 18.
Vegeta.
Majunior!
Huh...? "Majunior"?
Yeah, I thought
I'd go undercover.
Protect my identity
a little bit.
Oh, yeah. Sure, I get it.
Alright! Looks good!
Your names are
on the list!
Welcome to the
athlete's resort area!
You can take a sauna or a
whirlpool bath,
have a massage, play ping-pong
or enjoy our buffet style lunch!
Make yourselves at home!
[KRILLIN] Gee, thanks!
[GOKU] Yeah! That's really nice.
[VEGETA] Well,
I'd say it's about time
we got some special treatment!
[KRILLIN] Well, they
do make their money
'cause people
wanna see us fight!
Speaking of money,
think you can save some of
that prize money for me, Goku?
Well, you don't have to worry.
I don't need money
where I'm going.
Can't take it with you, huh?
Well, as your good friend,
I'd be happy to look
after your winnings.
No thanks. Why don't you
come to Other World with me?
What, no way! I'm married now,
bro! This is the good life!
Right, babe?
Goon.
[LADY REPORTER] Has anyone ever
told you how cute you are?
[TRUNKS] No.
So Brief is your last name!
Trunks Brief! I like it!
He's gonna be a
real heart-throb!
That's for sure!
Do you have any words for
your fellow countrymen
as the new Junior World
Martial Arts Champion?
Uhh, anything?
[TRUNKS] No.
What is your favorite
T.V. show, Trunks?!
Hey, Trunks! What was it like
fighting against the Champ?!
Ahh! Ask him!
He's coming out!
--[REPORTERS] Huh?!
--[TRUNKS] Goten!
[GOTEN] Huh? Oh, ha, ha!
Huh?! Look! There he goes!
[REPORTERS] Huh?!
[REPORTERS] Trunks, come back!
We haven't gotten
our interview yet!
[TRUNKS &amp; GOTEN grunt]
Reporters... They're
just rude people.
Yeah, whew.
Hey, don't forget your promise!
You've gotta give me
three of your toys, right?!
Ahh... Yes, I do.
But we have more important
things to talk about!
Huh?!
Yeah, think!
Wouldn't it be cool to fight
in the big championships?
Well, yeah! But are
we allowed to do that?!
[TRUNKS] Well, hmm...
[GOKU slurps]
[WAITER 1] There you are, sir.
Whew! This is good stuff!
Ugh... You know, I...
don't think I'll ever
get used to this...
Man, Goku. You sure
eat a lot for a dead guy.
You know, that's exactly what
King Kai always tells me!
But what can I say?
I just love to eat!
[KRILLIN] You're tellin' me...
Cool! It's chow time!
[GOKU] Gohan! Hey! Alright!
How did it go, guys?
[GOHAN] It was
pretty interesting!
Trunks beat Mr. Satan
with one punch!
[GOKU] Really?!
But everyone thinks that he
lost the match on purpose
just to be a gentleman!
[KRILLIN] Hmph!
What a guy, huh?!
He should get an
Academy Award for that one!
And just what do
you mean by that?!
You don't know Krillin!
He's always joking like that!
[GOHAN laughs]
Isn't that right?! You never
know when to stop, do you?!
[KRILLIN] That's right!
Now let go, please!
[VIDEL] Hmm...
Hey, guys! We ordered
for you already!
Pull up a chair!
It's really good!
Alright! Great! I'm famished!
Hey, Dad! We're out of pasta!
'Scuse me! More
spaghetti please!
[VEGETA] And bring some more
eggrolls while you're at it!
Good grief! You Saiyans are
like bottomless pits, I swear!
What's a Saiyan?
Krillin! Hello?!
[KRILLIN] Oops!
I'm sorry, Gohan!
I'm just not going
to talk anymore!
Yup, lips are sealed!
[GOKU] Mmmm, ahhhh!
That was incredible!
What a feast!
[GOKU] Woweee! I'm so full!
If I have to fight
one of you guys,
please don't punch
me in the gut!
You didn't eat anything!
You must be on a diet!
[KRILLIN] Believe
it or not, Gohan!
Most athletes don't like
to stuff themselves
before a big match!
[ANDROID 18] Hey, we should
go check the draw.
See who's fighting who.
[VEGETA] Well, if I have to
fight Kakarot the first round,
the first thing I'm going
to do is punch him in the gut!
--[PICCOLO] Hm?
--[GOKU] Aw, man! No mercy!
Huh...?
Hey, Gohan!
I'm picking up some
weird vibes from these guys!
Good afternoon.
You wouldn't be Goku by
any chance, would you?
Yeah. How did you know
that my name is Goku?
Well, your reputation as a
great fighter precedes you.
I was actually hoping for a
chance to fight you
during the tournament.
It's not that I'm confident
about beating you. Not at all.
It's just that I want to have
the greatest challenge
that I can think of,
and I know you're a man
who understands that.
Well then, It was
a real pleasure.
I'm honored...
And I'm very much looking
forward to today's competition.
I've traveled very far
for this opportunity
to meet you in battle.
You might even say that
I'm one of your biggest fans.
In any case, after meeting you,
I'm certain that I
won't be disappointed.
[GOKU] Gosh, thanks!
Goku, may I shake your hand?
Huh? Yeah, of course!
[chuckling]
Huh...?
Alright! Thank you. You're as
brave as everyone says you are.
[GOKU] Uhh...
Good day.
[GOKU] Hey, wait a second!
I didn't catch your name!
I don't like the feel
of it. They're strong.
Real strong...
But, hey, isn't that what
this tournament's about?
Finding the unexpected challenge
and seeing who
emerges as the victor?
[VEGETA] Hm!
Gee, I don't know...
They don't seem all
that strong to me, guys.
To tell the truth,
I don't think they know
what they're getting
themselves into.
[VEGETA] Well, we'll find
out soon enough, won't we?
I, for one, will be more than
happy to take on either
of those two clowns.
[NARRATOR]
Two strangers have appeared
at the World Martial
Arts Tournament.
What does their
eerie presence portend?
Are they really as strong
as Goku says they are?
On the next episode
of Dragon Ball Z!