[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Piccolo went one on one with
the diabolical Android 20!
Brave as ever, Piccolo stood
firm in the face of danger,
even as the evil Android
unleashed a powerful attack!
But Piccolo was ready
with an attack of his own!
Try as he might, Android 20
seemed incapable
of penetrating
Piccolo's defenses!
[ANDROID 20 growls]
Your desire to kill
is killing you!
[PICCOLO grunts]
[ANDROID 20 whimpers]
[NARRATOR] Outnumbered
and obviously outmatched,
Android 20's chances for
survival were growing slim!
His only option:
a hasty retreat!
[ANDROID 20 thinking] It
would be wise for me to return
to the lab at once!
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, Trunks
raced to the scene,
and when he arrived,
the young Saiyan
made a startling revelation.
[TRUNKS] Yeah. Even though
I've never seen him before...
I can tell that he's one
of Dr. Gero's creations!
[NARRATOR] Vegeta couldn't
believe his ears.
And neither could anyone else!
[GOHAN] Wha?
Yeah, no doubt...
[NARRATOR] Incredible as it
may seem, the two Androids
that Vegeta and Piccolo have
fought so hard to defeat
are not the same Androids that
plague Trunks' future world!
But if this mechanical menace
isn't one of the Androids
Trunks had warned
about, who is he?
Find out on today's exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!
--[GOHAN] Uhh...
--[KRILLIN] Wha...
What did he say? Those
weren't the Androids?!
[thinking] What?!
[VEGETA] Huh?!
It can't be!
[TRUNKS] Hmm...
[ANDROID 20 growls]
Check it out!
I'm glad I wasn't here to see
whatever made a mess like that!
Look! I think I can
see them up there.
We'd better go down there and
see if those guys need our help.
There's no way we're
going down there!
[BULMA] Don't worry
so much, Yajirobe!
Goku won't let
anything happen to us!
If you go down any
further, I'll...
I'll throw Trunks
out the window!
Oh? Really?
I don't think Vegeta
would like you talking
about his son like that.
[YAJIROBE gasps]
Well... I... uh...
I didn't mean, uh... I would
never, eh... I was gonna, uh...
I think, uh...
Let's just go.
[BULMA] That's more like it.
No... Nonsense...
If that's not the android
you warned us about,
then who is it?!
Hey, Vegeta, cut the kid a
little slack, would ya'?
So a few of the things he
told us about changed.
Maybe this did too.
We found two androids
just like he said we would.
Does it really matter that
they don't look the same?
Hmm?
[TIEN] I hope you're right...
[thinking] It is time I
returned to the laboratory.
But if I try to
fly through them,
they are bound to capture me.
I must hasten my retreat!
If I do not repair myself
soon, I will be finished!
Hm?
[KRILLIN] Huh?
Hey, Gohan, look! There's
Bulma and Yajirobe!
[GOHAN] Uh?
Hello!
Oh no! That android's
still down there!
I told you we
shouldn't have come!
Dr. Gero...?
What are you doing?!
Don't come down here!
Perfect...
Enjoy this short-lived
victory while you are able,
for soon I will unleash Androids
17 and 18 to destroy you all!
Seventeen...?
And Eighteen...?
[TRUNKS gasps]
[TIEN growls]
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN gasp]
[ANDROID 20 laughs]
[TRUNKS growls]
[BULMA &amp; YAJIROBE scream]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[PICCOLO] He's asking for it!
[TIEN growls]
[BABY TRUNKS wails]
[BULMA screams]
Wow! I'm still alive...
Where's my baby?!
--Oh... There you are...
--[BABY TRUNKS cries]
--Oh, thank you!
He's safe. Trunks!
[TRUNKS gasps]
[VEGETA] Impossible!
The Android! He vanished!
Blast it! Rrgh!
Where'd he go?!
[VEGETA growls]
--[GOHAN] Bulma!
--[KRILLIN] Are you all right?
We're okay, guys!
This young man saved us!
[KRILLIN] That's great!
[GOHAN] Yeah!
[TRUNKS growls]
[VEGETA] You'll never get
away from me, Android!
[VEGETA growls]
--[TRUNKS growls]
--Huh...?
Hey! Why didn't you try
to save them, Vegeta?!
Who?
[TRUNKS] Who?!
Bulma and your son!
Oh... them...
I have more important
things to worry about
than that foolish woman
and her blasted child!
Now, out of my way!
[VEGETA thinking]
I know I would've spotted
that infernal android if
he had taken to the air.
He must be sticking
close to the ground,
using these narrow canyons
to conceal his escape.
That means he's on foot...
And if he's on foot, he
can't have gotten very far!
So, that funny-looking
old guy with the mustache
was one of the Androids?
--Huh?
--[BABY TRUNKS cries]
Oh, there, there now...
Yeah. Sure was, Bulma.
Time to turn that
frown upside down!
[BULMA giggles]
Well, I think that
"Android" was Dr. Gero.
--Yes he was!
--[BABY TRUNKS cries]
--He was Dr. Gero!
I've seen his
picture before.
In one of my dad's
science magazines.
Of course, it looks like he's
changed a lot since then...
[BABY TRUNKS babbles]
And speaking of "change"...
[YAJIROBE grunts]
Some... help... please!
[KRILLIN] Heeeey!
Bulma says the Android
is really Dr. Gero!
[TRUNKS] Dr. Gero...?
[PICCOLO gasps]
[TIEN gasps]
Dr. Gero?!
How could you possibly
know a thing like that?!
I! Know! What! I! Saw, Vegeta!
It was a picture of that old guy
in one of my dad's
science magazines,
and underneath it in big, bold
letters it said "Dr. Gero"!
--[BULMA] There, now...
--[BABY TRUNKS cries]
--Don't cry...
--Shhh... that's my boy.
--[VEGETA growls]
--It's okay... Oh! Oh!
--[BABY TRUNKS cries]
Well, it was an easy
mistake, Vegeta.
What?!
[BULMA] With all of the
modifications Dr. Gero
made to himself, it's hard
to tell he was ever human.
It's really amazing
what he's done!
Too bad I read
he's such a jerk.
Now, now...
You told us a pack of lies!
Curse you, boy!
You said Dr. Gero was destroyed
by the Androids he created!
You didn't tell us he'd
turned himself into one!
[TRUNKS] The timeline as
I know it must have shifted
when I traveled here
from the future!
Oh, man...
I was afraid that this
might happen, but...
But it was a calculated
risk that I had to take!
[PICCOLO] Dr. Gero mentioned
two more Androids on the way.
They could be the
ones you told us about
the last time you were here.
[GOHAN] Huh?
But this time, I think
it would be a good idea
for you to tell us
what they look like!
We don't want to make
the same mistake twice.
[TRUNKS] The androids that I
know were created by Dr. Gero,
to be sure. But unlike the
clumsy androids you met today,
these two are
sleek and graceful.
Android 18 is designed to look
like a beautiful young girl.
Android 17 is a young boy
who wears a red scarf
and has long, dark hair.
But they both have the
same cruel, lifeless eyes.
Yes, it's their eyes that
will haunt me the most.
Man, these things
sound pretty mean!
Well, that's one
way of putting it.
These Androids are ruthless!
They seek only
to hurt and destroy!
Do they absorb energy
like the first two?
Huh?!
No. These two don't need to.
Their energy, it
lasts... forever...
[VEGETA] What?!
That's preposterous! They have
to run out of energy sometime!
--[TRUNKS growls]
--[BABY TRUNKS cries]
[BULMA] Aww... It's all right...
[BULMA coos]
Hey... How come Goku
isn't here right now?
Well, he came down with
that weird heart virus.
He went home for the
antidote that you gave him.
I thought you knew.
I can't believe history
has slipped this much!
[GOKU groans]
Oh, Goku! Please, don't give up!
Man! I hope we didn't give
him the antidote too late!
You've got to fight it, Goku!
[GOKU screams]
[CHICHI sobs]
No, please no!
--[GOKU yells]
--[CHICHI sobs]
[thinking] Those fools!
When I activate 17 and 18,
Piccolo and Vegeta
will understand
once and for all
the awesome power
of my creations!
[BULMA screams]
How dare you, Vegeta! Ugh!
Every time you stick
your geeky little face
in front of Trunks
you make him cry!
--[BULMA growls]
--[VEGETA growls]
[KRILLIN chuckles]
--It's all right...
--[BABY TRUNKS cries]
Your Daddy's not going to scare
you with that ugly mug of his.
Bulma, will you forget about
the child for one minute?
Do you know where
Dr. Gero's lab is?
What? What lab?
[VEGETA growls]
[BULMA] Hmm...
Well, now that you
mention it,
I think I remember reading
that Dr. Gero's lab
was hidden in a cave somewhere
just outside North City...
[BABY TRUNKS babbles]
I'll bet it's too late
to follow him there.
He's probably long gone!
Maybe not! Nobody saw
him fly away, did they?!
Huh...?
Uh... So what're you saying?
I'm saying that android
is trying to escape on foot!
Which means he probably
hasn't gotten very far!
If that's the case, then we
might just have a chance
to find this lab and destroy
the other two androids
before Gero even gets there!
--[VEGETA] Hmph!
--[KRILLIN gasps]
I would never do
anything that cowardly!
Huh...?
Only one course of action
can possibly satisfy me!
I will fight these
androids face-to-face!
And I will break them
with my bare hands!
No!
Huh?
You must never underestimate
the power of these androids!
If you really want
to destroy them,
we have to do this
Piccolo's way!
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA chuckles]
Listen! Don't go!
You won't be able to handle
the androids by yourself!
We have to wait for Goku!
Listen, I will only
say this once!
I do not have to
wait for Kakarot!
I am a Super Saiyan now, and I'm
stronger than that pathetic fool
could ever
dream of becoming!
Now out of my way!
[TRUNKS growls]
Man, he's such a jerk.
I must admit, now that Vegeta's
become a Super Saiyan,
he may actually be
stronger than Goku.
Perhaps he does have a chance
at beating the Androids
single-handedly.
[TRUNKS] No, I'm afraid he
doesn't have a chance.
And I know that...
because in my world,
these two androids have
already killed Vegeta!
Well I won't let
it happen again!
I won't let my father die!
"Father"...?
Did he say father?
[BABY TRUNKS babbles]
What did he mean by that?
There's something you
should know, Bulma.
That boy...
is Trunks.
And he is Vegeta's son.
He's the boy the baby you
are holding in your arms
eventually grows up to be.
Whaaaat?!
[KRILLIN whimpers]
Oh man, wow!
[BABY TRUNKS babbles]
Gosh... Who'dve guessed?
[KRILLIN] You know,
now that you mention it,
they do sort of look alike.
But how totally weird!
I mean, we all met Trunks two
years before he was born!
[BULMA squeaks]
I think it's time we started
searching for Dr. Gero's
laboratory, you guys.
We don't have long
if we want to get to those other
two androids before he does.
[TIEN] Mm...
I'm in.
Right!
[BULMA] Hm... Huh...? Hmm...
Well, Trunks, at least
we know you'll grow up
to be a handsome
young man!
And think!
All of this time, I was worried
that you'd look like your Dad.
Uhh...
Hey, Bulma?
Could you tell my Dad about all
this next time you see him?
And ask him to hurry here
as soon as he gets better!
I would, but it looks
like I'm stuck here!
That android totalled my plane!
Well, I think it would be best
if you took Bulma home, Gohan.
We should be able to handle
the androids without you.
O-Okay. But be careful...
[PICCOLO] All right,
guys! Let's go!
We're really going to
have to move fast!
--Right.
--Right!
Well, we'd better get going.
Not too fast.
We have a baby on board.
[YAJIROBE] Hey!
What about me?!
Huh...?
[YAJIROBE] I could
use a hand here!
Come on! Hurry!
[ANDROID 20 thinking]
I have run far enough.
I should be able
to fly at this point
without any fear of being seen.
--[ANDROID 20 chuckles]
--[beeping]
[ANDROID 20] Huh?!
[ANDROID 20 growls]
[thinking] Vegeta!
[ANDROID 20 thinking] But how
did he follow me this far?!
Hmm...?
[ANDROID 20 thinking]
They both followed me!
How did they know
which way I was going?
Wait...
Is it possible they are
headed for my laboratory?
No, it must be a coincidence!
Yes, it has to be
coincidence!
There is no way they could
know the location of my lab!
Only a few scientists in the
world possess that information.
Wait!
[ANDROID 20 thinking]
That girl! Bulma!
She is the
daughter of Dr. Brief,
the president of
Capsule Corporation!
She may have learned
of me from her father!
Huh?
[ANDROID 20 gasps]
[thinking] They ARE heading
for my laboratory!
I should never have told
them about 17 and 18.
If they find my androids
before I activate them,
they will try to
destroy them!
No! I cannot let that happen!
Fortunately, even
Dr. Brief does not know
the precise
location of my lab.
I may still get there
before they find it!
[BULMA] Gohan...? I, uhh...
I think it's safe if you
want to go a little faster?
[TRUNKS growls]
Your father, Trunks?
Well, he was a man
of amazing talents.
You wouldn't believe some of the
incredible things he could do.
[BULMA sighs]
[BULMA] But he was a proud man,
and sort of a hard
man to know...
And he never showed any
affection to anyone; even me.
That man never once told
me he cared about me...
But... I could tell...
[TRUNKS growls]
So, you think you
can keep up, boy?
[VEGETA chuckles]
Let's see...
[VEGETA yells]
[TRUNKS growls]
[thinking] It's still
hard for me to believe
that he could be a
Super Saiyan at his age.
But then again, he is my son!
[birds cawing]
[GOHAN grunting]
Darn it!
You're weighing
us down, Yajirobe!
Shut up!
[NARRATOR] While Gohan struggles
with his heavy load,
the rest of our heroes
are headed straight
for Dr. Gero's lab.
But what new evils
await them there?
Find out in the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!