[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Gohan trained Videl and Goten
in the secret art of flying.
[NARRATOR] After learning to
concentrate her energy,
Videl worked on using this
power to lift into the air.
It was a lesson learned
with impressive speed,
as what she lacked in experience
was made up for with
strength and determination.
[GOHAN] That's incredible,
Videl!
No one learns how to
fly on their first day!
Is that a fact?
[GOTEN] A birdie! A birdie!
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, Vegeta and
Trunks did training of their own
in an enhanced gravity room.
And Vegeta learned a
surprising ability of his son...
[VEGETA] So what
are you going to do?
Guess I'll go... Super!
Huh?!
[TRUNKS yells]
[NARRATOR] The preparations
are in the works,
and the tournament day is near.
[VEGETA] When was it that the
transformation to the legendary
warrior of the Saiyan race
was reduced to a
children's plaything?!
[VIDEL giggles]
[VIDEL] Look, Gohan!
I'm higher than the trees!
[GOHAN] Yeah!
You soak this stuff up
like a sponge!
[VIDEL laughs]
[GOHAN] Now we can work
on the harder moves!
[laughing continues]
[GOTEN] Hah! Yeah!
[GOTEN laughs]
[VIDEL] So... how long does
it take to fly around like that?
Um... Well...
It just depends on
the person, really.
I won't stop
'til I fly like him!
Ah? Uhh...
Hold on just a second...
This is so awesome! Yeaah!
[GOTEN laughs]
[GOTEN] Whoa!
Hey, bro... Try to slow it
down while Videl's here,
--could ya?
--But how come?
Just do it for me, okay?!
[VIDEL] Problem?
No! Just gave him
a little advice!
[VIDEL sighs]
It's break time...
[VIDEL] Listen...
I'd rather you don't tell
my dad about these lessons.
I want it to be a surprise
at the tournament, okay?
Sure! Don't worry.
I never run into him!
And that's for good reason!
If he knew I was hanging out
at a boy's house...
Well, I know exactly
what he would say...
I forbid it! You find a boy
who's stronger than I am
and then maybe I'll consider!
I mean, maybe I'll consider...
He says it 'cause he knows
there aren't any boys like that.
I mean, he saved the
whole world with his strength.
You're a pretty tough
guy, Gohan.
But you can hardly say
something like that!
[GOHAN laughs]
Videl...
Has your dad ever let you have
practice matches with him?
Come on, are you kidding?
He's the World Champion!
He'd tear me apart!
Dad doesn't even let me
watch him train now!
It's all a secret.
[GOHAN laughs]
[thinking] Yeah, no wonder.
He doesn't want Videl to know
she's stronger than he is!
So, um...
In the extremely unlikely
chance that someone, say,
beats your father...
You think you'd freak out?
I wish he'd lose!
This fame has gone
to Dad's head!
I know mom's been
gone for a while...
but that doesn't mean he
can go flouncing everywhere
with these silly women!
If he got beat,
they'd all disappear!
[GOHAN laughs]
[thinking] Perfect!
Now I can beat her dad
without feeling guilty!
[VIDEL] But unfortunately
that'll never happen.
My Dad's too strong
for his own good.
Now I've got a question:
Who taught you
these martial arts?
Well... First someone named
Piccolo and then my dad...
So, if your dad knows a
few fighting techniques
how come you've never
introduced him to me?
--My dad's not with us.
--But he's gonna be soon!
The lady's bringing him
back from the dead,
so he can play at
the big tournament!
What? What's back from
the dead? And what lady?
What do you mean?
Clamp it, Goten!
You're not supposed to
talk about that!
[GOTEN gasps]
Oh! I get it! Your
parents are now divorced!
And he's with a new woman!
And she's bringing
him to the tournament
so he can fight and win money!
Is that right?
[GOHAN] Hm?
[VIDEL] Oh yeah...
Seems we both have trouble
with parents. Mm-hmm.
I... guess...
All the more reason
we have to work together!
[MR. SATAN] Hey, you!
Servant guy!
Has Videl come in yet?!
[SERVANT] No sir.
The Mistress is still out.
She said she had errands to run.
[MR. SATAN growls]
[MR. SATAN] Errands my foot!
She's probably with
a boy right now!
[NARRATOR] The days roll on, and
Videl's long training sessions
are starting to pay off.
--[GOTEN yells]
--[VIDEL] Oh!
Sorry about that, Goten!
[VIDEL laughs]
[thinking] Videl is really
something special.
She's nearly mastered flying
after only ten days of practice!
Guess that does it, Videl!
You've graduated flying school!
Thanks a lot, Gohan.
Now I can go home and
finish off my training
in time for the tournament.
Yeah, me too...
Well, I'm off.
Hey, wow!
I bet I can fly home this way!
Yup.
Goodbye, boys! I'll
see you at the big match!
--Goodbye, Videl!
--[GOTEN laughs]
[GOTEN] Bye!
Finally, she's gone!
[GOHAN] Hey...
She's not so bad...
But yeah... Now that
it's just the two of us,
we can start our real
training sessions together!
Yeah!
Let's go!
[NARRATOR] The World Martial
Arts Tournament is days away,
and fighters all over the world
are entering their final
stretch of training.
[VEGETA grunting]
[NARRATOR] There are Vegeta,
and Trunks...
[TRUNKS] Nine thousand one...
Nine thousand two...
Nine thousand three...
Nine thousand four...
[NARRATOR] There is Piccolo...
[PICCOLO growls]
[low rumbling]
[MR. POPO] The floor is shaking!
[PICCOLO growls]
[KRILLIN grunting]
[NARRATOR] Even Krillin...
[grunting continues]]
[thinking] Oh, my
family's watching...
Okay, Krillin, look tough!
[KRILLIN grunting]
[NARRATOR] And,
of course, Videl.
She's... been at
it for an hour!
Still going!
Man, I wish I had
that kind of power...
[TRAINERS gasp]
[VIDEL] Would ya
put another one up?
Uhhh... Yeah!
Hey, Daddy...
Oh, hello Videl.
Shouldn't you be getting ready?
There's no need for it.
They should probably just send
the prize medal to my mailbox!
[MR. SATAN laughs]
[BOTH grunting]
[grunting continues]
[GOTEN growls]
[BOTH grunting]
[GOHAN yells,
GOTEN screams]
[GOTEN grunts]
No fair... As hard as I try,
I still can't beat you!
Hey, I've been
doing this a lot longer
than you have, little guy!
But those were some nice
moves you pulled!
Do you think our father's
really going to be there?
Guess it's gonna be your
first time to see him, isn't it?
You nervous?
Yeah...
The arrangements
have been made.
Is Goku ready for his
grand re-entrance?
[KING KAI] He's up there...
He finished his training
a few days ago.
Now he is training his mind
with intense meditation.
[VEGETA] I've ridden Galactic
Slugs faster than this vehicle!
[BULMA] Oh, hush!
So... Is Goku really
going to show up?
He'll be there! I know it!
Heh, heh! When has Goku
ever let us down before?
Of course he'll be there!
So, Krillin, I bet he'll
hardly recognize you
with your goofy hairdo!
Hey... It's stylish!
[OX-KING and YAMCHA laugh]
I forgot just how funny
you guys are together!
[OX-KING laughs]
Crack me up!
Are you going to be
competing too, Yamcha?
[YAMCHA] Me? Nah,
I'd just embarrass myself.
I gave up fighting...
So, listen Vegeta-- And this
goes for you kids too...
I think we should all agree
to not turn into Super
Saiyans during the fights.
What for?!
That's a good idea!
If people see you
guys transform,
there's a good chance
they'll recognize you
from the broadcasts
of the Cell Games!
And after that! Well...
The journalists would
get all your names
off of the entry forms and--
OH!-- TV cameras would be
all over my front yard!
Yeah, then you'd all know
what I have to deal with
in high school!
It's a real mess!
[VEGETA] I don't
see the problem.
When the journalists come,
I'll just destroy them!
[BULMA] Vegeta! Would
you behave yourself?
Fine... It's settled...
There'll be no Super Saiyan
transformations
in the battles...
Of course, I'll still
have the advantage.
That's okay
with us, Dad!
Yeah!
Alright! Thanks, everyone!
That sure is good news for me!
Heck, maybe this way
I'll stand a chance!
[KRILLIN laughs]
[KRILLIN] Y'know, fighting
a Super Saiyan is like
trying to fight a steamroller
with your hands tied!
--[KRILLIN laughs]
--[VEGETA] Pipe down!
[KRILLIN] Oh, sorry.
[BULMA gasps]
Look, guys! I see it!
There's the island
where the World Martial Arts
Tournament is taking place!
Ahhh... It's game time!
Hey!
Guess I better
complete my outfit now!
[GOHAN laughs]
Uhh...
[MARRON] Huh?
Hey, Gohan...
Are you really gonna
wear that thing to fight?
Yeah! This way they
won't recognize me!
Do I look cool or what?!
--Uh, yeah... "cool".
--[GOHAN laughs]
[PUAR giggles]
Ah, gee, look at all that
stuff! It's like a world fair!
You know I can't stand
to be around crowds.
I wonder if Goku's here...
[CROWD cheering]
--[GOHAN &amp; BULMA] Hmm?
--[OX-KING] What?!
[BOY] Wait for me! I saw him
first! I wanna get there first!
I want an autograph!
Oh, look guys, our hero! The
man who saved us all from Cell
'cause we were
too weak, remember?!
Do they really
believe that? Mr. Satan...
He sure does like to
ham it up, doesn't he?
[OOLONG] I hear you know
his daughter, Gohan!
--[CROWD cheering]
--[BODYGUARDS grunting]
[CROWD roars]
[MR. SATAN] Yeaah!
--[MR. SATAN whoops and yells]
--[CROWD cheers]
[MR. SATAN yells]
Loyal fans all over
the world, wait no more!
Your hero has arrived!
Mr. Satan, do you believe
you'll have any competition?
[MR. SATAN laughs]
Let's just say my
chances of winning
are about one hundred
and twenty percent!
We've heard that your daughter
is also taking part!
Videl, what will you do if
you have to fight your Dad?
Oh, I don't know...
guess I'll punch?
[MR. SATAN laughs]
Don't be silly, Videl!
[YAMCHA chuckles]
Old fool still hasn't
changed a bit.
Forget about him, Yamcha.
I'd much rather
track down my dad.
I don't sense Goku here,
but someone else we know is.
[GOTEN] Huh? Look!
It's Mister Piccolo!
Wow! He showed up!
[GOHAN] Hello, Piccolo!
I don't suppose you've
seen my father yet?
Not yet. But he'll be here.
That outfit... You're really
going to fight in that?
Of course!
Oh, where in the
world could Goku be?
Gosh, maybe they just weren't
able to bring him back!
I'll go comb the area!
Yeah! Me too.
[ALL] Huh?
Hey! I'm back!
Dad! It's you!
Goku...
Whoa! Pinch me!
[GOKU laughs]
You guys have changed
a lot in seven years!
Gohan! You're giant!
[GOHAN laughs]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
Oh... Goku!
[PICCOLO chuckles]
Welcome back to Earth, Goku.
--[OX-KING chuckles]
--It's him...
[YAMCHA laughs,
PUAR giggles]
Oh... Wowzas!
[GOKU] So, guys... are you
just gonna stand there
and stare at me all day?
--[GOHAN] Dad!
--[ALL] Goku!
Oh, sweetheart...
I've missed you...
I've missed you, ChiChi.
Huh?
[GOTEN] Oh!
Goten, it's okay.
Hey!
I think there's a little ME
hiding behind your leg, ChiChi!
I'm Goten.
[OX-KING chuckles]
[GOKU] And I'm Goku.
Hi!
--Daddy!
--Hey!
Whoa, li'l guy!
You're a strong one, aren't you?
[GOKU laughs,
GOTEN chuckles]
[GOKU &amp; GOTEN laugh]
[GOKU] Here you go!
You want to be an airplane?
[GOTEN] Yeah!
[GOKU &amp; GOTEN laugh]
Listen up, Goku.
Remember that you only
have twenty-four hours.
That's all I can do.
[GOKU] Mm-hmm.
Yeah, I know.
--[BABA] I'll see you then.
--[GOKU] Alright.
Thank you, Baba!
Hey! I think we should move
on to the registration desk
before it closes.
[RECEPTIONIST A] Sorry,
what was that name again?
[GOHAN] The Great Saiyaman!
Great... Saiyaman?
That's right!
Huh? Who is that?
[GOHAN] It's my super
hero name! Cool, huh?
Sure! I guess so!
[GOKU laughs]
Next, please!
Ah... Yes...
Another for the junior division!
[TRUNKS gasps]
What's that mean?!
It's for everyone
under 15 years old!
Oh, that's great.
They're sticking us with
all the little kids, Goten!
Huh?!
They've changed it from
the old tournaments.
What a good idea!
Thanks for the offer, man, but
we'll take the adult section!
I'm sorry, but I
can't do that!
There's rules!
But that's boring!
[KRILLIN laughs]
Your attention please!
All competitors come
to the waiting area!
This is your last call!
Now, good luck, Goku
and Gohan and Goten!
I want you boys to do
the best that you can!
Yes!
Don't worry, ChiChi, I'm sure
one of us is gonna win!
[thinking] It's gonna be
great to see Dad fight again!
See you in the finals!
I'll be there!
Don't forget to cheer
for your Daddy, okay?
[MARON] Okay!
[VEGETA] Hmph.
Buh-bye, Mom!
[CHICHI] Bye!
Be careful, okay?
Break a leg!
[NARRATOR]
After all these years,
Goku is back in the
land of the living.
The Z Fighters reassemble,
and the World Martial Arts
Tournament is set to begin.