[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Goku said his
farewells to Frieza,
deciding that the
weakened tyrant,
was no longer a threat
to the Universe!
[GOKU sighs]
[GOKU] Goodbye, Frieza.
May you live the rest
of your life in peace.
"Peace"?!
[NARRATOR] But peace wasn't
quite what Frieza had in mind!
As Goku launched off
towards his ship,
Frieza unleashed
his final attack:
[FRIEZA] Never!
I will never... never...
[NARRATOR] An energy disk that
can cut through anything,
and will follow Goku
wherever he goes!
You truly are a helpless fool!
I gave you one last
chance to live!
[FRIEZA laughs]
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU] And this is
how you repay me?!
[GOKU growls]
[NARRATOR] And so, the epic
battle between good and evil
swings back to life.
But with little time to spare!
Can the enraged Goku
avoid this last attack,
put an end to Frieza, and escape
from Namek before it blows?
[NARRATOR} It's a time bomb
the size of a planet,
on this explosive
episode of Dragon Ball Z!
[FRIEZA thinking] He thinks he
can pull up at the last second
and make the disc hit me!
[FRIEZA giggles]
[FRIEZA laughs]
[thinking] As if
I'm stupid enough
to be cut by my own attack!
You'll have to be much
more clever than that!
[FREIZA yells]
Gotcha!
[FRIEZA growls]
[GOKU] Looking for someone?
An after-image, eh?
That's a pretty good
little trick for a primate.
I don't understand why you call
Saiyans by such mindless names.
The only thing it does is reveal
your own fear and ignorance.
[FRIEZA growls]
I guess name-calling
is your only attack
because you're too weak to
challenge me any other way.
[FRIEZA growls]
[thinking] No one talks
to me like that!
Hmm...
Tell us, King Kai... What now?
[KING KAI] Goku seems
to be in complete control.
Huh?!
Then, you mean
Frieza's gonna lose?
[KING KAI] Yes, Chiaotzu...
It looks like Frieza's on
his last legs, but who cares?!
Maybe Goku is winning! Maybe
he'll beat Frieza after all!
But even if he does, the
planet is going to explode!
And Goku will still be doomed!
So my energy disk wasn't
challenging enough for you, huh?
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[FRIEZA] I guess we'll just
have to raise the stakes!
And double the fun!
As you wish, Frieza...
Give me a break!
Not this stupid routine again!
[birds chirping]
[VEGETA laughs]
[VEGETA chuckling]
Oh, this is too much! One
little explosion and "boom",
Frieza and Kakarot
are both out of my hair!
At last, I'm the most powerful
fighter in the Universe!
[GOHAN growls]
[PICCOLO growls]
[GURU wheezes]
I've waited so long
for this day!
Those years with Frieza,
swallowing my humiliation!
[VEGETA] We followed
Frieza's every command,
like sick, loyal dogs!
[screaming]
[VEGETA] We conquered
entire civilizations,
annihilated millions of people,
just to expand Frieza's empire!
[screaming continues]
[VEGETA laughs]
[VEGETA] Needless to say it was
a job we Saiyans excelled at.
[VEGETA laughs]
[screaming]
[NAPPA] That was great!
[RADITZ] Yes,
but I can't wait
to get to my healing capsule!
All this fighting
has made me sore!
[ALL laughing]
[NAPPA] Can you believe how
fast we banged up that planet?!
I bet Frieza will
give us a huge reward!
[RADITZ] Oh, yes!
[NAPPA &amp; RADITZ laugh]
Greetings, Master Frieza.
We have returned
from the planet Shik.
Everything was
done as you desired.
They pledged loyalty to you
after only three short days.
Hmm...
Did they really?
I'm surprised it took so long.
--[FRIEZA giggles]
--[NAPPA gasps]
[DODORIA &amp; FRIEZA laugh]
[ZARBON chuckles]
Very well, then.
You may go away now.
Huh?!
Hey! Wait! Is that all
you're going say to us?!
[VEGETA gasps]
We just crushed an entire race
of people in only three days!
And all you say is-is--!
Tell me, Zarbon,
how long do you think
it would take you
to conquer a planet like Shik?
Well, I imagine one
full day would be enough.
Really? A whole day?
It is a tiny planet.
[FRIEZA laughs]
[ZARBON chuckles]
[DODORIA chuckles]
[VEGETA growls]
[NAPPA &amp; RADITZ growl]
Is there anything else
you'd like to report to me?
You do understand I have
more significant matters
to attend to?
[NAPPA growls]
You cocky little--!
[NAPPA shouts]
Nappa!
[FRIEZA laughs]
Please excuse us, Master Frieza.
[ZARBON] What more
can you expect...
[ZARBON chuckles]
...from a monkey?
[VEGETA growls]
[NAPPA] I hate this! You
know, I've been hearing
talk about how our
home planet was destroyed.
At first I didn't
believe it, but now...
They say it didn't really
collide with another planet!
Like we thought...
What do you mean?
They say that Frieza did it!
Huh... Why?
Rrrgh... Vegeta, you
have to listen to me!
It was Frieza that
ordered it all!
To have your father killed!
And to blow up our home planet!
[VEGETA] I already knew that.
What? You knew?!
But how can you obey Frieza when
you know what he's done to us?!
[VEGETA] So he killed my father,
destroyed my people...
That means nothing to me now!
Strength is the only thing
that matters in this world.
Huh?
Everything else is just
a delusion for the weak.
There's only one
certainty in life:
[VEGETA] A strong man stands
above and conquers all!
[VEGETA] I know how
strong Frieza is.
There's no way
I can beat him now.
But wait and see,
as the last of the Saiyans,
we have flowing
through our veins
the blood of a warrior race!
The more we fight, the
more powerful we become!
And with each fight, I'll
get stronger and stronger!
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA] And one day I'll be
strong enough to beat Frieza,
and I will rule the Universe!
Exactly as I was meant to...
At last, that
great day has come!
Everyone who would
stop me is already dead!
[VEGETA laughs]
You're wrong about
all that, you know!
My father is coming back alive!
Huh?
[VEGETA chuckles]
[GOHAN growls]
[VEGETA sighs]
You sure do have a
wild imagination, kid.
No, it's the truth!
My dad'll beat Frieza
and come back home
and then
you'll be sorry!
[GOHAN growls]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
Monkey, I do think it would be
wiser for you to keep running!
[FRIEZA laughs]
Because I would just hate to
see you sliced into pieces!
[GOKU grunts]
When will you
ever learn, Frieza?
Please! Can't you try
something a tiny bit different?
[GOKU grunts]
Huh?!
[FRIEZA growls]
[FRIEZA] Nothing
but a lucky shot!
Now where'd that monkey go?!
[GOKU growls]
[FRIEZA grunts]
[FRIEZA growls]
[grunting]
[GOKU grunts]
[FRIEZA yells]
[FRIEZA grunts]
[GOKU] I'm gonna slap
some sense into you!
[FRIEZA grunting]
Oh yeah! Okay! Give it to
him, Goku! Oh boy! Uh-huh!
Make him really feel it!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
[FRIEZA yells]
[GOKU yells]
[FRIEZA gasps]
[FRIEZA grunts]
It's time to finish this
fight once and for all!
Hey! Look out behind you!
Get down now!
Huh...?
[GOKU gasps]
My own attack...
[KING KAI screams]
Just tell us, King Kai,
we can handle it!
It's Goku! He's
been defeated, right?
[KING KAI] Umm, no...
Let's just say Frieza
isn't feeling, uhh...
Quite complete.
[FRIEZA whimpering]
Though you brought
all this on yourself,
it's a shame that your life had
to end in such a miserable way.
[FRIEZA coughs]
I wanted to save you Frieza,
but you wouldn't let me...
And now you will have to
share the fate of planet Namek,
which you yourself destroyed.
[FRIEZA coughs]
[GOKU] I'm tired of
fighting. I'm going home.
[GOKU] Goodbye, Frieza...
[FRIEZA whimpers]
Please... help me...
You... can't leave me here...
[GOKU gasps]
[FRIEZA] You can't...
let me... die like this...
[GOKU growls]
[KING KAI gasps]
Goku! You mustn't listen to him!
You have to get off
the planet now!
[GOKU growls]
You... have to help... me...
Don't... let me die...
[GOKU growls]
Please... have mercy...!
How many people begged for
their lives at YOUR feet,
and you killed them anyway?!
Did you show ME mercy
when I asked you to spare
my best friend Krillin?!
[FRIEZA] Please... Please...
For... give... me...
[GOKU sighs]
[GOKU yells]
[FRIEZA grunts softly]
Huh...?
I gave you some
of my own energy...
You should be able to move.
[GOKU] Go and do
as you like with it.
[GOKU] You're on your own now.
[VEGETA laughs]
Hurry back, Dad...
[NARRATOR] At last, the mighty
Frieza has been derailed,
cut down by his
own deadly attack.
Could this truly
be the end of Frieza?
On the next episode
of Dragon Ball Z!