[DENDE speaking Namek]
[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
Gohan and Krillin used their
first wish to bring Piccolo back
from the dead.
Hey, cool! You're alive!
[NARRATOR] Piccolo
was back in action
and he asked Gohan
to use the second wish
to transport him to
the planet Namek!
This wish, too, was granted
by the great Dragon of Namek!
The one you call Piccolo
will be brought to Namek now!
[NARRATOR] Vegeta was
infuriated when he awoke
and thought he missed
his golden opportunity
to wish for eternal life.
[VEGETA] Well, you can
kiss each other goodbye!
[NARRATOR] But then he found
out there was one wish left
and it looked like eternal life
would be his for the taking.
Don't you get it?! I'm the
only one who can stop him!
[DENDE speaking in Namek]
[NARRATOR] But when
Guru passed away,
Porunga did too, and the
Dragon Balls turned to stone.
[DENDE screams]
[NARRATOR] And with
Frieza on the scene,
the situation could
not have been worse.
So, you are the ones?
Naughty!
[NARRATOR] The dreaded
moment had finally arrived!
An all-out battle with Frieza
today, on Dragon Ball Z!
[FRIEZA] Hmm...
There doesn't seem to
be any power readings
for the Ginyu Force...
So it is true!
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[FRIEZA] Somehow you wimps
have managed to destroy the
most elite fighting
team in the universe.
Ha, ha! What a farce!
I only wish that I could have
been there to see the look
on Ginyu's face!
[FRIEZA giggles]
[GINYU] Ribbit!
Whatd'ya say
we get started?
I know you are all anxious
to resolve this dispute
once and for all.
[FRIEZA] I always knew that
you would turn on me someday,
Vegeta, but I never knew when.
Now I see that you were just
waiting for the stakes
to get high enough before
you played your hand.
A valient effort, but in the
end, it just didn't work,
now did it?
I hope you've thoroughly
enjoyed your little rebellion,
because now it's over, my
restless little warriors!
[FRIEZA growls]
Now you die!
[FRIEZA] I should have done
this a long time ago!
You ruined everything,
you little scumbag!
How dare you stick your
nose in my affairs!
I could have been
immortal! I hate you!
Like I care if you
hate me. I quit.
I'm free now! To think I was
nice to you all those years!
Makes me wanna puke!
[FRIEZA chuckles forcibly]
That's right, get it all out!
Live boldly, even if it is
only for a few moments!
[FRIEZA chuckles]
Okay, time's up!
[FRIEZA growls]
[shouting]
[GOHAN whimpers]
Whoa, man! We're talking
serious power here!
Huh...?
[PICCOLO] Whoa! That's one
heck of a power increase!
[PICCOLO] Yeah, the
action is definitely
getting ready to start!
[PICCOLO] A dying power.
That better not be Gohan.
[NAIL groans]
He looks like me!
Could be worse, I guess.
[NAIL groans]
[PICCOLO] This guy's
definitely seen better days...
Yeah. You can say that
again. What a drag, huh?
Hey, it's you!
So the Earthlings got to make
their wishes. I love it.
I see. Well, if you know me,
than you know I'm out of time.
I'm quite sure we've
never meet before,
but I'm glad your
beating sure hasn't
made you lose
your sense of humor.
[NAIL chuckles]
You take good care
of yourself, my friend.
Wait a sec...
[PICCOLO] Hmm?
I can sense your great power.
But I just don't think
it's going to be enough.
[PICCOLO] We'll see!
If only you had come back
as your original self...
You could have beaten
Frieza for sure...
[PICCOLO] What?!
I fought him. I know
how strong he is...
So, if I united with Kami,
I'd have what I need right now.
How ironic!
He's probably laughing so hard
that we could hear him
all the way from Earth!
[NAIL groans]
No, you're wrong! Nobody wants
you to win as much as Kami does.
His very survival depends on it.
[PICCOLO] Kami!
[KAMI] Piccolo, we are one!
Hm... Well it's too late
now at any rate.
And I think I would
rather die than unite
with that old geezer anyhow.
Well, unite with me then...
Hmm?
It's the only help we
can give, sad but true...
I'm the last warrior
left on Namek.
You are? That's just great!
[NAIL] I know. But if we unite,
you'll be much stronger
than you are right now.
I appreciate the offer, I guess,
but there's just not enough room
inside me for the both of us.
Oh, your ego's too big, huh?
[FRIEZA laughs]
[DENDE whimpers]
[GOKU] What a horrible power!
I've gotta get better...
[PICCOLO] I'd better be going
now. Sorry I can't help.
Not by yourself,
but with me you can.
I'm not trying to
trick you, brother!
Please! I'm just
trying to help you out.
You are one of us.
We have to work together.
Frieza is just too strong.
If we don't use every scrap
of what we have to fight him,
then we're done for.
Will I still be "me"?
[NAIL] For the most part, yes.
Sure, you'll notice
a difference at first,
but who knows, you might
find it to your liking.
[PICCOLO growls]
[FRIEZA laughs]
Why not? Alright.
You're on! But if I don't like
it, you're out! Understand me?
Man, you're too much.
Just wait! You'll be
begging to keep me around.
[PICCOLO] Yeah, right.
I doubt that.
Now, tell me what to do, quick.
Right! Just keep your
hand right there...
You can stay, until
we beat Frieza.
After that, I'm gonna charge
you rent! You got that?
[NAIL chuckles weakly]
[PICCOLO grunts]
Wow. Unreal. My gosh...
This is amazing!
I feel incredible!
Yes, yes, yes, yes! I can win!
I feel great! I can do this!
[PICCOLO] Yes! I'm home! I'm
alive! This is all a miracle!
I'm awake! I'm wide awake!
[PICCOLO laughs]
[PICCOLO] Hang on,
Gohan! Here I come!
[FRIEZA laughs]
[FRIEZA] Now look at me, Vegeta!
You fool! How dare
you challenge me!
Have you forgotten
what I really am?!
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[FRIEZA] You'd better get that
smirk off your face, Vegeta!
Huh?
Hmph.
[FRIEZA] Haaaa!
--[KRILLIN] Come on!
--[GOHAN] Right behind you!
[FRIEZA] Ha, ha!
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN coughin]
Gohan! Look, we've got to attack
him while he's distracted, okay?
It might be the
only chance we get!
Right!
[KRILLIN] Let's do it!
--Haaah!
--Raaah!
[BOTH screaming]
[DENDE] Krillin! Gohan!
[ALL scream]
[VEGETA] Raaagh!
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN whimper]
He-He's too strong!
I-I don't think we can win!
[GOHAN] What are we going to do?
[KRILLIN] I-I don't know!
Well, I do! You are all going to
perish, and it won't be pretty.
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[GOHAN whimpers]
Nonsense.
Hmph.
That's right!
Our chances of winning are
just as good as yours are!
[BOTH] Huh?!
That's absurd! You're finished!
No way!
[FRIEZA laughs]
Oh, no? So what's your plan?
You're so blind!
Haven't you noticed yet?
Their fighting power is
increasing with every attack!
Hmph.
Oh, yes, especially
the little guy.
His power is enormous, but
he doesn't even know it yet.
Huh?
And that's not all! Soon,
I'll be a Super Saiyan!
Your worst nightmare!
Hmmm...
[VEGETA chuckles]
A Super Saiyan, huh?
Well, we'll cross that
bridge when we come to it!
[FRIEZA giggles]
That is if we ever
come to it, fool!
[FRIEZA yells]
[FRIEZA growls]
[VEGETA grunts]
[BOTH grunting]
[FRIEZA} You low-life
Saiyan! How dare you!
[ALL gasp]
[BOTH growling]
[scouter beeping]
[FRIEZA] What?!
[BOTH growling]
Not bad. You've definitely
improved, Vegeta, I commend you.
Perhaps you are close
to becoming a Super Saiyan!
[GOHAN] Wow. Maybe
Vegeta's right.
Maybe we can beat
Frieza if we work together!
We are all getting stronger.
And we do have him outnumbered.
[KRILLIN] I'm getting a
bad feeling about this.
Vegeta's definitely
a lot stronger,
but Frieza doesn't
seem to care.
He's so calm.
Why don't you transform, Frieza?
Hmmm?
Say what?
Transform! Oh, man...
That doesn't sound good.
Well, how about it, Frieza?
Why don't you stop playing
around and show us the real you?
So, you've found out
my little secret.
That's right! Your loving
minion Zarbon blurted it out.
Huh?
What are you talking about?!
The form of Frieza you see
standing before you
is not what he really is; it's
just a clever camouflage!
A simple mask!
He can transform to his
real self at any time,
he just uses this form
to conserve energy.
You rude, little
ruffian! Please!
I don't choose my real form
because my power is too
radical to control!
[FRIEZA giggles]
That's just great!
[VEGETA] Don't listen to him!
He's just saying that
to intimidate you!
His power won't
increase that much.
Is that so?
[VEGETA] Why don't
you show us, then?
[KRILLIN whimpers]
Oh, alright! I'll give
you what you're asking for!
Strap yourselves in, boys!
You're in for one
heck of a ride!
Oh, and Vegeta,
I want you to know
that any remote chance of
winning you may have had
is about to go
flying out the window!
Hold on. I almost forgot!
I never transform unless
somebody gives me a countdown.
Oh, come on! That's...
That's ridiculous.
You've got to be joking.
[FRIEZA] I'm waiting...
[VEGETA] Oh, fine!
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six,
five, four, three, two, one.
You happy?
Elated. You're too kind.
Here it goes!
[GOKU] Gohan... Krillin...
[FRIEZA yells]
[GOHAN whimpers]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[NARRATOR] Frieza
has finally begun
his horrible transformation.
Can Vegeta manage to stave
off this evil super power
until help arrives?
Does Piccolo have the
power to save the day
now that he has fused with Nail?
And can Goku, the
Saiyan from Earth,
heal in time to
make a difference?
On the next episode
of Dragon Ball Z!