[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z!
Crucial decisions
were being made...
I want to go with Bulma
and Krillin... Okay?
Sorry, Mom,
but I need to go to
try to help them bring
Piccolo and the others back
with the
Dragon Balls.
You should be making friends
and playing baseball
and building tree houses...
Not trying to save the world!
I'm going!
[KRILLIN] Ehh?!
Aaah! How did I raise
such a stubborn child?!
There's no time for those
childish things, anymore.
My friends are gone, and
they're not coming back!
I've got to go help
find the Dragon Balls.
Mom, Piccolo died
trying to help me,
so I think I should do
everything I can to help him.
I can't sit around and do
nothing while Piccolo needs me.
[NARRATOR] Despite the
protests of his mother,
Gohan chose to embark on
the long journey to Namek,
with Bulma and Krillin, in the
search for the Dragon Balls...
And with that, the three
young adventurers blasted off
from Earth in
Kami's spaceship,
and set out into the
vast expanse of space.
If their mission succeeds,
it will mean the return of
Piccolo, Kami,
and all who were lost
in the battle
against the Saiyans.
But little do these
travelers realize,
in a flight across the
galaxy, anything can happen.
And despite a
smooth start,
there's plenty of
turbulence ahead... Today!
[yawns]
Another boring day.
What is this...
day seven or eight?
Why did I forget to
install the new sleep pods?
That's the one thing that could
have made this trip bearable.
[yawns]
[BULMA] You guys doing
image training again?
I guess that's a good way
to kill some time, huh?
Hey, are you two
even listening to me?
[GOHAN grunts softly]
[KRILLIN grunts softly]
[KRILLIN and GOHAN
yell frantically]
[GOHAN whimpers]
[KRILLIN] Yah!
Yaahh!
[GOHAN whimpers]
[GOHAN screams]
[panting]
[GOHAN gasps]
Ah... Wow, Gohan...
You have some awesome moves.
We're gonna have to
train like this everyday
if we're gonna be
ready for Vegeta.
Yeah. We can't let
ourselves get lazy and slow
while we're
on this trip.
[BULMA] Boys...
[KRILLIN] Uh?
I don't want to
interrupt your training,
but this place
is filthy...
Can't you two find a
minute to clean this mess?
[KRILLIN] Um...
[BULMA] I like to
run a tidy ship.
Sorry Bulma, but we don't eat
junk food and read magazines.
That's all
your mess.
We already cleaned
up after ourselves.
Yeah, but, I'm busy.
I have too many other important
issues to deal with right now.
Besides, you two
never do anything
to help out
around here.
But, Bulma, you said
you were bored!
Oh, you're hopeless!
And don't cry to me
if I forget about
making your dinner.
[can clatters]
[BULMA yawning] I have
so much to do today.
[KRILLIN] The only thing she's
busy doing is complaining.
[NURSE hums]
[GOKU grunts]
Huh? Oh, not again!
Four more
sets to go.
Mr. Goku,
stop that!
[GOKU] There's no need
to worry. I feel fine!
Can I lend you a
hand, there, Nurse?
[NURSE screams]
[ROSHI] Oh, well,
what I mean is...
I really admire the work
you ladies do here...
And you know, I just wanna
help in any way I can.
[grunts angrily]
Can I offer you a
piece of sponge cake?
[NURSE grunts angrily]
[GOKU grunts]
[ROSHI] Eh?
[DOCTOR clears throat]
Huh?
Hello, doctor.
Goku, how many times
have I told you?
In order to get better
your body needs rest.
Exercising now could
do further damage.
No, I'm fine,
doctor. See?
[groans]
Now you listen up... As
long as you're in my hospital,
you'll do what I say
without question...
Do you think you
can do that for me?
Yeah... You're
right, doctor.
Please, come give the nurse
a hand... If you would, sir.
Um, why
certainly. I, uh...
Don't you have orderlies
for this sorta thing...
Good grief...
[NURSE giggles]
Eh?
It serves
you right.
[ROSHI] Heh, heh. ehh...
Do you know where I can find
the patient's wife right now?
Hm. Last time I saw her
she was on the roof
spending some
time alone.
I know you're out there
somewhere, Gohan...
And even though I wish
we could just have
a normal family life...
I'm very proud of you...
Just promise me you'll come
back soon, healthy and safe.
[sighs]
[BULMA] Hey.
What?
I've been meaning to ask you
a question about that Saiyan.
Does anyone actually
know what happened to him?
Or did he just
vanish into thin air?
Um... What
do you mean?
[BULMA] I thought the Saiyans'
home planet was destroyed
some time ago,
wasn't it?
That's right...
Vegeta was badly wounded
when he finally
got away,
so he had to go
somewhere to recover.
But I certainly couldn't
tell you where it is...
Hmm... Wait a minute,
I remember something
Goku's brother
Raditz said...
He told us the Saiyans
were planet brokers,
and that they took over worlds
just so they could sell them
to the highest bidder...
Raditz said Vegeta
found a buyer for Earth,
so maybe he's
hiding with them.
Yeah, I guess that
could be what happened,
but the problem is we still
have no idea where he went...
I mean, he could already be
on Namek as far as we know!
[BULMA groans]
Well, wherever he
is, for our sakes,
let's hope it's
far, far away...
[VEGETA grunts]
[thinking] Almost there...
It won't be long now.
[KRILLIN] Hmm?
[BULMA] Hm?
What is that?
[KRILLIN]
What is what?
[GOHAN] It's not
Planet Namek, is it?
I can't be. It's much
too soon to be Namek.
But look... Something
is coming right at us!
[beeping]
Whatever it is,
it's moving fast.
We should be able
to see it by now...
You see anything?
[alarm sounds]
There they are!
They're gonna attack!
[BULMA] Ahh! Oh no!
[BULMA and KRILLIN scream]
C'mon, do something!
[BULMA] Okay, Okay,
I know! I'll do it!
Fire counterattack!
[beeping]
[GOHAN and KRILLIN]
Woohoo! Yeah! Ha, ha!
Just hold on guys, cuz
we're not in the clear yet.
[beeping]
It looks like
a spaceship.
It looks almost
identical to ours.
Whatever it is,
it's getting closer...
And if it doesn't change its
course, it's gonna ram us.
Oh no!
Bulma!
Bank left!
It's headed straight for us!
We're gonna collide!
Aahh! This is it!
[GROUP screams]
[alarm sounds]
[alarm stops]
[BULMA yells]
That was weird.
One second we're about to
crash into our own ship,
and the next we're...
Well, we're who knows where!
It looks like we're
on another ship.
Yeah, a big one. Probably full
of big scary aliens, too.
Well, I hope
you're wrong.
[GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN] Hey, look at me!
I'm an alien!
Gohan!
That's not funny.
Hm. It'll do us no good
just sitting here,
so let's take a walk
and check the place out.
[KRILLIN] Um...
[KRILLIN grunts]
Let's do this.
[thinking] There's
something about this place
that gives
me the creeps.
But I don't know
what it is...
[BULMA] Oh great!
I forgot to put some
pants on before we left!
That's too bad...
It's freezing in here.
You think I
don't know that?
I'll deal with it.
As long as you
don't blame us
if you catch a
cold or something.
[GOHAN] Great, now
let's get moving.
Okay,
we're going.
[BULMA sighs]
And Gohan!
Don't walk so close!
[KRILLIN] Is that
what I think it is?
[GOHAN] Uhh...
[BULMA] Uh!
[GROUP whimpers and yells]
[panting]
We need to be
more careful...
I'm sure that's not the last
booby trap around here.
Listen! You two need
to be more aware
of what's going
on around here!
I almost got my
head shot off!
[KRILLIN]
Uh... Eh?
[BULMA] This hallway
never seems to end.
There should be a door
or a vent or something,
don't you think?
[loud thuds]
[BULMA] Oh no!
Open this door right now!
[KRILLIN] Bulma,
don't worry. Stand back.
[BULMA] Huh?
Ka me...
Ha me...
Eh? Uh...
[KRILLIN yells]
Ah! I can't get
out of the way!
[BULMA yells and gasps]
Ka me...
Ha me... Haa!
Thanks for the
ride, Gohan.
Sure is sweet of you
to carry a lady.
[footsteps]
Whoever owns
this spaceship
sure doesn't want us to
stay too much longer.
[GOHAN] What if this is a...
a Saiyan spaceship?
What do you mean?
[KRILLIN] Yeah, this
could be the place
that Vegeta
went to recover.
Enough talk
about that guy...
Let's change the subject.
I'm getting goose bumps.
But wait... If this
is Vegeta's ship,
maybe he's in there
somewhere waiting for us...
I wish Goku had let me finish
him when I had the chance.
[VEGETA grunts]
[thinking]
I must recuperate!
I can't allow Kakarot to
gain any more time on me!
Wait a minute...
This doesn't make any sense.
The hallway is starting
to curve in on itself
and we still haven't
found a door.
[BULMA] Ugh! There
has to be a door.
Maybe it's hidden
in the walls.
[KRILLIN] Found it.
[KRILLIN grunts]
Huh?
Krillin. Another hallway
just opened up down here.
[BULMA]
I knew it!
Great... It must be nice
to be right all the time.
All right,
let's keep moving.
[BULMA]
Be careful, Krillin.
Yeah, I know.
[GROUP screams]
[BULMA screams]
[groans]
[panting]
Wow... I thought
I was dead.
Man, I'm
really hungry.
I'm right there
with you, Krillin.
[KRILLIN sniffs]
You smell that?
[GOHAN sniffs]
Yeah...
Smells good!
Look!
Whoa, let's dig in!
[KRILLIN and GOHAN laugh]
Wait! It may be
another trick!
This looks
really good.
Control yourselves.
Don't eat it yet.
[GOHAN] Why?
Aahh!
[embarrassed laughter]
Now that was a close call
there, wasn't it, boys?
[rumbling]
Aaahhhh!
It was a trap!
[BULMA] Help me!
Get me outta here!
[KRILLIN] You're way too slow,
Bulma. You gotta be more aware.
[BULMA] I don't need
any lessons right now!
[KRILLIN] Hang on,
I'll get you out.
Alright now, Bulma,
just get under that table.
[BULMA screams]
[KRILLIN] Hm?
Krillin! Gohan!
Get me out of this rope!
It's starting to hurt!
[BOY A]
Don't move.
Don't hurt her!
[GOHAN] Bulma! Whatever
you do, don't panic!
Leave her alone!
[BULMA yells and whimpers]
Stay there! I don't
want to get shot!
[KRILLIN grunts]
[GOHAN and KRILLIN] Huh?
Krillin,
what's going on?
Why aren't there
any adults here?
Easy, everyone.
There's no need to shoot.
We're not here to hurt
anyone, just passing through.
[BULMA] Krillin!
Don't just stand there!
Make these stupid kids
get their guns off of me!
I don't know...
[BULMA]
Do it! Quick!
My arms feel like
they're gonna break!
All right.
Haa!
[BOY B whimpers]
[KRILLIN grunts]
[BULMA] Krillin,
don't fight them!
[KRILLIN] Eh?
If you attack, they're
just gonna shoot me!
Then what should I do? Uh...
Uh... Got any ideas?
I guess we should just
give ourselves up.
[NARRATOR] It seems the
deeper our heroes travel
into this
mysterious spaceship,
the more troubling
questions arise!
Who are these
young soldiers,
and what do they have in store
for Bulma, Krillin, and Gohan?
Is there any
hope for escape?
The answers are
sure to come...
In the next action-packed
episode of Dragon Ball Z!