[GOKU] Kaa...
[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
as the first competitor
in the Cell Game,
Goku came out swinging,
but everything he threw at
the slippery serpent Cell,
including the Kamehameha Wave
attack, had no effect.
And, a behind the
back sneak attack
only made Cell more psychotic.
So much so that he nearly
polished the Super Saiyan off
with a series of
power-packed punches.
[CELL yells]
[NARRATOR] Still in the game
and determined to beat
the beast in battle,
Goku carefully planned
his next attack.
But Cell's uncanny ability
to anticipate every one
of his moves
stifled any chance
of a strategy.
[ANNOUNCER] That was
just their warm up?
Well, it looks like they're
gonna fight for real.
[NARRATOR] While a world wide
audience watched in horror,
the two warriors
stood their ground,
stone faced and silent.
Making it impossible to know
what was really on their minds.
[NARRATOR] Now its time for Goku
to pull out all the stops.
He's got to use his
Super Saiyan powers
to topple that titan
of terror Cell.
They both posses
incredible power,
but it's going to take
brains, as well as brawn,
to win this competition.
Cell's passion for
inflicting pain
makes him a fiercesome
force to fight against.
And, to him, defeating Goku
would be the ultimate prize.
When these two
clash again
only one of them
will be left standing.
Which one will it be?
[GOKU grunts]
[gasping]
[GOKU growls]
What power!
That's for sure!
That's incredible!
No, fool!
I can't believe
this is happening.
[GOHAN] That's it, Dad!
You can do it!
[GOKU growls]
[yelling]
[screaming]
[GOKU yelling]
[PICCOLO grunting]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[VEGETA grunts]
[thinking] That's it, Goku.
Show me the true power
of a Super Saiyan.
Ladies and gentlemen,
can you believe
what just happened?
Incredible! I've never
seen anything like it!
If I hadn't seen
it with my own eyes
I wouldn't have believed it!
Could it be an optical illusion?
[ANNOUNCER] He can't
really be glowing?
Yup! He's glowing, alright!
My friends, could this
newcomer be battery powered,
or does he possess some
kind of otherworldly power
that you and I could
never comprehend?!
Ha! It's a trick! Yeah!
[CELL yells]
[grunting]
[screaming]
[PICCOLO grunting]
[KRILLIN grunts]
[TIEN grunts]
Now, Dad!
What's happening out there?
Cell is glowing
just like the other guy!
Ha! I tell ya, it's gotta
be some kind of trick!
Yeah, you said it! Fancy tricks
like that are for amateurs!
They don't scare anyone!
[BOTH whimper]
It's a standoff.
They're both fighting
at maximum power.
[ANNOUNCER] Ladies
and gentlemen,
something very unusual
is happening here.
The challenger
has dropped his guard
and is crossing the
ring towards his opponent.
What could he possibly hope to
gain by this bizarre maneuver?
Your move.
Of course.
[CELL grunts]
[GOKU grunting]
[CELL] Ah!
Hmph!
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL] Good work, Goku!
At last a worthy opponent!
This is the competition
I've been waiting for!
Since our powers
are almost equal,
it should make for
an interesting contest,
don't you think?
Yeah, count on it!
[VEGETA thinking] So at last,
I've seen Kakarot's true power!
How did he get so strong?!
Hey, Krillin. Between the two of
them, who do you think will win?
I say Goku is the man!
Cell is going down!
[GOHAN thinking] Of course
my Dad is gonna win!
This is what
he's been training for!
Now everyone will see
what he can really do!
[GOKU gasps]
[growling]
[BOTH grunt]
[grunting,
blows landing]
[CELL yells]
[GOKU growls]
[CELL gasps]
[gasping]
[grunting,
blows landing]
[BOTH grunt]
[GOKU growls]
[CELL growls]
[BOTH yell]
[grunting]
[CELL growls]
[GOKU yells]
[CELL grunts]
Hey, did you get all that?
No way! I'm only human!
How am I supposed to shoot
them when they move that fast?!
I see whatcha mean...
Let's get a professional opinion
from Earth's greatest fighter.
What do you think of this action
packed match so far, Mr. Satan?
N-Not bad!
[MR. SATAN laughs]
[ANNOUNCER] Uh, thanks. Mr.
Satan, Ladies and gentlemen!
A man of few words
but with large fists...
Now, let's go back to
the action inside the ring!
[CELL chuckles]
Huh...?
[CELL laughs]
[CELL cackles]
♪ I've got a surprise for you! ♪
[CELL chuckles]
Huh?!
[CELL] Multi-form!
H-He can't be!
I don't know.
This looks bad!
[CELLS chuckle]
[CELL] How do you
like these odds?
Look! He's separated
into four parts
by using one of
Tien's techniques!
No, Goku!
[ANNOUNCER] For those
of you just tuning in,
there has been a
dramatic turn of events!
Somehow there seem
to be four Cells now!
And they're all preparing to
go after the strange competitor!
I guess you could say
the odds are... against him!
Mr. Satan, can you explain?
[MR. SATAN] Uhhh... I, uhhh...
You had this planned,
right, Cell?
[CELLs chuckle]
[ANNOUNCER] Cell has moved to
the four corners of the ring.
He has the challenger
surrounded.
It doesn't look good
for our spiky-haired hero.
Are we about to witness
the first crushing defeat
in this competition?
No way, this trick
won't work on me!
[CELL] We'll see about that!
[grunting,
blows landing]
[CELL grunting]
[grunting,
blows landing]
This is the best
magic trick I've ever seen!
Okay, Cell's using
my fighting technique now,
but he should be much weaker
since he's divided into four!
I don't know about that, Tien.
They all look
pretty strong to me!
That creep!
To think that one
of my cells is helping that
monster to beat
up on my friend...
[TIEN growls]
Goku has more strength
than all four of them.
[BOTH gasp]
[GOKU grunts]
Well done. I see that your
fighting skills keep improving.
Well, thanks. I try.
Oh, but this
match isn't over yet.
You have no idea what
I have in store for you next.
Hey, isn't that...
Yeah. That's my technique.
[CELL] Special Beam Cannon!
Right this way...
--[GOKU growls]
--[CELLS grunting]
[CELL gasps]
[GOKU grunts,
CELL yells]
Pull yourself together, Cell!
He did it!
[ANNOUNCER] What an upset!
Cell is down and out and it
looks like it might be for good!
We could have a new champion!
This could be planet
Earth's lucky day!
Goku has beat Cell!
That means that
he won the tournament!
[VEGETA] Ha... I doubt it!
Can't you see that's exactly
what Cell wants you to think?!
He's playing another one of
his tricks on you, that's all!
If you weren't
so busy celebrating,
you would notice that Cell's
life force has not diminished.
Look, he's right...
No... It can't be!
[CELL] Kien-zan Discs!
[MR. SATAN &amp; ANNOUNCER yell]
That disc... Is that mine?
[CELL grunts]
Whoa... look at that!
That disc is following
Goku everywhere!
[KING KAI] No,
that's not Krillin's move!
That's the last technique
Frieza used against Goku!
And if Cell feels he cannot win,
he may destroy Earth just as
Frieza destroyed planet Namek!
That darn Dr. Gero!
How could he have released such
an evil monster on planet Earth?
Ha! Nice try, Goku!
The cell from
Frieza that's inside me
tells me you are
trying to draw that disc
back this way...
No chance!
[CELL grunts]
[yells]
[GOKU gasps]
It went right through him.
This time I'll
finish you off for good!
[CELL gasps]
[GOKU] There's no way
you can beat me
with your stolen
fighting techniques.
Now, give up!
No, not yet!
It's over when I say it's over.
[GOKU gasps
[thinking] He's concentrating
all of his energy
into something! What's he up to?
[CELL] Kaa...
Mee...
[gasping]
No, you can't put that much
power into the Kamehameha!
It's too dangerous!
[CELL] Haa...
Mee...
He'll kill us all!
Haaaa!
Hey, Cell! Up here!
[gasping, yelling]
[grunting]
[GOKU growls]
[CELL gasps,
GOKU growls]
[grunting]
[ANNOUNCER] Cell just fired
some sort of Earth-shattering
mega-blast at his competitor!
Luckily, the nimble newcomer
was able to divert the bomb
away from the planet!
We all owe that guy
a big thanks for saving
me from certain destruction.
Thanks to him, this broadcast
will go on. Oh, the humanity!
Hey, what was that?
[MR. SATAN whimpers]
[ANNOUNCER] Our two warriors
are still standing
so this contest isn't over yet.
But if another bomb
like that last one goes off,
it could mean the end of this
tournament and every one of us!
[GOHAN] Way to go, Dad.
That was a close one.
But how? That blast
was too close
for you to have
possibly escaped!
I guess it was luck.
Of course.
You're very lucky.
But how did you disappear
and reappear again?!
A new technique:
The Instant Transmission.
Instant, huh?
Sounds like a
useful little maneuver.
Yeah, it is.
You know, that blast
would have completely
destroyed the Earth if I hadn't
have flown up and diverted it.
Yeah, maybe so.
But I knew you would do
something heroic to save it.
Oh, I see. So you
were counting on me?
Well, don't get
the wrong idea...
I don't care one bit about this
planet or its filthy people.
But without it,
there'd be no one to kill!
[GOKU gasps]
[grunting]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU thinking] Where is he?!
[GOKU thinking]
He's increased his speed.
I can't even see where he is!
[ANNOUNCER]
Hold on to your hairpiece!
It looks like the Cell
Game is back in business!
[ANNOUNCER] Uh-oh!
Our underdog seems to
have lost sight of Cell!
--[GOKU gasps]
--Am I too fast for you, Goku?
[NARRATOR] Advantage: Cell!
The crafty creature
has done it again.
His super speed means
he can move around
the ring undetected.
Will Goku be knocked out of
the Cell Game permanently?
Don't miss the next
Dragon Ball Z!