[NARRATOR] Last time,
on Dragon Ball Z!
Yamcha stepped up to fight,
and he convinced Krillin
to stand aside until
the next round
in the Saiyans' twisted
Saibaman tournament.
The battle was intense.
But in the end, Yamcha proved
that his fighting skills
were far superior to those
of the maniacal green monster.
[YAMCHA]
Hyaaah!
[NARRATOR] His opponent
seemingly vanquished,
Yamcha was ready to claim
victory in the bout.
But with his
guard relaxed,
the Saibaman was able to
summon his remaining strength
and surprise Yamcha with
a final, diabolical attack.
[YAMCHA screams]
[NARRATOR] And in a
single, horrifying flash...
...Yamcha was dead.
[VEGETA laughs]
Now why did you have to
go and play the hero,
you big,
stupid, jerk?
It was my
turn to fight.
It shoulda been
me in there...
Do you hear me? You can't
die! It should've been me!
It should
have been me!
[BULMA sobs]
[OX KING] ChiChi, it's Daddy.
Wake up, sweetie.
[ROSHI] Don't worry, Bulma.
Everything's going to be fine.
[BULMA]
No, it's not...
There, there, child.
[BULMA]
Yamcha's dead now.
[PUAR]
Oh, Yamcha!
Puar! Oh, no,
another one's down!
Puar, say something...
Anything!
She'll be okay.
[BULMA sobs]
[ROSHI] C'mon, guys.
Let's cheer up!
Yamcha wouldn't want us
to carry on like this...
Hey, Bulma!
Enough is enough now!
It'll never be enough!
I'll have you know,
I was going to marry
Yamcha one of these days!
[BULMA sobs]
When Yamcha gets back,
you'll cheer up!
What?
Don't worry, dear.
He won't be dead for long...
We can use the Dragon Balls
to wish him back, remember?
Ah...! That's right!
You're a genius!
I know.
[ROSHI cackles]
Eh?!
[BULMA fumes]
[ROSHI giggling]
[whomp]
I take it back!
You're an idiot!
[KRILLIN weeps quietly]
[NAPPA] Get over it, little
man. Don't you get it?
You're all going
to die in the end!
[VEGETA]
Calm down, Nappa.
Heh. Give them a moment to clear
this trash off the battlefield.
[KRILLIN seethes]
[thinking]
How dare you?!
[NAPPA]
Hm.
[KRILLIN] You guys
stay out of this!
[KRILLIN seethes]
[KRILLIN groans]
[KRILLIN] I'll take on all
four of those goons at once!
Just like Yamcha
was going to do!
[KRILLIN roars]
[NAPPA]
Heh.
[VEGETA]
Attack.
[SAIBAMAN 3 grunts]
[KRILLIN grunting]
What the...
Let's go,
Chiaotzu!
I'm not sure what he's
planning to do...
But I know
this much...
We don't want to be here
when the blast hits!
Way to go!
[OOLONG]
That's my man!
[OOLONG] He did it!
He did it! He did it!
[BULMA] I can't believe it!
Did you see that?
Wow, Krillin!
Nice job!
Yeah! That was great!
Yeah. Thanks, you guys.
That was for you, Yamcha.
Enough...
[thinking] So, Piccolo's
become even stronger!
That was incredible! I'm glad
he's on my side for a change!
Thanks for saving
me, Piccolo.
Stay focused, Gohan... Don't
make yourself an easy target.
You're lucky I was
there this time.
But next time, you better be
prepared to save yourself!
[VEGETA] Ha! So much
for our little game...
[VEGETA] Oh well.
It was fun while it lasted.
Surprise,
surprise!
This is our favorite
part, you know?
You should see the
looks on your faces.
[NAPPA] Ha! They look like
they've seen a ghost!
[thinking] I don't believe it!
Not even a scratch!
[NAPPA] Whadda you guys say
we get the real fight started?
Any volunteers?
I put everything I
had into that shot!
What're we
supposed to do now?
[NAPPA] Hey, Vegeta,
why don't I handle this?
There's no sense in both
of us getting dirty.
[VEGETA] As you wish!
But, Nappa...
Make sure you don't kill
the Namek just yet.
Remember, he's the one
who's going to tell us
where the
Dragon Balls are.
Right... I got it.
So.. I can't kill
the Namek... Fine...
Then, you!
No! Here!
Oh, no!
Piccolo!
[NAPPA laughs]
You're a Saiyan. You should
be enjoying this, kid!
[TIEN]
Are you okay, Piccolo?
[PICCOLO] Yeah, I'm fine.
Just a broken rib or two...
[NAPPA growling]
[GOHAN whimpering]
[NAPPA yelling]
[yelling continues]
I... I've never felt a power
like this before!
[CHIAOTZU whimpering]
Hey! Tien!
Look out!
It feels like the whole
planet is shaking apart!
Oh, man...
This is bad!
[NAPPA laughing]
[PICCOLO] Get up!
Stand firm, Gohan!
[GOHAN whimpering]
I said get up!
Now, do it!
Don't let yourself be
overwhelmed by your opponent!
I'll try!
[NAPPA chuckling]
[thinking] This Saiyan is even
stronger than I imagined!
Raah!
Huh?
Hey, there's
Princess Snake's palace!
[screaming]
Wow! Was that
Goku? He's Fast!
Uh-huh...
That's the half
way point...
Looks like I'm making
pretty good time so far!
[thinking] Hold on, you guys!
I'll be there soon!
[NAPPA growling]
[growling continues]
[PICCOLO grunting]
[TIEN grunting]
[NAPPA roaring]
[thunder crackling]
[NAPPA yelling]
[ALL gasping]
Haah!
Rrgh!
[TIEN] Chiaotzu!
Be careful!
Haaugh!
[CHIAOTZU screams]
[PICCOLO] Watch it!
He's almost ready to attack!
[NAPPA laughing]
[NAPPA] Ahhh!
Yes! Now!
Which one of you
wants to die first?
[NAPPA] Well, if there's not a
volunteer... I'll choose!
[TIEN growling]
Raaah!
Hyaah!
Uraaugh!
Yaaugh!
Hraaugh!
Watch out!
Tien!
[NAPPA yelling]
Above you!
Urggh!
[TIEN screaming]
[screaming continues]
Tien! No!
[TIEN grunting]
[NAPPA laughing]
Hah...
He's been disarmed.
[NAPPA roaring]
Haah!
[TIEN growling]
[NAPPA yelling]
[NAPPA laughing]
No! No!
Mister Tien!
[NAPPA] Hmph! Why that
stubborn little...
He just refuses
to die!
No! We need to get
his tail somehow!
No! This ends here!
[PICCOLO] Krillin! It's too
late to save him! Wait!
Hyaah!
[NAPPA] Where do you
think you're goin'?
Rraah!
[NAPPA laughing]
[PICCOLO]
Incredible...
There's no bottom
to this thing!
[NAPPA laughing]
[NAPPA] That's just a pock
mark, you Namek lizard!
Wait 'til I really
get started!
[KRILLIN] Chiaotzu!
[KRILLIN]
Chiaotzu!
[KRILLIN] He's gone! He must
have been hit by the blast!
No...
[NAPPA] Ha, ha! I guess my
aim was a little off!
[TIEN] Chiaotzu!
[NAPPA] Aw. What's the
matter three-eyes?
Nappa! Watch it!
You're being careless!
[NAPPA] Huh?!
[TIEN] Chiaotzu!
Why... you...
little...
[NAPPA] Come here,
you little dwarf!
Aargh!
Haaaaa!
Chiaotzu! Get
away from there!
I can't look!
[PICCOLO]
Watch, Gohan!
I said watch!
Don't turn away...
Honor his bravery.
You're asking
for it!
Chiaotzu! Get off!
That's enough!
[CHIAOTZU using ESP]
Tien? Can you hear me?
I hope my ESP is working.
I have to say goodbye now.
What? What are you
talking about? Chiaotzu!
[TIEN] You're not going
anywhere! Just stop it!
[NAPPA] Heh...
[CHIAOTZU using ESP] I'm sorry,
Tien. I have to do this...
Thank you for everything.
You're my best friend. Always.
No, don't! Chiaotzu!
Please, this isn't the answer!
[CHIAOTZU using ESP] It's
the only way, Tien.
[CHIAOTZU using ESP] Don't
worry. I'm not afraid.
And if I can save you,
that's worth dying for.
No! Stop it!
Get off!
[CHIAOTZU using ESP] Goodbye,
Tien! Remember me!
What?!
Chiaotzu! No!
[thinking]
Chiaotzu...
[TIEN screaming]
[PICCOLO] What an
extraordinary feat!
You see, Gohan, size
alone is not enough...
You have to have heart,
and cunning, too!
Ahh!
[NAPPA laughing]
[laughing continues]
[NAPPA] Now you see him...
Now you don't!
Nappa! He almost had you!
You barely managed a defense!
What? It can't be!
Not even a scrape! So...
So that means... Chiaotzu
sacrificed himself for nothing!
Chiaotzu!
He's gone.
He's already been wished
back to life once before.
Now not even the Dragon
Balls can bring him back!
You! You'll pay
for what you've done!
Do you hear me?
You'll pay!
Fool! Go ahead!
Make your threats!
It doesn't matter
how angry you get!
You still don't have
a chance of beating us!
And the funny thing is...
you never did!
[NAPPA laughing]
[NARRATOR] Yet another of
the Earth's defenders
has given his life in the
struggle against the Saiyans.
And with their
numbers dwindling,
the odds of survival grow
slimmer by the minute.
Can these few remaining
fighters withstand
the Saiyan onslaught long
enough for Goku to arrive?
Or will they
fall before
the seemingly
unstoppable Nappa?
Find out, as the
life-and-death battle
for the Earth continues...
Next time on Dragon Ball Z!