[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball Z,
in a rash attempt
to save the Earth,
Piccolo destroyed the doorway
to the Hyperbolic Time Chamber,
trapping himself,
Gotenks, and Majin Buu
inside another dimension.
[MAJIN BUU]
Let me out!
[NARRATOR]
But in a screaming rage,
Majin Buu accidentally
ripped a hole
in the fabric of space itself,
using the powerful
vibration of his voice.
[MAJIN BUU] I knew
I could have my candy!
[NARRATOR] Fueled by
his monstrous appetite,
Majin Buu went to
great lengths to escape.
Leaving Gotenks and Piccolo
as the victims of
the Namek's own trap.
[NARRATOR] And the friends
and family atop the Lookout
were left without
any protection.
[YAMCHA]
Ah! What do we do now?
[NARRATOR] With nothing left
for the Z Fighters to do
but watch in terror,
Majin Buu laid waste to them
in the exact way he had
done the entire world!
[SUPER BUU]
Very dark!
[PUAR, YAMCHA scream]
[NARRATOR] Then, Gotenks
revealed a surprise ability
he had foolishly
hidden during the fight--
Super Saiyan 3!
And ripping a
dimensional hole of his own,
Gotenks and Piccolo returned
to the ruined Lookout.
[PICCOLO grunts]
Where is everyone?
What have you done to them?
[SUPER BUU]
They're in me!
Buu! You'll pay for each one!
[NARRATOR] With only
Gotenks and Piccolo left,
has Majin Buu cleared
the way for victory?
Find out now!
[GOTENKS] You killed
my friends, you monster!
[growls]
Aaah..! Aah!
The Lookout!
Too much more of this
and there won't
be anything left!
--[SUPER BUU groans]
--[TRUNKS grunts]
[chuckles]
For such a little guy
you have a stormy temper.
What would your
mother say to that?
You just keep on talking
while I smack you around!
[yells]
[SUPER BUU, GOTENKS grunt]
--[GOTENKS yells]
--[SUPER BUU grunting]
[breathing heavily]
[PICCOLO]
Gotenks!
Gotenks, pull yourself out.
Huh?
[SUPER BUU growls]
[SUPER BUU exhales gutturally]
[SUPER BUU]
Gotenks...
Splitting headache!
[groaning]
Yeah! Oh yeah! Ha-ha!
Now to finish the job!
[PICCOLO]
Perfect!
That's a Super Saiyan!
Wow, Gotenks is pulling out some
really nice moves, isn't he?
[SUPREME KAI]
Mm.
[GOKU] I don't know
what move that was,
but I haven't heard of
anyone being split in half
since Trunks beat Frieza!
And he's a fused
Super Saiyan 3?
C'mon, that's pretty impressive
no matter how powerful you are!
Uh, excuse me, but
what exactly's going on?
Not too long ago,
I ascended to level three,
and let me tell you, it's not
the easiest thing to control.
But he's moving around like
he's trained for years!
[GOHAN]
Uuh?
[OLD KAI] Gohan.
Bring your eyes to me.
You're delaying the process.
A great warrior should not
be distracted by anything.
The greatest of warriors
is always focused
on one thing--his victory.
I know your brother's plight,
but you must stay focused.
But, I should help him.
[OLD KAI] The best thing
for you to do now
is to continue
your training with me.
[laughing]
Oh, but seriously...
Wow, have you read
this book? It's funny.
[GOHAN thinking]
And you're telling me
how to stay focused?
[GOKU]
Man, that's awesome!
I guess when you've
got it, you've got it!
Can you believe it?
Those boys aren't even ten years
old yet and they're winning.
If I were Majin Buu,
I'd have to consider
running away at this point.
Goku, think about it.
Their strength and
skills are impressive.
But Majin Buu's
might possibly be greater.
Oh, really?
But he's been blown to bits!
You mean, he wants more?!
[chuckles]
Huh...?
Ah! Ah! Aah!
[yells]
Stop--Stop squeezing.
--[GOTENKS groaning]
--[SUPER BUU chuckles]
[SUPER BUU grunts]
My turn again.
Superghost Balloon.
[grunts]
[SUPERGHOSTS laughing]
Oh, Majin Buu, are you scared
of all the creepy ghosts?
You should be.
They've raised their power
levels as much as I have!
Attack, attack, attack!
--[SUPER BUU grunting]
--[SUPERGHOSTS laughing]
[SUPER BUU groaning]
[grunting]
That had to hurt!
[chuckles]
That's really
a bad look for you.
[chuckles]
[SUPER BUU growls]
[screams]
For a pink guy,
you've got a bad temper.
[screaming]
Aaah-la-la-la-la!
Ha-ha!
That's it, follow me.
[GOTENKS] C'mon, Majin Buu!
Try and keep up!
All right,
I must've worn him out.
He can't keep up
with my speed anymore.
Now, where did
that tube-head go?
--[SUPER BUU] Boo.
--[GOTENKS yells]
Eeeeh!
[SUPER BUU]
Bye-bye.
[GOTENKS groaning]
You don't have to do this.
Tube-head was just a joke!
[yells, groans]
Uuh!
[PICCOLO grunts]
[yells]
No! Gotenks,
what have you done?!
It's destroyed!
What are you so
freaked out about?
You destroyed the Lookout!
[GOTENKS]
Oh, yeah.
Hmmm.
I'll get him, Piccolo.
Aauh...
[MR. SATAN] There's not
a scrap of civilization
left anywhere.
And to think I could've
stopped this from happening.
[BEE barking]
Wait a second, that's a
cliff you're running toward!
[BEE barking]
It's... a city! Oh Bee,
you are a smart one!
They'll have
food and--and water and--
and beds for us to sleep on!
[MR. SATAN laughing]
Uuh...
Hey! Is there
anybody out there?
Anybody at all?!
This is Mr. Satan!
You know, the World
Martial Arts champion
and savior of the world!
Auh! It's no use.
They're all dead.
--[MR. SATAN] Uuh...
--[BEE whines]
[thinking] How did that
guy ever get so mean.
[thinking] The three of us
got along like family.
[panting]
[BEE barking]
[BEE barks]
[MR. SATAN sighs]
I know Bee. I miss him, too.
[MR. SATAN thinking]
You finally did it, Buu.
Just like you wanted
from the start.
You put an end to humanity.
[chuckles]
Aah! All gone! All gone!
[grunting]
Hey, Piccolo?
What's this guy tryin' to do?
[SUPER BUU laughs intensely]
Uh, he's starting to
look like a cannonball.
What did you do?
[SUPER BUU chuckles, yells]
Whoa! Hey, Piccolo, heads up!
[SUPER BUU laughing]
[yells]
[GOTENKS, PICCOLO] Aah!
Aah!
If he keeps this up,
the Lookout will be history.
[thinking] He could at
least let me take a look.
[grunting]
Gotenks, hit him before
he comes back around!
Yeah, I'll get him.
[yells]
A screaming ban--
[GOTENKS, PICCOLO groan]
A screaming banshee attack!
What are you doing?
Stop yelling and just
attack him before he kills us!
But, that's a little
boring, don't you think?
Isn't it, Piccolo?
Fine, have it your way.
Hold on to your socks,
Majin Buu. Uh!
[SUPER BUU groans]
[chuckles]
He looks kinda surprised.
[PICCOLO] That's the way
you were trained, Gotenks!
Nice move!
Thanks a lot, but he'll be
able to get out of here soon.
So, we should do something
else to finish him off.
Uh...
Which move should I use?
[growls lowly]
I got it! I'll do a
Spiking Buu-ball Slam!
[PICCOLO] What the heck
does that mean?
[GOTENKS] It's a new move,
fresh off the presses.
You wanna help?
[chuckles]
[GOTENKS] All right,
are you ready, Piccolo?
Come on, if we're going
to work as a team,
I need you to answer me
when I ask you a question.
--Do you see what I'm saying?
--Aah!
You taught me to be
a team player, Piccolo,
and right now
I need you to help me.
Believe me,
if there's any way
I thought I could
do this on my own,
I wouldn't be asking you.
Now, let's hurry! We don't
have a lot of time left!
Yes, I know that.
Are you ready?!
Just hurry!
[PICCOLO grunts]
[yells]
Spiking Buu-ball Slam!
[chuckles]
[thinking] Why does
the strongest fighter left
have to be so darn ridiculous?
Oh-ho!
[GOTENKS]
Oh yeah!
[GOTENKS chuckles]
Well, would you
get a load of that?
I've heard of meteorites
hitting the ground
that made smaller
craters than this.
Majin Buu must've been moving
pretty fast when he hit!
Hey! Down here!
Not too shabby, huh?
We make a good team.
Stay focused, Gotenks!
We're not done yet.
Are you sure?
Yeah! Now that's what I
call a slam-bang finish.
Wait, don't celebrate yet!
I'm sensing some
kind of disturbance.
Some great uprising power.
[GOTENKS] Hello! I know
you're still there, Majin Buu.
Come on! I've only got
five more minutes,
then we'll have to
wait an hour
until I can do Fusion again!
You'd be smart
to show your face.
Here I am about to
lose all of my powers
and be helpless to
defend myself! Really!
It's just poor
little Gotenks here,
all by his lonesome,
unable to fight back at all.
Can you hear me, Buu?!
Huh. I wonder
if he really died.
[laughs]
Just my luck.
I finally beat Majin Buu and
there's no one here to see it.
[BOTH gasp]
[PICCOLO]
Get back!
[yells]
[BOTH yell]
[NARRATOR] With a devastating
display of power,
Majin Buu has again
emerged from the rubble
to continue his destruction
of the planet Earth!
[NARRATOR]
Although Gotenks continues
to prove his worth as a warrior,
his strength is matched
by Buu's endurance.
Will Majin Buu
be able to hold on
until Gotenks
is no longer fused?
Stay tuned for more of the
excitement on Dragon Ball Z!