[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
hundreds of would-be
fighters gathered to compete
in the World Martial
Arts Tournament,
dreaming that maybe--just
maybe--they could
clench the title
of World Champion.
But the path
has many obstacles.
First off, there were one
hundred and ninety-four
adult entries, and
only sixteen spots.
And one was already
guaranteed to
the current holder of the
champion belt--Hercule.
The world's most famous fake.
To decide who would
stay and who would go,
a punching machine
was brought in
to measure the
fifteen strongest.
Hercule started the bidding with
an impressive one thirty-seven!
[PRELIM REF] Incredible!
He scored one hundred
and thirty-seven points!
[MR. SATAN pants]
[NARRATOR] At least, it seemed
impressive at the time.
Ha... ugh!
Next, please!
Number eighteen!
[NARRATOR] The Z Fighters
soon stepped to the plate,
trying their hardest to conceal
their ground-breaking strength.
But that's not
always easy...
[PRELIM REF] Seven hundred
and seventy-four?!
[squealing]
[gasping]
[NARRATOR] Then came Vegeta...
And, as we all know,
restraint is not his specialty.
[VEGETA grunts]
Oh, wow...
[NARRATOR] Needless to say,
the Z Fighters have
earned their places in
the tournament ring.
But it just might be a
while before the officials
can form enough
words to announce it!
[FIGHTERS whimpering]
[whimpering continues]
[VEGETA] Hmph.
[gasping, whimpering]
Break, you buy, right?
I'm giving up!
That guy would turn
me inside out!
[VIDEL gasps]
Nice, Vegeta...
Uhh...
Wait! You're not in the
least bit surprised?!
Didn't you see what
he did to that machine?!
Oh! I saw! Surprising!
I don't understand it!
It's like they're...
all in this big group together!
And... they can all
lift cars and busses!
They're all scoring
in the two hundreds
and my dad only got
a one thirty-seven!
Yeah... How weird...
Um... Hello...
We're experiencing a few...
technical difficulties,
but we should be getting
a new machine out here
pretty quick, so,
uh, stick around...
Hey, Vegeta...
I heard they're starting
the Junior Competition
in a few minutes in the
main arena! Do you wanna go?
Fine... Let's go...
Anything's better
than this lame sideshow!
[FIGHTERS gasping]
Just look!
See how they walk?
So tough...
Hello there!
Huh?!
So... you're the girl
I keep hearing about!
Introduce her, will ya?
Yeah! She's--
Ah...?
She's my friend, Videl!
[KRILLIN giggles]
Come on, Gohan!
Don't you mean
to say "girlfriend"?
You're embarrassing me!
[GOKU] Well, we don't want to
be late to see
Trunks and Goten fight.
It was nice meeting you, Videl.
[KRILLIN] Good luck, Gohan!
Bye!
[GOHAN] I wish they'd hurry
with that punching machine...
You know them?!
[GOHAN] Sure!
The man wearing
the orange uniform,
he's my dad!
What?!
I thought your dad was
with another woman!
Oh no! Just dead!
Didn't you see the ring
floating over his head?
Um, I think I need...
to lie down...
[CROWD roars]
[ANNOUNCER] Hey!
All you crazy fans!
Now first, let's make sure
you came to the right place!
Does anyone here
love martial arts?
[cheering]
[ANNOUNCER] Then
don't move an inch,
because you've landed
at the great--the only--
the World Martial
Arts Tournament!
First up:
The Junior Competition!
We've got 10 million
Zenni for the winner,
and 5 mil for the runner-up!
And we've also got
something extra special
for the Junior winner this year!
In fact, it's so special
it makes me wish
I were a kid just
for the chance!
You see, folks,
the winner gets to fight
with the legend himself!
The great Hercule!
[CROWD roars]
[MR. SATAN] Oh yeah!
[MR. SATAN laughs]
[CROWD cheers]
[CROWD] Mr. Satan!
Mr. Satan! Mr. Satan
[MR. SATAN roars]
[MR. SATAN yells]
--[MR. SATAN yells]
--[ANNOUNCER gasps]
[MR. SATAN gasps]
[MR. SATAN grunts]
[screaming]
[CROWD laughing, whooping]
[MR. SATAN] Yow! Oh, that hurt!
My head! Noo-urrghh...!
Can't believe it... Urrghh!
Are-- you okay there, sir?
[MR. SATAN squeals]
[CROWD gasping, murmuring]
[MR. SATAN gasps]
[MR. SATAN (mumbling)] Okay...
Pull it together... C'mon...
[MR. SATAN grunts]
Uh?
I'm jo-king!
[MR. SATAN laughs]
--[MR. SATAN] Yeah, it's a joke!
--[CROWD cheers]
You have an amazing sense
of humor, Hercule!
Hm, hm! Thank you!
[ANNOUNCER] Now, before we get
the Junior Competition rolling,
we've got a surprise treat
for all you loyal fans!
And I know you're gonna love it!
[MR. SATAN mutters angrily]
[ANNOUNCER] Seven years ago,
the world was left
hanging in suspense
when the live transmission
of the Cell Games
was violently interrupted!
But we have now have
completed a historic reenactment
of that day for you all to see!
[CROWD cheers]
What?! Hey, hold on!
Ooh! I always
wondered what happened!
Yeah, now we'll
see for ourselves!
[cheering continues]
This... won't be pretty...
You have got to turn that
blimp around immediately!
I never signed off on this film!
Come, now!
Don't be modest!
Who wants to
see this movie?!
[CROWD roars]
Great! Then let's hear
that world-famous cheer!
Wait! You know I can't--!
[CROWD] Mr. Satan! Mr. Satan!
Mr. Satan! Mr. Satan!
--Yeah!
--[CROWD roars]
That settles it!
Let the cameras roll!
[MR. SATAN gasps]
[TV JINGLE] ♪ Waves and rocks! ♪
[MOVIE NARRATOR] This
show was brought to you
by waves and rocks.
[CROWD whoops &amp; cheers]
[BOGUS CELL laughs]
Oh... You're kidding!
[BOGUS GOKU] We will
stop you, Cell monster.
That's me!
[PICCOLO growls]
[VEGETA growls]
[BOGUS CELL] Ha-ha.
It is I, Cell, who will
instead beat you! Ha-ha.
[BOGUS GOKU] Let's fight now.
Urgh.
[BOGUS CELL] Haah.
[BOTH grunt half-heartedly]
[BOGUS CELL] Take that.
[lame grunting continues]
It's... sickening!
Awwh, lighten up!
I think it's kind of funny!
[BOGUS CELL laughs]
[BOGUS CELL] You gang of
strangers were not hard,
but easy.
[BOGUS GOKU] Rats. We have lost.
[BOGUS CELL laughs]
[BOGUS CELL]
Now that I have beaten you,
I will blow up the world.
[BOGUS SATAN] Wait!
You haven't beaten ME!
[CROWD cheers]
[cheering continues]
[MR. SATAN groans]
[thinking] This
is embarrassing!
And they've got my
expression all wrong!
[BOGUS CELL]
You look very strong.
Here is a fire ball.
[BOGUS CELL laughs]
[BOGUS SATAN]
Stop your laughing!
[BOGUS CELL] What?
But how did you escape?
[BOGUS SATAN] Your useless
tricks are stupid and useless!
[CROWD cheers]
[BOGUS CELL]
Take my monster rays!
[BOGUS SATAN] Nothing you
do--huah--has scared me!
[BOGUS CELL] Oh my,
but now I am scared.
Please, will you forgive me?
[BOGUS SATAN] No!
Ha-ha! How can I forgive
an evil monster like you?!
You are a bad person and
you do not want to change!
--[BOGUS CELL screams (kinda)]
--[BOGUS SATAN] Hai-yaah!
--[BOGUS CELL grunts &amp; shouts]
--And take that! Ha-ha! Chop!
[BOGUS CELL yells]
[BOGUS CELL] Ah, I'm losing.
[BOGUS GOKU]
Mr. Satan is great
[BOGUS VEGETA]
I wish I were him.
[BOGUS CELL] I am beaten.
Aah.
[BOGUS SATAN]
Justice always wins!
[CROWD cheers]
[CROWD] Mr. Satan! Mr. Satan!
--Mr. Satan! Mr. Satan!
--[GOKU chuckles]
Well, it was
ridiculous and untrue,
but it kept me entertained!
[ANNOUNCER] Say, champ!
You're truly great!
Hey! Where'd you go?!
[MR. SATAN whimpers]
I'm finished!
That... was great
how you beat Cell!
Don't say that!
[CROWD] Mr. Satan!
Mr. Satan! Mr. Satan!
[KID 1] Are not!
[KID 2] Am too!
I'm gonna win and then I'll
shake Mr. Satan's hand!
Whatcha' buyin'
with the money?
[GOTEN laughs]
Toys, I guess!
You're such a toddler!
What about you?
I'm not sure what
I'm gonna buy...
Yeah, I guess when your family's
the richest in the world,
there aren't many
toys that you don't have.
Hah! Look at these kids!
One hit from me and
they'll start crying!
Hmph!
[KID 2] I swear I'm
gonna shake his hand!
[KID 1] Mm-mm!
I... can't decide...
Who are you
fighting first, Idasa?
[IDASA chuckles]
Oh, man! Just look!
It's that kid over there!
Whoa! He's, like puny!
[SIDEKICK B chuckles]
I say we give 'im a scare!
[IDASA growls]
We will...
Maybe I'll just buy you
a better-looking haircut.
[GOTEN] Hair what?
[IDASA] Hey, half-pint!
You're gonna be my first victim!
I hope you're
wearing your diapers!
[IDASA guffaws]
[IDASA] You'll need
the extra padding!
[IDASA grunts]
[chuckling]
Don't you flinch?
Not from... weaklings.
What?!
You had best walk away.
How dare you?!
Yeah, how dare him?!
[IDASA guffaws]
You've just sealed
your fate, shorty!
I'm gonna beat you so hard,
you'll have a concussion!
Sounds fun.
Gee...
[ANNOUNCER] Videos of the movie
you just saw will be on sale
at every exit
for only 19.95!
Now, lets grease
those fighting gears
and start the
Junior Competition!
[CROWD cheers]
It's amazing how it's changed.
Crazy, huh?
It looks like the ring's
a bit bigger this year!
Good... Makes for
better fighting.
Look! Trunks and Goten!
[ANNOUNCER]
Unlike the Adult Competition,
there is no qualifying round!
All 35 of these young fighters
are going to test
their might in the ring!
Rules are same
as the big leagues!
Whoever gives up,
lands outside the ring,
stays down for ten counts,
or loses consciousness
will lose it all!
Go all the way, Trunks!
Go, sweetie!
Like he knows
who "sweetie" is...
[IDASA'S MOM] This seat will
be absolutely perfect
for watching Idasa!
He's going to make his
mother so happy and wealthy!
[IDASA'S MOM laughs]
[ANNOUNCER] So
let's get crackin'!
The first match features
the 12 year-old Bert,
versus a 14 year-old named Fro!
Oh, darn!
It's starting!
I was hoping we'd
be done by now!
It's fine!
We'll see Goten
when he advances!
[CROWD cheers]
[FIGHTER KID A yells]
[FIGHTER KID B yells]
[BOTH yell]
[CROWD laughs]
Sir, about the videos...
Sorry for not asking...
But it was a gold mine!
We've already sold a
million copies today!
Great... Then I'll bill you!
[MR. SATAN laughs]
[LITTLE JAMES gasps, yelps]
[LITTLE JAMES wails]
[ANNOUNCER] Little James
has started to cry!
Is he going to give up?!
[wailing continues]
--[LITTLE JAMES yells]
--[FIGHTER KID C grunts]
[FIGHTER KID C yells]
[ANNOUNCER] Incredible!
Little James!
You have advanced
to the next round!
--[CROWD cheers]
--Yay! I won!
I won! I won! I won!
Boy... This is about as fun
as watching wallpaper dry.
[ANNOUNCER] Wow! Here's
another exciting match!
We've got
Kori-yu, at age 10...
Fighting against
Mokki, at age 8!
This should be a doosie!
Fight!
[KORI-YU grunts]
[MOKKI screams]
[KORI-YU growls]
[MOKKI yelps]
[ANNOUNCER] Hey!
[KORI-YU grunts]
[KORI-YU yells]
[ANNOUNCER screams]
[grunting, yelling]
[ANNOUNCER yells]
[ANNOUNCER] Out of
the ring! Kori-Yu wins!
[CROWD cheers]
[MOKKI cries]
[MR. SATAN] Don't cry.
It's okay!
Mr. Satan!
Be proud!
You have given all
these people a good show!
[MOKKI chuckles]
Ah, yeah!
[MR. SATAN] Good.
Now hop up here!
--[MOKKI laughs]
--[CROWD cheers]
Wow, folks! Is this
guy great or what?!
How could anyone not
cheer for a hero like this?
Fantastic!
[CROWD roars]
He's the greatest!
We love him!
[thinking] Tip one
for a successful image:
Look good with the kids!
[MR. SATAN yells]
What was that?
That's good marketing!
The goof really knows
how to milk a crowd!
[KRILLIN chuckles]
[cheering]
[GOHAN] Sounds like
they're having fun...
[cheering continues]
I just hate missing fun!
[HENRY grunts]
[ANNOUNCER] Henry is out of the
ring and Krishnikov advances!
Let's bring out the next pair!
8 year-old Trunks,
versus 15 year-old Idasa!
Yeah! He's finally up!
Do your best!
Oh, wait. Trunks' best
might hurt someone...
Do okay!
Are you ready to cry,
short-stack?!
Please... Don't talk.
Hah! You sure you
don't want to beg?!
You sure you
wanna live?
Wheee-hoo!
Whippernsapper!
He ain't got no chance
'gainst that 15 year-old!
Ice cream...
I love you!
--Idasa! I'm here!
--[OOLONG grunts]
--Yoo-hoo!
--Excuse me!
I wish they would match
Idasa with a bigger kid!
This won't even warm my boy up!
[BULMA growls]
Well, I just can't believe
my camera decided to break!
How do they expect me
to take a picture
of my son's rise to fame?!
Get him, Trunks!
You make that boy
sorry he ever met you!
Hon... You're dreaming.
[BULMA] Meeeh!
Let's go!
[IDASA growls]
Come on,
you little shortcake!
Fight!
Don't you worry...
You'll feel it soon
enough, big-mouth.
[IDASA yells]
--[IDASA screams]
--[CROWD gasps]
[IDASA'S MOM screams]
Oops.
Guess I shouldn'tve
hit him so hard, but...
...at least he's quiet.
This boy is out cold!
Trunks advances!
[CROWD whimpers]
[IDASA'S MOM squeals]
Idasa!
--[BULMA giggles]
--[OOLONG chuckles]
Oh well...
Looks like it won't be any fun
until Goten and Trunks fight.
You sure did beat
that boy fast, Trunks!
You see now why I wanted to
fight in the adult competition?
Do ya?!
Uh-huh!
[NARRATOR] The Junior
Competition is well underway,
and only one real
question remains:
Who will be the champion?
Trunks... or Goten?
Don't miss the next
episode of Dragon Ball Z!