[NARRATOR] Last time,
on Dragon Ball Z!
Mr. Popo led Bulma into
the barren reaches
of Yunzabit Heights,
in search of an
ancient spacecraft
that had once
belonged to Kami.
When their home
planet was in danger,
Kami's parents must have
put him on board this ship
and sent him here
to save his life.
[BULMA] It must run
by voice command...
But that means all of the
commands are in Namekian!
Let's try it...
See if you can tell it
to fly us to Jupiter...
Topurukuppa Jupe!
[COMPUTER]
Topurukuppa Jupe.
Look, we're here!
We're already at Jupiter!
All right! Now we can
fly this thing to Namek!
[NARRATOR] The adventure
continues... today!
[welding sounds]
[DR. BRIEF] I kind of feel
a little embarrassed asking,
but do you know
anything about
integrated micro-circuit
feedback loops
and their effect on after
burner ignition rates?
[BULMA] I didn't understand
anything you just said.
So, I guess just
plug stuff in
where it looks like it
fits and hope it works!
[DR. BRIEF]
Right-o!
He's got it all under
control, and don't worry,
it's an awesome ship...
It took us to Jupiter
in under ten seconds...
Seriously, I blinked,
and we were there.
Can you speak up? I'm having
a hard time hearing you.
I'm talking as loud
as I possibly can!
What?
I can't talk now, Krillin.
[welding sounds continue]
I can barely hear
myself think.
But, I'll stop by later...
And we can talk then.
[CHICHI humming]
What?
Heh, nothing...
Don't mind me.
[humming continues]
Here.
No...
Thank you.
Gohan, eat or you'll
never get better.
Do you want to spend the rest
of your life in a hospital?
No.
Good news... Goku!
[GOKU] Huh?
[door shuts]
Hey! Bulma said she
found a space ship
to take her to
Planet Namek.
She's already been
to Jupiter and back!
Her dad's
fixing it up now!
[GOKU]
Sounds great.
[GOHAN groans]
[KRILLIN snoring]
[footsteps]
[door opens, closes]
[CHICHI hums]
I thought these might
brighten up the room a bit.
Ah?
My little boy... Mm?
Huh?
[grunts angrily]
[CHICHI] What did you
do with my son?!
What do
you mean?
He's not here,
so where is he?
The last time I saw him, he
was in bed, reading his book.
That poor boy's hurt,
he needs to be in bed.
[grunts angrily]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[CHICHI] And you just
let him run off!
[KRILLIN and GOKU scream]
Thanks for
the flowers.
[car horns honk]
[GOHAN grunts]
Yow!
[GOHAN screams]
[GOHAN sighs]
That was...
a close one.
Gohan!
Surely he couldn't
go too far.
The doctor said his
legs were so weak.
I hope he doesn't
overexert himself!
[GOHAN grunting]
Here goes.
See, I knew
I felt better.
[CHICHI] Gohan!
Gohan!
I've been looking
all over for you.
Oh, hi Mom...
I, uh, thought some fresh
air would do me some good,
so I came up
here to read.
You had me
worried sick!
[GOHAN yells]
Hop on and we'll
go back to the room.
But... I can walk...
I feel fine.
[CHICHI]
Don't be silly.
Now, chop, chop...
Come on, Gohan.
There... See? That's
not so bad, now is it?
[BULMA] If the ship holds
up like I think it will...
Then we could easily make
it to the Planet Namek
in less than a
month's time...
I still have a few
repairs to make.
But I'd say we could leave
within the next five days.
Wonderful luck.
I thought we'd
never find a way
to get the Dragon Balls.
Great job!
Yes, congratulations, Bulma.
You've saved the day.
Well, Mr. Popo
found the ship.
And with his help, I'll find
the Dragon Balls in no time!
Huh? But, Bulma,
I can't go with you.
[BULMA] What?
I'm really sorry, Bulma,
but I can't go and abandon
the Lookout for two
months... I can't.
But you're the only person
I know who can speak Namek,
and how am I going to
start the ship without you?
You know, this entire mission
was counting on you!
You can't
just back out!
I'm sorry...
I have to stay here.
[BULMA gasps]
[KRILLIN] Don't worry, Bulma,
we'll figure something out!
I'm sure Mr. Popo can teach
you the Namekian words
you need to use
the computer!
I guess... It shouldn't
be too hard to grasp.
But, I don't wanna
go all by myself.
So who's gonna come
along to keep me company?
Hey, let's not everyone
volunteer at once.
I thought you
were my friends.
I am your friend,
but there's no way
you're getting me
in that tin can.
Yeah, like she was
really hoping you'd go.
[ROSHI] Ahem.
Two months alone
with Bulma...
Sign me up!
It'll be the trip of
a lifetime, I promise!
You better watch
yourself, old man!
Yes, ma'am.
Goku can't make it either...
That leaves you.
Krillin, will
you go with me?
It's not that I don't
want to help...
But I need
training...
We could be attacked
again at any moment...
And I want to be
ready next time.
Krillin... You can't
pass this up...
It would be a great
opportunity for training
once you get
to Planet Namek.
Alright, I'll go,
but when I get back,
I wanna see you in perfect
fighting mode again, Goku.
[GOKU] Don't worry about me.
I'll be out of here in no time.
Hey... Guys?
[CHICHI] What's wrong, Gohan?
Do you have a tummy ache?
[GOHAN groans]
I want to go with
Bulma and Krillin!
Wait a minute, Gohan...
You... don't wanna leave
me alone for two months.
But, Mom, Dad will
be here with you...
And... I really want
to go with them.
I... can't believe
what I'm hearing...
You'd rather go with
them than stay with me?!
Sorry, mom... But...
I really need to...
...try to help
bring Piccolo back.
ChiChi... Aw, let him go.
[CHICHI] I can't take
this anymore! I swear!
Why couldn't I have
a normal family
that sits down
and eats dinner?!
And talks about
their day!
And then maybe watches
some TV and goes to bed.
[ROSHI] You better find
a safe spot to stand in...
[GOHAN]
Don't be silly, Mom.
[CHICHI] I'm silly?
My son tells me I'm silly?!
I'm not the one who wants to
run around and be a superhero!
[GOHAN] Bulma, you'll take
me with you, won't you?
[CHICHI]
That's it!
I'm putting my
foot down, Gohan!
I won't let you leave me again.
You just came home!
After you had been gone
for a whole year, Gohan!
You're a child!
Act like one!
Don't throw away
your childhood
trying so hard to
be a brave adult!
Being a kid's the
best part of life!
You should be making friends
and playing baseball!
Not trying to
save the world!
I'm going!
[KRILLIN and ROSHI whimpering]
How did I raise such
a stubborn child?
There's no time for those
childish things, anymore.
My friends are gone, and
they're not coming back.
[GOHAN] I've got to help
find the Dragon Balls.
Mom, Piccolo died
trying to help me,
so I think I should do
everything I can to help him.
I can't sit around and do
nothing while Piccolo needs me.
I'm sorry I
yelled at you, Mom.
But I have to try...
You see, they're my friends.
[YAJIROBE chuckling]
Pretty good speech, kid.
You sure didn't learn
that from your father.
[OX KING]
Don't worry, ChiChi.
[OX KING] You have
a brave son there.
I'm sure he'll make
it back just fine.
[thinking]
That's my boy, Gohan...
Go show 'em what
you're made of.
I promise to keep an eye on
him at all times, ChiChi.
Nothing will happen
to your little boy.
[BULMA] And besides,
Krillin will be there, too.
Do you think you can learn
Namekian in five days?
Don't know... It could
take me a while longer
to input all the information
into the translator...
Hey... How 'bout we
meet up in ten days?
Sure.
On Namek,
hello is "Piconat".
[BULMA] "Picanot".
[COMPUTER beeping]
You get a clean
bill of health.
[KRILLIN screams]
[ALL laughing]
Aren't you
finished yet?
Be patient... Even
superheroes have to spend
some quality time
with their moms.
[CHICHI] It's time to
take your medicine.
I'll get
some water.
Give it a try.
Here goes.
Don't hold
back, Gohan...
I need to see if
you're really okay.
Okay.
[GOHAN] Hyaah!
Good... I think
you're ready, Gohan.
You sure made a
quick recovery.
But then again, I had
no doubt you would.
You've gotten
so strong!
[NARRATOR]
After ten stressful days
preparing for
the long journey,
the group gathered on
Master Roshi's island
to say their goodbyes and
set out for Planet Namek.
[KRILLIN]
I don't know...
You sure this
thing can make it
there and back in one piece?
It doesn't look very big.
[BULMA] It'll get
the job done, Krillin.
[BULMA] And besides,
if I were you,
I wouldn't be complaining
about a free ride.
You're lucky I'm gonna
let you sit up front.
You were going in
with the luggage.
[KRILLIN laughing nervously]
You think I'm
joking, but I'm not.
Did you do something with your
hair? Looks really good.
[BULMA] And don't try to win me
over with cheap compliments.
No, I mean it!
Well, thanks... I cut it
to fit in my space helmet.
That reminds me...
I wanted to ask you if I'm
gonna need a space suit.
'Cause I don't
have one.
It's not something people keep
in their closet, you know.
You'll be fine
without it.
Look! There's Gohan now!
Sorry we're late...
It took a while to
get all packed up,
but you wouldn't believe
how much stuff we've brought.
I hope you have
enough room in there.
This thing doesn't
look that big.
Come on, Gohan... Everyone's
out here waiting for you.
What's wrong, Gohan?
Why won't you come out?
[ALL gasp]
Are you feeling okay?
You sure you want to go?
[GOHAN] Mm-hmm...
[KRILLIN laughing]
I worried about not
having a space suit...
At least I don't have to
wear a little uniform.
Yeah... Dad thought I
looked pretty funny, too.
I don't know why.
I think it makes him look
like the cutest thing...
Well, don't you
think so, Gohan?
[KRILLIN] So, what's
with all this stuff?
Here's his
underwear, toothbrush,
coloring book,
and sleep mask.
And here's some snacks for
the trip and his medicine.
And we have
a hairdryer,
full dinner set with
salad and dinner forks, multi--
I think we
get the picture.
Can we go now?
This suit is heavy...
I'm looking forward
to zero gravity.
Careful out there...
You never know what
you might come up against.
Right.
Piccolo.
Bye, Grandpa...
Bye, Mom...
Bye, Master Roshi...
Bye, Turtle!
We'll be back. And
hopefully with our friends.
Piccolo.
[OX KING] Don't get
in too much trouble!
Bye, Gohan.
Mommy loves you!
Bye!
Wow, it's nice.
I'm impressed.
So, where should
I put this?
You said there was
a luggage compartment.
Just throw it in the
corner and sit down...
I'd hold on
to something.
What's wrong Bulma?
Are you mad?
No, I'm just
ready to leave...
We're departing
in five seconds.
Wait, Bulma, we're
not strapped in yet!
[BULMA]
5... 4... 3... 2... 1!
Uh, guys, I think we might have
left my stomach back on Earth.
I'm starting to wish you
stayed back there with it.
[ROSHI] I'm sure they'll
have a great time.
Namek must be a
beautiful place.
Bye, Gohan... Come
back to me safely.
It'll be smooth
sailing from here...
And now that we're
on autopilot,
how about cleaning
up this mess?!
Sure, Bulma.
[GOHAN] I can't even see
the Earth anymore.
[KRILLIN] Where you
going, Bulma?
I'll be right back...
I'm just going to change.
You mean you made yourself a
space suit just for take-off?
Man, I was only
trying to make a joke.
I guess we better start
cleaning up... Ready?
Give me a minute.
I need to change first.
Yeah, that's
probably a good idea...
What was your
mom thinking?
Sometimes I think
she really is crazy.
[GOHAN] It's all right.
[GOHAN] I packed my own clothes
when my Mom wasn't looking.
[GOHAN laughing]
[KRILLIN] You really do respect
Piccolo, don't you?
Yeah... About as
much as I do my dad.
[door clacking open]
So... Did you make that
outfit yourself, too?
You look tough.
Good, but I'm trying
to look mean...
I've had just about enough
of your wisecracks, Krillin.
So from now on we're going
by a whole new set of rules.
[BULMA laughing maniacally]
Uh-oh... I don't think I
like the sound of that much.
[thinking]
Good luck, Gohan.
[NARRATOR] Everyone is
counting on the young group
of adventurers to return
safely from their mission...
[NARRATOR] But they have
a vast distance to cross
before they reach
their destination,
and many unknown dangers
to face along the way!
Don't miss the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!