[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball Z,
Goku transformed himself
into a Super Saiyan 3,
stunning his opponents,
the evil wizard Babidi and his
forceful henchman, Majin Buu,
with his uncanny
strength and ability.
It seemed as though the monster
had finally met his match
in the form of
the Super Saiyan 3.
But even at this
intense power level,
Goku could not
topple Majin Buu.
Although for the time being,
absolute victory
was not Goku's goal.
[GOKU thinking]
What's taking Trunks so long?
I can't go on fighting
like this forever.
My energy's draining fast,
and Majin Buu just keeps
coming back for more!
[NARRATOR] The Saiyan just
needed to stall Majin Buu
while Trunks searched for
his mother's Dragon Radar.
[TRUNKS]
Hey, here it is! I found it!
Well, that's just
wonderful, Trunks.
Now, we all have
time for a relaxing lunch.
What is it with you and food?
Gotta go, love ya!
[GOKU thinking]
There he is. Good.
He's on his way
back to the Lookout.
He must've finally
found the Dragon Radar.
I guess it's time to
wrap up my business here
so I can head back, too.
[NARRATOR]
With Goku's task complete,
he powered down
to his normal state,
and bid adieu to
Babidi and Majin Buu.
[GOKU]
See ya.
[BUU]
Huh? Uh? Huh?
Don't just stand there floating.
Get your doughy pink body moving
and find him right now!
[NARRATOR] But Majin Buu had had
enough of being bossed around
and abused by Babidi.
The time had come for a mutiny.
[BUU] You teach me
lots of good things,
but Buu think it time
Babidi go bye-bye-bye.
[NARRATOR] Now there's a new
master of evil on the loose,
and he's angry!
[BUU]
Bye! Bye!
[BABIDI screams]
[BUU] You go bye-bye now!
Bye-bye, Babidi!
No more tell Buu what
to do! No more meanie!
Pull!
Ha, ha!
[cackles]
Woo! Ha, ha!
[cheering]
What's the matter?
What's wrong, Dad?
Goku, what is it you're sensing?
[GOKU]
It's Majin Buu. He's-He's...
[PICCOLO]
He's what?
He's killed Babidi.
[GOTEN, KRILLIN gasp]
He killed him?!
Well, this is quite a
surprising turn of events.
I had a feeling that he might.
They didn't really
seem to get along.
So, what happens now?
Majin Buu has no one telling
him what to do anymore.
There's no denying that Babidi
was definitely the brains
of that particular operation.
[sighs] Maybe things will
turn out happy after all, guys!
Yeah!
I'm not so sure.
The only thing
we can do now is hope.
I promise, give them two days
and they'll be ready to fight.
There's no need for
you to destroy West City
or kill anyone else.
I'm asking, have some patience.
They'll come to you.
Are they really strong?
Unbelievably.
[GOKU thinking]
We can only hope.
[BUU] Buu so free! Buu so free!
Like bird in no cage.
[laughs]
So free!
[BUU]
What do Buu do first?
Buu have so much fun now!
No more Babidi tell
Buu what to do.
Over there! Look fun!
Look like fun! Look like fun!
Over there! Fun!
Huh?
[yelps]
[DRIVER] Hey! Watch where
you're goin', hot shot!
It's Majin Buu!!
[BUU thinking] This make
Buu happy. Verry happy!
They look much like toys!
Buu like to play with toys!
[inhales]
[screams]
[BUU giggles]
[inhales]
[CROWD screams]
[BUU]
You go, Buu!
[laughs]
[CROWD screams]
[CROWD murmuring]
[BUU]
Ready?
Set!
[can rattling]
[CROWD murmuring]
Go!
[BUU giggling, cackling]
[laughs]
Hm?
[shrieks]
P-Please!
Ooh!
[shrieks]
Help! Somebody, please
help me! It's Buu!
P-Please, don't hurt me!
Hello girl, you think Buu sexy?
[yelps] What? Yes, I think
you're very, very sexy!
Yay! Then give Buu smooch!
[screams]
Why you teasing Buu?!
--[screams]
--You play with Buu feelings!
[BUU]
Hm... What this?
So, Earth girls like boys
pretty like this, huh?
How Buu s'posed live up
to body image in magazine?
Ah, Buu know!
[gulps]
Baby!
[screams]
Oh no! Get away!
You girls don't
know what you want!
How do you like candy?!
[screams]
[BUU]
Mm-mm-mm!
Ah! Yes, yes. Very nice!
Buu like girls!
Buu so great!
Now, do a flip! Ha, ha!
Boom! Boom!
[BUU cackles]
Buu can't wait to
play with the strong guys!
That whole city! This is bad!
[growls]
He's even worse without Babidi!
[GOKU] Hmm. I guess it's just in
his nature to cause destruction.
It's probably the only
thing he's ever known to do.
No! Don't go making
excuses for him.
There's no reason
to demolish planets,
regardless of
personality defects.
Don't worry, I'm fairly certain
we can keep him from
wiping out the entire planet.
Buu seemed very
eager when I told him
stronger fighters
than me would be
facing off against
him in two days. So...
...that buys us some time.
But I can't help feeling bad
for all the innocent people down
there who stand in his way.
But we can bring
everything back to normal
with the Dragon Balls, right?
Perhaps, Krillin, but that
doesn't do us any good
if the boys aren't prepared
to fuse and defeat Majin Buu
in these next two days.
[GOTEN]
Hm?
[PICCOLO]
That should be our priority.
You and the boys are going
to have to learn fast, Piccolo.
My time here on
Earth is running out.
I have less than an hour.
Less than an hour?!
No, you must have
more than that.
It hasn't been a full day yet.
Why do you have to
leave so soon, Dad?
Please don't. I like you.
I like you too, Goten,
but it seems Super Saiyan 3
is a level that can only be
handled in Other World.
The living world has more
rules than Other World,
and transforming
takes too much energy.
So I got very, very tired.
Oh no! So that's why you
seem so exhausted, huh?
A little fatigue and energy loss
is nothing Dende
can't take care of.
No I can't. For this I have
to return to the Other World.
[BABA]
Tick-tock. Tick-tock. Tick-tock.
Greetings, Goku. At the tone,
your time remaining on this
Earth will be 30 minutes.
Baba, what are you--
Thirty minutes?! Ah!
Is that all the time I've got?
[BABA]
At the tone, Goku -- beeeeeep!
Trunks had better hurry up.
There's no time!
[TRUNKS thinking]
Trunks is on the way, guys!
[GOHAN grunting]
[GOHAN thinking] The sword
is an extension of my body.
Feel the sword.
Be the sword.
[grunting]
Don't hurt yourself, Gohan!
[panting]
Incredible!
Gohan's natural ability
to handle the Z Sword
with such finesse is uncanny.
I've never seen anything
quite like it, Master.
What did I tell you, Kibito?
Gohan is the one!
Everything is going exactly
according to my plan.
Soon enough, Gohan will
be ready to slay Majin Buu,
and restore order
to the universe.
[panting]
Don't wear yourself out, Gohan.
Rest for a few minutes.
You've done so much,
more than I even dared hope.
No, I still have
a long way to go.
Huh?
[GOHAN thinking]
I won't let them down again.
I may have been unprepared
for Majin Buu before,
but I refuse to be
defeated by him this time.
It's gonna take
everything I've got,
but I'm willing to
give that and then some.
I just hope that's enough.
Until then, all I
can do is practice.
[KRILLIN, GOTEN grunting]
Goku, I've been meaning
to ask you a question.
Go ahead.
When you went
Super Saiyan 3...
Would it have been possible?
Could you have actually defeated
Majin Buu once and for all,
if you really tried?
Well, I don't know.
I mean you have to
admit that Majin Buu
is no ordinary opponent.
It might have been
impossible for me to win.
Might?! Why didn't
you at least try to
give him everything
that you had?
Were you afraid of
what would happen
if your body was
destroyed on Earth?
No.
By all accounts,
I shouldn't even
be here in this world.
It's not my place to do that.
This is their world, Piccolo.
Even if I did somehow
defeat Majin Buu,
he wouldn't be the last villain
to terrorize the Earth.
And then who would be
prepared to save them?
Call me crazy,
but after watching those
boys fight each other
at the Junior Division,
I decided to take a chance.
[PICCOLO] So you're going
to wager the world's future
on the shoulders
of little children?
[GOKU] I think it's a
pretty safe bet, don't you?
You've always been a
hopeless dreamer, Goku.
Goku, I'm sorry.
Well, give him my regards when
you see him in the Other World.
[GOKU] I'm sure that Gohan
misses you very much, too.
He was always fond of you.
[GOKU] You were like
family to him, Piccolo.
Hey! Heads up, guys!
Trunks just flew in!
It's so good to see my little
Trunks. You must be tired.
Mom! I'm fine.
[BULMA] Of course you are,
dear. You're so grown up.
Here it is, sir! Confirm:
Is this your Dragon Radar?!
Confirmed! Good job, soldier.
Mission accomplished.
Thank you, sir!
Great! Now, thanks to Trunks
we can track down
the Dragon Balls
and wish for everything
to be brought back to normal.
When do we get to
train for the fusion?
You guys didn't start
without me, did you?
Of course we didn't.
It takes two to fuse.
Ooh! Ooh! Wouldn't it be cool
if I could fusion with myself
and become two of me? Huh, Dad?
[GOKU chuckles]
[laughs]
[GOKU, GOTEN, TRUNKS laugh]
[TRUNKS]
I don't get it.
[GOKU] Goten! Trunks! We have to
begin our training right away.
[GOTEN, TRUNKS]
Yes, sir!
[GOKU] Now, I don't
have much time left,
so we're going to need
to work hard and fast.
The fate of the world depends
on your cooperation. Got it?
[BOTH]
Sir, yes, sir!
Wow! What do you
think got into them?
Well, maybe you
can teach these kids
some new tricks after all, Goku.
Let's begin!
First, you two have to realign
your energies with one another.
[GOTEN, TRUNKS]
Yes, sir!
Buu!
Target has been located
and confirmed, Major.
This operation should
be a piece of cake.
Preparing to launch missiles
once we get that freak
in our cross-hairs.
Lock and load!
[BUU laughs]
Abort! Abort!
Buu want to play! Don't you
want to play with Buu?
Okay, I think, uh, we managed
to lose him back there--
Huh?
[screams]
[BUU]
Peek-a-Buu!
That tickles!
[whimpering]
--Buu!
--[PILOT screams]
[BUU grunts]
Wa-hoo-hoo!
Toys don't last long as used to.
[GOTEN, TRUNKS yelling]
It's amazing how great
their powers are,
especially at
such a young age, wow!
Trunks, Mommy's proud of you!
[GOTEN, TRUNKS yelling]
Great!
Your energies are perfectly
matched. Just keep practicing,
otherwise you'll slip out
of sync with each other.
Hey, you don't look so good,
Goku. Even for you.
Thanks, but I'll be all right.
Just a little tired.
Yeah, it's nothing, really.
[PICCOLO thinking] I've never
seen Goku so weak before.
That Super Saiyan 3
transformation
must have really taken its toll.
[GOKU grunts]
Now, are you ready to attempt
the most difficult
part of fusion?
It'll require
a lot of patience,
and some real discipline.
--Well, yeah!
--Yes!
Once you've matched
your energies precisely,
you must strike a delicate
series of poses together.
If either one of you is
even the slightest bit off,
the fusion will fail.
Now, I'm about to teach
you the exact moves.
So, pay close attention, 'kay?
Yes!
To get it started,
the two of you will stand
right next to each other.
Then go like this,
and make sure your arms
are straight. Then you say:
Fu... You'll approach each
other with outstretched arms,
moving exactly three steps over,
and once you got that you say...
...sion!
Quarter turn and watch
the angle of your knee.
Ha!
Now watch! Point your
fingers parallel,
and don't forget the angle of
your legs! It's very important.
This might be a bit tough.
[BUU]
Boooooooooooom!
[NARRATOR] Without anyone
to keep him under leash,
Majin Buu has become even
more dangerous than before!
Now, it's your turn
to try, boys!
[BOTH]
Yes!
[NARRATOR] Can Goten and
Trunks really master
the complex art of fusion
before Goku has to
return to Other World?
They'll have to,
if there's any hope
of defeating Majin Buu.
But they'd better hurry.
Goku's time is running out,
and so is the planet's!
Don't miss the next exciting
installment of Dragon Ball Z!