[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z!
Piccolo squared off
against the diabolical Cell
in an effort to prevent
the evil Android
from absorbing
any more innocent victims!
[NARRATOR] Cell is Dr. Gero's
most fiendish creation.
Designed by a computer
and created from the cells
of Goku, Vegeta, Frieza,
and all the other
great martial arts masters.
His unquenchable thirst
for power makes him
the most dangerous foe
the Z-Fighters have ever faced!
His mission: to seek out
and absorb Androids 17 and 18
into his being,
thereby transforming himself
into the most powerful
fighter who has ever lived!
Piccolo stood firm,
the only obstacle between
Cell and his ultimate goal.
But the cunning creature
managed to easily evade
the Super Namek's clutches!
...I have a date
with a couple of friends,
and it would be rude
of me to make them wait.
But here's a
parting gift before I go!
[chuckles]
Solar Flare!
[NARRATOR] Disappearing
behind the blinding flash
of his Solar Flare,
Cell fled the scene
to begin his search
for Androids 17 and 18!
Now, it's up to
Trunks and the others
to reacquire the monstrous
creature before he can
absorb the other Androids!
If Cell succeeds in
accomplishing his goal,
all hope for the earth is lost!
Hurry Z-Fighters!
Failure is not an option!
[PICCOLO] And for that reason,
he stole Trunks' time machine
and traveled here,
where for the last four years
he's been living underground,
developing into
the monster you saw today.
There. So you see,
this "Cell" will try to find
the other Androids at all costs.
Uniting with them
is the only way
he can ever become "complete."
Great... Just great...
Well... once again it's up to
us to stop him isn't it?
Whatta jip!
How do we find him now?
I mean, if Cell knows
that Piccolo is strong enough
to beat him before
he becomes complete,
he'll probably try to keep
his energy concealed from us.
Well, we'd better
figure something out
before he finds those Androids,
or I'll tell ya what guys,
we're going to be
in big trouble!
And not just us, Tien.
This monster is a danger to
every planet in the universe!
Remember,
Frieza and Frieza's father
are both a part of Cell now.
[gulps]
[VEGITA] Big deal!
I say let him become "complete."
If Cell destroys the Androids
he'll save me the trouble.
And fighting one battle is
much simpler that fighting four.
[VEGITA] I don't care
how powerful he becomes,
I'll still beat him!
Hold on, Vegeta.
The Androids alone were
more than we could handle,
and if Cell absorbs their power,
he'll be stronger
than all of them combined!
Do not question
my ability, Namek!
Not unless you want to find out
how powerful I really am!
[grunting]
[VEGITA] I do not
fear this new challenge!
Rather, like a true warrior,
I will rise to meet it!
[grunts]
Yes... I am now a Super Saiyan!
But I won't stop there!
I will ascend!
Huh?
Uh...
Huh? What? How can he be
stronger than a Super Saiyan?
I'm sure Kakarot
will try to do the same.
Don't you think?
[VEGITA] Now, if any of you
would like to take on Cell
or the Androids
while I'm away, be my guest!
I'll be back to finish
the job once you've failed!
[KRILLIN coughing]
Sometimes he really
gets on my nerves!
He's going to try
to surpass a Super Saiyan!
Is that...
Is that really possible?
[KRILLIN] Hey, Trunks!
Hm? Huh?
Explain this to me again.
Tell me what would happen
if we went back in time
and destroyed the Androids
before they woke up?
Well... it... might help
the future of that world,
but it wouldn't change anything
that's already happened here.
So if that's how this
time travel stuff works,
then it wouldn't do us
any good to destroy
the unfinished Cell
back at Gero's lab... Right?
[KRILLIN]
It wouldn't affect the Cell
from the future, now would it?
Right. Not the Cell
from my world.
But at the very least,
we should prevent another Cell
from ever being born
into this world!
[PICCOLO]
All right! Listen up!
You two go to Dr. Gero's lab
if you think it will help.
I'll stay here
and try to track down Cell!
Right. I'll give you a hand!
[grunts]
You know, If for some
reason you can't find Cell
you should head back
to Master Roshi's.
I mean, if nothing else,
you might be able to
find him on
the TV News stations.
Yeah... Good idea...
That's it!
Man, to be stronger
than a Super Saiyan...
I've never even
considered that a possibility!
[KRILLIN] I'm not sure
I believe it either, Trunks.
But if it is possible,
Vegeta and Goku are
just the guys to do it!
[thinking] And if they
can do it, then so can I!
[birds cawing]
[GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN] Huuuh! Ha!
[yells, grunts]
[yells]
[CHICHI] Go-han!
Gohan... It's your mom!
Oh... There you are!
[CHICHI] You're really
studying hard today, Gohan.
Why don't you take a break
and have a little snack.
You've certainly earned it!
[chuckles]
Wow. My little boy
is finally growing up.
I'm so proud.
Someday people will say,
"Who's that great man
with his nose in the book?"
[laughs]
Now... Keep up
the good work, Gohan.
M'kay!
[CHICHI humming]
I'm tired of studying! Darn!
I just wanna train
and get strong
so I can help everybody
like my father does!
[yells]
Hm.
Yep! That boy
is really somethin'!
[ROSHI]
Just like his old man...
♪
[teeth chatter]
It's cold.
Hey Trunks...
How do you suggest we
go about finding the entrance
to the basement
under all this rubble?
[TRUNKS] Krillin...
I think you better stand back.
Huh?
Hm...
[TRUNKS] Krillin!
[KRILLIN] Huh? What?
You find something?
[TRUNKS]
I think this is it!
Take a look!
[KRILLIN] Well whatta you know?
That's it!
[TRUNKS]
C'mon, let's check it out!
Okay.
[KRILLIN]
Sure is dark down there...
Watch your step, now.
Hm...?
[TRUNKS] This must be
Dr. Gero's master computer.
[quavers]
[KRILLIN]
This thing is the brains
behind the androids... and Cell?
Trunks. Let's destroy it!
It's responsible
for all this mess!
Look. There's something
inside of here...!
[KRILLIN] What?
This has to be Cell
still in his larval form...
Wow...!
Man, that thing is
made up of cells
from all of the greatest
fighters of the world.
It has Goku's cells
and even some of mine!
[KRILLIN] Ewww... Gross!
Yeah. Especially since we know
what this will become.
[TRUNKS] Eventually this
larva will outgrow its tank.
After that, it's not long
before it sheds its skin
in some sort of a
bizarre metamorphosis...
Then, it will continue to grow
into a monster--
into that evil monster, Cell!
[TRUNKS] And all because
this computer is programmed
to carry out
Dr. Gero's master plan.
Come on. Why don't
we just blast that thing
and the lab too?!
No...! Stop...!
Wait a minute, Krillin.
[KRILLIN] What is it, Trunks?
[TRUNKS] I can't believe it!
It's all here!
What? What's all there?
What is it, Trunks?
Well... it looks like
the designs for Android 17!
Android 17?
[KRILLIN] I don't mind
telling you, Trunks,
that thing scares me.
It's those eyes
of his, you know?
There's something
about them that's just...
creepy...
Yes! This could be
our lucky break!
By studying this
we may be able to find out
Android 17's weak spot.
Hey! Yeah! Great idea!
[KRILLIN] Hey are there any
other plans over there...?
You know, like, maybe Cell's?
[TRUNKS]
Nah... Just some crazy plan
for a gas powered toaster oven.
[KRILLIN]
We've got what we need!
Whatta ya say we blow
this place to smithereens?!
Yeah!
♪
Payback time! For all
the suffering you've caused!
[TRUNKS yells]
[TRUNKS and KRILLIN] Haaahhh!
[TRUNKS] Krillin,
this place is coming down.
Let's get outta here!
Okay!
[KRILLIN] Woo yeah!
That was a blast!
Now for the grand... finale!
[KRILLIN] Finding the plans
for Android 17
really was a
lucky break wasn't it?
[TRUNKS] Yeah!
[thinking] I just hope we can
decipher them in time
to do some good.
[TRUNKS] Krillin...
I want you to take these plans
to my mother. I'm sure she'll
be able to figure them out.
[KRILLIN] Uh, sure, but...
aren't you coming with me?
[TRUNKS] No. I'm going to find
my father and train with him.
If he really is
able to achieve something
beyond his Super Saiyan powers,
maybe he can
show me how to as well!
[KRILLIN] Listen, Trunks.
I don't want to be
the bearer of bad news,
but I don't think Vegeta
will let you train
with him. He's very... uh...
independent.
Yeah. I don't really want to go,
but I think I should, Krillin.
See, it's my father.
I must prove to him
that I am worthy
to fight along side of him.
And if I train with him,
maybe I can
convince him of that.
Well... All right...
If it's something
you really have to do...!
[TRUNKS]
Take care of this, my friend.
[KRILLIN] I will.
Wish me luck?
You'll need it!
Yeah.
Oh yes, it was Cell all right.
[TIEN] It's just as we feared.
He's feeding on these people!
Making himself stronger,
little by little!
There's a good chance that
he's still somewhere nearby.
[TIEN]
Let's get a better view!
Do you sense anything?
No... Nothing.
[grunts]
♪
Whoo...
[gasps]
[PEOPLE murmur]
[commotion]
[screams]
Ah!
Hm?
It's Cell... I know it is!
He's attacking!
Somewhere close!
Let's get him!
[MAN] No, please!
[groans]
[chuckles]
Down there!
[grunts]
[TIEN] Look at this place!
What a disaster!
How could he do this
all by himself?
I don't believe it!
Darn! Cell! We're too late...
He moves too fast!
He knew we were coming.
Of course! He could
sense us. That's just great!
Now we need to hide
our energy, but we can't!
[TIEN] Not if we wanna move
fast enough to catch him!
[laughs] Good... Good...
Let the silly fools
continue looking for me
while I enjoy another meal!
[DR. BRIEF]
Everything you need to know
is right here
in black and white.
[BULMA] You mean,
we just have to figure out
the weak points
of Android 17, right?
And then we have to stop him
from uniting with Cell!
Mmm... Yup! You've got it now!
However, there's one
thing I don't get.
It's sad...
You know, if only Dr. Gero
had used his talents for good,
the world would be
a better place today.
Wow! It looks like
these Androids are made up
of organic substances
patterned after human cells.
So that's how it's possible
for Cell to merge with them
at a cellular level.
Uh... What?
Hmmm. I may know where
to find a few weak spots.
If I'm right,
I believe they'll lie
in the smaller
control mechanisms.
[chuckles nervously]
Hey! We'll have to
run a few tests. Hold on!
Uh! Well, hurry up!
[GOHAN yells]
[breathes heavily]
[GOHAN thinking]
Father, don't worry...
Everything will be all right.
I'll look after you.
I'm training and I'm
getting stronger everyday.
I will protect you! I promise.
We must be getting close.
16, how far are we
from Goku's house?
Not far now.
[NARRATOR] As the Androids
draw nearer to their target,
the sinister Cell
continues his rampage!
Attacking anyone
who stands in his way
and draining them
of their life force.
Victim by victim,
he is getting stronger.
And it's only a matter of time
before he completes
his evil plan.
[NARRATOR] Cell is scheming to
unite with Androids 17 and 18,
and if he succeeds,
the fate of the world is sealed.
But what's to become
of the bedridden Goku?
Will he ever
break free of the virus
that has him in its grasp?
Find out on the
next exciting episode
of Dragon Ball Z!