[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Goku journeyed into space
and brought back a friend.
Dende!
Taking over Kami's position
as guardian of Earth,
the young Namek
didn't waste any time!
His first task: a new
set of Dragon Balls!
[NARRATOR] By restoring
the dragon,
Goku hopes to bring
back all the people killed
during Cell's violent rampage.
Now all he has to do is
find the Dragon Balls!
And as history has shown,
that can be a painful task.
[GOKU] Only five more.
[NARRATOR] But he
better make it quick,
because the evil Cell
is growing impatient.
[CELL] How boring, I should
not have given them this long.
[NARRATOR] And the
tournament is coming soon.
Now, get ready for today's
episode of Dragon Ball Z!
[TRUNKS yells]
[grunting]
Uh, are... you
really studying, Gohan?
Yeah! I've spent all this
time training with my dad,
so I kinda figured I should
study for a while
like my mom wants.
Yeah! I guess that'd be fair.
[DENDE] Hey, I brought
some notes with me too.
Here, we'll study
them together!
[KRILLIN] Whoa, gee! They give
you guys homework on Namek too?
[DENDE] Well, yeah!
It takes a lot of
hard work to learn
how to be a good
guardian, you know.
Huh. And here I thought
that all just came naturally.
All this homework!
This is giving me bad
flashbacks from algebra class.
[ALL laugh]
[TRUNKS grunts]
[laughing continues]
[KRILLIN] Well,
you guys give me a shout
if you need a study break.
I'm gonna go to Master Roshi's.
[GOHAN] Okay!
There are only
a few days remaining.
I wonder if Goku will be able
to find all the Dragon Balls?
[ANNOUNCER] Welcome everyone
to today's extravaganza!
Now let me ask you a question:
Who here loves Mr. Satan?!
'Cause I sure don't hear ya!
[CROWD roars]
[cheering continues]
Well, here he is! The
man with the iron hands!
World-wide
Martial Arts Champion!
[drumroll]
[ANNOUNCER] Hercule Satan!
[MR. SATAN growls]
[CROWD roars]
[growling continues]
[ANNOUNCER] I-I simply
don't believe it!
Mr. Satan is not pulling one!
Not two! Not three!
But FOUR tour busses behind him!
--Oh my! Isn't that incredible!
--This guy's too much...
[CROWD cheering]
[MR. SATAN] Who do you love?!
[MR. SATAN yells]
[CROWD cheers]
What's this? He's pulling
something from his cape...
What do you suppose
our hero has got?!
Oh my!
He's got three
mega-sized phone books!
They're from West Town,
Ladies and Gentlemen,
and you all know
how big THOSE are!
[MR. SATAN growls]
Surely he's not
going to rip them all?!
[MR. SATAN yells]
[ANNOUNCER gasps]
[MR. SATAN laughs]
[CROWD murmurs]
He did! He really did it!
[CROWD roaring]
Mr. Satan, can you tell
us all about your ambitions
for the Cell Games?
So, you want to know
what I'm gonna do to Cell?!
Exactly the same thing
I'm gonna do to this bus!
[MR. SATAN yells]
[ANNOUNCER laughs]
[ANNOUNCER] Well,
that settles it, folks!
Cell's about to have
a big iron fist
where his stomach should be!
Let's have a cheer
for the man of the year!
[CROWD roars wildly]
[ANNOUNCER]
Seriously, Mr. Satan,
is there anything you can't do?
Hold on!
[MR. SATAN growls]
[laughing]
[ANNOUNCER] Now why
don't 'cha come over here
and sign some autographs?
[CROWD cheering]
That's just sad...
[ROSHI sips]
It sure is. Somebody
could have used that bus.
[GOKU] Alright! This makes four!
So... how'd it go?
Did you advance?
[VEGETA chuckles]
[PICCOLO] Not bad, Vegeta.
[PICCOLO] But it's not enough.
Oh, wow! How do you like that?
Two Dragon Balls
are moving at once!
Somebody must've beat me to 'em!
[chickens clucking]
[TAO grunts]
[INTERCOM] Who is it?
[TAO] It's me.
[INTERCOM] Oh, General Tao!
I've been waiting for you!
So Tao, I sure hope you brought
the goods that you promised me.
[TAO chuckles]
[TAO] But of course!
[VODKA gasps]
[TAO chuckles]
So these are the
famous Dragon Balls
that make any wish
come true, is that right?
A valuable buy at any price,
and a bargain at just
two hundred thousand each.
And even if that monster
destroys everyone on Earth
I can still survive with these?
I can sit as snug as a bug
in my fortress here
and wait for
Cell to go away, ah?
I accept gold only.
And then, after Cell
has done his dirty work,
I will step out from
the rubble and build an empire!
Think of it!
No rival gangsters!
No meddling police!
They will call me "Emperor!"
Now how long
will it take you
to find the rest of
the Dragon Balls?
[TAO] Don't you
worry about that,
notice how quickly
I found these two!
Yeah, that's right!
I trust you there, General!
[TAO chuckles]
[TAO] I probably won't
find the others
on the black market like these,
but he doesn't have to
know about that.
That's what I call a big door!
[sirens blaring]
Huh?!
Hey, I'm not expecting anyone.
Huh? That's funny!
What? A Dragon Ball?!
What the--?!
I'll bet they're
in here for sure!
Seems the chicken has
brought his own frying pan.
Huh? Chicken?
Where's a--?
[TAO] We should take
care of him at once!
[VODKA] Huh? Uh...
Oh! Oh, yeah, sure!
Let's get him!
[VODKA chuckles]
Chicken...?
Huh?
Hello? Is anybody home?
Well, I'm coming in now!
[VODKA chuckles]
[VODKA] Alright, Mister!
It's time to cook your chicken.
Huh?
[VODKA laughs]
[ALL cheer]
[VODKA] That's what
I'm talkin' about!
Wow! These things are sharp!
Someone could really get hurt!
[VODKA] Uhhh...
[VODKA] Uh, what just happened?
Could someone please explain?
Looks like your weapons haven't
been inspected very recently.
Well, have they been?!
[HENCHMEN] No, boss! We, uhh...
You idiots!
How many times have I told you
to inspect the weapons
so that they'll work
when we need them to?!
[HENCHMEN] You never said that!
Well then, we'll just
have to wait
'til he comes in here
with his Dragon Balls
and then we'll
threaten him in person!
Hey, I'm really close.
Well, stranger, why don't
you come in here and visit?
[VODKA chuckles]
[GOKU] Hello?
[VODKA] That's right, over here!
[VODKA] Don't just stand
there! Please, come in!
[GOKU gasps]
Yeah, now I've got 'em!
Wouldn't 'cha know!
I was about to
say the same thing.
Now just give up
the Dragon Balls
nice and slow
and then go away
or this is going
to get very ugly!
[VODKA whimpers]
Huh?
Hey, General Tao, is that you?
Pardon?
Remember me? My name's Goku!
[TAO] Go... ku?
We've had our differences,
but it's good to see you again!
Why me...? Why...?
[VODKA chuckles]
But first you'll tell me where
you've hidden your chicken!
That's right,
I know you have one!
Chicken?
Where?
Don't play dumb!
The one with the fryin' pan!
Is this chicken
like a pet of yours?
[HENCHMAN A] Stop confusing him!
Just give us your Dragon Balls!
[GOKU] Hey, wait!
[HENCHMAN A grunts]
[VODKA gasps]
[HENCHMAN B growls]
Quick! Pump him full of lead!
I should really learn
not to use that much power.
Fire!
--[gun fires]
--[VODKA squeals]
[VODKA whimpers]
[HENCHMAN B gasps]
He's some kinda monster!
[HENCHMAN B wails]
[GOKU] Sorry about that,
mister. Are you okay?
Hmm?
Boss, what now?
Nobody panic!
I've had a perfect
defense mechanism
installed for bad situations
such as we have here.
[VODKA] Everyone get inside!
[HENCHMAN A gasps]
Wait! Wait for me!
Come on, you can make it!
Are you okay?
Yeah, boss.
[VODKA laughs]
[VODKA] What are you gonna
do now, strong guy?
This wall... it's solid!
[VODKA] Just try to get in
here! I double dare you!
Try it!
[VODKA laughs]
[VODKA stammers]
General, please!
Make! Him! Go! Away!
Well, I'm feeling...
a bit... sick today!
I feel bad!
You guys spent all that time
finding those Dragon Balls
and I don't have anything to
give you in exchange for them.
I wish I could
make this a fair trade...
[TAO] Oh really?
How about this, Goku?
Let's play a little game.
[VODKA gasps]
If you can untangle all three
of these puzzle rings
by tomorrow at dawn,
then both of our
Dragon Balls will be yours!
But if you cannot,
then you will surrender
the ones you've collected!
Fair and square,
wouldn't you say?
Yeah, I guess.
Oh! Puzzle rings!
Tao, now that is a great idea!
Well, yes! So, Goku, do we
have ourselves a deal or not?
You bet!
I've never tried it, but
I'm sure it can't be too bad!
Surely not!
Now let's say we get our
good friend here a comfy chair.
Yeah, sure!
Now, may I get
your jacket for you?
We want you to be comfortable.
[GOKU] Oh, thanks!
[TAO] I'll just hang this up!
[GOKU laughs]
[TAO] Now we'd hate to disturb
you, so, we'll withdraw.
Sure, that's fine.
[TAO] We'll leave this man with
you in case you need anything.
And I'll just turn this off.
So distracting.
Okay? See you
in the morning, Goku!
Bye!
[ALL laugh]
[VODKA] Hey, wait!
[rings jingling]
Gosh! It's harder than it looks!
Hmm... Maybe if I, umm...
We should drive until morning.
General Tao, you're my new hero!
[TAO] I know,
Mr. Vodka. I know...
Oh yeah!
There, that's one down!
[crows cawing]
[GOKU] Oh, man!
[GOKU] Feels like
my brain is frying!
[GOKU growling]
What if you, uhh....
Don't help, please!
I'm not gonna... cheat.
Oh... right...
Just one more!
I got it!
--I got it! I got it!
--Oooooh!
Very good work, sir!
Very good!
[TAO] Ahh... My guess is
Goku is just now giving up.
[VODKA] Yeah, he ain't
never gonna find us here!
[GOKU] Hello?
[HENCHMAN B] Maybe they went off
to get some breakfast somewhere.
[GOKU] Don't worry,
I'll find them.
[VODKA screams]
What? G-Goku?!
Look, guys, I'm done!
H... How pleasant.
So I guess I'll take
my Dragon Balls now!
Yeah, go right ahead!
Well, thank you.
--You guys take care!
--[HENCHMAN A whimpers]
[crow cawwing]
[TAO] So... Do I still get paid?
Whew! That should do it...
[BULMA] Come on, big guy.
And that makes seven,
just in time!
[NARRATOR] Ten more times the
Earth has seen the sun
rise and fall...
And the dawn of the
17th of May has broken.
A day that will either
ensure the planet's peace,
or pave way for
its destruction...
[CAMERAMAN] Are you ready?
Go, we're rolling!
This is Jimmy Firecracker,
coming to you live.
We're standing here
on a cliff
above the infamous
fighting arena
where the Cell Games are about
to begin in one short hour!
And Cell seems
frozen like a statue!
Who will be victor
in this ultimate match?
Will it be the perfected Cell?
Will it be our hero Goku?
Or is the Earth's salvation
to be found in the hands
of one of these brave fighters?
Let the games begin,
next time on Dragon Ball Z!