[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z!
With the wizard Babidi no longer
acting as his puppeteer,
the hideous Majin Buu set
forth to destroy the world.
And he came dangerously close!
[NARRATOR But somewhere beneath
the surface of the Earth,
the last hope of
a savior was waiting.
The world champion Mr. Satan
emerged from his
training facility,
determined to put an end
to Majin Buu's violent rampage!
[NARRATOR] But his method
of attack was quite different
from any the Z Fighters
had thought to try.
[MR. SATAN chuckles]
[NARRATOR] And, unfortunately,
it was also less productive.
[BUU] Buu really like when
the video game goes boom!
Wow, that's the part
most people would hate.
[thinking] Yeah, you just
enjoy your bath, tubby.
I've got you right
where I want you.
I hope.
[GOKU] Do you think
that Gohan's power
is really going to increase
like that old dude says?
I don't about you two,
but all this sitting still
just makes me want
to take another nap.
It will work.
There is no reason
to doubt my ancestor.
He seems very
confident of the process.
[GOKU]
I guess.
[snores]
[gasps]
Wait a sec, are you sleeping?
[snores]
I asked you a question!
[gasps]
Where am I?!
You fell asleep, didn't you?
No, I didn't!
I was in a meditative state!
It just appeared
that I was asleep.
It appeared to me
that you were snoring.
To the untrained, meditation
can appear as sleeping.
Besides, it's a well-known
fact that Kais do not lie.
[OLD KAI]
So, come now,
this is no time to be
questioning your tutor.
Let's get back to work!
[yawns]
[snores]
[growls]
[thinking]
I don't care what he says,
you don't have
a bubble floating
from your nose if you're awake.
Now, it's time
for the next step.
You must try fusing
as Super Saiyans.
Right!
[PICCOLO]
And if you are successful,
do not let your ambition
control your emotions.
You remember what happened
last time, don't you?
[GOTENKS ]
[GOTENKS yells]
[laughs]
Not too smart, huh?
No, GO!
[PICCOLO] Good! Your energies
are aligned perfectly.
Now perform the technique!
Fu-sion HA!
[PICCOLO grunts]
[gasping]
Whoa, that is amazing!
Yeah, and on their
first try, too!
[PICCOLO] Yes, it's an
impressive transformation,
but I'm very curious...
...about your control.
[GOTENKS]
Not so fast.
It's dangerous, showing off
in a place like this.
What's that?!
We don't want to
blow everything up, do we?
Better fly someplace else.
[PICCOLO]
No! Gotenks!
[GOTENKS]
Yee-haaw!
That ego, he's gotta
do something about that.
[GOTENKS laughs]
[yells]
His speed is better
than his self-control.
[chuckles]
Guess that was a little
too fast for Piccolo.
Oh well, you
snooze, you lose.
[GRAMPS] Come on, dear,
just a little farther.
As long as we make
it to the mountains,
we should be able
to hide from Majin Buu.
[GRANNY] Well, I just
hope our grandchildren
made it out of
West City in time.
[GRAMPS]
I know others have made it.
Yeah...
[gunshot]
[GRAMPS]
Oh no!
Oh no, honey!
What did they do to you?!
Yeah, one shot and she's down!
You really think that's
the right thing to do?
Smitty, it's the
end of the world.
Majin Buu is flying
around killing everyone,
why shouldn't I?
All bets are off now,
and I'm cashing my chips in.
I'm gonna do everything
I ever wanted to do.
Like murder...
You should give it a shot,
if you know what I mean.
[gasps]
Shoot the old guy,
let's see what you're made of!
[whimpers]
Hey there. You're
almost as good as me.
[whimpers]
[laughs]
[SMITTY]
I never thought I had it in me.
That wasn't so bad, was it?
No, it wasn't,
it was a lotta fun!
Did you see 'em fall?
[VAN ZANT laughs]
And guess what, Smitty?!
We've got ourselves a
town that's still standing.
There outta be lots
of people in there!
What took you so long?
I've already been around
the world, like, eight times,
so I decided to relax a bit.
You were just wasting
energy... and time.
[GOTENKS laughs]
I won't need a lot
of time to beat Majin Buu.
Can't you see how strong I am?
Of course, I see it.
--[GOTENKS] So...
--[PICCOLO] No!
[GOTENKS] ...guess I
passed the test, then.
Wait!
I'm sorry, Piccolo,
I know you're right.
I really should
stop wasting time.
[PICCOLO]
No, Gotenks! Don't go!
He's going to get
himself killed!
He has less than a minute
before the fusion splits!
Stupid!
[GOTENKS] This time,
that blubbery thing's
going down fast!
He's gonna regret the
day he set eyes on Gotenks!
Hey, Majin Buu, get out here.
I'm back for a rematch!
[BUU] Who out there disturb
Buu's reading time?!
[BOTH whimper]
[MR. SATAN]
Oh, Mr. Buu,
I'm sure it was just
your imagination.
Who would be stupid enough
to challenge such a
brilliant fighter as you?
[MR. SATAN] "And as he looked
over the smoldering battlefield,
Sergeant Medeski
knew he had done wrong.
The men he had led so bravely
into battle were dead.
Oh, they had placed
their trust in him,
and he had taught them only
one thing: how to die quickly.
[laughs]
Buu like funny
book when people die!
Wanna hear more, more, more!
[BUU laughs]
Wait, where are you going?
Buu kill more people now.
[gasps]
Do you want kill people, too?
I'm really more of
a chef than a fighter.
I, uh, I'll work on some
dinner while you're out.
Buu like cheese and
macaroni and mustard.
Anything you want.
I'll even throw in some
fried eggs and bacon for ya.
Buu say goodbye!
Have a good time.
Don't be gone too long! Bye!
You fat pig! I'll give you
your stinkin' macaroni!
And it's gonna be your
last meal, I'll see to that!
[chuckles]
Tubby won't even
know what hit him!
I got enough dynamite
here to blow up a tank!
All I have to do is
push this little button,
and it's goodbye Majin Buu!
They're gonna have to
scrape him off the walls
after this blast!
Yeah! And I'll be the "Man Who
Saved The World" again!
[chuckles]
This ought to do nicely.
[laughs]
Don't be gone too
long, Majin Buu!
[MR. SATAN laughs]
[guns firing]
[VAN ZANT laughs]
[VAN ZANT]
All right! Yeah!
39... 40...
[laughs]
This is great!
Hey, Van Zant? Maybe this
isn't the best place to be.
I heard Majin Buu
built a house around here.
What if he hears all this
and comes looking
to hurt us, what then?
Every single person on
the Earth is gonna die soon.
Wouldn't you like to go out
with a bang in the end?
[MR. SATAN chuckles]
Oh yeah, I am a hero!
[MR. SATAN gasps]
Oh, no, what's he doing
back here already?
Mister Majin Buu, sir,
I-I'm really sorry,
but I'm not quite finished
cooking your dinner yet, sir.
[BUU]
You look at puppy dog.
[DOG whines]
Where in the world did
you find that little guy?
He no scared of Buu. He no run.
Me try saying words to him,
but he just go "beeee, beeee."
Uh, well, I don't know
how to talk to a dog either,
but it looks like
this poor little guy
mayt have hurt his back leg.
Maybe that's why
he didn't run away.
Huh?
You leg broken?
Me make better,
then you run away.
[gasps]
[BUU]
Now get scared and run.
Me make you dead.
[barks]
Why he no run away?
He not scared of Buu, huh?
Nah, he's thanking
you for fixing his leg.
You're his new best friend.
Now he wants you to
play with him a bit.
You know, run around and stuff.
[DOG barks]
Puppy think Buu his new friend.
[MR. SATAN]
Well, you are.
You see his tail
wagging back and forth?
That means he likes you.
Buu friends with
you and puppy now?
[laughs]
Sure, we're all friends!
Ha, ha, ha!
Buu feel happy now!
[laughs]
Here, eat chocolate.
[MR. SATAN] Oh, now, chocolate
can make a dog really sick.
We should get
him some dog food.
[BUU] How do we get
little doggy food?
Why don't I run to the nearest
grocery store and pick some up?
[chuckles]
[MR. SATAN]
I won't be gone long.
You two just stay here
and play around for a while.
[BUU]
Okay!
[laughs]
[chuckles]
Yeah, now's my chance.
One flip of the
switch, and... Ka-Boom!
[laughs]
He... looks different. Gentle...
[growls]
All right, maybe I'll give
this guy a little time.
[MR. SATAN] Who knows, if people
can change maybe he can, too.
Look at him, he's sure
got a good appetite.
Dog food no taste good.
Uh, excuse me Mr. Buu,
do you mind if I ask
you a personal question?
Okay.
Uh, why do you fly around,
ah, ya know, killing people
and destroying
all our cities?
Buu was told to.
Who... told you that?
Bibidi told Buu to kill people.
Babidi said to destroy.
You know, you don't
have to listen to them.
Buu not know
what else Buu can do.
There's lots of things to do!
You can go to the movies,
play with your puppy,
watch football.
Anything as long as it
doesn't involve destruction.
I-I'm just kidding,
you can do whatever
you want to the world
just don't hurt me!
[whimpers]
Please, make it quick...
Is to kill people a bad thing?
Yes, it is a bad thing.
Then... no more.
[MR. SATAN] You're not
gonna kill people any more?
Mm-hmm.
[MR. SATAN] A-And won't
destroy any more cities?
Mm-hmm.
[thinking] I did it! I got
this guy to change his ways
and I didn't have to
throw a punch or blow him up!
Oh, Mr. Satan, you
are truly the greatest!
[BUU giggles[
[SMITTY] I don't know
about this, Van Zant.
We're real close to
Majin Buu's house out here!
And you're still
whimpering like a baby.
What if we find
Majin Buu first?
We... what?
We surprise him,
and then I put a bullet
in his fat pink head.
[BUU laughs]
He fetches that ball
quick, doesn't he?
Make the bark noise!
[barks]
You go fetch ball now.
[BUU laughs]
Yeah...
--[gunshot]
--[DOG squeals]
[gasps]
Huh...?
[VAN ZANT] We-he-hell, that's
one beast out of the way!
[whimpers]
[SMITTY]
Why, I think that's Mr. Satan
standing next to Majin Buu.
What... happened to the puppy?
[NARRATOR]
For the first time ever,
Majin Buu had known
the joys of friendship.
Now, for the first time,
he has experienced
the pain of loss.
Will the actions
of this crazed madman
send Buu on a vengeful
spree of desctruction?
Or can Mr. Satan find a way to
keep him from blowing his top?