[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Cell tested his might
against Vegeta,
the Super Saiyan Prince.
Composed partly by cells from
all of the greatest warriors
in the Universe,
Cell already knew Vegeta's
fighting techniques by heart.
And, suddenly, Vegeta found
himself on the other end
of a Gallic Gun blast.
An attack that he had
invented himself, long ago.
[KRILLIN grunts]
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL gasps]
[NARRATOR] But when
the dust settled,
it was Vegeta who proved
himself to be the stronger one.
[CELL yells]
[NARRATOR]
Having trained for a day
in the Hyperbolic Time Chamber,
Vegeta had transcended
the level of Super Saiyan
and achieved a new level
of speed and strength
that not even Cell
was any match for.
Do you understand
how fruitless this is?
I've been allowing you to
deceive yourself, that's all!
You never had a chance to win!
If by some miracle
you managed to get by me,
Trunks would've
finished you off!
Face it, Cell, you
took a gamble and you lost!
[CELL yells]
[NARRATOR] Could this
really be the end of Cell?
Find out today
on Dragon Ball Z!
Man! Cell's just
dying to find 18!
[KRILLIN] Somehow,
I've got to find her first
and use this on her!
Once she's immobilized,
I'll blast her!
Oh, man! What a job...
[KRILLIN] Surely she's
not still on this island?
She might be though!
Girls are funny.
[CELL yells]
[KRILLIN] Boy o'boy!
Cell doesn't sound like
he's having a very good
time down there...
[CELL growls]
[CELL yells]
This can't be!
[KRILLIN] Holy cow! I wouldn't
want to be Vegeta right now!
Man! Scary!
[CELL yells]
[CELL] Noooo!
[CELL growls]
[CELL thinking] Why? Why?!
Not fair...
If only I could
complete my evolution!
[CELL] Someone like
Vegeta would be nothing!
Fool! He thinks he knows power!
Huh...?
[VEGETA] I couldn't
help overhearing
your annoying babbling!
Yes! Funny! But I thought
I heard you say that I'm a fool
who doesn't know
what real power is!
That's right! You have no idea!
Your power is substantial,
I'm not denying that!
But if I absorbed
Android 18, you would
quickly discover that
you had serious limitations!
And then you would be a nobody!
[VEGETA yells,
CELL grunts]
[CELL growls]
No! I refuse to believe
that this is my fate!
I am Cell!
This isn't supposed
to be happening to me!
Noooo!
[CELL grunts]
[CELL yells]
My gosh!
Was Vegeta just pretending
to be weak when he fought me?
No. He is not the type
that would hold back.
You were stronger then.
Now he is the strongest.
[ANDROID 18] But how could
he gain that much strength
in such a short amount of time?
[KRILLIN gasps]
16, it doesn't compute.
There's just no way!
She's here! I don't believe it!
Oh, my gosh!
[KRILLIN yelps]
[KRILLIN] Gotcha!
Man! Don't they have brains?!
I mean! Cell's right over there!
[thinking] Oh, great! Now
I have to use this thing!
Everything that I've ever
learned on the battlefield
tells me that I need
to do this, and fast!
But it just
doesn't feel right!
[KRILLIN groans]
[KRILLIN gulps]
Remember, Krillin!
You have to be within ten meters
for that thing to work! Got it?
[KRILLIN thinking] Bulma,
why do you have to be so smart?!
Oh, why me?!
[thinking] Alright, here goes!
[KRILLIN gulps]
[CELL groans]
Where are you, 18?
I need you!
[VEGETA] Talking to yourself?
[CELL] Huh? Ah-Ahhh...
Vegeta, l-listen--
[CELL screams]
[thinking] Alright...
Just take this one step
at a time, Krillin!
You can do this!
Everyone is counting on you!
It's up to you now!
[CELL grunts]
[thinking] Oh my goodness!
They're right there!
But I still need
to get a little closer
in order for the
remote to work!
[KRILLIN thinking] Oh, wow!
Just look at her!
She's so...
...beautiful...
[KRILLIN gasps]
[thinking] What are you doing?
You know better than to think
like that at a time like this!
C'mon, Krillin!
Huh?!
[KRILLIN gasps]
[KRILLIN sighs]
[thinking] Man!
What's wrong with me?
[KRILLIn gasps]
[SQUIRREL squeaks]
[KRILLIN] Huh...?
[VEGETA] This is ridiculous!
Your power is laughable!
Fighting you in this state
is just a waste of my time!
Do you honestly believe that
you could challenge my powers
if I allowed you to
absorb that other Android?
Yes! It would be the ultimate
challenge! Are you up to it?!
Well...
Let's just say that
I'm thinking about it!
It sounds interesting!
No! Father! You can't!
You must hide.
I am hiding! With you!
You must leave.
Vegeta might let Cell go.
[ANDROID 18 gasps]
[ANDROID 16] Yes!
For the sport of fighting him
after he absorbs you.
[CELL] You're like a kid
who just got a new bicycle
but doesn't have
a place to ride it!
[CELL] Get it? Your power!
It's like a new toy but you
don't have anyway to test it!
Well, I understand your dilemma!
I know your Saiyan blood
is boiling for a challenge!
Allow me to absorb the android!
This may be the only
opportunity you ever get
to truly test the
depths of your power!
I can promise you!
You will not be disappointed!
[thinking] Father...!
Say the word and it's done!
It shouldn't take too long!
I'll absorb her and then we
can resume where we left off!
[thinking] Alright!
Almost there!
Just a little bit closer
and this thing should work!
[thinking] Okay... Go!
[thinking] Alright! That oughta
do it! I'm in range! This is it!
[thinking] Wait a sec! I better
think this over a bit first!
[thinking] This thing is
going to immobilize her
but I have to do the rest!
If I don't destroy her,
she can be absorbed by Cell!
And she wouldn't even
be able to defend herself!
[thinking] I can't
let that happen!
I'm going to have to
charge over there
and blast her when
I push the button!
The big guy's
not going to like it,
but he looks like
he's pretty banged up!
[thinking] Why can't I stop
thinking about that kiss?
[thinking] Come on, Krillin!
Snap out of it!
She's an android,
for goodness sake!
She's not even a real person!
[KRILLIN thinking]
On the other hand,
she's standing right over there!
Doesn't that make her real?
And she looks scared...
She has to be real!
She's so beautiful...
[thinking] There I go again!
What's wrong with me?!
I can't stop thinking about her!
Could I be in love
with an android...?
[KRILLIN thinking] No!
That's impossible! Isn't it?
Can a man fall in love
with an android?
Ugh! It doesn't matter anyway!
Everyone's counting on you!
You have to push
the button, Krillin!
I can't!
You have to!
Aaahhh...
[GOKU laughs]
[GOHAN laughs]
[GOKU] Whew! Pretty toasty, huh?
[GOHAN] Yeah! It feels
like one of Mom's baths!
Aahh...
Are you worried, Dad?
About Krillin and the others?
I feel kind of guilty taking
this relaxing bath
when we could be
out there training!
I know, Son! But
you have to understand,
sometimes rest is as
important as training!
Maybe even more important!
[GOHAN] It is?
[GOKU] Sure it is! If we
give our muscles a chance
to rest and build back up, we
can get a lot more out of them
than if we just kept
training the whole time!
[GOHAN] So... if we rest,
we can train even harder!
[GOKU] Exactly! Now
you've got it, Gohan!
So no more wasting your
energy on feeling guilty! Deal?
Deal! But you have
to promise not to give me
any special treatment just
because I'm your son! Okay?
[GOKU] Okay!
[GOKU laughs]
[GOHAN] Hey! No fair!
[GOKU giggles,
GOHAN yells]
Alright, Dad!
You asked for it!
[BOTH laughing]
[GOHAN] Give it up, Dad!
You're mine!
[GOKU] No way! Here comes the
Super Saiyan Splash Attack!
[BOTH laugh]
[GOHAN] No! I give up!
I give up!
[laughing continues]
[thinking] C'mon, Krillin!
You might not get another
chance like this! Don't blow it!
[ANDROID 16] Please, 18.
You must go.
[KRILLIN] You can't let
your personal feelings
cloud your judgement!
Good luck...
[KRILLIN thinking] Oh, man!
That was cloudy!
That was very cloudy!
C'mon Krillin! Get rid
of all those clouds!
Very poor visibility!
See ya!
[thinking] Don't let your
feelings cloud your judgement!
[thinking] What am I doing?
I can't do this!
[thinking] I can't
let her go! The others!
[thinking] They're all counting
on me! I can't let them down!
[thinking] Krillin! Hold on!
You can do it!
She's just an android!
[VOICES echoing]
[KRILLIN thinking]
I can't do it...
I love her...
[BOTH gasp]
Hey, it's you...
[ANDROID 18 gasps]
[ANDROID 18 thinking] Oh, no!
That's an Emergency
Suspension Controller!
How did that little guy
get a hold of one of those?
Uhhh... He looks mad.
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL] Your thirst for
the ultimate challenge
may very well lead
you to your doom!
But you will seek it anyway,
won't you, Super Saiyan!
I have ascended beyond
the level of Super Saiyan!
Fascinating! Yes, this
will be a rare match indeed!
If you don't run away.
Now you're dreaming.
[TRUNKS] Huh?
So be it! You've managed
to arouse my curiosity!
Now go and absorb your android!
Oh, no!
[VEGETA] Hopefully
the next time I see you,
you won't be in such
a pitiful state!
It's embarrassing!
Please, no! Father!
That's your weak point!
Can't you see?
Cell's exploiting
your only weakness!
Shut up, you fool!
Mind your own business!
I don't remember asking you
for your opinion on the matter!
How can you
understand my power?!
I've gone beyond
the Super Saiyan!
Now go!
Get out of here
before I change my mind!
[CELL] As you wish!
This better be worth it, Cell.
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL gasps]
If my dad won't stop you,
then I'll do it myself!
[CELL growls]
Nice day, huh?
I came here to kill you.
[ANDROID 18 gasps]
Yeah, I guess you
recognize this device?
[ANDROID 18] Yes, I do...
[KRILLIN yells]
[ANDROID 18 gasps]
You shouldn't be here!
Look, if Cell finds you,
then we're all doomed!
Please, go!
You can sneak off of to the
other side of the island!
Just fly low...
[ANDROID 18]
Why are you doing this?
You're taking a great
risk by letting me go!
--I don't understand!
--[KRILLIN] It's because I...!
Move along, kid!
[CELL growls]
[CELL] I don't have the patience
to deal with you right now,
you young punk!
You'll need a lot more than
patience to deal with me!
[CELL] Huh?!
You heard my father,
I'm as strong as he is!
Oh, yeah? We'll have
to see about that!
[CELL growls]
[CELL yells]
[TRUNKS yells]
[VEGETA] I can see that this
is going to be a problem...
You scoundrel!
[CELL growls]
Sorry, but you're
not going anywhere
unless you go through me, Cell!
[CELL growls]
Darn kid! Just like his father!
[CELL yells]
[CELL growls]
I know that you're
tricking my dad!
You know his weakness because
some of his cells are in you!
Well, you're not going
to talk your way
through this
road block, Cell!
It ends here!
[CELL] Rrrrgh! Curse you!
Hey, Vegeta! Look!
I thought we had an agreement!
Huh? It can't be!
[thinking] Android 18!
She's here!
This is too good to be true!
Huh?
Oh, no!
The Android!
She's here!
[NARRATOR] Unaware that she
has been discovered by Cell,
Android 18 stands
transfixed before Krillin,
both wondering
who will draw first
in this
emotional showdown.
The pressure is on Krillin to
put an end to this ordeal.
But the real danger lies above!
Hovering ominously with
the darkest of intentions,
and the blackest of desires.