[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z...
Cell blasted a chain of
islands into oblivion
hoping to uncover
the hidden androids.
We are safe here.
[NARRATOR]
The beautiful Android 18
and her battered
buddy Android 16
soon realized their safe hiding
place wasn't so safe anymore.
With Cell closing in
they would either
have to surrender
to the synthetic serpent,
or they'd be reduced to scrap.
[CELL] This is the
last island. Last chance.
[NARRATOR]
Cell was ready to unleash
an Earth-shaking energy blast
that would expose the androids
when suddenly two unexpected
allies arrived and saved
the digital duo from disaster.
[VEGETA] Are you ready
now to witness a power
not seen for thousands of years?
[CELL chuckles]
[NARRATOR] Now that Vegeta
has completed his training,
he's got something to prove.
[VEGETA yells]
[NARRATOR] His burning
desire is to destroy Cell
and prove once and for all
that he is the strongest
warrior in the universe.
[yelling continues]
[NARRATOR] There's no doubt
Vegeta is a pumped-up powerhouse
more than ready to put
Cell's lights out permanently.
[NARRATOR] Now that the self
centered Saiyan has ascended,
is he just a flash in the pan?
Or can he really bring
the monster Cell to his knees?
--[VEGETA yells]
--[CELL grunts]
[CELL growls]
What's wrong? I hope I'm
not making you uncomfortable?
What's wrong? I'll show you...
Oh, wait you're making a joke.
[CELL chuckles]
I do so enjoy your
classic Saiyan wit!
Thank you.
[CELL yells]
[CELL grunts]
[VEGETA growls]
--[VEGETA grunts]
--[CELL yells]
[VEGETA chuckles]
[CELL gasps]
[blows landing,
CELL grunts]
[CELL yells]
I could barely follow
Vegeta's movement.
[ANDROID 18] Maybe he does
have the power to finish Cell.
[CELL growls]
[VEGETA chuckles]
[CELL] You insignificant pest!
Are you really so proud
of these irritating little
tricks you've learned?
You'll need much more
if you ever hope to beat me!
[VEGETA chuckles]
[CELL] Did you think that I
would be so easily intimidated?
You fool! Have you
forgotten? I know you!
Your cells are woven
into my very being!
You, Vegeta, are a part of me!
Now I'm going to
take you apart. How ironic.
Clever 'til the end, huh?
[ANDROID 18]
They're just standing there.
Cell isn't attacking.
I don't understand.
Is he actually afraid of Vegeta?
[SQUIRREL squeaks]
[ANDROID 16] Hmmm...
[CELL yells]
[TRUNKS thinking]
I almost can't believe
that this day has finally come.
All of our training!
All of our hard work!
It was all for this moment.
[VEGETA chuckles]
[TRUNKS] Spending an entire year
in the Hyperbolic Time Chamber
was the most difficult
task I've ever had to face.
The gravity was so
intense I could barely walk.
The air was so thick
I could hardly breathe.
And the temperature
fluctuated wildly!
Sometimes freezing cold,
and others raging hot.
Everyday presented
its own hardship
a new obstacle to be
met and overcome.
Of course, some days
were harder than others!
[TRUNKS] And just when
I'd given up all hope,
when I was sure that I
wouldn't last another moment
in that awful place...
...I saw him.
He stood at the heart
of that raging inferno,
enshrouded by the flames
thousands of fiery
tongues licking at his body,
threatening to swallow him into
the furious blaze completely!
What?! No! Noo!
[TRUNKS] In that instant,
all of my fears and all of
my pain dropped away!
I knew only that
I had to be strong!
I had to step through
that wall of flame!
I had to do it for him!
Father!
Get back! I don't
need your help.
I train alone.
Stay away.
[TRUNKS] Suddenly
everything became clear.
Those raging flames
hadn't been a product
of the time chamber at all!
They had come from him,
their intensity fueled by
the one burning desire
that consumed him...
the desire to be the best!
I knew then that my
father would reach his goal.
He would achieve an
unprecedented new power level!
He would surpass a Super Saiyan!
And realizing this,
I was left to face the
trials of the void alone!
Father!
[TRUNKS yells]
[TRUNKS] The weeks
and months that followed
exist in my memory
mostly as a blur.
A seemingly endless
succession of grueling days
and sleepless nights.
Never had I known such effort.
And never had both
my mind and my body
been closer to the
breaking point!
But through it all I
persisted, the enormous shadow
that loomed over me a
constant reminder of my goal!
[VEGETA grunts]
[TRUNKS] The blood that
flows through my father's veins
flows through mine as well!
[VEGETA yells]
[TRUNKS] I was determined to
prove this fact at all costs!
My every thought,
my every action
was directed toward
this singular purpose!
I honored my father's
wishes to be left alone,
but I watched him from afar
when I could, and I learned.
I knew that my father would
achieve the greatness
he desired. He would climb any
mountain that stood in his path!
And I vowed that I would
follow in his footsteps.
I would make my own ascension,
so that one day I might
face my father as his equal!
And he will know
that I am his son.
[VEGETA yells]
[thinking] Father, one day
I will prove myself to you!
Maybe then you'll understand!
All of these dangers that
you're so eager to face
you don't have to
face them alone...
[VEGETA chuckles]
[CELL growls]
[CELL grunts]
[VEGETA] All to easy!
[CELL growls]
Hear me, Saiyan!
This time you die.
[CELL] I am done humoring you
and your petty maneuvers.
I will show you the
true nature of my power!
Come forward and meet your doom!
Wow! I guess that huge power
level I've been sensing
really is Vegeta's after all!
[thinking] I don't believe it!
He's even stronger
than Cell now!
But how could he get so much...
[KRILLIN gasps]
[thinking] Of course!
I know why!
That's what Goku
was talking about!
Vegeta got a year of
training in one day!
He must be totally pumped up!
I gotta see this!
I can't forget what I'm after!
The androids!
[CELL yells]
[VEGETA growls]
[CELL grunts]
Hey! What's happening? Come on!
Tell me how Trunks and
Vegeta are doing down there!
[TIEN] It's incredible!
Vegeta's got Cell on the run!
Hey! He might
actually be able to win!
[BULMA] That's great,
but how about some details.
Cell is getting the
beating of his life.
[PICCOLO growls]
What's wrong with him?
[BABY TRUNKS babbles]
Hey Trunks, your
Daddy's beating Cell.
[BABY TRUNKS babbles]
Yes, you'll grow up
to be just like him.
So what's wrong with Piccolo?
[PICCOLO growls]
[BABY TRUNKS growls]
[BABY TRUNKS wails]
Ah, don't cry, baby. Don't cry.
[PICCOLO thinking]
Vegeta could have beaten
Cell ten times over by now!
He's toying with him!
Leaving him an opportunity
to fuse with Android 18!
He's putting us all at risk to
satisfy his own selfish pride!
[PICCOLO yells]
[PICCOLO] Vegeta!
[GOHAN yells]
[yelling continues]
[GOKU] Gohan, listen to me!
You can't become a Super Saiyan
just by increasing
your power level!
I've told you it
doesn't work like that!
The power comes in response
to a need, not a desire!
You have to create that need!
Son, use the pain of loss!
But how, Dad?
I haven't lost anything!
Hey, now here's an idea.
Try to imagine that
Cell is destroying me
and all of your friends.
[GOHAN growls]
Wait! Dad, I've never seen Cell.
[GOKU] Ah... Uhh...
Well, then picture
Frieza instead!
[GOHAN growls]
Die.
[KRILLIN gasps]
[PICCOLO growls]
[GOHAN gasps]
[VEGETA growls]
[DENDE gasps]
No!
[GOKU gasps]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[FRIEZA giggles]
[PICCOLO rasps]
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU yells]
Oh, no! Nooo!
[GOHAN screams]
[GOHAN pants]
Daddy...!
[GOKU] You did good, Gohan.
Really good. I'm proud of you.
[GOHAN] Thanks, Dad.
Do you want me to try it again?
I think I'm getting
the hang of it now.
[GOKU] No, that's
enough for today.
We don't want you
to burn yourself out.
Rest now, Son.
[CELL yells]
[VEGETA] Hmm?!
[CELL growls]
--Hah!
--[CELL grunts]
[VEGETA snarls]
[blows landing]
[blows landing,
CELL grunts]
[VEGETA chuckles]
[VEGETA] So, tell me, Cell,
is this your true power
that I'm sensing?
[VEGETA laughs]
[VEGETA] You do take a punch
well, I'll give you that!
Otherwise, I'm afraid
I'm really not impressed!
Poor Vegeta, you just
don't understand, do you?
Try me.
[CELL yells]
[VEGETA gasps]
--[CELL shouts]
--[VEGETA grunts]
[CELL yells]
[thinking] Oh no... Is it...
It it over...?
[CELL laughs]
[laughing continues]
[CELL thinking]
That foolish boy.
What does he think
he's looking at?
--[VEGETA] CELL!
--[CELL gasps]
[CELL growls]
[blow lands,
CELL &amp; VEGETA grunt]
[CELL grunts]
[VEGETA laughs]
All done? Too bad.
[CELL groans]
[CELL] Not so fast.
I'm not done yet.
I see, so you're a
glutton for punishment.
Cell, I think you just
don't know when to quit.
[CELL chuckles]
[chuckling continues]
[CELL laughs]
[CELL growls]
[CELL yells]
[KRILLIN] Whoa!
That was no smoke signal!
There's something
going on down there
and it can only
mean one thing:
Cell... He's there...
Cell's power
is increasing greatly.
[CELL yells]
[CELL growls]
Ah-ha!
So you can raise
your power, after all!
It still won't save you.
[CELL] I admire your
determination Vegeta,
but your arrogance
will be your downfall.
This could get rough.
[thinking] They're both so
powerful! I don't want to watch!
Ah, but I don't want
to miss this either!
[CELL] What are you waiting for?
Well, if you won't make
the first move, then I will!
[CELL yells]
[VEGETA grunts]
[CELL gasps]
That one was free.
Now I'm going to show you
what true power really is!
[CELL] You're not Vegeta!
You're not!
You've changed. You've...
You've become something else!
[VEGETA chuckles]
That's right! I am Super Vegeta!
[NARRATOR] Vegeta
is ready to make
his royal Saiyan ancestors
proud by fulfilling his destiny.
But if he wins this battle,
will he become an even
bigger monster than Cell?
Find out next time!