Buu! Buu!
[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z.
The Supreme Kai met the
titanic terror Majin Buu.
And even a lethal blast
of his mental energy
couldn't put a dent
in the barbaric blob.
In the blink of eye, Majin Buu
sent the Supreme Kai sailing.
Then he landed on the little
guy's back with a boom.
Luckily, Gohan jumped in.
But his rescue was cut short
when he took a
full force hit head on.
[laughs]
[NARRATOR] The overweight
ogre didn't walk away
without a scratch, however.
Much to the surprise of Babidi,
Dabura turned on Majin Buu.
Have you gone insane?!
Don't be such a fool.
This Majin Buu creature
is far too powerful
to be kept under
your control for long.
[growls]
What?!
Now new plan... Now I eat you!
[NARRATOR] Babidi's pet monster
has a real appetite for evil
and he's just put Dabura
at the top of the menu.
Can the demon king
survive a tangle
with the voracious
villain Majin Buu?
[VEGETA] Lets see, the fastest
way for me to get into
Babidi's spaceship might
be to smash through the top.
But it it might be easier just
to destroy the whole ship
and go in after
Majin Buu instead.
Then If I catch him off
guard I've got him! I hope.
I can since it,
Kakarot's son is gone.
Gohan... I'm sorry.
Kakarot.
[BABIDI cackles loudly]
Me eat you up!
Ah! You wouldn't dare!
[snickers]
Buu!
Me eat you up! Me eat you up!
[cackles] Oh what fun!
Majin Buu is going to take
care of everything for me now.
[BUU] Me eat you up!
Me eat you up! Me eat you up!
I'll show you!
[BABIDI]
Oh no! Majin Buu!
Good riddance!
[growls]
Ahhh!
[laughs]
[BABIDI] That's it Majin Buu,
well done, nothing
can stop you my pet.
Me gonna eat you up!
That guy looks pretty scary
when he gets mad, doesn't he?
This will finish you off!
Hahahaha!
Aaaaaugh!!
[DABURA] What do you think
of your pet now Babidi?
Uh? He's gone? Majin Buu? No!
[DABURA chuckles]
Huh? You! Stop your
laughing or I'll make you pay!
[BUU] Me eat you up!
Me eat you up! Me eat you up!
Huh?
What? No!
[BUU]
Me eat you up! Me eat you up!
Me eat you up!
[cackles]
Oh, this is wonderful!
Get him Majin Buu!
Me eat you up! Me eat you up!
You turn into a cookie!
[DABURA screams]
Ahhhh!
[giggles]
Huh?
[BABIDI]
Beautiful! Well done Majin Buu!
[BABIDI] What a tasty
performance! [chuckles]
[GOTEN] I don't believe it!
He... He ate him!
Uh-huh...
Look, it's Krillin!
[TRUNKS]
Huh?
[KRILLIN] What happened?
I don't remember a thing!
You don't?
Somebody turned you
into a stone statue.
[KRILLIN]
A statue?
Ah. That's right.
I remember now.
It was that Dabura guy's spit.
It turned me to stone.
I couldn't move. What a creep!
[KRILLIN]
Well, looks like I'm okay now!
He must be talking about
the guy who just got eaten up!
Well, duh!
I'll bet his powers
probably wore off
when he got
turned into a cookie.
That's why Krillin's
back to... Hmm...
[gasps]
Oh no, you know
what that means?
[KRILLIN]
What's wrong Trunks?
Oh, I know.
Trunks knocked over
Piccolo's statue and broke him.
Hehhhhh?!
Huh?
[GOTEN]
Uh, is he there?
[TRUNKS] Uh? You don't
want to go up there.
Trunks what is it?
Please... We gotta...
Keep this a secret okay?
[PICCOLO]
Keep what a secret?
[chuckles]
[gasps]
No! What in the world is giving
off all that terrible energy?
Is that thing... Majin Buu?!
[TRUNKS] Hey, Piccolo...
How did you get back to normal?
I can regenerate as long
as my head isn't damaged.
But enough about that.
What's been going
on around here?
Where are Goku and the others?
[TRUNKS] Uh, I don't know...
We just got here.
[KRILLIN] Hey, you talkin'
about that pink guy down there?
[gasps]
Is that Majin Buu?!
I think so.
[KRILLIN] Well,
he doesn't seem very tough.
Uh, So... If it's all
right with you guys,
I think I wanna go home now.
[BABIDI] Did you enjoy
your snack Majin Buu?
Hahahaha!
You can eat the
Supreme Kai too if you like!
[groans]
[BUU laughs]
Oh! Is that the
Supreme Kai down there?
[KRILLIN] Hey, uh, Piccolo!
What are you planning on doing?
Control yourself...
Don't do anything hasty okay?
I mean, don't you think
we should at least
wait for Goku to
show up... or something.
Yeah, I'll bet my dad
could beat him up!
He wouldn't let that stupid
monster turn him into a cookie!
Darn!
[groans]
[laughs]
What should me turn you into?
Chocolate or jelly?
[laughs]
He looks tasty!
Go on now eat him up!
Huh?
What... What's that?
What's goin' on down there?!
[BABIDI]
Oh... Huh... [coughs]
Uh? Where am I?
Ah! I can't see!
Ahh!
My spaceship?
It's been blown up!
No! No! No! My ship! No! No!
How could this happen?!
Ah! My ship! Majin Buu I want
you to find out who did this!
Hmmm...
Wait? Someone's coming!
Oh!! It's Vegeta!
[VEGETA chuckles]
Yes!
Dad!
[KRILLIN] I never thought
I'd be glad to see him!
Vegeta what are you doing here?
No, get away...
Are you the one that
blew up my spaceship?!
[VEGETA] That's right!
It was a little messy
but it was the quickest
way to get the job done!
[BABIDI]
Uuugggh!
But why? I never gave you
an order to destroy my ship!
Why did you do it?!
You clumsy fool!
Do you know what you've done?!
How am I supposed to get
off this wretched planet?!
Hehehehe!
[VEGETA] I assume that
ugly blob there is Majin Buu?
If so... you're the
one that killed Gohan!
[gasps]
Piccolo what is it?
What did my dad say?
Piccolo?!
[PICCOLO thinking]
G-Gohan...
He say, 'oogly'?
What means that, oogly?
Urrrgh!
He means your face would
frighten small children.
Now be quiet!
[giggles]
Heh. Heh.
[growls]
[BABIDI gasps]
Oh no!
Majin Buu?
[steam whistle]
What a strange creature!
Majin Buu mad! Pow!
Pow! Pow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
Vegeta... This is it!
Get him!
Show him what happens to
those who dare to disobey me!
Buu! Buu! Buu! Buu! Buu!
[KRILLIN] Great!
Now why'd Vegeta have to go
and get him worked
up like that?
This is gonna be rough.
Not for my dad!
He can do any-thing!
I hope so.
[BABIDI] Get him Majin Buu!
Give him everything you've got!
[VEGETA thinking]
What was that?
Kakarot!
Is that clown playing
tricks on me?
Or am I just seeing things?
Why is it that
Kakarot haunts me so?
Is it because he's always
been one step ahead of me?
Always succeeded
where I have failed?
First it was Frieza,
defeating the tyrant
that had held me in
bondage my whole life!
And then there was Cell,
"Noble Kakarot"!
Giving his life for
the lives of his friends...
Good bye my son.
[VEGETA thinking]
For my life!
[VEGETA thinking] Well no more!
After all we've been through,
it's finally my turn.
I'll settle this so we
can both rest in peace.
[VEGETA thinking]
Kakarot, when you wake up,
this will all be over.
I may be gone but
this planet will be safe.
I'll stake my life on it!
Okay, Buu, your time has come!
And you too, Babidi!
We end this here!
No, don't! Don't do it, Vegeta!
[TRUNKS] All right!
Check out my dad's power!
[KRILLIN] Yeah, but,
look at that Majin Buu!
He's not exactly running scared!
I've... never seen
him like this.
Uh, Majin Buu? Get up! Please!
Way to go, Dad!
You got him! Go for it!
[NARRATOR]
Vegeta has only just begun
to unleash his rage
on Majin Buu.
While Trunks cheers
his father on,
Babidi watches in horror as
his precious pet is pummeled.
The stakes are
high for this battle
and there's no
turning back now.
Vegeta's the only one
left that has a chance
of taking down Majin Buu
and saving the planet.
Will he succeed?
Find out on the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!