[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
two androids, 19 and 20,
appeared on an island
nine miles southwest
of South City,
just as Trunks had predicted.
It was a violent arrival,
marked by devastating
destruction and
the presence of a
certain super hero
who was there to stop them!
But when a harsh blow
from Goku did little more
than knock the android's
hat off, it was clear
that the Saiyan was
up against an enemy
of incredible strength.
In addition,
the android revealed
that their creator had already
studied Goku's strength
and technique and had
consequently equipped them
with superior abilities!
[NARRATOR] But Doctor Gero's
research didn't span
into far reaches of space,
and there was one ability
of Goku's that he
hadn't accounted for!
[GOKU yells]
[NARRATOR] His ability to
transform into a Super Saiyan!
Yes...
It is a most
impressive ability.
But it is nothing
we cannot handle.
19 will demonstrate
this by himself.
Hmm.
Hah! Alright,
have it your way,
but I wouldn't bank on
it if I were you!
[GOKU growls]
[NARRATOR] Goku's clash with
the androids continues today!
[ANDROID 19 gasps]
[GOKU grunts]
[blows landing,
grunting]
[fightin sounds continue]
[ANDROID 19 grunts]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU] You're mine!
[ANDROID 19 giggles]
[GOKU grunts]
[ANDROID 19 hums]
Huh...?
[GOKU growls]
Haah!
[ANDROID 19 yells]
[GOKU] Haah!
[GOKU] Hm?!
[ANDROID 20 gasps]
That's it, Goku!
[PICCOLO] Hmm.
[ANDROID 19 growls]
[GOKU grunts]
[ANDROID 19] Huh?!
[ANDROID 19 screams]
[GOKU grunts]
[ANDROID 19] Hmm?
[grunting]
[ROSHI laughs]
[ROSHI] Oh, dear me! What
will they think of next?!
[OOLONG groans]
[ROSHI] Huh...?
[OOLONG] Whoa!
Oh, Tien... I hope
you're safe...
[MARON] Hello in
there! Knock, knock!
Krillin, it's me!
[OOLONG] Hm?
[MARON] Your Maron
is back! Yoo-hoo!
Oh, no! Where is he?
Where's Krillin?
Oh, uh, he left a
little while ago!
They're off trying to save the
world from annihilation again!
You know how it is!
Hm?!
Hi, pretty plant!
What's your name?
Have you seen Krillin?
Nice branches, huh?
[ROSHI chuckles]
[MARON]
Yes, it's a beautiful plant,
but it's sad that it doesn't
know where Krillin is!
[MARON groans]
[ROSHI giggles lecherously]
[ROSHI] Give us a hug, baby!
[ROSHI chuckles]
[ROSHI muffled giggles]
Oh?
[CHIAOTZU] We know where he is,
it's just too
dangerous to go there!
Gosh! My Krillin's in danger!
I should have never left him.
He was so good to me...
With that cute little round head
of his and all of those muscles!
I didn't know what
love was 'til I met him!
[MARON sobs]
[MARON] Please take me back!
Oh, Krillin...
Come back!
[MARON sobs]
Oh, no... My poor, dear Krillin.
He's lost. But I won't give up.
Where are you, Krillin?!
Please... No...
Don't do this to me! I need you!
Krillin?
Maron, he's not lost!
Krillin's off fighting
some androids
made by the leader of
the old Red Ribbon Army!
What? Red ribbon?
Oh, my goodness!
Krillin! You sensed I was coming
so you went out to get
a red ribbon for me!
[ALL shout]
[CHIAOTZU] After he warned us,
he got right back in his
time machine and took off!
Then the Androids showed up,
just like he said they would!
Three years later!
Which means he was
telling the truth!
What a fight! You
talk about power!
We're usually right
there with those guys.
Darn shame. We feel left out.
But... I... want...
my... Krillin now!
Ohh-ho!
Okay! Okay! He'll be back soon!
I promise, it
won't be long now!
But allow me to keep you
company in the meantime.
Will you tell me the story
about the Red Ribbons again?
Well, that's not exactly
what I had in mind...
[MARON] Please?
[ROSHI] Oh, all right.
It all started back when
Goku was still just a boy.
He was on a mission to
collect all seven Dragon Balls!
It was a training mission,
designed to sharpen his skills.
There's one up ahead.
[ROSHI] Little did Goku know,
that the Red Ribbon Army
was also after the Dragon Balls
for their own evil purposes!
Thanks to Dr. Gero,
the chief scientist,
this dreadful organization had
radically advanced robotics
at their disposal!
Ka... me... ha... me...
Haaaaa!
[MAJOR METALLICA screams]
[ROSHI] Luckily,
Goku was no ordinary boy.
Or he would have
perished for sure!
Wow! I just knocked
his block off!
And he's still standing!
What a guy...
[ROSHI] General Tao was Goku's
most dangerous adversary by far!
He was a true master
of the Martial Arts!
But like so many others,
his power only made him
hunger for more power!
The mastermind behind all
of the Red Ribbon Army's
military operations, he
wanted nothing less
than to rule the world!
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU yelps]
[ROSHI] And he would have had
his way if it wasn't for Goku.
[GOKU] Ka... me... ha...
--[GENERAL TAO] Hmm...?
--me... haaaaa!
[ROSHI]
General Tao never expected that
such an advanced attack would
come from such a small boy!
He was speechless!
Not bad... I'm impressed!
Unbelievable!
Your turn!
--Raagh!
--[GOKU screams]
[GOKU grunts]
[GENERAL TAO gasps]
You're just a big bully!
I'm not scared of
you anymore, Tao!
[ROSHI] Then Goku gave
him the old duck and go
and winded the General!
Ooh, it wasn't
pretty after that.
Goku brought the hammer down
and treated the General's head
as if it were a punching bag!
[ROSHI laughs]
[ROSHI] Goku knocked
the General silly,
even had him
begging for mercy!
I'll change! I promise!
[ROSHI] But it was just a trick!
A shameless trick by an old pro!
Haaa!
[GOKU yells]
[ROSHI] The General jumped
straight up to avoid the blast,
but Goku kicked that
thing sky-high.
And that was the end
of one of the foremost
Martial Arts experts
in the world.
Now, if you
considered General Tao
to be the heart of
the Red Ribbon Army,
then Doctor Gero would have
to be considered the brain!
[ROSHI] Goku still
had work to do.
And in a classic style that
could only work for someone
as strong and as
crazy as Goku was,
he attacked the entire
Red Ribbon Army head on!
[GOKU yells]
[SOLDIER 1] Hey, kid!
Say cheese!
Okay, "cheese"!
[SOLDIER 1 screams]
[ROSHI] Little by little, Goku
was doing the impossible!
[ROSHI] He was chipping away
at the Red Ribbon Army
singlehandedly!
Fools! I want him stopped!
He's just a stinkin' kid!
[ROSHI] It was inconceivable
that such a small boy
could have such enormous power!
[GOKU yells]
[ROSHI] Soon, there was
only one man standing
between Goku and
Doctor Gero himself!
[ROSHI] But with the help of
one of Dr. Gero's machines,
he was able to gain
the upper hand on Goku!
He knocked the poor boy
senseless for starters,
and then he gave
him the hot pants!
[GOKU yells]
[ROSHI] Things weren't looking
too good for ol' Goku!
[GENERAL BLACK] Here, I have
a little surprise for you, kid!
Why am I not excited?
[ROSHI] So Goku did
what he usually does
when he's plum out of options:
[GENERAL BLACK]
Stay right there... Perfect.
[ROSHI] He used his head!
Let's see whose head is harder!
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU yells]
[GENERAL BLACK screams]
[ROSHI] And that was that!
The entire Red Ribbon
Army was no more!
[GOKU] Flying Nimbus!
[ROSHI] They had been defeated
by a mere boy,
a very special boy mind you,
but, a boy, nonetheless!
[ROSHI] Well, this made quite
an impression on the mastermind
behind the Red Ribbon Army,
Doctor Gero, who
Goku let get away!
He was no longer interested in
creating an entire army anymore.
What was the use if only one boy
could destroy the whole thing?!
Instead, he was bent
on using his genius
to create a robotic
being like Goku.
A single entity that had the
power of an entire army.
But he knew that any creation
he made had to be even stronger
than Goku, or Goku
would simply beat it again!
So he secretly watched Goku over
the years and studied his power!
Finally, he invented a
pair of killing machines
that he felt were even
stronger than Goku!
And this marked the end
of Doctor Gero's dark,
but brilliant, career!
His new creations were so evil
that they took the Doctor's life
the second they awoke
into the world...
[ROSHI] And that's
the whole scoop, Maron!
Right now, Krillin is
with Goku and Gohan
and they're trying to stop
those crazy monsters!
Quite a tale, huh?
Do you think you
understand it now?
Umm...
No! Who'll protect me
from the monsters?
[ALL yell]
Whoa! Man! I can feel
that energy big time!
That's my dad, isn't it?
Yeah! I can't
sense the androids.
I guess you were right
about not being able
to sense their power levels...
[ANDROID 19 growls]
[GOKU yells]
[ANDROID 19 grunts]
[ANDROID 19 screams]
Man, Goku's all over that thing!
He's dominating! There's no
way that android can win,
he hasn't even touched him yet!
Goku's got it in the bag!
Maybe...
[blows landing,
BOTH grunting]
[ANDROID 19 growls]
[GOKU yells]
[grunting,
blows land]
[GOKU yells]
[blows landing,
BOTH grunting]
[grunting]
[GOKU yells]
[ANDROID 19 grunts]
[ANDROID 20] Hmm...
[thinking] Goku's new abilities
greatly exceed anything
I had anticipated!
If the opportunity does
not soon arise for 19
to steal some energy, he will
drain his power reservoir
and begin to malfunction!
[blows landing,
BOTH grunting]
That's them right there!
Gotcha!
Father!
Hey, don't worry! Your dad
has everything under control!
That android never
had a chance...
[blows landing,
BOTH grunting]
[KRILLIN] Has it been
like this the whole time?
[TIEN] Yeah, it hasn't
laid a finger on Goku!
[ANDROID 19 grunts]
[thinking] C'mon,
Goku... That's it...
[GOKU grunts]
[thinking] Goku!
[ANDROID 19 shouts]
[blows landing,
BOTH grunting]
[KRILLIN] Man, oh man!
Goku's definitely got the
upper hand on that guy!
[TIEN] No kidding!
Look at him go!
He's rewriting history up there!
It looks like we're all
going to live afterall!
[KRILLIN] Yeah, I'm not
even worried anymore!
Are you, Gohan?
Yeah...
You're right to worry, Gohan...
Huh...? I am?
Goku's just not his
usual confident self!
His attacks aren't even
hurting the android!
He's going to need
our help, you guys!
Hey, wait a sec. He seems
fine. You're being paranoid.
I mean look at him.
What could go wrong?
[GOKU grunts,
blows landing]
I tell you, something's
not right...
Goku's maxed out
for some reason!
He's going to give out
if this keeps up!
Yeah, right. I can see it too.
Hey, guys! Remember
what Yamcha said
about feeling weak when
the android touched him?
Like it was
absorbing his energy?
[PICCOLO] What?!
Yeah, I felt
energy leaving me!
Like I was being
drained or something!
But it felt weird...
Goku would know if it
was happening to him.
[GOKU shouts]
[ANDROID 19 grunts]
[ALL grunt]
Right on!
All right! Way to go, Goku!
--Awesome!
--Excellent! What a shot!
--Man, what a champ!
--Did you see that?!
--Incredible!
--Yeah, no kidding!
Wow!
[ANDROID 20] Mmm...
[ANDROID 19 pants angrily]
Man! Look! If Goku
hit me like that,
I wouldn't be able
to move for a week!
[TIEN] Yeah! What are those
things made of, anyway?
[GOKU pants]
Kaa... mee...
[GOKU growls]
haa... mee...
haa!
[ANDROID 20] Hm?!
Ha-ha!
[ANDROID 19 giggles]
[ANDROID 19 laughs]
[gasping]
[ANDROID 20 chuckles]
[ANDROID 19 laughs]
[GOKU pants]
[BOTH whimper]
Uh... Man... That's not good...
Yeah! He absorbed
it! I was right!
[PICCOLO] Goku, don't use
any of your energy waves!
They absorb energy
through their hands!
It will only make them
stronger! Understand?!
You're kidding!
Great... Now what?
Oh, man... That's too much!
[ANDROID 19 laughs]
[ANDROID 20 chuckles]
Uh, oh... Look,
guys, it's...
Goku, he's tired! Man...
How did that thing take
so much of his energy?
I don't think it did.
Something else must be
sapping all his strength!
[GOHAN gasps]
[thinking] Excellent!
Now 19 is fully charged again
and it seems that
Goku's new technique
is taking its toll
on him! Yes... Yes!
The "mighty" Goku is finished!
[ANDROID 19 grunts]
Hmph.
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU growls]
[ANDROID 19 giggles]
[GOKU grunts]
[ANDROID 19 growls]
[GOKU yells]
Ka-me-ha-me
Goku! No!
[GOKU] Ha...
Dad... Something's wrong...
[GOKU growls]
Darn! What's wrong?!
I can't... give... up!
[GOKU grunts]
[YAMCHA] I don't believe it!
Goku's backing off!
[KRILLIN] He must
be hurt really bad!
[YAMCHA] But how?!
Daddy...
[GOKU grunts]
[GOHAN yells]
It's that virus! It's
attacking his heart right now!
Father!
Yes! That's it!
But it's happening much later
than the boy from the future
said it would!
Goku just thought that
he'd made a mistake,
but somehow his visit has
already changed history!
Man...
[YAMCHA whimpers]
[TIEN whimpers]
[PICCOLO growls]
[GOHAN whimpers]
[GOKU pants]
[NARRATOR] As the Androids
look on like vultures,
the deadly virus attacks
Goku from within.
Trunks' prediction is
finally coming true,
but at a most unexpected
and inopportune time.
What will Goku do now?
And how long does he have
before the deadly
virus runs its course?
Find out on the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!