[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z,
shocking as it seems,
it looks as though everyone's
worst nightmare has
actually become a reality.
[NARRATOR] And now the entire
gang must prepare itself
for a close encounter with
the two most terrible forces
of darkness that the
universe has ever known:
It's King Cold and Frieza.
But even Piccolo knows.
Without Goku here,
they'd all be crazy
to take on these evil titans!
[VEGETA]
You really have no choice!
So what say
we put an end
to all this pathetic whimpering!
[FRIEZA]
Begin your search!
And when you find them,
show no mercy!
[NARRATOR]
But just when you thought
nothing could stand
in Frieza's way...
A mysterious young stranger
lands on the scene!
[BOY]
Ah, so you must be Frieza!
I've been waiting a long
time to meet you face-to-face.
Well, we have a guest.
Now I'm going to destroy you.
Ooh! We'd better run!
Isn't that right, Father?
[FRIEZA chuckling]
You don't know what
you're up against, boy!
[BOY] I know exactly what
I'm up against Frieza,
and let me tell you,
I'm not worried.
Make no mistake. I'm going
to finish you once and for all.
[FRIEZA] Well, you certainly
are an arrogant little thing...
And maybe in whatever
little hole you just
crawled out of,
you're pretty tough!
But you're no match for me!
Really, fighting a pitiful,
young punk like you
isn't even worth my time!
[BOY] Maybe I haven't
made myself clear yet!
You're finished, Frieza!
[FRIEZA growls]
Enough idle talk!
Foot soldier!
Sire!
Vaporize this little rodent!
[GREEN SOLDIER]
With pleasure!
[FRIEZA]
The rest of you, spread out!
[BOY] I think it's only fair
that I should warn you, guys.
You don't stand a
chance against me.
Kid, you don't scare us!
Hey! Stand back! I need
some room to work here!
[GREEN SOLDIER] Hmph!
His power is only at level five!
Well, kiddo, I hope
you've said your goodbyes!
'Cause it's about
time for you to go!
[GREEN SOLDIER gasps]
But-- I...
[GREEN SOLDIER yells]
Well!
Seems the little
dog has some bite
to go with his bark after all!
Why... you... Attack!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[SOLDIER gasping, whimpering]
[FRIEZA]
Coward!
[crunching]
Why? Lord Frieza? Why...
I must admit I'm impressed!
[ALL gasp]
Guys? Hey! What's going on?
I'm sensing another
huge power level, and...
...and this one makes
Frieza's seem like nothing!
You know, guys,
it's not too late!
We can still
turn around and go home
if we want... right?
[TIEN]
Be strong, Yamcha!
[VEGETA thinking] Incredible!
I've never sensed anything
like this before!
Where would someone with this
kind of power have come from?
What a pleasant surprise.
[FRIEZA]
You're right, Father.
This may prove to be a bit more
amusing than I had thought!
And now, you two
are going down!
[KING COLD chuckling]
One thing is certain:
If nothing else, I'd say
this little creature
is quite the comedian!
He is at that.
I'll tell you what, kid...
Let me give you
a piece of advice.
He who acquires
his skills quickly
is he who is the
first to perish.
Thanks for the tip.
Huh? Why you--
[BOY] Listen up! Now I've
got one for you, Frieza.
Know your enemy!
You've already made some pretty
big assumptions about me,
and that's a mistake that's
going to cost you dearly!
You insolent brat!
You should really learn
to control your tongue!
Just destroy him, already
We haven't got all day.
[FRIEZA] Really, Father!
Have some patience!
I'm just trying to have a
little fun, if you don't mind!
He's right, though.
You really don't have all day.
More like five minutes...
Oh, that's too bad.
[FRIEZA chuckles]
And here I've made dinner plans!
[BOY] So I've heard!
Well sorry, Frieza,
but I'm canceling your
date with Goku!
[FRIEZA grunts]
What's a "Goku"?
Father, I know you're bored,
but please try to keep up.
So I take it you know
that worthless Saiyan?
By reputation,
but we'll meet soon.
Oh! Don't be so certain.
But I couldn't be
more certain, Frieza!
Any time now, Goku
will be coming home,
and only one of us is going to
be here waiting for him, get it?
Definitely! As it so happens
I was just about to suggest
that very thing myself.
It's so nice that
you and I can finally agree
on something, don't you think?
[TRUNKS chuckles]
For once, you're right!
Well, then I guess all that's
left is for me to decide
just how I'm going
to annihilate you.
[BOY]
Enough kidding around!
Huh?
It's time you understood
who I really am.
So, I'll tell you what.
I'm going to let the two
of you in on a little secret.
You're about to find
out what it's like
to fight a real Super Saiyan!
And I'm not talking about Goku!
What?!
[KING COLD growls]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
You crack me up, kid!
[FRIEZA laughs]
[FRIEZA] I've never met
anyone who laid it on
quite as thick as you!
[FRIEZA cackling]
[KING COLD chuckles]
[FRIEZA cackles,
KING COLD laughs]
Huh?
No! It can't be!
What is he?
[BOY yelling]
But... But... it's--
It's imposible!
[yelling]
[BOTH gasp]
[YAMCHA] Sounds like the
fight's starting without us!
[BULMA] Oh! Somebody stop
this thing! I want to get off!
It might be my dad!
You think?
Who else would try to
take on Frieza alone?
I don't know!
[VEGETA thinking] Kakarot! No! I
absolutely refuse to believe it!
There's no way his power level
could have increased this much!
It's impossible! Even if
he is a Super Saiyan!
[FRIEZA gasping]
[GOKU]
Frieza!
So this is a "Super Saiyan"...
It's those eyes!
They have the same eyes!
[FRIEZA gasping]
Is it something I said?
No! Saiyan!
[KRILLIN]
If that's Goku...
[KRILLIN yelling]
[VEGETA]
No! You'll give us all away!
Until I know what
we're dealing with,
I'd prefer to remain unnoticed!
So unless I tell you otherwise,
you stay put!
Are you hurt?
Just my pride...
Man, Gohan! What are
we supposed to do?
[GOHAN mumbling] I don't know...
What if Goku actually
is over there?
And what if he needs
are help right now,
while we're all just sitting
here doing absolutely nothing?!
Hey, maybe it would
help us relax a little
if we all sing a song!
Shut up! You haven't had
one useful thing to say
since you got here.
Now you stay in the back
and keep quite, woman!
I don't have time for
your stupidity right now.
Wha-- Stupid?
Take that back,
Bulma isn't stupid.
So you think I'm smart then?
Well, I guess you're
as smart as you can be,
being a girl and all.
[YAMCHA yells]
I'm not letting go
until you say you're sorry!
All right, all right! I'm sorry!
[GOHAN laughing]
[ALL laughing]
Oh! You make me sick!
This might just be our last
chance to laugh, you guys.
[BULMA]
Wait!
Oh, how could they just
leave me behind like that!
Does this mean we can go now?
No! I won't turn back now!
Huh?
They think they can
ditch me 'cause I'm a girl!
Well I'll show them
what this girl can do!
Those boys better watch out!
'Cause here I come!
[BULMA laughing]
[BULMA]
Come on, Puar!
We'll teach those guys
not to run off and leave us!
My, I would say that was
all rather anticlimactic,
wouldn't you?
I mean, the little runt
certainly didn't last
very long, now did he?
Well, what did you
expect? He was only a--
[FRIEZA gasping]
Monkey...
[FRIEZA growls]
[BOY] I really hope that's
not the best you can do,
'cause if it is,
you better give up now!
You can't win, Frieza.
We'll just see about
that, boy! Take this!
Frieza!
[FRIEZA yelling]
You'll destroy us all!
[BOY yells]
[grunting]
What!
What the--?
[BULMA] Hey, what's
going on? I can't see!
What in the world happened
down there, Yamcha?
[BOY] It looks to me like you're
running out of tricks, Frieza!
This Saiyan is
really something else!
[KING KAI] I didn't think it
was really possible, Bubbles.
But this new kid is much
stronger than Frieza!
And after all that Frieza
did on Planet Namek...
I hope this kid
cleans his clock!
You hear me? Kick his butt, kid!
[KING KAI laughing]
Huh?
[BUBBLES babbles]
[KING KAI growls]
Okay! That's two! I'll
give you one more chance
to hit me with
everything you've got!
And then it's
strike three, Frieza.
Game over, you're out!
[FRIEZA] Hmph! It's time
we put an end to this!
[FRIEZA yelling]
[KING KAI gasps]
Oh no! It's just like on Namek!
Frieza's going for broke!
He's trying to destroy
the entire planet!
[FRIEZA cackling]
Hurry up! Are you going
to end this or not?
Just watch me!
This one's for you, Father!
[FRIEZA cackling]
What the...
Huh!
Everyone! Get down!
[KING COLD] You know, Frieza,
you could have done this
right from the start and
saved us a good deal of effort!
[FRIEZA] There's just no
pleasing you sometimes, Father!
Huh?
There's no way!
How?!
Impossible!
[FRIEZA growls]
Why you little...
Excuse me! Is this yours?
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[KING COLD]
Well done, Frieza!
It only took you four tries
to destroy that little boy!
[FRIEZA] I was just warming up,
Father! That's all! Really!
[KING COLD chuckling]
Of course, son! Of course!
Hey! Frieza!
Huh?
[FRIEZA gasps]
Ugh! When I get my hands on--
[BOY yelling]
[yelling continues]
[KING COLD gasps]
[NARRATOR]
Can it really be true?
Has Frieza finally met
his fate at the hands
of this mysterious
young stranger
who claims to be a Super Saiyan?
Find out all this
and more on the next
action-packed episode
of Dragon Ball Z!