[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z...
the battle between Frieza
and Vegeta raged on
though it was clear who had
the upper hand in this fight.
[NARRATOR] Grasping
him with his tail,
Frieza took full adventage
of his couterpart's
vulnerable state
and pummeled the Saiyan
prince mercilessly.
[blows landing,
VEGETA yelling]
[NARRATOR] While Gohan,
Piccolo, and Krillin
watched the horror unfold,
Goku sensed the severity
of the situation as well.
Fortunately, Goku's healing
process was complete
and he erupted
from the spacecraft
determined to use his
regenerated power
to help his friends.
[NARRATOR] But after the
display Frieza has put on,
will it be enough?
Find out... today!
[VEGETA groaning,
blows landing]
[blows landing]
[ALL whimpering]
[VEGETA groans]
[blows landing,
VEGETA grunts]
[GOHAN growls]
Uh...
Ah, but Piccolo...!
[GOKU] Mmmm...
[GOKU] Hm... That's good.
They're close by.
Alrighty, then, this is it.
Just hold on guys!
[blows landing,
VEGETA grunting]
[ALL whimpering]
[VEGETA continues grunting]
[GOHAN grunts]
[VEGETA coughs]
[heavy blow lands]
[VEGETA grunts]
[VEGETA yelling]
[ALL gasp]
[FRIEZA] My, my...
What do we have here?
A fallen prince. Oh, dear!
[VEGETA groans]
[VEGETA yells weakly]
[FRIEZA] It pains me to
see you like this, Vegeta.
I don't know why, but
I still care for you enough
to put you out of your misery.
[VEGETA groans weakly]
Hmm...?
Don't worry.
Everyone gets a turn.
[FRIEZA] Goodnight,
sweet Prince.
[FRIEZA yells]
[FRIEZA] Hmm?
--[PICCOLO] Hn?!
--[KRILLIN] Huh?!
[GOKU] It's okay, guys.
It's really me.
[ALL gasp]
[GOKU] I'm glad to see that
you're all in good health.
This is the first time I've
arrived at the battlefield
that you haven't
been all beat up.
[PICCOLO] Yeah, well, we had a
little help in that department.
It's great to see you again!
I can tell you're
a lot stronger now,
and not just physically.
Hey, Dad! Welcome back!
We missed you!
[KRILLIN] Heh! What do
you think of our new duds?
Not bad... but I don't
think Master Roshi
or ChiChi would approve.
[GOHAN laughs]
[GOKU] I'm proud of you guys!
Especially of you, Gohan. Leave
the rest to me! It's my turn!
Say what?!
Hm?
Goku, did you get hit in
the head or something?
It's going to take everything
we've got to beat him!
I'm fine!
[PICCOLO growls]
[GOHAN] I believe in you.
[KRILLIN] Hey, you're
the man, Goku! Do it!
Take care of that big bully!
And be careful. And
watch out for that tail!
[GOKU] Thanks!
[thinking] He's either
making a huge mistake...
or he's infinitely improved
since I fought him on Earth!
[GOKU] You must be Frieza.
The one responsible
for the horrible
chain of events
that have taken
place on this planet.
The proof is in the pudding,
don't you think? Huh?
Whatever problems
you have with Vegeta,
you can take them
up with me now!
Huh...?
[FRIEZA thinking] I'm sure I've
seen him somewhere before...
Hey, Kakarot...
Looks like you made it...
Kakarot? But that's a
Saiyan name, isn't it?
Huh?! Yes... yes...
that's it! Now I remember!
[BARDOCK] Frieza! Show yourself!
We're not scared of you anymore!
[BARDOCK laughs]
That's it. Face the music...
Don't be afraid of him, men!
I'd rather be a free
man in my grave,
than living as his
puppet or his slave!
[SAIYAN troops muttering]
Come on! Let's get to it!
That's it...
Now we're talkin'!
[BARDOCK chuckles]
Here! Have it!
[FRIEZA cackles]
No way!
[BARDOCK screams]
[screaming continues]
My... son... lives... on...
[BARDOCK screams]
[FRIEZA] Yes, you are a Saiyan.
I was in a skirmish with a
Saiyan who looks just like you.
You're his offspring.
The resemblance between
you is unmistakeable.
I don't care.
Huh?
[thinking] Kakarot's
different than before!
Maybe his last battle
pushed him over the edge!
Maybe he's done it at last...
[VEGETA gasps]
[thinking] A Super Saiyan!
Well, shall we proceed?
Your call...
[FRIEZA grunts]
[FRIEZA gasps]
[GOKU] Haah!
Amazing! I couldn't follow
any of it! How 'bout you?
No...
[thinking] Either my eyes
were playing tricks on me,
or Goku got the best of
him in that little scuffle!
[FRIEZA] Nice move,
but your shoe came untied.
[GOKU] I'm not going
to fall for that.
I don't even
have shoe laces!
[FRIEZA] Darn. I guess
you're a little smarter
than the average Saiyan.
[GOKU] Very funny.
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[FRIEZA] Goodness!
No sense of humor.
No! Don't try to block it, Goku!
[KRILLIN] Everybody
hit the dirt!
[GOKU &amp; KRILLIN yell]
You fool! Die!
Hmph!
[FRIEZA growls]
[FRIEZA yells]
[PICCOLO gasps]
[FRIEZA continues to yell]
[FRIEZA snarls]
[GOKU] Hyyah!
Huh?!
One hand? Not only
did he block them,
but he was able to aim them
away from his friends.
[VEGETA laughs]
Who would have thought?
A lowly soldier like you,
Kakarot. I commend you.
[GOKU] Hmm.
[VEGETA] Frieza, you fool! You
don't get it, do you?!
Kakarot's not an
ordinary Saiyan!
Kakarot is a Super Saiyan!
[FRIEZA gasps]
[VEGETA] That's right!
You heard me!
If there's a God,
He must be good
for letting me live long
enough to see this day.
[VEGETA laughs]
How great! This is a dream come
true!
To see you...
beaten by a Saiyan!
[VEGETA laughs]
[VEGETA gasps]
Huh?!
Oh, no...
[PICCOLO growls]
Enough! Loud mouth. On and
on like a broken record.
[VEGETA whimpers]
Oh, no!
What's your problem?! He was
no threat to you any more!
He couldn't even defend himself!
There's no honor in that!
Huh?!
[FRIEZA] It was the only
way I could shut him up.
He insists on babbling about
that ridiculous legend.
There's no such thing
as a Super Saiyan!
[VEGETA grunts]
[VEGETA] Kakarot!
Listen to me...
Don't be so soft! There's no
stinking honor in any of this!
It's just a game! Play to win!
There are... no rules!
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU] Krillin, no!
You're going to have to get over
your soft-heartedness! Do it!
Forget about your feelings! You
have to! They'll get you killed!
They'll get you killed, Kakarot!
I can't! I can't change who I
am! Not on the battlefield!
My feelings
are my guide!
Besides, everybody deserves a
chance to change their ways,
just like you had!
Fool! You don't... know what
you're dealing... with!
[ALIEN speaking]
[ALIEN screams]
[SAIYAN SOLDIERS laugh]
[ALIEN 2 shouting]
[KING VEGETA chuckles]
[KING VEGETA &amp; VEGETA laugh]
[FRIEZA laughs]
[KING VEGETA grunts]
[FRIEZA] Long live the King...
[FRIEZA cackles]
Oh, my! This is... stupendous!
Wow! What a great show!
Unbelievable! Look at that!
[FRIEZA cackles]
[GOKU] Save your
strength, Vegeta!
No! There's more! He killed our
home planet! It... was him!
He's just a corpse and
he's still blabbing.
I'll have to gag him
to shut him up...
Your father! And mine!
The whole planet!
He blew it up! It's true!
No one... survived... but us...
Ask him if you want! He'll
tell you! He's proud of it!
Please stop talking, Vegeta!
It's sapping all
of your strength!
[VEGETA] No! Listen!
You have to hear this!
We worked so hard for him!
We did everything he
asked of us and more...
He took me... from my father...
when I was just a little boy!
He made me do whatever he wanted
and said he would kill
my Father if I didn't!
I did everything he asked,
but he killed him anyway,
along with
everyone else...
[VEGETA sobs]
[VEGETA] He was scared of us!
Scared that a Super Saiyan
would be born to rise up
and overthrow him...
A touching story.
[VEGETA sobs]
Please... no more.
Save your strength...
[VEGETA] Kakarot! Please!
Destroy... Frieza!
He made me what I am...
Don't let him do it
to anyone else...
Whatever it takes...
stop him... please...
[GOKU] Vegeta...
Wel it's about time.
Saiyans tend to linger
like a bad odor.
[GOKU] Goodbye, Vegeta...
You're not as cold-hearted as
you believed yourself to be.
A heart of stone can't
shed tears like you did.
You must have been holding
them back your whole life...
[GOKU] I'm the only one left...
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU] I think I
understand you now.
You weren't grieving
over your own death
or because our home
planet was destroyed.
You were grieving
because he turned you
into what he wanted you to be.
You never had a chance
to be anything else.
Well, I still respect you.
I know you made a
lot of mistakes...
[GOKU] But now I see that it
wasn't all your fault.
[GOKU] You had the
fiery will of a Saiyan!
Please share that with me
now... 'cause I need it.
[GOKU] Thank you for
saving my son's life
and for buying enough time
for me to recuperate.
I'll do my best to
carry out your wish.
It's true! Vegeta's right!
You have no honor!
For him! And for everyone
else you've destroyed!
[GOKU] I am going to...
finish you!
We'll see about that, won't we?
[NARRATOR} Many have suffered...
And many have perished
at the hands of Frieza!
Can Goku rid the
universe of this evil?
Find out on the
next Dragon Ball Z!