[NARRATOR] Previously
on Dragon Ball Z,
Goku was having
an energy crisis,
but fortunately
the good Majin Buu
was able to
take up the fight
when the mighty Super
Saiyan lost his shine.
But the kind Buu
wouldn't last long!
Something had to
be done, and fast!
Hey! I know you've got a plan.
[VEGETA]
Yes. And?
Well, I hate to pry, but
um, what is it, exactly?
Kakarot, how many times have you
saved the world up until now?
Hmm. What?
How many? I'm not sure.
[VEGETA]
Then perhaps it's time
to let the world
fend for itself, for once.
Now, listen carefully, Dende!
This is very important.
[NARRATOR] And so Vegeta's
plan was put into action!
And Moori summoned the
Dragon on the new Planet Namek.
[PORUNGA]
Name your first wish.
[NARRATOR]
With the first wish,
the planet Earth was brought
back to its original state.
[NARRATOR]
And with the second,
all of its inhabitants
were restored to life.
But staying alive
was the problem.
What did Vegeta have in mind?
[VEGETA] Let's do it.
Now! It's time!
It's time? Time for what?
The Spirit Bomb!
That's your big idea?
A spirit bomb?!
[chatter. laughing]
Is it really you, baby doll?
Of course it's me!
Whoa, dude!
This is totally cosmic!
[BOTH laughing]
Yep. Same old world.
[BABY giggling]
What in the world is going on?
It's all back, as if
nothing ever happened!
Yeah! This is really bizarre!
Hey! How come Majin Buu
isn't here, guys? Hmm?
Neither is Mr. Satan.
Aah! Don't tell me
he beat him!
Wow! Wouldn't that
be something!
[CHICHI, BULMA lauging]
[BULMA] And just where were you
two in the next world, huh?
Well, Krillin and I got to do
a little bit of
training with King Kai.
Oh, I guess we
had it all wrong then!
We just assumed that you
went down to you know where!
Gee! Thanks a lot!
[BULMA, CHICHI laughing]
[MARON]
Daddy!
[KRILLIN]
Huh?
Hey! Whatcha doin'
there, squirt?
[MARON]
Daddy! Daddy! Daddy!
I missed you so much!
Yeah! What a journey!
Being dead wasn't
so bad, now was it?
Huh?
[chuckles lightly]
Dear Videl, Chichi, Bulma.
I'm so glad you made it home.
Oh, how I wish I
could have joined you,
but not this time.
For too long, love has been
a stranger in my cold heart.
Maybe next time, dear ones.
Maybe next time.
A Spirit Bomb?!
But that didn't
work against Frieza,
what makes you
think it'll work now?
It will.
So, that's what you meant
about the world saving itself?
You want the people of Earth to
supply the energy to beat Buu.
Uh.
[KID BUU grunting]
Come on! Get him, Buu!
Give him a wham!
An a pow! An a wap!
--[BUU whimpers]
--[KID BUU grunting]
Punch him back, Buu!
Awe, don't let him do that!
You're bigger than he is!
Pretty please, Buu!
--[KID BUU yells]
--[BUU groans]
[yells]
[BUU]
Uuah!
[KID BUU panting]
[whimpers]
[panting]
You be candy!
[KID BUU yells]
[startled gasps]
Hmmm?
[BUU yelps]
Buu! Buu!
Keep your guard up!
[VEGETA]
Now. It's time.
You know what to do, Kakarot?
Yeah but... do you really
think the people of Earth
have that much energy?
[VEGETA grunts]
Uh! I'm not doubting your plan,
it's just that
Buu's so darn powerful!
It'll be enough!
I've learned not to
underestimate the power
of the human race.
We won't just take a little bit.
We'll take as much as
they can possibly give.
The maximum, huh?
[PORUNGA] What is your
third and final wish?
[DENDE] Uhh! Please,
just one moment!
Vegeta!
[VEGETA]
What?
Uh, Porunga wants to know
what your third wish is!
How 'bout some new boots.
Size nine, please.
New boots! He's not
serious, is he?
Uhh...
Uuhhh...!
Of course not!
[VEGETA] Idiot!
Is Kibito Shin there?
Yes! Here!
I need to speak to the
inhabitants of the Earth!
All of them at one time!
Huh? Uh, are you
saying that you want
to speak telepathically
to the entire planet?
[VEGETA]
Exactly!
It can't be done!
Eeehhh!
Uh, Vegeta, we don't know how.
Great, now what?
[KING KAI] Hey, fellas!
I can arrange that!
[chuckles, snorts]
What?
Oh, hey! It's King Kai!
Can you really do it?
Of course, I can.
It's a cinch.
Planetary telepathic
communication is my specialty.
[chuckles]
Okay, Vegeta.
You've got the floor.
Whenever you feel
the urge, just go for it.
That's more like it!
People of the Earth!
Listen carefully!
[VEGETA]
As you know,
some very strange events have
been taking place recently.
Your entire planet was destroyed
at the hands of Majin Buu.
But then, in a snap,
everything was
restored back to normal.
Many of you are doubting if
all of this actually happened,
but I can assure you
that this is not a dream.
Not a dream?
Wait!
Hey! What's this
guy talking about?
Shh!
Oh, uh... Uh, right!
He's speaking to
the people of Earth.
Hm?
Uhhh, that's not possible!
Uh, you guys.
Instead of pretending
to talk to the people
of the Earth and all,
why don't you go over
there and please help Buu!
We are trying to help.
Trust me.
This is the best way.
Unfortunately,
Majin Buu is still alive
and the Earth is
still in great danger.
A small group of warriors
have taken up the fight
on your behalf.
Hey! It really is him!
That's Vegeta's voice!
Shh!
[VEGETA] However,
the battle has been
extremely difficult,
and we can't
win it by ourselves.
[sighs]
Vegeta!
[VEGETA] That is why I am
speaking to you right now.
To ask you for your help.
If all of you would raise
your hands up to the sky,
and offer a portion
of your energy,
we could use it to defeat
Majin Buu once and for all!
No more being slaughtered
like sacrificial lambs!
Consider this your
first small stride
towards becoming
a warrior race!
Now, let's begin!
Raise your hands up! Now!
He ah, certainly has a way
with words! A bit dramatic.
They're ready, Kakarot.
Take your place.
Right!
[chuckles]
You're really on top
of things! I'm impressed!
All right! If there was ever
a time, guys! This is it!
It's time! My dad's ready!
This is really fun!
Yeah!
Hmm! Who would have thought!
Vegeta comes
through in the clutch.
Whoa, yeah! Here it is!
One Spirit Bomb, coming up!
[thinking]
Ahh! Wow!
At this rate, this thing's
going to be enormous!
This is just
from Gohan's group.
Yeah! What an incredible start!
When everyone
else kicks theirs in,
I think we'll
have energy to spare.
[VEGETA thinking]
Yes! Yes! That's it!
It's working! Keep it
coming! We need more!
Give it everything you've got!
People of Earth!
Don't stop now! It's working!
All of you!
Raise your hands up!
Okay, yeah! I get it!
Here!
Uh... Like this?
[laughs]
All right!
Yipee! Yeah! Like this!
[giggles]
Yeah!
[ROSHI chuckles]
[OOLONG, PUAR laugh]
[ALL laugh]
That boost was from
Krillin and Bulma's group!
Vegeta! Keep it comin'!
[thinking] Good, good!
They're doing it!
[DENDE] Look how big
it is! Wow, it's huge!
That should be
enough to destroy Buu!
Not quite! But at this rate
it won't take much longer!
It looks like they're
actually going to pull it off!
--Yeah!
--Ha-ha!
[KING KAI] Wait!
Something's wrong!
[KING KAI] If Goku's gathering
energy from everyone on Earth,
the Spirit Bomb should
be much larger by now!
Something's not right!
Give it some time!
I'm sure it's going
to get bigger and bigger!
Yeah! Surely!
[MOORI]
Let's see here!
Porunga! Are you
absolutely positively sure
that all the Earthlings
were brought back to life?
Do you doubt me?
It is as I said!
[BUU yelps]
[chuckles]
[groans, coughs]
Huh?
[whimpers]
[bellows]
No! He didn't!
There goes our planet!
[grunting]
[thinking] I can't
lose this energy!
[MR. SATAN yelling]
Blast it!
Darn, the fat one's dead!
[KID BUU chuckles]
Hmm!
It's all over!
We needed more time!
[VEGETA grunts]
[chuckles]
Hm?
Look there!
It's Buu! He's alive!
[BUU chuckles]
[KID BUU grunting]
--[BUUS chuckle]
--[KID BUU groaning]
[laughing]
That's it! A quadruple whammy!
Nice! We're still
in the game!
[GOKU] Vegeta! It's not
getting any bigger!
There's no way
this is going to cut it!
We need more energy than this!
Now what?
No! It should have been
fully completed by now!
Darn! What's going on?
[GUY 1]
Raise your hands!
[MAN 2]
You raise your hands!
I don't believe
in that nonsense!
Where did that come from?
There's nobody there! Is there?
[WOMAN 1]
Whose voice was that?
[WOMAN 2] I don't know,
but he sounded nuts!
What? I don't believe it!
Are you gonna
raise your hands up?
Naa! Let's go see
a movie or something.
That was so weird!
No kidding!
Mommy! My tummy's growling!
Huh? Oh, well, how 'bout
a big ice cream cone?
--[KIDS] Yay!
--[GIRL] Yay! Ice cream!
[DUDE 1] It must
have been a trick!
[DUDE 2] Yeah! Some sort
of mass hypnosis!
Aaah!
Are they mad?
[barks]
Quiet, boy! Sshhh!
Now is not the time!
Darn those idiots! Don't they
care about their own world?!
They're like children!
Everything has
to be done for them!
When are you going to grow up?!
Can't you Earthlings
do anything for yourselves?!
[thinking]
What's the hold up?
Why isn't everyone
giving their energy?
Don't have much time!
Every second is vital!
[growls]
Ah! Good heavens! Buu...!
[laughing]
[grunting]
[BUU]
Aaah!
Oh, no!
[chuckles]
Ooh!
--[KID BUU grunts]
--[BUU yelps]
[laughs intensely]
[BOTH whimpering]
[yell]
You have to help! Please help!
If you don't,
he's going to die!
[grunts]
[MR. SATAN]
Please! I beg of you!
[VEGETA grunts]
[sobbing]
[thinking]
Darn those Earthlings!
Maybe they're not worth saving!
Fine! I'm going!
[KING KAI] Wait! Vegeta!
Please! Don't be rash!
You've got to try
to persuade them again!
It's our only hope!
[KING KAI] Think of it
from their point of view.
Would you obey a
strange voice from the sky
if it told you what to do?
They're frightened.
This sort of thing doesn't
happen to them every day.
I think you should try again.
All right! I'll do it!
[VEGETA]
People of the Earth...
Raise you hands up right now
or you're all going to die!
[KING KAI hollers]
[indistinct chatter]
[chuckles]
Vegeta is a master tactician.
His plan is excellent.
[chuckles]
Except for one thing.
He put his faith in a plebeian
race from the dark ages.
[chuckles]
I finally get to
see those monkeys fry!
[laughs intensely]
Hey! What the heck's
going on down there?
No one except
our family and friends
have offered any energy!
I know that!
For some reason
those idiot Earthlings
won't do what
I tell them to do.
[BUU wailing]
[GOKU] Vegeta!
You've got to try again!
Okay.
Hey! People of the Earth!
You are all in great danger!
Majin Buu has not been
defeated! He lives!
Recently your whole
planet was destroyed!
That was not a dream!
And it will happen again
if you don't act quickly!
Stand up for your planet!
Raise your hands!
Lend your strength
and get rid of Majin Buu
before he gets rid of you!
[NARRATOR] Vegeta's plea
has fallen on deaf ears.
As Goku holds the
Spirit Bomb up in the sky
like a symbol of hope,
the Saiyan Prince agonizes
over how to break down
the dam of doubt
that is holding back the vast
reservoir of human energy.
Can he get through in time?
Stay tuned for scenes from the
next episode of Dragon Ball Z!