[NARRATOR] Last time,
on Dragon Ball Z!
Nappa and Vegeta continued
their conquest of the planet,
much to the terror and
dismay of Krillin and Gohan.
But Goku, having finally
returned to Earth
with the new skills taught
to him by King Kai,
put a sudden halt to the
Saiyans' sinister plans.
Thanks a lot,
Vegeta...
[NARRATOR] Not to be outdone,
Vegeta took the shame
of his comrade's failure
into his own hands,
and brought their
partnership to an end...
Die!
[NARRATOR]
Permanently.
[NARRATOR] Vegeta seems
confident of victory,
but Goku still has a
few surprises in store
for the evil Saiyan...
When the battle
continues... today!
[VEGETA] So, Kakarot,
are you ready?
[VEGETA chuckling]
[GOHAN whimpering]
I know a
better place!
Wherever!
Just lead the way!
[GOKU thinking]
I've got to be careful...
There's no telling
how powerful he is...
[KRILLIN]
Well, there they go.
[GOHAN]
Yeah...
[KRILLIN] Gohan, I, uh, I
guess we'd better get going.
Hey, Gohan, try
not to worry!
Your dad knows
what he's doing,
he's got everything
under control!
Really, I mean it!
Goku is the toughest
guy in the whole world!
Hey, plus, you
and I are a team!
We really did great!
Don't you think?
Yeah!
[KRILLIN] Now, let's get you
back to your mother.
I think she'll be pretty
happy to see you.
Yeah, no one will get hurt
if we fight way out here.
Kakarot...
I have a
proposition for you...
[VEGETA] I'm only going
to say this once,
so listen
carefully.
I, Vegeta, Prince
of all Saiyans,
would like to
offer you, Kakarot,
the opportunity to stand
beside me in this conquest.
With Nappa gone,
I could use a good man!
[VEGETA] Think about it...
We would rule the planets.
You could have
anything you desired.
There's no one in the
universe that could touch us!
[VEGETA] Nothing would
be out of your grasp!
Well, what do you
say, Kakarot?
I have everything that
I could ever want
right here on Earth!
So, I'll have to say...
no thanks.
Besides, I've seen how
you treat your partners.
Not much
job security...
[VEGETA chuckling]
Alright, then, so be it!
You had your chance!
[GOKU] Hyaah!
[fighting sounds]
Raah!
[GOKU yelling]
[VEGETA] Say goodbye!
Man, he's good! Far better
than I expected him to be...
I'll still
beat him!
Kakarot...
What's wrong?
I was hoping for a more
interesting fight!
You'll get one!
I promise!
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU snarling]
Kaio-Ken...
Attack!
Ah?!
Ngagh!
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Haah!
Hmph!
[VEGETA] That Kaio-Ken
Attack is a nice trick,
but I've encountered something
just like it before!
Hah?!
[VEGETA chuckling]
Don't tell me that's
all you've got?
If it is,
you'd better quit!
[VEGETA laughing]
Heh. Funny... As grim as
things look right now,
I kind of like
the challenge!
[BABA] Look into
my crystal ball,
with your own eyes,
you'll see it all!
[chanting]
[BABA] Crystal ball,
bring to our sight,
news of this
important fight...
Uh, we're
all waiting!
What's wrong
with it?
You banging it
around, that's what!
Alright! I've
had it with you!
Bring it on,
bow-head!
Wait, girls! It's
not broken! Stop it!
I think the crystal
ball is overwhelmed.
Goku and Vegeta
are emitting
an inconceivable
amount of energy!
This isn't exactly
an ordinary fight!
So, it's started?
I mean Goku and that
guy are fighting?
Yes, I believe so.
I know! We can check
it out on the Scouter!
[ROSHI] Good thinking,
Bulma! What does it say?
Let's see... Two huge
power levels due west!
Only two?
Uhh... mm-hmm...
[CHICHI] Oh, Daddy!
[OX KING] There, there...
[CHICHI crying]
[thinking] Please, Dad...
Be careful...
[VEGETA thinking] Look at him!
Smiling and ready for more!
Who does he think he is?
What kind of power could
he possibly be hiding?
Guess I'll just
have to find out...
That's it?
That was your best?
I've got some bad
news for you...
You may be stronger than
anyone else on this planet...
But even at your peak,
you're still no match for me!
Wanna bet?
[VEGETA] Hah! No need
to wager... Behold!
The true power of
a Saiyan Prince!
[VEGETA growling]
[VEGETA snarling]
[VEGETA roaring]
Oh, man!
What power!
I think the whole planet
is actually shaking!
[TV NEWSMAN]
Although our brave news team
has been reporting
live on location
throughout this
entire ordeal,
unknown technical difficulties
beyond our control
have repeatedly
interrupted our broadcast.
We can only assume that the
fighting is still taking place,
and that these strange displays
of power and abilities,
far beyond that of
the human condition,
are behind the abrupt changes
in the state of our planet.
In a related story,
world leaders from countries
around the globe met today
to discuss possible
plans of action
to deal with these super
powered beings, hoping--
Well, I guess we'll
never find out
what's going on
out there...
Hey! Go sleep it off
at home, blondie!
Can it, jerk...
Fill 'er up!
That'll be your
tenth! You got money?
[LAUNCH] Here...
Whu--!
The whole world's going
down the toilet...
Which means all that cash
is useless now anyway...
Hey... are you alright?
Well, if you don't want this
money anymore... I'll just...
[LAUNCH] What's that?!
Guh! What's what?
What's that sound?
Listen!
Uh... That's
just static!
[distant rumbling]
[crowd murmuring]
What's going on?
Look! Up in the sky!
[screaming]
[birds squawking]
That's freaky...
What's wrong with them?
[VEGETA grunting]
Hunh?!
What power...
Amazing!
[VEGETA growling]
[growling continues]
[VEGETA shouting]
[GOKU shouting]
[VEGETA yelling]
[yelling continues]
[GOKU panting]
[GOKU] I think it's
finally over...
Whoa...
That was incredible!
And now everything
is calm... too calm...
[VEGETA] Kakarot!
Farewell...
You're finished!
[GOKU shouting]
[VEGETA] What's the matter?
Can't find me?
Haah!
Kaio-Ken!
Times two!
Hraagh!
[VEGETA chuckling]
Well now, missed him...
How nimble!
[VEGETA] Nice one!
[thinking] What an
incredible level of power!
I'd better think of
something fast...
I don't know how much
longer I can keep this up!
I've got
no choice...
If the Double Kaio-Ken
Attack doesn't work,
I guess I'll
try a triple!
Sorry, King Kai, but I
don't see any other way!
[VEGETA] What's the
matter, Kakarot?
You don't seem too
eager to continue!
Don't tell me you already
need to catch your breath?
We were just
getting started!
[GOKU] Don't wait on me!
Feel free to lead off anytime!
[thinking] Goku's insane!
This guy's beating
him senseless,
but he just keeps
coming back for more!
I know Goku's tough,
but it seems like this time,
he's finally
met his match...
[VEGETA] This staring contest
is beginning to irritate me.
Are you planning on continuing
our fight anytime today?
What's it going to be?
I'm tired of waiting!
[thinking] Alright, I'll try
the triple Kaio-Ken attack!
I sure hope my
body can take it!
[VEGETA laughing]
I keep forgetting that
you're an Earthling now!
You don't even have
a tail, do you?
You let them
operate on you?
What'd they do, get you
while you were sleeping?
Now I see why you have no
desire to join me on the hunt!
If we still had
a home planet,
you'd be a
laughing stock there!
[YAJIROBE thinking]
Oh, man!
It looks like Goku's
in big trouble!
I've got to help
him somehow...
And I guess the best
way for me to do that
would be to, uh... Hide!
Somewhere over this way...
[thinking] Okay, this is it!
Time to see what I'm made of.
[GOKU grunting]
Hmm?!
[GOKU growling]
Alright, here goes nothing!
Kaio-Ken Attack times three!
What? No! I told him not
to go over a double!
No matter what!
This isn't good. I don't know
if his body can handle it!
I didn't have time to
prepare him for that...
[KING KAI whimpering]
Oh, Goku...
Please be careful...
[BUBBLES chattering]
[GREGORY] C'mon, Goku!
You can do it!
[GOKU yelling]
Uh!
[CHICHI]
What's it say?
Wow! Look at it go!
Hey, let me
try it, Bulma!
Can it, Oolong!
This isn't a game!
Goku's power level
is rising rapidly!
At this rate
he'll explode!
[BABA] Oh, my!
[CHICHI] Oh, no! Goku!
Seventeen thousand... Nineteen
thousand... Over twenty-one!
Ahh!
[OOLONG] Whoa!
[CHICHI] Bulma,
are you okay?!
Yeah, I think so...
[OOLONG] Whoa-hoa!
Talk about overload! Man!
Uhh... ahh!
Huh?
[GOHAN whimpering]
[KRILLIN] Hey, Gohan,
what's the matter? Gohan?
[KRILLIN]
Let's keep moving... Come on!
We gotta get to Kame House!
[thinking] Daddy, what is
that? Something's different...
[GOKU growling]
What? No way!
Rraagh!
[NARRATOR] What new level
of power has Goku reached?
And is this new power
enough to stop
Vegeta's path
of destruction?
Goku is determined to see
this through to the end,
but, with the
unpredictability of Vegeta,
what else might be
in store for him?
Find out, on the next
action-packed episode
of Dragon Ball Z!