[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
the kettle was boiling over
on the Planet Namek!
The Nameks' home planet
had been severely damaged
by a blast from Frieza and it
was due to explode any minute.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
Frieza was struggling
to gather enough
energy to achieve
his maximum power level;
one hundred percent of
his true potential.
[FRIEZA growls]
[FRIEZA yells]
Frieza, let's do this
while we're still young!
[NARRATOR] And the
final battle began:
The ultimate Frieza against
Goku, the mighty Super Saiyan.
[NARRATOR] But it
appeared that Frieza
had regained the upper-hand over
Goku now that he had attained
his maximum power level.
[blows landing,
GOKU grunting]
[NARRATOR] It was beginning to
seem as if King Kai was right:
That Goku had made a terrible
mistake by allowing Frieza
the time that he needed
to fully energize himself.
[FRIEZA yells]
[GOKU] Huh...?!
[NARRATOR] Things were
looking grim indeed
for the mighty Saiyan.
[FRIEZA pants]
Well, fancy that!
One shot and he's
throwing in the towel.
Strike up a dirge!
[NARRATOR] But Goku
wasn't done just yet.
[GOKU] Don't get
too excited Frieza!
Because this battle
is far from over.
You're running out of time.
[GOKU] Don't worry!
What I have to do won't
take long, trust me!
[FRIEZA] You fool!
Do you really believe that?
Don't you understand?
I've won! Not you! Me!
Get it?
[FRIEZA yells]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
Superb! Really!
A very rare power indeed!
But I go on and on!
I am lord of the Universe!
Nothing can stop me!
Nothing! See?!
I remain untouched!
You! Them! You crumble! You die!
But I-- I live on!
[FRIEZA giggles]
[YAMCHA] King Kai,
what's the matter?
[TIEN] Something happened!
[CHIAOTZU] Tell us,
King Kai, please!
I-It's, uh, Goku... He's,
uh, running out of time!
I don't understand!
It didn't have
to end this way...
[KAMI] King Kai?
King Kai, are you there?
This is Kami.
Can you hear me?
[KING KAI growls]
[KING KAI] Yes, Kami!
I can hear you!
What is it now?
[KAMI] Uh, yes, pardon me, sir,
but I wanted to let
you know that Mr. Popo
has located the
seventh Dragon Ball
and that he should
have it shortly.
[KING KAI] Yes, and...?
[KAMI] Oh, uh,
yes, of course!
Let me get to the point:
I was wondering if I should use
the wish to bring Yamcha and
Tien back to this dimension.
[KING KAI] Oh! Yes, I see...
[KAMI] Unfortunately, Chiaotzu
can't be wished back
since he's already been revived
once by the Dragon Balls.
[KING KAI] Oh, yeah...
[CHIAOTZU groans sadly]
[TIEN] Chiaotzu...
It's no big deal, right?
Huh?
H-Hey!
No worries, I'm stayin'!
I wouldn't take off without you!
No way! You can't!
You have to go!
Hey, he doesn't have to go
anywhere, and neither do I!
Are you nuts?
You've got a
sweetheart back home!
Bulma! Remember?
Uh, yeah, you're right...
Uhh... Yo!
Hey, yo! Hey, yo!
[KAMI] U-uhh yes,
King Kai, I'm still here.
[KING KAI] Kami, you said
that Tien and Yamcha
could be wished back.
Does that mean that more than
one person can be revived
with these Dragon Balls
at the same time?
[KAMI] Of course, as long
as they perished
under some common circumstance,
they certainly can.
[KING KAI] Ahh, yes, very good.
Okay, okay, lemme
get this straight:
So if we asked the Dragon to
restore all of those who were
killed by Vegeta, for
instance, would it work?
[KAMI] Uhh, well,
yes, it should.
But only for those
who were killed
within a year's time at most.
[KING KAI] I see!
And that doesn't just
apply to those from Earth,
but includes people from
other planets as well?
[KAMI] I think so...
I don't see any reason
why it wouldn't.
[KING KAI] Good!
Now, Kami, this is the most
important question of all:
What if a mother lost her
children at the hands of Vegeta,
for instance, and her grief
caused her to pass away, too?
Now if we wished back all of
those who were killed by Vegeta,
would her life be
restored as well since
Vegeta's actions were the direct
cause of her passing away?
[KAMI] Mm... Oh, dear me...
[KAMI] Gosh, King Kai, I'm
not at all sure about that one.
We've never had a case
like that before...
But I would say that there's
a very strong possibility
that she, too, would
be restored to life.
[KING KAI] I see...
[TIEN] Are you
alright, King Kai?
Yes! I'm fine!
Now! Kami! Listen up, please!
[KAMI] Huh?! You
have a wish, King Kai?
Yes! To restore all
those killed by Frieza
and his gang
back to life!
Please work...
Man, this is crazy!
It's falling apart!
My gosh, this is scary!
This thing could
blow at any second!
This is bad! This
is gonna be the end!
Hey, think positive.
How dare you, you twerp!
You have no idea what
I've been through, do you?
It's been horrible!
Well, look on
the bright side.
[BULMA] Bright side?!
I've been chased
by dinosaurs,
I had my body stolen
by a crazy frog,
I was nearly crushed to
death, I have major B.O.,
and my legs are so bristly
I feel like a cactus!
So tell me: What's
the bright side?!
[GOHAN gasps]
[BULMA screams]
[BULMA] Gohan! Don't you
ever do that to me again!
You scared the life out of me!
[GOHAN] Look! There's
the bright side!
We made it to my Dad's ship!
And it's still
in one piece!
That's a miracle
if I ever saw one!
Alright! We're going
home! We made it!
Whoa! Ha!
[GOHAN] Uh, oh!
There goes the ship!
[BULMA] What do you mean "There
goes the ship"?! Do something!
Hey! Stop!
You can't just leave
without our permission!
As an expert on
destroying planets,
I'd say that you're
just about out of time.
Agreed?
And yet you're standing
there like a statue
waiting for me to
make the first move.
It doesn't make any sense.
The longer you wait,
the worse your chances are.
I know!
You're stalling,
giving those kids
a chance to escape.
That's it!
[FRIEZA giggles]
Well, that's okay.
They'll be my next targets.
It shouldn't be too hard to
track them down, should it?
Well, that depends.
If you're dead, it will be.
Huh?!
You're through! Done!
It all ends here!
[FRIEZA giggles]
You're the one
who's through!
Not me! Do you hear me?! You!
[thinking] Gohan, why
haven't you left yet
like I told you to?!
[FRIEZA yells]
Huh?!
[yelling continues]
[FRIEZA growls]
[GOKU grunts]
Huh?!
[FRIEZA grunts]
[FRIEZA yells]
[GOKU grunts]
[FRIEZA growls]
[GOKU yells]
[FRIEZA yells]
[FRIEZA growls]
[FRIEZA] Super... Saiyan...
[KAMI] King Kai, I have
relayed your wish to Mr. Popo.
He's very close
to the seventh ball.
It won't be long now.
Thanks to Popo, we'll
soon have them all.
[KING KAI] Ah, very good!
Excellent, Kami! Nice work!
[KAMI] Thank you, King Kai!
Sir, If you don't mind my
asking, can you explain
the reasoning behind the wish?
[KING KAI] Yes, of course.
I know it's a little confusing.
But if we revive all of the
victims of Frieza and his gang,
then the Nameks will
all be brought back
and I think Guru will be too!
[KAMI] But I thought Guru
died of natural causes?
[KING KAI] No, Guru
died of a broken heart...
Such was the pain that he felt
over the loss of his people.
Frieza's handywork!
[KAMI] I see...
[KING KAI] Now,
when Guru returns,
then there will be one more
wish to be granted by the
Dragon of Namek because Gohan
and Krillin only used two!
Oh yeah, right! I see!
And that wish?
[KING KAI] That wish will be to
transport everyone on Namek
except Frieza to
the planet Earth!
And as a going away present,
we'll give the planet Namek
to Frieza which should
explode in his face
and blow him to smithereens
after everyone's gone!
Not bad!
It's brilliant,
but extremely risky!
[KING KAI] This plan
requires a great sacrifice
on your part, guys!
You'd have to stay here
at least a year longer!
I don't
have a choice...
Don't look at me.
Yeah, that's fine. No prob!
Bulma can wait a while!
Well, that's
three thumbs up!
I'm in! Sure!
[KING KAI]
Good!
Okay, Kami! It's unanimous!
Proceed as planned
and keep me informed
of Mr. Popo's progress!
As you know, timing is
everything in this venture!
[KAMI] You can rest assured that
we'll do everything we can
to get this done as as quickly
as possible, King Kai!
[BULMA] Gosh, I don't
know about this, Gohan!
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure. Hey, come on.
Okay... Here I come.
But I think I'm going to
stay over here by the door...
Whoaa...
[GOHAN] Gosh, I wonder why
all the lights are out...?
[BULMA] Whoaa!
Okay... I guess I'm in...
Okay. Now about those lights.
Please work...
Hey! We have power, Gohan!
Huh?!
[BULMA whimpers]
[BULMA screams]
Look, Gohan, look!
Right there! It's Piccolo!
Yeah, I know.
Oh, I get it! Gee, thanks!
Well, I'm not traveling
across the galaxy
with a shady character
like Piccolo on board!
Who do you think I am?
There's no telling
what he might do
once we're out in deep space
in the middle of nowhere!
There's just no way!
If he stays, you
can count me out!
But he's not bad,
he's good!
Really!
And that's the truth!
He's coming or we're
not going anywhere!
[BULMA gasps]
Now, look, Gohan.
Piccolo belongs here.
It's his home.
I doubt he even
wants to leave here.
[GOHAN growls]
R-Right! Nevermind!
[thinking] Oh, man!
This is just great!
How do I get myself into
these predicaments?
[BULMA screams]
Huh...?
[FRIEZA growls]
Huh?!
[GOKU yells]
[FRIEZA] Hm?!
[GOKU] Yikes!
Huh?!
[FRIEZA gasps]
[GOKU yells]
[FRIEZA grunts]
[FRIEZA growls]
[GOKU thinking] He's struggling
not to be blinded by his rage!
Hey! This isn't funny!
We're sinking even more!
That does it, Gohan!
We can't wait anymore!
Do you hear me?!
We need to get
out of here rght now!
Oh, my gosh!
[BULMA] Oh, man! Come on!
Huh?!
We're not
leaving, Bulma!
Not yet!
Please take
your hand away
or I'm going to bite
it as hard as I can.
He's my Dad! I love him!
Please, Bulma! I know he'd do
the same for you if he could!
Please, my Dad needs us!
He does!
Gosh, Gohan...
[rumbling]
[BULMA] Alright, Gohan...
Two more minutes.
[GOHAN] Thank you, Bulma.
[KAMI] Piccolo, I'm very
proud of you, Piccolo.
But you have to try to
hang on a little bit longer.
They're counting on us now.
Don't give up yet, son.
[KING KAI sighs]
[MR. POPO] Kami!
Kami, it's me, Popo,
can you hear me?
[KAMI] Loud and clear, Mr. Popo!
Go ahead!
I'm done, Kami.
They're all here!
All seven balls!
I'm waiting for your final word.
[KAMI] It's time, Popo.
Make the wish!
[FRIEZA yells]
[FRIEZA growls]
Speak! Name your wish!
Say it now, and it
will be granted.
Yes, of course!
Can you please restore the
lives of all those killed
by Frieza and his gang?
Is it within your power
to grant this wish?
I... don't know.
[MR. POPO] It's very bad
that you don't know!
If you don't know, who does?
So many lives are
depending on this!
[SHENRON] I will try!
[KING KAI] This is it, guys!
All we can do now is pray.
[FRIEZA growls]
[GOKU] Frieza! You're through!
[NARRATOR] As the Eternal
Dragon tries to fulfill
Mr. Popo's wish, Goku and
Frieza are on a collision course
with one another.
Who will emerge victorious from
this battle of good versus evil?
[FRIEZA yells]
[GOKU growls]
[NARRATOR] Time is
of the essence...
The planet Namek
is about to explode
next time on Dragon Ball Z!