[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball Z,
the malicious
new form of Majin Buu
unleashed his
Human Extinction Attack,
bringing the Earth's
dwindling population
only a handful away from zero.
Tired of the
effortless plunder,
Majin Buu desired
only one thing.
A fight with his
promised challenger.
And in the
Hyperbolic Time Chamber,
that's exactly what he got.
[NARRATOR]
So the battle began.
Majin Buu versus Gotenks,
the cocky fusion
of Goten and Trunks.
Drawing from the
borrowed week of training
inside the time chamber,
Gotenks deployed an onslaught
of never-before-seen,
and somewhat
juvenile, techniques.
Hold on. Ugh!
[yells, grunts]
[NARRATOR]
None of them worked,
and Gotenks was forced
to fight more seriously.
After revealing he could power
up to Super Saiyan levels
while already in a fused state,
Gotenks prepared for
his favorite new trick.
[GOTENKS] It's new so sorry
if it's a little sloppy.
A Super Ghost Kamikaze Attack!
Huh?
[NARRATOR] The fate
of the empty planet
hinges on the
strength of a child,
and with the imagination
only a child could posses,
Gotenks has delivered,
producing what is perhaps
the most bizarre technique
in Z Fighter history.
What... is that?
[NARRATOR] Now,
as the battle within
this altered-time
dimension rages on,
two important
questions must be asked...
[SUPERGHOST]
Ready Buu?
[NARRATOR] Who will
claim victory in this fight
between Gotenks and Majin Buu?
And secondly, what in
the world is going on?
[GOTENKS]
You're dead.
[SUPERGHOST laughing]
Nnahhhh!
Do I scare you?
Watch out,
I'm coming to get you!
Nahhh!
[laughs intensely]
Uh, what is that thing?
How did he do that?
[GOTENKS] I'll give
you one warning, Buu!
[BOTH] If you
mess with the ghost,
you'll be toast! Ngh!
[BOTH laugh]
Now let's put his lights out!
Get ready, ugly!
'Cause here comes
the beat-down
of the Super Ghost
Kamikaze Attack!
That's me!
[yells, grunts]
[SUPER BUU grunts, yells]
[growls]
[SUPERGHOST groans, laughs]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[PICCOLO]
What happened?
Huh?
[SUPER BUU gasping]
Yeah! Gotcha!
Just a touch
from the Super Ghost
and you go off like a grenade!
[gasping, groaning]
[GOTENKS]
Kinda hurts, doesn't it?
Ha-ha! Yeah! All right!
Hurry up, Gotenks!
You'll be separated soon!
Ah, just relax, would ya?!
I know what I'm doing!
Super...
Ghost...
Kamikaze...
Attack!
Now for the big finish.
I'll be legendary!
[grunting]
[PICCOLO gasps]
[SUPERGHOSTS grunt, groan]
[GOTENKS chuckles]
[SUPERGHOSTS chuckle, holler]
[snoring]
[SUPERGHOST 5] Nghhh!
[laughs intensely]
[GOTENKS grunts]
Hey! Wake up!
[SUPERGHOST 4 yawns]
Line up! Arms out n' forward!
Hey pal! Not so close!
We'll explode
if we touch, ya know!
Yeah, in your case that
would be an improvement!
Hey! You! I never said
you could talk, did I?!
Who's that guy?
Well I guess
he's the boss-boy!
He's not the boss of me!
I think he's
the boss of us all!
Quiet! Eyes forward!
Now! Sound off!
Sound off!
[SUPERGHOSTS]
1, 2, 3, 4, 5,
6, 7, 8, 9, 10!
Good!
--Hey!
--Huh?
In case you haven't
noticed, he's back.
That punk!
Of all the nerve--!
I'm about to blow him up
and he's drinking a soda!
Get on your feet, Majin Buu!
Hm? Why should I?
Number One and Number Two!
Make him sorry!
[SUPERGHOST 1, 2]
Yes sir!
[SUPERGHOST 1, 2 groan]
Ha! Your same trick
won't work twice!
Nnnaaahhh!
Right! New plan!
[PICCOLO]
Huh?!
[GOTENKS] Okay listen,
we've gotta hit this guy
in his weak spot; his stomach!
[SUPERGHOST 3] Should we
give him indigestion?
[SUPERGHOST 4] And make
him pop like a balloon?
[SUPERGHOST 3]
It'll be easy 'cause he's
already full of hot air!
[SUPERGHOSTS laughing]
Hey, Supreme Kai?
You feel that?
[SUPREME KAI gasps]
Majin Buu's energy signal's
completely gone!
Ah! Yes, you're right!
What does that mean?
Has he died?
Well, no. Something
tells me he's still alive.
And the strange thing is,
I can't sense
the boys' energy either!
That's because,
they're fighting
in a different time
dimension of course!
[GOKU] A different
time dimension?!
Yes, that's what I said.
Think about it, kid!
The Hyperbolic Time Chamber?!
Well gee, I wonder why
they're fighting in there?
Maybe Majin Buu
barged in on them
while the boys were training.
No, I'm afraid it was the
big green fighter from Namek
who led Majin Buu
into that room.
But I have no idea why.
Huh? Oh, thanks for the tip.
Wow, he's good.
And the Old Kai's even
boosted Gohan's power.
You better be careful,
Supreme Kai,
or you could be out of a job!
Hm!
Truly, you'd think
I hadn't done anything
for you and Gohan at all.
[ROSHI, KRILLIN]
Hm?
[ROSHI]
Whatcha got, Bulma?
Oh nothing--
just a little snack.
Once they get out of that room
I'm sure they'll be hungry.
I doubt that they'll
have the energy to eat.
[BULMA] Well I
had to do something!
I don't know how
you guys can stay so calm.
You said be optimistic!
They're the sons of
Goku and Vegeta, right?
If there's anybody who can
save the world, they can.
[GOTENKS] Okay, so you all
know what to do, right?
[SUPERGHOSTS laugh]
Hurry up, Gotenks!
Seriously, you don't
have much time left!
Ghosts! Ready!
Move out!
[SUPERGHOSTS]
Yeah!
Hey! Good luck, buddy!
Let's do it!
Uh...!
That was not the idea.
Okay, forget those two idiots!
Number 10 stay with me.
Everyone else go forward
and carry out this attack!
[SUPERGHOSTS yell]
Oh yes!
Hey! What is that?
I don't know.
[SUPERGHOST 7]
Sure looks tasty!
[SUPERGHOST 6]
Naturally.
[SUPERGHOST 8]
Yeah it's candy coated!
[SUPERGHOST 9]
Is it a cookie?
[ALL]
Mmmm... Yummy!
Ah.
Hey there,
wanna bite there, buddy?
--Aaah!
--See-ya!
It worked!
Yeah!
Don't celebrate yet!
Let's wait until
the smoke clears!
[gasps]
Now! It's up to you, 10!
Fly down Buu's throat
and really give him
somethin' to chew on!
Yes sir!
[SUPERGHOST 10 laughs]
Legend!
[MR. SATAN] I-I just don't
understand how it happened.
Nothing makes sense...
I mean, we were happy,
weren't we?
[stomach growls]
[barking]
[BEE panting]
If you don't keep quiet
I'll turn you into a hotdog!
[BEE whines]
[groans]
[BUU laughs]
Buu...
[laughs]
[BUU screams]
[laughs intensely]
[yells]
[MR. SATAN, BEE yell]
[chuckles]
[BUU laughs]
[MR. SATAN]
Let's keep going!
[BEE]
Arf! Arf!
[MR. SATAN] That's strange.
There's no one here.
Where did everyone go?
Hello? Hello?
Ha-ha! That worked
just like I planned.
My ghosts made
mincemeat out of him!
This battle isn't over yet!
He could still
come back to life.
We've got to make sure we
destroy every piece of him now.
Get to work!
I got it under control.
Bummer, I mastermind a
scheme that stops Majin Buu
and I still get stuck with
cleanup duty! Whatta jip!
Just keep blasting!
Right, right.
[grunts]
That does it!
Yep, it's all over.
You did well.
I'm very proud of you.
For a minute there
I'm sure even you
didn't think
you could beat him!
[chuckles]
[grunts]
Aah!
Where's this wind coming from?
A-bove us!
That smoke,
it's coming together!
It's him! Majin Buu! No!
Oh good, he's come
back for some more.
[chuckles]
Uh? This time,
you have any ideas for me?
I've tried everything
and I'm fresh out!
[PICCOLO grunts]
[SUPER BUU chuckles intensely]
[GOTENKS]
Uh-oh. Hey Piccolo,
I don't like that look
he's got in his eyes.
We failed. He's back!
Even blasted into molecules
there was still enough
left of him to re-form!
It's my fault.
I thought that
by luring Majin Buu
into the
Hyperbolic Time Chamber
it would give you the advantage
you'd need to destroy him!
I put too much faith in you.
Gotenks! Can you do
another one of those
Super Ghost Kamikaze
Attacks like the last one?
[GOTENKS thinking]
I've got Piccolo thinking
I'm out of ideas.
Man is he going to be
surprised! I'm so good!
[chuckles]
Go on, do it!
Something's wrong!
I'm trying but
I can't find the power
to do that trick again!
It's no use!
I can't fight anymore!
The world is finished!
[SUPER BUU yells]
Ah! Aaah!
[PICCOLO]
Ah!
[GOTENKS yells, groans]
[GOTENKS groaning]
Let me go... ugly!
Hey, that hurt!
So you wanna play rough,
do ya? You got it!
Ding Ding Ding Ding!
Gotenk's best move has
just arrived out of nowhere!
Let's see you pull yourself
together after this one!
[GOTENKS]
Uh-uhhh.
What's that?
He shot the door! How come?
Now, we're all stuck
in here, for good!
[PICCOLO]
That's right!
The only door
between this dimension
and the outside world
has been destroyed.
We're trapped!
[grunts]
Aah!
Make yourselves at home.
You're indeed stronger
than Gotenks and I
but it doesn't matter now.
Whether you like it
or not Majin Buu,
we'll be spending
the rest of our lives
in this place together.
Uh, Piccolo, we're stuck here?
Yes, of course our friend here
could still try to
get rid of us if he wants.
But, then he'd be all alone.
[NARRATOR]
What has Piccolo done?
Fooled by Gotenks'
childish showmanship,
he has trapped Majin Buu,
Gotenks, and himself in this
strange dimension forever!
Could Gotenks' final technique
truly have saved the day?
Will there ever be
a chance to find out?