[CELL] NOO!!
Haaa!!
[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z...
Goku demonstrated his might by
unleashing a powerful attack
that left Cell's body almost
completely disintegrated.
[NARRATOR]
Unfortunately for our hero,
the resilient Cell
proved once again that
when dealing with him,
"almost" just isn't good enough!
[GOKU gasps]
[NARRATOR] Thanks to the
regenerative powers
that he inherited from Piccolo,
Cell was able to restore his
body and continue the fight!
Cell closed in for the kill,
but Goku
still had more to give.
And in an explosive outburst,
he let loose a furious volley
that stopped the
android in his tracks!
[GOKU shouting]
[NARRATOR] But Goku's
advantage was fleeting,
for with only
a minimum of effort,
Cell was able to
reduce the Super Saiyan's
massive onslaught to a
harmless fireworks display.
[NARRATOR]
The situation was bleak.
Clearly unable to put a dent
in Cell's impenetrable armor,
Goku, the Earth's
last shining hope,
was left with only one option:
[GOKU] You win, Cell! I give up!
[VEGETA gasps]
[NARRATOR] Is this the end
for the Earth?
Has Goku really surrendered to
the diabolical monster?
Find out today.
[GOKU] You win, Cell! I give up!
You know, I wasn't sure
when I came here today
that I'd have what it
takes to beat you.
I know now that I don't.
Fighting you
has shown me
that there's still a lot
I have to work toward.
We may be enemies,
but today you've given
me a valuable opportunity
to learn more about myself,
and for what it's worth,
I thank you.
What's he doing?
He's gone crazy! Cell must've
knocked his screws loose!
[TIEN] Quiet, Yamcha!
I can't hear what he's saying!
[GOKU] It's pointless for us
to continue this fight.
Surely you're joking!
You can't just say "I give up"
and expect to walk away!
Sure I can. You beat me
fair and square. I give up!
[ANNOUNCER]
What's going on over there?
Can you hear what
they're saying?
Yeah, just barely. Sounds
like this guy's giving up!
Figures. A puny
little guy like that?
I'm surprised the little punk
lasted as long as he did.
You said it, Hercule!
You'll show him how
it's done, won't you?
Well, Goku, I hope you fully
appreciate the consequences
of your actions!
Heh...
[CELL] You may quit if you wish,
but if there's
no one left to fight me,
I'm going to reduce this
entire planet to rubble!
[GOKU] Not so fast, Cell!
I may be giving up,
but that doesn't mean
the tournament's over!
There's still one more
person for you to fight!
You're not serious!
[CELL] Who?! One of them?
And exactly which one
of these pitiful specimens
did you have in mind, Goku?
Who, Trunks? Piccolo? Vegeta?
Please, don't waste my time.
[VEGETA growls]
[PICCOLO growls]
[TRUNKS gasps]
[ANNOUNCER] The big moment
has finally arrived!
Mr. Satan versus
Cell, mano a mano!
Champ, now that the man in
orange has thrown in the towel,
you're our only hope!
Give us your thoughts
as you prepare
for this historic battle!
Oooh! Mr. Satan,
what are you going to do?
What is plan, maestro?
[MR. SATAN] Uhh...
Well, the first thing
I'll do is plant my foot up
that green freaks backside!
[PIIZA] Yes!
[MR. SATAN grunts]
Oh no! The champ has collapsed!
Mr. Satan? Are you okay?
It's my stomach! Aaargh!
I-I really wanna fight Cell!
I'm gonna whoop up
on him real good!
I'm gonna cause him bruises
up and down... oh, but the pain!
[MR. SATAN groans]
Hey, don't you worry
about it, Mr. Satan!
I've got some
medicine right here!
Take one of these pills
and that stomach ache
of yours will disappear!
Put those away!
What are you thinking?
Aaaargh! The pain! The pain!
It hurts! It hurts!
I just don't think I can
fight right now! Oww!
[MR. SATAN grunting]
So, you don't mind if I pick
who gets to fight next, do you?
[CELL growls]
You actually intend
to go through with this?!
[thinking] What are
you thinking, Kakarot?
There must be a plan behind
all this... this insanity!
I know it sounds crazy, but
you'll understand soon enough.
The person I'm about to name
is a lot stronger than I am.
So if you enjoyed the
challenge of fighting me, Cell,
you're going to like
this next one even better!
[LIONEL] Now, I think he's
saying something about butter?
Of course, you probably
won't feel that way about it
after he's beaten you.
What's that?
I said, you probably won't feel
that way about it
after he beats you!
A bold statement.
You certainly seem
to have a lot of confidence
in this "mystery
fighter" of yours.
[GOKU] Mm-haa!
[CELL] Well,
I hope for your sake
that your confidence
has not been misplaced.
Now where is he?
Where is this "great
invisible champion"?
[GOKU] Oh, he's here.
He just doesn't know it yet.
[CELL growls]
[CELL] I am losing my
patience, Goku. Say the name!
[GOKU] All right. I will.
[ANNOUNCER] Hey,
what are they saying now?
Cell just told
him to say the name.
Okay...
Let us know who he picks.
[thinking] Uh oh, he's
gonna pick me. I know it!
[MR. SATAN gulps]
Hey, listen...
[PIIZA] Huh?
Would you explain
it to this guy?
I can't fight right now because
I have this stomach ache!
Uh... okay.
[GOKU] All right, guys!
I'm afraid that
I can't win this fight!
I need someone to take over!
That someone is you...
Son.
[GOHAN gasps]
Huh?!
[TRUNKS gasps]
Kakarot!
[thinking] Gohan?!
He's going to get his
own son killed! That fool!
[thinking] He wants me to fight?
But... what can I do?
I mean, if my dad
can't beat Cell,
how can I? It's impossible!
[CHICHI] What?!
Goku, what are you doing?!
That's our little boy!
Oh my goodness!
He's going to make my precious
Gohan fight with that monster!
Oh, Gohan!
[CHICHI growls]
Now, ChiChi, calm down!
[BOTH screaming]
I think... he said he needs
someone to "take an order"?
Maybe they want to take a break
and send out for
something to eat
before he names
the next fighter.
You know, I wouldn't
mind having a bite myself.
You can do it, right?
Me? Fight with... with Cell?
Disappointing...
He promises me a challenge, and
he gives me nothing but a child.
Goku! Stop this! Think
about what you're saying!
Think about what's
going to happen
if you maintain this
course of action!
If Gohan fights with Cell,
he's going to die!
Listen, Gohan has a power
hidden within him that you or I
can't even begin to imagine.
Just think about it.
Don't you realize that he's been
keeping up with the rest of us
ever since he was
just a little boy?
I can remember back
when I was his age,
I wasn't half as
strong as he is!
Hey, Goku, we all know that
Gohan is strong for his age,
but... but fighting Cell?
You're just going
to have to trust me.
I wouldn't be doing this if
I didn't know Gohan could win.
[GOHAN groans]
Look at me, Son.
Tell me something: When Cell
and I were fighting back there,
did you think it was
hard to keep up at all?
I mean, were we ever
moving too fast for you to see?
No. I could see it all.
But that's only
because you and Cell
weren't fighting with
your full power.
I'm sure if you'd been
moving as fast as you could
--then I wouldn't--
--I don't know about Cell, Son,
but I was giving it my all!
You thought I was holding back,
because you were comparing
the energy you sensed
from me to your own!
Is this true, Gohan?
Yes.
[thinking] This is unbelievable!
He's just a child!
How could he be--
It's impossible!
Any day now...
Whaddaya say, Son?
Go out there and win
this one for me, okay?
Then we can all go home.
Okay, Dad. I'll do it.
[PICCOLO growls]
Uhh... Gohan...
[VEGETA growls]
--[CHICHI] Gohan! Darling!
--[OX-KING] Easy! Easy!
[CELL] Hmph!
How absurd!
[ANNOUNCER] Folks,
as you can see,
a young boy
has just appeared!
Perhaps this brave
lad will be the one
to take the monster's order!
Hey, I'm starving!
Have him pick up something
for me, too, will ya?
[PIIZA] Hmm...
[MR. SATAN groans]
What sort of food
will satisfy
this terrifying creature's
dark appetite?!
Will it be Chinese? Perhaps
submarine sandwiches, or pizza?!
Say, dear? Doesn't that
look a lot like ChiChi's son?
It seems like he's some
sort of a delivery boy...
And he used to be
such a nice young man, too,
but just look at him now.
Oh my, he's gone
and dyed his hair
like some sort of
a little hoodlum.
I don't know how
ChiChi puts up with it!
Well, at least he's got a job,
unlike that "karate
bum" father of his.
[OLD WOMAN] Karate Bum
Whippersnapper!
Gohan? What in the world?!
I don't know
about you, Bulma,
but I've got a bad
feeling about this!
Krillin, still got
one of those Senzu Beans?
Let me have one, okay?
Huh? Oh! Oh, sure!
[GOKU] Ahh, thank you!
Hey, Cell... catch!
Hey!
[GOKU] There you go! I think
you're going to need it!
That's a Senzu Bean. Eat it!
Okay, it's official!
You've completely lost it!!
[GOKU] Look, Cell's kind
of worn out right now.
It just wouldn't be fair
if Gohan beats him
when he isn't
at his best, you know?
That... That's Cell up there!
Who really cares
about "being fair"?!
[CELL chuckles]
What a fool. Doesn't he realize?
The only thing he's
managed to do here
is ensure his son's demise.
[CELL chuckles]
Thank you, Goku. I will take
this bean without hesitation!
[CELL laughs]
[CELL] Your overconfidence
has betrayed you!
You will regret
this act soon, indeed!
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL grunts]
[yelling]
Oh no!
[yelling continues]
Wonderful!
Now let's get started!
You guys! We can't let
Gohan go through with this!
No, I'm afraid it's too late
to turn back now, Krillin.
[CELL] So, child...
are you ready?
[GOHAN grunts]
[yelling]
[yelling continues]
[grunting]
[GOHAN yells]
[yelling continues]
[PIROZHKI] I'm not anymore
so sure about this kid!
I think not he is delivery boy!
[KING KAI gasps]
That's Gohan!
I don't believe it! Hmm...
Unless I'm mistaken, he may
be actually stronger than Goku!
This is amazing!
[VEGETA gasps]
[thinking] That's it, Son.
[thinking] Hmm. Perhaps
there is more to this "boy"
than I thought!
[GOHAN] Okay, Cell. I'm ready!
Gohan, I hope you are ready.
You aren't going
to get a second chance.
He's... actually doing this!
How can he expect to be any
sort of a match against Cell?!
Well, perhaps Goku
wasn't entirely bluffing
about his son's strength!
Of course, it was a bit
of an exaggeration to say...
that he was stronger
than me, but, oh well!
Well, I'll give you this:
You certainly are brave!
And loyal, too!
Not many sons are
willing to die fighting
their fathers'
battles, you know.
Your devotion really
is most admirable!
[GOKU] You can do this, Gohan!
[CELL chuckles]
[grunting,
blows landing]
[CELL growls]
[CELL yells]
Good, Son! Keep it up!
Make him come to YOU!
Make him fight on
YOUR terms, not his!
I know you can do it!
This is... too much...
Gohan...
Incredible!
This young lad we
thought to be a delivery boy
has actually begun to fight!
And, amazingly enough,
he's holding his own!
But against a
monster such as Cell,
how long can
a child really last?
[grunting]
[YAMCHA gasps]
[ANDROID 16 growls]
[grunting continues]
You're pretty fast, aren't you?
What do you say we try to
kick things up a notch or two?
[CELL growls,
GOHAN grunts]
[GOHAN whimpers]
[blows landing,
GOHAN grunting]
No, this was a mistake!
Goku! You've... you've
got to help him!
Before it's too late!
[GOHAN grunting]
[blows landing,
GOHAN grunting]
[CHICHI shrieks]
[CHICHI] Gohan, please stop it!
You don't have to do this!
Oh no, no! My baby!
Please! Stop it!
[GOHAN grunting]
[GOHAN groans]
[CELL] Hmm!
[GOHAN grunts]
[CELL chuckles]
[TRUNKS gasps]
He's losing!
Don't you even care? Huh?!
Goku, if you don't do
something right now,
Gohan is gonna die!
[CELL] ♪ Hmm! ♪
[GOHAN growls]
[NARRATOR] Goku has
an unwavering faith
in his son's abilities,
but the rest of the
Z Fighters fear the worst,
and not without good reason!
Gohan's about to begin
round two in a battle
against the most
fearsome villain
ever to terrorize the Earth.
And one thing is certain:
the young Super Saiyan
will need a lot more
than his father's confidence
if he's going to win this fight!
The hopes of an entire planet
rest on the
shoulders of a child!
Can Gohan muster the strength
and courage he'll need
to defeat the deadly android?
Don't miss scenes from
the next exciting episode
of Dragon Ball Z!