[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Trunks pushed his strength
to record-breaking levels.
But the Saiyan's bulky
muscles made him too slow
to land a decent punch.
Giving Cell the advantage.
[NARRATOR] Down but not out,
Trunks got back on his feet and
was ready to go another round,
but Cell had
other plans in mind.
[CELL] How did you
get so strong?
I can't believe you developed
those fighting skills
in such a short time.
If I gave you more time,
could you get stronger?
Maybe! Why do you
want to know?
Because there is going
to be a tournament!
Each member of your
team may challenge me.
I will fight them one-on-one.
It should be very entertaining!
[CELL chuckles]
[NARRATOR] Cell has allowed
the young Saiyan live,
but now he must take part
in a deadly tournament
to decide the course
of the future.
The countdown begins...
today on Dragon Ball Z!
[CELL] This tournament
will be a guaranteed hit.
Everyone will be watching me...
I can't wait to see that
look of panic and fear!
That's it! That's the look!
[CELL laughs]
[TRUNKS growls]
[TRUNKS yells]
[yelling continues]
[TRUNKS grunts]
[KRILLIN] Hey, look down
there! Is that Trunks?
Yeah, that's him.
What's he doing?
Hey, where's Cell? He's not
there! He's gone! Where is he?
Hey, wait for me!
I'm sorry.
[VEGETA] Tell me,
what happened to Cell?
[TRUNKS] I tried to beat him...
I couldn't do it!
It's okay. Take it easy.
What happened here?
[VEGETA] Tell us what
happened... now!
I lost... his power
is much greater than mine!
[VEGETA laughs]
[VEGETA] Of course it is!
Foolish boy, what made you
think you could take on Cell
now that he's complete?
Hey! Trunks saved
your life, Vegeta,
and already his power
level is way beyond--
No, Krillin!
Huh?!
Hmph?
[PICCOLO growls]
[TRUNKS cries]
[BULMA] There, there, now
don't cry, Baby Trunks.
[crying continues]
[BULMA] Hey, what
are you waiting for?!
Trunks needs your help!
He could be hurt or even worse!
What's happening
down there anyway?
[PICCOLO] Don't worry,
Trunks is still alive.
Are you sure?!
Huh? And Cell?
[PICCOLO] I thought Trunks was
going to beat Cell for sure.
His power had grown to
such an incredible level.
Yet, Cell's complete power
was still too much for him.
We must find a way to beat Cell!
Perhaps it's time I entered
the Hyperbolic Time Chamber
for some intensive
training of my own.
[KRILLIN] What?
A Martial Arts Tournament?!
Mm-hmm...
Uh? Are you sure about that?
[thinking] Cell! So he wants to
try and humiliate me again.
[KRILLIN] So... what's the deal?
Who's gonna be in this?
I mean, nobody can beat Cell,
so it won't be much
of a tournament.
[TRUNKS] Yes, you're right...
I thought I could beat him.
I was certain I could
do it, but I failed.
Maybe he is unstoppable...
Wait! Of course!
When Goku and Gohan get out of
the Hyperbolic Time Chamber,
I'll go back in again
and continue my training!
Huh?!
There's no need
for you to do that!
I will be the one who goes
back inside that room...
then I'll beat Cell!
[ANDROID 16] I will also fight.
Let me help... You must!
Huh? You're still alive?!
I need help, please take me
to someone who knows
how to repair me.
[ANDROID 16 grunts]
No! Why should we help you?!
[ANDROID 16] Once my
circuits are restored,
I will fight along side you.
I will, I promise you.
No way! You're a
plague to the Earth
just like all the
other androids!
Why would anyone
want to help your kind?!
Stop!
[KRILLIN] Hang tight, I'll get
you the help you need.
[ANDROID 16 gasps]
No, Krillin!
Hey, it's okay... Relax.
He's gonna be one of the
good guys from now on.
[TRUNKS] He's an android!
Yeah, well he's also a
living being, and I think
he deserves a second chance.
Things don't have to happen
like they did in your
time line, Trunks!
An android may save
the world this time!
Come on. You and I both know
we need all the help we can get!
Thank you...
[thinking] I'm not going to
sit around here and wait for
Kakarot to get out of that room!
I alone have the
strength to beat Cell.
But I must get back
in there and train!
[GOKU grunts]
[GOHAN yells]
[grunting,
blows landing]
[GOKU yells]
[GOHAN grunts]
[grunting,
blows landing]
[BOTH grunt]
[grunting,
blows landing]
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU yells]
[GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN sighs]
I'm sorry.
I'll do better next time.
--[GOHAN] Dad?
--Huh?
Dad, I promise.
You did fine today, Gohan,
you just need a
little rest that's all.
I do? You mean...
you'll wait for me?
Of course. We're in
this together aren't we?
That's right!
We can do it! You and me!
[GOHAN grunts]
[GOKU chuckles]
I think it's about time
to call it a day.
Yeah! I guess so.
Hey, Gohan, listen...
You're gonna make it, son!
Don't give up. You, and me...
we have the ability
to do great things.
Yeah!
[GOKU] Now how 'bout
getting something to eat?
Hah! Sure!
[MRS. BRIEF hums]
Oh?
Hi, Vegeta, how are you?
You're looking good.
Nice of you to visit?
Oh, and I see you
brought a friend with you.
Oh my, you're handsome too.
You think so? Well, thank you.
[KRILLIN] Heads up!
Coming through!
Oh... Hi ma'am... Is Bulma here?
Hi, Krillin!
Yeah, hi! Is, uh...
[DR. BRIEF] Hey, Krillin!
Huh?
[DR. BRIEF] Bulma just called.
She's on her way.
Yep! She'll be here
any minute now.
What? She's not back from Kami's
place yet? Wow, that's strange.
[ROSHI] Hello, down there!
[KRILLIN] Hey, Master Roshi!
You made it!
[ROSHI] Mm-hmm.
Bulma told us to meet her here
at the Capsule Corporation.
So, uh... here we are.
What's this all about, Krillin?
Come on, what's going on?
Where's Gohan?
[KRILLIN gasps]
[KRILLIN] He's still
training at Kami's place.
[CHICHI sighs]
Great...
[DR. BRIEF] Let's see... Hmm...
Mm-hmm... Hmm...
Ah! Now, let's put that there...
Hm? Ahhh...
Uh-Oh! That doesn't look right!
For real? He wants a tournament?
That's what Cell said.
He told me to watch the
television for details.
Can anyone who wants
enter the competition?
[TRUNKS] He'll take on anyone
who challenges him...
and he expects to have a battle
with each of us. One-by-one.
Of course, you know what
he's trying to do? I do.
His plan is to eliminate the
competition once and for all.
Well, I kinda like the idea of
another Martial Arts Tournament.
I mean, hey...
I think I'll dominate!
Yeah, let's get 'em!
Yeah!
Just make sure you
don't get another hand
through your stomach!
[BOTH groan]
[MRS. BRIEF] There ya go!
[MRS. BRIEF giggles]
Hold on... now wasn't there a
martial arts tournament
a long time ago?
That's correct... ahh, yes,
I believe I'll explain since I
once won the tournament myself.
--[VEGETA] Hmph!
--[PUAR] What? Master Roshi?
I never knew you won it!
Oh, you just had
to get him started!
[ROSHI coughs]
Alright, I'm sure
you've all heard of the
World Martial Arts Tournament.
It was a contest held to decide
the world's greatest fighter.
Masters of the
Martial Arts gathered
from all over the world to
take place in the competition.
I believe Goku first appeared
in the 21st tournament.
And went all the way
to the final round.
However, his last
opponent was Jackie Chun,
an unbeaten master who proved
Goku still had a lot to learn.
Five years later,
the 22nd World Martial
Arts Tournament was held.
That's where Goku met
Tien and Chiaotzu.
It was Goku and Tien
in the final round
and it was a doozy of a battle.
They both gave it
everything they had,
but neither could
out do the other.
Goku narrowly missed
becoming the champion...
and they had to call it a draw.
Ha! That's not much
of a competition...
Now I know why
Kakarot got involved
in such an easy tournament.
[KRILLIN &amp; YAMCHA growl]
No... It's not that the
competition was easy...
There were just factors involved
that made it more difficult.
You know, love has a way
of throwing everything
out of perspective.
By the time the 23rd
tournament came around,
Goku had married ChiChi.
Piccolo was on the scene
and showed some moves
that were really
out of this world.
This was a competition
that separated the
tough guys from the wimps.
Goku made it to the finals, but
not before facing some of his
fiercest opponents.
Toughest of all was Piccolo.
Those two fought with everything
they had and it looked like
Piccolo would claim the title
of the world's greatest fighter.
But anyone who knows Goku, knows
you can never count him out...
even when things
look their bleakest.
The result of their battle left
the tournament rink destroyed
and the surrounding area
in a shambles.
That's why there hasn't been a
World Martial Arts
Tournament since.
In the end, when all was said
and done, Goku was declared
the strongest fighter
on the Earth!
10... 12... how many years
ago was that, Krillin?
Quite a few! Heh!
[DR. BRIEF slurps]
[DR. BRIEF] Interesting story...
Might make a good movie!
[DR. BRIEF slrurps]
[ROSHI sighs]
[CROWS cawwing]
But why would Cell
host a tournament?
Yeah, why? I mean, if he
wants to rule the world
why's he wasting time
with this competition?
Cell doesn't want to rule the
world, he wants to destroy it.
--[YAMCHA gasps]
--[CHIAOTZU] Huh?
The androids have never
been interested in power.
It's just that
they find pleasure
in causing fear and chaos.
And Cell's no different, he's
using this stupid tournament
as a way to spread fear!
[KRILLIN] Boy,
he's got some nerve!
Don't worry, Krillin.
This time we'll knock the wind
out that windbag for good!
[CHIAOTZU] Right!
[VEGETA laughs]
Oh, stop deluding yourselves!
Cell will make short work
out of every one of you.
[YAMCHA growls]
[CHICHI] Well, I for
one am very relieved.
Hey, what's she talking about?
What am I, psychic?!
Don't you understand?
If it's a tournament,
it will have to have rules
that even Cell
must follow, right?
Huh?
[CHICHI] And everyone knows that
in a Martial Arts Tournament
killing is not allowed!
Yeah!
Heh! Well, I have to admit,
she's gotta point!
In that case, I'm in!
[OOLONG gags]
Would ya stop tryin' to
relive your glorious past?!
It's pathetic--
My head!
[TRUNKS] Cell wants to test the
limits of his complete body.
He's uncertain about
the Super Saiyans,
and we must use that
to our advantage.
My father, Goku, Gohan, and I
must all try hard
to surprise him.
[KRILLIN] Yeah!
Throw 'im a curve!
Hold it right there!
[ALL gasp]
I have accepted the fact that
Goku will be fighting
in the tournament...
But I refuse to let
Gohan take part in it!
[KRILLIN] But ChiChi,
you said yourself
that killing wouldn't be aloud!
So what's the big deal?
[CHICHI] I do not want Gohan
entering that tournament!
He is not going to be a
fighter like his father!
We need him...
Goku and I have already
talked about this.
We made a deal.
Gohan can go and train,
but when he gets back
he's going to have to
buckle down and hit the books.
[KRILLIN] Aw, but ChiChi we
really could use his help!
I've made up my mind about this
and I'm not going to change it!
When Gohan was born, Goku and
I both agreed on his future.
His bottle is ready...
[GOKU] He sure eats
a lot, doesn't he?
[GOKU chuckles]
[GOKU] Lunch time, kiddo.
[GOHAN babbles]
Gohan, someday you'll grow
up to be a great scholar.
A scholar?!
Goku, there's no reason
for him to have to fight...
If we raise him to be
a scholar, then he'll really
be able to help people.
I guess so...
Guess I'll have to take
back those training weights...
So there! Gohan will
have to start his studies
right when he gets back...
And he will not be joining
up with your little gang!
Our gang?!
What gang?
Hey! Can I join?
[ROSHI chuckles]
[GOKU snores]
[birds chirping]
Perfect. This looks
like an ideal spot.
Now, to build a ring.
[sighing]
Now, let's see...
I'll have to clear some
of this land away first.
Perfect.
Ah... I like it...
It will make a strong floor.
Yes... This will do just fine...
It looks large enough.
It's time, to get the word out.
[NARRATOR} The stage
has been set.
The tournament
is about to begin.
Soon the Z Warriors
will learn where the next
World Martial Arts
Tournament will be held...
Are they ready to take on an
monster like Cell one-by-one?
Will Cell play by the rules?
Will there be any rules?!
Find out next time!