[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball Z,
the evil Frieza had Gohan
in the palm of his hand.
But Krillin wasn't about
to take this lying down.
Cutting off Frieza's tail
with his Destructo Disk attack,
Krillin escaped using
the Solar Flare technique.
[NARRATOR] Even so,
as the Earthlings gathered
to launch their assult
against Frieza,
their odds didn't look good.
[NARRATOR] Will Gohan and
his gang's combined power
be enough to topple
the tyrannical Frieza?
Or can Piccolo's new persona
take Frieza on all by himself?
Find out Frieza's fate today!
Stand back, kid. I'll
take care of him myself.
What?!
No way! I know he's strong,
but I'm just not sure he can
really do it all by himself!
[thinking] Piccolo?
I can sense Piccolo's power has
increased since he's left here.
I wonder how that
happened to him?
Wait a second. Are
you saying you think
he's strong enough now to
actually defeat Frieza?
[KING KAI] No!
I'm just saying that for some
strange reason he's stronger,
but he's still no
match for Frieza.
If Piccolo fails then we'll
have to remain here forever.
I knew he'd botch this up!
If only I were there,
I'd take Frieza out myself.
[YAMCHA growls]
Yamcha, have a little
more faith in Piccolo.
He'll come through for us...
I just hope you're
right about that!
Call me crazy, but I
got a funny feeling
that Piccolo doesn't have a
clue what he's up against.
Someone should tell HIM that.
I can't put my finger on it,
but I sense something
different about Piccolo.
What the heck are you
talking about, Gohan?
The Piccolo I know
would never fight
unless he felt for
sure he could win.
You think he has a chance?
Would you two cut the crap?!
There's nothing different
about your stupid green friend
and there's no way he can
win against Frieza, alright?!
B-Bu.. But Piccolo
said that...
[thinking] Piccolo is back! And
his power is stronger than ever!
I just hope he's strong enough.
This is just too weird!
I can't seem to put my
finger on what it is
but there's something about
Piccolo that reminds me of Nail.
Hmph.
So you think you're
pretty tough, huh?
Well, it won't take me long to
have you face first in the dirt
begging for mercy!
Give it a try.
[PICCOLO roars]
[grunting]
[ALL grunting]
Come back here!
Huh?!
Piccolo won!
I can't believe my eyes!
[thinking] Oh, these
idiots actually believe
Frieza's finished.
Well, I'm no fool! He'll
be back! Mark my words.
[KRILLIN laughs]
[thinking] What a moron.
[PICCOLO yells]
[grunting]
[GOHAN screams]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[FRIEZA] Well, who's next?
Or should I just come down
and pick one of you at random?
Ahh! He's alive!
You surprise me, my friend.
I thought our time together
had come to an end.
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[PICCOLO growls]
Vegeta!
Hmm...?
[VEGETA gasps]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
Excuse me, Vegeta,
but I really hate it
when someone leaves
and doesn't say goodbye.
[FRIEZA laughs]
No... No!
[VEGETA gasps]
[FRIEZA] You are quite
the comedian, Vegeta.
If only the rest of
your Saiyan people
were around to see the brave
Prince Vegeta now, huh? But...
[FRIEZA laughs]
That really doesn't matter
because I've got you cornered
like a frightened little mouse!
Oh, don't worry, dear Prince.
I'm going to save you until
I've taken care of your
little Namek friend.
[VEGETA whimpers]
[VEGETA grunts]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[FRIEZA] Pardon me
for the intrusion,
but I just had to take
care of something.
Time to wipe that
smug look off your face.
[PICCOLO growls]
[grunting]
It's amazing!
For a guy that I thought was
a goner five minutes ago,
he's sure hanging
in there, huh Gohan?
There's something
strange about him...
Do you think he can take Frieza?
Yes!
[DENDE screams]
[DENDE gasps]
It's him! It's Nail!
[PICCOLO grunts]
Huh?!
Any sign of Piccolo?
[FRIEZA chuckles]
Piccolo!
[FRIEZA] Aw, don't look so sad.
Your green friend is just fine.
And to prove it, I'll
bring him up for you.
Well, maybe I exaggerated
about the "just fine" part,
but hey, who's
keeping score anyway?
Are you okay, Piccolo?!
[BOTH whimper]
Well that takes care of your
lime-colored little comrade.
[FRIEZA gasps]
What?!
Piccolo!
You underestimated my power!
You know what? We might
even stand a chance, Gohan!
I think you're right!
It's just like Vegeta said, all
we have to do is fight as one.
Now let's go for it!
[PICCOLO] You two stay put!
[BOTH gasp]
[PICCOLO] Didn't I say
I'd take care of Frieza?
[GOHAN] B-But Piccolo?
[KRILLIN] You'll never
beat him alone!
Don't argue with me.
He's even a bigger fool than I
if he really believes he
can take on Frieza by himself.
But then again, I'm not that
stupid to tell him not to try.
You disgust me.
Well, I'm sure you're wondering
how I can anticipate your
every move. Right, Horn Boy?
Huh?!
[FRIEZA] What'd you call me?!
[PICCOLO laughs]
[FRIEZA growls]
[KING KAI] Ahhh,
who's going to win?!
Piccolo!
Piccolo...
[thinking] Strange! Piccolo
seems to have the upper hand.
What's going on?!
[NAIL] Is that the best you can
do against me? Huh, Frieza?
Huh?!
That voice...
Today, I will fight you while
my other hand is behind my back.
[NAIL growls]
[NAIL] Raaah!
[FRIEZA giggles]
[NAIL grunts]
[NAIL] Raaah!
[NAIL gasps]
My dear friend, you
really are quite stubborn.
It doesn't make any
difference to me.
One way or another,
I will get that password!
[NAIL grunts]
[groaning]
[FRIEZA] So, just to make myself
clear, that was my last warning.
Now, divulge what I want,
or you won't ever get up again!
[NAIL] Piccolo and I
are of one body.
What?!
It's just like I thought!
[PICCOLO] And with our
combined strength, you Frieza,
are no match for our us.
I know how strong
he is. I fought him...
If we unite, you'll
be much stronger...
If we don't use every scrap of
what we have to fight him,
then we're done for...
Yeah, right. I doubt that.
[NAIL] You're one of us.
We have to work together...
Frieza's just too strong.
I'm not trying to
trick you, brother.
Please! All I'm doing is
trying to help you out...
[PICCOLO] Why not? Alright.
[PICCOLO grunting]
[grunting continues]
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
I can do this! I can win,
I feel great! Aah! Yes! Yes!
[PICCOLO growls]
[PICCOLO laughs]
[FRIEZA whimpers]
[GOHAN whimpers]
Oh boy...
I-I don't believe this!
Now that I have
gained ultimate power,
it's time to finish off
this little game.
[PICCOLO growls]
[FRIEZA grunts]
[PICCOLO shouts]
[FRIEZA yells]
[YELLING continues]
[FRIEZA roars]
Huh? What's happening? Piccolo!
Piccolo, no!
No! You can't!
[PICCOLO growls]
[PICCOLO yells]
[yelling continues]
[PICCOLO roars]
[FRIEZA whimpers]
[PICCOLO shouts]
[FRIEZA screams]
He did it...
[FRIEZA growls]
[FRIEZA] You're dead!
[growling continues]
[NARRATOR] Even with
their combined strength,
Piccolo and Nail still
can't defeat Frieza.
It looks like there's only
one hope left for our heroes.
Can Goku make it in time?
Find out on the
next Dragon Ball Z!