[NARRATOR] Previously
on Dragon Ball Z,
As the new guardian
of the Earth,
Dende quickly
created a new Dragon,
and thus brought back
the shining powers
of the Dragon Balls.
[NARRATOR] As a result,
our heroes could bring back
all the people killed by Cell,
but first, Goku had
to zap around the world
to collect all seven.
[NARRATOR] And after a
troublesome run-in with
a goofy gangster
and his hired killer,
the robotically
enhanced General Tao,
Goku's journey
was almost complete.
He'd gathered up six
of the seven Dragon Balls
and was on his
way to find the last.
[VODKA] Yeah, go right ahead.
Hey, alright! I've got
all seven Dragon Balls!
[TRUNKS yells]
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
back at Kami's lookout,
a handful of the other
fighters were spending
their last few moments
in preparation.
Trunks continued
to train his body,
while, much to
Krillin's astonishment,
Gohan and Dende chose
instead to train their minds
with homework!
[ALL laugh]
[NARRATOR] But time
is quickly running out.
Cell has been
waiting days on end
for his Martial Arts Tournament.
And it begins
in less than one hour!
Well, I better go...
[BOTH sigh]
Be careful out there, Goku!
Come back safely...
Hey, don't worry.
Promise me Gohan
will not fight!
Ahh... Well...
Goku, you have to promise me
that Gohan won't get involved!
I gotta run...
[CHICHI] Goku, wait!
Oh no... he wouldn't even
promise me. And that means--!
[CHICHI gasps]
D-Dad!
[KRILLIN] Alright!
Today's the day.
Huh...?
Where's Vegeta?
He went on ahead.
I see. He must be pumped up
from all his training.
So, what level's he at?
Hey, guys, what's
with the silent treatment?
Uhh, anybody wanna explain?
Goku, we seem to have
a bit of a snag here.
It's about the dragon...
See, Dende made it so that
all the people killed by Cell
could be brought
back with one wish.
Yeah...
But unlike on Namek,
this dragon can't restore life
to anyone who's died before...
I'm sorry. I should have told
that you before I made it, Goku.
Don't worry,
nothing's gonna happen!
He's not gonna beat us, guys!
[KRILLIN] Hel-lo?!
We're fighting Cell here!
Hey, just take it easy!
Now, let's hurry up
or we're gonna be late.
[thinking] Ahhh, Goku, the day
of judgment is at last at hand.
Here we are just
twenty minutes away
from the start of
the Cell games!
And by the looks of it,
no one seemed to show up
to watch for fear
of their lives!
As you can see,
Cell continues to stand
in the middle of the ring
without moving a muscle!
And with not a lot of time
left until the opening bell,
we're still awaiting the arrival
of the people's grand champion!
The one and only Hercule Satan!
[ANNOUNCER] Wait a minute...
Yes! Someone's coming!
[brakes screeching]
[ANNOUNCER] Ladies
and gentlemen!
Mr. Satan is here!
Yeah!
[ANNOUNCER] So put your hands
together for Mr. Satan!
[CROWD cheering]
[ANNOUNCER] Mr. Satan is now
making his way to the ring.
[MR. SATAN] You're going down!
Whoaaa!
Ladies and gentlemen,
the tournament's about to begin!
And Mr. Satan is already
declaring his victory!
But wait, folks,
even with the world's strongest
man about to challenge him,
Cell remains as calm
as a cucumber!
Well then, let's begin.
So, it looks like Cell's anxious
to get the show on the road,
and so are we!
Ladies and Gentleman,
let the Ultimate Games begin!
[ANNOUNCER] The hopes and
dreams of the entire planet
rest on the shoulders
of Hercule Satan,
but between you and me, we don't
have a thing to worry about.
[ANNOUNCER] Mr. Satan is now
making his way toward Cell.
But the champ appears
to be taking his sweet time!
And from my
vantage point, folks,
you can cut the
tension with a knife!
[ANNOUNCER] Wait a minute!
Huh? Wh-What's he doing?
He wants US to come down there?
[MR. SATAN] Mm-hmm.
Yes, well... ahh... sure. Huh?
Okay, we're coming!
Just hang on!
I don't think I have a choice!
This just might be my last
broadcast, ladies and gentlemen,
but being a true professional,
it's my duty to you
my viewing audience!
[ANNOUNCER] Oh my...
On a personal note,
just in case this is
the last event I ever cover,
I'd like to thank each
and everyone of my loyal viewers
for the cards and letters you've
sent to me over my years at ZTV.
[ANNOUNCER chuckles nervously]
So, ah, I suppose
I should thank you
for the ringside
seats, M-Mr. Satan.
C'mon up here, and quickly!
[ANNOUNCER] Sure,
what ever you say!
So, uh, a-are you ready
for the fight, Mr. Satan?
Any last remarks?
I'd like to give
Cell my condolences.
It's too bad my unworthy
opponent didn't know
that I existed before he
started this tournament of his!
Anything else?
I'll give him one
last chance to back out.
He might think he's a champ,
but he's just a chump!
[CROWD cheers]
Listen up, you bum!
You are going down
in the first round!
I know you beat the
Royal Military
by planting bombs beforehand!
I know all your stupid parlor
tricks and I'm not impressed!
I can't believe
he won't respond!
[MR. SATAN chuckles]
He's just upset
I know his weaknesses!
[ANNOUNCER laughs]
Hey, Cell, get a
load of this one!
[ANNOUNCER laughs]
[MR. SATAN laughs]
You can kiss my butt!
[CROWD cheers]
[ROSHI] You know, it might
be fair if he gets killed.
Huh...? Ha-ha!
Hey, look, guys,
it's Yamcha and Tien!
We'll come with you,
but we want you to know
that we're not going to fight.
Sure. Now let's go.
[MR. SATAN raspberries]
[laughing]
You're a little thick,
aren't you there?!
[MR. SATAN laughs]
Sucker!
[laughing continues]
And another verbal jab! The
fight hasn't even started yet!
And in this announcer's
humble opinion,
it seems Mr. Satan
is already winning!
[ANNOUNCER] Huh?
[ANNOUNCER] What the...?
What is that?
What are you talking about?
[ANNOUNCER] What do you
think it could be?
[thinking] Ahh... Vegeta...
I thought you would
have learned by now.
I hope for his sake
he's powerd up.
[ANNOUNCER] It appears that
we have another visitor,
but I don't recognize him.
He just came flying
in here unexpectedly.
One of Cell's tricks!
I'm not sure what
he's doing here,
so why don't we
go up and ask him?
So, who are you and
what are you doing here?
And if you've
just come to watch,
back away from the ring
before you get hurt!
Quiet! I've had enough
of your insolence!
--Huh?!
--Get out of my face!
[ANNOUNCER laughs]
If you ask me,
that guy's totally nuts!
Have any thoughts, champ?
Ahhhhhh... He's probably
just one of my fanatical fans.
[ANNOUNCER growls]
[ANNOUNCER] Ladies
and gentlemen,
according to my watch,
we're just five minutes away
from the start of the Cell Games
that will decide
the fate of the Earth!
As I predicted, Mr. Satan
is the only challenger
to step forward
to take on Cell!
But then again, what
more do we really need
when we have the World Champion
of Martial Arts on our side!
Coming up, it's the
fight of the century!
Huh?
Hm?!
Wh... Where are
they all coming from?
Ahh... it's another
one of those tricks!
Well, what a surprise...
Android 16.
You're still alive and kicking,
and with beautiful
repairs, no less!
[thinking] Bulma and her
father made that android
just as powerful as before!
What idiots! Why
did they even bother?
Cell just said something
to the red-haired guy!
Do you think that those
two know each other?
Who cares?!
You can tell by
his outfit he's a nobody!
Hmm?
[CELL chuckles]
Ah, there you are, Goku.
And just in time!
I can hardly wait...
Keep. It. Rolling...
[MR. SATAN] Wha...?!
Goku, down there!
Let's do it.
[CROWD gasping,
murmuring]
W-Who are those guys?
They're gonna get in
Mr. Satan's way!
[CHICHI] Gohan,
my darling, nooo!
My precious, little baby!
Get out of there!
Please, you've
got to get out of there!
[OX-KING] ChiChi, calm down!
There's nothing you
can do for him now!
[CHICHI] You've got to help
me get him out of there!
Please, before my
little pumpkin gets hurt!
My precious, little Gohan,
listen to your mommy and run!
Welcome, welcome, everyone!
[thinking] Why did they
have to come?!
But how... how is it physically
possible for all of them to fly?
I-I guess that trick's
very... popular today!
Huh...? Huh?!
Android 16! Hey, you're back!
Yes, and thank you.
Because of your help,
I am at last fully
functional again.
[KRILLIN chuckles]
Aw, shucks. You're welcome.
My name's Goku.
I know your name.
I was created solely to destroy
you. Though I've chosen not to.
Get a load of Mr. Personality...
[ANNOUNCER] Ladies
and gentlemen,
I'm not sure what to
make of all these newcomers!
I must say it's
verrry intriguing!
Hey, don't forget about me.
Excuse me, have
the games started?
Not yet, but almost...
Okay then!
[bones popping]
Let's get this thing going.
And if you want, I'll be first!
Goku, you don't have to
be the first one to fight!
What d'ya say, Vegeta?
Be my guest.
We all know it will be me
who ends up finishing off Cell.
[MR. SATAN stammers]
Hey, don't you know
I'm the Champ around here?!
Ah, excuse me, sir,
but I was just wondering
if you or your friends
were going to take
part in the tournament?
Of course, I'll be going first.
[MR. SATAN growls]
I've had about enough of you
clowns and your stupid jokes!
Now clear outta here
before I get angry!
Hey, don't blow
a vein you grease ball.
[MR. SATAN gasps]
[chuckling]
I'm sorry, I forgot.
You ignorant hicks have
spent your whole lives playing
banjo in the woods,
so you don't realize that I,
Hercule Satan, am the MARTIAL
ARTS CHAMPION OF THE WORLD!
And the other challengers have
been left totally speechless,
by the one and only...
MARTIAL ARTS CHAMPIONS
OF THE... whuh?
Okay, seeing as you don't
know who I am, I'll show you.
[MR. SATAN growls]
[yelling]
[MR. SATAN yells]
[growling]
Now who rules?
Champion of all Martial Arts
in the World, Mr. Satan!
Mr. Satan! Mr. Satan!
Mr.-- Uh?!
They... They aren't
buying it at all.
I say... we let the
Neanderthal nerd ball go first.
You... think we should?
It's time!
[NARRATOR] The buzzer
has sounded,
and the time for waiting
has come to a close!
But who will be victorious?
Will it be our hero,
the strangely confident Goku?
Or has Vegeta finally
become the strongest of all?
There's always Piccolo now
that he's reuinited with Kami.
[NARRATOR] Will Yamcha
and Tien decide to fight?
Or could Trunks fulfill his
goal to save the future?
Don't forget Gohan and Krillin.
The biggest battle ever in the
history of Dragon Ball Z
is about to begin,
so don't miss the
next exciting episode.
Non-stop action is guaranteed.
And yet, the question remains:
Will our heroes come out on top
and destroy the mighty Cell?
Or will it be the end of the
Earth as we know it?
The pressure is on Goku and the
Z Fighters to save mankind.