[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z...
Dende used the newly
remodeled Dragon Balls
to summon a new and
improved Eternal Dragon!
The scaley, green
titan now had the power
to grant two
wishes instead of one!
It was a bargain
for ball gatherers
that couldn't be refused!
And while Earth's Special
Forces were seeking
to restore life above,
a shameless opportunist
was taking all the credit
for their victory, down below!
What a bunch of suckers!
And what a turkey!
[MR. SATAN]
Who loves me?!
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, the wish
to restore Cell's victims
back to life was granted
and the others realized
that a special trip
to see Porunga could
bring Goku back as well!
But he had other plans!
[GOKU]
Hey, don't I get a say in this?
As a Saiyan baby, I was
sent to Earth to destroy it.
And unfortunately,
it's kinda like
I've been fulfilling
that mission all along.
So I'm gonna stay here now.
I don't really mind.
King Kai says I can
get special treatment
'cause I saved
the Earth and all.
I'll be able to keep my body,
and from what I hear
there's lots of
interesting people to meet!
It'll be fun!
I guess what I'm
trying to say is...
I appreciate your
feelings towards me,
but you'll have to find
something else to wish for.
This is my home now.
Dad!
[GOKU] You all better
take notes of everything
that happens in your life,
'cause when they're through,
I'll want to hear all about 'em!
Until then, bye!
Huh?
[NARRATOR]
And so their beloved Goku,
who had been both
savior and friend,
decided to continue his life
beyond the mysterious
frontier known as death!
But those who know Goku,
know that he will be watching!
Always and forever!
[DRAGON]
You have one wish remaining!
One wish!
Make it!
It is time!
[GOHAN]
Gosh! What d'ya say, guys?
Can anyone think of a good wish?
[MR. POPO] I can never
think of a good wish
when the Dragon is here!
[TIEN]
Me either!
[PICCOLO]
I'm kind of at a loss myself!
The wish!
[YAMCHA laughs]
If we can't think of a
good wish, what about a bad one?
I mean wouldn't it be cool
if we were all filthy rich?
Well, guys?
[PICCOLO growls]
[DRAGON]
I'll wait no longer!
Do you have a wish, or not?
Yes! I do!
I'd like you to change Androids
17 and 18 into human beings,
so that they can live
their lives in peace!
[GOHAN]
Gosh, Krillin!
That wish can not
be granted now!
[DRAGON]
It is beyond my power to do so!
[ANDROID 18]
What's he doing?!
[KRILLIN]
Sorry, guys! I had to try!
Hey, look! No prob!
The girl's cool!
But her boyfriend!
I'd never wish that guy back!
Would you guys?
Sure! Haven't we already tried?
We wished all of
Cell's victims back, right?
And he was one of them!
Besides what would Goku do
if he were in our shoes?
[YAMCHA]
Right! I see what you mean!
Hey, you've got the floor, bro!
Great! I have one more wish!
Could you take the explosives
out of the Androids' bodies?
That shouldn't
be too hard, right?
Man! Krillin!
[YAMCHA] I hope you know
what you're doing!
I can!
Alright!
[GOHAN]
Krillin...
There! It has been done!
Thanks! Thanks very much!
You're welcome! I must go now!
[KRILLIN]
Wow! Beautiful!
Man! Listen to that!
What's the deal?
Why are you so bent
on helping those two?
Well, I guess,
I guess, it's that...
I guess, it's that
I like that girl, guys!
Gosh! You dog!
You really like her!
[KRILLIN] Doctor Gero's the one
that made her into an Android!
She hasn't done anything wrong!
Yamcha, sorry about earlier!
[YAMCHA]
Huh?
I didn't mean to hog the wish!
It wasn't fair! You had one too!
Oh my gosh!
You didn't know I was
just kidding about that?!
Hey! Come on, guys!
You didn't really think
I was gonna ask the
Dragon for money, did you?
Man! Gimme a break!
[YAMCHA]
What a buncha kooks!
Me, ask the Dragon for money!
That's a good one!
Gosh! They're nice!
[TIEN]
Hey! You like the girl, right?
So what's up? Why did you
wanna wish that guy back, too?
Well, I know it's strange!
But I want her
to be truly happy!
And those two make
such a good couple
that I thought she'd
be happier with him!
Well, that's why!
[YAMCHA]
Dude! You're hopeless!
[ALL laugh]
If that's what you humans
call love, count me out!
[ANDROID 18]
Hello?!
[GROUP]
Huh?
Oh, wow! There she is!
How'd she get here?
Hey! Bonehead! 17 is
my twin brother!
Oh, man!
No! This is excellent, you dope!
Didn't you hear her?
That guy's her twin brother!
I wouldn't celebrate
if I were you!
If you think you
won my heart
because of that lousy
wish, you're mistaken!
I didn't ask for your help!
[ANDROID 18]
But it was really nice of you.
It was? Y-You mean,
you're not mad at me?
[ANDROID 18]
Not really, no.
[KRILLIN] Well, then, would you
like to come over and join us?
No thanks!
[KRILLIN]
Aw, man!
Whoa! Krillin!
You are so in there!
That chick digs you,
man, I can tell!
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure!
But she's a woman, dude!
Oh man!
Like I say, she's a girl
and there's no tellin',
but I think you have a chance!
[YAMCHA] Stick close to my
advice and you'll do just fine!
After all, Krillin!
It's my specialty!
Trust me! Goku may have taught
you how to be a great fighter,
but when it comes
to love, I'm the master!
[YAMCHA &amp; GOHAN laugh]
There's no comparison!
[YAMCHA]
I heard that!
At least you're man enough
to admit it, Piccolo!
Fighting's relatively easy!
[GROUP laughing]
Man! I really
wish Goku was here!
Nobody could let go
and laugh like he could!
[YAMCHA]
Yeah! No kidding!
Celebrating just isn't
the same without Goku!
Let's not be sad!
That's not what
Goku was all about!
I guess you're right, Tien!
Of course! Well, look guys,
I need to be heading that way!
Peace, huh? May it last!
[YAMCHA]
Hey, take care of yourself, bro!
Goodbye, Tien!
Tell Chiaotzu I said hi!
Yeah, sure! And guess what?
You're the man
of the house now, Gohan!
So take good care
of your mom, alright?
Hey, Trunks!
Go show those two Androids what
you're really made of, alright?
If you need help,
we'll be here! Always!
Thanks! You don't know how good
it makes me feel to hear that!
See ya!
Bye, Tien!
[YAMCHA] Well, guys,
I guess it's about that time!
[KRILLIN] Yeah, Yamcha, I guess
we oughta be going now!
What's your plan, Trunks?
Are you goin' back right away?
Nah! I'm gonna get a good rest!
I'll head out in the morning!
Great! We'll see you off, okay?
Cool!
What now, Piccolo? Are you
planning on living up here?
Yeah! I think so!
Then I'll come visit,
if it's alright with you!
You know it is!
I wouldn't miss
it for the world, kid!
[DENDE] Yeah, don't be
a stranger, Gohan!
I'm counting on you to visit!
[GOHAN]
Gosh, Dende!
It can be lonely at the top!
[GOHAN]
Aw! You're gonna love it here!
Mister Popo's the greatest!
Well, I guess this is it, guys!
Here we go!
This is the beginning
of the rest of our lives!
Bye, guys!
[POPO]
Goodbye, everyone!
[GOHAN]
There's Korin's place!
Hey!
Trunks, get some good
rest before your trip!
Well, we'll see
you guys tomorrow morning!
It's been great!
Bye!
[TRUNKS] My Father
did that? Are you sure?
Yeah! He went ballistic!
When he saw you get killed,
he went bonkers!
He attacked Cell like I've
never seen him attack before!
[TRUNKS]
You've gotta be kidding!
I'll be darned!
[YAMCHA]
See ya later, Trunks!
[TRUNKS]
Adios!
[GOHAN]
And that's the whole story, Mom!
[CHICHI sobbing]
I'm sorry, Mom!
So, he didn't wanna come back?
What an amazing man he is!
Isn't that just like him?
Please, Mom! Don't be sad!
This is the way
he really wanted it!
He told me so himself!
Besides, I can feel him,
Mom! He's there!
ChiChi, Gohan's right, honey.
Yeah! Since Goku
chose to stay there!
I'm fine about it!
Goku's always known what's
best for everybody! Always!
[BULMA]
I'm really proud of you, Son!
[TRUNKS]
Thanks, Mom!
Be careful!
Right!
[TRUNKS]
Dad.
So long!
Love ya Trunks, goodbye!
[GOHAN] Bye, Trunks!
You're the greatest!
[TRUNKS]
Goodbye, Gohan!
Later, Dude!
Bye, Trunks!
[TRUNKS]
See ya, guys!
Huh?
Father!
[KRILLIN]
Hm?
[CHICHI] Gohan!
It's time to take a break!
Gohan? Hey!
Open up! I have
a snack for you!
Oh, no! What am I going
to do with that young man?
I'll bet my Father is in on
this little escapade as well!
[CHICHI] Honestly!
Escaping through the window!
How juvenile can they get?
It won't last!
They'll come crawling back
right around dinner time! Mm-hm!
[GOHAN]
Gosh, it's such a great day!
And I don't feel as guilty
sneaking out with you, Grandpa!
Yeah, it's nice to sneak
out with your Grandpa
because you don't
get in trouble!
At least you won't! I'm dead!
Poor, Grandpa!
[OX-KING] Ahh, well!
Somebody's gotta take the fall!
[GOHAN]
Thanks!
[OX-KING] Ahh! Fresh air,
sunshine-- this is the life!
[GOHAN]
Yeah!
[GOHAN] Have you ever
lived in the city, Grandpa?
[OX-KING] Me? Oh, no! I don't
think I could stand it!
It's too crowded in the city!
A guy my size
needs plenty of space!
Yeah!
Come on!
Where are you going?
I'll show ya, Grandpa.
It's right over here!
[OX-KING]
Gohan, it's almost dinner time!
Where are you going?
[GOHAN] To a place my dad
used to take me. Follow me!
[OX-KING] Oh, man. I'm gonna
be in so much trouble
and I'm hungry.
Gohan? Gohan?
Where'd he go?
Grandpa! See this?
[OX-KING]
That a boy! Bring him on up!
We'll take him home with us!
[OX-KING]
Huh?
Goodness! That's one
whopper of a fish!
Your dad would be proud
of you for that one!
Gohan! Look out!
You want this, don't you?
Well, you'll have to
fight me for it! I'm hungry!
You're serious! Aren't you?
Look, I'll share this with you,
but only if you behave!
Do we have a deal?
Man! What a feisty, old bird!
Yeah, what an unlucky bird!
First, he runs into the
strongest guy in the world
in the middle of nowhere,
and then he tries
to take his fish!
[BULMA] Look, Mom!
Look, Dad! He's doing it!
I can't believe it!
[MRS. BRIEF]
Oh, my goodness!
Yay! What a little champion!
[BULMA]
That's it!
[MRS. BRIEF] Come here,
you poor baby! Goodness! Uhh?
What a stubborn little guy!
I don't think he gets
that from our side!
You're a tough guy
like your daddy, aren't you?
Well, come on! Let's see it!
Get up! You can do it, Trunks!
Now turn into a Super Saiyan!
[MRS. BRIEF] Isn't it a little
too early for that, Dear?
Hello! Welcome, folks!
Without further delay,
it's time to begin our special!
Whoo! And now,
ladies and gentlemen,
the hosts of our show,
Burt and Lana Yakamoori!
Come on! Let's hear it!
Give it up! Give it up
for Burt and Lana!
[ANNOUNCER] Righty, right!
Welly, well! Bring them on!
Good evening, everyone!
[LANA] Tonight, we have
a very special guest!
The man who saved
the world! Mr. Satan!
[BURT] Or so he claims!
Some say he didn't do it!
[LANA]
But Mr. Satan has vowed
to silence his
skeptics tonight with
a demonstration of super-human
strength that can't be denied!
[BURT] So let's hear it, for the
one and only, Hercule Satan!
[MR. SATAN yells]
What a loud mouth, my gosh!
[OOLONG] Listen to those idiots!
They're eating it up!
[BURT] And now, for the moment
you've been waiting for, folks!
Mr. Satan is going
to attempt to break
twenty bricks with
a single blow!
Unbelievable!
Can we have quiet, please?
We need absolute quiet--
Yeah!
[BURT]
Maybe not!
Mister Satan! Twenty bricks!
My goodness! That's
quite an undertaking!
Whether you defeated Cell
or not, you're one powerful man!
I defeated Cell, Burt!
And that's that!
And if this doesn't prove it,
I don't know what will!
Alright! Alright!
You heard it right here!
Hercule Satan!
The man who saved the world is
here to set the record straight!
Quiet, please!
Haa! Gotcha!
Hey, all you
little punks at home!
Don't try this or you
might get hurt! You dig it?
The pass is complete and now
it's time for the touchdown!
Folks! This is what
you've been waiting for!
Mister Satan will
now try to break
twenty bricks with
a single blow!
[BURT]
Can we have quiet, please?
We need to have complete silence
for this incredible feat!
[MR. SATAN yells]
[BURT] Unbelievable!
Unbelievable! Nineteen bricks!
Mr. Satan has broken nineteen
bricks with a single blow!
A new world record, folks!
Let's hear it for the
strongest man in the world!
[MR. SATAN]
Yeah! Oh yeah! Come on!
Yeah, Hercule, Mr. Satan--
Who cares what they
call me? I'm huge!
Being a celebrity
can be painful!
[KING KAI]
I can't believe that guy!
Taking all the credit
for your hard work!
It's despicable! Mmmm!
He's a cheat!
But, you know what?
He's a really good actor!
[KING KAI] Well, I'm not
amused! Imagine that face
on a cereal box!
Yeah! Man! I can see
it now, Hercule Puffs!
My! That is funny! Oh, Goku?
Hm? You rang?
Why, yes! Don't you think
it's time we built a house?
We need one!
Well, yeah! But that
takes some real skill!
Where can we find someone
who knows how to build?
Hm! Why, right here!
Oh! You mean Bubbles!
I didn't know
Bubbles was that smart!
You mean, Gregory?
I mean me, ya big dummy! M. E.
Oh! Why didn't you say so?
He did!
I never knew
you were that smart!
Gosh! A real builder, huh?
So, uh, how do we
get started, King Kai?
Well, I'm glad you asked that!
Oooh! Here we go! Come on!
Ah, yes! There we are!
Choice lumber!
Really?
[KING KAI] Well, let's
get started, shall we?
Come on! What are
you waiting for?
[NARRATOR] As Goku and King Kai
break ground on their new house,
Trunks heads downstream on
the mystical river of time,
thinking of the serious
tasks that await him
upon his arrival!
Join us on the next
episode of Dragon Ball Z!