[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball Z,
a repentant Vegeta courageously
gambled his own life
to avenge the fallen Gohan.
Unfortunately, even this
bold, selfless act
wasn't enough to put an end
to the horrible Majin Buu.
Vegeta crumbled, and the
Z Fighters hopes of victory
were scattered to the wind.
If a sacrifice of this magnitude
ultimately proved futile,
what chance could they
have of defeating Babidi
and his monster?
[BUU]
Buuuu!
[NARRATOR]
What would our heroes try next?
[BABIDI] Doesn't make
much of a difference.
[NARRATOR]
Is Babidi right to be so cocky?
Is this odd creature under
his control truly invincible?
It wouldn't seem so,
judging from his face,
but Majin Buu has
already shown the deceit
of that innocent smile.
Up at the Lookout,
even Goku doubted his ability to
overcome the monstrous Buu.
As evenly matched as they
were in their last fight,
if Vegeta couldn't stop
Buu, how could he?
But as the others soon learned,
Goku mourned the loss of
his fellow Saiyans
for another reason.
[GOKU]
We could've done a fusion!
[gasps]
Fusion? You mean a merger?!
It's an ancient merger art
that can be performed
between two people
of similar size and
physical ability.
You wanna try that again?
[NARRATOR] And as Goku explained
this new method of Fusion
he'd learned in Other World,
the Z fighters came up
with a most unusual idea.
Making a fusion
requires two warriors
of equal size and strength.
And the young Goten and Trunks
seemed to be a perfect match.
A new strategy begins!
[GOKU] We can't ever
give up hope, you guys.
[thinking]
I must find the Supreme Kai,
but I can't detect his presence.
What if the worst has...
No, I won't allow myself
to think that! Not yet...
Huh...?
Oh, he's still alive!
[KIBITO] Don't worry, Master.
Wherever you are, I'll find you!
[SUPREME KAI whimpers]
Gohan must still
be alive, I can feel it.
He has... to be...
He's the only one...
[groans]
Hey, Majin Buu! Where in
blazes are you taking me?
[BUU hums]
Hey!
Buu!
[growls, screams]
[PEOPLE gasping]
[BUU]
Buu stick landing!
[DRIVER]
What the...?!
Hey, listen punk,
I'm driving here!
That's it! Stinkin' tourists.
Don't know where they're goin'.
You yell to Buu? Bye-bye!
"Bye-bye"?
[CROWD gasps, screams]
You... go bye-bye now!
[screaming]
[DRIVER screams]
Buu!
[CROWD screaming]
Where do you
think you're going?
Wait! I command you!
[mutters] Oh, what's the use?
[BOTH]
Huh...?
[BOTH scream]
[screaming]
Oh, sir, are you all right?!
Have you been injured at all?
[BUU] Buu, like!
Buu, like! Buu, like! Buu, like!
[laughs]
Welcome to our store, sir...
Can I help you get
anything today, sir?
Want all!
Ah, you want all? I-I don't...
[BUU sighs]
[BOTH shriek]
[BOTH whimper]
[BUU hums]
Majin Buu! Stop this! Let's go!
Buu no go!
Buu have big hungry!
[BAKERS gasp]
Buu!
[BAKER A] You're not allowed
to be back here!
[grunts]
[BAKERS yell]
[BUU]
Buu want more!
Quit stuffing your face, you're
fat enough already! Let's go!
Buu have more hungry!
Wait up! Majin Buu--
[BABIDI] What's going on here?
Why have I stopped?
Oh, it's you.
What are you looking at?!
If you'll kindly remove your
Amazonian person from my cape,
I'll leave!
You're not going anywhere,
you wrinkled freak.
[BABIDI]
Why, how dare you--
[WAITRESS B]
Can it!
I'll have you know
something, bub!
If you don't pay
for your friend's cakes
and the windows and the walls,
THEN it comes
out of my paycheck!
So, you're not going anywhere
until you flash
the cash, mister.
Young lady, apparently you don't
know who you're disrespecting.
Apparently.
Well, my insolent little child
you won't remain oblivious
to my genius much longer.
In fact you may not remain
at all much longer for, you see,
I hold the fate of the
entire universe in my hands.
I am the great wizard Babidi!
[gasps]
I don't care if you pull
a rabbit out of a hat,
if you don't make some money
appear right this instant,
we'll see if you can fly!
[BABIDI screams]
I'll show you what
I can do: Paparapa!
OUCH!
She left us...
You want a piece of
me too, Blondie?!
[whimpers]
[WAITRESS B] Somebody please
get me down from here!
[whines] Somebody!
[POLICE CHIEF] This is the
police. We have you surrounded.
Come out peacefully
with your hands up,
and nobody's gonna hurt.
Majin Buu! Haven't you had
more than your fill yet?!
[BUU] Buu's tummy super big,
these cakes itsy-bitsy,
but they taste
so very yum, yum, yum.
[BABIDI] Well, those blue people
outside want the cakes, too!
They don't want you
to have any of it!
Huh?!
[BABIDI]
They told me so themselves.
[BABIDI thinking]
Imbecile...
[giggles]
[OFFICER A]
Don't move.
[OFFICER B]
You're under arrest.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say--
[gasps]
[OFFICER C]
Wouldja lookit that?
Hey!
[OFFICER D] What does he
think he's doin' over there?
Huh?!
[screams]
[gasping]
No, those Buu's cakes!
[BABIDI]
That was fabulous, Buu!
A little more of
that kind of action
and we'll be terrorizing entire
galaxies with no one to stop us.
[giggles]
Oh yes, boys. We're coming.
You don't mess with the great
Babidi and get away with it.
[KIBITO thinking]
Where could the Supreme Kai be?
[gasps]
[KIBITO thinking]
I'm on my way, Master!
[KIBITO thinking] I can't
sense his life force anymore.
I must be too late!
[gasps]
[KIBITO thinking] I'm sorry
for your loss, noble creature.
But at least there's still
some hope for my Master.
Huh?!
[KIBITO thinking]
This just might be him!
[gasps]
There! That has to be him!
[KIBITO]
Then I'm not too late!
I know that you're alive
my Master, I can feel it.
[SUPREME KAI whimpers]
Ah! Hold on, I'll help you up.
Master?
[SUPREME KAI grunts]
Greetings, Master!
K-Kibito?!
What's going on here?
I watched Dabura kill you
right before my eyes!
Is this Other World?
[SUPREME KAI] So you just awoke
as though nothing had happened?
How very peculiar.
[KIBITO]
Yes, indeed.
I must admit, I was
quite surprised myself.
I was certain I was dead.
Ah! It's Gohan!
Huh?
Kibito! Hurry!
Gohan's life hangs
in the balance!
No matter what, we absolutely
cannot let him die!
[BABIDI]
Come on, Buu.
No.
[BABIDI] I wish you'd stop being
such a miserable sourpuss.
We're about to take over
the world, you know.
Buu still hungry!
Kibito, do you feel that?
Majin Buu's power level
continues to increase
substantially.
Yes, of course.
His negative energy is
impossible for me to ignore.
It seems that...
even after being
out of commission
for thousands of years,
Majin Buu is as unstoppable
a force as ever.
Every horrible possibility
that I never even dared to fear
has materialized today.
This situation's not
entirely hopeless.
There's a possible
beacon of light
that has made
itself known to me.
Huh? Are you sure?
Does this have anything at all
to do with our search for Gohan?
It does...
Let's just say for now
that Majin Buu,
however invincible he
might seem to us,
may not necessarily be the
most impressive force
in the universe.
[KIBITO]
Master, what are you saying?
Surely you can't expect
me to believe that--
[SUPREME KAI]
Of course.
You can't believe it because
you haven't witnessed
the awesome power of the
Super Saiyans for yourself.
We'd best hasten our search.
Gohan's fragile
life force is waning.
I can just barely sense its
remains in that forest up ahead.
Hurry, Kibito,
before we're too late.
He should be around
here somewhere.
[KIBITO]
There he is, right over there!
[SUPREME KAI]
Yes, that's him!
He's still alive. However,
he's in a critical state,
like you were before
I revived you, Master.
Ah! Then there's hope.
[SUPREME KAI]
No!
Huh...?
Kibito, let's wait to
restore Gohan's energy
until we take him with us
back to our world.
Huh?! But, Master!
Surely you don't suggest
bringing a mere Earthling
back to the World of
the Kais, do you?!
Why, even the Grand Kai himself
is not permitted to set foot
on such hallowed ground.
[SUPREME KAI] You heard me.
Now let's go home!
[KIBITO]
Yes, Master.
[KRILLIN] So, Bulma, what
did you do with your parents?
[BULMA] They couldn't
bring themselves to
leave their stupid pets.
They said that even if
they meet their horrible,
gruesome ends at
the hands of Majin Buu,
I can bring them back
with the Dragon Balls.
Logic must be genetic.
You really think so?
It's too dangerous down there.
If I only knew where
Tien and Chiaotzu were,
I'd tell them to come up here.
That's very interesting.
Now, where'd you say
Goten and Gohan are?
[gasps]
And what about my
Trunks? And Vegeta?
[whimpers]
You're a fool.
[VEGETA screams]
Goku, where are my sons?
Come on, Goku.
What I have to tell you
isn't easy for me
to say right now. But...
Goten and Trunks are
going to be all right.
But Gohan and Vegeta are dead.
[gasping]
Majin Buu, destroyed them both.
But, Gohan, he can't be!
He just can't!
No, ChiChi!
Vegeta...
Nooo! Vegeta!
Bulma, pull yourself
together! Bulma!
[BULMA wails]
[GOKU]
ChiChi!
[BULMA sobs]
Noooo!
ChiChi!
[BULMA sobs]
How... can this be...?
I love him...
[VIDEL]
Gohan...
[KORIN]
Well, well.
You know, it's never easy
dealing with the
loss of loved ones.
Hey, Korin.
But I'm afraid there's no
time for mourning, Goku.
You have to take action.
Even in this place, none of you
are going to be safe for long.
From what I've seen,
Majin Buu's power could soon
gobble up this whole world.
[BABIDI]
Snap out of it, you big baby.
What's the matter with you?
Buu still hungry!
All those sweets are
just empty calories...
I've got something
more satisfying.
We'll give those meddlers
their just desserts.
Goku, what about the fusion?
Good thinking!
Mister Popo, would you
wake up Goten and Trunks?
[BABIDI using ESP] People
of Earth! Can you hear me?!
Testing, one, two...
I am the all-seeing
all-knowing,
all-powerful wizard Babidi,
son of the all-seeing,
all-knowing,
all-powerful wizard Bibidi.
Now, now, no peeking. There's
no sense searching for me.
You're not even close!
I'm using my unprecedented
magical abilities
to transport my words
directly to you, the people.
I'm so sorry to
bother you like this,
especially if you're having
an otherwise pleasant day.
I, too, know what it's like to
be pestered while having fun.
You see, earlier today,
three nuisances did just that.
Now I'm simply looking
to return the favor.
I really am senile.
[MAN B] Did anybody else
hear that talkin'?
Uh, yeah, I don't
know. Did you?
[BABIDI using ESP] Now, sit
back, relax, and enjoy my show.
Please be courteous and remember
that silence is golden, okay?
What's he up to now?!
[growls]
[BABIDI using ESP]
I now present the stars
of my own personal nightmare.
These are the three cretins
that I'm looking for.
Get a good look at
their ugly mugs,
for they are the ones
to blame for any
and all destruction that
may come your way.
Come out, you cowards!
Unless, of course, you're
scared of little old me.
I've got a preview
of what's in store for you
if you refuse to
show your faces.
Oh, but wait. First, please
allow me to introduce myself.
The handsome devil you now
see is none other than me,
the great wizard Babidi.
And this is my faithful
servant, Majin Buu,
the heavyweight champion
of the universe.
He may not seem like much, but
he's actually quite unstoppable.
Just look at him pumping
his fists like that.
Now, do you see this city?
It looks like a
lovely place, doesn't it?
Well, its citizens are about to
get a special sneak preview
of the high cost
of your cowardice,
while you look on from
your hiding place.
Ah! Darn him!
[BABIDI using ESP] The following
material is of a violent nature
and may be considered
quite gratuitous, enjoy!
This program has been
sponsored by your fellows.
Let the fun begin, Majin Buu!
Woo-hah!
[PEOPLE gasping, screaming]
What is he doing?!
No, not the people!
Ahh... What Buu want for eat?
Hmm... Oh, Buu eat
too much cake. Oh yes! Yes!
Buu want candy!
[PEOPLE screaming]
[gasps]
[MARON]
Huh?
[giggles]
[growling]
Aahhh...
This is but a small
taste of what will happen
if you don't surrender!
[laughs]
[NARRATOR] Will our heroes
risk their own lives
to save the innocent
people in Babidi's way?
Do they have any choice?
Not as long as the always-hungry
Majin Buu threatens
to eat everyone in
sight until the trio of
Piccolo, Trunks, and
Goten reveal themselves!
[NARRATOR]
Will the wizard keep his word,
and stop at nothing
to lure them out?
Don't miss the next episode
of Dragon Ball Z,
as the entire world
is held hostage,
by Babidi and Majin Buu!
[BABIDI, BUU laugh]