[NARRATOR]
Last time, on Dragon Ball Z!
Using a strange sneak attack,
Majin Buu ensnared both Piccolo
and the freshly fused Gotenks...
[NARRATOR] ...and absorbed
them into his body.
Knowing he could not match
Gohan's newly acquired powers
in his present state, Majin Buu
opted for a transformation.
Incorporating the powers of
Gotenks at Super Saiyan Three,
and the combat
wisdom of Piccolo,
a new, Super Buu was created.
And because it merged
Gohan's childhood teacher,
as well as his little brother,
it was a Buu who
knew Gohan all too well.
[GOHAN gasping]
[SUPER BUU]
What do you think of it?
New clothes,
and a few new abilities.
[GOHAN] If you're using
Piccolo's brains,
you know you've
got thirty minutes
until this newfound
strength of yours defuses.
[SUPER BUU laughs]
[SUPER BUU] I assure you,
it will be over before then.
And I didn't absorb you
because I needed a punching bag.
I kept you around because
I'm stronger than ever,
and I have to try it on someone.
[GOHAN]
Sounds fine, I'm all yours.
Let's do this.
[NARRATOR]
And so the battle
with the newest
incarnation of Buu began.
And where Gohan had previously
been in total control
of the action,
he was now struggling
with all of his might
just to stay alive.
[SUPER BUU] Remember, not so
long ago, I was the one hiding.
I needed time to stall.
Is that what you're
doing now, Gohan?
Your beloved Piccolo
is a part of me,
and I can sense that
you're alive down there, kid.
[NARRATOR] Will Gohan
have to fight this battle
for Earth totally alone?
Find out now,
on Dragon Ball Z!
[yelling]
[GOHAN grunting]
Come on, you're going to
have to try harder than that.
[groans]
You're not paying
attention to my moves.
Piccolo taught you better
than this, didn't he?
Yes, he did!
[gasps]
[SUPER BUU]
Could've been your head.
[SUPER BUU chuckles]
[SUPER BUU] And with all that
training on the cliffs.
[GOHAN growls, groans]
I can't see what's happening.
Uh, Gohan's in top form,
but it's simply
not going to be enough!
Gohan!
[GOHAN growls]
[GOHAN gasps]
[gasping]
[yells]
[GOHAN grunts]
[MR. SATAN groaning]
[DENDE]
Oh no!
[sighs]
[SUPER BUU] Now that
felt like a Piccolo technique.
[GOHAN groans]
[SUPER BUU] I really didn't
think the Special Beam Cannon
packed that much of a punch.
[SUPER BUU] But maybe
it's just that much stronger
now that it's coming through me.
What do you think of that?
Are you even awake?
[SUPER BUU chuckles]
[SUPER BUU]
You're letting them down again.
[grunts, yells]
[GOHAN yelps]
I possess the greatest
powers in the universe!
[groaning]
And I'll use them all
to kill you!
[GOHAN groans]
[inhales]
[gasping]
[laughs]
[gasps]
[screams]
Did you see that?!
Majin Buu just burped up
some kinda mini Buu!
What is that?!
How do you expect me to know?
[SUPERGHOST cackles]
Whoa, what the heck
is that thing?
[laughing]
Die time!
Gohan, get out of the way!
Don't touch him!
--[GOHAN yells]
--[SUPERGHOST groans]
[SUPERGHOST laughs]
[GOHAN screams]
[BOTH groaning]
[SUPER BUU] You can thank
Gotenks for that technique.
I know my little Superghost
could've spun a dozen
different moves at you,
but you just keep
making it so easy, Gohan.
It's kind of sad.
I almost feel guilty.
[coughs]
Ah...
There must be something you're
still anxious to prove, Gohan.
How amusing.
[crying] Oh, please,
don't let me be dead,
there's so many
things I never did!
Am I alive? I'm alive!
We've been saved!
[gasps, screams]
Where'd the puppy go?
[choking]
The whole world
is depending on you,
you're the savior, and you're
three breaths away from the end.
[GOHAN choking]
[SUPER BUU laughs]
[MR. SATAN]
Where is he? Bee!
Over there!
[MR. SATAN]
Huh?!
[BEE barking]
[screams]
[choking]
[GOKU] He can't keep
this up any longer!
There's got to be
something we can do!
That's an interesting
point you make, Goku.
Perhaps we can help Gohan
by sending you down to fight.
[BOTH gasp]
But, I can't go.
Yes, that's correct.
In his present state,
he's unable to return
to Earth ever again.
You think I don't know that?
[SUPREME KAI]
Huh?
I'll give you the life
that's left inside of me.
Then you can make
your return to Earth.
You mean you're giving
up your life, for me?!
Venerable Elder, this is
the most unorthodox behavior.
You can't just
offer up your life
to handle a single situation.
As usual, you're missing
the bigger picture.
After Earth,
Majin Buu will come here.
If that is true, then
let me give up my life!
What? No, master!
Majin Buu has been
my enemy to destroy
since Bibidi,
thousands of years ago,
and repeatedly I have failed.
You must allow me
to pay my own debt!
You're ambitious,
but too hard on yourself.
Let the old men
sacrifice their lives
so that the young ones can live.
My dear Kai.
You're too kind.
[BABA]
What is going on here?
Is this some kind of a joke?
No, far from it.
We're going to send the best
fighter we have here
to help them fight Buu.
I want you to escort
him there, Baba.
I will take care of the rest.
For the record,
you should know
that this is a bad idea,
but if you think it will
save the universe...
[VEGETA chuckles]
[VEGETA] The mighty King Yemma
comes groveling to me.
Well the deal stays,
regardless of the outcome,
and I don't plan to blow
myself up for him again.
You're what we have.
You two must leave immediately
if you're to make a difference.
Now, go.
Very well, sir.
But does it have to be me?!
Baba, I won't take no
for an answer.
I'm just saying, Majin Buu
is really big and strong,
and look at me, I'm just a wiry
old woman floating on a ball.
Enough!
Back to Earth, then.
So be it.
[VEGETA thinking] Kakarot, pity
you won't be there to greet me.
[groaning]
[SUPER BUU laughs]
[GOHAN groans, sighs]
Good night, Gohan.
[SUPER BUU chuckles]
[SUPER BUU] Without your father
holding your hand,
you really are nothing.
[BEE barking]
[growls]
[barking]
[yells]
[MR. SATAN grunting]
[screams]
[SUPER BUU grunts]
[yells]
--[SUPER BUU grunts]
--[GOHAN groans]
[roars]
Ha!
[screams]
Another Gotenks
move out of the hat.
Hope it's not too tight.
How does it feel to be bound
by your baby brother's moves?
[screams]
[DENDE]
Gohan, no!
[gasps]
Stop me if you've
heard this one before.
[groaning]
One final move, and game over!
[yells]
Kamehame-HA!!
[screaming]
He's got a spark left.
What are we supposed to do?
I'll see you later.
[gasps]
[GOKU]
Goodbye, Old Kai.
[crying]
[gasps]
Thank you, I promise
I won't let this go to waste.
Then, hurry up!
[gasps]
What are you doing?
You're standing there
looking like fools,
when you should be
saving the universe!
[chuckles]
Hiding only proves your
cowardice, my young fighter.
[gasps]
[laughs] That really hurt,
didn't it Gohan?
Facing your fears would
have been far less painful.
[SUPER BUU]
Still wanting to fight?
Take your best shot.
You can't hit me.
[GOHAN grunts]
[gasps]
[yells]
[DENDE, MR. SATAN whimpering]
[growls]
[gasping]
Still alive, well I guess
I'll have to make sport
out of smacking you around!
[gasping]
[energy blasts]
That's bad, that sounds
like somethin' really bad!
You should grab the puppy
and get as far away from
here as you can, right now.
Don't you worry about me.
I'm a master of Martial Arts,
and I'm also packin'
some serious heat!
And as soon as Majin Buu pops
his head outta' that hole,
he's gonna be
eatin' a lead salad!
[gasping]
Okay, I've got to go.
Hold on one second, Goku.
[GOKU]
Huh?!
What you're doing is noble,
but do you even have a strategy
for defeating Majin Buu yet?
I hate to rain on
your new-life parade,
but Majin Buu can still beat you
and Gohan without much effort.
Uh, all right.
Hm...
Okay, I got it!
I'll just do fusion with Gohan,
and that way we're
bound to win, right?
Ah, fusion.
You mean of the type
those kids have been using?
You think Majin Buu is just
gonna sit on his laurels
and wait for you two to practice
and get into just
the right stance?
I don't think so.
I'm afraid I don't
understand, Old Kai!
Why did you give up your life
if you didn't think there
was a way I could beat him?
He, he, he.
Try these on!
[OLD KAI]
Go ahead,
snap this onto your left ear,
would you?
Uh?
But, what will dressing
him like a Kai accomplish?
Strange...
[OLD KAI] Quiet, you two.
It's time you learned.
Is this suppos'd to make
me feel strong or something?
'Cause I don't
feel much different.
Now simply have Gohan snap
this one onto his right ear.
Immediately your bodies
will be bound together,
and much stronger,
my type of fusion!
--[GOKU] No kidding?!
--[SUPREME KAI gasps]
[NARRATOR] As Gohan bravely
tries to hold his own
on planet Earth,
Goku has taken a new life,
and readied himself to
come to his son's aide.
Will the secret of the elder
Kai's fusion earrings be enough
to finish Majin Buu
once and for all?
Stay tuned for more excitement,
on Dragon Ball Z!