[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball Z,
under the guidance
of his master and father,
Gohan was able to
reach radical new depths
and unleash a power
that had no rival!
Cell could only look on with
horror as the tides turned,
his evil vision--
and his body--
disintegrating right
before his very eyes!
It was the mother
of all energy waves!
As beautiful
as it was deadly!
A good omen,
that signaled a time of new
beginnings on Planet Earth!
But instead of donning
their party hats,
the Earth's Special
Forces celebrated
by summoning
the Eternal Dragon--
which, thanks to Dende,
could now grant two
wishes instead of one!
The first wish was easy!
Please revive all those on
Earth who were killed by Cell!
So be it!
[NARRATOR] Oh, death,
where is thy victory?
Oh, grave, where is thy sting?
And when it was
time to try to bring
Goku back with the second
wish, the Super Savior said,
Thanks, but no thanks!
It was time for a change.
To move on and
face new frontiers.
A new generation
on Earth was arising
and the groundwork had
already been layed!
His work was complete!
Trunks was ready to set sail
on his new adventure as well!
After finding a group
of true friends
and the power to set
things right in the future,
it was time to head for home!
Love you! Goodbye!
[GOHAN] Bye, Trunks!
You're the greatest!
[TRUNKS]
Goodbye, Gohan!
Later, man!
Bye, Trunks!
[TRUNKS]
See ya, guys!
[NARRATOR] Although peace has
been restored to the Earth
in the present, the future
from which Trunks came
is still a very bleak place!
No one knows where
Androids 17 and 18
are going to strike next!
The people are
living in constant fear!
[screaming]
[MAN 1] Get out of the way!
Go, go, go!
[MAN 2]
Move it!
[WOMAN 1]
Oh, help us!
[ANDROID 17]
It's a stampede.
[ANDROID 18]
Time for bonus points.
[screaming]
[ANDROID 17] I think we
just got extended play!
[ANDROID 17 &amp;
ANDROID 18 laugh]
This is great!
[ANDROID 17]
It's sudden death!
Whoever gets the
most buildings wins!
[ANDROID 18] Hey, no fair!
You got a head start!
[ANDROID 17 &amp;
ANDROID 18 laugh]
[TRUNKS] It's falling apart...
but it's still home!
[TRUNKS]
Hey! Watcha readin' there?
Hi, Mom! I'm back!
Yes. Yes. I see!
[BULMA]
Wow!
My gosh!
Trunks! Just look at you,
you've grown so much!
You even look older!
Yeah, I am!
I spent some time
in a room where
I lived out an entire
year in one day's time
and Dad was there with me!
You know it was pretty neat!
Yeah, that sounds
like your father!
Stuffing a whole year of quality
time with you into one day!
Hey, guess what?
There's tea made. How 'bout
we sit down and have a cup?
Sure!
[TRUNKS] And that's
pretty much the whole thing
in a nutshell, Mom.
[BULMA]
My gosh...
So Goku died after all?
[TRUNKS]
Mm-hm.
Goku not wanting to be wished
back--that sounds like him.
So he helps save the world
one last time and moves on.
What a guy!
Yeah!
Guess what, Mom?
Dad defended me in a battle!
Trunks, you've
gotta be kidding!
It's true!
I didn't see it,
but Yamcha told me
all about it afterwards!
Dad went all-out. Cool, huh?
[TRUNKS]
Cell was outrageously strong,
and I was having a bad day,
to say the least!
Yamcha said that when my dad
saw me, die he went mad!
He was so upset, he charged
Cell like a wild man
and without any hopes of
winning, attacked him head-on!
[TRUNKS]
Yamcha said it was the best shot
that anyone got in
on Cell all day!
Isn't it great, Mom?
Hard to believe, huh?
Mom?
Of course!
It's wonderful, honey!
Yeah!
[BULMA]
Unbelievable! Vegeta?
I can't believe
that arrogant man
actually did something noble!
It's a miracle!
--A true miracle!
--[ANNOUNCER] We interrupt
this program to bring you the
latest news of Android activity.
Parsley City
is under attack!
The interstate
has been destroyed!
The remaining survivors
are fleeing on foot!
All right! That's it!
It's their turn!
Please, Trunks!
Don't worry, Mom!
I'll be fine!
I've been hanging out
with Goku, remember?
[ANNOUNCER] We now return you
to our regularly scheduled...
Nightmares never last, Mom!
One day you wake up
and they're gone.
[BULMA]
Trunks, you be careful!
[TRUNKS]
I will, Mom! Don't worry!
[TRUNKS] Things are different
now. I can see the light.
I believe in you, Trunks!
Go get 'em, Son!
Oh yeah!
Hey! Calm down, Sis!
You're gonna blow a circuit
if you keep this up!
You shut up! I'm still
not talking to you!
[ANDROID 17] Why? Because I
blew up that clothing store?
[ANDROID 18]
No!
[ANDROID 17]
Because I killed that one guy
you thought was cute?
[ANDROID 18]
Everything I like, you destroy!
You demon... That was
my son you killed.
[OLD MAN] Stay away
from me, you murderer!
[ANDROID 17] So you wanna
play cowboy, huh, tough guy?
Well alright then,
old timer! Draw!
Now it's my turn.
Check it out.
Aw! Your not the only one
in town with a peace-keeper.
Please, don't shoot me.
Hey, sorry, Gramps!
You shot first!
Huh?!
What was that?
Hey, it's you.
Yeah, it's me.
The name's Trunks.
Look, it's over!
It stops here.
It does, huh?
Trunks, don't you remember
what happened last time?
Nothing stops here, except you.
Gosh, how rude! He is such
an arrogant little punk!
Man! That's it!
I want him dead.
It's a matter of principal.
I don't mind.
Consider it done.
[whispering]
But look, Sis.
We'll be blowing weeks
worth of fun. Comprende?
I don't care. I need this.
I've been in a bad mood all day!
Huh?!
Hey! He's behind you!
Darn him!
He's so dead!
[ANDROID 18]
Darn it!
Man, he's changed! I don't
know how, but he's good!
Argh! I hate you!
[TRUNKS] You hate the fact that
you're powerless to stop me!
That you're
completely outmatched!
Well, imagine feeling the way
you do now all of the time!
Like the people
of this planet do!
Fools! How do you think
my Master Gohan felt
when you ganged up on him in
the rain and he had no way out?
Well now it's your turn!
I hope you enjoy it!
You've improved, but you
can't beat the two of us!
17! Let's kill this punk!
[TRUNKS]
This is for Gohan!
It-It can't be!
You killed her!
Kid! That was one mistake
you won't live to regret!
[TRUNKS] You think this life
is all about you, don't you?!
What about the others?!
The ones that you two killed!
[TRUNKS] It's going to be
alright, sir, I promise!
[OLD MAN weakly]
My son...
[TRUNKS] I lost someone who
was like a father to me.
I know how you feel!
[TRUNKS] I wish I could
say that it's all over,
but there's one more
thing that has to be done!
Yes, I can feel it in my bones.
I know you're out there, Cell.
[NARRATOR]
With the Androids gone,
it was a time of new
beginnings on Earth.
The cities were being rebuilt
and old wounds were
beginning to heal.
At last the darkness
had been overcome
and the light was
shining in once again!
The special young man
responsible for this change
was preparing to take
one more trip into the past,
to tell his friends
the good news!
[TRUNKS] Hey! Don't worry!
I'll be back for sure this time!
You're right. Goodbye, Son.
Don't stay gone too long!
Hey! No way!
You know I'd start missing
you too much, Mom!
Hm?!
Hey, Mom! Would you
mind going inside now?
What? Inside? But why?
Ahh!
Where is she, Trunks?
I know you!
Who has a new girlfriend?
[TRUNKS]
Mom...
[BULMA]
Trunks?
[TRUNKS] Come on out, Cell!
I know you're here!
Huh?!
You're so lame!
Sneaking around
like the Boogie Man!
What's your plan, Cell?
To kill me and take
my time-machine to the past?!
You're having trouble
finding the Androids, huh?!
I'll bet you just
long to absorb them.
What?! How do you
know all this?!
I read your palm, big guy!
You have a short life-line!
[CELL]
So you're a joker, huh?!
Well, I don't like your jokes!
I subscribe to a different
kind of amusement
than you Earthlings!
[TRUNKS] Yeah, I know how
you get your kicks, Cell!
But it's not going
to happen anymore!
And I'm going to see to that!
You've gone back already?! Yes!
You've learned about
me in the past!
That's right! But there
wasn't much to learn!
You need to absorb
a couple of Androids!
Well, not in this time!
I've already made sure of that!
Huh?! You did? No way!
That's not possible!
Wait, I see!
You're bluffing, aren't you?
Your data makes that clear.
That's right, Trunks!
I know a lot more about you,
than you know about me!
You fool! How dare you!
You're a peon compared to me!
Yes, the data shows that you're
no match for the Androids!
And you're certainly
not a match for me!
Oh, yeah! Well see, I just
destroyed both of the Androids.
I knew it! I've been
searching this whole time!
But I knew it!
You! Do you realize
what you've done?! Idiot!
I have no further
use here! My babies!
They're gone!
I can't believe it!
But it doesn't matter,
does it, Trunks?
No, it's fine!
I'll just take a
little trip to the past!
You've given me the tool that
I need to complete my evolution!
I haven't given you anything,
but I'll tell you what!
If you can get by me,
then you can get to the past!
I'm not going to
let you! Goodbye!
[CELL] You shouldn't be throwing
your life away like this.
No one will know!
Just let me leave!
[TRUNKS] There is someone
watching and laughing!
A friend of mine that
you killed in the past!
He's not someone
I could let down!
[CELL] Don't worry, you'll be
seeing your friend shortly!
[TRUNKS]
We'll see about that.
Yes, we will. You won't
be alone. There's a long list.
Now you too
will be a part of me!
That's right!
I'm going to suck you up!
Your energy will be refreshing!
A nice treat to start off my
journey in the time machine!
Enough! You freak!
[CELL] Don't you shush me,
you little punk!
[TRUNKS]
You're over-confident, Cell!
[CELL]
There's no reason not to be!
I've come across
thousands like you!
Yes, you have.
But count me as the last.
This isn't possible!
He's faster!
It doesn't make sense,
my design is superior!
He's just sitting there
daring me to attack!
[CELL gasping, panting]
Cell! It's your fault!
You hear me?!
You've brought this on yourself
by killing those people!
[CELL]
Who do you think you are?!
Enough of this!
You're gone, and here's
your going away present!
Kaa... Meeh...
Haa! Meeh!
Ha! Ah?!
The nightmare
is over, Cell! Die!
No! No! No!
[CELL screams]
[TRUNKS] Now I can finally
say that it's really over.
Thanks to you, Father.
And to you, Gohan!
And especially to you, Goku!
You're the greatest.
[KING KAI]
This is ridiculous!
Why am I doing all the work?!
I'm the King!
When you get to be King,
you're not supposed to
have to do all the work!
It's like living with
a bunch of two-year olds!
All they wanna do is play!
[GOKU] Come on, you guys.
You can't give up.
You almost got me!
What's the matter?!
You so look tired!
What a bunch of weaklings!
You can do better than that!
[GREGORY]
Come on, Bubbles!
[GOKU] Uh-oh! Here they come!
They've got me cornered!
Whoops!
[GREGORY]
You take that side, Bubbles!
Man, you guys, that was close.
I can't believe it!
I thought you had me for sure!
Hey! I'm done!
[KING KAI laughs]
[GOKU] Wow! That's awesome!
It looks really sturdy, too.
[KING KAI]
Mm-hm.
[BUBBLES chatters]
[GOKU] Well, it...
uh... looked sturdy...
[laughs nervously]
Oh, man! Sorry, King Kai!
Gosh! I really blew it!
I feel so dumb!
[BUBBLES chatters]
No... No, it's not true,
Bubbles. It's not his fault.
Hey! I know! Yeah!
This is a sign!
I don't think we're supposed
to be living here, King Kai!
Do you believe in signs?
--[KING KAI] No!
--[GOKU] Huh?
Come on! Let's go to the
Other World! Take a trip!
Huh?! You mean hit the road?
Hm...
Come on!
There's nothing holding us
here except a pile of lumber.
We're as free
as birds, King Kai!
Let's hit the road right now
and go on an adventure!
Well, gosh! I don't
usually migrate!
And I hate.. travel...
Here! It'll be okay, come on.
Bubbles!
Gregory! Road trip!
Yay!
[NARRATOR] Goku and King Kai
have begun their journey
to the Other World!
What is this
mysterious place?
And what will our adventurers
find when they get there?
Join us next time
on Dragon Ball Z!