[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball Z,
Majin Buu touched down
on the sacred world of the Kais,
and the battle began!
[NARRATOR] Goku was the
first to enter the fray!
Rather than attack Buu
as a single fused warrior,
he and Vegeta had decided
to fight one at a time!
It would be a one on
one fight to the finish,
the ultimate test,
for the ultimate Saiyan Warrior!
[KID BUU laughs]
[GOKU] Darn you.
Where's your weak point?
You're twice as strong
as you were before.
Your speed, your power,
your recovery.
[SUPER BUU laughing]
[GOKU screams]
[NARRATOR]
As Goku soon realized,
if he was to win this fight,
he could hold nothing back!
Majin Buu seemed pleased
by this new development,
but does he really
know what it means
to do battle with a
Super Saiyan Three?!
[GOKU]
Okay, let's see what you've got!
[KID BUU laughs]
[VEGETA grunting]
[VEGETA]
Steady!
[MR. SATAN] He changed!
Again! Look at his hair.
[KID BUU laughing]
[GOKU]
Uh?
[GOKU grunts]
[VEGETA thinking]
It's about time.
--[GOKU grunting]
--[KID BUU groaning]
[GOKU groans]
--[KID BUU grunting]
--[GOKU groans]
[GOKU grunts]
[KIDD BUU screaming]
[HERCULE, BEE scream]
I know we're both
under a lot of pressure,
but let's try to keep
our heads on our shoulders.
[growls]
[KID BUU yells]
--[KID BUU grunts]
--[GOKU groans]
Wow, the heavens themselves
are shaking. What a battle!
[OLD KAI]
Come on, Goku! Yeah!
[YAMCHA] So far so good. Seems
like Goku's holding his own.
Goku! Hang on!
[gasping]
Man, I've never seen
a fight like this.
Neither have I. Yes, this
is most unusual, indeed!
Mez, take a look.
Isn't that the same guy
that fell off Snake Way
and beat you in a foot race?
Hey, you're right, Goz!
Well, no wonder he was able
to beat me. What a guy!
He's not that great.
I know I could have beat him if
I didn't lose both of my legs.
Lousy, no good Saiyan monkey!
Who's Goku fighting with?
That imp's giving him a
tougher fight than I did,
and he quit against me.
I don't know, but I
do like that pink.
He sure packs a wallup!
[BABIDI laughs]
That's my boy! I'm responsible
for that demon of disaster!
[ALL gasp]
Really?!
That's right,
I'm the great wizard, Babidi.
Majin Buu's mentor.
[ALL murmur]
Oh yes, I taught him everything
that he knows about fighting.
He's not much on brains
though, it's all brawn.
[ALL murmur]
Amazing! You must be the
greatest fight trainer there is!
Yes, so true.
You're real smart, for an ogre.
Come by for a lesson
sometime, why don't ya?
[BUZ]
I will, sir, I will!
[ALL gasp, cheer]
[FRIEZA] Destroy that
squirrelly monkey, Buu!
[BABIDI] You disobedient,
disrespectful creature.
Buu, I hope you get
blown to smithereens!
How dare you make
a mockery out of me!
Do it, Goku! Beat the Buu!
Whoa, I really don't think
our planet's gonna make it.
Naa! The World of the
Kais can take it! So can Goku!
Give it to him, Goku!
Yeah! That's it!
[KID BUU yells]
--[BUU growls]
--[GOKU groans]
[VEGETA gasps]
Ah!
--[MR. SATAN groaning]
--[BEE whines]
Have no fear, boy! I'm here!
I won't let anything bad
happen to you, I promise!
After all, I am the Martial
Arts Champion of t--
World!
[GOKU thinking]
All right! Where are you, Buu?
[GOKU groaning]
Buu!
[GOKU thinking]
He's tunneling under the ground.
He's got to come up sometime.
[groans]
[KID BUU laughing]
How does he keep it up?
[laughing]
[GOKU thinking]
I can't even keep up with him
at Super Saiyan Three!
[GOKU thinking]
All those hits,
and he's not even showing
the slightest sign of fatigue.
[KID BUU laughing]
[VEGETA thinking]
His strength is preposterous.
[laughing]
[KID BUU grunts]
[gasps, growls]
[KID BUU screaming]
I know I'm going to regret this,
but this isn't the time
to conserve energy.
Ka... Me...
Ha... Me...
Haaa!
--[GOKU] Haa!
--[KID BUU gasps]
--[GOKU yelling]
--[BUU screams]
[KING KAI]
He's down. He's exhausted.
[KRILLIN]
Goku...
[YAMCHA] Hang in there,
Goku! C'mon, you can do it!
[GOKU groaning]
[KID BUUS laughing]
Wh-wh-wh-wh-wh-what the heck?
Even my nightmares
don't get this freaky.
[GOKU groaning]
[yells]
[groans]
No, Kakarot!
[gasps]
Kakarot, I'm right here.
--[GOKU groans]
--[VEGETA gasps]
[VEGETA] Look I know
it's your turn Kakarot,
but I think I'd better
cut in at this point!
Unless you're
finished eating dirt?
[GOKU] Yeah, sure, be my guest.
Please! Be careful, Vegeta.
Count on it!
[laughing]
[VEGETA yells]
--[BUUS laugh]
--[VEGETA groans]
[VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA grunting]
--[VEGETA grunting]
--[KID BUUS scream]
[panting]
Peek-a-buu-buu!
[laughs]
[VEGETA grunts]
[laughing continues]
[VEGETA screams]
Vegeta!
[yells]
--[KID BUU yells]
--[VEGETA groans]
--[VEGETA groaning]
--[KID BUU grunting]
This is terrible! Vegeta hasn't
been able to land a single blow.
He's outclassed.
--[VEGETA groans]
--[KID BUU grunts]
[KID BUU laughs]
[VEGETA thinking]
What? How dare he!
Ahhh!
[VEGETA thinking]
No one does that
to the Prince of all Saiyans!
[VEGETA grunts]
[KID BUU laughs]
[VEGETA yells]
[gasps]
[KID BUU chuckles]
[VEGETA grunting]
[VEGETA grunts]
[KID BUU chuckles]
[gasping]
Great! No effect at all!
Vegeta!
[laughs]
[VEGETA groans]
[GOKU gasps]
[laughing]
[groaning]
[gasps]
[VEGETA thinking] I can't
do it. I'm no match for him.
[KID BUU laughs]
[VEGETA thinking]
Uh! It's over.
[KID BUU yelling]
[GOKU grunts]
[KIDD BUU groans]
[VEGETA thinking]
Kakarot...
Sorry to butt in like that,
but I'm not done yet.
Majin Buu's so much stronger
than anyone I've
ever faced before,
but I know there's
still a way to win!
[VEGETA gasps]
[KID BUU laughs]
[GOKU grunts]
[yells]
[GOKU grunting]
[VEGETA thinking] Amazing!
How do you do it, Kakarot?
[GOKU, KID BUU grunting]
[VEGETA thinking]
You've always been like this,
ever since the day
I first met you.
Always ready to meet
the next challenge,
even if it's bigger
than you are.
[VEGETA]
So we meet at last!
We have been expecting
you, Kakarot!
We were begining to
think you wouldn't show!
Hopefully now things will get
more interesting around here.
[GOKU, VEGETA grunting]
--[VEGETA grunts]
--[GOKU groans]
[GOKU grunting]
--[GOKU grunts]
--[VEGETA groans]
[VEGETA thinking]
How can this be happening?
I am a Super Elite!
The prince of all Saiyans!
[VEGETA thinking] And he is just
a low level, a common soldier!
I am one of the greatest
fighters in the Universe!
It was the same on Namek,
you had improved so much
that it made Recoome look
like he was standing still.
[VEGETA thinking] Your power
had increased so dramatically
since our battle on Earth,
that I thought you had done it.
I thought that you had
become a Super Saiyan.
It tore me apart.
How could a low-class soldier
accomplish so easily what I,
I had struggled my
whole life to achieve?
[VEGETA thinking]
After three millennia,
it has finally happened, a new
Super Saiyan has emerged!
And some how, I have become
this pompous witness.
[VEGETA thinking] Then at last,
it happened! I too, transformed.
[VEGETA thinking] After living
every moment of every day
for the singular purpose
of surpassing you,
I finally became
a Super Saiyan myself.
The Prince had
reclaimed his throne
and fulfilled his destiny!
[VEGETA thinking] But no
matter how strong I became,
your power still exceeded mine!
[VEGETA talking] At first, I
thought it was your loved ones,
that it was your
instinct to protect them
that spurred you on, and
pushed you beyond your limits.
[VEGETA thinking]
But then I found myself
with a family of my own,
and my power
didn't increase at all.
[VEGETA thinking]
I used to fight
for the sheer pleasure of it.
For the thrill of the hunt!
Oh, I had the strength
immesurable! I spared no one!
And yet, you showed
mercy to everyone,
even your fiercest enemies.
Even me!
Yet you never fought
to kill, or for revenge.
Only to test your limits,
and to push yourself
beyond them,
to become the strongest
you could possibly be!
[VEGETA thinking] How can a
Saiyan fight like that and,
at the same time,
be so gentle that he
wouldn't hurt a fly?
Oh, it makes me angry
just thinking about it.
But perhaps it is my anger
that has made me blind
to the truth for so long.
I see it now. This day
has made it all too clear.
You're better than me,
Kakarot. You are the best.
--[GOKU grunting]
--[KID BUU groaning]
[KID BUU laughs]
[grunts]
[GOKU groans]
--[GOKU grunts]
--[KID BUU groans]
[MR. SATAN, BEE scream]
[MR. SATAN]
Please, no!
[screams]
[GOKU]
Ah!
[KABITO KAI] My goodness!
That one had to hurt. Ow.
[KRILLIN thinking]
Hang in there, Goku.
[YAMCHA thinking]
Yes, go!
[WEST KAI]
Oh my, wow!
[CROWD cheering]
All right! No one fights
like this! This is incredible!
[NARRATOR] Vegeta has given
Goku his vote of confidence,
but can the mighty Saiyan
sustain his monumental effort?
The fight that will decide the
fate of the Universe continues
on the next episode
of Dragon Ball Z!