He knows that we're here!
[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z,
the Z warriors discovered
the hiding place
of the wizard
Babidi's spaceship.
Dabura, King of the Demon World
welcomed them by blasting
the Supreme Kai's sidekick
Kibito to smithereens.
But he didn't stop there.
He had more than a mouthful
for anyone that got in his way.
[KRILLIN gasps]
[PICCOLO gasps]
--[SUPREME KAI gasps]
--[KRILLIN whimpers]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[NARRATOR] Dabura turned
Piccolo and Krillin to stone,
but there was no time
for the good guys to
ponder the fate of their
concrete comrades.
They decided to
launch a full-on assault
against the wicked wizard
and headed into the
heart of Babidi's ship.
With three of the Earth's
most powerful fighters
falling right into his hands,
Babidi is now confident
he can resurrect the monster
Majin Buu ahead of schedule.
[BABIDI] I'd be shocked if
any one of them had a brain.
[BABIDI laughs]
[DABURA chuckles]
Yes, trapped so easily...
[NARRATOR] Majin Buu
lies dormant in his shell
waiting to be released
so that he can wreak havoc
on planet Earth.
All he needs is enough power to
break the spell that binds him.
Babidi knows that if he can
drain Goku, Gohan and Vegeta
of their power it will be more
than enough to free Majin Buu.
So he's used his magic to
manipulate a fierce force
of warriors into
fighting for him.
And now, Vegeta must
face the first fighter,
the powerful Pui Pui.
[PUI PUI chuckles]
Welcome, fellow warriors.
You've arrived at Stage One.
[PUI PUI] Master Babidi is at
the bottom level of this ship.
We are currently on the top
level, also known as Stage One.
And there's no way of
getting down to him
unless you beat the warrior
that appears at each stage.
[NARRATOR] Babidi has
cleverly designed his ship
to absorb the
power of the fighters.
There are three stages that
the Z Warriors must pass
if they want to get
to the wizard.
But at each level a new and more
powerful foe waits for them.
Can the good guys get Babidi
before he gets them first?
Today on Dragon Ball Z!
[yells]
You're mine!
[PUI PUI grunts]
[gasps]
[growls]
Well. You fight pretty good.
But not that good!
[yells]
[PUI PUI grunting]
[gasps]
[PUI PUI grunts]
[SUPREME KAI gasps]
[PUI PUI whimpers, grunts]
There you go,
didn't I tell you?
See, Vegeta can handle
this guy no problem.
[PUI PUI grunts, growls]
[growls]
[PUI PUI grunts, yells]
[PUI PUI grunts]
[gasps]
[VEGETA]
You looking for me?
[PUI PUI gasps]
He's good.
He's really good.
It looks like he's
gotten a lot stronger.
Well that's what happens
when you spend all
your time training.
[whimpers]
[BABIDI]
This is pathetic!
What is Pui Pui doing up there?
Just look at him...
He's losing...
That's not good, not good all.
How are we supposed to
get energy for Majin Buu
if he can't damage that fighter?
Master, don't worry.
Pui Pui has a lot more
fight left in him.
[PUI PUI growls]
What's wrong?
Had enough?
No!
[PUI PUI grunts]
[growls, grunts]
[PUI PUI grunting]
[BABIDI gasps]
[grunts]
[growls]
Tell me.
Where's a place that Pui Pui
can fight at his best?
On his home planet,
Planet Voon.
Yes! Planet Voon it is.
Ooohhh... [growls]
Papparapa!
[gasps]
Ah! What happened?
Where are we? Ah, weird...
It's that Babidi!
He's used his magic to
change the room!
It seems, he's trying to give
that fighter the advantage.
Ahh, should be interesting.
Goku!
It isn't Vegeta he's
giving the advantage!
Yeah. I know.
[SUPREME KAI gasps]
[laughs] Welcome...
...to my home planet!
[PUI PUI] I've won
many great battles here!
And by now, you've
noticed that my planet
is very different from yours.
It's the gravity! Ten times
stronger than Earth!
Your hopes of winning are
falling faster than that stone!
You won't leave here alive!
[laughs]
[chuckles]
[gasps]
[VEGETA] Maybe if this was
500 times gravity,
you might have an advantage.
But ten?
I don't even feel it.
Huh?!
You're just bluffing!
I know you are!
Maybe I am...
Hard to tell.
Enough! [yells]
[PUI PUI grunts]
[PUI PUI growls]
[gasps]
So do you still think
I'm bluffing?
[growls]
[laughs]
[yells]
[PUI PUI snarls]
[VEGETA chuckles]
[gasps]
[PUI PUI screams]
[BABIDI gasps]
[SUPREME KAI gasps]
[GOHAN]
All right!
[VEGETA]
Ha!
I'm amazed that Babidi would
send us such a weakling...
[GOKU] Hey look,
the floor's opening up!
[GOHAN]
It looks like an elevator shaft.
[GOKU]
C'mon!
[GOHAN]
Right behind you, Dad!
[VEGETA]
Children. So easily amused.
[GOKU]
Hey! Supreme Kai!
What're you waiting for?
Come on! Let's go!
Now... I see...
They're very strong.
[BABIDI growls]
That's weird...
This room looks the same
as the last one we were in.
Yeah, and Babidi is probably
going to try and change
this room with his magic, too.
[BABIDI] Yargh! That fighter
beat Pui Pui far too easily!
[growls] I thought there
wasn't supposed to be anyone
this powerful on Earth!
I don't understand it.
When we checked this
planet 300 years ago
there was no one
here that strong.
Curses!
[DABURA] They may be powerful
but there is no need to worry.
There are still two more levels
for them to get through.
And even if they do succeed...
I will be waiting for them here!
[laughs]
[CROWD yelling, shouting]
[yawns]
Well, a break, huh?
What do you think the
hold up down there?
--[screams]
--[OX-KING, YAMCHA gasp]
What is it?
[CHICHI, ROSHI gasp]
[whimpers]
What?! Talk to me!
Where's Goten?
Huh?
Please! We've got to find him!
Goten, where are you?!
Huh...? I haven't seen
Goten for some time now.
That's strange...
And Trunks is gone, too...
Goten said he would
come and find me,
but I haven't seen him
since his match with Trunks.
That boy. He's probably
too embarrassed
about losing our prize money to
come up here and sit with me...
Hey, uh, ChiChi,
maybe he just went home.
They were flying?
[FRIAR D]
I saw it with my own eyes!
[GOTEN]
Trunks. Stop!
[TRUNKS]
Huh?
[GOTEN]
I'm tired...
Can we rest for awhile?
Yeah. Okay...
I guess you're right, Goten.
Let's go find a place to rest.
[GOTEN pants]
Wait! That way!
[TRUNKS]
No! No! No, the other way!
[GOTEN pants]
[TRUNKS]
Hello, there! ...Stupid...
[gasps] Oh. I really should
tell Mister Mighty Mask
what's going on! Hey!
[TRUNKS]
Keep going, Goten!
[ANNOUNCER pants]
[TRUNKS]
That way!
[GOTEN pants]
[TRUNKS]
That's it! Right here, Goten!
Okay. The coast is clear.
Oh.
There he is!
[TRUNKS sighs
[GOTEN]
Hurry up! Get off of me, Trunks!
[TRUNKS]
Wait a minute!
[GOTEN]
I can't wait any longer!
[TRUNKS]
Tough!
I'm the brains of
this outfit, remember?
I hear children.
--[ANNOUNCER gasps]
--Move it or lose it, big boy!
[WOMAN hums]
[ANNOUNCER clears throat]
Hey! watch your step, pal!
I just washed there, ya know!
Come on!
Oh? Excuse me,
but I'm in a bit of ru--
[WOMAN] Yeah!
You and everybody else!
[TRUNKS grunts]
[laughs]
[GOTEN]
Juice! Juice!
I'm gonna have
some juice! [laughs]
[sighs]
[GOTEN]
That's the one!
[WOMAN hums]
[ANNOUNCER thinking]
Now's my chance.
Uh, Mighty Mask?
[gasps]
Uh?
[whimpers]
Uh... Uh...
Hold on... What's this?
All right, you two.
You better start explaining.
[gasps]
Yes, sir!
[ANNOUNCER]
This area is off limits, boys!
Don't you know that?
Uhh...
Uh... Yeah!
We just wanted to get Hercule's
autograph that's all, sir!
Yeah, we want an
autograph please!
[ANNOUNCER]
Mmm... Oh, why not?
After all, you kids did pretty
well in the youth division.
[BOTH laugh]
Now where's Mighty Mask?
Have you two seen him?
I know I saw him come
into this locker room.
[BOTH gasp]
[stammers]
Huh.
Well, he must be here somewhere.
Here's his outfit.
[gasps]
I wonder where he's gone?
Uh, he's gone...
Uh... He's... In there...
[ANNOUNCER]
Mister Mighty Mask?
Are you in there?
[chuckles]
[ANNOUNCER]
Huh?
[chuckles]
[ANNOUNCER]
Oh, I see... He's in the shower!
Well, then.
I'll just say hello.
[GOTEN]
Stop! No!
He'll get mad, uh,
if you see him!
[ANNOUNCER]
Hmm... Yes... That's right.
These masked fighters
don't really like to show
their faces that much do they?
Okay, no problem.
[sighs]
[ANNOUNCER] Can you hear me,
Mister Mighty Mask?
[gasps]
Mighty Mask?
[stammers] Yeah! What's up?
Oh! Hi there!
We don't know when we will
be starting the next match
so please don't leave the
stadium, all right?
Sure! You bet! ...Stupid...
Well, that's that!
[gasps, laughs]
[TRUNKS, GOTEN laugh]
You two... Don't hang
around here too long, okay?
[TRUNKS, GOTEN]
Yes sir!
[BOTH laugh]
[sighing]
[GOKU]
It's my turn to fight next!
So, I wonder who's
behind that door?
I sure hope he's gonna be
tough enough for me!
[BABIDI giggles]
[DABURA]
Babidi!
Who are you going to
appoint to defend Stage 2?
[BABIDI]
Hmm...
Send Yacon!
What...?
This situation hardly calls
for such extreme measures.
I believe we may
have underestimated
the strength of those three...
You see... Pui Pui
was defeated easily,
without inflicting any
damage to their fighter at all.
Of course...
But if Yacon fights now,
I'm certain he will
finish everyone off,
and there won't be
anyone left for me!
[BABIDI]
We're not here to have fun!
We're here to free Majin Buu
and destroy planet Earth!
Got it?! Understand?!
[DABURA]
Yes, of course... Forgive me.
Tell Yacon to fight!
At stage 2!
[SUBJECT A]
Sir!
Yacon!
[YACON roars]
[SUBJECT A gasps]
--[SUBJECT B gasps]
--[SUBJECT A screams]
[bones cracking]
[screams]
[YACON growls]
[BABIDI]
Yacon!
[BABIDI] Sorry to keep
you waiting, my friend.
I have some
fresh victims for you!
Have as many as you like!
Yes... Babidi!
Hey! C'mon! Get out here!
[VEGETA] Why don't we just
smash through the floor
and get to the
bottom of this place?!
[We can't do that! Even though
he's not at full power,
an unnecessary shock
could free Majin Buu
and that would be disasterous!
Augh. I'm beginning to think
that this Majin Buu
may not be worth
fighting after all.
And the same goes
for that Dabura.
What...? No, you
can't be serious.
Then you won't fight them?
Well, why should I? From what
I've seen of Dabura so far
I don't see any reason
to be so afraid of him.
I watched his
movements outside
and the only thing I have
to worry about is his spit.
If I avoid that,
I know I can beat him.
Your friend Kibito
was careless, that's all.
[SUPREME KAI]
Ah...
So, do you agree with him, Goku?
Yeah. Vegeta's right!
Dabura's not that tough...
If it was a few years ago,
we might be afraid of him.
About seven years ago, we
fought this guy named Cell.
Now that was tough! Oh-ho!
[SUPREME KAI thinking]
I can't believe this...
Can these Super Saiyans
really be that strong?
[SUPREME KAI thinking]
I suppose it is possible.
It was extremely difficult to
restrain Gohan's movements
after he became a
Super Saiyan...
And that may not even
have been his full power!
Hey! Get out here now!
Let's go! I'm ready to fight!
Huh...?
[YACON growls]
[GOKU]
Uh...
[YACON growls]
[GOKU, GOHAN gasp]
What is that thing?!
[YACON snarls]
That's it... Be a good boy,
Yacon, and finish him off
for me! [laughs]
[YACON roars]
What...? Oh no!
[YACON growls]
[NARRATOR It looks like Babidi's
pet monster Yacon
is about to have a
Super Saiyan for lunch.
Goku had better be on his toes.
One slip, and all his
power could be drained and
sent straight to Majin Buu.
Could this be Goku's
most difficult fight yet?
Find out on the next
Dragon Ball Z!