[NARRATOR] With Kami back on
his throne and Garlic Junior
safely locked inside of the
Dead Zone, the Earth was
back to normal once again!
Well, as normal
as it gets anyway!
[MARON] Krillin, come on!
We don't have all day!
You have to keep up!
I'm comin', Maron! I'm comin'!
[MARON humming]
[KRILLIN]
Man, just look at her go!
She's a shopping machine!
What stamina!
[KRILLIN laughing]
[GUY] Yes way!
[GIRL] Cool!
[KRILLIN groans]
Uh, man!
[MARON] I guess you're feeling
pretty silly right about now,
aren't you, Krillin!
He, he... Huh?
Yeah, uh, actually, I am
feeling pretty silly!
[phone ringing]
[BULMA] Alright! Alright
already! Now what kind of idiot
would let it ring 25 times?
Yeah! Me here!
Say what!
Bulma! Come quick!
Please, no time to lose!
We've got a big
emergency here! Hurry!
Hey! Noodle arm! What
was that? Gimme a break!
[PLAYER 1] Hey, Yamcha!
[YAMCHA] Huh?
[PLAYER 1]
You got a telephone call!
What? Really?
[phone ringing]
[OX-KING]
Hello. What? Master Roshi!
Of course, we'll be right there!
[CHICHI groans]
[phone ringing]
[KRILLIN] Hey, this is Krillin,
[MARON] and this is Maron!
[KRILLIN] You can leave
a message after the beep,
[MARON] or you can be a
hopeless loser and hang up!
[KRILLIN, MARON]
Chow!
[ROSHI]
Krillin!
[KRILLIN] I don't get it!
She seems perfectly happy now!
What was all that about earlier?
That guy... with the hair...
Aw, how can I compete with
a rich-slick like that?
Man, I wish Goku was here!
He'd know what to do!
[MARON screaming]
Oh, my gosh!
[MARON] Isn't it beautiful,
Krillin? Don't you think
it's the perfect dress for me?
Wouldn't I look gorgeous in it?
[KRILLIN] Uh, w-well, yeah,
sure! But it's a lot more, um
frilly than the
dress you have on!
[MARON] It's supposed
to be frilly, silly!
It's a wedding dress!
Guh...
[MARON giggles]
Yeah! Uh, wowee!
[KRILLIN] You sure would
look great in that dress!
[KRILLIN] Uh, wait a second!
Does she mean with me
or somebody else? Oh, my gosh!
[KRILLIN laughing]
[CROWD cheering]
You dog! Good luck!
[KRILLIN laughing]
[MARON]
Oh! Krillin!
Check it out! That's the car
I want! It goes with the dress!
Oh! And look! Yeah!
That one there! Wow!
[KRILLIN]
Eh?
[MARON] If I was married,
I'd want to live in a house
just like that!
[KRILLIN]
Oh, yeah, it's beautiful!
[KRILLIN] Chin up Krillin. Where
there's a will there's a way!
No way!
Please! Have a little
compassion!
[BULMA]
Compassion?
You lied to us and said
that it was an emergency!
That's right! Guilty
as charged! What an example!
And you call yourself
a Master! Bad! Shame on you!
Yeah, that's one of your
oaths too, isn't it! No lying!
[ROSHI] B-But he's 1,000 years
old today! And I totally forgot!
When I remembered
this morning, I panicked!
You know how
sensitive he is! Right?
[TURTLE]
Master?
Huh?
[BULMA, CHICHI]
Oh, my! I can't believe it!
You remembered my birthday!
That's so sweet! Oh, my!
You're all so sweet!
[ALL]
Happy Birthday! Cheers!
♪ Happy Birthday, Turtle!
Happy happy Birthday! ♪
Golly! They're all there! Mmm!
That's right! 1,000 candles
for one millennium on the Earth!
[OX-KING]
Happy Birthday!
[ALL]
And many more!
Hi!
[ROSHI]
Hey glad you made it!
Yeah! Hi, guys! Hi, Yamcha!
[YAMCHA laughing]
Hi!
[BULMA growling
What a flirt!
So, hey! What's the deal?
Ah! Oh! Krillin, look!
This cake, it's perfect!
Yeah, well uh. She means
perfect for a wedding!
We're kind of shoppin' around!
[BOTH]
Huh?
So you guys are engaged?
Well, no not officially! But uh,
you know we're talking about it!
[ROSHI yelping]
That's great! Alright!
Congratulations!
Man! This is just like
Beauty and the Geek!
Married life! Oh, my,
you're in for a real treat!
Out of the question!
You know you have
to clear that with me, first!
Aw, come on!
We'll see! It's possible!
As long as I get
to kiss the bride first!
[ROSHI groans]
[ROSHI muffled grunting]
[MARON giggling]
Yay! Come on,
Turtle! Blow hard!
[GOHAN]
Wow! He did it!
[BULMA]
Unbelievable!
[KRILLIN] Ah.. who am I kidding?
I can't make her happy! No way!
Shoot! She's too good for me!
[TURTLE]
That's not true, Krillin!
She's not too good! She's not!
You're a very, very good person!
[KRILLIN]
I know I'm good, Turtle!
But she's tall, and
beautiful, and charming!
If she can't love you
for who you really are,
try giving her a giant pearl!
[KRILLIN]
What?
[TUTLE] Yep! Legend has it,
that the Mermaid's Tear
is somewhere near here,
at the bottom of the sea!
It's the largest
pearl in the world!
That might do the trick! Wow!
[TURTLE] You can't win Maron's
love with a pearl, Krillin!
[KRILLIN]
I can't?
[TURTLE] Nope, but it
could be just the spark
you need to get the blaze going!
[KRILLIN]
Alright, I'm gonna go for it!
I can't just throw
in the towel now!
Shoot yeah! This is just like
every other battle I've been in!
And I'm not giving up!
[GOHAN]
Wow!
Hey, late for school?
[TUTLE] The Mermaid's Tear
is extremely rare
and precious, Krillin!
It's priceless,
a gift worthy of a queen!
[KRILLIN]
I'll find it! Maron deserves
to have the best of everything!
And I'm gonna make
sure she gets it!
Gosh! Wow! It's a beautiful
morning, isn't it Ox-King?
Sure is! Yes!
The beach! The waves!
Whoa!
Fruit-cakes!
You should be
ashamed of yourselves!
[BOTH whimpering]
[MARON] Where'd Krillin go?
It's no fun! I'm bored!
Hey, what's up? I'm bored!
Are you? 'Cuz yeah.
Yeah, sure!
So hey! Maron!
When's the big day!
Have you and Krillin
set a date yet?
A date? No way! No!
What does that mean?
No way? Huh?
[CHICHI]
I know! She's playing it smart!
It's wise to be cautious
in these matters! She knows!
It's all about commitment
and hard work! Right?
[MARON laughing]You middle-aged
ladies crack me up!
What middle...
...aged ladies?
[BOTH] Well she's a
lot older than I am!
I'm not middle-aged, she is!
You have some nerve!
You're older than
me and you know it!
But I've always been
the prettiest one!
And you know that!
You think skimpy
clothes make you prettier?
Well, think again, you bimbo!
[BOTH growling]
[ROSHI meows]
Catfight!
Nobody wants to have
fun around here!
Oh, well. Shoot! I'll just
go somewhere else then!
[GOHAN] Krillin!
Are you sure about this?
It's an awfully big ocean!
[KRILLIN] The Turtle said
it was around here somewhere!
[KRILLIN]
Gohan, look!
[GOHAN]
Yeah, I see it! Good eye!
[KRILLIN]
C'mon!
What in the-- Huh?
[GOHAN]
Strange little guy!
[KRILLIN]
Aw, man! Bummer!
[GOHAN]
Huh?
Oh, wow! It's beautiful!
[GOHAN] Krillin! There's a
treasure! Back in that ship!
Huh?
Man!
[GOHAN]
Krillin, look!
[KRILLIN]
Oh, wow! Yeah!
[GOHAN]
Wow, cool!
[KRILLIN]
Yeah! This is awesome!
[GOHAN]
Look how bright it is!
[KRILLIN]
I know, it's like daylight!
Huh?
[BOTH]
Whoa!
[KRILLIN]
This is crazy!
[GOHAN] Calm down, guys!
We're not going to hurt you!
[KRILLIN]
Gohan!
That's it! Wow!
The Mermaid's Tear!
[GOHAN]
It's incredible!
[KRILLIN yelping]
[GOHAN] Man! This place
is really mystical! Look!
[KRILLIN] Wow! I had no idea
that it was this beautiful!
It's fantastic!
Huh? Krillin! Behind you!
Huh?
[KRILLIN yells]
[GOHAN]
Look out!
Holy cow!
[KRILLIN]
Yow!
Oh, man!
Uh, oh! Here we go again!
[KRILLIN sighs]
[KRILLIN yelps]
[KRILLIN yelling]
Krillin, no!
Huh? The Mermaid's Tear!
Krillin, The rocks!
Huh?
[KRILLIN]
Are you seeing what I'm seeing?
[GOHAN]
Yeah!
Unbelievable!
Oh, my gosh!
Look, Krillin,
they're protecting it!
They think the Mermaid's Tear
belongs to them!
[KRILLIN] But they're just fish!
What do they want with a pearl?
[GOHAN] I don't know but look!
They're ready to fight for it!
Yeah, I guess you're right!
[GOHAN] Are you sure you want
to take it from 'em, Krillin?
Look at 'em!
Gee, I-I don't know,
Gohan! What do you think?
Well, we could get it
from them easy enough,
but I think I'd kind
of feel like a member
of the Ginyu Force
if we did!
Huh? What do you mean?
[GOHAN] You know, like
the fish are the Nameks
protecting one of their Dragon
Balls and we're the Ginyu Force
that's come to take
it away from them!
[KRILLIN] Yeah! Wow, I never
looked at it that way!
Oh, man! Maron's like the pearl!
I have to let her go!
[KRILLIN]
Gohan!
Huh?
[KRILLIN] Hey? Let's get out
of here! Let's go home!
Krillin! Are you sure?
[KRILLIN]
Yeah I'm positive!
Thanks Gohan.
Thanks for being you.
[KRILLIN]
Hi, Maron! It's me!
Huh! Oh, hi.
[MARON]
Hey, what's the deal?
You're not being your
usual fun self, Krillin!
I'm starting to get bored!
Oh, sorry! It's just that
well, sometimes... sometimes--
Sometimes?
When you love
someone, sometimes
you have to set 'em free!
Because it's the best thing!
So, uh... that's what I'm doing!
I'm setting you free! Goodbye!
Bye, Krillin!
Thanks for everything,
Krillin! We had fun!
You'll always have a
special place in my heart!
[KRILLIN]
Thank you, Maron! Goodbye!
[MARON]
Goodbye!
I would've said yes, you know!
I couldn't refuse
someone as sweet as you!
Sure, I know you
would've said yes!
Yes! Holy cow!
[KRILLIN]
Did I really just hear that?
Maron! Hey!
[KRILLIN yelps]
Uh! I must be nuts!
[KRILLIN]
Just look at her!
Maron, wait!
Huh?
Hey!
You need a ride?
I'm going downtown, babe!
[MARON]
Buy me an ice-cream?
Sure thing.
[MARON]
Goody, goody! Sure, I'd love to!
[KRILLIN]
Hi, everybody! It's me!
[BULMA]
Where's Maron?
Well, things were
gettin' complicated,
so I broke up with her!
You know how it goes!
[ALL gasp]
Oh poor guy!
Aw. It's a darn shame!
Well, I don't believe it!
I'll bet she dumped him!
Oolong!
You're outrageous! Bold move!
I'm glad! I hate to say it!
But there was something
about her I didn't trust!
Yeah, you're much better off.
I think that Maron girl
was nothing but trouble.
You too? Man!
[KRILLIN laughing]
Krillin...