[NARRATOR] Previously
on Dragon Ball Z,
a stranger from the future
arrived to inform
Goku and the others they
had three years to prepare
for the arrival of
two evil androids,
androids more powerful
than any enemy
they had ever faced before.
[TRUNKS] Once
this pair surfaces,
the Earth and everything you
know will be gone for good.
[NARRATOR] Heeding
the advice of Trunks,
our heroes stepped up
their training.
Vegeta is training
like never before.
And he won't stop until he's
become a Super Saiyan
even if it kills him.
[VEGETA grunts]
[NARRATOR] Piccolo's not taking
this ominous message
from the future lightly,
and neither is Goku!
Together, they're
training night and day
in the hope that
they will be ready to
meet head on whatever
challenges might lie ahead.
[NARRATOR] Gohan is growing
stronger by the day as well.
Pretty soon, he may even be able
to teach his dad a thing or two
on Dragon Ball Z!
[CHICHI screams]
--[BOAR snorting]
--[CHICHI screams]
[CHICHI] You don't want
to eat me! Really!
[CHICHI screams]
[BOAR roars]
[CHICHI] Oh no!
[CHICHI screams]
[CHICHI sobs]
[CHICHI squeals]
[BOAR roars]
[BOAR snorts]
[CHICHI] Huh...?
[CHICHI sighs]
[GOKU] Hmm... That cloud
looks like somebody I know.
I'll be! It's him!
It's Master Roshi!
Except his nose is a bit bigger.
And that cloud
looks like Piccolo.
Eww! Scary!
[GOHAN] Hey, Dad!
Look what I caught!
That sure is a big fish!
Your mom will be proud of you.
[GOHAN chuckles]
[GOHAN] Do you think we
can have it for dinner?
[GOKU] Sure we can!
[thinking] Aww, fish again?!
That's all we've had
for two weeks straight!
[CHICHI] My feet are killing me.
I wish I had a car...
[GIRL giggles]
--[GIRL] Ya-hoo!
--[BOY] Woo-hoo!
[BOTH laughing]
[CHICHI sighs]
[door opens]
[GOHAN] Hiya, Mom! Look what I
caught for you down at the pond!
Just in time for dinner!
More fish. That's great.
[CHICHI growls]
[thinking] And it looks
like I'll be cooking
for one extra again tonight!
Doesn't that Piccolo
have any where else to go?!
Huh...?
[GOKU groans]
[GOKU] Pee-yew!
Come on, Gohan!
Let's go take a bath!
Hmm...?
[GOHAN] Ew! My clothes
smell like fish!
[GOKU laughs]
[GOKU] Hey, ChiChi! Could you
give these clothes a wash?
--Easy on the starch, okay?
--[CHICHI growls]
We worked up
quite a sweat today.
--[GOKU laughs]
--[CHICHI growls]
--[GOHAN laughs]
--[growling continues]
Hold it right there!
Now, let me get this straight:
You expect me to get dinner
ready and wash your clothes
while you and Gohan relax
in a nice hot bath?!
Well that's not going
to happen mister!
Do you even care what
kind of day I've had?!
I don't know what
I liked better:
being chased half way
home by a wild boar,
or walking the rest of the
way on my tired, aching feet!
And it's all because
we don't have a car!
Uh, ChiChi, I'd drive
you if I could.
But you know I don't have
a driver's license yet.
Well, it's time you got one!
I don't know why you have to
be the only man in this town
who doesn't have a
driver's license or a car!
You can't drive can you?
LEAVE ME OUT OF THIS!
I want both of you to put
your training on hold for now
and go to driving
school tomorrow!
I think it's about
time the two of you
learned something
useful for a change.
Say what?!
[GOKU] Aww, ChiChi,
do we have too?
Listen, all I'm
asking you two to do
is get your driver's license.
It's not like I'm asking
you to save the world.
And if you don't...
you'll have to cook your
own meals from now on!
Understand?
[BOTH gulp]
--Mm-hmm...
Oh man! Piccolo, where
did you get those clothes?
You're wife got them
for me out of your closet!
[GOKU] Oh, uh, sorry about
that. ChiChi means well.
Listen, since we're here,
let's get this over with.
Sounds good to me.
Of course, I'm still not sure
how I got suckered into
this in the first place.
She's not even my wife!
[INSTRUCTOR] Alright,
which one of you is Goku?
Oh, I'm Goku!
[INSTRUCTOR] Ah. I'll be
your driving instructor today.
[INSTRUCTOR coughs]
[INSTRUCTOR wheezes]
Let's go!
[INSTRUCTOR moans]
[INSTRUCTOR] My back!
Hey, mister, are you,
uh, all right?
[INSTRUCTOR] I'll... be... fine!
There, good as gold now!
Hi, there!
You must be my student.
You're Piccolo, aren't you?
We're going to start with the
basics for your first lesson.
I'm going to demonstrate
proper driving technique.
So please pay attention.
[thinking] How did I ever let
myself get into this mess?
First of all, always remember
to fasten your seat belt!
[FEMALE INSTRUCTOR giggles]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[PICCOLO growls]
Hmm...
[FEMALE INSTRUCTOR coughs]
[FEMALE INSTRUCTOR chuckles]
--[FEMALE INSTRUCTOR laughs]
--[PICCOLO gasps]
YEAH! Burn Rubber!
[PICCOLO whimpers]
[FEMALE INSTRUCTOR] Yeah!
Listen to that engine!
You know what that
sound is?! Power!
Yee-haw!
[PICCOLO screams]
[brakes squeal]
Are you sure you know
what you're doing?!
[FEMALE INSTRUCTOR growls]
[FEMALE INSTRUCTOR]
Come on! Come on!
YEAH!
[PICCOLO screams]
Okay, I can do that.
[MALE INSTRUCTOR]
Ah... Let's see... Come on, now.
Blasted foreign cars!
[MALE INSTRUCTOR grunts]
Huh?
And today's first lesson
is: Opening the door.
[GOKU chuckles]
[MRS. BRIEF]
Vegeta's still training?
Oh my, that man works so hard!
[BULMA] Oh, Mother! Can we
just forget about him?
I mean he hasn't come
out of that capsule in days!
Well, I must say that I'm
becoming quite impressed
by that boy's unshakable
determination.
Why, just the other day,
he was training
in four hundred times
Earth's gravity!
Isn't that amazing?
[SCRATCH meows]
Oh, he's nothing but
a thickheaded ape!
[COMPUTER]
Increasing gravity simulation.
[VEGETA yells]
[COMPUTER]
Increasing gravity simulation
450 times planet's
normal gravity.
[thinking] No! I can do more!
[growls]
[GOHAN sighs]
[GOHAN] I wonder what my dad
and Piccolo are doing right now?
--[CHICHI] Gohan!
--Uh-oh!
Gohan, you've been such
a good boy studying all day
I thought I'd bring you a snack!
[GOHAN] Thanks, Mom.
[CHICHI] I know you've got
a lot of catching up to do.
And this should give
you just the energy
you need to really
hit those books.
[GOHAN] Oh boy, my
favorite... Thanks, Mom.
[CHICHI] You're welcome.
[GOHAN sighs]
--[ICARUS coos]
--[GOHAN gasps]
[GOHAN laughs]
Hey! I can't play right
now, I have to study!
Oh?! Wait!
I've got an idea!
[GOHAN chuckles]
You're doing just
fine, Mr. Piccolo.
Are you sure you haven't
been driving before?
[MALE INSTRUCTOR] All right,
try it again. Start the engine.
[MALE INSTRUCTOR]
Well, what's wrong?!
Uh, how do you start
this thing again?
[MALE INSTRUCTOR yells]
Come on! I've shown
you three times already.
If you really want to
learn how to drive,
you'd better start
paying attention!
I will! Give me another chance!
Why should I? You stink!
[GOKU sniffs]
I can't smell anything.
Are you sure?
I don't mean you! Your driving!
Never mind, just
turn on the ignition,
step on the accelerator
and let the brake out
slowly... Very slowly!
Ah! Yeah! Here we go!
[MALE INSTRUCTOR yells]
[BOTH grunt]
You're in reverse!
This baby's got a lot
of power, doesn't it?
[MALE INSTRUCTOR yells]
You're driving too fast!
You've got to slow down!
--Step on the brake!
--[GOKU] What?!
But I thought I was
stepping on the brake!
[BOTH yell]
[MALE INSTRUCTOR yells]
--[brakes squealing]
--[yelling continues]
[GOKU] Hang on, mister!
[MALE INSTRUCTOR wails]
[screaming]
[MALE INSTRUCTOR screams]
Just step on the brake!
The brake? Uh...
Now which one was that?
[MALE INSTRUCTOR screams]
[GOKU laughs]
Cut the ignition!
Huh?
[MALE INSTRUCTOR]
Cut the ignition!
Okay...
[screaming]
[MALE INSTRUCTOR] Hurry!
[GOKU yells]
Now what?
[MALE INSTRUCTOR gasps]
[screaming]
[GOKU] I know that was
kind of a rough start,
but how long before
I get my license?
Son, at this rate it'll
take you a hundred years.
That's too long!
I still have to get in
shape for a big battle
against two killer androids,
and ChiChi's going to kill me...
[GOKU blubbering in water]
[FEMALE INSTRUCTOR] Really,
Mr. Piccolo! You're a natural!
Ha! No sweat.
[GOHAN] Come on, Icarus, we've
got to find my Dad and Piccolo!
[ICARUS caws]
[GOHAN] Faster, Icarus! Faster!
[MALE INSTRUCTOR grunts]
Go ahead! But
this time, go slow!
No problem.
Now, then, put on
your seat belt.
[MALE INSTRUCTOR yells]
Alright! Look,
I made it go forward!
Slow down before you
break the sound barrier!
[FEMALE INSTRUCTOR] This is
the highway, Mister Piccolo.
You don't have to drive
like an old lady out here.
[GOKU] Woo-hoo!
[PICCOLO gasps]
[GOKU] Eat my dust, Piccolo!
Was that a challenge?!
Well if it's a race you want,
it's a race you'll get!
There! That's more
like it! Much better!
[MALE INSTRUCTOR whimpers]
[GOHAN] Look!
Here they come, Icarus!
And there they go...
Look out!
That was very impressive
driving, Mister Piccolo!
--[FEMALE INSTRUCTOR giggles]
--[MALE INSTRUCTOR yells]
[FEMALE INSTRUCTOR screams]
[MALE INSTRUCTOR screams]
[GOHAN gasps]
Luckily these two
are going to be okay.
[MALE INSTRUCTOR] You two
are by far the worst students
that have ever attended
this driving school!
I'll give you one more chance,
but any more stunts like
the one you pulled yesterday,
and I will see to it that you
never get your
drivers' licenses!
[thunder cracks]
[GOKU] Boy, this road
sure is treacherous.
Hi!
[MALE INSTRUCTOR] Both hands
are not on the steering wheel.
Minus one point!
You're testing me now?!
Your eyes are off the road!
That's one more point!
No fair!
[GOKU growls]
--[brakes squeal]
--[MALE INSTRUCTOR yells]
Hey! What's the big idea?!
You almost knocked
my false teeth out!
That's ten points! So there!
[thunder rumbles]
[CHILDREN scream]
[GOKU gasps]
[MALE INSTRUCTOR]
What are you doing?!
[FEMALE INSTRUCTOR screams]
[CHILDREN screaming]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[screaming continues]
[BOTH scream]
[screaming]
[GOKU grunts]
[PICOOLO grunts]
[CHILDREN scream]
[BOTH grunt]
[grunting]
Piccolo! Wait here!
[GOKU yells]
[PICCOLO yells]
[GOKU growls]
[PICCOLO growls]
[GOKU yells]
[CHILDREN cheer]
[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH sigh]
[CHILDREN cheer, giggle]
[GOKU] Goodbye, kids! Take care!
I'm sorry, sir! I guess we
didn't get to finish the test!
And I turned your new
convertible into a compact.
What a disaster...
Hey! Don't sweat it!
You mean you're not going to
totally freak out or something?
No way! Not after witnessing
that terrific rescue!
Oh? Does that mean I might
still get my driver's license?
Not a chance! You're a danger
to everyone else on the road!
[PICCOLO] What about me?
Nope!
Then we both failed?
[MALE INSTRUCTOR laughs]
Neither of you passed,
but so what?
I'd trade my driver's license
in a second for a chance to fly!
So would I!
--[PICCOLO gasps]
--[FEMALE INSTRUCTOR laughs]
[thinking] What's
ChiChi going to say?
[CHICHI] Failed the test?! What
do you mean you failed the test?
You're telling me neither of you
muscle heads got your license?!
Uh, yeah...
Mm-hmm...
Mom?!
Was it something I said?!
[NARRATOR] In no time, three
years have come and gone.
[CHICHI] Promise me that you'll
all take care of each other.
How about a little
lunch before you go?
Mom, we don't
have time for that!
Thanks! Bye!
Let's do it!
[NARRATOR] The time has come
for Goku and the others to unite
and face the two killer androids
that Trunks warned them
about three years ago!
[TRUNKS] Only you can change
the course of the future now.
Please stop them!
You've got to destroy
the androids
that Dr. Gero will create.
The future of this
planet is at stake.
You and your friends must
change the path of the future.
You are the last chance!
Please stop them!
Ready or not, Goku and the
others have a date with destiny!
A destiny that depends
on them defeating an enemy
more powerful than any
they have ever faced before!
It should be a piece of cake!
on the next
Dragon Ball Z!