[NARRATOR]
Previously, on Dragon Ball Z!
With only one year before
two evil Saiyan warriors
descend upon the Earth,
the world's most
powerful fighters
have little time to
prepare for their arrival!
Now in Other World,
Goku has begun a
10,000-mile journey
down the treacherous
Snake Way in order to train
with the legendary
fighting master, King Kai.
Meanwhile, back on Earth,
Gohan's first
day of training
put him face to
face with danger!
Gohan has a
long way to go
before he can become
a hero like his father,
but even on
his first day,
glimpses of his true
power shine through!
[thud]
Wow! Apples!
Wow! These look good!
[PICCOLO] I hope you
enjoyed it, kid.
That's the one and only
time I intend to help you.
If you can't survive
on your own after this,
then it means I was
wrong about you.
And you're just a
normal little brat.
[NARRATOR] Gohan's
transformation continues today!
[animals cry]
[animal roars]
[roaring continues]
[GOHAN] Mommy?
[CHICHI] I can't believe
those two aren't back yet.
Ugh! It's way past
Gohan's bedtime
and he hasn't even called.
And then Krillin
comes over here
acting all weird
and everything...
There's something strange
going on. I just know it.
If those guys think they
can hide anything from me,
they're crazy!
I mean, what is
Goku thinking?
Doesn't he know this is
the most important time for
Gohan as far as establishing
good study habits?
Hmph!
[sighs]
Goodness... All this worrying's
going to give me wrinkles.
[snoring]
[KRILLIN sighs]
[KRILLIN thinking] Oh, man...
What am I gonna do now?
I couldn't tell 'em,
Goku... I really blew it.
I don't know where you are,
Goku, or what you're doing.
But it couldn't be
as hard as this.
I better get
out of here...
[OX KING] W-Wait!
Where are you going?
Don't you know Mommy said
we can't play there anymore?
Becky saw a snake
there the other day.
[OX KING snorts]
[snoring continues]
[thinking] Great. Now I have
to tell Bulma and Master Roshi
that I wasn't able to
break the news to ChiChi.
Oh, I hope you're having
better luck than I am, Goku.
Ahh! That's bright!
Ahhh...!
What am I gonna do?
I'm never gonna get down
and I'm still starving!
Waaah! Waaah!
Believe me.
When your stomach
rumbles loud enough,
you'll find
a way down.
[ROSHI] So, uh, how did
she take it, Krillin?
I didn't tell her.
Ehh...
No way!
Seriously?
Yep.
I can't believe
you, Krillin!
So what have you
been doing all this time?
W-Well, we started eating
dinner, and it got late,
and uh, they made me spend
the night over there.
You are going to march
right back over there
and tell them
what happened!
No! Anything
but that!
Well, I can't
blame you.
Why not?
I just did.
I know it's hard.
Tell you what...
I'll write a letter
to ChiChi instead!
Wow! I'm off the hook!
Thank goodness...
Okay, so what about
the Dragon Balls?
Like the two at Goku's?
Tell me you still managed
to pick them up, at least.
[exclaims]
I forgot!
You're such a dweeb!
[ROSHI]
Oh, boy....
ChiChi, try
to calm down.
[CHICHI grunts angrily]
Okay. You can be like
that if you want to.
But I don't think
Goku deserves it.
[CHICHI] Ha!
He kept Gohan out all night
and he didn't even call once!
But, it's been so long since
he's seen his friends.
He probably just
lost track of time,
then decided to spend the
night with Master Roshi.
Well, he should have
brought Gohan back...
Gohan is attending
school you know!
Hey, come on.
Goku's so good...
When's the last time he
got out and had some fun?
And what about Krillin?
Why wasn't he with them?
They're
hiding something
and I'm going to
find out what!
Aaaaaahhhh!
ChiChi!
Slow down!
[OX KING yells]
[BULMA yawns]
[BULMA] I haven't
pulled an all-nighter
since I got out
of college...
There, I hope
that did it.
Let's see...
[beeping]
Hm!
Hey, guys! Let's go!
I've got this thing working!
Uh, guys?
[grunts angrily]
[gunfire]
Listen! I have
been up all night,
and I am a little bit
irritable right now!
So... You do not want to get
on my bad side this morning.
Now, then...
Let's try this again.
Let's go, guys!
Uhh, go where?
Come on, stand up so
I can try this baby out!
This should tell us what
your Power Level is...
And it's... 139!
139, huh? That seems
a little low to me.
No, I'm sure it's
a good rating,
considering
you're an old man.
I don't know
which hurts worse...
the lousy power rating, or the
commentary that goes with it.
[KRILLIN]
Hey! Check mine out!
I'd love to know what
my Power Level is!
[BULMA] All right,
you've got it!
206! Not bad!
Oh wow! Hear that
Master Roshi?
My power level's
higher than yours!
Eh... That proves it.
The gizmo's busted!
Oh, you think?
I know a way
to find out.
All right, Turtle.
Put up your dukes!
I'm going to check the
calibration on this thing.
Power level
point 001.
[BULMA giggles]
Sorry, Roshi. I'd say
it's pretty accurate!
[KRILLIN]
Oh yeah!
[ROSHI]
I'll be...
Oh, cheer up. You're
still stronger than me!
[MAN]
Hello?
Hey!
I wonder who
that could be?
[MAN]
Come on! Open up!
I don't have all
day, you know.
Now what kind of visitor
could possibly be so rude?
It's me.
Huh... Oh yeah,
I remember you.
You're, uh...
What's your name?
You know I'm Yajirobe, you
near sighted cue-ball head!
I don't need
any grief.
I already had enough
trouble finding this place.
Anyway, I'm s'posed to tell
you to go to Korin Tower
for special
training.
So uh, did
Korin send you?
Hey, look at me.
I'm know-it-all Korin.
That's the guy. And he wants
you to bring Yamcha.
And Ten-somebody,
and, uh, Chow-whatever.
Oh, you mean
Tien and Chiaotzu.
Not me?
Yeah, like I said...
Get all those guys
and bring 'em
to Korin Tower...
I'm training
with you, too.
What? No way?!
Yeah, crazy, huh?
I told Korin I'm not
fightin' any stupid aliens,
and he went
through the roof!
I thought he was gonna
kill me. He's serious.
Well, it sounds like
we don't have a choice.
You don't or at
least I didn't.
But do what you want!
I'm outta here.
Oh, yeah,
I almost forgot...
Don't wish Goku back to
life with the Dragon Balls
until the Saiyans arrive
one year from now!
What? B-But why?
Beats me. Somethin'
about special training
in Other World or
somethin' like that.
Some lady named Baba's
supposed to come by
to tell you the rest.
You can ask her.
[air-car blasts off]
Wait! Baba's coming here?
So... Goku's doing what?
No idea...
Huh?
Hey, uh...
Look. He's coming back.
[BULMA] Hm? Uh...
I don't know.
It looks like a
different air-car to me.
[OX KING]
Ahoy, there!
[gasps]
[OX KING] Request
permission to come aboard!
Hello, my friends!
Long time no see!
Ahhh!! It's Ox!
And he's with ChiChi!
I'm outta here!
Who's with me?
No, it's better to meet
life head on, Krillin.
[OX KING] It's so good
to see you, Master Roshi.
My finest memories are still of
when you taught me as a boy!
[ROSHI]
You were a good pupil.
But, Ox, I'm glad
you're here...
There's something I need
to talk to you about...
Alright, where are they?!
I know they're
here somewhere...
And don't bother
lying, either!
I know something's going on!
So where are they?
Well, it's, uh,
it's like this...
[CHICHI and OX KING]
Huh?
[ROSHI whispering]
A long time ago...
[whispering continues]
[both exclaim]
You guys let that green
monster take my son?!
So you're saying that Goku
had to, I mean, that he's...
Yep. He's, uh, dead.
[stammering]
[thud]
[OX KING] Oh! ChiChi!
Get the smelling salts, Krillin.
[rumbling]
Hey!
Hello!
Help! Up here!
Aww. There they go...
[cries]
I'll never get
down from here...
[GOKU thinking] Man! Talk about
your long and winding roads!
This is ridiculous!
Oh, hi...
[hisses]
Hey, wait...
It's okay. I'm not
going to hurt you...
[SQUIRREL squeaks]
Here, it's okay.
You can have it...
I'm not gonna
eat any more...
[laughs]
[winces]
Ow! That's not nice...
Hey, where you going?
He makes it look easy.
But, still...
I can't.
I'm too scared...
[GOHAN]
I hate this place.
What's he doing?
And I don't even know
how I got up here...
Hey, I have
a shadow...
But the sun's not
up. It's night.
Oh, wow!
That's the biggest moon
ever! It's so bright!
It must be
a full moon!
I've never seen
that be--Uh... Uh...
Huh? What the...
[GOHAN breathes raggedly]
[grunts]
[roars]
Huh?!
[PICCOLO]
He transformed?
This is insane!
I don't understand!
Why is this happening?
[roaring]
[PICCOLO] If I don't find
a way to stop this monster,
there won't be an
Earth left to defend!
I've got to
change him back!
Wait!
[RADITZ] Do you have any
idea what you've done?
Your true power
is gone now!
Without your tail,
you've lost your ability
to transform at
the full moon!
[PICCOLO gasps]
[PICCOLO] The moon!
They need the moon!
Aaahhh!
[PICCOLO groans]
[roars]
[breathes heavily]
So that's the secret
to the Saiyans' power.
It's that tail!
Somehow it gives
them the ability
to transform
at a full moon.
In that case, it was for
the best that I destroyed it.
If Gohan did
this much damage,
I hate to think what
the other two Saiyans
would have done
when they arrived...
Without the moon, they
won't be able to transform.
And we'll be on a more
level playing field.
In fact, we have
an advantage.
Because we know that their
tails are a weak point.
Which means right now,
that tail is only a liability.
There!
Now, I guess you'll
need some new clothes.
And a sword would help.
Now you can't say I never
gave you anything, kid.
[chuckles]
The clothes are
like your Dad's...
But the symbols show
you're from my camp.
Alright. I've already done
more for you than I intended.
I don't have time to
baby-sit you anymore.
I have my own
training to do.
But if you can survive for
six months on your own,
you'll see me again.
And that's when
you'll learn
the art of fighting
the hard way!
I'll teach you
everything...
That's right. You'll
learn to be just like me.
[NARRATOR] The countdown to
the Saiyans' arrival continues.
And the Earth's fighters
are one step closer
to being prepared.
But for son and
father alike,
a long, hard road
still lies ahead!
On the next
Dragon Ball Z!