[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
more visitors arrived
on Planet Namek.
[KRILLIN] It looks
like a Saiyan ship!
[BULMA whimpering]
It's Vegeta!
It's gotta be.
Rrrgh... Raagh!
[NARRATOR]
Vegeta landed on Namek
with only one thing
on his mind:
Revenge.
[VEGETA] My time
has finally come.
I'm about to remove the only
obstacle standing in my way.
[BULMA squealing]
W-Was that Vegeta's
ship again?
[FRIEZA laughing]
Heh, heh...
[NARRATOR] The young
adventurers have no idea
that the mighty Frieza
is also on the planet
and in possession of four
of the Dragon Balls.
Now, their simple mission
is moving quickly
into messy territory.
Stay tuned for
Dragon Ball Z!
[BULMA sighing heavily]
This may be the most
depressing day of my life...
Yeah, today isn't
starting off too well.
So, what do
you think, huh?
[KRILLIN] Who could have been
in that second ship?
[GOHAN] Hmm...
[HENCHMAN]
For you, Lord Frieza.
Very good.
Only three more to go.
[chuckling]
Guard them
carefully, Dodoria.
Vegeta wants them,
and I'd rather not
waste any time hunting
them down again.
Lord Frieza,
Cui has just arrived.
He's been
tracking Vegeta,
so we should know his exact
whereabouts soon enough.
Also, those small power
levels we noticed earlier
appear to
have vanished.
However, it's unlikely
they've traveled far
from their last
known position.
I've already sent out two
scouts to search the area.
Whoever it is, they won't be
able to hide from us for long.
Fine. But I don't want my
scouts chasing apparitions
when they could be helping
to search for Vegeta.
Yes, I understand your
concern, Lord Frieza.
And I would agree,
if I didn't believe Cui
was more than capable of
handling the job on his own.
His power level is much
higher than Vegeta's.
I don't think you'll
have to worry about seeing
that monkey-tailed
abomination again.
Ahh... There you are.
[CUI laughing]
Hello, Vegeta.
Do you read me?
Fair warning...
I'm coming for you.
And I'm brining a little
message from Lord Frieza!
So, you've been following
me, have you Cui?
Well, I have a message
you can take to Frieza.
His days are numbered,
as are yours!
[CUI laughing]
[CUI] Take a good look
at your scouter.
My power level is way
higher than yours!
[CUI chuckling]
[CUI] You arrogant Saiyan.
It's about time someone
put you in your place.
[GOHAN] What are we
supposed to do now?!
Well, it's not doing us any
good just sitting here.
So it's settled! We'll
stick to the original plan!
I'll hurry back to
Earth and get Goku!
You guys
have the radar,
so you shouldn't
have any trouble!
See you in
two months!
Hold on, Bulma.
Give us a second.
Ahh...
Ah?!
[KRILLIN] Uhh...
So, um, Gohan.
Hmm?
Whaddaya say you and me,
well, maybe we should go, too?
Wha--?
Hmm?
Hey, c'mon! Two enemy
ships have already landed.
Even with the Dragon Radar,
the odds are stacked against us.
It might be best
to cut our losses.
I'm not saying I'm
scared or anything,
I'm just lookin'
out for Gohan!
ChiChi would kill me
if I let him get hurt!
But, we can't
just leave now.
If we do, then Vegeta will
get all of the Dragon Balls.
Uhh. Yeah, well, uh... Maybe
we should let him have 'em.
I mean, we can always
try again next year!
That's not funny,
Krillin.
You know what kind of
damage he can do with them.
We're talking
about Vegeta.
Krillin, look!
Someone's coming!
Hmm?
Ahh!
[BULMA squeals]
Is it...
Vegeta?
Don't think so...
This energy level feels
way too low to be his.
Keep your
eyes peeled.
They should be right
around here somewhere.
I bet it
was a native.
[BULMA]
Who are they?
Let's hope
they're Namekians.
[BOTH scream]
Those are definitely
not Namekians!
Hey, who's that?
Whoever they are,
they're not from around here.
Looks like we get to
have ourselves some fun.
Zarbon said if
they're not Nameks,
we don't even have to question
'em before we kill 'em.
[laughing]
Check out what
they're wearing!
That's weird, it
looks like they're
wearing Saiyan
battle uniforms.
But they
aren't Saiyans.
What are they?
I guess they're hired
muscle or something, but...
Either way,
it's not good.
They sure don't
look friendly.
Aren't you two
gonna do something?
You've gotta
protect me!
Gohan. Keep your
energy suppressed
until we know what
we're dealing with here.
All right.
[SCOUT B laughing]
This will be easy.
Their power levels
are almost non-existent.
They're
probably tourists.
Heh, heh, heh. Let's attack
their ship first.
It would be a shame
for them to get away
before we
have our fun.
Sounds good!
[BULMA screams]
No! Not
the ship!
[SCOUT A laughing]
[SCOUT B] Did I destroy
your precious ship?
Please forgive me!
Well, I think
I've seen enough.
Time for us to do some
serious powering up!
Hmm!
[GOHAN growls]
Hey, take a
look at that.
Looks like
the little one
is having stomach
cramps or something!
[SCOUT B] Huh?
[BOTH laughing]
Wait! Hold on!
Their power reading
just skyrocketed!
[BOTH whimpering]
Let's do it!
Yeah!
[SCOUTS yelling]
[GOHAN] Haah!
[KRILLIN] Raah!
[GOHAN] Ha-ha!
[KRILLIN laughing]
That was easy
enough, huh?
Don't look
so happy!
[BULMA quietly sobbing]
--[BULMA] Our poor ship.
--[KRILLIN] What's wrong?
[BULMA] How are we
supposed to get home now?
Zarbon, what is it?
Something's troubling you.
It's the search
party we sent out.
Both of our scouts stopped
transmitting at the same time.
I realize those scouts
weren't the best that we had,
but it still worries me that
they were defeated so quickly.
Whoever is responsible
for this attack
knows what they're doing, and
they seem to have the ability
to suppress their power.
Well. That's
very interesting.
But why are you wasting my
time with these things?
The two unknown power levels
came in at fifteen hundred.
It's possible Vegeta has brought
with him some extra help.
Only fifteen hundred?
That means nothing to me,
nor should it to you.
Just concentrate on
retrieving the Dragon Balls
and we'll be on our way.
They'll be dealt with when
I destroy this puny planet.
[GOKU quietly grunting]
[thinking] Yes...
Just a little more.
[grunting continues]
[water bubbling]
[GOKU] Ngh!
[CHICHI] Goku?
Uh... ChiChi?
Honey, what
are you doing?
[GOKU chuckling sheepishly]
Well, I was bored,
so I started to, uh--
Goku, really.
Why can't you understand
that you're badly wounded?
You need to
stay in bed.
Look at you.
Your hair is all wet.
You don't want to catch
a cold now, do you?
[GOKU wailing]
I hope Gohan is taking
good care of his hair
like I
asked him to.
That boy's
hair is so fine
that he has to keep up
with washing it daily.
I wonder if he's
using the conditioner
I gave him
before he left?
I don't want him
coming back to Earth
with a frizzy mop
on top of his head.
And he better not be
using his hair dryer,
because that will
only make it worse.
His scalp is already
dry enough as it is.
[thinking] Gohan, I sure
hope you're doing okay.
[BULMA whimpering]
It's no use! We'll never
get back to Earth!
We'll be stuck on this
planet for eternity!
[KRILLIN] Come on, Bulma.
We need to get out of here.
Whoever is sending those
scouts knows our location now,
and there's bound to
be more on the way.
Don't worry, Bulma.
I'll bet if we find
some Namekians
they can help us
repair the ship.
We're not going to be
stuck here. I promise.
We'll make it back
to Earth somehow.
Okay.
He's right.
We'll find a way.
We just have to
keep our cool.
That was the first
thing Piccolo taught me:
Never panic!
Oh, sure...
Easy for you to say!
[BULMA crying]
Bulma?
Hah!
It's about time.
Took him
long enough.
[CUI laughing]
So nice to
see you, Vegeta.
You have no
idea how much
I've looked
forward to this.
The day when I
would get to wipe
that smug little smirk
off your face forever.
You should have never
defied Lord Frieza.
Oh, we'll
see about that.
[VEGETA chuckling]
Cui, you just
don't get it, do you?
I'm through
taking orders.
It's time Lord Frieza
started bowing to me.
[CUI] You're old news, Vegeta.
You turned on Frieza and you'll
pay for it with your life.
Maybe, yes,
but not today.
[VEGETA growling]
Wha--? M-My scouter's
going haywire!
[growling continues]
That's right! I've been
suppressing my power.
It's a little trick
I learned on Earth.
Impossible! Your power level
was never anywhere near mine!
Idiot! Do you really believe
that you can keep up
with my experience
in battle?
I am constantly fighting
on the front lines.
I have been to the brink
of death and back again!
Meanwhile,
you've been hiding
behind the shield of
Frieza, growing soft!
[VEGETA yelling]
Twenty-two thousand?! I've
never seen a reading that high!
[shouting continues]
Zarbon. What happened?
I don't know. It must be
some kind of malfunction.
For a second there,
it registered
Vegeta's power level at 22,000,
and then it shorted out.
22,000? You've got
to be kidding me.
It must be that older
scouter model you're using.
Let me check
it on mine.
The number?
It... doesn't make
any sense.
This stupid thing
can't be right!
Now it's reading
twenty-four thousand!
Twenty-four?
Are you sure you're
reading that thing right?
It would mean Vegeta's power
level is even higher than ours!
I'm sure! It must be
some kind of a trick.
He's never been
above 18,000...
[FRIEZA] Is it really
so surprising?
Don't forget
that Vegeta
has been in heavy
combat for a while now.
With all the
fighting he's done,
especially on Earth,
he must have picked up
some new techniques.
Yes, but...
But nothing. There's
no need for concern.
It's only 24,000.
And while that may seem
impressive to some,
compared to me,
it's still insignificant.
[FRIEZA laughing]
[FRIEZA] Why do you think
Vegeta is so desperate
for the
Dragon Balls?
Hmm? I'll tell you.
He knows that without them,
he doesn't stand a
chance against me.
That's why he went to
Earth against my orders.
And that's why he's come
to this wretched planet.
He's been secretly
plotting to overthrow me,
biding his time, waiting for
his opportunity to strike.
And now, with the hope of
the Dragon Balls in sight,
he dares to
oppose me openly.
That stupid,
arrogant fool...
I am going to enjoy making
an example out of him.
Wait! Hold on, Vegeta!
I thought of a great idea!
I could join forces with you!
I never liked Frieza anyway...
And with both of us
working together,
we can take Zarbon and
Dodoria, no problem!
Think about it, Vegeta!
We've fought so much that we
know each other's moves
like the back
of our hands.
We'd make a
fantastic team!
[VEGETA] Stop blabbering
like a pathetic fool, Cui.
Your cowardice
makes me sick.
I'm not lying!
[VEGETA growling]
Please, you've got to
believe me, Vegeta!
[growling continues]
Hey! Look,
it's Frieza!
Huh? What?
Idiot!
[CUI] Ah-ha!
Rraaagh!
Huh...?
[CUI laughing]
He should've taken my
advice back on Planet Frieza.
I tried talking
some sense into him,
but, oh well...
[VEGETA] Is that so?
Huh?! Aaah!
Apparently your idea of advice
is to submit to my adversary,
and you know
I won't do that.
How'd you
escape that?!
Once again you've
underestimated your enemy,
Cui, and you won't be walking
away from this mistake.
But--! I--Aah!
What happened to
all that confidence
you had built up
for yourself?
It doesn't seem to
be working anymore.
[CUI whimpering]
[CUI] Aah!
[VEGETA growling]
[CUI screams]
[VEGETA] Rrrgh...
Raah!
[VEGETA] Heh, heh...
Goodbye.
See you in hell, Cui.
It looks like Zarbon
was right after all.
We really underestimated
Vegeta's power level.
He destroyed Cui in
a matter of seconds!
[FRIEZA] There's still nothing
to be concerned about.
Continue your search
for the Dragon Balls.
That's all
that matters.
[thinking] I'm sure
they've sensed my energy
through their scouters,
so they know I'm here. I can
take Zarbon and Dodoria,
I'm confident of that.
But Frieza...
Frieza is still
much too powerful.
I can't risk a
direct confrontation
until I've collected
all seven Dragon Balls.
Wait, of course! Without
all seven, they're useless.
Which means, if I
can find just one,
Frieza won't be able
to make his wish.
[VEGETA chuckling]
And then, after
he and his goons
have gone to all the trouble
of collecting all six,
I'll sneak in
and take them
right from under
their noses...
[laughing]
[thinking] Ah, yes...
I can almost feel my
immortality already.
Lord Frieza, we've
detected a group of Nameks,
not far in
that direction.
Well, that's good news.
And with any luck, they'll
have the fifth Dragon Ball
in their possession.
I'm sure we can convince
them to part with it.
But stay on
your guard.
We have a few troublesome
little pests lurking about.
Yes. Right.
[FRIEZA]
Very well. Let's go.
That's it, Frieza. Find
those Dragon Balls for me.
Each one you gather brings you
one step closer to your doom!
[VEGETA laughing]
Come on, Bulma.
Let's pick up the pace.
They'll catch us if we
don't find a place to hide.
[BULMA panting]
You guys can fly, can't you?
Why don't you just carry me?
Well, you know
we would, Bulma,
but, when we fly, it puts
out way too much energy.
Sorry, but they'd pick
up our power levels
on their scouters
for sure,
and then they'd know
exactly where to find us!
[BULMA screams]
[KRILLIN] Hey, look!
I found a cave.
It should be a great spot
to lie low for a while.
You're kidding,
right, Krillin?
You can't expect me
to live in that hole.
[BULMA sobbing]
[GOHAN] Hey, Krillin...?
Huh?
Are you sensing that?
That energy...
Think so.
It feels pretty strong,
and it's
still rising.
I don't know.
Whoever that is, it's--
Hmm! Ah!
Trouble! Everyone get into
the cave and hide, right now!
[NARRATOR] Once again,
our heroes find themselves
standing directly
in danger's path.
But for now, they are
still in the dark
as to the identity of
the approaching foe...
Could it be Vegeta? Or is it
someone far more sinister?
Find out...
Next Dragon Ball Z!