[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
King Kai and Goku hopped a plane
to the planet of the Grand Kai,
ruler of Other World!
[NARRATOR] There, hundreds of
dead warriors were gathered,
practicing for centuries on
this eternal training ground.
[GOKU] This place
is a dream come true!
Look at all the fighters.
[NARRATOR] The tour turned
quickly into a shouting match
with the arrival of West Kai,
who was showing off his
prize fighter, Pikkon!
[NARRATOR] But before a
brawl could break out,
the quirky Grand Kai appeared.
And he had an important
mission for Pikkon.
[GRAND KAI] Hey!
[coughing]
--[CELL laughs]
--Good odds!
Wouldn't you say, boys?
[GINYU FORCE]
Yeah!
[NARRATOR] Down in the Hell,
Cell, Frieza, and the Ginyu
Force were trying to take over.
What a fearsome team!
[NARRATOR] But as Goku
watched in amazement,
the mysterious warrior Pikkon
stopped the villains
with the greatest of ease.
[CELL yells]
[KING COLD grunts]
[FRIEZA gasps]
[FRIEZA grunts]
[NARRATOR] With fighters as
strong as Pikkon in this world,
it looks like Goku has his
work cut out for him.
[GOKU] You should've
seen it, King Kai!
Pikkon knocked Cell
out with one blow!
It was wild!
[KING KAI] Ah. Yes.
I'm sure it was...
[GOKU] C'mon, King Kai,
I'm serious!
[KING KAI] Goku, you'll
soon see Pikkon's strength
is not uncommon.
[KING KAI] Knock knock!
Anybody home?
[MAN] Greetings, King Kai!
It is good to see you!
This is our newest
student, Goku!
[ALL] Hello!
Goku, these are warriors
from the North Quadrant.
Keep your ears open and
you'll learn a great deal.
[KING KAI] Migoren here fought
off an army of evil invaders
about 7,000 years ago.
Sarte bravely protected his
planet from meteorites
3,600 years ago.
And, there's this guy.
Olibu.
He's from Earth like you!
This is the guy who most of your
heroic legends are based on!
As well as a few cartoons.
[KING KAI laughs]
[KING KAI] And I could go on!
All of them were righteous
martial artists in life.
And here in Other World,
they're all working on their
10,000 years of hard training.
That will earn them
a private lesson
from the Grand Kai himself.
Huuh?!
Are you telling me that everyone
has to train for that long
before he'll instruct them?!
Well, yeah! You have to show
that you're perfectly qualified
or else you'd just be
wasting the Grand Kai's time.
I guess...
[KING KAI laughs]
Did you think you could
just knock on his door?!
[KING KAI laughs]
[VOICES]
D-E-A-D! D-E-A-D!
Oh my gosh, it
cannot be!
D-E-A-D! North Kai
is really dead!
--We found a halo on his head!
--[KING KAI screams]
And only one thing can be SAID!
Congratulations!
You're really...
[ALL]
Dead!
Cut it out already! Just exactly
how did they get in on this?!
I called them of course!
You know, none of us have
ever seen a dead Kai before!
Not ever!
And so now...
we'll have a big party!
Leave me alone!
Who are those people getting
King Kai all worked up?
Those are his counterparts.
The tall one is South Kai...
And she's East Kai...
Wait, now how many of these
Kai's are there again?
Only these...
Well, at least on their level
Think of it as a ladder.
On the bottom rung
is all of space...
Higher up is Hell
and then Snake Way...
At the next level are
the planet's of the four Kais,
who oversee their
parts of the Universe.
And higher still, above
the four Kais and all the rest
is the Grand Kai's planet.
Ohh... I see.
And that's where we are right?
Funny, I never knew this
the whole time I was alive!
Well, I never knew there
was anything past the Earth.
There's just no denying it,
you're one dead Kai!
Mind your own business,
you nosy old hag!
[EAST KAI] You take that back!
--I am NOT nosy!
--[WEST KAI] Hey! Knock it off!
A reunion's
no time for arguments!
This is the first
time we four Kais
have been together
in 300 years.
So, we should prove which
one of us is better
with a Martial Arts Competition.
[KAIS]
A tournament?!
An Other World Tournament.
I think that's just a
killer idea, West Kai!
Hah! Why, thank you, sir!
And, to make things exciting,
I'll throw in a
free private lesson
to whomever brings
home the gold, baby.
[FIGHTERS gasp]
You mean... the winner
of the tournament...
...gets a lesson...
...from you?!
Hey, that sure beats training
for ten thousand
years, doesn't it?
A great chance indeed.
Like a dream...
[FIGHTER 1] Let's hear it
for the Grand Kai!
[FIGHTERS cheer]
Wow, the last tournament
was so long ago...
Okay! Follow the leader!
[FIGHTERS mumble]
[GRAND KAI hums]
[GRAND KAI] Oh yeah,
turnin', baby.
[GRAND KAI hums]
[GRAND KAI] Aaaaaand stop!
[GRAND KAI] Now, I've done
a little redecorating,
so watch the wet paint, y'all.
[GOKU gasps]
[OLIBU gasps]
[GRAND KAI] So, be honest
now, whatcha think?
It's great!
[WEST KAI] Perfect for fighting!
[SOUTH KAI] Indeed.
Oh! Wow! This tournament's
gonna be amazing!
I just can't wait to start
fighting in this place!
What'd you say, boy?!
You think you'll fight?!
Well, of course!
This is a serious
bout, young man!
It is not for rookies!
Can it, East Kai!
If you'd open your eyes for a
second instead of your mouth,
you'd see Goku's plenty
strong for this tournament!
[EAST KAI] Hmm... Mm-hmm...
Guess I have no choice but to
test your "qualifications."
Whu...?
If I lose in a race against you,
then I'll approve
your participation.
There she goes again...
Indeed...
We can't take her
anywhere these days
without her finding some
excuse to go racing.
[GRAND KAI] Let's see it.
It's bound to be more
interesting
than watching you four bicker.
[engine revving]
[EAST KAI moans]
Hear that engine?
[EAST KAI laughs]
Oh, please win, Goku.
That woman irritates
the whiskers off of me.
[GOKU gulps]
First one to pass through
the archway wins.
Ready?
♪ Ready! ♪
Go, go, Goku! Beat her!
Now on your mark...
Set...
[gun fires]
[FIGHTERS scream]
[EAST KAI] Yoo-hoo!
Ya-hoo!
[EAST KAI giggles]
[GOKU screams]
[EAST KAI] Huuh...?
[GOKU chuckles]
[thinking] The boy's got more
spunk in him than I thought.
[EAST KAI giggles]
[EAST KAI] I'll just have to
throw her into...
hyper speed!
[GOKU yelps]
--[EAST KAI laughs]
--[KING KAI gasps]
Come on, Goku,
win one for the team!
[GRAND KAI]
It's gonna be close one...
[EAST KAI laughs]
Hey! Get off my tail!
[BOTH gasp]
The Archway! I'm going to win!
[brakes screeching]
[BOTH gasp]
Ha-ha!
But, the...!
Grand Kai!
[GRAND KAI] You both
ran a very good race.
But the winner is...
Oh, I knew it!
Myself.
What does that mean?!
We all agree I got here first.
And by the rules,
that means I win.
Yes, but...
You didn't even tell me you were
going to be a part of this race!
Well, you didn't even
bother to ask me.
[GRAND KAI laughs]
[crowd roaring]
The Kai's sure have
done a stupendous job
whipping this old arena
back into shape.
[EAST KAI] We must win!
Or you'll all be grounded!
[SOUTH KAI] Remember
what we've talked about.
Slow and steady!
[WEST KAI] They're all
wasting their breath.
You're going to make us
champions, Pikkon!
[PIKKON] Yes, of course.
Pikkon is fighting in it too?!
Yeah!
It's gonna be great!
This tournament will
be much more intense
than anything you
experienced while alive!
You must be very careful!
Sure.
[MUSHROOM MC] Ladies, gentlemen,
and everything in-between!
The Other World Tournament
will now begin!
In celebration of the
North Kai's death!
We'll start off our festivities
with a word from the
Grand Kai himself!
You should fight fair.
And I want you all
to fight clean.
But above all,
fight like you mean it
and give us
something to cheer for!
[FIGHTERS &amp; CROWD cheer]
Thank you, Grand Kai!
Now I'll explain the rules
of the tournament!
Each quadrant submits
four contenders.
They will be pitted
against each other
in accordance to the draw
sheet that you see here.
The last person
standing advances.
If you fall from the ring,
start to cry,
or give up,
you lose the match.
And poking in the eyes,
orr hitting below the belt are
plain mean and are not allowed!
Needless to say, you can't kill
anybody in this tournament.
'Cause...
--They're already dead!
--[CROWD cheers]
--Now...
let's get this
crazy show on the road!
There's big prizes at stake!
The winner will receive
bragging rights, a gold medal,
and a special private
lesson from the Grand Kai!
Can't the winner
get a good pastry
or something else instead?
Don't you be silly!
[MUSHROOM MC]
Who here wants to win?
--[FIGHTERS] Me!
--[CROWD cheers]
[MUSHROOM MC] Who's wants
a lesson from the Grand Kai?
--[FIGHTERS] Me!
--[CROWD cheers]
[MUSHROOM MC] Are you SURE?!
--[FIGHTERS] Yeah!
--[CROWD cheers]
Then let's get started
with today's first match!
Fighting first for
the North Quadrant
will be the heroic Olibu!
And against him,
from the East Quadrant,
our good friend Chapuchai!
Don't fret about his size!
Attack his foot!
Do your best, Olibu!
The East Quadrant fighters
are all known for their speed!
Stay on your toes!
[gong crash]
[OLIBU growls]
[CHAPUCHAI screams]
[grunting]
[MUSHROOM MC] And the
Other World Tournament
is off to an electric start!
Wow! Chapuchai is
moving so quickly
it appears there are
seven of him in the ring!
You've gotta think!
[CHAPUCHAIS] Haah!
[CHAPUCHAIS grunt]
Oh! What a spectacle!
The copies Chapuchai
made of himself
have actually all collided
with each other!
[CROWD cheers]
Mysterious...
[gong crash]
[grunting]
[grunting, laughing]
[yelling, grunting]
[gong crash]
[yelling]
[grunts]
[CROWD cheers]
[MUSHROOM MC] Next up
in the arena are Goku,
the newest face from the
North Quadrant, and Caterpy,
a long time favorite from
the south side of space!
This should
be interesting!
[gong crash]
[CATERPY chuckles]
[GOKU] Huh?
[CATERPY growls]
Don't look into his eyes!
[CATERPY shouts]
[GOKU yells]
Darn it!
[CATERPY laughs]
You can't escape me now!
Goku!
[CATERPY laughs]
--[GOKU laughs]
--[CATERPY] Goochy-goochy-goo!
--[laughing continues]
--[KING KAI groans]
[GOKU laughs]
Caterpy is giving
Goku the tickle torture!
Could he be any cheaper?!
Yeah, how do you like that,
little man?! Goochy-goo!
Just give up!
Say you give up!
[GOKU laughs]
[KING KAI whimers]
South Quadrant must be a
very peaceful place...
[laughing continues]
--[CATERPY] Yeah! Say give up!
--[GOKU] O-Oh, man!
--It's the only way!
--[GOKU laughs]
--Tickle, tickle!
--No, please--!
[GOKU laughs]
[GOKU] I... don't... give up!
[GOKU growls]
[CATERPY grunts]
[CATERPY groans]
Uhh... Gee, guy...
You're not very strong...
You... meanie!
Picking on me like that!
You're...
gonna be sorry!
[GOKU yells]
[CATERPY sobs] He hit me!
But aren't you supposed
to fight in a fight?
[GOKU gasps]
What a development!
Caterpy's begun his
metamorphosis!
[FIGHTERS gasp, mumble]
What's... he doing?!
He's become a pupa.
In time he will change
into his ultimate form!
Pardon me, South Kai,
but may I just ask you
how much time
this metamorphosis
of his is gonna take?
[SOUTH KAI coughs]
I'd say somewhere in the
neighborhood
of about twelve hundred years...
[ALL gasp]
Ahh... I don't think I can
wait THAT long to finish this!
Yeah... Well, neither can I.
So Goku wins this
round by default!
[FIGHTERS &amp; CROWD cheer]
Guess...
They like me...
[cheering continues]
[NARRATOR] And so, the Other
World Tournament has begun...
Can Goku, in his rookie attempt,
punch his way to the final bout?
And what sort of
strange maneuvers
will his next
competitors employ?
Stay tuned for more of the
excitement on Dragon Ball Z!