Run, 17! Now!
[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z,
Piccolo was K.O.'d by Cell
after bravely trying
to prevent the monster
from absorbing Androids
17 and 18 into his being.
Knowing that his friends would
have little hope against Cell
if his deadly
evolution was completed,
Piccolo sacrificed
everything he had
in a daring bid to stop him.
[PICCOLO yells]
[TIEN gasps]
[GOHAN gasps]
[GOKU gasps]
[NARRATOR]
In the face of great adversity,
noble men must
often do noble deeds.
And so it was with
the mighty Piccolo,
who gave everything he had
for the Earth and its people.
But, back at
Kami's Lookout,
not being able
to help Piccolo
was more than Gohan could bear.
[GOHAN] Piccolo
needs me! Let go!
[GOKU] Gohan, listen!
You've got to listen to me!
I know it's not fair!
But we only have one
chance to beat that monster
and we have to play to win!
If we don't, Piccolo's
sacrifice will be in vain!
[GOHAN] But it hurts, Dad.
[GOKU]
I know, Son! I know...
[NARRATOR] It's a dark day
indeed for anyone who hopes
for a peaceful life on Earth...
No! I can't take this anymore!
Forget the plan!
Stay if you want to!
I'm going! Now! Goodbye!
[MR. POPO gasps]
[MR. POPO]
Gohan?! Oh, dear!
There, there, now. It's okay...
Man. Gosh, Dad.
You would've been killed, Son.
So?! Wouldn't that be better
than just sitting around here?!
Piccolo would never turn
his back on you like this, Dad!
[MR. POPO] Gohan?
Your dad is hurting too, son.
He is?
Just as much as you or I.
You must know that, don't you?
[GOHAN] Then why
don't we attack?!
Isn't that better than
just wasting our time up here
and letting that monster
get away with it?!
[GOHAN growls]
Gohan, you're Dad's not
letting Cell get away with it!
He just wants to do what's best!
Piccolo doesn't want you to die
for him. He wants you to live!
So get the training first!
Fight Cell when it's
to your advantage, not his.
--[MR. POPO] Huh?
--[GOHAN] Huh...?
[GOHAN]
Daddy... Wow...
[MR. POPO]
Look at your dad, Gohan!
I know it's hard to believe
but I think it's even harder for
him to wait than it is for you!
[GOHAN] Uh, Dad,
I'm sorry about what I said.
[GOKU] It's okay, Gohan.
I'm sorry that
I knocked you down.
I know how deeply
you care about Piccolo.
I promise, I won't let
his sacrifice be in vain.
[thinking] Come on, Vegeta!
[CELL chuckles]
For some reason,
destroying Piccolo
was especially
satisfying. Indeed!
Now, yes. Android 17.
Come here to me, 17...
So nice of you not to run off.
Tell me, does this seem
oddly familiar to you two,
as if you've been here before?
Of course it does.
It's because
this is your destiny!
We were all drawn here,
as if to a magnet,
to this time, to this place!
This is where the three
of us shall become one!
[CELL growls]
Alright. Let's play.
Here goes nothing!
So you want me?!
Well, here I come!
[ANDROID 17 yells]
[ANDROID 17 growls]
[CELL] Huh?
[BOTH grunt]
[ANDROID 17] Huh...?
[CELL screeches]
[ANDROID 17 gasps]
[CELL growls]
You're not absorbing
me, you freak!
[CELL giggles]
[grunting]
[ANDROID 17 grunts]
[CELL laughs]
[ANDROID 17 screams]
[thinking] Oh no!
It doesn't look like
he'll be able to hold
off Cell for very long!
[BABY TRUNKS babbles]
[babbling continues]
Trunks! Hey! No!
Here, can Mommy have
that?! Why, thank you!
You don't want
this silly thing!
[BABY TRUNKS whines]
Ma... ma!
Aw, gosh! Hey! Wait
a second! I know!
Now where is
that thing?!
Ahh! Here!
Look, Trunks! Do you want to
play with Mama's cell phone?
Good! That a boy!
[BULMA sighs]
Paw... paw?
Oh, yeah! Here!
That's his button, there!
Now listen closely, Trunks.
Your grandpa should come on!
Dad?! It's me, Bulma!
Hey, guess what?
[DR. BRIEF]
Not another conference call!
Yay! Grandpa!
[DR. BRIEF]
Trunks, is that you?
Bulma! Your darn
phone's been busy!
[BULMA] I'm sorry! Trunks has
been talking to his grandpa!
[ROSHI] Bulma! Look around!
Do you see Krillin anywhere?!
He should be on
his way to meet you!
No sign yet!
[ROSHI] He's coming out
to get the remote because
he thinks he can get it
here faster than your jet!
Oh, yeah! Is that so?
I wouldn't mind having a little
race to settle that one!
Hey! Just keep your
eyes peeled! This is serious!
Tien's at the
battlefield as we speak!
And we're not sure,
but we're all fearing
the worst about Piccolo!
[BULMA]
Right! Gotcha!
I'll speed up,
but I'll stay on course
and watch out for Krillin!
Well! Hey, Trunks!
You ready to hit the turbos?
Da, da!
[BULMA] Alright, then!
Here we go!
[ANDROID 17 grunts]
[ANDROID 17 yells]
[CELL] 17... I never planned
on humiliating you like this.
It's a simple merger,
that is all.
Your resistance is
the cause of your pain.
16, perhaps escape is best.
Yes, agreed.
You go, I will stay here.
Huh?
[ANDROID 16]
It is best that way.
You are the one that Cell
is seeking to unite with,
so you are the one
that must leave. Not me.
[ANDROID 18] But, 16,
what will you do here?
I will kill Cell.
This world is a good place.
Cell wishes to destroy it.
I will not let that happen.
[ANDROID 18] Hmm... Huh?!
[ANDROID 18] 16! What
do you think you're doing?!
Come back! You'll be killed!
That does not matter.
Life is good, but living in
fear is not my idea of living.
[ANDROID 16] By the way:
I enjoyed the time
we spent together.
You guys are "cool!"
[TIEN] Wow! It looks
like the big guy
is walking right into it!
He's either extremely strong
or that guy's just plain crazy!
[ANDROID 17 whimpers]
[ANDROID 17 yells]
[ANDROID 17 growls]
Yes, I'd have to say that you're
ripe for the picking, 17.
Unless you have any more
objections, it's dinner time.
Enough of this.
You are mine now. Come.
You... You monster!
You disgust me!
Nothing could be more detestable
than becoming part of you!
Ah! Your words hurt me.
But that's okay!
All that you fail to understand
will now be made clear to you.
[ANDROID 17] It's perfectly
clear what you are,
you insect-looking freak!
Let go of me-- Ahh!
[CELL laughs]
[ANDROID 17 wails]
Welcome home!
[ANDROID 17 yells]
[growling]
[CELL laughs]
I won't... let you... do this!
[laughing continues]
[ANDROID 17] Nooo!
[CELL] Hmm?
[CELL] So, the big one is
more powerful than I thought!
Interesting...
Huh?
16! It's you!
I don't believe it!
How did you manage to
get him off of me?
[ANDROID 16]
I used one of my hard punches.
I find this disturbance
to be refreshing! Oh yes!
Hey, thanks for the help, 16.
But I think you just
made him angry!
I am going to destroy him.
Sure! May I ask how?
According to my calculations,
I am just as strong as Cell.
Huh?!
[ANDROID 16]
Cell, I recommend surrender!
[CELL] What? To a piece
of junk like you?!
[CELL chuckles]
[ANDROID 16 yells]
Wow! The big guy's
holding his own!
[TIEN thinking]
Amazing!
This android could be the
solution to all of our problems!
At least I hope...
[CELL growls]
[ANDROID 16 yells]
[ANDROID 17 gasps]
[TIEN gasps]
[CELL laughs]
Yes, good boy! Sleep,
this won't take long!
[CELL roars]
Now! You die!
[ANDROID 16 chuckles]
[CELL] What?! Impossible!
You should be immobilized!
I pierced your neck! That's
where your neural link is!
[ANDROID 16]
Not in my design!
So! Dr. Gero made
some improvements!
[ANDROID 16] Hmmm.
[ANDROID 16 yells]
[CELL yells]
Huh?
So! You're fast, too. Well then.
This is where I cut out!
[ANDROID 16 grunts]
Now I've got you.
This little altercation has
been stimulating. Thank you.
[BOTH growling]
[CELL yells]
[CELL screams]
[CELL grunts]
[ANDROID 16 growls]
[CELL shouts]
[CELL screams]
[TIEN] Unbelievable!
[CELL wails]
That should put a stop to
your absorbing capabilities.
Now you are like a bee
without a stinger.
[TIEN laughs]
That guy did it! Awesome!
Not exactly!
Your analogy of the bee...
It's not quite accurate.
When bees lose their stingers,
they're gone for good.
The bee dies.
[CELL yells]
[CELl] But when
Cell loses his tail,
well, he just grows
another one!
Since some of Piccolo's cells
comprise my cellular structure,
I, too, have the ability
to regenerate my body!
I love the Nameks.
An amazing race.
I am the best
of every race
all neatly rolled
into one super being!
[CELL cackles]
[NARRATOR] The ominously
confident Cell continues
his bid to assimilate Androids
17 and 18 into his being.
Can the strong,
silent Android 16
rescue his comrades
from this ugly fate?
And what about Tien?
With all three eyes glued
to the battlefield,
does he have a
special plan in mind?!