[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Cell continued his
quest for Android 18.
Hoping to flush her out
from hiding, the vile android
launched a series of blind
attacks on the islands below,
raining down terror on hundreds
of unsuspecting civilians.
He's a monster on a
mission who won't stop
until he gets what he's after.
And now he's after Android 18.
Because once he absorbs her,
Cell will reach his final stage
and become a
pure entity of evil.
[NARRATOR] And back at Kami's
Place,
Vegeta and Trunks completed
their intensive training.
Eager to demonstrate
his new-found abilities,
Vegeta took off to face
Cell on his own.
Trunks followed close behind,
ready at any moment
to back up his father.
Oh good! The fireworks
have already started!
[NARRATOR] While Vegeta prepared
for his confrontation with Cell,
Goku and Gohan
crossed the threshold
into the Hyperbolic
Time Chamber.
If they can endure it, they
will get a year of training
in a single day and become
stronger than ever before.
But is taking a day away
from the pursuit of Cell
a wise decision?
Find out today!
[CELL growls]
Come out now, 18!
You know you can't hide from me!
[CELL grunts]
[ANDROID 18 whimpers]
[ANDROID 18] He's blasting
the islands one-by-one...
You said he wasn't
going to destroy them!
I was wrong.
[SQUIRRELS squeak]
Cell will find us
if we stay here.
We've got to get away!
[ANDROID 18] Ugh... But
you're in no shape to travel.
But he'll see us for
sure if we try to leave now.
Maybe your friends can help us.
[ANDROID 18 gasps]
Cell!
Where are they?
All this time,
I've wasted looking.
I should have been
complete by now.
I will find her.
I did not travel
this far back to fail.
[CELL grunts]
[thinking] Look at all
these destroyed islands!
This must be Cell's handiwork.
I don't know what Kakarot and
the others are so afraid of!
Wait until they see
what I can do!
[TRUNKS gasps]
[thinking] Father's powering up!
He must be even more anxious to
fight Cell than I thought!
[thinking] I can't
let him get away!
[BULMA] Do you think Vegeta
can handle Cell by himself?
I have no idea how powerful
Trunks and Vegeta have become.
But they've got to try
and stop him. If they can...
If Cell gets his way and
manages to absorb Android 18,
there's no telling what kind of
horrors are in store
--for the Earth.
--[TIEN growls]
It's as simple as this:
Cell wins. We lose.
[TIEN growls]
They need our help.
We don't have time
to wait for Goku and Gohan!
Tien you know you're
no match for Cell.
All you have to do
is wait one day.
Then with Goku and Gohan's
help you can crush Cell!
[BABY TRUNKS wails]
[BULMA] There, there,
Baby Trunks, now don't cry.
Everything is going
to be okay. I promise.
[GOHAN] It's so bright!
My hands feel heavy.
And it's so hot.
It's hard to breathe.
[GOKU] It's just me
and you now, Gohan.
Get used to this.
We don't have a choice.
Now, are you sure that
you are ready to train
like Trunks and Vegeta?
Yes, I am. Let's do it.
[GOKU laughs]
You can take that
bed over there.
[GOKU] And most
important of all,
this is where the food is kept.
There's enough here
to last a whole year.
Cool, huh?
Dad, with the way you eat,
I really don't think
that'll be enough!
[GOKU laughs]
[GOKU] This place has
everything we're going to need.
[GOHAN] Yeah I guess the
rest is up to us, right?
That's right! Go look out there.
Then you'll understand why I
couldn't even last a month
in here when I was a kid.
[GOHAN gasps]
[GOHAN] I don't believe it.
How is this possible?
How can this room be floating
in the middle of nowhere?
There's nothing out there.
[GOKU] That's right, Gohan.
It stretches for an eternity.
[GOHAN] But that's impossible.
Curses! Still no sign of
those foolish androids.
They could be hiding underwater
but I doubt they're
smart enough to try that.
Alright, this bores me.
Time to end this little game.
[CELL grunts]
[ANDROID 18 gasps]
[ANDROID 16] No!
Cell would sense your blast.
[CELL growls]
[CELL] Androids!
[CELL yells]
[BOTH grunt]
Cell is at the next island!
Stay still.
Cell is watching carefully
for any movement in the area.
He will not find us if we remain
quiet and stay perfectly still.
[ANDROID 18 growls]
[BOTH grunt]
[CELL growls]
[SQUIRRELS squeak]
[CELL] One island left.
[CELL chuckles]
I've got her!
[CELL laughs]
[ANDROID 18 gasps]
[ANDROID 18] There he is!
Calm down! We cannot be seen!
If you hold your position
we will not be discovered.
Last island. Last chance.
[ANDROID 18 grunts]
[CELL chuckles]
Huh?!
[CELL whimpers]
[VEGETA chuckles]
It's you! Vegeta!
Yes, and you're Cell. Hello.
[ANDROID 18]
Who is that with Cell?
Vegeta?!
What are you doing here?
Have you come to protect the
androids from being absorbed?
How noble!
That's not why I'm here.
I've come to tell you.
Your time is up.
[CELL chuckles]
I see. Is that right?
[VEGETA chuckles]
[CELL chuckles]
Come on.
[VEGETA] I find it hard to
believe that my cells
are in your body.
How could you have turned
out so ugly? What a waste!
Although, it's obvious
where you've gotten
most of your strength.
You should consider it
an honor to be part of me.
I am the strongest
in the universe.
[VEGETA laughs]
[VEGETA]
That's where you're wrong.
I am the strongest
and I will prove it!
Just look at me!
I have changed!
[ANDROID 18]
Is Vegeta challenging Cell?
He barely survived
the battle we fought.
Now he thinks he can just
defeat Cell on his own?
[CELL] I don't believe
you are as powerful
as you think you are.
[VEGETA chuckles]
[CELL gasps]
[TRUNKS] I hope this
isn't a private party.
Is that you, Trunks?
It appears you have been
through some changes as well.
Aah! So I guess it's two
Saiyans for the price of one.
Will your other friends
be joining us too?
[VEGETA] There will be
no more interruptions.
And he's only here
to watch the fight!
I don't need reinforcements.
Just you? That won't
be much of a challenge.
[VEGETA] For me? Absolutely not!
[CELL chuckles]
Very well.
I must say I am impressed
by your determination.
I agree with Cell.
Vegeta is no match for him.
He has no chance!
What are you thinking, 16?
Don't you think now would
be a good time to escape?
16, I'm talking to you!
Wait, stay here until
they start fighting, 18.
Vegeta has changed.
His power has grown since
the last time you fought.
He just may have a chance.
What? How?
How could he have
changed that much, so quickly?
Was he just toying
around with me?
Do you really think
he might beat Cell?
Are you ready now
to witness a power not seen
for thousands of years?
[CELL chuckles]
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA yells]
All right.
[yelling continues]
[PICCOLO gasps]
[PICCOLO] Can you sense
Vegeta's energy, Tien?
It's growing!
And now... we wait!
No, I can't wait.
Vegeta can't beat Cell alone.
[PICCOLO] Let him try.
He's determined to
prove himself to all of us.
Vegeta! It's your turn!
Now show us what a pure
blooded Saiyan can really do!
[GOKU] Don't let the vastness of
this place get to you, Gohan.
[GOHAN] Where does it end?
and... and where does it begin?
[GOKU] Gohan!
I don't want you to go out
there without me, okay?
You could get lost
and never get back.
Yeah, okay.
[GOKU] The temperature
can change fast.
The air gets denser
the deeper you go
and the gravity is
ten times that of Earth's.
It's not a very safe place
to be by yourself.
We'll be here for a year
so we have to make sure
we don't get separated.
Oh! Wow!
A year in this place?
Gohan, this isn't
going to be a holiday.
We came here to train.
[GOHAN grunts]
[GOKU] Oh yeah!
Watch that first step.
It's a doozy.
Huh...?
I know this is your first time
training under this gravity.
It's tough! But trust me,
you'll get used to it.
Listen, Son, you are going
to become a Super Saiyan.
[GOHAN] Me a Super Saiyan?
Yes!
Wow! Really? You mean,
you think I really can?
[GOKU] In time!
But you have to take this
training very seriously.
Of course, we'll take
it one step at a time.
When you're ready,
you'll move to the next level.
But it's not going to be easy.
[GOHAN] I understand,
but how hard will it be?
[GOKU] It'll be the toughest
thing you've ever done.
[GOKU chuckles]
Hey, you're my son.
I know that you'll
be able to do it.
And don't forget,
you're a descendant
of the Saiyan race too.
I want you to do the
best that you can!
And no matter what, I'll always
be proud of you. Understand?
Sure, Dad.
--Good.
--[GOHAN chuckles]
[GOKU] Then we're gonna try
to reach a power level
higher than Super Saiyan.
That is the only thing that
matters to us in this place.
Gohan, I want you to train hard
and become stronger than me.
Wha--?! What?
Me stronger than you?!
[GOKU] That's right!
That's what I want to see.
And I think we can
do it together.
[GOHAN] I hope you're right.
But Dad? Trunks said
that I eventually become
a Super Saiyan in the future
and the androids still get me!
Do you think that
prediction will still come true?
[GOKU] That's nonsense, Gohan.
The future has changed a
lot since Trunks said that.
I was supposed to get
sick and kick the bucket.
But look, I'm still here
so you can't believe
everything Trunks has said.
Things have changed.
Oh yeah!
It's all up to us, now!
Okay! Let's do it!
Right. Gohan,
you should know
I'm a stricter teacher
than Piccolo!
Think you can handle it?
Yeah, sure!
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA yells]
Huh? What's this?
His energy's still growing!
[CELL gasps]
--[ANDROID 16 gasps]
--[ANDROID 18] Incredible!
Look! Vegeta is transforming.
Where did he get
this kind of power?
[VEGETA snarls]
[VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA growls]
[growling continues]
[CELL whimpers]
{VEGETA yells]
The training did work after all.
Vegeta is transforming!
[BULMA] What's going on?
It's Vegeta and Trunks, right?
Something's happened hasn't it?
Whoa! That's a lot of power!
[thinking] He did it!
He's ascended!
[VEGETA growls]
[CELL whimpers]
[VEGETA chuckles]
[VEGETA growls]
[CELL grunts]
[NARRATOR] Vegeta puts
his training to the test
and delivers a power punch!
But will it be the final
blow that puts an end
to Cell's deadly rampage?
Stay tuned for scenes from the
next episode of Dragon Ball Z!