[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball Z,
Goku said a few quick goodbyes
and then used his Instant
Transmission to zap himself
and the exploding Cell
away from planet Earth.
[NARRATOR] Teleporting Cell
to King Kai's planet
before the monster
self-destructed,
Goku managed to save the
Earth from certain doom...
at the cost of his own life.
[NARRATOR] It was a
heartbreaking scene for Gohan,
who had to watch
his father vanish
because of his own missed
chance at finishing Cell.
[GOHAN] Daddy!
[NARRATOR] But Goku and Gohan
were not the only father and son
split apart by Cell's rampage.
[NARRATOR] Stealing Trunk's
life with a deadly blast,
Cell made his horrific
reentrance onto Earth!
Somehow he had survived!
[NARRATOR] And with
sparks of pure energy
shooting from his body,
it was clear that the
genetically engineered killer
was stronger than ever before!
[NARRATOR] This apparent
power-up, however,
did nothing to stop the enraged
Vegeta from assaulting Cell.
Yet, despite his newfound
passion to avenge his son,
the Saiyan Prince could
do little against the enemy
And Cell prepared to add Vegeta
to his long list of the slain.
[NARRATOR] Now it was
Gohan's turn once again,
as he threw himself
in front of the blast.
The noble move saved Vegeta,
but left one arm lifeless
and his energy
severely docked.
[NARRATOR] With Gohan badly
injured and Cell turbocharged,
is there any way
for our heroes to win?
The battle's end
is drawing near!
[CELL] I will live forever!
[CELL  laughs]
This place has
been good to me.
But all my
feasting here is done.
[CELL] And I'd hate to leave
without first cleaning my plate!
Soon it'll be nothing
but a cloud of dust!
[thinking]
I can't stop him!
I can't!
He's come back so strong!
Dad, I'm sorry.
It's my fault it's come to this.
'Cause I didn't kill
him quickly, like you said.
Just like it's my fault, Dad,
that you're not
here with me anymore!
[LIONEL whimpers]
[whimpering continues]
It's a trick!
Fancy trick!
[ANNOUNCER] Cell has
turned on his monster beam!
And strong winds
are shooting out!
It's like a typhoon!
Or a wind tunnel!
Or a typhoon in a wind tunnel!
Wait a second!
This isn't my mic!
Who am I talking to?
Aaaahh!
[VEGETA grunts]
I've... become completely
useless on this battlefield!
I'm making a total
mockery of my Saiyan race!
I'm sorry, Gohan. I am...
[thinking]
Sorry?
I never thought
I'd hear that from Vegeta.
He must be saying that since he
knows there's nothing we can do.
Ohh... Please, Gohan....
[PICCOLO screams]
Darn it!
If I only had more power!
[GOHAN gasps]
[GOHAN growls]
What is it, Dende?
It's Cell!
Why does his energy feel
so frightening, Mr. Popo?
It's evil.
That's why.
Gohan...
Elder Moori! Tell us!
What in the world is
happening out there?
It's coming from that planet
where Dende is guardian!
Isn't it?!
Will that horrible
power destroy it, sir?
[CELL chuckles]
Ultimate perfection!
I have spent
decades waiting for it.
And I thought after
absorbing the androids
my game had been won!
But now, only now, do I
understand what Dr. Gero meant
by those words
"ultimate perfection!"
[CELL laughs]
[thunder cracking]
[keyboard clicking,
computer beeping]
Doctor. Don't you know you're
going to type your life away?
[DR. GERO] Well,
that's my choice to make!
[ANDROID 18] If you're
bent on killing Goku,
I assure you we
can take care of that.
[ANDROID 17] Look at this, 18.
Careful!
Those are the blueprints
for my ultimate android!
Ultimate android?
I'm standing right here!
[DR. GERO] Idiot!
You won't even tread water
against what I'm creating!
Because, unlike you, he won't
rely on gears or computer chips.
He'll be purely bio-mechanical.
Now unless you want
me to push the button again,
go back to your
capsules and sleep.
[ANDROID 17 grunts]
[DR. GERO screams]
You will see...!
Some day, he...
will swallow you up!
And then... you will become a
part of his ultimate perfection!
Cocky, for a dead man.
You know, it's kind of cute.
And to think, it's
supposed to eat us.
Dr. Gero must have gone mad.
I would hate to disturb
your sleep little guy,
but this lab has
got to go. Bad memories.
I've got to get
some new clothes
to celebrate our
freedom from this place!
[CELL] Dr. Gero died
and his lab laid in ruins,
but my chamber stayed intact,
and my growth continued under
the computer's careful eye.
Even the doctor's
voice stayed with me,
his pre-recorded
messages instructing me
in my test-tube womb.
[DR. GERO] You are my
ultimate achievement...
[CELL] And after many years,
my cultivation was complete.
I made my first
steps onto hard ground.
[CELL] It was glorious!
[CELL growling]
[CELL] But the world I emerged
into was a dead one,
almost completely destroyed
by the android pair.
I sucked up what
little life I could find,
gaining strength
from their bio-extract.
Of course, it wasn't enough.
I needed the Androids,
whom I learned had
been killed by Trunks!
But thanks to
his own time machine,
I was able to travel back
to when the Androids
were still alive.
[CELL] Fitting inside
the time machine
meant regressing
into my larval state.
And it was a long process
to gain back my mature form.
[CELL] But patience was one
lesson my experiences
had taught me.
Waiting, after all,
is a small price
to pay for perfection.
It wasn't long before
Android 17 was mine.
And I got my first big
step towards being complete!
[CELL cackles]
[CELL] You can't possibly
understand what's it's like
to taste perfection
on your lips!
After that, nothing
could have kept me
from absorbing 18 and
becoming complete.
As always, it was
only a matter of time.
[ANDROID 18 screams]
[CELL yells]
[CELL] And in that
sudden moment,
following years
and years of waiting,
everything had changed!
The Androids
had been absorbed,
and I underwent the
incredible transformation
that had filled
every corner of my mind
since my days
in that tiny chamber.
[CELl] My muscles bulged,
I could feel every
tendon tightening,
changing, filling
with indescribable energy!
It was all I'd ever expected!
And yet, with it came
a strange sense of emptiness.
It seemed all of my
obstacles had been shattered.
And there was
nothing left to do.
[CELL] The Universe is said
to have begun with a bang.
How appropriate!
For now an explosion has
given me the power to finish it.
And it is all because of the
attack you made against me.
[CELL] Now I realize the
true genius of my design!
[CELL] Like Piccolo,
I can fully regenerate
as long as my core remains.
Like the Saiyans,
my power increases greatly
after I heal from near-death.
And like Frieza,
I can survive anywhere.
I thought Dr. Gero only meant
for me to defeat the Earth,
but I know now I was
designed for much more.
Once I'm finished tearing
this world into pieces,
I'll just use Goku's
Instant Transmission technique
to move on to other planets.
[CELL growls]
[CELL] That is my destiny!
I am the Universe's end!
[ANDROID 18 grunts]
Please!
Isn't there any
way out of all this?
[PICCOLO screams]
We've done too
much for this world
for it all to end this way!
[CELL laughs]
Forget the Earth,
I can destroy the entire
solar system with my energy now!
Now Cell's secret
monster beam is glowing!
[ANNOUNCER screams]
All hope for humanity
is lost! We know that!
But how is he doing all this?!
Trick! It's a trick!
Has to be!
[screaming]
[MAN] This way! Hurry!
[GIRL wails]
[screaming continues]
[horns honking]
What's happening out there?!
Earth's shaking!
TV has no picture!
Gohan! Gohan!
Show me Gohan!
Chichi! You've got
to keep your cool now, okay?
How in the world
can I keep cool?!
He's my baby!
Gohan! Gohan! Gohan!
[OX-KING] ChiChi! Stop!
[FORTUNETELLER BABA]
ChiChi! Are you home?
Could that be--?
Fortuneteller Baba!
Ah, ChiChi, Good thing
I caught you.
I figured you'd want to
see how your son was doing,
since the newscasters
have managed
to mess things up as usual.
[CHICHI sighs]
Crystal Ball, start to glow!
Let these people see the show--
Hurry up!
I have to see!
[FORUNETELLER BABA chants]
[FORTENETELLER BABA] Look deep,
deep, into the ball.
Crystal ball, show them all.
I am Baba, hear my spell.
Show the fight
of Gohan and Cell...
of Gohan and Cell!
Faster!
Hey! Watch it!
Gohan?
Oh, you look so
scared out there!
Gohan! What's
wrong with your arm?
[OX-KING] ChiChi!
Gohan...
What's wrong, Gohan?
Aren't you going
to try and stop me now?
[CELL laughs]
What's the point?
I know I've lost my
one chance to beat you.
Now all of us will die
together and be with my dad.
How boring!
I expected the end to
be a little more dramatic,
but if this is all I get there's
no use in dragging in out.
[thinking] So this is it.
This is how it ends.
[GOKU] You've got to be joking!
Giving up already?
Well, that's nothing
like the Gohan I know!
[GOHAN gasps]
Da-Dad!
Where are you?
The Other World!
And thanks to King Kai,
I can communicate
with you telepathically!
[KING KAI growls]
[BUBBLES gibbers]
I know you have the
power to beat him, Gohan.
I've sensed it all along!
Now... Give him the biggest
Kamehameha you've got!
I know you can do this,
Gohan, I promise.
No, Dad!
I can't even use
one of my arms anymore!
And my energy's
been cut in half!
Hey! Who the heck's
he talking to?
Look! He's been driven
insane by his own fear!
[GOKU] Remember what you
learned in our training,
and trust yourself!
It may feel like
Cell weakened you,
but really, what's draining
your strength is your own doubt.
Just don't listen to it, okay?
Okay, it's all starting
to become clear now, Dad.
I've got one arm left,
but that's all I need!
And don't even think
about feeling sorry for me
because King Kai and I
couldn't be having any more
fun up here if we tried!
Speak for yourself,
home-wrecker!
But Dad, it's-it's my fault you
died cause I got carried away!
If I had only finished
Cell off sooner, I--
Hey!
Who knows what
would've happened!
For all we know, what you
did was the best move!
Sometimes life's just
too uncertain to have regrets!
Yeah, but--
If you want to blame
anyone for this, blame Cell!
Make him pay for what he's done!
I will!
[CELL gasps]
Gohan...
He's finally ready to face him.
Kaa...
Meeh...
Haa...
Ahh! Now that's more like it!
[CELL growls]
[GOHAN grunts]
Dende, is something wrong?
Oh no, it's very right.
[CHICHI whimpers]
[CHICHI] Oh, Gohan...
[ANNOUNCER yells]
[ALL grunting, whimpering]
[CELL laughs]
[CELL growls]
Meeh...!
Now... you... die!
[GOHAN] HAA!
[screaming continues]
[NARRATOR]
At the last instant,
Gohan has decided to fight!
He has his father's strength.
He even has his
attack technique.
But has Gohan inherited
that most important trait?
Has Gohan become... a hero?