[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
the Royal Military
set out to vanquish Cell
with good,
old-fashioned fire power.
Guns ready!
[NARRATOR] But if there's
anything the people of Earth
should have learned by now,
it's that you can't
destroy super-villains
with normal military muscle.
[NARRATOR] And after letting
the soldiers have their fun,
the devilish Android arranged
for some amusement of his own.
[CELL] Judging from your silence
I'd say it's my turn now.
[NARRATOR] And all the while,
Goku listened helplessly
through the radio.
[GOKU] Cell, no!
[SOLDIERS screaming]
[NARRATOR] With quick,
horrid precision,
Cell turned the battlefield
into a graveyard.
[NARRATOR]
It was a massacre
that the soft-hearted
Goku couldn't bear.
Determined to bring
Cell's victims back to life,
Goku announced a wild plan:
Bring back the Dragon Balls!
Hoping to recruit
a new guardian
from the survivors of Namek,
Goku called on
King Kai for help.
Does this goofy teacher know
the location of the Nameks?
Find out today!
Goku?
[GOHAN] Hello, Master Roshi?
[ROSHI] Oh, hello, Gohan!
You've gotten so big!
[KRILLIN sighs]
I'm afraid Goku won't be
joining us today, Master Roshi.
He ran off and
left us in the car!
Of course, none
of us know how to drive!
I'm just glad
the roads were clear!
[KING FURRY] Dear citizens!
This afternoon
the Royal Military,
despite valiant
heroics of countless men,
suffered massive losses
at the hands of the
tyrannous creature Cell.
My heart weeps for these men.
But please know that these
soldiers fought bravely
to the very end,
and will always be remembered
and honored by the great nation
for which they
laid down their lives!
With utmost honesty I do
not know what more can be done.
But I must ask
you to remain strong.
My friends, a difficult
road lies ahead.
All we can do is pray...
Oh, wow, guys...
It's really happening.
An android?
Well, that's a new one!
And you say he's
even stronger than Frieza?
Must be hard for you
to get good life insurance!
Trouble follows you
like a lost puppy.
Yeah! And that's why
it's so very important
that I find a new
guardian for the Earth!
All I need from you is the
location of the Nameks!
Well... Uh...
If you could at least point
me in their general direction
I would really
appreciate the help!
--[BUBBLES babbles]
--[KING KAI growls]
Alright, I'll take a look!
[BUBBLES babbles]
[GOKU] Do you think you'll
find them? I hope so!
Mr. Popo is looking pretty
lonely now that Kami's gone...
And you know,
I don't blame him.
Yeah, that place is... huge!
And it's pretty quiet when
you're there all by yourself!
I remember this one
time, Kami went on vaca--
Be quiet!
I'm trying to concentrate!
[KING KAI screams]
--Huh?!
--[screaming continues]
--♪ A, B, C, D ♪
--[GOKU groans]
[GREGORY giggles]
Can't you be serious?
[KING KAI laughs]
Sorry 'bout that!
Huh...?
Pack your suitcase!
I think I've found 'em!
Look, there!
Really? Great!
Now let's see...
It didn't work last time,
but if I know which way
to look, then maybe I can--
I see! Instant Transmission!
The Yardrat's trick!
Oooh! I bet they taught you that
while you were staying
with them, didn't they?
Didn't they? Didn't they?
You know, I've always thought
it had some handy uses!
I could've taught you!
But you never asked me!
You're making this hard!
Ha ha! I'll be quiet.
There we go! I got it!
Wow, I can't believe
I missed it earlier!
It was so obvious!
Oh well, thanks
for the help I guess!
[NAMEKS gasping]
A stranger!
[gasping]
Wow! Look at all the Piccolos!
[MOORI growls]
Elder, be careful!
Are you friend or foe?
Umm, friend. See I've
come from the planet Earth.
My name is Goku and
I was just wondering--
Ah! Then you must be
the Great Saiyan Goku!
The one who saved
our people from Frieza!
--[gasping]
--[GOKU laughs]
The way I way I remember it,
Namek still blew up!
Well, Goku, it seems your
planet is the one in danger now.
You mean you already know about
the android that's attacking us?
Not in such detail,
but we could sense
the incredibly
destructive energy
that has been
released on your planet.
[GOKU] Good, then I won't
have to explain much.
The source of the energy
is an android named Cell.
He's destroyed
many lives on Earth,
and we need the Dragon Balls
to reverse what he's done!
Makes sense, right?
[NEMEKS] Right!
The problem is,
all of our Dragon Balls
are gone because our
guardian fused with Piccolo.
Piccolo! Ah, you mean the
Namek who Nail is fused with?
Yeah, I guess so.
Now, I was hoping
that one of you guys
would come and be
our new guardian!
[gasping]
Earth? No thanks!
I know, we do have
one person here
who would love to be
your new guardian.
Oh! Really?
[gasping]
Yes, Dende!
Come here, my child.
Yes, yes sir!
This one, his name is Dende
and he's very good friends
with Krillin
and your son Gohan.
Oh, hey!
He's been talking about
the Earth ever since.
He misses Gohan
very much,
and I think he'd
really like to see him.
That'd be great, except, will
he be able to do the job?
Oh, of course!
Dende may be young
but he's exceptionally gifted.
He'll be a wonderful guardian.
Well then, you're hired!
Glad to meet you!
Thank you! I'm glad too!
So, are you ready to get going?
[DENDE gasps]
[GOKU laughs]
[NAMEKS murmur]
Thanks a lot!
We'll take good care
of Dende from now on.
I give you my word!
Bye, everyone!
Bye, Dende!
Be a good guardian, Dende.
Goku, we shall keep
your home in our thoughts.
Good!. Thank you.
[NAMEKS gasp]
[BUBBLES babbles]
Hey, King Kai!
I made it to the Namek's planet
and everything worked
out great okay! Gotta go!
Hey, look who I brought
home for dinner, everybody!
Huh? Dende?!
Is he our new guardian?
Yep!
Are you sure it's not too
much for him? He's just a boy!
Hey, don't worry!
Now just sit tight,
I'm going to go pay
a visit to Krillin and Gohan.
[ANNOUNCER] Hey, folks, I've
just heard some incredible news!
It's the great Mr. Satan!
He's just announced
he'll be fighting in the
World Martial Arts
Tournament
against that wicked
monster Cell!
[cheering]
Now here's our man!
Hercule Satan!
[cheering continues]
[MR. SATAN yells]
[MR. SATAN roars]
What's with the goofball?
He's the world champion
of martial arts.
Aren't you worried,
Mr. Satan? Even a little?
Cell destroyed the entire
Royal Military with his power!
What do you have to say to that?
[MR. SATAN chuckles]
This was all just a cheap trick!
Cell planted bombs just
before the Military came.
He might be an
expert with explosives,
but as you can see, from
a Martial Arts standpoint,
he's an amateur!
And I, Hercule, the greatest
fighter in the world,
will crush that fake
with my little finger!
Now, yell if you love me!
[CROWD cheers]
[KRILLIN sighs]
Man\, that guy's a real moron!
[ALL gasp]
Now where on Earth
have you been, Goku?!
Do you think I know
how to drive?!
[GOKU] I'm sorry, ChiChi,
but if I could just talk to
Krillin and Gohan for a minute,
there's someone at the
lookout who'd like to see them!
[GOHAN] Who is it, Dad?
[KRILLIN] Is this person,
uh, friendly?
[GOKU laughs] Come on!
[DENDE gasps] Krillin!
Gohan! You're here!
Dende! It's you!
Ha-ha!
[DENDE giggles]
--[GOHAN &amp; DENDE laugh]
--It's been so long!
Sure is good to see you, Dende!
[GOHAN] So is it true you're
gonna take over Kami's position?
[DENDE] I think!
Guardian of Earth! Wow!
That's one heck of a title!
Now we can see
each other every day!
Yeah!
[PICCOLO] Now, Dende!
Are you
absolutely certain
you're ready to handle
the Dragon Balls?
Lighten up, Piccolo. After all,
the old guy told me that Dende
was one of the most talented
Nameks on their planet!
Old guy?
He's talking
about our Elder Moori.
That's right!
That old guy said Dende had
everything it takes to make
a good guardian for Earth!
I'm pretty sure
I should be able to make
new Dragon Balls
within 100 days!
Oh no! We... really
can't wait that long!
[KRILLIN groans]
[DENDE sighs]
Hold on, if you still
have the old Dragon Balls
and the model
of the Dragon,
then I should be able
to do it right away!
Alright!
The old Dragon Balls are
scattered across the Earth,
changed into stone!
And yes, the Dragon
Model's in my room!
Awesome!
Let's cook this dragon up!
Yeah!
Oh, hey, Dende,
what about wishes?
Can you make it grant
three just like on Namek?
Sure!
What about its power?
This isn't Namek,
and with three wishes
the Dragon might be weakened!
Now think, can you
make it bring back
all those killed
by Cell with one wish?
[DENDE gasps]
Well, all I have to do is
re-channel some of its energy
into its wishing power,
but that way it can only
grant two wishes each time.
Wow! You can really do all that?
Uh-huh!
Good enough, make
the dragon like that.
Yes, I'll try.
So, should I start?
[PICCOLO] Mr. Popo,
bring us the model please.
[MR. POPO] Yes.
[MR. POPO] Here we are.
Careful, I made
this dragon myself.
[DENDE] What an
interesting shape.
Okay, I guess I'll begin.
Good luck, Dende!
[KRILLIN] Yeah! We're
behind ya all the way!
Hey, thanks!
[DENDE chants in Namekian]
[ALL gasp]
[DENDE] It's all done.
The Dragon can
be summoned as soon
as the Dragon Balls
are collected.
Already?
So fast!
[PICCOLO &amp; NAIL thinking]
Good work, Dende!
I always knew you
would be something great.
Now, I'll borrow Bulma's
Dragon Ball Radar
and go collect them right away!
Good luck, Goku.
Yeah, thanks!
Hey, Gohan, why
don't you stay here
and have fun with Dende
until the tournament begins?
Uh, are you sure?
I'm positive,
just have a good time!
[TRUNKS] Goku! Uh, can
I ask you one thing?
What's that?
It's because you've discovered
some sort of weak point to Cell
that you're acting so calm
and confident, isn't it?
Well, I'm afraid Cell
doesn't have a weak point.
Alright, see you later!
Goku! You really do just pop
in and out of places, don't you?
You should take a look
at the circuits on this guy!
Dr. Gero was a genius.
Huh. Well, Bulma,
I'm kinda in a hurry.
See, I got the Earth
some new Dragon Balls
and I was hoping I could
borrow your radar for a while?
Oh, sure!
The radar should be right
there in the second drawer.
Gee, thanks!
Great! Seems to be working!
I should be able to find the
Dragon Balls in no time at all!
Well, see ya!
Hey, Goku!
Huh! Oh well!
I was just going to ask him
how Trunks is doing up there,
but... I'm sure he's fine!
Must be close!
Alright, it's right here!
Huh! Well?
[GOKU chuckles]
I don't see it...
Gohan, did your
father tell you anything?
We've all heard Goku say that
Cell is stronger than he is
and that Cell has no weaknesses.
So why is he acting so cheerful?
I've asked my dad and he
hasn't told me anything.
All he says is, "Don't worry".
"Don't worry"?
I don't know. I mean,
if that's what he said,
maybe he really does
have some plan to defeat Cell.
Or maybe he's in denial...
What's up?
It says it's here, but it's not!
[MAN] Hey! You there!
Hey! Watch out!
There's a sandstorm coming!
Better shut your eyes!
[GOKU] ...Ohhh!
Of course! These heavy winds
must have buried
the Dragon Ball
underneath the sand!
Thank you!
Now!
Here goes nothin!
[GOKU yells]
This one's bad! I feel
sorry for that guy!
[MAN gasps]
Aw yeah! I can't believe Dende
really brought them back!
[NARRATOR] The Dragon Balls
have been restored...
But the clock
continues to tick,
with each fighter
passing the time
in their own way.
[NARRATOR] Some train...
--[GOHAN] So that's what we did.
--[NARRATOR] Some talk...
[KRILLIN] So, you're
always a Super Saiyan?
[GOHAN] Except for
when I sleep.
[NARRATOR] And others
seek to make sense
out of the days
that lie ahead.
[birds chirping,
wings flapping]
[elephants trumpet]
[GOKU mumbles]
[GOKU screams]
Only five more.
[NARRATOR] And alone
on the battleground,
the mighty Cell is waiting.
How boring, I should not
have given them this long.