[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Vegeta powered up
to face the monstrous Cell,
who had finally
reached his perfect form.
[NARRATOR] It was a battle
neither fighter could resist,
as both Vegeta and Cell were
anxious to test the extent of
their newfound powers.
[NARRATOR] But as
the fight progressed,
it quickly became clear that
Cell was merely
playing with the Saiyan,
a realization that made
Vegeta angrier than ever!
[NARRATOR] But try as he might,
Vegeta couldn't even make the
Android powerhouse flinch.
[NARRATOR] Vegeta's attacks
proved ineffective
against Cell's awesome power,
and our heroes couldn't help
but ask themselves
an important question:
Who would be next?
[NARRATOR] Has Vegeta's thirst
for a challenge backfired?
By allowing Cell to
absorb Android 18,
has the Super Saiyan
sealed his own fate?
[CELL chuckles]
[NARRATOR] Vegeta's
pride is on the line.
Will his gamble pay off?
Find out today!
I cannot believe it.
Vegeta dealt him a
direct blow to the head,
yet Cell was not
affected in the least.
[ANDROID 16] Perhaps it is true.
Perhaps there is no
limit to Cell's power.
[CELL] What seems
to be the problem?
[CELL] Cat got your tongue?
Im... possible...
[CELL chuckles]
I put all my energy
into that kick!
[CELL] So Vegeta,
do you understand now
what I mean by perfection?
[CELL] Hmm...?
Or shall I educate you further?
[VEGETA grunts]
[VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA shouts]
[growling]
[KRILLIN] Whoa...
We are in deep trouble.
[TRUNKS thinking] Father,
what have you done?!
[VEGETA gasps]
Now look.
You spent all that time saying
I wouldn't be a challenge,
and now you're giving
up without a good fight?
That's very rude.
[KRILLIN thinking]
That arrogant monster!
[TRUNKS thinking]
Just you wait, Cell.
If it's a good fight you want,
then it's a good
fight you'll get!
[TRUNKS grunts]
C'mon, Trunks, what
are you waiting for?!
If you take any more time,
Vegeta's gonna be fish food!
It's now or never, bro...
Vegeta may get mad,
but at least he'll stay alive!
Wait!
I can't do anything
to help him until the moment
he loses consciousness.
That way, he won't find out
that I've become even
stronger than he is.
Forget his pride!
But I can't!
Huh?!
I don't think you realize how
much honor means to my father...
It's the only thing
that keeps him going...
It's what makes him a warrior...
Oh, sure, some might see
it as arrogance, but I think,
down at the core, it's
much more noble than that.
I believe that's what
my mother saw in him...
and it's what I see, too.
I didn't know...
[TRUNKS] How could you?
Well... for your sake
I hope he passes out soon.
Vegeta... I hate to
interrupt your little nap,
but I think it's time
we should continue.
[VEGETA] Why... you...
But first, there's one
thing I'd like to mention...
I must thank you for sparing
me before I became complete,
regardless of how
utterly foolish it was.
You see, I've been waiting
for this for a long time,
and it's always nice
to receive a helping hand.
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL] Ah-ah-ahhh!
Don't even think about it 16.
If you value what's
left of your head
I suggest you stay
right where you are.
[VEGETA snarls]
[VEGETA yells]
[yelling continues]
Ahh... Father!
What does he...
What does he think he's doing?!
[VEGETA yells]
[yelling continues]
[CELL chuckles]
[ANDROID 16 grunts]
Don't... do it!
[VEGETA] Cell!
Once again, you have taken
for granted the powers
of a true
Saiyan warrior!
[CELL chuckles]
Now, if you really
want to test your strength,
stay right where you are!
So that's what he's doing!
He's trying to provoke Cell
into challenging his attack!
Okay, that's one explanation!
How about this one:
Vegeta's lost his mind
and he's gonna fry us all!
[CELL chuckles]
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA chuckles]
You're going to destroy
the whole planet, Father!
You've got to stop it!
Trunks, let's go!
Final Flash!
[CELL gasps]
What's this?!
[ANDROID 16 screams]
[GOHAN growls]
[GOHAN] Yaah!
[GOKU] Yes! Lunch time!
I'm starving!
Let's see what we've got in
here. Oh yeah, that looks good!
Ooohh, and a little of
that... and this for sure...
Gohan loves this!
Alright!
[GOHAN growls]
[GOKU] Go-han!
Come and get it!
'Kay!
[GOKU] It's time
to load up, Son.
And remember,
a true Super Saiyan
eats everything on
his plate, got it?
Right!
Oh, and could you
grill this for me?
Hii-yaah!
Ahh, yeah!
...Huh?
Uh... Dad... your hair...
Now what did I tell you
about controlling your power?
I know...
But, Dad, your hair is on...
[GOKU] Don't change the subject
Gohan, you've got to learn to--
--Ahh! Ahh! Put it out!
--[GOHAN] I told you, Dad!
--Put it out! Whoa!
--Hold still!
Ahhh! That was a close one!
Father knew what
he was doing all along.
He focused his blast
only on Cell!
[VEGETA pants]
There. Did you like that?
[CELL growls]
[growling continues]
[VEGETA chuckles]
I'll take that as a yes...
You... You actually hit me!
[VEGETA chuckles]
[laughing]
He... did it!
He really whooped Cell big time!
Yeah!
[CELL grunts]
Look at this! You maimed me!
[VEGETA laughs]
Stop laughing!
[VEGETA cackles]
You're a fool.
Have you already forgotten that
Piccolo's regenerative cells
are a part of me?
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL grunts]
[yelling]
Are you impressed?
[BOTH whimper]
Nooo...
[CELL] Well, shall we continue
from where we left off?
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA shouts]
[CELL chuckles]
[VEGETA growls]
No!
[VEGETA shouting]
[shouting continues]
[VEGETA gasps]
[VEGETA grunts]
[VEGETA yells]
[KRILLIN grunts]
[VEGETA grunting]
[KRILLIN gasps]
[TRUNKS gasps]
[VEGETA screams]
Oh no! Look! He's not
a Super Saiyan anymore!
Which means... he's either
unconscious... or he's...
Well, you know...
[CELL laughs]
Now, Vegeta, I will end
your miserable life.
Alright! This is it, Trunks!
If you still plan
on saving Vegeta
you better not
wait any longer!
[TRUNKS growls]
[KRILLIN gasps]
What...?
Uh, Trunks?
[TRUNKS roars]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[TRUNKS growls]
[KRILLIN yells]
[CELL] Thank you for
the warm-up, Vegeta.
Your petty efforts were
just enough to get me started.
[CELL] Hmm...?
[TRUNKS growls]
[CELL gasps]
[NARRATOR] With Vegeta
down for the count,
Trunks is finally ready
to unleash his true power.
But can the young Saiyan
hold off Cell long enough
to save his
father's life?
Find out next time,
on Dragon Ball Z!