[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z...
After returning
from Other World,
Goku raced away from the
Lookout, on the Flying Nimbus,
to join his friends
on the battlefield.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, Piccolo,
Gohan, and Krillin
put their training and
skills to the test
as they fought desperately
against Nappa and Vegeta,
two Saiyans bent on
conquering the Earth...
But their combined strength was
no match for the evil pair.
[GOHAN]
Piccolo, we need you!
[NAPPA laughs]
[GOHAN whimpers]
[NARRATOR] While the
others watched in vain
for news of the battle,
the Saiyans continued
their ruthless conquest,
as Nappa unleashed the full
force of his rage on Gohan.
You...
I'll kill you! Ahh!
[GOHAN whimpers]
[NARRATOR] Is this
the end for Gohan?
Find out next
on Dragon Ball Z!
[NAPPA yelling]
[GOHAN screaming]
[PICCOLO growling]
[NAPPA yelling]
Hurgh!
[PICCOLO shouting]
[KRILLIN grunting]
[NAPPA panting]
[chuckling]
[GOHAN whimpering]
Huhn?!
[PICCOLO panting]
P-Piccolo?
It's okay, kid.
No sweat! Heh, heh, ha...
[GOHAN whimpering]
[GOHAN] No! You can't be hurt,
Piccolo, you just can't!
We need you!
I'm... I'm not
gonna make it...
It's up to you...
[PICCOLO]
You must stop them!
[GOHAN] Piccolo! Hold on
just a little longer!
My Dad's coming! He'll
save us! Just hold on!
Aww, too bad. I wanted to
take my time with the Namek!
Oh well, I can still
have fun with the kid...
[thinking]
Something's not right...
One of the big power
levels is fading fast...
They're in trouble!
Hang on, Gohan! I'm coming!
[KAMI grunting]
Kami! What is it?
[KAMI] Piccolo's life force
is fading away,
and mine along
with it.
Goku must not have
gotten there in time.
When we cease
to exist,
so will the Dragon
Balls of this world.
But, legend tells
of others on Namek.
Find them! Use them
to wish us back!
[MR. POPO]
Wait! Kami! Please!
Don't leave me!
[PICCOLO]
It's ironic, isn't it?
After all my years of
training to defeat your father,
I'd go out like this...
Trying to save you, his son.
Piccolo?
Gohan... You're the
only real friend
that I've ever had.
I want to thank you...
[GOHAN] Just hold
on a little longer!
[PICCOLO] I still remember the
first day I brought you here.
You were small,
helpless...
You've changed
so much since then.
[PICCOLO] The harder things got,
the more determined you became.
The more dangers
you faced,
the stronger you
grew as a warrior...
[PICCOLO] I know
I was hard on you,
but it was for
your own good...
You're like the son I never
had. I'm proud of you...
[GOHAN] No! Please!
Good-bye, my friend...
Noo!
Goodbye, Popo!
Remember...
[MR. POPO] Kami!
Kaammii!
[KRILLIN]
Gohan...
[GOHAN screaming]
Huh?!
Huh?! Alright!
Let's go!
Masenko!
Huh?!
Gohan?
[GOHAN grunting]
[VEGETA] That runt's power
level is over two thousand!
Hold on...
It's over three thousand!
Nappa, watch out!
This one is much more
powerful than he appears!
Here I come, boy!
Haa!
Raagh!
[NAPPA panting]
[GOHAN whimpering]
Oh man!
Hey, not too bad, kid...
That made my arm numb!
[NAPPA laughing]
Alright, then...
It's my turn!
Ah, that one shot must have
drained all of his energy.
His power level has
returned to normal...
They're... too strong!
We just can't stop them!
[KRILLIN growling]
[CHICHI] Let go of me!
[OX KING] I can't let you go,
ChiChi! It's too dangerous!
[CHICHI] I've got
to help them!
[OOLONG] I've got her!
[CHICHI]
Gohan needs me!
[ROSHI] Hold on, Oolong!
I'm coming!
[BULMA]
Somebody stop her!
Nice to see
you, too!
[ALL] It's Baba!
[BABA] I've come to tell
you that Goku has returned
and will soon join
the others in battle!
You mean...
He's really back?
[thinking] Goku...
Thank goodness.
I know! Let's see how
things are going out there
by looking into
Baba's crystal ball!
You swine! This
isn't a television!
My crystal
ball is sacred!
[CHICHI] Grab it!
[BULMA] Come on,
Oolong, hurry!
Don't worry, Piccolo...
I won't let you down!
[NAPPA chuckling]
Gohan! Run away! Hurry!
Ha ha! That's right,
run away and hide!
No way...
Piccolo's counting on me.
[NAPPA laughing]
Gohan! No!
Nice knowin' ya, kid!
There'll always be a
soft spot at the bottom
of my boot for ya!
Ha ha, so long!
Huh?!
Rrgh!
Hnn. Huh? Huh?!
Huh?! Hrghh...
[NAPPA] Hey! Where did
that thing come from?
Huh? Nimbus?
How did he...?
What the..?
Hnn?!
[NAPPA] What is that thing?
What's going on?
Huh?!
Aah! Daddy!
It's... Goku!
Welcome, Kakarot.
Nice of you to join us!
[VEGETA laughing]
[VEGETA] Well, I was
beginning to think
you weren't
going to show up,
especially after your little
family reunion with Raditz.
Did you two have
fun catching up?
Goku...
You're here!
My Dad's back!
I see... Not much for
words, eh, Kakarot?
Well, you're
just in time!
We were getting
tired of beating on
these so-called fighters over
and over again. What a joke!
Piccolo...
[GOHAN] He was protecting me...
He saved me!
[GOKU] Tien...
Yamcha...
[NAPPA laughing]
Oh, were these guys friends
of yours? Sorry about that...
They were fun to
fight for a while,
but they all met the
same fate in the end...
[NAPPA laughing]
Yeah, that's right...
I took care of them all!
Well... except for
that little guy.
He decided to
blow himself up.
[GOKU growling]
And the whole time I
was pounding them,
they were waiting
for you to show up!
Somehow they knew you were
coming, but it didn't matter.
You were too late!
[NAPPA laughing]
[VEGETA] Hmm...
Kakarot's power level
is increasing!
They were weak...
Just like you are!
Weak and not
worth my time...
Hraah!
Huh? Hunh?!
[thinking] He's fast!
[GOKU]
Come on, Gohan...
[GOKU] Hey, Krillin!
Are you alright?
Fantastic!
I was a little late.
Sorry... But it's okay now.
Oh, I almost forgot! Special
delivery from Korin. Here...
[KRILLIN] Wow! A Senzu Bean!
I sure am glad to see that!
[GOKU] This was
his last one...
[KRILLIN] Whoa!
Wait a minute!
Maybe you should
keep it then...
[GOKU] Nah, I've already had
one for myself, Krillin.
This one's
for you!
I'd be wasting it!
You'll need it, if
you're gonna try
and take down both
of these guys...
It's your help that
I might need...
That's the truth,
Krillin, I promise!
Here, take half...
Thanks, Goku...
[GOKU] The other half's
for you, Gohan...
[KRILLIN] We gotta learn
how to grow those beans!
[GOKU] Krillin, you've gotten
a lot stronger. I can feel it.
Yeah, I was doing great
until the fighting started!
We've all improved!
Thanks to Kami, of course!
But, man... I guess...
It just wasn't enough!
Hey, Gohan, you
look stronger, too!
I can tell you've
been training hard!
Mm-hm. Piccolo's been taking
care of me. He was great!
And he taught me
so many things...
Now he's gone... and it's...
it's up to us to bring him back.
I don't know how we can
do it, but we have to.
We just have
to, Dad!
[GOKU]
We will, son, we will.
But first, we have to focus
on taking these guys down,
once and for all!
[GOHAN whimpering]
You're right,
Goku! Man!
It's not over yet!
Hey! With your
increased strength,
and us back
at full power,
we should have a pretty good
chance of beating those jerks!
Right! But you've
done your part.
Maybe it's best if the two of
you sit this one out.
This time, I think
I'm gonna take them
on all by myself...
Goku, you can't!
See that big
guy over there?
He beat every last one of us
without even breaking a sweat!
The only chance we have
is to stick together!
He's right, Dad! That
guy... He's really strong!
[GOKU growling]
[KRILLIN] Oh, wow! Goku?
Amazing!
[GOHAN]
No, Dad! Don't!
[KRILLIN] Wait, Gohan!
Just let him go!
[GOHAN] Come back! Please!
I've never seen him
like this, Gohan.
He's different somehow...
I...I think we should just
do what he says...
[GOKU] This has gone
on long enough...
[GOKU] It ends, right
here, right now...
[NAPPA chuckling]
[BABA] Look deep,
deep into my crystal ball!
Crystal ball, show them all,
what they want to see...
their friends and family!
[BULMA] Look! Something's
happening! Is that...
[ROSHI] Could it be...
[OX KING] It's Goku!
[CHICHI gasping]
Go-ku...
[OOLONG] Look!
Krillin! And Gohan!
Gohan! My baby!
He's all right!
ChiChi! Are you okay,
dear? What a day...
Goku! Tear them up!
Come on! Knock 'em out!
Piccolo!
If Piccolo's gone...
That means...
Kami's gone as well!
And the Dragon Balls!
They're gone, too!
That means we...
can't wish them back?
Mmm...
[BULMA] Oh, Goku...
Be careful.
Come on, I haven't
got all day!
I wanna see what the
great Kakarot's made of!
Ha! You want me?
You got me!
[GOKU snarling]
[GOKU yelling]
All that's
from... my Dad?
Power level's... 8,000.
How? Wait! It's over nine!
[GOKU yelling]
Vegeta! What did you
say his power level is?
It's over 9000!
9000? There's no way
that could be right! It can't!
Don't be so sure...
I'll have you know I was
trained in the art of Kaio-Ken!
Huh? Kaio-Ken?
Kaio-whatever!
Who cares?
I'm still
gonna crush you!
I don't care
what you've learned!
Raagh!
Augh!
Whoa! How did
he do that?
You... You'll pay for
that... You'll... pay!
We'll see... But I haven't
even warmed up yet...
What? Why you little...
That was luck!
I'm the second strongest
Saiyan in the universe!
[GOKU] Heh. Well, if your
friend is stronger than you,
then I'd say that makes
you the third strongest!
Heh... heh heh...
Kakarot... I'm gonna
rip you apart!
Hyaah!
Huuh! Hyah hyah hyah!
[NAPPA's shouting continues]
It's strange... Just a year
ago he couldn't beat Raditz
and now he's making
sport of Nappa...
Haahh!
Hah? Huh? Hunh?!
[GOKU] Over here!
Ha?! Haah?!
[NAPPA growling]
[KRILLIN] Wow... Did you see
how your father did that?!
Uh... Nuh-uh...
Did you?
[NAPPA] I'll get my hands
on you! And when I do...
[NAPPA growling]
[thinking] I've never
heard of anyone
increasing their power level
that much in one year!
What?!
[NAPPA growling]
Raagh!
[NAPPA grunting]
That's for my friends,
all four of them!
[NARRATOR] Will Goku's
increased level of power
be enough to
stop the Saiyans?
Find out next time,
on Dragon Ball Z!