[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Vegeta reduced Android 19
to scrap metal.
The advanced,
robotic humanoid
with artificial intelligence
was no match
for the Super Saiyan Prince.
Even the superior Android 20
model decided to run for cover
rather than fight
Vegeta head on.
[NARRATOR] Suddenly it was no
longer a battle of raw strength
but a tactical game
of hide and seek.
[VEGETA] Darn!
How could I?!
A mistake like that
is inexcusable!
[NARRATOR] Lurking just above,
but unable to be sensed,
was the crafty Android 20.
[ANDROID 20 chuckles]
His frustration
is apparent.
He's no longer the cool,
confident fighter
that he was before.
[NARRATOR] Though
outmatched in strength,
the diabolical Android 20
decided to stalk the others
and quietly take what he
needed from them.
[NARRATOR] Unaware
that the deadly predator
was watching them, Gohan,
Tien, Krillin and Piccolo
continued their search.
Little did they know, they were
walking right into an ambush.
I will steal the energy from
these pathetic fools one by one!
Then Vegeta is mine!
[ANDROID 20 chuckles]
[NARRATOR] Stay tuned...
[thinking] Ahh... So many
victims to choose from.
Hmmm...
Hmm...
[ANDROID 20 chuckles]
Hm?
[GOHAN gasps]
[GOHAN] Oh, so
it's you guys, huh?
Oh, man! I'm too tense...
[thinking] Where
the heck did he go?!
Oh, man...
With my luck, I'll be
the one that finds him.
Just watch...
[KRILLIN] Huh?!
[KRILLIN screams]
[KRILLIN] Oops...
[KRILLIN sighs]
Man! Someone's going to get
hurt if I'm not careful!
Uhh, namely me...
I'm really on edge.
I'd rather just fight
and get it over with!
This is nerve racking!
[PICCOLO] Hmm?
Fools. Look at them all.
Who shall I choose first?
[ANDROID 20 chuckles]
[ANDROID 20] Piccolo is the
strongest next to Vegeta!
Perfect! He is
definitely the one.
Ah, yes, victory
will soon be mine!
Hmm! This should give
me all the energy I need.
[PICCOLO growls]
All right...
He doesn't need food or water;
he could hide out here for days!
[PICCOLO grunts]
[ANDROID 20 chuckles]
Well, Piccolo, it seems
that you have found me.
[PICCOLO grunts]
[ANDROID 20 chuckles]
[ANDROID 20] It is
pointless to resist.
You are already
too weak to stop me.
[ANDROID 20 chuckles]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[PICCOLO using ESP] Gohan,
I need your help, come quick!
[PICCOLO using ESP]
Gohan, it's me! Hurry!
The android has me!
[GOHAN gasps]
Right! But where...?
[PICCOLO grunts]
[ANDROID 20 chuckles]
Huh?!
There's a big power
fading rapidly over there!
It's got to be him!
[ANDROID 20] Ah, yes!
This is invigorating!
We should have done this sooner!
[PICCOLO grunts,
ANDROID 20 laughs]
[ANDROID 20] Oh, my! Feeling
a little sluggish, I see.
It is almost over!
--[ANDROID 20 laughs]
--[GOHAN grunts]
[ANDROID 20 groans]
--Huh?!
--Hnn?
Uh?!
[ANDROID 20 grunts]
[hat clanks]
[ANDROID 20 groans]
Huh?!
Thanks, Gohan!
You saved my life!
[ANDROID 20] Rrrgh! Pest!
He found me! But how?
[ANDROID 20] Huh?!
[ANDROID 20 gasps]
[ANDROID 20] So! The whole
gang is here! No matter!
I have gathered enough energy
to destroy all of you!
[VEGETA chuckles]
[VEGETA] Get over yourself!
[ANDROID 20 growls]
[PICCOLO growls]
[GOHAN] Krillin! Piccolo
needs a Senzu Bean! Quick!
Right! Here!
[PICCOLO] Thanks, Krillin!
[KRILLIN] Sure!
Don't mention it!
[thinking] Piccolo's energy
has substantially
increased my power. But Vegeta
still may pose a problem!
Well! Shall we start
where we left off?
If I recall, we were about to
fight when you ran away!
[thinking] I still need
to steal more energy
to be assured a victory!
[GOHAN] Piccolo!
[VEGETA growls]
[ANDROID 20] Ah...
[PICCOLO grunts]
[ANDROID 20] Hmm?
[PICCOLO] Stay out
of this one, Vegeta.
I owe him! He's mine!
If he manages to get by me,
then he's all yours!
How does that grab you?
I don't care if you
want to fight him!
I don't even care if you
get yourself killed!
But I do care if he manages to
steal more of your energy
and makes himself
even stronger!
So just keep that in mind while
you're having your little fun!
Got it?!
[PICCOLO] Yeah. I got it.
I'll make sure that
doesn't happen again.
[ANDROID 20 chuckles]
[ANDROID 20 thinking]
Well, I will make sure
that it does happen!
Yes! This is the opportunity
I was looking for!
[ANDROID 20 gasps]
[ANDROID 20 grunts]
Heh.
[KRILLIN] Man!
[GOHAN laughs]
[ANDROID 20 groans]
[ANDROID 20 growls]
[thinking] I allowed myself to
lower my defenses for a moment.
A careless mistake
which I will soon rectify.
Piccolo will not find himself
so lucky a second time!
[PICCOLO growls]
[ANDROID 20 growls]
[ANDROID 20 yells]
Huh?!
[ANDROID 20 growls]
[ANDROID 20] Huh?
[ANDROID 20] Hmm...?
--[PICCOLO growls]
--[ANDROID 20 grunts]
[ANDROID 20 groans]
[ANDROID 20 grunts]
No! What is this?!
Piccolo is classified as
one of the weaker fighters!
My data indicates that I should
be able to defeat him with ease!
How is it possible, then,
that he should cause me
this much difficulty?!
[TRUNKS] What a mess! It
looks like I'm too late!
I should have gone back
a little further!
It's too risky now! The ship
doesn't have enough energy!
I wouldn't be able to
make it back home again!
I'd be stranded in the past!
[TRUNKS growls]
Man! I can't believe
that it's already over,
I thought Goku would
make a difference
against those monsters!
You were my only hope, Goku!
But I guess I was destined
to handle this alone!
Huh?
Wait a second...
I can feel some power
levels over there!
They're huge!
The fight must
still be going on!
Awesome! It's not too late!
There's still a chance!
[ANDROID 20 growls]
[ANDROID 20 grunts]
He's the best! Yeah!
[KRILLIN] Holy cow!
Piccolo has really improved!
What a guy! I'll bet he's
as strong as a Super Saiyan!
Hmph. Right!
[ANDROID 20 growls]
You will die!
[GOKU panting]
[CHICHI] Oh, my gosh!
I can't take this!
What's wrong, Yamcha?!
Why isn't the antidote working?!
It will! Just watch! You'll see!
This prescription came from
twenty years in the future!
Shoot! C'mon! Man...
We're going to miss
all of the action!
Miss all of the action?
Big deal! You're crazy!
Man!
Look, I've been on
the front lines!
Got it?!
And it isn't pretty!
This isn't a T.V. show
we're talking about here!
It's the real thing!
[BULMA] Don't start playing
playing the hero around me!
I know you! If there's a fight
you hide in the bushes!
[YAJIROBE] Who
the heck is that?!
It's that guy! That's him!
Cool! He's back!
[BABY TRUNKS cries]
[YAJIROBE] Whoa! Great!
Now look what you've done,
Bulma! Man! Hurry up!
Please!
[BULMA] Now you're
talking, Yajirobe!
That's the spirit!
With the turbo's we
can make it there
in half the amount of time!
[YAJIROBE] No! Wait!
I didn't mean it!
There they are!
Huh?!
[thinking] No way!
What does it mean?!
--[PICCOLO grunts]
--[ANDROID 20 yells]
[blows landing]
[ANDROID 20 grunts]
--[PICCOLO] Here I am!
--[ANDROID 20 grunts]
[KRILLIN gasps]
[ANDROID 20 growls]
Huh?
[KRILLIN gasps]
He grabbed him!
[GOHAN] No, wait a second!
Piccolo grabbed the grabber!
[ANDROID 20 grunts]
[PICCOLO] You just
can't get enough, can you?!
[ANDROID 20] You are going
to die! Do you hear me?!
Mark my words!
[PICCOLO] You know,
I used to be like you.
One day you'll learn that
the more you hurt others
the harder your life becomes!
It's simple! Your desire
to kill is killing you!
[ANDROID 20 grunts]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[ANDROID 20 whimpers]
It's a darn shame, you could
have put this hand to good use!
What a waste of technology!
[ANDROID 20 growls]
Alright! History has changed!
We're going to make it through
this without losing anyone!
Yes!
[TRUNKS] Oh, boy!
Man! What is this?
I've never seen it before...
This isn't one of the androids
that killed Doctor Gero!
[PICCOLO growls]
[ANDROID 20 grunts]
[ANDROID 20 gasps]
Oh, man! This is mind boggling!
Huh?!
Shoot! I can figure
this out later!
[thinking] Maybe history changed
and it changed the
appearance of the androids!
Either that, or this is
just a first generation
and there are
more on the way!
[ANDROID 20 grunts]
[ANDROID 20 growls]
[ANDROID 20]
I do not understand!
My data indicates
that their abilities
could not have
improved this much!
Your data probababy
would have been accurate
if we hadn't been
warned about your arrival
three years before
you got here!
In other words: We
knew you were coming
so we got all of
our ducks in a row.
[ANDROID 20] Ducks?!
That makes no sense!
What do you mean?!
I mean that we've been
preparing for you, my friend!
[ANDROID 20 growls]
[KRILLIN] Yeah!
Thank goodness for that!
Dying is such a bummer!
[GOHAN] I'll bet!
Yeah, I've been
down that road.
But this time around I
wouldn't mind growing old
and doing it
the natural way.
How about the coup
de grace, Piccolo?
Or do I have to step
in and handle it?!
No! This is my job!
I know if the
tables were turned,
that this guy wouldn't hesitate!
Believe me! No problem!
Huh?!
Huh...?
--Huh?
--Uh?
[KRILLIN] Over there!
Yeah, but who?!
Trunks is back!
[VEGETA gasps]
[thinking] Trunks?! How bizzare!
He has the same name as my son!
Wait a second...
A Super Saiyan
from the future?!
Of course! It has to be!
He's my son! Unbelievable!
[VEGETA gasps]
[TRUNKS] I see it,
but I don't believe it.
[ANDROID 20 growls]
[thinking]
This one's different, too!
[ANDROID 20 growls]
[thinking] Now what?!
Not another one!
I don't have any data
at all on this one!
What is going on here?
[ANDROID 20 growls]
[thinking] The chances for my
survival in this situation
are slim at best.
I have made far too many
errors in my calculations.
It would be wise for me to
return to the lab at once.
Yeah! Even though I've
never seen him before,
I can tell that he's one
of Doctor Gero's creations!
Say what?!
What do you mean you
haven't seen him before?!
Isn't he one of the androids
you warned us about?!
No, this one's different!
What?! How could
he be different?!
[TRUNKS] I'm not sure!
Huh?!
Man, that's not good!
Not at all!
Yeah, no doubt...
[NARRATOR] Once again,
Trunks is the bearer
of a startling
revelation from the future!
But what does it mean?
[VEGETA gasps]
[GOHAN gasps]
[NARRATOR]
How could it be possible
that the horrible androids that
Trunks has been battling
in the future are
completely different
from the androids of today?
Find out on the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!