Aaah!
[NARRATOR] Last time,
on Dragon Ball Z!
Frieza got a bitter
taste of his own attack!
Despite Goku's
attempts to warn him,
the enraged Frieza was cut down
by his own deadly energy disk.
[NARRATOR]
Sliced into pieces,
it seemed like the end
for the fallen tyrant!
Please... have... mercy!
How many people have begged
for their lives at your feet,
and you killed them anyway?
Did you show me mercy
when I asked you
to spare my
best friend Krillin?
[NARRATOR] But as
Frieza pleaded for help,
the pure-hearted
Goku couldn't resist,
giving up some of his last
energy to save Frieza's life.
[yells]
[NARRATOR] As the epic match
draws to a close,
will the battle-worn Goku
have time to escape Namek
before it explodes?
It's a race against the planet,
on thodays episode...
of Dragon Ball Z!
[wheezing]
[grunts]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[FRIEZA] Well, little Saiyan,
since you seem to have
all the answers, tell me this;
what do you suppose I'll do,
with this energy?
You told me you could survive
without any air, didn't you?
Then why don't you
go out into space
and just drift for a while!
That way you'll have
plenty of time
to think about your defeat!
[grunts]
[birds chirping]
[NAMEKIAN CHILDREN laughing]
Yes, all is well...
[heavy inhale, exhale]
[laughing]
[exhales]
[GURU moans softly]
This day, rich with life.
What a wonderful time to die.
No Guru, you can't die!
[VILLAGERS gasp]
Guru, please don't leave us!
[BOTH] Huh?
[VILLAGERS gasp and murmur]
It is time.
Please gather
all the villagers here.
[NAMEKIAN A] Yes, of course!
--[CHILD A] Don't go away, Guru!
--[CHILD B] We love you, Guru!
--[CHILD A] Don't go away!
--[CHILD B] Don't leave!
Oh.. You mustn't
be sad, my children.
I have lived a full
and blessed life!
Don't be afraid...
Death is simply
another stage of our life!
[murmurs]
They're not here!
What? Who's not here?
We've looked everywhere,
and we can't seem to find
anyone from Guru's village!
But, that can't be!
[VEGETA] Are you talking
about those whiny villagers
I defeated?
I believe the Dragon Balls
brought back everyone
who'd been killed
by Frieza or his henchmen.
Isn't that right?
Well that doesn't
include me. How very sad.
[grunts and growls]
Huh?
Ah.. The Dragon Balls have
followed me to this place!
They, too, feel the time
is right for me to go!
[coughing]
Guru, we need you now!
Ah... No. You are all so much
stronger than you realize!
[GURU] It is a tough road ahead,
but we are a race of survivors.
You will make it.
M-Moori.
Uh... yes?
Please.. give me your hand.
[MOORI] Yes..
[VILLAGERS gasp]
You.. are the eldest now.
Please take good care
of all our people!
[GURU] Soon the Dragon
Balls will sparkle again.
Use them, but use them wisely.
Watch over them.
Guard them like children!
Yes. I--I will try!
You.. will do fine...
[VILLAGERS gasp and scream]
Oh, Guru! We'll miss you!
[GURU]
Good-bye, my children!
You made me, so very proud!
[murmurs and sobbing]
He really is gone!
[DENDE] Why?
[sniffs]
You helped me become who I am!
[GOHAN] So could
you please, Mr. Guru?
[GURU] So you're Gohan!
Ahh! Let's take a look!
[coughs]
[GURU] I can feel that you have
truly amazing hidden powers.
The strongest I've ever felt!
Quick, you've gotta help!
It's Vegeta!
He's right outside! Uh--
[quavered breathing]
[DENDE exhales nervously]
[groans]
[yells]
Farewell, Guru. I swear
I won't let you down!
Huh?
[NAIL'S VOICE]
Be strong, Dende!
Nail! I just knew
it was true all along!
Piccolo needed your help,
so you fused with him, right?!
[chuckles]
[laughs]
[MOORI] Listen, all of you!
We must be strong
and work together...
...so we can finally realize
Guru's dream of peace
for all Namekians.
It looks like
they're all gonna be okay.
If only Krillin could
have seen this happen.
Yeah. After all that fighting,
he would've really loved
to see everyone
here at peace again.
Well, why don't you use our
Dragon Balls to wish him back?
Namek's dragon can
revive someone many times.
Hm?
[DENDE] Sure, if it's
not a natural death!
Then... Then...!
We can wish Krillin
back as soon as
the Namek's Dragon Balls
become active again!
And Chiaotzu!
Chiaotzu's the same way!
We can bring him back too!
Oh my gosh, it's just too good!
[laughing]
Okay! Did you catch
all that, Dad?
Now you have to come home,
because it's only right that
you be here when
we bring back Krillin!
[chuckles]
[growls]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
I'm afraid the planet
is about to go boom!
So where do you think
you're going? Hmm?
You know you
can't survive in space!
[chuckles]
Oh, you can run all you want!
But sometimes you have to
meet your problems head on!
Face it, monkey,
you're going to die!
[laughs]
[chuckles]
[FRIEZA] Well aren't you
gonna keep running, monkey?
Aren't ya? [chuckles]
Like a little circus chimp!
Come one, come all!
See the spectacular
chimp and amaze!
Where will he run today?
You don't have enough time
to get back to your space ship,
and Vegeta destroyed mine.
[FRIEZA laughs]
But please, just for my sake,
don't stop running!
It's far too entertaining!
[chuckles]
It's ironic. After all
your heroic efforts...
you're still going to die!
[FRIEZA] And I will live on.
So much for the awesome power
of the legendary Super Saiyan.
Can't even beat a dead planet.
[GOKU] Maybe not. But it was
enough to beat you, Frieza.
[growls, yells]
[GOKU] It's done!
[FRIEZA] What do you mean?
Don't just stand there,
say something!
[GOKU] Your energy is
decreasing with every blow.
You're not even a
challenge to me anymore.
[GOKU] It would be
meaningless to fight you now.
You're too scared and ashamed.
Nothing but a monkey.
[GOKU] You must be Frieza!
The one responsible for
the horrible chain of events
that have taken place
on this planet.
Hm. The proof is in the
pudding, don't you think, huh?
I don't care if you're a million
times stronger than me, Frieza!
Mark my words! I'm not going
to let my friends down!
So get ready, Frieza,
because this time
you're going down!
[GOKU bellows]
[yells]
[GOKU] Kamehame... ha!
[FRIEZA groans]
[GOKU grunts]
[FRIEZA grunts]
[yells]
[FRIEZA] Something is
strange about this warrior!
How does a Saiyan have
such incredible power?
They are, after all,
inferior creatures!
[FRIEZA] I've never
met a fighter with
that kind of strength!
[FRIEZA]
I must take him out now!
Prepare for battle!
It is time...
for your demise!
[heavy breathing]
[grunts]
[FRIEZA] It's all over, Saiyan!
[yells]
[GOKU yells]
Huh?
That's not possible!
[FRIEZA groaning]
[yelling]
[yells]
Th-That's impossible!
You made a direct hit
with your Spirit Bomb
and no one could survive that!
Ah... Mommy...
[quavered exhales]
[growls]
Help me! Aah--
[GOKU grunting]
I... won't let you...
get away... with this...!
[grunts]
[chuckles]
[grunting]
[GOKU continutes grunting]
I won't let you...
[grunting]
[bellows]
What?!
[stammers]
[GOKU grunts]
[FRIEZA groans]
[groans]
[GOKU grunts]
[FRIEZA yells]
[FRIEZA breathes heavily]
You!
It's done!
Uh? What are you saying?
You just said it was done!
What does that mean?
Your energy is decreasing
with every blow!
You're not even
a challenge to me anymore!
[GOKU] It wouldn't be fair
for me to keep fighting you.
I'm satisfied now.
Your pride has been
torn to shreds.
You've challenged and lost to a
fighter who is superior to you,
and to make it worse...
...he was just a monkey, right?
[GOKU] It would be
meaningless to fight you now.
You're too scared and ashamed!
Live with the shock.
Keep it bottled up
inside you... silently.
[FRIEZA grunting]
Poor, stupid Saiyan.
You honestly think you've won.
[FRIEZA] Your puny mind
never could understand.
I am Frieza, the most powerful
being in the Universe!
And you are nothing but
a beast; a fragile animal!
[FRIEZA] You can't win,
because I am mighty!
And you are not!
[grunts]
Now learn...
Learn what happens
when you mess...
[FRIEZA] with the most powerful
being in the Universe!
Huh?
You fool!
[GOKU yells]
[FRIEZA grunts]
[yells]
[FRIEZA screams]
[NARRATOR] With one last blow,
it seems that Frieza
has finally been laid to rest!
Indeed, Goku has
saved the Universe
from Frieza's wicked reign!
[NARRATOR] But with Namek's
explosion only moments away,
can Goku save himself?
Find out on the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!