[NARRATOR] Last time
on DragonBall Z,
Frieza was still
taking shots at Goku.
[NARRATOR] And though
it seemed Goku
was throwing his arms
up in defeat,
he was actually powering up
for the ultimate attack.
[NARRATOR] Taught by King Kai,
this attack called on
the entire Namek
solar system for help,
drawing its energy from every
living organism around.
[GOKU thinking] I know I
shouldn't use the Spirit Bomb.
Its force could wipe
out this entire planet...
[FRIEZA] Pity.
He tries so hard.
[NARRATOR] But in
all his arrogance,
Frieza hasn't realized the
danger of the incoming assault,
thinking the weakened
Goku is merely trying
to delay his own demise.
[KRILLIN gasps]
There... in the sky!
That's the Spirit Bomb!
[NARRATOR] With the fate of
the universe on the line,
could it be the last hope?
Find out, today!
[GOKU grunts weakly]
[weak grunting]
[thinking] What is he doing?
I can't figure him out.
Is he taking a break?
[GOKU thinking] I call upon the
trees and the water, the sun,
the moon and the stars,
the plants and the animals...
All living things...
Let me share your power!
[GINYU] Ribbit... Ribbit...
Tell me,
Mr. Frog,
how strong do you
think Goku really is?
I mean, I know he's
strong and everything,
and that he did learn
from Master Roshi
which does account
for something...
And when he was a kid,
he won every competition
he ever entered.
Goku beat every single person
that tried to take him on.
[GINYU groans]
Do you understand?!
[GINYU croaks]
I guess what I'm saying is
I hope Goku's strong enough
to beat that horrible alien.
Hey, you're a friend of
that freak, aren't you?!
[GINYU growls]
Well, you better tell
your buddy back there
that he better give up before
Goku decides to get serious!
And don't think
I didn't warn you!
[GINYU] Ribbit...
[BULMA] Get going!
You don't have
any time to waste!
Ah, man, look at it!
It gets bigger every second!
I've never seen
anything like it!
[GOHAN] Krillin, do you
think it will keep growing?
[KRILLIN] I'm not sure...
It all depends on
Goku's concentration.
[GOHAN] Ohh!
The ball's around
50 metres in diameter,
which means Goku must
be drawing energy
from other planets as well...
And if that's the case,
there's no telling how big
the Spirit Bomb will become!
Frieza doesn't seem to be
capable of detecting the attack.
So tell me what's taking
Goku so long to use it?
Probably because Goku
doesn't think it's big enough
to defeat Frieza...
At least that's the only
explanation I can think of.
[GOHAN] Oh, please hurry, Dad...
There isn't much time left!
[thinking] Stars in heaven,
give me more power!
One question,
my unworthy opponent:
What do you think you're doing?
Watering your garden?
An interesting way of
spending your last few minutes
before I annihilate you.
[GOKU growls]
[thinking] Drawing in enough
power is taking too long!
I just hope he holds off
for a few more minutes!
Recoome!
Burter!
Jeice!
Guldo!
[GINYU FORCE]
All of us together are...
the one and only Ginyu Force!
Well, I can see that
they're impressed!
[JEICE] I gotta admit our
fighting poses are awesome
no matter how many
times we do them!
Ohhhh!
By the looks of it this place
seems to be a real nice planet.
I think we should make it our
new fighting headquarters.
Now that sounds a plan!
And, using our
superior strength,
we, the Ginyu Force,
will conquer this planet!
Tien...
these guys are idiots!
You can say that again.
And If I'm not mistaken,
wasn't it the Ginyu Force that
took on Vegeta and got beat?
I think you're right!
So, you're friends
with Vegeta's, huh?
That makes things
a little clearer...
We're the Ginyu Force.
The most elite fighting
force in the universe.
Your friend Vegeta was
an insignificant worm
compared to us!
That's right!
We would have beaten
that monkey with one blow
except we ran into
a little bad luck!
[ALL] Hmph.
Yeah, but that's all
ancient history...
Besides, we are here now
and we like this place.
And we are going
to make it our home!
So why don't you make
like a hair and split!
Hey, just who do
you think you are?!
It's you who's going to leave!
[CHIAOTZU] Yeah, get lost!
[GULDO laughs]
Please, don't
make me laugh!
[GULDO laughs]
If they want to fight,
bring it on!
'Cause I believe we all
could use the exercise!
Ohhhh!
Wait a second...
Remember what our
fearless leader said?
"When on a new planet, make sure
that you test your powers first!
Because the
climate might affect
your ability to fight!"
You got a point
there, Recoome.
All right...
[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH laugh]
[YAMCHA] Why, you!
What do ya' think you're doing
blowing up King Kai's stuff?!
Now it's my turn!
[GULDO yells]
[TIEN &amp; YAMCHA gasp]
[yelling continues]
[GULDO yells]
Nicely done!
On a scale of one to
ten, definitely eleven!
[GULDO chuckles sheepishly]
While that was excellent,
Guldo, watch me...
Recooommmee...
Breath Blast Attack!
[YAMCHA &amp; TIEN gasp]
[CHIAOTZU whimpers]
[thinking] Amazing!
There's ten times
the gravity up here!
That's some power!
[JEICE] We don't charge
for the landscaping.
Now, let's hop-to, mates!
[GINYU FORCE laughs]
[TIEN &amp; YAMCHA growl]
[KING KAI] What's
going on out here?!
We have company!
[KING KAI] Hmm...
I have no time
for intruders,
so I suggest you leave!
And I suggest
you do it now!
Oooh...
What a strange fellow?
Hey, Odd-Ball, how would you
like to come andplay with us?!
[KING KAI laughs]
With your
limited powers,
I don't think it would
be a very fair fight...
[RECOOME guffaws]
Oh, you're making
a joke, huh?
Well, then, why
don't you try me
and figure it out for yourself?
Rrgh... Okay!
[KING KAI gasps]
[thinking] It's Goku is using
the Spirit Bomb Attack!
When are you going
to quit stalling?
My patience is growing thin.
[GOKU] Almost.. . there...
Frieza...!
[GOKU chuckles]
Why, you
insolent little...
[FRIEZA yells]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU groans]
Oh no! Frieza knows!
Don't think so!
Not yet...
What seems to
be the problem?
Or have you finally
decided to give up?
[GOKU chuckles weakly]
[FRIEZA growls]
How dare you ignore me!
[GOKU chuckles]
[FRIEZA snarls]
[blows landing,
GOKU grunting]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN gasp]
[GOKU] Just... a little bit...
longer...
So, have you
had enough?
[GOKU chuckles]
[FRIEZA growls]
[blows landing,
GOKU grunts]
Goku's not
fighting back!
Dad, please! C'mon!
[PICCOLO growls]
Gohan! Krillin!
We have to surrender
our powers to Goku!
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN] Huh?
[PICCOLO] Give me your hands!
[GOHAN] Here...
[blows landing,
GOKU grunts]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU laughs]
[GOKU] Could ya
lighten up a little bit?
You want me
to lighten up?
Well how about this?!
[GOKU gasps]
[GOKU screams]
[screaming continues]
[GOHAN gasps]
[PICCOLO] C'mon!
You've got to concentrate!
Concentrate!
There is one thing
that truly agitates me...
And this may sound strange...
I never could
quite understand
your pathetic Saiyan mind.
But that really
doesn't matter now.
I have no interest in your
trivial little thoughts.
I only want to rid myself
of you once and for all.
And after I'm all finished
"playing" with you...
I will take care
of your bratty son,
and then the Universe
will be rid of your kind!
Hah! Super Saiyan!
Don't make me laugh!
[FRIEZA giggles]
[FRIEZA gasps]
[FRIEZA] What's that...?
That's not the sun...
Need... more time...
Oh no!
What is that up there?!
It's some kind of
enormous ball of energy...
HUH?!
[thinking] He created it!
[PICCOLO] That should do it!
We don't want to give up
all our energy...
Frieza knows about
Goku's attack...
Gohan!
Krillin!
You stay put and don't move!
I've got some unfinished
business to take care of!
[FRIEZA] So that's what he's
been up to all this time!
Collecting energy
into one giant ball!
But where did he
get so much power?!
[thinking] Okay, Frieza,
turn and run for it!
C'mon, get moving
before I use it!
Oh no, he's not taking the bait!
He must know it's
not strong enough yet!
Oh, man...
Oh, I get it.
That ball is your idea
of a clever diversion.
Well I hate to ruin
your little "game",
but your trump card
won't work on me!
[FRIEZA laughs]
[GOKU growls]
Say good night...
[GOKU gasps]
[PICCOLO thinking] Oh no!
Ka-boom.
Huh--
[FRIEZA grunts]
Piccolo?!
Goku...
You must hurry and
finish collecting energy
for your attack!
Yeah, you got it!
[GOKU growls]
[PICCOLO] C'mon you've
got to hurry up!
That attack used up all the
power I had left in me!
[GOKU] I'm trying!
[FRIEZA growls]
I spy with my
little eye...
one pitiable Namek who got away!
I think it's time to exterminate
this chubby little insect, huh?
[GINYU FORCE] Yeah!
Wait!
All right, boys, show
them what you've got!
What d'ya mean by that?!
Get ready for
a real fight!
Tien...
[NARRATOR] Is there time for
Goku to gather enough energy
for his Spirit Bomb Attack?
Or will Frieza stop
our hero in his tracks?
Find out on the next
exciting episode...
of Dragon Ball Z!