[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Cell left Trunks with
an unusual announcement.
The android plans to revive the
World Martial Arts Tournament.
With his body and
ego badly bruised,
the young Saiyan
returned to his friends
to bear the ominous message.
Word of the
tournament was greeted
with shock and suspicion.
Who could trust a seemingly
unbeatable android that is bent
on destroying the world?
[ROSHI] Okay, but I am!
Only I can beat Cell.
[NARRATOR] There is
little time to prepare,
so the fighters
better make it count.
Because if Cell gets his way...
these days just
might be their last.
[NARRATOR] The competition
is set to begin in 10 days,
but Cell has yet to
reveal the location
of his terrifying tournament.
He's been busy carving
up the landscape,
building the
perfect battleground
to put his enemies to rest...
[NARRATOR] Cell is
ready to go public
with the location
of his tournament.
But the question is, will he
be playing by his own rules?
[CELL] Yes, that
will do just fine,
it should be large enough.
And now, to get the word out.
[COMPUTER] Diagnostic
scan initiated.
[COMPUTER] Subject in position.
[DR. BRIEF] Hm? Now let's
see what we've got here.
Interesting... Hm...
A most unusual design...
[DR. BRIEF] Hm... I wonder
what this device does?
[DR. BRIEF] I can't make
sense of these plans!
Oh... they're upside down.
No, no, that's not right... Hmm?
This is strange. Based on what
I can gather from these plans,
I'd say your device is
completely different
from the other Androids.
Yes, very interesting...
[COMPUTER] Diagnostic complete.
Terminating program.
I was designed to be
a perfect machine.
Yes I know. That means...
these plans are useless.
So... can you fix me?
I don't know if I can. But just
wait till Bulma gets back.
She knows a great deal
more about you than I do.
[ANDROID 16] Hmm...?
[SCRATCH meows]
[SCRATCH purrs]
[DR. BRIEF gasps]
[OOLONG] Yowza! That's tasty!
[OOLONG smacks]
Aah!
Maam, this is great
cake. Thank you.
I'm glad. There's a lot more,
so everyone help
themselves, alright.
[OOLONG] Oh boy, I'll have
that big chocolate cake please.
Hold it! I had my eye on that!
You pig!
[OOLONG] Oooh! Chocolate!
--[ROSHI gasps]
--[OOLONG chuckles]
Ah, you snooze,
you lose, old man!
[ROSHI] I'll show you!
Watch this!
[ROSHI chuckles]
[ROSHI] You see, I always
have my cake and eat it too!
Don't touch that Oolong, or all
you'll get is a pie in the face!
[thinking] Note to self:
These two are a definitely
a bad influence on Gohan.
--[ROSHI] Wow, it's delicious!
--[MRS. BRIEF laughs]
Gimme some o' that!
[ROSHI laughs]
[OOLONG] Ooh, and I'm
gonna have me some o' this!
[OOLONG &amp; ROSHI yelling]
Wow... they don't
seem to be worried at all.
It's over Marsha.
Happy! Happy! Happy!
Stay tuned for the news.
--[ROSHI] You can't have that!
--[OOLONG] You bit my finger!
[yelling incoherently]
[REPORTER] It's been
a slow news day...
Traffic seems to be moving at a
steady pace and there have been
no other problems
reported in the city.
Stay tuned for more news and
information after this program.
[thinking] Cell!
I know you're out there!
Where are you hiding?
Show yourself!
Hey, Trunks...
Cell said that we
should watch the T.V.
to find out where the
tournament is, right?
Yes... That's right.
Yamcha! Come back!
Puar, call me if Cell
shows up on the television.
I've got some training to do!
Oh, please don't go!
I've got to! 'Cause, time is
running out for all of us.
And I've got to be
ready to fight Cell!
Hold on! I'll go too!
You're right, we really
do need to stay in shape.
Alright, let's go.
Hey! At least we know
that Cell will have to
stick by the rules, ha-ha!
Hey, I'm kinda looking
forward to this tournament.
It could be fun!
[VEGETA] Go out and
play if you want!
But leave Cell to me, because I
don't want anyone
getting in my way.
Do you understand?!
That's a lot of talk for
someone who got pounded
by Cell don't you think?!
What?! No! He tricked me!
I'm stronger than him!
Cell cannot defeat me!
I alone have the power
to beat Cell!
And Goku?
Kakarot...
he doesn't have a chance.
Father!
We can't think like that!
We're going to have to
work together on this one!
Goku and Gohan, they're both
an important part of our team!
Trunks?!
Where's Trunks?!
Trunks!
[ALL screaming]
[yelling]
[PUAR grunts]
[BULMA whimpers]
There you are...
Oh, good! You're okay!
Right?
[TRUNKS gasps]
Piccolo said you might be
hurt after your fight with Cell.
You are feeling okay,
aren't you? You look great!
Uh... I-I'm fine.
Well... that's good. We were
all really worried about you.
I'm sorry about that.
[thinking] Wow, that's me.
[BABY TRUNKS babbles]
Hey! Let go!
[BABY TRUNKS giggles]
[TRUNKS laughs]
Come on, let go!
Gee, look at that. Trunks
is pulling on Trunks' hair!
[BULMA &amp; TRUNKS laugh,
BABY TRUNKS giggles]
Oh... That young man
is named Trunks too?
That's odd...
I mean, what a coincidence!
[CELL laughs]
[WOMAN screams]
[PEOPLE screaming]
[screaming]
Excuse me, could you
tell me where I might find
the global broadcasting room?
U-Upstairs on the left, sir...
I-In studio B!
Upstairs... thank you, miss.
[whimpering]
[KRILLIN growls]
[YAMCHA grunts]
[YAMCHA yells]
Whoa! Be careful, Yamcha!
Krillins head is
pretty slippery!
[KRILLIN grunts]
[YAMCHA grunts]
Wow, Krillin... I think your
head is your secret weapon!
[KRILLIN grunts]
Yeah maybe, but
you bruised my brain!
[YAMCHA laughs]
[YAMCHA] Come on,
don't be a wimp!
Your head is as hard as a rock!
Hey, pal! Are you
making fun of me?!
I sure am!
[YAMCHA grunts]
Oh boy, look at those two! They
have no idea what they're doing!
[ROSHI chuckles lecherously]
[ROSHI] That's it, girls!
Keep up the good work!
We've got to stay in shape!
[ROSHI chuckles]
Old man, you are pathetic!
Master Roshi always
watches that program.
[OOLONG giggles]
Jump! Jump!
[AEROBICS INSTRUCTOR screams]
[BOTH screaming]
[AEROBICS INSTRUCTOR screaming]
[DIRECTOR] Hey,
that's not in the script!
[AEROBICS INSTRUCTOR screams]
[screaming]
Cell!
Hey, Yamcha!
It's Cell! He's on T.V!
[ANNOUNCER] We
apologize for  this
interruption in programming.
It is only temporary... we hope.
[WEATHERMAN] These
storm clouds on--
[CELL chuckling]
Show off!
[JULIA screams]
[KATHY screams]
[MASCOTS scream]
[ALL whimpering]
And now it's time for
the international news.
[NEWSMAN screams]
Hey, what's the idea?!
[NEWSMAN rasps]
You... tell me,
is this Studio B?
[NEWSMAN gurgles]
Of course it is!
Call security! Hurry!
[screaming]
[ALL growling]
[GOHAN grunts]
[GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN growls]
I have to... get stronger
than a Super Saiyan!
[GOHAN yells]
[CHICHI] Gohan... Gohan!
[GOHAN growls]
Huh?
You stop that
right now, young man!
Hi! Mom, what's up?
[CHICHI] I've come
to take you home.
You've been gone
a long time, Gohan!
Aw, come on, Mom...
No! You've got a lot of studying
to do back at the house, Gohan,
and I do not want you to end
up in a gang like your father!
Dad's a Z Fighter, Mom.
He's not in a gang...
I don't care!
All I know is if you
don't hit the books,
you'll end up in a gang!
I'm sorry, Gohan.
I tried to stop her,
but I couldn't.
Ahh...
[CHICHI] Goku!
Hey, Goku!
I know you're hiding
in here somewhere.
Goku, come out this instant!
You've got some
explaining to do!
Hmm...?
Uh? Goku--
[CHICHI grunts]
Noooo!
Cell!
[GOHAN whimpers]
[PICCOLO yells]
Mom... I'm... so...rry...
No! Piccolo!
[GOHAN gasps]
[GOHAN] Mom! Get up! Please!
[GOHAN screams]
--[GOHAN] No!
--Wake up! Wake up!
--Cell, I'll get you!
--Wake up!
Wake up, Gohan!
[GOHAN whimpers]
I'll get you! I'll get you!
[GOHAN growls]
[GOHAN screams]
I let him kill my mom!
Relax. It was only a nightmare.
[GOHAN growls]
What?
[GOKU] Ah, good.
Yeah! That feels right.
Gohan, you're okay!
You had a fever but it broke!
[GOHAN] A fever?
Hey, don't sweat it...
Now... Back to bed.
Hey, Dad? Are we still
training tomorrow?
Yeah, of course! We've still
got a whole lotta work to do!
Okay?
Okay...
I'll try to get some
sleep, but it's hard when
I keep having those bad dreams
about Cell... Let's get him...
[thinking] Don't worry, Gohan.
We will... we will.
I... am Cell. I have a message
for all the people of Earth...
Now pay attention to what I say.
[DIRECTOR] Zoom in! Camera one!
[CAMERAMAN yelps]
[DIRECTOR] Focus, camera one!
Focus! Come on!
[CELL] Your boring
lives are about to
get a lot more interesting,
thanks to me.
I have enjoyed terrorizing
Earth, but now I have something
far more entertaining planned
for this pathetic planet...
For those of you who
don't remember me,
take a close look at my face.
The big monster of Nicky Town?
I am the evolved
form of that creature...
and I owe it all
to this worthless planet,
for providing me with
the bioextract I needed.
[CAMERAMAN B gasps]
[CELL] But the reason I'm here
is to announce my decision
to hold a Martial
Arts Tournament.
I'm calling this competition,
"The Cell Games"...
It's a catchy little
title don't you think?
[CELL chuckles]
The Cell Games, will be held
nine days from today at Area S,
Point 5, 28 miles
northeast of Eastern City.
There you'll find an arena
that I have designed myself.
I modeled it after the
one used in the original
World's Martial Arts Tournament.
I believe it is
the ideal location
to crush my competitors.
Bring me your best fighters
and I will face them one by one
in a contest of strength.
This is the last
chance for planet Earth...
If I am not defeated,
it belongs to me!
[CELL laughs]
My competitors will have the
advantage since I won't be able
to rest between matches and
my new opponents can enter
the competition immediately.
The rules will be the same
as the World's Martial
Arts Tournament.
If you give up or your body
touches the outside
of the ring, you lose.
And though, I will
try to avoid this...
if you die, you will, of
course, be disqualified...
Cell!
[KRILLIN growls]
[ROSHI growls]
I hope I haven't
frightened any of you
from playing the Cell Games.
Now that you know where
the competition will be held,
all you have to do is find
the courage to show up.
[CELL laughs]
[ANDROID 16 growls]
[ROSHI gasps]
Curse him!
Now watch this.
Here's just a little taste
of what you'll be up against!
Come and get me if you dare!
[screaming, gasping, whimpering]
Now, let the games begin...
The tournament starts
in nine days! Good luck!
[CELL laughs]
He's really serious!
He'll destroy the planet
if we don't stop him!
That's right...
The stakes are a lot higher
than we originally thought!
We're in trouble guys!
Oh.... We're history!
What are we going to do?
Not one of us can beat Cell!
Not even Vegeta or Trunks could
beat him... We need Goku!
[KRILLIN growls]
[BULMA] What are
you doing, Vegeta?
Hear me out. I don't care
about the people of Earth,
but I promise
I will destroy Cell!
I'll go with you!
[BULMA] Wait! Let me cut
your hair before you go.
It might get in the way.
Uh, thank you!
[VEGETA groans]
[NARRATOR] Cell's evil
extravaganza is well underway.
The Cell Games will no
doubt captivate audiences
all over the world,
spreading fear and chaos
just as the android wants.
And with Cell's
impressive fighting record,
the odds seem heavily
stacked in his favor.
But as it is with
any good competition,
there's still plenty
of room for an upset.
[NARRATOR] Because up
in Kami's Lookout,
behind the doors of the
Hyperbolic Time Chamber,
Goku and Gohan
continue to train...
If this father-son duo can
harness the true potential
of the Super Saiyan,
there's no telling what
could happen when the
tournament day arrives!
[NARRATOR] All eyes
are on you Goku,
next time on Dragon Ball Z!