[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z,
Babidi set into motion another
one of his sinister schemes.
The wizard's plan:
to draw Piccolo, Trunks,
and Goten out of hiding
and feed him to the
monster Majin Buu.
But to draw them out,
he would first need some bait.
[PEOPLE gasping, screaming]
[BUU]
Aaahh...
Buu want candy!
[NARRATOR]
At Babidi's command,
Majin Buu used his power to
turn the unsuspecting citizens
of an entire city into candy.
Then, like a
vile vacuum cleaner,
he devoured the population
in a single gruesome gulp.
[NARRATOR]
How much more of this horror
can our heroes bear to witness
before they are
forced out of hiding?
And how many more victims
will Buu have to devour
before he satisfies
his evil appetite?
You'll have to
watch to find out!
[BABIDI]
Please be courteous
and remember that
silence is golden, okay?
[BABIDI] Aww,
look at that. What a shame.
This city is completely useless
if there are no people in it.
[BUU]
Mm-hmm! Mm-hmm!
Let's fix that! All these old
buildings are spoiling my view.
Go ahead, Majin Buu.
Clean up this town.
Just don't overdo it.
We wouldn't want the whole
planet to disappear!
[BABIDI laughs]
Okay! Okay!
Ooh!
Darn it, he's made
his point already.
Now he's just rubbing
it in our faces.
[BABIDI giggles]
[BUU]
Puuu!
[BABIDI giggles]
[BUU giggles]
That's more like it.
It's what I'll do to
those three meddlers, too.
So one last reminder.
It's him...
...and him...
...and him!
There's really no point
in protecting them.
They are not your friends.
They are spineless cowards!
If they valued
your lives at all,
they would have already
turned themselves over to me.
Obviously, they don't.
Well, shame on them, I say!
You now have an
opportunity to teach
these selfish brats a lesson.
One chance to stand up
for your self-worth
and for Earthlings everywhere.
[BABIDI using ESP]
It's simple really.
Just tell me where they are.
By the way...
You have five days to
measure the importance
of your meager, little lives.
Take too long, and I'll
have Buu annihilate you all!
[giggles]
[growls]
Piccolo.
Stay calm.
Don't let him get to you!
Oh yes, there's one
more important thing.
You will need to contact me,
so I'll tell you how you can.
If you have some information
for me, I can hear you...
Start talking and I'll
hear you inside my head.
I'm listening, so speak up now!
If you tell me where those
uncaring louts are hiding
I might even spare you!
I'm sure they're
all here on the list!
Find them! If we don't,
we'll all be turned into candy
and eaten by that monster!
Somebody has got to know where
those three guys are?!
Nobody knows where they're
hiding! We're all done for!
Somebody's gotta do something!
I know I'm sweet, but I don't
wanna turn into candy!
[shrieks]
How do you think I feel?
I've had my nose buried
in these books for a year.
A whole year, trying to
get into a college
that just got blown up.
Whatta jip! I coulda
been at the beach!
You think that's bad,
our wedding is tomorrow!
And ever since
I was a little girl
I've dreamed of my wedding day.
You're not getting out
of this that easy! Ah!
Ow! Sorry sweetheart!
[BUU giggles]
Oh! Someone's already
trying to contact me.
[FRIAR A] Uh, hello, Mister
Babidi, sir, I was, uh...
I'm in charge of the World
Martial Arts Tournament
that was held e-earlier today.
[BABIDI]
Mm-hmm. I hear you.
U-Uh, those three guys...
They were all participants
in, uh, the competition!
[BABIDI using ESP] Excellent!
Are you sure it's them?
Ah, oh! Their
names are Goten...
And there's Trunks... And
Majunior... Yes, that's them!
--Please don't kill me!
--Listen, I don't care
about their names.
Just tell me where to find them!
[BUU]
Whee!
[FRIAR A] Uh, I don't know
where they are, sir!
You don't know, huh?
Then you're useless to me!
Ahh! I'm... sorry.
[screams]
--[screaming continues]
--[whimpers]
[FRIAR B]
Aaah! No! Marvin!
[sobs]
Now, don't give me anymore
useless information.
Give me what I want or else!
I can't stand this!
No rest for the wicked!
I've got to keep you
humans on your toes,
so perhaps a little
more destruction
will keep you all in line.
Majin Buu! It's time to go!
[BABIDI] You never know,
the next place we visit
may be your hometown.
Yes, you can consider this
to be your last warning.
Remember, you have
only five days left
before we tear
this planet apart!
Come on, give me a call!
[BUU giggles]
[snarls]
Curse him!
That demented wizard!
We've got to stop them!
I don't know if
they can be stopped!
So! Those are the ones
that took Gohan
and Vegeta away from us?!
[growls]
Yeah...
Vegeta, Gohan,
all those people...
And unless we do
something quickly,
for the next five days, that
list will keep on growing.
There's no way I can allow that
to happen. I'll show myself!
No! That won't help anybody.
And you know it, Piccolo.
[GOKU] Babidi's going to
wipe everyone out,
no matter what you do.
Stay. Help me teach Goten and
Trunks the fusion technique.
That is the only way
we can truly put an end
to this nightmare.
We have five days before the
Earth is history. We can do it!
Look, I know it's hard
to sit here doing nothing
while he's out there
hurting so many people,
but you said it yourself.
We have to be prepared to cope
with anything that happens.
Don't worry, okay? We can still
revive Majin Buu's victims
with the Dragon Balls.
So, just hang in there!
Yes, he's right, Piccolo.
Don't leave! Not when you
could still do some good here!
I'll stay.
[TRUNKS]
Huh?!
Huh? Hey, where am I?
[TRUNKS]
Whoaa...
What a place.
What is this? Hey! Goten!
Get up! Goten! Come on, get up!
Darn! Dumb kid
sleeps like a rock.
I know! Hey, Goten.
Get up, it's time to eat!
--[TRUNKS chuckles]
--[gasps]
Yeah! Let's eat!
Huh? Huh? Food?
[TRUNKS]
Why do you even have ears?
You hear much better
with your stomach.
Huh? What did you say?
Where is this?
Uh... I don't know? You tell me.
[GOTEN]
I don't know. It's sure nice!
Oh, hey! That plate
looks expensive!
Who cares about that? I want
to know what we're doing here.
[gasps] Where's my dad?
Oh yeah! We were with him.
That's right!
[VEGETA] Trunks. There's
something you must know.
You've made me proud, my son.
[TRUNKS grunts]
What did you do to him?!
Why did you do it?! Tell me!
Why did you do that to Trunks?!
[GOTEN grunts]
So then, he... isn't here?
But I... I think we should
check this place out.
[GOTEN]
Mm-hmm.
[TRUNKS]
This place is huge!
It looks like
there's nobody home!
Hey, hold on?
Where have those boys gone?
Kibito, revive
Gohan with your power.
[gasps]
Whoa! What the...?
[GOHAN]
Supreme Kai? Where... are we?
It's my world.
It's the World of the Kais.
This is where you live?
Well I, uh, guess this
means I'm dead, doesn't it?
Hey, I don't get a
halo like my dad has?
No. Now don't worry.
You were in bad shape,
but you're alive.
'Kay... But if I'm not dead,
then what am I doing here?
You are asking too many
questions of the Supreme Kai!
You should try to
be more respectful.
You are a guest here.
No living mortal has
ever stood on this ground.
Oh! So then I
really did die, I guess?
And that's why I'm here?
Huh? Gohan, you're alive!
But I don't know why you are
here. It is very strange.
It is very strange indeed!
[GOHAN] Then what's wrong
with asking a few questions?
Supreme Kai, what's going on?
[KIBITO]
I am also puzzled, Master.
It's not right! Gohan does not
belong in a place like this!
I brought Gohan here
to get the Z sword!
It's the only way that
Majin Buu can be defeated now.
[gasps] The Z sword?!
You-You can't be
serious, Supreme Kai?!
How can a mere Earthling do what
the Kais themselves could not?!
Don't you remember?!
None of the Kais, not even you,
were capable of
freeing the Z sword!
I'm aware of the
power of the Z sword.
And I'm certain that Gohan is
the right person to wield it.
Uh? What's the Z Sword?
Master! Please! Have you
really thought this through?!
There's no harm
in trying, Kibito!
Let's go! Gohan! Come with me!
[GOHAN] Wait, aren't you going
to tell me what the Z sword is?
Guess not...
He won't pull the Z sword from
that rock! I guarantee it!
[GOTEN]
This is really good, Trunks!
Where are they? Piccolo,
your dad, where are they?
Goten, don't you know it's rude
to talk with your mouth full?
Your manners are really bad.
You shouldn't talk,
when you're eating.
I'm sorry...
Ah, that's okay.
[MR. POPO]
Ah! There you are!
[BOTH]
Huh?
Well, I see you found the food.
[screams] Ow! Let go of me!
We didn't do anything wrong!
I-It was just sitting here!
If you wanted it so bad, you
should have got here first!
Hey! Hands off, buddy!
Goten, what are you doing?!
This is no time to be
stuffing your face!
Hold on, Trunks. Please be
quiet till I finish my meal.
[growls, screams]
[GOTEN] You were the one that
said it was bad manners
to talk when a person
was eating, remember?
If you want to see bad manners,
then you've got it!
My, even Goku wasn't that
powerful when he was a boy!
Hey, let's go!
[GOTEN]
Okay!
[MR. POPO]
Hold it!
Let's get him!
[MR. POPO grunts]
Hey, Goten! Get out of here!
Right!
[TRUNKS]
Huh...?
--[GOTEN grunts]
--[MR. POPO whimpers]
Yeah-heah! Good work!
[GOKU]
You two! Stay right there!
It's Dad!
Oh boy...
[MR. POPO] Those boys certainly
have a lot of energy, Goku!
Well! I guess I'll have to get
them to work it off, won't I?
By teaching them
the fusion technique!
[BOTH]
Hmm?
What a view!
You know, in a lot of ways
this reminds me of
where I live back on Earth!
[growls]
Look at you!
This is a sacred place
and you're dressed like that!
[gasps]
[laughs]
Those clothes suit
you well, Gohan.
Ya think so? Thanks!
Ah, this is it. We're here!
Uh?
[SUPREME KAI]
This is the Z sword, Gohan.
Now try to pull it out.
No one else has done it.
Gohan, if you can pull it from
the rock, you will be the first.
[GOHAN]
Whoa... The first one, huh?
You know, this
might sound strange,
but I feel like
I've done this before.
[TRUNKS]
What?! No, that can't be!
That could never
happen to my dad!
No way! No!
[wails]
My brother is not dead!
[sobs]
Stop that! We don't
have time for this now!
We've got a lot of work to do
and you'll have to learn some
new skills fast! You got it?!
[BOTH sob, whimper]
[GOKU]
I know that might seem harsh,
but there's a chance Babidi
could find this place!
So I want both of you to
start practicing right away!
What about the
Hyperbolic Time Chamber?
No, that room can only be
used twice in a lifetime.
I'm sure in the future we're
going to have to use it again.
We'll be just fine.
If I'm right about these two,
they should be able to master
the fusion technique in no time.
Now let's begin!
[BOTH whimper]
You'll have to learn this
pretty quick, too, Piccolo.
Good luck, you guys...
You're gonna need it.
[BOTH whimper]
I said stop that! There'll be
no more tears from now on!
You will have to be tough
to stop Majin Buu!
[NARRATOR] The news that
Gohan and Vegeta were victims
of Majin Buu hit
Trunks and Goten hard.
Now, they must
swallow their pain
and channel all of
their energies
into learning
the fusion technique.
Little do they know,
Gohan is in the other world
preparing for a
challenge of his own.
He's got to free the legendary
Z Sword from its resting place,
a feat no one before him
has ever accomplished.
Time is running out.
In five days, Majin Buu
will destroy the planet.
Can these three
warriors save the day?
Find out on the
next Dragon Ball Z!