[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
Majin Buu restored Vegito
to his humanoid form
after a painful bout
with the calamitous candy!
[VEGITO]
Oh, it's me again!
[NARRATOR] But, big or small,
the pain remains the same
when dealing with the synthesis
of Super Saiyan legends!
[VEGITO] Is this how you
want it to end? Huh?
So much for the tough warrior!
[NARRATOR] When his last
desperate attempt failed,
it was time for
the final countdown!
Vegito had had enough!
[VEGITO] I'm going to
count to ten, Buu!
[NARRATOR] But rising like
dough in a hot oven
was a perfect
recipe for disaster!
[NARRATOR] Silently, it
stalked its prey and struck!
Consuming Vegito
in one swallow!
[NARRATOR] Had Majin Buu
done the impossible
and, against all odds,
toppled the greatest
fighter in the Universe?
[cackling]
You fool! Oh yeah!
Who's on top now?
Majin Buu! Me! You big
loud-mouthed jerk!
[laughs]
Yeah!
[KIBITO KAI]
I failed!
Despite all my power,
I failed! Sir,
I'm a disgrace to the Kai line!
[KIBITO KAI]
It's over! The Earth is doomed!
The entire physical Universe
is at the mercy of Majin Buu!
[OLD KAI]
Maybe. Maybe not!
[KIBITO KAI]
Huh?
Lookee! Notice
something strange?
[KIBITO KAI]
Hm? No!
Come now! Take a closer look!
In the past, when Majin
Buu absorbed his victims,
he mutated and took on some
of their characteristics!
Hey, you're right!
He looks exactly the
same as he did before!
But, but just
what does it mean?
[OLD KAI]
It means it's not over yet!
He's having trouble
digesting those two!
I have that problem
with Mexican food!
[SUPER BUU]
Yeah!
[SUPER BUU laughing]
[laughing]
[SUPER BUU yells]
[SUPER BUU cackles]
[SUPER BUU yelling]
[SUPER BUU cackling]
[cackling]
[SUPER BUU]
I should've saved some people!
It's not as fun without hearing
their ridiculous cries for help!
Whew.
I could've been killed!
[DENDE]
Mr. Satan, are you okay?
Okay?! Just what is there
to be okay about? Huh?
Well, it seemed as if Vegito was
going to win there for a while!
But now the future of the Earth
is in the hands of Majin Buu!
What are you talkin' about?
You're supposed to be
the Guardian of the Earth!
So come on and do somethin',
use that power of
yours to beat 'im!
[DENDE]
Sorry! I would if I could!
But it's beyond
my power to do that!
Now, put me down!
[MR. SATAN] What am
I doin'? I'm sorry, Dende!
I'm losin' my head!
--[BEE yips]
--[MR. SATAN, DENDE] Huh?
[SUPER BUU cackling]
[BOTH gasping]
Hit the deck!
[SUPER BUU] What a
beautiful place to destroy!
Except, I'm wondering...
Why haven't I changed?
Oh, well! That guy was
tougher than I thought!
He might take a while to digest!
But when he does,
my power will jump to a level
that will truly
be unsurpassable!
There will be no one left who
has the audacity to stop me!
Soon, I will be
the sole proprietor
of the entire Universe!
[laughing]
[VEGITO] Ew! Doesn't get any
more disgusting than this!
[SUPER BUU cackling]
Give me a break! Ah, fruitcake!
It's bad enough to be in here!
But to have to endure that
ridiculous laughter of his...!
On the bright side,
the barrier did the trick!
He hasn't been able to
turn me into Buu goo!
Well, I'd better get busy!
Finding a way out of this
place won't be a picnic!
The others are still
in here somewhere!
I can feel it! But where?
[OLD KAI]
I don't believe it!
He actually got sucked in
on purpose! What a guy!
He wanted to rescue the others
before he annihilated Majin Buu!
He's fantastic!
[OLD KAI] Let's just hope
his plan doesn't backfire!
[sighs]
Huh? Ah!
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU groans]
[VEGETA groans]
[GOKU]
I-I don't get it!
Why did our bodies separate
when we let the barrier down?
How would I know?!
How bizarre!
I was told that once you
and I were joined together
by these earrings,
we could never separate!
Well then, I guess
we lucked out!
I'm me! And you're you, Kakarot!
And that's just the way
I like it! So, there!
Hey! What are you doing?
Put that back on!
[GOKU] We'll probably
fuse together again
as soon as we leave Buu's body!
But, if we're not ready,
we could blow our chance!
[crunching]
Huh?
[yelps]
[BOTH gasp]
He crushed it!
Vegeta! Have you
lost your mind?!
Now there's no way for
us to join bodies again!
Why do you have
to be like that?
Isn't it worth you and
I being stuck together
if we can beat Buu?
No! I perfer to be
the captain of my own ship!
Besides, we can beat
him anyway, Kakarot!
How do you know that? Huh?
Even if we do manage to get
Gohan and the others out,
there's no guarantee that
Buu is going to change back
to the way he was before!
Well, I guess it's going to be
very interesting to find out,
isn't it?
Well, yeah! I mean, no!
[VEGETA]
Come now! You'd better hurry!
Buu could blow up
the world any minute now!
Fine! Have it your way.
[crunching]
[GOKU]
Hey! Vegeta! Wait up!
How do you know this is the way?
[VEGETA]
I don't.
Whoa! It really stinks
in here! You know it?
[VEGETA]
Yes! It's disgusting!
And, uh, thanks for
pointing out the obvious.
[GOKUI] We must be close
to the bowels or something!
It's really nasty!
[VEGETA grunting]
[GOKU]
Vegeta!
Uh? What? It's got me, too!
What the heck is it?
I... can't get... can't get...
[GOKU, VEGETA scream]
[VEGETA gasps]
[GOKU gasps]
Oh, man! Ugh!
[VEGETA] Well, now we know
where that disgusting smell
is coming from!
[VEGETA]
Look at this place!
Doesn't he eat
anything but sweets?
Oh, he's worse than a child!
This is revolting!
Not a singal bit
of meat at all!
Huh? Oh, wow!
What's that smoke?
Huh? Idiot!
You're being digested!
That smoke is coming from your
roasting carcass, you moron!
[yelps]
[GOKU]
Uh-oh! Do you hear that?
Great galaxy!
If I know my anatomy,
that leads strait
for the southern exit!
[GOKU]
Oh, ew...
[rumbling]
[VEGETA]
What are we going to do?
[GOKU] We're going to get
sucked into that hole!
[VEGETA] No, Kakarot! I mean,
how are we going to stop it?!
[VEGETA]
Huh?
Well, I think it's too late...
[GOKU]
Uh-oh!
Man! Some rescue
operation this is!
[VEGETA] I will not suffer the
same fate as cream filling!
[VEGETA, GOKU yelping]
[GOKU thinking]
Got to think of something fast!
We're out of time! Hm?
[GOKU muffled]
Mm? Vegeta!
[VEGETA grunts]
[SUPER BUU] Uhh! Indigestion!
Must've been the meat I ate!
Darn him!
Even going down,
he's a royal pain.
Soon, he'll be something
you wipe off your shoe!
[GOKU, VEGETA yell]
Phew! That was close,
but I think you and I
might want to be a little
more discreet down here
so Majin Buu doesn't figure
out that we're still alive!
[VEGETA]
Oh! I see!
We should have just gone quietly
down that little hole like mice
and become part of
Majin Buu's excretions?!
Ha! No thanks, Kakarot!
I'm a true Saiyan!
I'm going out the front door!
Now let's get a move on!
The Earth is on a
short fuse right now!
[GOKU] I don't know how I ever
managed without you, Vegeta!
[GOKU]
I don't know how he does it!
You'd think that he
would just keel over
from eating this many sweets!
[VEGETA] Oh, you have no
room to talk, Kakarot!
Oh, I've seen you eat desert!
Ho! As bad as it seems,
I'd much rather be down here
than in your stomach after
one of your pig-out sessions!
[giggles] You're kidding!
[VEGETA]
No, I'm not! Huh?
What? What's wrong?
Quiet!
Listen! Do you hear that?
[rapidly pulsing beat]
Yes! What is it?
[VEGETA]
I don't know. But I don't
have a very good
feeling about this.
[GOKU]
Me either!
[VEGETA] What direction
is it coming from?
[GOKU] It seems to be
coming from every direction!
[VEGETA] Precisely! We're being
surrounded! But by what?
There!
[VEGETA]
Look out!
[GOKU] Hm... Hey there!
What's up, little guys!
Ow!
[VEGETA laughs]
Oh, he almost defeated
the great Kakarot!
[GOKU]
Get out!
Look! Voracious little
rascals, aren't they?
[VEGETA] Yes, they are.
Little savages, all right!
There's millions of them!
I mean... what are they?
That's what I was wondering.
Look at 'em go!
It's possible they roam
about breaking down any food
or whatnot that doesn't
make it into the intestines!
[GOKU] I think we fit into
that category, don't we?!
[VEGETA] Yes, but I doubt
they've ever tried to eat
a full-blooded Saiyan before!
[GOKU] It looks like
they're about to try!
[VEGETA] Well, you must have a
sweeter scent than me, Kakarot!
They obviously prefer you!
[GOKU]
Yeah! Gee! Aren't I lucky?
[GOKU] Vegeta? Uh... Since there
are about a million of them,
I don't suppose you would mind
lending me a hand, now would ya?
Who, me? Of course not!
I'm a team player!
Hey! Seriously!
This could get ugly!
[GOKU grunts]
[VEGETA grunts]
[GOKU, VEGETA grunt]
[GOKU grunts]
Ugh! They're everywhere!
[VEGETA]
All right!
[VEGETA grunts]
[VEGETA yells]
What's he doing? He's going
to blow our cover!
That crazy--
[GOKU]
Ah! Little boogers!
[screams]
No, Kakarot!
What? What's that?
[screams]
[VEGETA]
It feels like an earthquake!
[GOKU]
Maybe he's having a, you know?
Huh?!
[VEGETA]
Look out!
Son of a Namek! What is it?
[GOKU]
I don't know!
[gasps]
[GOKU]
What in the world?!
[roars]
[GOKU screams]
Kakarot! It's the slime!
The creature is communicating
with it! Get rid of it! Quick!
I can't!
[roars]
[VEGETA]
Kakarot!
[screams]
[NARRATOR]
As Goku struggles to get free,
the jaws of death are
about to close on him!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z!