[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Cell had almost
reached his final stage
in becoming the Ultimate
Indestructible Android.
And it looked like
Krillin and Android 18
would be no match for
his immense power.
You monster!
[CELL yells]
[NARRATOR] Android 18
has been absorbed,
and now it looks like Cell
has consumed the final
piece of the puzzle to
gain his full potential.
[NARRATOR] Has all
hope now vanished
for the people of Earth?
[CELL growls]
[VEGETA] It has begun!
[NARRATOR] Is there any warrior
left who is strong enough
to challenge the
superiority of Cell?
Or is the entire
universe doomed?
Find out today
on Dragon Ball Z!
[ANDROID 16 growls]
[thinking] Yes! Cell's
final transformation
is at last at hand!
Soon he will be the greatest
adversary I have ever faced...
What the...?!
[ANDROID 16 grunts]
[thinking] Aw, man,
this is all my fault!
I should've shut down Android
18 when I had the chance!
[TRUNKS growls]
[thinking] Oh no!
It's happening again!
[TRUNKS screams]
[TRUNKS] It's just like
what happened in my world!
All of the pain... all of
the senseless destruction!
[thinking] No matter
how hard I tried,
I was powerless to prevent it!
[TRUNKS] And now,
I'm afraid that this world
will suffer the
same fate as mine.
[TRUNKS] Cell...
I've already seen
one world laid to waste
by Dr. Gero's evil creations,
and I won't let it happen again!
I promise you this: as long as
there is breath in my body,
I will fight!
Do you hear?! I won't let
you destroy this world too!
[TRUNKS yells]
[TRUNKS grunts]
[CELL roars]
[TRUNKS gasps]
See?! Nothing to worry about!
[ROSHI grunts]
[CHICHI] Master Roshi, we
have got to get out of here
or this tidal wave is going
to carry us all out to sea!
[OOLONG] That's horrible!
I mean we'd be stuck out
there without anything to eat!
[OOLONG chuckles]
But at least we'd
have clean clothes!
[CHICHI grunts,
OOLONG yells]
[YAMCHA grunts]
I don't know if there's
anywhere we can go, ChiChi.
I'll bet disasters like
this are happening everywhere!
But, there must be some place...
[ROSHI grunts]
[VEGETA chuckles]
[TRUNKS gasps]
It is finally done...
[CHICHI hums]
[YAMCHA} Well, I guess
the worst of it's over.
[ROSHI] No. I'm
afraid not, Yamcha...
--[OOLONG] Huh?!
--[CHICHI] Ah?!
Are you... serious?!
The worst is yet to come...
[PICCOLO growls]
Cell's transformation
is complete.
Huh...?
[BULMA gasps]
[TIEN] Mmm...
What do you mean?
Are you saying Krillin didn't
use my controller
to shut down the androids?
That's right. He crushed
the controller and let her go.
[BULMA shrieks]
Why would he do that?!
[BABY TRUNKS wails]
[PICCOLO growls]
Vegeta... You've doomed us all!
[wailing continues]
[VEGETA chuckles]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[GOHAN screams]
[GOKU growls]
No... Dad, don't!
So, had enough?
Okay, that should
do it for training today.
What? You don't trust me?
[GOKU laughs]
[GOHAN growls]
Gohan?
I think Piccolo
was right about you, Dad...
You're way too gentle
with me to train me right.
You've got to push!
Fight me, Dad!
You're holding back!
Gohan!
I said fight!
[GOHAN grunts]
Listen, you can't go easy
on me just because I'm your son!
[GOKU growls]
No Dad! That's not good enough!
Not if you want me to
become a Super Saiyan!
You have to come at me
with everything you've got--
Even if it kills me!
[GOHAN growls]
Don't you get it?!
It's the only way!
It's all or nothing!
There is no in-between!
[GOHAN growls]
[GOHAN] Look, Dad,
I know you love me
and that you don't
want to hurt me,
but unless I become
a Super Saiyan,
all the time we've spent
in here will be for nothing!
Don't you see?
[GOKU yells]
[GOHAN yelps]
[GOKU growls]
Yeah, that's the way to do it.
[GOHAN] One way or another...
We're going to find out
if I really am a Super Saiyan.
It's now or never, Dad!
Don't hold back!
[thinking] I hope
you're ready, Son.
[GOKU] Ka...
Me...
Ha...
[GOKU] Haaa!
[GOHAN yells]
[thinking] I've got to do this!
I won't let you down, Dad!
[GOKU yells]
[GOHAN thinking] No! I've...
I've been letting people down
my whole life!
[GOHAN whimpers]
[GOHAN] How many times
have I let my friends down
when they needed me?
[PICCOLO] Attack, Gohan! Attack!
[GOHAN] And how many of
my friends have gotten hurt
because I've been too weak
or too scared to help them?
If only I'd been stronger...
[GOKU} The power comes
in response to a need,
not a desire.
[GOHAN] If only I
could've done more...
[GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN] Whenever I
get into trouble,
any time I'm
in over my head
and I don't think
I'm going to make it,
Dad, Krillin, Piccolo,
one of my friends
is always there
to bail me out!
[GOKU] The power comes
in response to a need!
You have to create that need!
[GOHAN] But when the
situations are reversed,
I just stand there like
a little, helpless child!
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[FRIEZA giggles]
[KRILLIN yells]
Krillin! No!
[FRIEZA snarls]
Help me! Aaa--!
[GOHAN] Krillin...
I'm so sorry...
[GOKU] Son,
use the pain of loss!
[GOHAN] Dad, you've always
been able to do anything
you set your mind to.
There's never been a
challenge you couldn't meet.
And when the time came,
you were ready.
You became a Super Saiyan!
[GOKU] ...responds to
a need, not a desire!
[GOHAN] But Dad,
I'm not like you...
I-I just don't think
I have what it takes!
[GOKU] Use the pain of loss!
The power comes in response
to a need, not a desire!
Use the pain of loss!
[GOKU] No! I have to be strong!
If I can't do this, then
Dad, Krillin, everyone!
I'm going to lose them all!
[GOHAN screams]
[GOHAN yells]
[GOKU thinking] Wow. He did it.
My son is a Super Saiyan.
[GOHAN grunting]
So, do you still think
I'm too easy on you?
[GOHAN growling]
Gohan, listen!
You've got to calm down!
Try to focus your energy.
[GOHAN growling]
I'm really proud of you, Gohan.
I'm so sorry, it was so hard...
Hey, don't worry about it! Just
catch your breath, all right?
We'll take a little break...
Then what do you say
I give you a haircut?
If it gets any longer I'm
going to lose you under there!
[GOKU laughs]
[BOTH laugh]
[CELL] Hmm...
[VEGETA chuckles]
[VEGETA] So this is the
"Ultimate Android's"
new body, eh? What a joke!
He's even smaller
than he was before!
[KRILLIN growls]
[thinking] I can't believe it!
She's gone! She's really gone!
[ANDROID 18 screams]
Krillin, no!
[KRILLIN yells]
[KRILLIN shouting]
[thinking] At last... All that I
have ever imagined is now mine!
I have become what no other
could ever achieve...
I am perfect!
[shouting continues]
[VEGETA chuckles]
[TRUNKS growls]
Yes, that's right, children.
Have your fun.
[KRILLIN yells]
You monster!
Chew on this!
[KRILLIN yells]
Destructo Disk!
[KRILLIN laughs]
Yes! Direct hit!
Huh?!
[TRUNKS gasps]
[CELL] So you want to play, huh?
[CELL] Very well. It's
my turn. Are you ready?
[CELL chuckles]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
--[CELL chuckles]
--[KRILLIN gasps]
[chuckling continues]
[KRILLIN grunts]
[TRUNKS gasps]
[NARRATOR] Cold this the
beginning of the end?
Is there no stopping
the all-powerful Cell?
There's only one
way to find out...
Don't miss the next
exciting episode of
Dragon Ball Z!