[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Goku and Gohan headed home
after completing their training
in the Hyperbolic Time Chamber.
Elsewhere, Cell was
doing his own training
to prepare for the approaching
Martial Arts Tournament.
As Vegeta quarreled
with the others over who
would get to train in the
Hyperbolic Time Chamber,
Goku decided to take
a different approach!
[GOKU] Let's get your
Mom and go on home.
We'll have time to relax there.
I figure we'll have
three days of rest,
plus three days of training,
and then three more days of
rest before the tournament.
[GOHAN] Hey, Dad. Can
I ask you something?!
--[GOKU] Hm?
--Well, I just wanna know...
Do you think we have
a chance to beat Cell?
[GOKU] Hey, let's not worry
about all that right now!
We've got nine days!
Let's kick back for a while!
[NARRATOR] And so Goku's
unusual training program began!
[GOHAN] Gosh! How nice!
[NARRATOR] The Super Saiyans'
stomachs have been filled,
and now it's time for
Gohan to do his chores!
Today on Dragon Ball Z!
[GIRL] Ahh! I see you!
[GIRL] C'mon!
Just a little closer!
[GIRL] You little rascal!
[GIRL screams]
[coughing, gasping]
Are you okay?
[GIRL screams]
How dare you?! You fiend!
What? For saving you?
[GIRL growls]
You!
Neeh!
[GIRL] Go back where
you came from!
Uh?
[GOHAN] Huh?
Oh, wow! Cool!
I don't remember
that being there!
[GOHAN] Oh, man! Shoot!
Don't tell me this
village is deserted too!
Gosh!
At this rate, I'll never
get Mom's shopping done!
This is the fourth
village I've been to!
Cell has really put
a scare into people.
I wonder where
they've all gone?
[GOHAN] Oh!
Great! Someone's still here.
Now what do you need
money for, you fool?!
The world's ending!
Perhaps. But no one
knows that for sure.
Especially not you.
Ahh! Shut your face, old man!
We're just gonna take it!
Look! We'll trade ya for it!
You can have free lodging
in the shelter with us!
You dig?
--That shelter is a bad idea!
--Huh?!
I've said that from the start!
--[GOHAN] Excuse me?
--Huh?
[MAN 2] What do you think
you're doing, small fry?!
Well, just picking a few
things up for my mom.
Hey, leave him be, Birdwell!
He's just a young punk!
Buzz off, kid!
We're sold out!
[GOHAN] Huh?!
But what's all this!
The Bourbon family
bought it! For the shelter!
Stop your nonsense! Now!
Hey, young man! Just tell me
what you need, okay?
Sure!
Let's see... One bag of--
Listen! What's your
problem, old man?!
Are you deaf?!
We need this! To survive!
Not just us! Everyone!
All of the villagers
are counting on you!
Give us the food!
Why should I?!
So the Bourbon family can
make the villagers work for it?!
Kasdan! Hey! I don't
think he's getting it!
I think he needs a
little persuasion!
--[GOHAN growls]
--Hey! Stop that!
What are you doing?!
[BIRDWELL chuckles]
[BIRDWELL]
This oughta do the trick!
[BIRDWELL chuckles
[GIRL screams]
--[GIRL] Cell! It's Cell!
--What?! He came back?!
--He's back!
--What?! Cell's been here?!
[KASDAN] Darn right!
I knew he'd come back!
Let's get to
the shelter, Birdwell!
See?! You should have taken us
up on our offer, you old coot!
[BIRDWELL screams]
[thinking] What the heck
is Cell doing out here?!
[GIRL] Oh, my gosh! Run!
Run! It's Cell! Cell's here!
--Heh?!
--Huh?
[GIRL] Run everybody! Run!
Hey! I know you!
[GIRL gasps]
Well, Miss Lime! Where's Cell?!
[LIME screams]
[LIME giggles]
Now, Lime! How many times have
I told you never to lie again?!
Huh?
Cell's not here?
[GOHAN] So that's the shelter
they were talking about!
[grunting]
Yes. The villagers have
gone there for protection.
Just in case Cell comes back.
So... Cell was actually here
before in the village?
[grunting]
That's right.
There weren't a whole lot of
fireworks so to speak,
not in those days. He was still
stalking his victims for energy.
Oh... I see.
Oh yes. Mind you, he was
comparatively weak back then.
Still gathering lifeforce
to build up his strength.
[MAN screams]
[CELL] Hmmm...
What a waste of time.
Just a bunch of
weaklings! Pitiful!
[LIME sobs]
[growling]
[GOHAN sighs]
Yes, Lime lost her
parents that day.
My gosh!
[LIME sniffles]
If you've seen... seen the
Cell then you know that
there is no use in running
away or building a shelter!
I'm not sure why they're
deluding themselves.
Believing in the shelter
brings them comfort, I guess.
They're a bunch of
fools! That's all!
Anyway, we still
have eight days to live.
That's not bad!
So here we are!
Trying to make the most out
of these last peaceful days.
[groaning]
[LIME] Hm? Uh-oh, Gramps!
It's your back again!
Why can't I do it?!
I'm big enough!
You're still a little
young, child! Thanks!
Uh... Hey, I can help!
Ooohh...
[GOHAN] Uh... Hmm...
Hm?
Yes, I'd love your help!
[GOHAN] Okay, let's see here!
[GOHAN grunts]
[LIME] Hey, silly!
[GOHAN] Huh?!
[GOHAN grunting]
Aren't you
forgetting something?
Even I know that you can't
chop wood without an axe!
Here!
[GOHAN] Huh?!
Uhh... Yeah!
Gosh! Oops!
[GOHAN grunts]
[BOTH] Gasp]
Hmm...
[GOKU yawns]
H-Hey...
Is it possible we're
taking things too lightly?
Hm? What do you mean?
I mean the tournament!
We only have eight
days left, you know?
All this yawning is
making me lose my focus!
I'm getting too relaxed here!
Oh, man. I'm sorry.
[GOKU yawns]
[KRILLIN growls]
You bum! You never worry,
do you? My gosh...
Hey! Come on, now! Move!
We only have eight
days left, you know?!
You wanna be
ready, or what?!
[BOURBON] That does it!
You idiots!
You need money?!
What in the world for?!
He's just an old man!
Look, didn't I explain
it? Now listen, dopes!
We don't have any
more liquid assets!
It's all tied up in
buiding materials!
The money's all gone. Now off!
[KASDAN &amp; BIRDWELL]
Yes, Mister Bourbon!
Well, not quite all of it.
I did save myself a bit.
After all, somebody's
got to make a fortune,
and it might as well be me!
Hoo-hah!
Hello! Yes!
You're all mine!
I missed you!
[BOURBON smacks]
I love you!
Yes! I! Love! You!
[BOURBON laughs]
[MAN] A-hem.
Huh?! Oh! I didn't
see you come in!
[BOURBON whistles]
Ah! General Tao, what
brings you to my office?!
[GENERAL TAO] Well,
I've come to kill you
and take all of your money!
How does that plan grab you?
[BOURBON gasps]
Relax! It's just my dry
sense of humor, chief.
Five thousand is all
I require right now.
[BOURBON laughs]
Ahh, five thousand
is all you require!
That's nice! But please
tell me what's it for?
For me! Haven't I done my job?
With me here, no one's
dared to cross you.
So you can either pay me
for it, or I'll take it all!
[BOURBON] Oh, no!
No, no! Please! Please!
I'll pay! I'll pay!
Good work! Good work!
Thank you
[BOURBON] Don't be
silly. You earned it
[GENERAL TAO chuckles]
[VEGETA thinking] Piccolo,
if you're even in there
one second longer
than the alotted time,
I'm coming in after you!
[PICCOLO panting]
Hey, Piccolo.
What's the matter?
Growing weary already, huh?
You don't scare me, Cell!
[PICCOLO growls]
[yelling]
[PICCOLO B growls]
[BOTH grunting]
[BOTH growling]
[yelling]
[PICCOLO yells]
[PICCOLO B grunts]
[PICCOLO grunts]
Alright, round two.
[LAO] There!
Mm-hmm.
Hey, Gohan!
Are you sure these spices are
all that your Mother needs?
Ah.
[LAO] Hm? Now where have
those two rascals gone?
You'd never fight!
You're too sweet!
Right?
[GOHAN] Huh?!
[LIME] You're too gentle!
To fight, I mean.
You think so!
Mm-hmm! I know so! For sure!
I can see that!
[GOHAN chuckles]
I like strong men!
Like my Grandpa!
He's a real fighter!
[GOHAN gasps]
Your Grandpa's a fighter?
Sure, he used to be a
great Martial Arts master
back in the old days.
Hey! I'll bet if you asked,
he'd give you some pointers!
Hey! You think so?
Mm-hmm! You bet!
Then you could give it
to that Bourbon family!
Ha! Ha! That would teach them
to mess with Grandpa's store!
--[fireworks popping]
--[BOTH] Huh?
What's that?
Oh! It must be the grand
opening for the shelter.
Come on! Let's go see!
[GOHAN] Uh-huh.
[CROWD cheering]
[BOURBON] Thank you! Thank you
very much! Thank you!
Now, give yourselves a hand!
Afterall, it's your home!
[CROWD applauding]
My, my!
It's so fantastic to see all you
pulling together like this!
It warms my soul
to see such unity!
Yeah, right! Fraud!
I know!
It's Cell! Cell is here!
[GOHAN screams]
What are you doing?!
[CROWD]
He's here already?!
What?! On the grand opening?!
--[CROWD screaming]
--[LIME] Cell's here!
He was at the village!
--[BOURBON] Make way! Make way!
--He's coming! Cell's coming!
[BOURBON] Hey! Shut
the doors! Quick!
But, Sir! You're the
only one who made it in!
[BOURBON] I said shut
the doors, you imbecile! Now!
Oh! Yes, sir!
[beep]
[CROWD screaming]
[LIME] It's Cell! Cell's here!
That oughta show 'em
Mister Bourbon's true colors!
--[KASDAN] So you're the one!
--[BOTH] Huh?! [gasping]
Mister Bourbon, would
like to have a few words
with you two punks!
[CROWD yelling]
--Hurry, hurry! Open up!
--[CROWD screaming]
--Cell is here! Just let us in!
[BOURBON] Please!
Don't be alarmed!
Some of you may qualify
for a partial refund!
--Boo, let us in! No! Please!
--[CROWD yelling]
Hey, calm down!
It was just a joke!
A little kid was
playing a stupid prank!
[BOURBON] What?!
[BOURBON growls]
Alright! Where's
that stinkin' kid?!
[KASDAN] This is her,
Mister Bourbon! She did it!
Why, you little runt!
You're in big trouble!
[GOHAN] Uh, excuse
me there, Sir!
Pardon! It was wrong
of my friend to lie!
We're sorry!
But I don't think what
you're doing is right either!
Who cares what you think!
Go home to your mommy, kid!
And where's your Mom?
Was she one of the ones
that you locked outside?!
That's enough out of you,
you delinquent!
Hey, boys! All eyes here!
Shut this kid up!
[MEN IN BLACK] Right!
Hey, wait! He's just a boy!
Let's bring him to his home!
This is my land! And this
is my shelter, old man!
And if you want in,
then you better do as I say!
[whimpering]
-[LAO] Stop it!
--[ALL] Huh?!
[CROWD murmuring]
Wow! It's Grandpa!
Yes! It's me.
Now back off!
Uh-oh!
Don't be fools!
He's just an old man!
Get him!
[MEN IN BLACK] Yes, sir!
Let me help! There's
too many of them!
No, no. No, I think
I can handle this one.
[LAO grunts]
[BIRDWELL grunts]
Old man! Now you're
going to get it!
[LAO grunts]
[ALL yell]
[grunting,
blows landing]
Haaa!
[grunting]
[KASDAN growls]
[LAO yells]
[gun fires]
[BOTH gasp]
[BOURBON] Ah! Why you! General
Tao! Come out! I need you!
What is it, Mister Bourbon?
Just a small task! Yes!
For someone so great!
It's that man! I want
him eliminated!
Hmph!
Him? Oh, I'd be happy to.
[CROWD gasping]
[GENERAL TAO yells]
[blows landing,
grunting]
--[LAO growls]
--Ahh! Not bad, old man!
[GOHAN &amp; LIME gasp]
[LAO] No, son! You stay there!
This is the villagers' fight!
Not yours! I know you'd win!
Wow! You know that?
But how were you able to tell?
Hmmm...
[LAO yells]
[BOTH gasp]
[BOURBON] KO'd! Now
finish him off, General Tao!
That'll teach them to cross me!
Sure, that's what
I'm paid for!
I'm your friendly
neighborhood killer!
[LIME cries]
[GENERAL TAO] No hard feelings,
old man. It's just a job.
Dodonpa Wave, fire!
[LIME] Ahhh! No!
[BOTH chuckle]
--Say what?!
--What happened?!
I happened! That's what!
[LIME] Oh, my goodness!
Cocky little kid. No matter.
This will shut him up!
[thinking] Wait a second!
That face... It can't be!
Hey, kid! What's your name?!
[GOHAN] It's Gohan!
[GENERAL TAO] Well!
Thank goodness!
I thought you were
someone named Goku!
Close enough! I'm his son!
What?!
[thinking] Not that kid!
[GOKU yells]
[blows landing,
GOKU yelling]
Here, kid!
[GENERAL TAO grunts]
Take that!
[GENERAL TAO chuckles]
[GOKU yells]
Hmm?!
[GENERAL TAO screams]
[GENERAL TAO whimpers]
Hey, what the heck's
wrong with you?!
You look like you've
just seen a ghost!
Oh, no! Not me!
You will soon though!
If you fight that kid!
As for me, I quit!
[GENERAL TAO yells]
[BOURBON] You can't quit!
[GENERAL TAO] I just did!
[BOURBON whimpers]
[CROWD]
[WOMAN] He was going to
lock us all out!
[MAN 1] He's a thief!
[BOURBON] No, no! I can explain!
[MAN 2] Let's beat
the tar out of him!
[BOURBON] You're super strong,
right! Please! Please!
Help me! They're mad!
Blood thirsty!
That's because
you cheated them!
[BOURBON] I know! I know!
But I can make up for it!
Please! I'll do anything!
Anything! Please!
[BOURBON whimpers]
[LIME gasps]
Yaaah!
[CROWD gasps, screams]
What have you done?!
Don't you see? If I can
do that to the shelter,
just think what
Cell could've done!
That thing can't protect
you against a guy like Cell!
[BOTH] Mm-hmm!
[GOHAN] Hi, everybody,
I'm Gohan!
I know that Cell's scary, but,
instead of expecting the worst,
I think we should
hope for the best!
Cell isn't invincible!
Haven't you ever heard
that the bigger they are,
the hard they fall?
[GOKU] Gohan! Hey! Up here!
[GOHAN] Dad! What
are you doing here?
Well, looking for you.
Aren't you supposed to be
getting stuff for your Mom?
Oops! I forgot!
Hey! No you didn't!
Thanks!
[LIME giggles]
[LAO] It's been a great pleasure
getting to know your son.
Gee, thanks.
His power is enormous.
Just like his Dad's.
[GOKU laughs]
Don't tell! Okay?
[LAO] Hm?
[GOHAN] Mister Lao?
Thanks a lot for everything.
Please come and visit us.
Sure!
Hey! Let's boogie.
Right!
Beat Cell. I know you can do it!
[BOTH] Huh?
I know you'll
both be there.
At the big tournament, right?
[LAO chuckles]
[LIME] Goodbye, Gohan!
Come back and see us soon!
[NARRATOR] With only 8 days left
until the tournament begins,
Cell is consumed
with the desire
to test his abilities in combat!
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
our pure-hearted heroes
are more worried
about what's for dinner,
and how best to enjoy
the precious time
that they have together.