[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball Z,
with Gohan, Piccolo,
Goten, and Trunks in hand,
Goku and Vegeta
made a daring escape
from inside of
Majin Buu's head!
[NARRATOR] It was a moment of
triumph for the super duo.
Never before had
anyone managed to escape
after being
absorbed by Majin Buu.
At last, the weary
captives were liberated
and laid down in a
safe place to rest.
But was anywhere safe?
The new Buu was about
to unleash an attack
that would destroy
the entire planet!
[VEGETA]
Hey, Buu!
[NARRATOR] The fusion earrings
could help, but was it too late?
[KID BUU screeches]
[NARRATOR] Yes!
It was time to abandon ship.
[GOKU] Vegeta!
We'll grab the boys
and use Instant Transmission!
[VEGETA]
Yes!
[NARRATOR] When Goku saw Dende
and Mr. Satan in distress,
he made a detour to save them
as well. But what had he done?
Now, there was no time left
to recover Gohan and the others.
It was over.
[NARRATOR] On the wings of
Instant Transmission they fled,
just as the Earth
breathed her last breath.
Stay tuned.
[gasps]
[grunting]
[KIBITO KAI]
The Earth!
[OLD KAI] Yes... I'm afraid
she's gone. Blown out of space.
Sir! What about
Gohan and the boys?!
[OLD KAI]
Mm?
They're gone, Goku.
Along with the Earth.
The Earth is gone you say?
[laughs]
Who are you trying to fool?
What do you think this is?
Huh? Put that in
your diaper, old man!
[DENDE] Please! You don't
know what you're saying!
That's no ordinary
old man! He's a Kai!
He does look a little strange!
A Kai? What's that?
Some sort of purple leprechaun?
[DENDE] No! The Kai's are
the illustrious overseers
of the Universe!
Each Kai protects
one of the quadrants.
But these two-- they're
actually Supreme Kais!
No one in the whole Universe
has more authority than them.
Really? Hmm?
I've got a question, then!
If these two are
so "great and powerful",
why don't they stop Majin Buu?!
[BOTH gasp]
[DENDE]
Uhh...
They saved this nut? My word.
Hey! They have
pointy ears, too!
And I'm thinkin' you
must be one of them, kid!
[DENDE groans]
Huh? Hey!
[gasps]
Yeah! Now I get it! [laughs]
This is all a dream!
[laughs]
Just a silly ol' dream!
Of course! Of course!
Now it all makes sense!
First of all, there couldn't be
somebody who's stronger than me,
the undisputed martial arts
champion of the world!
[chuckles]
Secondly, pink monsters
like Buu don't exist!
And neither do purple people
with pointy ears, now, do they?
And there's no such
thing as little green men
that guard the Earth from evil.
But, sir!
[MR. SATAN] And how absurd is
this? Look at all those moons!
Hey, wait!
Where are you going?!
[MR. SATAN] I'm gonna
fly away! It's my dream!
And I can do whatever I want!
Hey! Yo! Majin Buu!
I don't care
if this is a dream!
No one hurts my daughter
Videl or the Earth!
Do you got that, pal?!
I'm coming for you,
you pink stink! Prepare to die!
[grunts]
--[MR. SATAN yells]
--[BEE barks]
[MR. SATAN screams]
[BEE squeals]
[MR. SATAN grunts, groans]
Ow! T-The pain! Oooh!
Eeeh! How can it hurt this bad
if this is a dream? Ughh...
You can't pay for
entertainment like this.
[VEGETA]
Kakarot! I can't believe this!
Do you see what we
have to put up with
because of your
incompetent decision?!
And you're
supposed to be a Saiyan?!
They're gone!
We can't even wish them back!
The Dragon Balls were
destroyed along with the Earth!
[KIBITO KAI gasps]
There he is!
[gasping]
[KIBITO KAI] How can he
possibly reform so quickly
after a blast like that?!
[KID BUU grunts, yells]
[chuckles]
He's mad!
That fiend! Darn him!
Ah! If he can withstand an
incredible explosion like that,
how are we ever
going to defeat him?
Did you see that?
[GOKU] Yeah! He's using
Instant Transmission!
[KIBITO KAI] But how could
he have learned it that fast?
Now he can travel
at the speed of light!
[KID BUU chuckles]
[KID BUU laughing]
[ALL gasp]
[GOKU thinking]
All those people!
I think that he's
searching for you two.
Sensing spirits that
are stronger than average
and going there
to check it out.
[GOKU growls]
What's he going to do?
Destroy every single
place he looks? My gosh!
Yes! I'm afraid so!
This Buu, he experiences
no remorse whatsoever!
He's a killing machine!
[GOKU]
With Instant Transmission,
he can destroy an entire solar
system in less than an hour!
The Universe will
never be the same again!
Hey! Wait!
Huh?
I forgot! The Dragon Balls!
The new ones on Namek!
Frieza destroyed
our original home world,
but he couldn't
destroy the Dragon Balls!
Not as long as they live in
the hearts of my Namek brothers!
And I'm sure Elder Moori
has made a new set by now!
We can use them to
wish back the Earth,
and everyone
Majin Buu has killed!
Yes! He's right!
[GOKU]
There's a small problem.
Dende, the other
Nameks are too far away.
I can barely sense
them from where we are.
Which means we can't reach them
by using Instant Transmission.
We'd need a spaceship
of some sort to get there.
Which we don't have...
[growls]
Wait!
I'm not sure what the
Dragon Balls are, but I'm a Kai!
My instantaneous movement
is not limited by distance!
I can go anywhere I want, see?!
[gasps]
If you guys have a plan,
then the least I can do is
get you where you wanna go!
Yes! All right!
At last! Things seem
to be going in our favor!
[OLD KAI]
Hold it right there!
I'm familiar with
the Dragon Balls.
And using them in
this case just isn't proper!
Those balls are
strictly for the edification
of a very advanced
and peaceful race!
They aren't meant
to be used anywhere
except on their home planet!
Using those balls
elsewhere could upset
the natural evolutionary
process of the Universe!
Aren't you being
a little strict?
[OLD KAI]
Hmm?
After all, the Earth has some
very beautiful women on it!
There's one in particular
I'm thinking about!
Remember your reward
for helping Gohan?
[VEGETA]
Hm?!
Oh, you mean that one!
The one you get to kiss!
Oh, yeah!
[GOKU] I've known her since
I was a boy! She's great!
[growls]
But didn't she die
when the Earth exploded?
Sure, but we can
use the Dragon Balls
to wish all
the Earthlings back!
Hey! Kakarot!
You wouldn't happen
to be talking about
Bulma by any chance?
Oh, you are, aren't you?!
You idiot! How could you?!
Don't you have any sense at all?
Let him kiss your woman!
But she's not near
as pretty as Bulma is, see?
It's a compliment!
He blew up another world!
What an insane creature!
He keeps blowing himself to
smithereens and then reforming!
[chuckles]
[OLIBU roars]
[BOTH giggle]
[KRILLIN]
Ready! Set!
[YAMCHA]
Go!
[BOTH grunting]
[gasps]
[BOTH whimper]
[KING KAI gasps]
[chuckles]
[gasping]
It's him!
Who in the heck is he?
Something tells
me this isn't good.
Hey, what's got
you so shaken up?
That's Majin Buu!
Huh?
How did he get here?
He's not dead!
Darn him! He's found
his way to Other World!
Let's go get him!
[OLD KAI] Hey! I think it's
time you got around
to giving them your
earrings, don't you?
These two will clean Buu's
clock if they fuse together!
[KIBITO KAI]
Yes! Of course!
Gosh! Goku! Vegeta!
If it wasn't for you
where would all of us be?
Cheers!
[GOKU] You'll have to forgive
me, guys... but no thanks!
[BOTH squeal]
I think some things are even
more important than victory.
These just aren't right for us.
Maybe if they weren't
permanent, you know?
I... understand.
[GOKU] Besides! Buu's not a
fused being himself anymore.
It's only fair that I fight
him in my natural state.
What are you saying?!
Have you lost your marbles?!
Put those on!
This isn't about your ego!
This is the fate of the Universe
we're talking about here!
[KIBITO KAI]
Perhaps you should reconsider.
Kindly, allow me to put an end
to any further speculation!
[BOTH scream]
We're Saiyans after all.
We do have our pride.
But how do you think you're
going to beat Majin Buu
in his present state?!
This is his original form!
He's more powerful than ever!
Don't worry!
It'll work out somehow.
[gasping]
How dare him, that little louse!
[KID BUU chuckles]
[KRILLIN thinking]
He looks different than before!
[YAMCHA thinking] I will
not become a chocolate bar!
Whoa! Get away from him!
What has gotten
into you, Northy?
Huh! Well, now.
I see you've come here
for a little training
from us, have you?
Scrawny little
thing, aren't you?
The training is tough!
If you want to back out,
now's the time!
[gasps]
No ring?
Well, I'll be darned!
[laughter]
[PIKKON] We've got a
live one here, boys!
[laughing continues]
No! Don't get him riled up,
Pikkon! Please!
Nice ventilation! Just
don't drink too much water!
[KID BUU giggles]
[gasps]
Take cover!
[screams]
[OLIBU grunts]
[screaming continues]
[screaming]
[KING KAI screams]
[screaming continues]
So what? What did you prove?
That you're a
big loudmouth, huh?!
That's it!
[giggles]
Whoa! He's healed! Incredible!
[OLIBU, PIKKON grunt]
Good gravy! Is he training
or trying to kill us?!
[FIGHTERS yelling]
[KRILLIN thinking] I know I'm
going to regret this,
but... here goes!
Destructo Disc!
Yeah!
[KRILLIN grunting]
[YAMCHA]
Krillin!
Hey! Stop it!
Are you okay?!
That was a great try, man!
It would have worked
on anyone else but him!
[giggles]
Stop that! Are you insane?!
You'll destroy the planet!
[KIBITO KAI]
Good heavens!
He's gonna blow up
the Great Kai Planet!
That's not good! Krillin and
Yamcha have already died!
If it happens again, they won't
exist in this realm anymore!
But I'm not going to
allow that to happen!
[VEGETA]
Kakarot! Wait!
Why don't we call
him to us instead?
That way we can get him away
from all of those
innocent people.
It is us he's after.
But how do we call him?
Oh, use your brain, Kakarot!
All we have to do is
raise our power levels
and he'll come running.
Of course!
[VEGETA]
Let's do it!
Right!
[GOKU, VEGETA yell]
[KID BUU laughs maniacally]
[giggles]
We're adding fuel to the fire!
[YAMCHA]
That attack isn't meant for us!
He's gonna blow up
the whole darn planet!
[GOKU, VEGETA yell]
[KID BUU laughs]
He's crazy!
Ah! This is it!
[GOKU, VEGETA yell]
[YAMCHA]
Krillin, if we die again...
[KRILLIN]
I know! I know!
Buu squash you like bugs! Huh?
[chuckles, laughs]
Dumb-dumbs!
[KID BUU cackles]
[KRILLIN]
What's the deal?
Huh! Don't ask!
[GOKU yells, gasps]
[GOKU]
That was quick!
[KID BUU chuckles]
--[MR. SATAN groans]
--[BEE barks]
Help!
[NARRATOR] Majin Buu has been
summoned by Goku and Vegeta
to the sacred land of the Kais.
But without the
fusion earrings,
does the super duo stand a
chance against this radical,
pink menace?
Stay tuned for scenes from the
next episode of Dragon Ball Z!