[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
the mutating monster, Majin Buu,
found himself totally outclassed
by Super Saiyan Vegito,
the radical warrior formed by
the fusion of Goku and Vegeta!
[VEGITO]
Still hungry, Buu?
Curse you!
Eat this!
[NARRATOR] It was a hard
pill to swallow for Buu,
who had dominated
every opponent thus far,
and decimated the entire
population of the Earth!
But to Vegito,
an amalgam of the two greatest
Saiyans that ever lived,
the universal giant of evil was
a mere plaything in his hands!
[NARRATOR] The simmering anger
at his own inferiority
worked itself up to a boil
and Majin Buu flew into a rage
that shook the very
foundations of the Universe!
[NARRATOR]
As the temporal boundaries
between dimensions began
to be compromised,
Vegito had to either stop
Buu's radical power surge,
or bear witness
to the destruction
of the entire physical cosmos!
[NARRATOR]
But in true Saiyan style,
Vegito pierced
Majin Buu's defenses,
and prevented the horrible
cataclysm from taking place!
[VEGITO]
Well, if you ask me,
that was a little too
close for comfort.
But have the decency
to learn your lesson!
There's no way you
can ever beat me!
Unless you'd like to try that
technique you've been saving!
[KING YEMMA]
Huh, huh, ho! This is great!
Pay per view! You can't beat it!
Can you believe that pink
galoot? I mean, that selfish oaf
almost destroyed the
entire physical universe!
[KING YEMMA chuckles]
Not with Vegito there!
If it were Goku by himself,
it would be all over by now!
Thank goodness he
has a little help!
Well, King Yemma, it sure
is a lucky coincidence
that you decided to preserve
Vegeta's body, isn't it?
[laughs]
Coincidence?
You're not suggesting
I didn't see this coming,
are you, Baba?
Oh, that's a good one!
You're a funny old witch!
Great King Yemma
didn't get this job
because of strange coincidences!
[laughs]
[GOBLINS cheer]
Well! Forgive me!
I guess I was just thinking
you were a brainless bouncer
who knew how to
use a rubber stamp!
[yelps, groans]
[GOBLINS groan]
[growling]
[sighs]
Great power! Don't waste it!
What d'ya say that you
try it out on yours truly?
Huh?
--[VEGITO gasps]
--[SUPER BUU grunts]
[grunting]
[SUPER BUU grunting]
[growls]
[SUPER BUU groans]
[SUPER BUU screams]
[SUPER BUU cackles]
[yells]
[VEGITO chuckles]
[VEGITO] I guess he
fell to pieces on me!
[SUPER BUU cackles]
You didn't think it
was over, did you, Vegito?
Yeah, but I'm not disappointed!
[yells]
[gasping]
Come now, you shoudn't be angry.
You know I was only
trying to help you!
Besides, you looked ridiculous
with that big
banana on your head!
This is a much
better look for you!
[growls]
You! I hate you!
Sheesh! What's wrong?
Why is he tempting fate
by toying with Buu?
The fusion with Vegeta must
have skewed Goku's judgment!
He's just too darn arrogant!
It's this younger generation!
Hey! Stop clowning around!
Move! What do you think
you're doing? Attack!
It's a darn shame
he can't hear me!
That would have done the trick!
No way! Curse you! You-You pig!
[VEGITO] You're the one
with the pink skin!
[growls]
Hey! Don't get so
down in the dumps!
You've won every
fight you've been in!
You know, everyone meets
their better sooner or later!
No! I won't lose! You'll see!
[SUPER BUU grunting]
Uh?
[GHOST 1 cackles]
[GHOSTS cackling]
Fright, fight!
Super Ghost Kamikaze Attack!
[VEGITO]
You're not being very original!
That attack belongs to Gotenks!
Oh! So you know, huh?
Then you know how dangerous
these little ghouls can be!
The slightest touch
and you will explode!
[GHOSTS cackling]
I'd hoped you'd do better
than these childish pranks!
Ha!
[GHOSTS cackling]
[SUPER BUU cackles]
Banshee Blast!
[GHOSTS whimper]
[GHOSTS scream]
Did you really think that
ridiculous attack would work?
It's nothing more
than a kids game!
A game dreamed up
by two children!
Come on! You can do better
than that! Can't you?
[SUPER BUU]
I knew that it wouldn't work!
I was conducting
a little experiment!
I know all of your
friends' attacks! Ha!
And I've already come up with
a variation to this one!
You'll love it!
[growling]
[chuckles]
You think it's going
to be the same?
Well, you're wrong!
Yeah! I noticed you had
a bigger litter this time!
Fool! Mock me while you can!
Super Kamikaze Ghost Attack!
[GHOSTS cackling]
There!
[GHOSTS]
Ka... Me... Ha...
Oh, man!
[GHOSTS cackling]
[GHOST 2]
Me...
[gasps]
[GHOSTS]
Ha!
Ka... Me... Ha...
[gasps]
Oh, man!
[GHOSTS
Me...
Ha!
[GHOSTS cackling]
Not with my attack, they don't!
Confound him!
What?
[growls]
[GHOSTS]
Galic Gun!
[yelps]
[laughs]
So it's a silly kid's
game, huh? Well, bug off!
It was good enough
to beat you, loser!
[SUPER BUU]
Where's the blasted body?
Surely it's underneath
that rubble! It has to be!
Too bad it's not permanent!
It's a nice improvement!
How did you do that?
[VEGITO] Instant Transmission!
It's the only way to travel!
Hey, that was a clever idea,
using the Kamehameah Wave, Buu!
[SUPER BUUS growl]
No! Really! And then
that Galic Gun! Whoa!
Yeah, I coulda been killed!
Maybe I am exaggerating
a little bit!
But I could've at least gotten
a bruise or a little cut!
[SUPER BUUS growling]
[OLD KAI] Now, why doesn't
he finish him off
before it's too late?
If you're playing with fire,
you're gonna get burned!
Yes! I don't understand
what he's doing!
I do! He's showboating,
that's what! Silly numbskull!
It's not always
the most powerful one
that wins the fight!
[yells]
Huh?
[SUPER BUU groans]
--[VEGITO grunting]
--[SUPER BUU groaning]
Come on, Buu.
You're using your eyes
instead of feeling where I am!
There's no need to continue!
Why don't you give up?!
Never! Fool!
[SUPER BUU]
You're nothing!
Without the fusion, I could
rip both of you apart!
Oh, yeah? Well,
look who's talking!
You got your strength from
eating my sons and my friends!
[SUPER BUU]
I'm going to kill you!
[VEGITO] Or at least
make me use my hands!
Oh, that does it!
[SUPER BUU yells]
[DABURA]
Gohan! Gohan!
[BULMA]
Gohan! Come on out! It's us!
Gohan! Hey! Son! Where are you?
Gohan! Hello?
It doesn't seem like we're
ever going to find him!
Don't lose hope, dear one!
I, Dabura, will find
your son at all costs--
even if I have to give
up my own life to do it!
Hey, bud!
That's a very
noble of sentiment,
but you are already dead.
You can't give what
you don't have, ya know!
[VIDEL]
Gohan still has it! To give!
I really think Gohan
still has it to give!
I know! You guys must think I'm
losing it, but I have a feeling!
I just don't believe
that Gohan's dead!
Call me crazy! Go ahead!
But I feel like he's
very far away from here!
I can't sense
spirits like he can,
but for some reason,
I just know it's true!
Oh, Videl!
I hope my heart's
not playing tricks on me!
No way! It couldn't be!
There's absolutly
nothing more powerful
than a woman's intuition,
I always say!
No harm can come from
wishing that it's true!
Besides, I think you and Gohan
have a special connection!
Gosh! Thank you!
You're deeply in love
with Gohan, aren't you?
Uh-- What? No way!
Yes! There's no hiding it!
I can see it written
all over your face, Videl!
So, this is love!
Beautiful, lovely love!
Ohhh! Now I've seen
it with my own eyes! Love!
The most powerful
force in the world!
[laughs nervously]
[SUPER BUU groans]
You can't even
lay a hand on me,
and yet you still
refuse to admit defeat!
Your pride is blinding you!
Can't you see the writing
that's on the wall!
You're done! Cooked!
It's all over!
Admit that you're
wrong and surrender!
[SUPER BUU thinking]
You wretch!
I'll find a way to kill you
if it's the last thing I do!
It's up to you! Do you
want to continue or not?
[SUPER BUU thinking] You fool!
I will never surrender to you!
Yes! There is
still one chance!
Let's go, blondie!
You know you can't win!
That's why you want
me to surrender, right?
Ha! Come on! I'm calling
your bluff, coward!
Huh?
What's wrong? Are you chicken?
Yeah, that's it! Let's do it!
[SUPER BUU thinking]
A little closer...
[SUPER BUU]
You're just a paper tiger!
If you can finish me off,
let's see it! Come on! Do it!
Fine! Let's end this
thing right now!
I like your style! You're
going to make great candy!
Huh?
[screams]
[BOTH gasping]
Candy?!
No! Vegeta! Goku!
[cackling]
[cackling] Yes!
[chanting] Majin Buu!
Big fat Buu!
Take that, sucker!
Yes!
Aaaah! Candy?
You idiots!
Bigheaded, arrogant,
no good bums! I knew it!
What a lost generation!
They're too full of
themselves to see straight!
[laughing]
Coffee flavored candy!
That's my fave!
Should I chew you to bits
or lick you to death?
[laughs]
Candy?!
Yuk! Why coffee? That's gross!
[NARRATOR]
Through his evil stratagems,
Majin Buu has managed to
turn the tides once again!
Is there any hope
for the Earth
now that Vegito has been
turned into a coffee-flavored
Super Saiyan Sucker?
Find out on the next
episode of Dragon Ball Z!