[NARRATOR] Previously
on Dragon Ball Z,
Piccolo and Nail
have become one,
and at first it seemed like they
stood a chance against Frieza.
But since his transformation,
Frieza has become unstoppable.
[FRIEZA] Now you'll
see I wasn't bluffing
because I'll be transforming
before your very eyes.
Watch carefully, now.
And keep in mind it's
not my ultimate form.
I still have one more
transformation!
You're full of it.
So, are you ready to get
this over with or what?
Yaah!
[NARRATOR] After his
transformation,
Frieza's superior speed
and strength have rendered
Piccolo totally powerless
and in dire straits!
[NARRATOR} Can Gohan save
Piccolo from certain death?
Find out today!
[PICCOLO grunting]
[grunting continues]
[GOHAN yelling]
[FRIEZA] Hmm...?
[GOHAN] Haah!
[GOHAN] Masenkooo...
Haaa!
[BOTH yell]
[FRIEZA laughs]
[FRIEZA grunts]
[GOHAN grunts]
[GOHAN yelling]
[FRIEZA grunting]
[yelling continues]
Gohan...
Gohan!
[DENDE grunts]
[GOHAN yells]
Yaaagh!
[FRIEZA grunting]
[GOHAN growls]
I've had enough
of you, Friezaaa!
[FRIEZA grunts]
[GOHAN yells]
[grunting continues]
[GOHAN grunts]
[KRILLIN] Just a little
further, Gohan!
[FRIEZA yells]
[GOHAN gasps]
[PICCOLO grunts]
I guess I owe you, Piccolo.
[thinking] Phew. That was close.
[FRIEZA] Strange! Where did the
little one get all his power?
[FRIEZA] That kid's stronger
than any Saiyan
I've ever fought.
I better keep my
eye on that one.
I wonder who he is? I'm sure
I eliminated all the Saiyans
except for Vegeta, Nappa, and
Raditz twenty years ago!
How'd he survive?
Neither one of those misfits
could possibly be his father.
[FRIEZA] No matter.
In the end they all must
be expunged anyway.
I can't believe
Frieza survived that.
But boy, that Gohan...
What a pistol.
[GOHAN thinking] Oh no!
I think that last attack
used up all my power!
Now what am I going to do?
[VEGETA thinking]
What I'd like to know
is how did that kid
become so powerful?!
[VEGETA] Hey, Cueball!
Huh?
[VEGETA] Listen up
and listen good,
'cause I'm only going
to say this once!
The only way we can beat Frieza
is for you to whip me to
within an inch of my life!
Because, as you've just
witnessed,
a Saiyan's power grows
stonger after recovering
from serious injuries.
I need to be stronger!
Understand me?!
Y-Yeah.
[VEGETA] Good!
The time is now. I must crush
these miserable Saiyans.
Because they're
like pesky insects.
Once you let them
get a foothold,
they can be hard to wipe out.
Best eliminate them now,
before they gain momentum.
Well, what are you
waiting for, huh?!
Punch me! Cut a hole in me!
'Cause if you don't,
we are doomed!
B-but I could hurt you...
if I beat you up too much!
Very unlikely. Let's get
the show on the road, shall we?
Now, according to my plan,
once that Namekian gnome down
there sees I'm nearly toast,
he has no choice
but to heal me, right?
[KRILLIN growls]
Even though I can't stand
your guts, I can't do it!
Why, you...!
Besides, after what I just
saw Gohan do, who needs you?!
[VEGETA] Give me a break!
After that attack, the kid
doesn't have any power left!
[FRIEZA laughs]
Pardon me,
I hate to interrupt a spirited
conversation such as yours,
but I am running on a bit of a
tight schedule. So, to be fair,
I'll even give you the choice
of which one of you
will be my first victim!
I, uh, i think he's
talking to us, Vegeta!
No! I'm not ready!
[FRIEZA] My dear, dear friend,
who is ever ready to meet
their final fate? Hmm?
Now feast your eyes on my
ultimate transformation!
[whimpering]
[growling]
[FRIEZA growls]
It's... incredible.
Now what do we do?
[VEGETA] C'mon, c'mon! We
can still do it if we hurry!
C'mon!
[VEGETA] Do it... Do it!
[DENDE whimpers]
[FRIEZA growls]
[FRIEZA yells]
[BULMA gasps]
[BULMA screams]
[BULMA] What's going on here?!
[BULMA wails]
Ahh, it's all over. Doomed
without any mascara on...
Oh, why did I even come to this
stupid planet to look for those
stupid Dragon Balls anyway?!
Nobody cares if I exist!
Stupid Krillin! Stupid
Gohan! Stupid Goku!
I hate you! I hate you all!
Oh, I think I broke a nail...
[thinking] I can feel
Frieza's power growing!
I've got to get out of here!
[FRIEZA yelling]
[VEGETA] C'mon, c'mon,
what are you waiting for?!
Can't you see
it's now or never?!
[KRILLIN] B-But I can't
fight you, Vegeta!
[KRILLIN screams]
[KRILLIN] Here goes nothing!
Yaah!
You've gotta do
better than that!
Now try again!
Ah, humans! You are pathetic!
I know infants who can
fight better than you!
[KRILLIN screams]
Uh...?
Huh?!
[VEGETA chuckles]
Now, I too, will become a Super
Saiyan... and annihilate Frieza.
Hey, what's going on? What'd
you do that for, Krillin?!
[FRIEZA laughs]
[PICCOLO gasps]
Gohan, you better get
out of here right now!
B-But...
[GOHAN gasps]
[GOHAN] Are you okay, Piccolo?
[PICCOLO] I'm... not sure.
[FRIEZA yells]
[yelling continues]
[FRIEZA laughs]
Wait a sec! I've got it!
My friend Dende can help.
He's a Namek with a
special healing power
to fix you right up!
C'mon! There's no time to waste!
[KRILLIN] Gohan!
Krillin! We gotta find Dende!
[DENDE whimpers]
[VEGETA] C-C'mere kid!
You gotta help me...
If you know what's good for you,
you will. You understand?
[DENDE] But I can't help you!
What are you saying?
I know you can help!
I've seen you heal
other people!
[DENDE] I can only heal
those who have a good heart.
You! Your heart is black
from the people you've hurt.
Why, you little...! Unless
you heal me, you little brat,
Frieza's going to
wipe us all out!
Sorry, I can't!
[FRIEZA yells]
Hey, c'mon...
I don't have time for your
stupid moral dilemma, kid.
Alright! I-I'll try.
I'm sorry, I can't do it!
[VEGETA] You'll pay for this!
Game... over...
[KRILLIN] So then, Vegeta
told me to beat him up
because he said if I did,
he'd get Dende to heal him and
turn him into a Super Saiyan!
[GOHAN] Oh!
Well, I did it, figuring
once he was a Super Saiyan,
he'd take on Frieza and
whip his sorry butt!
[GOHAN] Really?!
[KRILLIN] Huh?
--It's Dende!
--Dende?
Look!
It's Vegeta!
[FRIEZA yells]
So, I hear... you... have the...
power to heal. Can you heal me?
[DENDE] I'll try...
[FRIEZA growls]
[laughing]
[growling continues]
[FRIEZA laughs]
[PICCOLO Well, everything
looks back to normal.
Thanks kid, I owe ya.
Well, I didn't do it
to help you out, sir.
I did it to help Nail.
Dende, listen. The only way to
beat Frieza is to heal Vegeta.
You gotta understand
it's our only hope.
[DENDE] I... I can't.
[BOTH] Huh?
He's just like Frieza!
I can't help someone who
destroyed my people!
[NAIL] Sorry, kid, but I have
to agree with your friends.
[DENDE gasps]
[NAIL] All of us combined
are no match for Frieza,
so we need Vegeta.
There's no other way!
[FRIEZA groans]
[FRIEZA yells]
It's.. It's Frieza!
What are we gonna do?!
He must be finished
transforming!
[KRILLIN] Uh, guys? I say we
get outta here while we can.
At least until
Goku's up to speed!
[PICCOLO] If we do that, Frieza
will destroy this entire planet,
including Goku!
I know Frieza has no regard
for anyone or anything.
In my wildest dreams I've never
seen anything so... powerful.
I wonder what "it"
will look like...
I'll bet it's the most hideous,
ugly, repulsive creature
in the universe.
Please, Dende.
You have to forget about
the past and heal Vegeta.
[DENDE whimpers]
Thanks, Dende.
[PICCOLO] I can see him!
[VEGETA grunts]
Oh, by the way...
Thanks!
Hey, punk! You're just lucky
you caught me in a good mood!
Ah, at last Frieza
decidees to show himself.
And from here, he doesn't
look so tough anymore!
Well, I guess now that
my power has increased...
It's time to let my
fists do the talking!
[VEGETA chuckles]
[DENDE whimpers]
[thinking] Oh no, I can sense
something terrible... Frieza!
[NARRATOR] Now that
Frieza has completed
his final transformation,
the stage is set for
the ultimate showdown.
Find out who will survive
in the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!