[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z.
In a desperate attempt
to defeat Gohan,
Cell prepared to release
a deadly Kamehameha Wave
aimed directly at the Earth.
[CELL] Here you go!
Let's see you try
and stop this!
[NARRATOR] But Gohan
stood his ground.
[CELL] HAAA!
[GOHAN] Kaa... meeh... haa...
meeh...
HAA!
[NARRATOR} At the last moment,
Gohan countered Cell's attack
with his own more
powerful blast,
catching the monster
off guard
and saving the Earth
from certain destruction.
[CELL screams]
[NARRATOR] When the smoke
cleared, it was obvious
that Gohan's clever tactic
had done the trick.
Cell was half the cruel
creature that he used to be.
[GOHAN] I'm going
to let him suffer.
[NARRATOR] But Cell quickly
regenerated his lost limbs,
and bulked himself
up to maximum power
in an explosion of insane anger.
[CELL] Boy! You won't defeat me!
A worthless Saiyan like
you can't compete with me!
I am invincible!
[NARRATOR] Gohan took
Cell's words as a challenge
and booted the
beast in the belly
giving him a monstrous
case of indigestion.
It was too much for the
dastardly demon too handle.
His evil appetite came back to
haunt him as he lost his lunch
and his complete power
when he regurgitated
the unconscious Android 18!
Cell's strength is fading fast.
Will Gohan deliver
the final blow
and end his reign of terror?
Today on Dragon Ball Z!
[CELL grunts]
[grunting continues]
Don't touch her!
[PICCOLO] Krillin!
[CELL growls]
[CELL yells]
Oh my! I don't believe it!
It looks like Cell has
been damaged beyond repair!
Is this the end?
Will that tough kid
be declared the champ?!
Has he won the Cell Game?!
Uh... boss the microphone
is still broken...
Just great!
This is such a shame.
My voice, has been silenced!
[CELL grunts]
Oh man! What's happening?
[CELL growling]
[gasping]
[CELL whimpers]
Look! He's changed!
He isn't in his
final form anymore!
Yes! Gohan has won!
Cell was no match for him!
[thinking] I don't believe it!
[CELL growling]
[growling continues]
BOY!
[CELL growls]
[CELL] You little insect!
You've made a fool of me!
[CELL yells]
[CELL snarls]
[CELL grunts]
That's the way!
Gohan! Finish him off now!
[CELL grunts]
[CELL] Stay away
from me, you monster!
[CELL whimpers]
[CELL screams]
[CELL grunting]
Give up or fall.
[CELL growls]
Nooo!
[CELL grunting]
[CELL grunts]
[CELL screams]
--[GOHAN yells]
--[CELL yells, grunts]
[CELL grunts]
[CELL] I'll get you for this,
boy! I swear I will!
Cell, give up.
You aren't going to beat me.
[PICCOLO] Gohan is
toying with him!
Now, Gohan!
End it right now!
There's no time to waste!
Get him, Gohan!
[CELL whimpers]
[whimpering continues]
No! Stay back!
[CELL screams]
[CELL grunting]
[gasping]
Cell has changed once again!
What kind of
crazy strategy is this?
He has pumped himself
up like a balloon
and it looks like he
could burst at any moment!
[CELL growls]
[KRILLIN] What is Cell
trying to do now?
Look at the size of him!
[thinking] I don't like
the look of this!
Run, Gohan!
[CELL laughs]
Boy, this is the end for you!
You thought you could
beat me but you can't!
[CELL laughs]
I'm going to blow myself up now!
And I'm going
to take you with me!
Say goodbye to
your precious planet!
No, don't!
What? Blow up the Earth?!
[GOKU growls]
Yes, that's right!
Cell's not bluffing this time.
I know he'll do it!
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[CELL laughs]
[CELL] You lose, little man! I'm
going to destroy this planet!
[GOHAN growls]
No you won't!
Watch out!
You might make me explode!
You don't
want to make me upset!
One little shock
could set me off!
Then it's, bye-bye Gohan,
bye-bye Goku, and so long Earth!
[GOHAN growls]
[CELL laughs]
One minute, boy! Ha, ha, ha!
And then it will all be over!
--[CELL laughs]
--[GOHAN gasps]
We're done for!
[TIEN] No! Somebody has
to come up with a plan!
Darn! This time...
there's nothing we can do!
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[CELL yells]
There's forty
more seconds left!
[thinking] Dad was right!
I should have destroyed
Cell when I had the chance.
I let my powers go to my head!
[CELL whimpering]
Gohan! Listen to me!
You've got to get him!
Do it now!
We all know
you have the power!
It's time to use it!
I could have destroyed Cell!
Now there's nothing I can do!
I failed...
[GOHAN] What have I done...?
[GOHAN growls]
I've been a fool!
I've let Cell win again!
[KRILLIN] Gohan's in trouble!
No! Time is running out!
Cell has beaten
us again! It's over!
[CELL laughs]
[KRILLIN] What is it, Goku? Do
you have a plan or something?!
What? What do you
want us to do?
Listen, there's
not much time left
and I can only think of
one way to save the Earth now.
[KRILLIN gasps]
What are you talking about?
No, don't!
I think I know
what you have planned, Goku!
You don't have to do this!
Goodbye, friends...
[VEGETA gasps]
[KRILLIN gasps]
Goku? Wait, don't leave us!
[CELL laughs]
[CELL] Ten more seconds
and the Earth will be gone!
I guess we'll
call the game a draw!
[GOHAN whimpers]
[CELL laughs]
NOOO!
[CELL gasps]
Hey, you put up
a good fight, Gohan.
I'm proud of you.
What? Daddy?
Take care of your mother
for me. She needs you.
Tell her that I
had to do this, Gohan.
[GOHAN gasps]
Goodbye, my son...
[CELL growls]
Goku!
[CELL] No, don't--!
[GOHAN grunts]
NO, COME BACK!
GOKU!
[gasping]
[KING KAI screams]
Goku!
What have you done?!
Are you out of your mind?!
[GOKU] Sorry, guys!
This is the only place
I could think to bring him.
Well, you could
have called first!
[CELL growls]
[screaming]
[BUBBLES screams]
[GREGORY screams]
[KING KAI screams]
[CELl growls]
[screaming]
[ALL screaming]
[GOHAN whimpers]
No, Goku. He's gone...
[KRILLIN] Goku...!
[GOHAN whimpers]
DADDY!
[ROSHI] Hmm!
What's wrong?
[ROSHI] It's strange.
I can't feel Goku or
Cell's life force anymore!
Can you tell if
Goku is still alive?
[ROSHI] Hmm...
[BULMA gasps]
[GOHAN growls]
Well, that's it.
The Cell Game is over!
Yes, this is the end;
they're gone.
Both of them!
They've both disappeared!
[ANNOUNCER gasps]
[ANNOUNCER] I wish my
microphone was working.
Hey, Hercule Look! It's over...
[MR. SATAN] What a shame.
[GOHAN sobs]
That's right. Cry.
You just let it all out,
little buddy.
[GOHAN sobs]
It's all my fault!
Dad, didn't have to
sacrifice himself!
I wish it
would have been me!
Now, he's gone
and I'm still here!
Hey, don't blame yourself, kid!
If it weren't for you, the Earth
and all of us would be history.
You saved us.
[GOHAN whimpers]
Your dad was very proud
of you, Gohan. You know that!
And he had to do what he did,
because he loves you.
Now, come on. Let's go.
Huh...?
[KRILLIN] Android 18!
I almost forgot about her!
[KRILLIN] Come on, you guys!
She needs our help!
She's still alive!
Daddy...
Hey, guys, sorry for
involving you like this.
But I really had
no other choice, honest!
Goku, how could you?
And to me! Have you no respect?!
This is no way to treat a king!
I didn't deserve that!
[BUBBLES chatters]
What a mess! Look at us!
Because of you,
my planet was destroyed!
And now I'm stuck here
on Snake Way!
Aw, King Kai, I did it
to save the Earth!
I had to do it!
How many times do
I have to say I'm sorry?!
Yeah, how many times?
Goku! You've got some nerve!
You know what you are?!
You are a pest!
[GOKU] Sorry!
Hey, where's Cell?
Shouldn't he be here with us?
Yeah... I don't see
him around anywhere.
[KING KAI gasps]
[KING KAI] If Cell's not here,
then that means, oh no!
He's gone! He's gone!
This can't be!
When Cell blew himself up,
he should have been sent to
the Great Snake Way with us!
[GOKU] Huh?!
Then what does
this mean, King Kai?!
It means Cell was not
destroyed! He's alive!
Alive?!
Krillin! What are you doing?
Put that android down right now!
[KRILLIN] What?!
Destroy it now!
It's still alive!
No! She's hurt!
Come on, she's that not bad.
She just needs
some help, that's all!
You're pathetic!
Go do what you want to!
I don't care!
[GOHAN grunts]
Hey! What's that?!
[ALL gasp]
No! It can't be!
What is that?
He's... He's back!
[TRUNKS grunts]
[TRUNKS screams]
[VEGETA gasps]
[KRILLIN gasps]
[CELL chuckling]
[CELL laughing]
[CELL] My aim is
as good as ever!
It's so good to be back.
[CELL laughs]
[NARRATOR] Oh no!
Cell has somehow managed
to survive the explosion
on King Kai's planet!
He's come back stronger
than ever,
and now he's ready for
another round of evil!
Will Cell have the
last laugh after all?
Find out on the next
episode of Dragon Ball Z!