[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z!
[ANDROID 16] ...mountain
village, East District 439.
[NARRATOR] Android 16
knows the exact location
of Goku's house!
And now that Android 17 has been
pointed in the right direction,
it won't be long before
the mischievous machine
parks his van on
the ailing hero's doorstep.
[NARRATOR] Well aware of the
approaching Android threat,
Goku's friends raced
to move him to the safety
of Master Roshi's island.
Meanwhile, back at
Capsule Corporation,
Bulma had some puzzling news.
She's discovered what appears
to be a second time machine
abandoned in the countryside.
Trunks, I want you
to take a good look at it.
[beeping]
Here, check it out.
[NARRATOR] Could it be
that there's really
another time machine out there?
And if so, where and when
did it come from?
Find out today!
I'm sure that this is
the same time capsule
I used to come here
from the future...
This is so weird!
Krillin, ask her if
she knows where this is.
Hey, Bulma, listen.
This capsule...
Where did you say it was?
Hmmm.
Well, I'm not sure exactly.
But it looks like it's somewhere
out in the west 1050 area.
You going?
Yes! I've got
to check this out!
[BULMA ON RADIO]
All right then. I'm going too!
I'll meet you there!
[BOTH gasp]
But... do you
think that's safe?
[BULMA] Trunks, remember,
Mother always knows best!
Are you positive your
time machine is one of a kind?
Yes. I'm sure of it!
[GOHAN] Hey, Trunks!
[TRUNKS] Huh?
Is it all right
if I come along with you?
I won't get in the way.
Uh--Gohan...
Aww... Don't worry, Mom.
I'll be just fine!
Gee, it's not like I can't
take care of myself!
Listen to me!
You're staying put
'til your homework is done.
[YAMCHA, TRUNKS,
and GOHAN groan]
[GOHAN] But, Mom,
I'll finish it all...
when I come back!
Mmm.
[MRS. BRIEF] So then,
how are my two favorite
love birds doing? Hmm?
[giggles]
Hey, Mom. I'm going
to go out for a while.
Can you watch Trunks for me?
[MRS. BRIEF] Well, I guess so...
Where ya goin', sweetie?!
Nowhere, really. I've just
got to go meet with Trunks!
Huh?!
[aircraft noise]
Trunks. Remember when
you were talking about
your world in the future?
Is it really true
that the Androids
have destroyed everything?
Yes. The Androids
managed to pretty much
annihilate our
entire population.
Some of us
escaped from West City
before it was destroyed,
and now the only way to survive
is to hide in our
secret base under-ground.
That's horrible...
Do you think we'll
be able to find some way
to stop them before
they destroy this world too?
Yeah... I do.
Now go out there
and finish them!
[TRUNKS] It stands to reason
that Dr. Gero would have known
about Android 17 and 18's
rebellious nature.
I doubt he would have
chanced activating them
unless he had some way
of turning them off again.
You're not going to
put us to sleep again.
Too late! Aaah!
[TRUNKS] With all of the
confusion that my father caused
when he blasted down
the door to the lab,
it was impossible to tell
how Dr. Gero lost control.
But it was obvious
that whatever safeguards
he put in place had failed.
You will do as I tell you to do!
I am your creator!
[gasps]
[TRUNKS] In the end, the
Androids destroyed Dr. Gero--
the only one who had any
knowledge of their weaknesses.
Nonetheless,
I'm confident that we can
still find the means to
deactivate those monsters.
Hm!
Once we figure out
how to turn them off,
we'll be able to prevent them
from taking over this world.
And I'll finally
be able to take back
what's left of mine.
That's great, Trunks!
I really hope you're right!
Well, that makes two of us...
[beeping]
Okay, we're coming over
West Section 1050.
[GOHAN] Let's check it out!
[SQUIRRELS squeaking]
Aaah...
[GOHAN] That's it!
Trunks!
[laughs]
[GOHAN] Trunks,
I found it! I found it!
[GOHAN]
Come on! It's down here!
That's it all right,
Gohan! Good work!
[distant aircraft noise]
Hey, I'll betcha that's Bulma!
I'll go tell her where we are!
♪
--[SQUIRRELS squeaking]
--[TRUNKS] Huh?
[BULMA] Hello down there!
Hi, Trunks! I'm back!
Did you miss me?
I guess so...
Well tell me,
what do you think
of the younger version
of your mother?
Pretty cute, huh?
Well, I'd say
you haven't really
changed that much.
You mean then...
I'll keep my girlish looks
for at least another ten years?
Oh, this is great! [laughs]
This is so embarrassing.
[laughs]
[BULMA laughing]
--[TRUNKS] So anyway...
--[BULMA laughing]
Look at this.
As you can see,
this is the time capsule
I traveled back here in.
[BULMA] Which means...
the other capsule
isn't yours after all!
They're both mine.
Remember, I said
we only managed to make
one time machine in the future.
The two capsules
you see here--
they're actually
one and the same.
I don't get it.
[TRUNKS] Here, look at this...
[BULMA] Hm? H-O-P-E...
Hope?
Yes. You wrote it just before
I left from the future.
And...
[TRUNKS] You'll find
the exact same thing
written on that other capsule.
But then...
what happened here?
The old capsule looks to me
like it's been here
for a pretty long time.
Wow...! How weird...
It's melted... but the
blast came from inside!
[GOHAN] Why would someone
wanna do that?
It doesn't make sense!
So--So Trunks...
What do you think
made that big hole?!
Honestly, I wish I knew.
[TRUNKS] Stand back!
[beep]
[eerie music plays]
What's this?
What in the world are those?
They look like
a couple of turtle shells.
Hey! Let me have a look!
[BULMA] Hm.
[GOHAN]
Well, what do you think, Bulma?
My guess is... maybe they're
like eggshells or something.
Eggshells?
It sure is strange...
What comes out of
a shell like this?
[BOTH] Hm.
Huh?!
Hey, wait a second!
Maybe whatever
hatched out of that egg
made that hole
in the capsule canopy!
[beeping]
It looks like there's
not much energy left in here.
I better work fast!
[beeping]
C'mon, c'mon,
don't give out on me.
I think I've figured out
when the capsule landed here.
It looks like
it was three years ago.
[BULMA] Huh?
No, wait! It came here
four years ago...
That just might
explain a few things.
[TRUNKS] It means that
by the time I battled Frieza
three years ago, whoever
used this other time machine
had already been
here for a year!
I-Is it possible
that he's... the one who...
changed history?
[TRUNKS] There can't be
any other explanation!
[birds cawing]
And that's what happened.
So that's the
whole story, eh?
Let's just hope that
Goku gets back on track
before those Androids
find us all here!
[ROSHI] That's all
we can do now is hope.
[OOLONG] Hey, wait a minute!
If those Androids are
going to Goku's house first
and they don't find him there...
isn't this the next
obvious place they'll look?!
[YAMCHA] Yeah, probably.
That seems logical enough!
[OOLONG] Huh?
Then what are we doing
waiting around here
like sitting ducks?!
When they get here
we're finished!
Speaking of ducks,
I'm getting hungry!
What am I? Chopped liver?
There's one thing you're
forgetting, I'm still here.
Right, Krillin?
Huh? [stammers]
Hurrah for our side...
Don't sass me, pig!
I'm Master Roshi, the supreme
Master of all Martial Arts!
[ROSHI] I was once considered
the strongest fighter
in the world!
And I didn't do too bad
with the ladies either!
Oh yeah?! Well that was
a long time ago!
Now you're just
a washed up old man
[OOLONG] who couldn't
fight his way out of
a wet paper bag
and you know it!
I don't understand how 16
can be so calm right now.
[ANDROID 18] It's been hours
since he opened his eyes,
let alone said anything.
You'd think that
he would be excited
that we're on our way
to Goku's house,
but instead he just
sits there like a rock!
Leave him alone, 18.
[ANDROID 17] 16 is just
focused on fighting Goku.
Now relax. We'll be
in the next town soon.
You'll finally be able to
find some new clothes there.
Excellent! I can't wait
to get out of these old rags.
You think you can
drive a little faster?
Yeah!
Well I guess that proves I'm
a genius after all, eh boys?
[BULMA] Imagine--me building
a time machine in the future!
[chuckles]
I don't think it's
such a good idea
to leave the time machine
out here in the open like this.
[TRUNKS] I'd better put it
back into it's capsule.
I'll put away the other capsule!
Okay. Thanks, Gohan.
I'll take the weird
eggshell thingies,
if that's all right with you.
Sure... Go for it.
Bulma...
Listen, I think we'd all better
hurry over to
Master Roshi's now.
Master Roshi's? But why?
Because, at any time now,
those Androids are
probably going to show up
there and try to fight my dad.
But if he's still sick in bed,
he won't be able
to defend himself.
I just think it's best
we get over there,
and if he's not
a hundred percent
we'll still have
a chance to move him!
I see. But shouldn't
enough of your dad's friends
already be there
to help him out, Gohan?
I don't think
you understand!
Even with the
combined strength
of Piccolo, Tien,
myself, and my father,
we're no match
against those Androids!
Wow... They're that strong, huh?
So how is Vegeta? Is he okay?
Did he go back
to Master Roshi's too?
He's gone off
to train alone somewhere.
Man! He's so focused on
himself that the thought of
helping anyone else probably
never even occurred to him!
[BULMA]
Well that sounds like Vegeta!
Hmmm? What?
I think... I see
something over there...
[BULMA] What? What do you see?
Uh...
[eerie music plays]
[gasps]
Hey you guys,
come here quick!
[BULMA gasps]
Ah, Trunks, wait for me!
[TRUNKS]
What? What is it, Gohan?!
--[TRUNKS] What's going on?
--[GOHAN] Behind the bushes...
[gasps]
[screams]
That thing is disgusting!
Aah...?
Yeah, but what is it?
I've never seen
anything like it!
You think it's dead?
Looks like whatever it was
crawled off after
it shed its skin...
Shed its skin...?
Do you think it might have been
some kind of a giant cicada?
I don't think so.
Not this thing.
Right, Trunks?
Mhmmm. This might be
what hatched out of the shell
we found inside the capsule.
Right. It grew up and then
molted out of it's skin.
You think?
[BULMA] What do you mean?
That some kind of
monster shed it's skin
and is now lurking
around the countryside?
[GOHAN] I'm not sure.
I've never seen
anything like this.
[TRUNKS] But the question is,
how did it get here
in the first place?
Did someone send the egg back
from the future all by itself?
Or did someone come back in
the time machine along with it?
Regardless of
where it came from,
it's totally revolting.
[TRUNKS] Ah! Ugh...
It's still wet...
This thing must be
somewhere close.
[screams]
♪
[TRUNKS] Huh?
[BULMA whimpers]
[distant rustling]
[BULMA screams]
[BULMA screaming]
[BOTH grunt]
[squeaking]
[BOTH sigh]
Uh, well guys...
level with me would ya?
Something's out there... right?
Right!
I guess I should go,
'cause I don't want to
get in the way...
If anything happens,
call me at Capsule Corp.
Or, uh, I'll call you
at Master Roshi's...
She's kinda bugged out.
[BULMA] Oh, and Trunks,
don't be a stranger
and visit me sometime!
You're grandparents
would love to meet you!
[thinking]
I wish I knew what on Earth
was going on around here.
Hmmm.
[KAMI] These new developments
are most unsettling, Mr. Popo.
[POPO] Yes, Kami.
Haven't you gotten tired
of standing there yet?
You're just wasting
your time, you know...
[PICCOLO] You can watch events
unfold as long as you'd like.
It won't change anything.
We're still going to have to
combine our powers
to fight the Androids!
For the last
four years I have felt
a terrible disturbance taking
shape on the earth below.
A great evil.
But I'm afraid it wasn't
the Androids that I sensed...
Huh?
There is another threat...
A vile creature, which I'm
afraid will prove to be
a hundred times
more lethal and cunning
than even the Androids!
What are you talking about?
Explain yourself
right now, you hear me?!
[KAMI]
I'm sure the day will come
when I give up being
guardian of the earth.
Then, and only then, can we
ever unite to fight as one.
[KAMI grunts]
[PICCOLO groans]
[growling]
[KAMI] Piccolo!
We will wait for
this new evil to surface.
And you will trust me.
I know what is
best for the earth.
But until I know exactly
what we're dealing with
I cannot make my decision!
[NARRATOR] Things are getting
interesting for our heroes.
While a monstrous creature
has mysteriously
come from the future
in Trunks' time machine,
three unstoppable
Androids are preparing
to bear down on a sickly Goku!
If Kami's hunch is correct,
the world faces a danger
unlike any it has
ever faced before!
Is there anyone who can
oppose this terrible threat?
Find out, on the
next exciting episode
of Dragon Ball Z!