[growling]
[groaning]
[NARRATOR] It's looks
like Garlic Jr.'s plan
to take over the world
is almost complete!
So far, he's shrunk Kami
down to the size of a toy
and turned almost
everyone else into zombies
by forcing them to breathe
in his evil Black Water Mist!
Even Krillin hasn't
escaped his madness!
[KRILLIN yelling]
[GOHAN yells]
Krillin!
Get 'em, Gohan...
Ma-sen-ko!
[GOHAN yells]
[SALT screaming]
Now it's up to Gohan
to save the planet!
Save some for me!
[PICCOLO growls]
Piccolo...
[NARRATOR] But does
he even stand a chance
with everyone against him?
[GARLIC JR. cackling]
Yes my pet. Destroy him!
Then the entire universe will...
[NARRATOR]
Can Gohan escape the clutches
of his possesed friend?
Find out today!
[GOHAN gasping]
[PICCOLO grunting, cackling]
Piccolo... It's me... Gohan...
[GOHAN gasping]
[PICCOLO growling]
[GARLIC JR. cackling]
[KRILLIN]
Gohan... No...
[GOHAN groaning]
What's wrong with you?
[cackling]
You know what?
Piccolo's all right.
[growling]
Huh?
What's he doing?
He's gonna blow us up, too!
[GOHAN groans]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[GOHAN yells]
[grunting]
[GARLIC JR. cackling]
Excellent work, Piccolo!
Yes, once he was
young Gohan's mentor...
but the table's have turned!
And now... Piccolo will
destroy the rodent for me!
Kami, I have a
surprise for you!
I wouldn't want you
to miss the moment
Gohan becomes
part of my family!
Huh?
[GARLIC JR. cackling]
He's insane!
[GOHAN groans]
[GOHAN groaning, panting]
That's enough! We'll take
it from here, Piccolo!
[VINEGAR growling]
Our revenge for
Mustard and Salt!
[SPICE growling]
You're mine, maggot!
[growling]
Huh?
[PICCOLO growling]
[GOHAN groaning]
What's he doing?
I thought you told him
to leave the kid to us.
I did, but remember, Piccolo
and Gohan hate each other.
That hatred has been pent up in
Piccolo for years and probably
was released when he breathed
in the Black Water Mist.
Oh!
[GOHAN yells]
Wh-What are you gonna do?!
[PICCOLO cackles]
[GOHAN yells]
[PICCOLO groans]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN groans]
[KRILLIN]
It's now or never!
Now!
[KRILLIN grunts]
[KRILLIN groans]
[GARLIC JR.]
You are an idiot!
How dare you? You think
you can come into my chamber
and try to steal my pet?
[KRILLIN grunting]
Well, baldie, I dare you!
If you're so tough,
go ahead and try to snatch
the bottle from my hand!
Eat my boot!
[KRILLIN groans]
Stop Piccolo, please!
And now it's time...
to finish you off!
[GARLIC JR. yells]
Piccolo...
[GOHAN screams]
[PICCOLO yells]
[KRILLIN yells]
[GARLIC JR. growls]
Huh?
No... Is he? Uh...
[PICCOLO grunts]
[KRILLIN]
Gohan! Look out!
[grunting]
[KRILLIN yelling]
[PICCOLO grunting]
[GARLIC JR. giggles]
[KRILLIN yelling]
[PICCOLO growling]
[PICCOLO growls]
[KRILLIN yells]
Put him down!
[KRILLIN yelling]
I said put him down, now!
[PICCOLO grunts]
[GOHAN]
Krillin!
Snap out of it!
It's your turn!
[KORIN chuckles]
[MARON giggles]
[KORIN]
Huh?
[MARON] Yes! There you go!
Read 'em and weep!
That makes 22
games straight!
[YAJIROBI]
Wha...?
This is just great, Korin!
I thought you could
read people's minds?
So how come she keeps winning?
Would you keep it down?! Please!
I tried, but it doesn't
seem to work on her!
What?
The girl doesn't have a
single thought in her head!
[KORIN] Look at her!
I've seen party balloons
that have more on their minds!
[YAJIROBI]
What an airhead!
I win the bell!
I never would have
imagined a little bell
could get me into heaven!
So, you two, what do
you have left to bet?
[KORIN]
This!
It's a mystical magical wand
that works with the bell,
to get you into heaven. Oh and,
it's also a letter opener!
[MARON]
Hm...
[YAJIROBI]
Hey, wait a sec...
What are you
trying to do, Korin?
Will you zip it?
I'm not going to
lose to this ditz again!
Krillin said his friends were
a little "funny" in the head
and he was right!
[KORIN]
All right, just one more game!
And this time,
quit looking at my cards!
[YAJIROBI] Why are you
getting mad at me, Korin?
She's the one who's winning!
[KORIN]
And it's all your fault!
[GOHAN]
No, Krillin... Please, no!
Come on...
Listen to me, Krillin. Wake up!
[cackling]
You gotta come-to!
[PICCOLO grunts]
[GOHAN grunts]
[GOHAN grunting]
[PICCOLO growls]
[GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN grunting]
Hmph! That's what you get
when you send a Namek
to do a man's job!
[GOHAN panting]
[GOHAN growls]
Huh?
[GOHAN groans]
[PICCOLO grunting]
[GOHAN groaning]
[GOHAN panting]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[grunting]
[GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN panting]
[PICCOLO growling]
[PICCOLOS grunting]
[grunting]
[GOHAN panting]
[GARLIC JR. cackles]
[GOHAN growls]
[GARLIC JR.]
Well, on the bright side,
at least you'll
get to see the bottle
of Sacred Water
before I terminate you!
How dare you...
Don't take another step forward
if you know what's good for you!
[growling]
That's it!
[VINEGAR grunts]
[GOHAN groans]
[GOHAN coughing]
[GOHAN]
Krillin!
[KRILLIN grunts]
[GOHAN groans]
What... happened to you?
Oh... Oh no!
Krillin's one of them now!
Don't you get it, Gohan?
Huh?
[GARLIC JR.] Whether you breathe
in the Black Water Mist,
or get bitten by someone
who has, it's all the same!
You become one of us
and your only mission
is to serve me,
the almighty Garlic Jr.!
Huh?
Why don't you join us?
You're the only one
who's left, kido!
[VINEGAR] S'cuse me, sire!
It'd be my pleasure
to rid you of this roach!
[SPICE] Unless, of course,
you would like the honor
of finishing off the little
ratbag yourself, my lord!
Nah! Have fun, boys!
[grunting]
[GOHAN gasps]
[GOHAN groans]
That's enough!
Wait! I think I will
finish him off after all!
Oh, the pleasure is all yours!
Huh?
[grunting]
Krillin! Catch!
I got 'em!
[GARLIC JR. growling]
You'll pay for that!
Yeah, well I don't think that's
gonna happen, Garlic breath!
[PICCOLO grunts]
[PICCOLO groans]
[GARLIC JR. growling]
[KRILLIN] Hey! That was one heck
of a plan, Piccolo, but uh...
Gohan here's pretty messed up!
[PICCOLO]
Ha! He's fine!
Don't worry, I know I've
trained Gohan to withstand
a lot worse than this!
[KRILLIN]
Hey!
Huh?
[GARLIC JR. growling]
This isn't over yet,
mark my word!
Hmph!
[NARRATOR]
It looks like Piccolo has bought
our heroes a little time!
But one thing's for sure,
Garlic Jr. and his henchmen
won't take this sitting down!
The real battle is still ahead,
don't miss the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!