[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Goku and Gohan
struggled to adapt their
incredible Super Saiyan
strength to life at home.
[GOKU] You gotta control it,
like me. Watch this, see?
[NARRATOR] But when you're used
to holding planet-conquering
tyrants in your grip,
everyday life
can be tricky.
[NARRATOR] With Cell's deadly
tournament only days away,
Goku was determined to enjoy
the simpler things in life.
[GOKU laughs]
Family ties were
strengthened as ChiChi
held a party for
Gohan's eleventh birthday!
It was a time to share
laughs and memories.
[NARRATOR] Dark days lie ahead,
and Goku's family and
friends are spending
this precious time in the
best possible way: together.
Now, can our heroes find
the strength to beat Cell,
and restore the planet's peace?
Find out today!
[VEGETA growls]
Agh! What is taking that
Namek so long?! Really!
Doesn't he know he's wasting
important people's time?!
Well, he's almost
done, just stay calm.
[VEGETA] "Calm"?!
Oh, I will show you calm!
If he stays there any longer,
I'll knock that door down
and calmly drag him out!
Look! He's done!
[VEGETA] Well, it's about time!
Great! A dramatic entrance!
Alright! Out of my way!
[thinking] Wow! Piccolo's
power has gone way up!
That's funny. You
haven't changed at all.
[VEGETA chuckles]
What were you doing
in there? Taking a nap?
[thinking] Now I will
show you, Kakarot!
I'm going to surpass you.
Once and for all!
[KING FURRY] And so, my dear
citizens, do not be afraid.
The Royal Military shall
mount a courageous attack,
and silence the infamous Cell
with one triumphant swoop!
As I have often said, there is
nothing to fear but fear itself!
Those guys are in
for some big trouble.
They should know by now
that Goku's their only chance!
Dr. Gero's androids
really are something!
And that goes for this guy, too!
I mean, the level
of detail in his circuitry?
It must have taken Dr. Gero
years and years to finish!
[BULMA] Now if only
I could decode
this energy detection sequence.
See? There's one! Right there!
I told you this lake
was perfect for fishing!
Is this okay, Dad?
I feel bad that we're
not training right now.
Yeah, it does feel kinda
weird acting so relaxed.
Oh, come on, you guys.
I think we can handle Cell!
"Think"? What do
you mean "think"?
Don't worry! We can win,
and remember:
we've reached a level that
there's no point in passing.
We've done all
that we can! Okay?
Okay!
Well, if you say so, I suppose
that's enough for me!
Hey guys! Wash your
hands, lunch is ready!
Oh, coming!
Now, son, let's try
to enjoy ourselves
and not worry about Cell!
There'll be plenty
of time for that.
[GOKU] Woo-hoo!
Would you look at this?!
ChiChi, you've outdone yourself!
[KRILLIN] Hey, Goku,
I've been meaning to ask.
Since when have you
had a driver's license?
Oh, you know!
He and Piccolo went to get
a license three years ago!
And... they gave him one?!
[CHICHI] Well, not exactly...
You see, Piccolo and Goku
decided to have a little race
during their driving test,
and they were just
flying across the road like
a couple of 16-year olds!
[INSTRUCTOR] Look out!
[CHICHI] That's just like
you guys, to turn something
as simple as a driving
test into another competition.
It was a wonder no one got hurt.
[GOKU laughs]
[GOKU] Well, my driving
instructor may have hurt
his lungs screaming so much!
He sure was scared!
[CHICHI laughs]
[CHICHI] Can you blame him?
From what I hear, you
nearly had about
fifty head-on collisions!
[GOKU chuckles]
[GOKU] Yeah, some of 'em
were kinda close...
Now what?
[INSTRUCTOR sighs]
[CHICHI] After that day, I never
thought Goku
would get his license.
But then, I pleaded
with the instructor
to give Goku another chance,
and after five
more tries
this big lug of mine
finally got it right!
Well, are you glad he did?
Yeah, I love when
Goku drives me places.
Yeah, I bet!
You know, it's really
the smallest things
that can make you
happy in your life.
[CHICHI sighs]
A nice Sunday drive.
A family picnic on a warm day.
Or when you close your eyes and
fall into your husband's arms.
My hands are full.
[CHICHI groans]
Goku, we can all stop
by Master Roshi's house
on the way back
if you want to.
Yeah. Huh?
[GOKU] Where do you
suppose they're going?
[horns honking]
You big jerk!
You've got at least
two feet in front of you!
Shut up! Man, I really
hope Cell eats you!
[honking continues]
What a pile-up!
I guess they're running
away from the city.
Well, you can't blame 'em.
I mean, you tend to think
you're a lot safer
in the countryside, right?
Wish that were true...
[radio plays music]
This place is so quiet,
like a ghost town.
Well, when you think you only
have seven days to left to live,
who wants to go to work?
But it sure does make
it impossible to shop.
Yeah, it looks like we're
not going to be able to get
that gift for Master Roshi.
[REPORTER]
We interrupt this program
for a special news report.
Ah! There's
someone who's working!
[REPORTER] Early this morning,
the Royal Military was summoned
to stop the monstrous
tyrant known as Cell.
Ground troops, fleets
of tanks, and full air support
are now reaching
Cell's location.
What?!
[REPORTER] To those
tuning in on radio,
I only wish you
could see this now.
It really is an amazing
display, as the entire
Royal Military has assembled
to stop this global threat!
It is a sight that makes this
reporter feel much at ease!
M-Military Force?!
Fools! Don't they understand!?
They're all giving
up their lives for no reason!
Pathetic, all these
men still playing with toys.
Guns ready!
[CELL chuckles]
He's running!
Running?
I just don't want these
clumsy idiots to ruin my ring.
Now, men! Engage!
Don't let him get away!
[screaming]
[REPORTER]
The Military has unleashed
a full-scale attack
on the monster!
I'm sure you can hear the
roar of machine guns
and missiles in front of me.
Amazing!
The monster
has no doubt
been reduced to a pile
of blackened ashes!
I say we can all let
out a giant sigh of relief.
No! No! Get out!
Stop! Cease fire!
[screaming]
[PILOT] Yee-haw!
Cease fire, cease fire!
--Cease fire!
--[screaming continues]
[laughing]
Oh yeah! You like that?
Aahh...
[COMMANDER] Huh?!
[COMMANDER] There's, no way!
Just no way!
You... see that?
[SOLDIER E] Yeah, I see it, too!
He's.... He's still alive!
Judging by your silence,
I'd say it's my turn now.
[CELL chuckles]
[whimpering]
[SOLDIERS screaming]
[REPORTER] I don't know how,
but Cell is still alive!
The troops are retreating!
And... now Cell seems
to be raising his hand!
Don't do it! They're helpless!
[SOLDIERS screaming]
Cell, no!
[CELL grunts]
[SOLDIERS screaming]
[screaming]
[GOKU growls]
That monster!
[CELL] Now that was amusing.
[CELL chuckles]
I'm sorry about this,
ChiChi, but I have to go.
I need to ask Piccolo something.
That's... odd. What does
this have to do with Piccolo?
[TRUNKS] Goku!
[GOKU] Hey, Trunks.
Hey, Mr. Popo.
Oh, wow, Piccolo!
You've been
doing some training
in the Hyperbolic Time
Chamber haven't you?
That's right.
I can really tell!
You're strong!
A lot more powerful than before!
Why don't you just
say it? I'm stronger,
but you still don't
think I can beat Cell.
Nope, don't stand a chance.
Thanks. You've always
been the honest one.
So why did you come up here?
Well, I've been thinking.
You can split yourself
in two again, right?
So that there's
a Piccolo and a Kami?
[PICCOLO] What?
See, with Kami gone all the
Dragon Balls have disappeared,
but we really need
a wish from the Dragon.
We need to wish for
all the people Cell killed
to be brought back to life.
And I mean every
single one of 'em.
[GOKU] It's the only
way we can make up
for letting Cell come this far.
[PICCOLO] Sorry, Goku,
but I can't.
Once two Nameks
have fused together,
they can never split apart.
That's why
I was so hesitant
to fuse with Kami-- it was
a permanent deal.
Too bad. 'Cause I was really...
[GOKU sighs]
...hoping.
Wait! I remember
Gohan told me once
that all the
survivors from Namek
went to live on a new
planet somewhere!
Maybe I can get a hold of them!
Why?!
Maybe I can get one
of them to come here!
Yeah, and then he could become
the new guardian for Earth!
That way we'll have a new
set of Dragon Balls, right?
[MR. POPO gasps]
[GOKU] If we explain
our situation,
I'm sure they'd
be happy to help!
I would just love a new
guardian to keep me company!
But, you don't have
the time to be doing this.
You don't even know
what planet they're living on!
It'd take years to find them!
Ah, I doubt that! Not if
I use my Instant Transmission!
It's just a simple matter
of finding a planet
with an energy signature
that's similar to Piccolo's!
[PICCOLO] You can't sense
energy that far away!
Oh, sure! I must admit
I've never actually tried.
But if I put my
mind to it, I bet I can.
Now please, everyone
be really quiet.
[MR. POPO gulps]
Funny. You were
right! I can't!
[ALL gasp]
Hey! I know what I'll do!
I'll go to King Kai's planet
and locate them from there!
Now, if I can just get
a good picture of King Kai!
Oh! There we go!
So, do you think he'll do it?
I don't think we should rely
on it if that's what you mean.
[GOKU] Hmmm, I wonder what
that goofy guy is up to.
[KING KAI snoring]
Huh?
[snoring continues]
Sleeping, I should have known!
[BUBBLES chatters]
Hello, Bubbles!
[KING KAI snores]
Hey, King Kai. Hey!
Will you wake up for a sec?
It's me, Goku!
Goku?
Uh, hey! I like the new 'do.
You make a good blonde.
So what brings ya up here?
Need some good jokes?
No, no jokes.
Not right now.
Don't you know
about all the horrible things
that are happening on Earth?
[NARRATOR]
Goku continues with his plan
to bring Cell's victims
back to life.
But with the World Martial Arts
Tournament only days away,
shouldn't he be thinking
about his training?
The clock is ticking,
next time on Dragon Ball Z.