[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
the World Martial
Arts Championship
was about to get underway!
Careful not to break
the punching meter,
Goku and the others easily
qualified for the tournament.
But, as usual,
the stubborn Vegeta
wasn't pulling any punches.
[GOKU sighs]
[NARRATOR] Before the main
attraction could begin,
the Junior Division
Championship was being held,
and Trunks found himself
facing a boy twice his age.
[KRILLIN] Trunks!
[IDASA grunts]
Come on, you
little shortcake!
Fight!
Don't you worry...
You'll feel it soon
enough, big-mouth.
[IDASA gasps]
--[IDASA yells]
--[CROWD gasps]
[NARRATOR] The match
marked the rise and fall
of a promising
young Karate fighter.
Mostly the fall.
[TRUNKS] Oops...
Guess I shouldn't've
hit him so hard but...
at least he's quiet.
This boy is out cold!
Trunks advances!
[CROWD gasping, murmuring]
[CROWD cheers]
You sure did beat
that boy fast!
[NARRATOR] The Junior Division
Championship continues.
Will Goten fare
as well as Trunks?
[CROWD roars]
[CROWD] Yeah! Yes! All right!
[CROWD whooping &amp; cheering]
Hyaaah! Huh?!
[wailing]
--[chuckles nervously]
--[wailing continues]
[grunting]
[wailing]
[whimpering]
[ANNOUNCER] Ladies
and gentlemen!
Unbelievable! We have
a winner by knockout!
What a punch! And he used
the old cry-baby attack,
--the oldest one in the book!
--[CROWD laughs]
[lauging continues]
Alright, folks!
That was exciting!
But I know you're ready
for the next match, right?!
Yeah, baby! Sounds like a dandy!
Here we go!
We've got Ikose, an
expert 14 year-old,
against Goten,
a 7 year-old boy!
Come on, folks! Let's hear it
for these young warriors!
[CROWD cheers]
[GOTEN whimpers]
[cheering continues]
[IKOSE chuckles]
[GOTEN gulps]
[ANNOUNCER] Here they come!
Oh my gosh! It looks
like David verses Goliath!
Ikose has a full head
over young Goten!
[CROWD cheers]
[IKOSE chuckles]
You look nervous!
Uh-huh...
[GOKU] Alright, Goten!
Woo-hoo! Yeah!
Wow! He looks like
a miniature you, Goku!
Aww! What a little guy, huh?
And handsome, too!
[ANNOUNCER] Ladies
and Gentlemen,
the match is about to begin!
Small fry! Tear him up, Ikose!
Remember what happened
to your brother?!
Show no mercy!
Goten! Relax, you'll do fine!
Hm?! Eh!
That vulgar, little,
preschool, tiny-tot
doesn't have a chance
against my big, strong Ikose!
Whoo! Let him have it, Son!
Hey!
Wasn't that your
other big, strong son
that my little boy
knocked out cold earlier
with one l1ittle kick?!
Grrrh! So?! That little
pip-squeak punk was your son?!
Well, he got lucky! One miracle
is enough for one day!
[GOTEN] Hm?
I can't believe that all
of these people are here!
[IKOSE] It's enough to make you
want to run home crying,
isn't it, kid?!
[IKOSE chuckles]
Look, I don't want
to embarrass you
in front of all of these people.
For your sake,
I'm gonna  end this quick!
--Capiche?!
--[GOTEN] Uh-huh...
What?! Oh my gosh!
Goten, huh? Hmm...
[ANNOUNCER] Remarkable!
He looks just like Goku
when he was a boy and
faught against Jackie Chun
all those years ago!
[GOKU (BOY)] Ka... me...
ha... me...
Haaa!
[ANNOUNCER] I'll
never forget it...
That was the best match
that I've ever seen.
--[CHUN yells]
--[GOKU (BOY) yells]
[grunting]
[ANNOUNCER] There was no
junior class back then.
But Little Goku still
made it to the finals!
[GOKU (BOY)] I am champion...
Oh, yes! The
resemblance is uncanny!
If that's not Goku's son,
then I'm a monkey's uncle!
Alright! Fighters,
are you ready?!
[IKOSE grunts]
[ANNOUNCER] Let the match begin!
[CROWD cheers]
Come on, Goten!
You can do it, Son!
Rrgh! Ikose! Beat the hoo-haa
out of that little runt!
[FIGHTER 1 grunts]
[TECHNICIAN 1]
Seven seventy-six?!
No wait! Error...
[FIGHTER 2] Hey! Come on!
[FIGHTER 3] Yeah,
we haven't got all day!
I heard the name Goten.
We're missing your
brother's match!
Yeah, bummer!
I wish Vegeta wouldn't have
knocked the you-know-what
out of that machine...
Excuse me! You there,
making the repairs!
What's up?!
Hold on!
It takes a little time bit of
time calibrate the machine.
[CROWD cheers]
[grunting]
Hey! What's the matter?
That's your friend out
there fighting, isn't it?!
Don't you want to
see his match?
Well, don't you?!
I already know the result.
Huh?
Hey! He says his
friend's going to win!
--Let's go see!
--[BOY 2] The little guy?!
[BOY 3] No way!
[IKOSE] What's the matter,
kid?! You scared?!
[IKOSE grunts]
[IKOSE] Come on! It ain't
gonna hurt that bad!
[IKOSE] Let's do it!
[IKOSE grunts]
[IKOSE sighs, pants]
[GOTEN] Are you okay?
Heh! Me? Yeah right,
kid! Gimme a break!
Am I okay?! Man!
You're asking for it!
[IKOSE yells]
Huh?!
[IKOSE chuckles nervously]
[IKOSE yells]
Hey. Stop fooling around.
--Come on. Let's be serious.
--[IKOSE gasps]
[IKOSE] Touché!
So, you know a little
Martial Arts after all.
Not bad for a
pint-size kid!
Ooooh-ho-ho-ho!
Look! He's too scared to
throw a punch at my Ikose!
I'll give him five
minutes at the most!
And that's only if
he's extremely lucky!
Knock him out! Ikose, floor him!
I want you to knock that kid's
block off, do you hear me?!
[IKOSE yells]
Gosh... This is it?
This isn't very fun...
[IKOSE grunting]
[CROWD cheering]
Yeah! That a boy!
Alright, Goten!
What a cliffhanger...
Goodness gracious!
Wow! What a punch!
He's out out... out cold!
Folks! We have a
winner over here!
--Let's hear it for Goten!
--[CROWD roars]
--[BULMA blows a raspberry]
--[IKASA'S MOM whimpers]
--[BULMA giggles]
--[IKASA'S MOM growls]
I'm going to kill you!
[IKASA'S MOM grunts]
[MASTER ROSHI gasps]
C'mon. Who d'you
think taught them?
[BOY 1] Hey! Dude!
You're friend knocked that big
guy, Ikose, out with one punch!
Yeah, yeah. I know.
I told you I knew the result.
Yeah, right...
[CROWD cheers]
[FIGHTER 4] Dude,
you should have seen it!
This little 7 year-old kid
decked a 14 year-old!
It was awesome!
Hey! Your little
brother won, Gohan!
Isn't that amazing?
He gets to go to the next round!
[GOHAN] Mm-hm...
[GOHAN thinking] Poor kid
never had a chance...
Hello? Don't you even care?
Huh?
Yeah! Of course, I do!
That's great!
[GOHAN laughs]
[ANNOUNCER] Ladies
and gentlemen!
We've seen this
young man before!
It's Goten against Big Boomer!
Let the match begin!
[BIG BOOMER growls]
[BIG BOOMER grunts]
[BIG BOOMER yells]
Another victory for Goten!
[CHICHI &amp; BULMA] Yeah!
Woo! Woo! Goten! Yaye!
[ANNOUNCER] Alright! What
about this young man, folks?
[FIGHTER C howls]
[FIGHTER C] Oh yeah!
Here we go! Aw yeah! Uh-huh!
[FIGHTER C grunting]
Now it's time to get
it on, little man!
Hello?!
[FIGHTER C growls]
Whoo-hiyaa!
[FIGHTER C screams]
[groaning]
[ANNOUNCER]
Another victory for Trunks!
Right on!
[ANNOUNCER] Another
spectacular performance
from the other member of
the eight-and-under club!
[ANNOUNCER]
Trunks has done it again!
Look out! Trunks wins!
He's going to the finals!
It's Goten against Trunks
for the Championship!
Now! The moment you've
all been waiting for!
The Junior Division Championship
between 8 year-old Trunks
and 7 year-old Goten!
Which one of these
fabulous young fighters
will be the new
World Champion?
I think being World
Champion's gonna be fun!
I'll definitely let
you know how it is!
[ANNOUNCER] We've seen each of
these warriors valiantly advance
to the finals, but now
only one of them
can be World Champion!
Which of them will it be?
Trunks or Goten?!
[BULMA] Alright,
Trunks! You rule!
Woo-hoo! You can do it, Goten!
Try your best, sweetheart!
Yeah! You both look
like champions! Yaye!
Finally, we get to
see a good match!
This is gonna be awesome!
Definitely!
[ANNOUNCER] Outside of
the ring of competition,
these little guys are friends!
They usually fight
in the woods together
but now they've moved
to a different place!
The World Championship
stage! Wow! That's amazing!
[CROWD cheers]
[VIDEL] Gohan, the Championship
is about to start!
Huh?!
Man! What's the hold-up?!
I can't believe this!
Ahh! It's fixed!
She's ready to go!
Wow! Cool!
[GOHAN giggles]
[FIGHTER 4] Hey, you there!
There's no cutting in the line!
[FIGHTERS] Yeah,
no cutting in line!
Please, guys! Just once!
[TECHNICIAN 1] Oh, no you
don't! Not on my shift, buddy!
Please, I'm in a hurry, sir
[VIDEL] Hey, stop!
His little brother's in
the Junior Championship!
So what?! I'm sure
he'll do fine!
Yeah? Well,
gee, thanks alot!
[CROWD cheers]
Come, on Trunks!
Lay it on him, guy!
Goten! Yeah! Goten!
Woo! Go, Goten! Yeah!
[cheering continues]
--[ATTENDANT] Sir! Excuse me!
--[MR. SATAN snores]
--Oh dear. Mr. Satan, excuse me.
--Please, Mr. Satan? Sir?!
--[MR. SATAN snores]
Sorry, I didn't know
that you were sleeping.
[MR. SATAN] Oh,
I wasn't sleeping!
Fooled you, huh?
I was actually
in a deep meditation!
Even though I showed
the outward signs of sleep
I could still sense you
coming down the hall
and entering my room!
Whatd'ya think of that?!
[MR. SATAN laughs]
Sure! That works for me!
With your keen perception,
you probably already know
why I'm here,
but just to let you know,
the Junior Finals
are about to start!
A 7 and an 8 year-old boy
made it into the final!
Sir, they're fighting
rather impressively
I thought you might take a look.
[MR. SATAN] Hmm!
Watch a couple of kids pound
the heck out of each other?
Sure! That sounds fun!
Besides, I'm supposed to
have an exhibition match
agains the winner
of tthis thing!
[MR. SATAN chuckles]
Ladies and gentlemen!
It is our great pleasure to
present the final match
in the Junior World Martial
Arts Championship!
Just to let you know, I am
going to win. Understood?
Yeah! I'm going
for the win, too.
[MR. SATAN]
Those two little tykes
made it to the Championship?!
These tournaments just aren't as
competitive as they used to be!
[MR. SATAN] Hmm...
I think I recognize
that little guy!
Yes!
I'm not exactly sure where,
but I've seen that kid before!
And I never forget a face!
Hmmm...
[HERCULE screams]
No! I-I'm thinking
of someone else!
Go, boys!
Let's see some
action down there!
[OOLONG] Yeaaah!
Relax and have fun, guys!
You're both looking
great down there!
[KRILLIN] Looking sharp!
Go for the gusto!
[CROWD cheers]
[cheering continues]
[GOTEN growls]
[GOTEN yells]
[BOTH growl]
[blows landing]
[grunting,
blows landing]
Yeah! Great!
Wow! They're really going at it!
[CROWD cheers]
Hey, Dad! Hey, Krillin!
We finally finished
the qualifying test!
What took so long?
Hmmmm?
[KRILLIN chuckles]
Oh, I see!
You were hanging out
with your girlfriend!
Egh! Krillin! It's not like
that! We're just friends!
Yeah, right! Whatever!
Gohan? Is that sunburn?
Or are you blushing?!
[GOKU &amp; KRILLIN chuckle]
[TRUNKS grunts]
[GOTEN grunts]
[VIDEL gasps]
Man! Look at them go!
[TRUNKS] Huh?!
[grunting,
blows landing]
[OLD MAN whimpers]
[grunting,
blows landing]
Fantastic, you guys!
Wow! Keep it up!
[GOTEN growls]
Huh?!
[GOTEN yells]
[GOTEN screams
Goten, stop!
[GOTEN growls]
[TRUNKS] What?!
[grunting,
blows landing]
[BULMA &amp; CHICHI
yelling incoherently]
[GOTEN yells]
--[TRUNKS gasps]
--[GOTEN laughs]
Get him, Son! C'mon!
You got him, Goten!
--Trunks! Do something, quick!
--[OOLONG grunting]
[grunting]
[GOTEN screams]
[TRUNKS growls]
[GOTEN growls]
[grunting,
blows landing]
[OLD MAN whimpers]
[CROWD gasping]
[grunting,
blows landing]
That a' boy, Trunks!
Now you're doing it!
Alright!
Goten!
[blows landing]
[grunting,
blows landing]
[BOTH yell]
[TRUNKS chuckles]
[GOTEN chuckles]
[This... isn't happening!
Who are they?!
My gosh! Goten and
Trunks are more powerful
than most of the
adult fighters here!
Those two are
really tearing it up!
They'll be stronger than us
soon if we don't watch it!
I know!
Alright! Looking good,
Trunks! You too, Goten!
--More! We want more!
--[CROWD cheers]
Man! This is the best
match that I've ever seen!
Tear it up, dudes! Tear it up!
[cheering continues]
[ANNOUNCER] Yes! Yes!
Ladies and gentlemen, have you
ever seen anything like it?!
The World Martial Arts
Championship continues!
Who will be the next
Junior Champion?
Will it be 8
year-old, Trunks?!
Or will it be 7
year-old Goten?!
It seems like it could go
either way at this point!
What a match!
[NARRATOR] The fight between
the two strongest boys
in the world continues on the
next episode of Dragon Ball Z!