[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
Vegeta let down his
defenses during his
life and death struggle
with Majin Buu
and displayed his
affection for his son.
The cold exterior had been
melted away by the love within.
[VEGETA]
You've made me proud, my son.
[TRUNKS grunts]
What did you do to him?!
Why'd you do that?!
[GOTEN grunts]
[NARRATOR] But it didn't
take long for Vegeta
to show the more
"practical" side
of his love for
Trunks and Goten.
With an adversary like
Majin Buu on the horizon,
Vegeta didn't need
any distractions.
He was planning on
going all the way,
and he didn't want to take
the well-meaning
youngsters with him!
[NARRATOR] Vegeta knew that
this fight was to the death!
[VEGETA chuckles]
You're a fool.
I'm going to crush you.
And throw you into the wind!
Huh...?
[thinking] Trunks, Bulma,
I do this for you.
[NARRATOR] In an attempt to
blow Buu to smithereens,
Vegeta unleashed a
horrible attack
of unfathomable magnitude!
But can the mighty prince
survive the blast himself?
[VEGETA screaming]
[BUU screams]
[KRILLIN yells]
[KRILLIN]
Has he lost his mind or what?!
It's too much! He could die!
What has he done?!
Vegeta, I can't let him do this!
[KRILLIN]
Piccolo, wait!
It's too late!
You know as well as I do
he can't survive
a blast like that!
Let him finish
what he started!
Remember, even you yourself said
that for the first time,
Vegeta's risking his own own
life for the sake of others!
[KRILLIN]
He needs this, Piccolo!
Nobody's making him do it!
[CHICHI] I don't know who this
Majin Buu thinks he is,
but if he even lays a
finger on my boys...
[YAMCHA] Uh, ChiChi, you didn't
bring any guns on board, did ya?
[CHICHI]
No, of course not!
M-Maybe a grenade
or two, though...
Videl, you're absolutely sure
that's where they went, right?!
I mean, you actually
heard them say
they were going to fight
this Majin Buu character?!
Yes...
You know, I hate to say it,
but I resent the fact that
you let Gohan and the boys go.
You could've at least
stopped Goten and Trunks.
I'm so sorry, ChiChi!
I wasn't using my head!
I should've tried to stop them!
Hey, whoa! I wouldn't feel
too bad if I were you.
Those little imps
would've found a way!
Even if you told 'em a thousand
times they couldn't go!
Stopping Pre-K Super Saiyans
from going to a fight
is virtually
impossible! Trust me!
Gee, thanks...
[YAMCHA] Sure! Anyway,
there's no mistaking
they went this way, huh?!
Right! They went
straight ahead! For sure!
[YAMCHA]
Hold on, guys!
I'm gonna put the
hammer down a bit!
[thinking]
Vegeta...
How could you be so reckless?
How could you kill all of those
people? It doesn't make sense!
Vegeta!
[screaming]
Ohh! Vegeta!
No! How could he...?
This is too awful. There must
be some kind of mistake!
[CROWD scremaing]
[thinking] And that horrible
grimace on his face!
He looked like a
bloodthirsty animal!
Hey, Bulma! Lighten up,
would ya? Come on.
The worst that could happen is
that one of us gets killed!
And if that happens,
we just wish 'em back with the
Dragon Balls! No big deal!
Oh? If that's the case,
you wont mind if I kill you!
[YAMCHA screams]
[ROSHI grunts]
--[grunting]
--[MARON cries]
Look what you've done,
you idiot!
Straighten this thing out
or I'll kick your butt!
[YAMCHA whimpers,
MARON cries]
No need! I've got it!
Everything's under control!
Look, I know you're
troubled, Bulma,
but he wasn't normal when
he killed those people!
The Vegeta we know may be
arrogant and hotheaded,
but he would never do something
like what we saw today!
Yeah! They did something to him!
[BULMA thinking] If they
did do something to you,
you need to fight it and
get back to the way you were!
[YAMCHA] Wow, look, guys,
something's brewing up there!
[ROSHI] Yeah, I see it!
But what the heck is it?!
Huh...?
I dunno, but the instruments
are going haywire!
Uh-oh...!
[YAMCHA]
Hold on, everybody!
[screaming]
[ROSHI] I've fallen,
and I can't get up!
Hey! You're making
her cry! Stop it!
I'm not doing anything!
[YAMCHA]
If this keeps up,
this whole ship is
gonna shake apart!
[screaming]
That got the old heart rate up!
[YAMCHA]
Yeah! Sorry, guys!
I should have had the
fasten seat belt sign on!
[ROSHI] Mmm! That was
no common turbulence!
That was the after shock of
an incredible explosion!
[gasps]
[BULMA thinking] What's this
horrible feeling in my heart?!
I-I think I know...
[thinking] Vegeta!
What's happened to you?!
[YAMCHA]
Uh-oh! This isn't good!
Darn it! The controls,
they're not responding anymore!
They've been damaged!
Engine one's down!
[CHICHI]
What?!
[ALL scream]
[YAMCHA]
Engine two's down!
[CHICHI] Yamcha, do something
or we're all going to die!
[YAMCHA] How can I do something
without any engines?!
[screaming]
Guys! It's no use!
We're going down!
[ANDROID 18]
Videl! Here! Take Maron!
[screaming]
[ANDROID 18 grunts]
[ALL sigh]
Wow, why didn't I think of that?
[ANDROID 18] Easy does it,
old girl! That's it...
[MARON]
My mom's flying the plane!
--Yaay!
--[sighing]
Vegeta...
[KRILLIN] No, are you sensing
what I'm sensing, Piccolo?
Vegeta's energy signal has
completely disappeared!
He's gone...
[whimpers]
Listen, I'm going
to go check things
out over there
on the battlefield.
Take care of these
two, would you?
I'm going, too! I'd like the
chance to pay my last respects.
[PICCOLO] Nothing personal,
but I'd rather go alone.
Huh? I gotcha. Yeah.
Buu might still be alive.
[PICCOLO]
I don't think so,
but there's no sense in
taking any chances.
Here. Make sure nothing
happens to them, okay?
[KRILLIN]
Don't worry...
I-I'll take care of them.
Just be careful, okay?
[PICCOLO]
I will...
Oh, yeah, one more thing.
Huh?
[PICCOLO]
I'm going to have to ask you
to do something, Krillin,
and it's not going to be easy.
[KRILLIN]
I can do it. What is it?
Tell the others about
what happened here today.
Right, but what do you mean?
What should I say?
I'm not sure
what happened to Goku.
He may still be around
but apparently Gohan was
killed by Majin Buu!
Gohan?! Wait...
Wait, are you sure?
I'm afraid so, Krillin.
I heard Vegeta say it
before he died.
[gasps]
[PICCOLO]
Go now, I'm counting on you.
[KRILLIN]
Hey, wait, Piccolo!
How am I s'posed to...?
Ahh, great! Why me?
That's not fair!
I'd much rather fight Buu...
Say now, you think you'll be
done this year, Mr. Fix-it?!
[YAMCHA] I think you're
underestimating the damage!
That was quite an explosion!
We're lucky to be alive!
Yeah! You saved our lives,
18! Thank you!
[thinking]
Vegeta... Trunks...
I don't sense anything...
...but that's
definitely the place.
[grunts]
He went out
with a bang, all right!
Wow, what power it must've taken
to produce a crater like that.
Vegeta...
[thinking]
No sign of Buu...
I think it worked, Vegeta.
[thinking]
Wait a second!
There's Buu.
Or what's left of him.
He's been blown into
a thousand pieces.
[thinking]
Now I understand.
Buu would simply regenerate
if damaged in the normal way.
So you had to make an
attack powerful enough
to blow him to bits.
[PICCOLO thinking] Well,
you did it, Vegeta! It worked.
Your sacrifice wasn't in vain.
I've walked through
that door before.
I know it's not easy.
[thinking] Especially for a
selfish guy like you.
Oh, I was just like you once.
Until Gohan's love changed me.
I know you were changed, too.
I know how much courage it
took to do what you did.
[PICCOLO thinking]
Goodbye, my friend.
[BABIDI whimpers]
Help me, please!
[PICCOLO]
Help you? Why should I?
[BABIDI]
Please!
[PICCOLO] When you help others,
you receive help!
When's the last time you used
your powers to help someone?
I'll bet it's been
a while, hasn't it?
[growls] Help! Don't lecture me!
You don't like
being hurt, do you?!
But you delight in
hurting others!
You're right,
you don't need a lecture,
you need to be exterminated!
[BABIDI]
No!
Huh?!
[BUUS squeaking]
They're alive!
How is this possible?!
He's-He's regenerating!
There are hundreds of them!
[BUUS squeaking]
[BUUS giggling]
[thinking]
This is insane!
[gasps]
[BUUS cheer]
[thinking]
This can't be happening!
[BUUS giggle]
[BUU]
Ready! Buu!
[BUU grunts]
[whimpers]
[PICCOLO thinking]
What kind of creature is he?!
He was in a million pieces!
How can we beat a
monster like that?!
[gasps]
[thinking] I'd better get out of
here while I still can!
[whimpers]
[PICCOLO growls]
[PICCOLO thinking]
We're done for!
Not even Goku has what it
takes to deal with that!
Buuuuuuuuu!
[BUU giggles]
Ha-ha-ha, ooh-ooh-ooh!
[screams, giggles]
[BABIDI]
Majin Buu! Help me!
Please...!
Uh-ho! You stuck in hole?
You fool! Of course I'm stuck!
I only have one arm left!
And not a leg to speak of!
Buu no help! Buu no can help!
[BABIDI]
What are you talking about?!
I know darn well that you
can help me! Now, do it!
Oh! You do first!
What happened? You tell.
[BABIDI]
What does it matter?
Just hurry up and help me,
lame-brain! It's not important!
Yes, yes! Buu want
to know now! You tell NOW!
Majin Buu, will you be quiet?!
Just get me back to normal!
Back to normal? Back to normal?
No! Never normal!
Never normal! Can't go back!
Can't go back!
Hurry up, Majin Buu!
Do you realize what
will happen if I die?!
If I'm gone, no one will
be left to set you free
if you get sealed up again!
[BABIDI]
Ahh! At last!
It looks like I
finally penetrated
that rubber head of yours!
Now fix me up before
I keel over and die!
[whimpers]
[BABIDI gasps]
[BABIDI] Oh, that feels good!
Thank you very much, Buu!
Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
That green freak
and those two brats
are going to pay for
their hand in this!
[growls] There'll be no quick
end for those scoundrels!
We're going to make
them suffer, Buu!
The three of them will
be begging for death!
[BABIDI giggles]
They'll discover what it means
to make war with Babidi and Buu!
Pain and agony will
become their bedfellows!
Their lives will
become a cesspool
in which foul things breed!
Darkness will be their light!
If you look suffering
up in the dictionary
you'll see a picture
of the three of them!
[BABIDI giggles]
[PICCOLO]
Krillin!
Huh?!
[KRILLIN]
Piccolo?
Hey, what's up?
We're in big trouble,
that's what!
Take those two to the
Lookout, immediately!
What's going on?
What about that big blast?
Vegeta's attack!
Don't tell me it failed!
No one could have survived that!
Piccolo! Buu's alive! Isn't he?!
Yes, Buu survived!
He's alive and well!
No! Impossible!
What about Vegeta?!
There wasn't even
a shred left of him!
[KRILLIN] But if that
attack didn't affect Buu
then there's no hope!
There is hope!
But if Buu finds it, he'll
destroy it! It's these two.
[KRILLIN]
Huh?
[PICCOLO]
Goten and Trunks.
They need to be safeguarded
until they're ready
for the challenge.
It may take some time,
but they're the only
chance we have left.
[PICCOLO]
Son of Goku... Son of Vegeta...
The future of the Earth
depends on you two!
[BABIDI] Whoo-hoo! Let's raise
some cane, Majin Buu!
A little killing
spree is in order!
[BABIDI laughs]
Destroy everything in
sight! Everything!
And let's lure those three
meddlers out of hiding.
[SUPREME KAI]
Gohan... You've got to be alive!
Where are you...?
[NARRATOR]
As Supreme Kai continues
his desperate search for Gohan,
the rejuvenated Babidi
and Majin Buu
are terrorizing the
inhabitants of Earth.
Vegeta has already
given his life
trying to stop the evil Buu,
and Gohan is at death's door,
hanging on by a mere thread!