[NARRATOR] Last time,
on Dragon Ball Z!
Krillin paid a visit
to the Eldest Namek,
where he received
a Dragon Ball,
and another
unexpected reward!
[KRILLIN cackles]
Power!
A lot of power!
[NARRATOR] With his hidden
potential released,
Krillin raced off with
his prize. Meanwhile...
Now, go find Vegeta.
I want that Dragon Ball!
[NARRATOR] Frieza sent
his henchman Zarbon
to search for Vegeta,
in order to discover the
location of the Dragon Ball
that the Saiyan
had hidden...
Well. So you are still
alive, after all...
I guess that's lucky for me.
Not so lucky for you.
[NARRATOR]
Krillin has one Dragon Ball!
Can Gohan find the last one
before Vegeta is forced
to reveal its
whereabouts to Frieza?
If not, the race for the
Dragon Balls may be decided
before Goku even
arrives! Stay tuned!
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU panting]
[grunting continues]
I hope Yamcha
and the others
are at least making better
progress at King Kai's.
[GOKU panting]
[thinking] I wonder if they've
caught Bubbles yet? Heh.
I can only imagine the
time they must be having.
Oh well. No
time to daydream!
[GOKU grunting]
[BUBBLES chattering]
[YAMCHA shouting]
[chattering continues]
[YAMCHA growling]
I'll get you!
[chattering continues]
You think you're
pretty smart!
[YAMCHA shouting]
[BUBBLES giggling]
Thought he had 'im.
I know...
[YAMCHA] Ugh! Damn... monkey...
[KING KAI humming]
[KING KAI] Don't
blame the monkey!
[TIEN] My turn!
[BUBBLES chattering]
Huh?
All right.
[CHIAOTZU] C'mon!
Get him, Tien!
[KING KAI] No need to
hurry, boys. Take your time.
What's up?
I've already proven I'm
above these foolish games.
So what do you say we
just cut to the chase?
[KING KAI] Nope. Sorry.
You'll have to go through
the proper procedure
like everyone else.
Aahhh...
No one's forcing you
to sit out, Piccolo.
You're free to join
the others at any time.
But if you'd
rather not do that...
You're more than welcome
to give me a hand
weeding the garden,
if you'd like.
[PICCOLO growls]
I'm curious, why are
you in such a rush?
You made a promise that
you wouldn't fight Frieza.
You're not thinking
of breaking it?
No, no, of course
you're not.
Because that would
mean you're a liar...
And I think
we both know,
the only thing worse than
a liar is a no-good thief!
I make it a rule never
to train either one!
Not that you'd have to
worry about that, right?
Ah, forget I
mentioned it.
Uh? So you don't want
to help with the garden?
Hmmm...
Huh?
[BUBBLES chattering,
YAMCHA panting]
[TIEN panting]
[KING KAI] Heeey!
It's time to eat!
[ALL gasp]
Hmm...?
They're eating more
than Goku did!
You could lose a
hand in there.
Wait!
Slow down!
Try to save a little
bit for me, you guys!
It's really great,
King Kai.
Oh! Glad to hear it!
I try to prepare
a healthy menu
for all my trainees
while they're here.
There's fried rice,
fried fish,
fried chicken, fried
sausages, fried pork,
refried beans, fried cheese,
and milkshakes for desert.
Huh? Hey! Where'd it all go?!
[ALL] Ah... Couldn't
eat another bite!
Well, then, I see
in our next lesson
we should definitely
discuss moderation.
[YAMCHA] Now that I'm full,
you're in big trouble, ape-face.
[KING KAI] Hey! Don't
call me ape-face!
I'm not talking about you,
King Kai. It's him I want.
[BUBBLES chatters]
You won't feel like dancing
when I'm through with you.
[chattering continues]
[YAMCHA] Monkey!
[YAMCHA shouting,
BUBBLES chattering]
[YAMCHA] Gotcha!
[BOTH] Yeah, Yamcha!!
[YAMCHA] Yeah! I did it!
I caught the monkey!
Oh, yeah!
Piccolo... Are you sure you
don't want something to eat?
[PICCOLO growls]
[PICCOLO] I'm fine.
[BUBBLES chattering]
[BUBBLES screams]
[screaming]
[TIEN] Hrgh!
[BUBBLES gibbering excitedly]
Did it!
All right!
Way to go, Tien!
[CHIAOTZU] Yay! Ha, ha, ha!
They're doing
great work.
They just keep on getting
faster and faster.
Pretty impressive, no?
[PICCOLO] I came here
to get stronger...
To do that, I have to
train with someone
who's stronger than I
am. And they're not.
[KING KAI groans]
[CHIAOTZU] I got him! I got him!
[BUBBLES whooping,
CHIATOZU laughing]
Oh. Well, now.
Even Chiaotzu's gotten fast
enough to catch Bubbles.
Good, good!
[KING KAI laughs]
Then you're ready
for step number two!
Oh, Gregory!
Ta-da! Hi there everybody!
The name's Gregory!
This will be your
next challenge.
All you have to do
is take this hammer,
give me a good tap,
and then you win!
And don't go
easy on me!
Because, I'm sure not
gonna go easy on you!
Heh, heh! So who's first?
[YAMCHA chuckles]
How 'bout I
give it a try!
Here.
[YAMCHA chuckles]
[yells]
What?! It's like... an anvil!
Excuses, excuses.
[YAMCHA grunting]
Yeah? Bring it on!
[GREGORY] See ya!
Ha! Too slow, sucker!
Argh! Why you--!
Yamcha! Hang tough!
Let's go! Let's go!
[KING KAI chuckling]
Hey, Piccolo! Why don't
you give it a try?
[PICCOLO] Because I have better
things to do with my time
than take swings at a
cricket. I'll train myself.
Very well...
[YAMCHA] All right! Ready
or not, here I come!
[ALL shouting]
[CHIAOTZU] Come on! Get him!
Here! Let me
give it a try!
[CHIAOTZU yelling,
GREGORY laughing]
What's the matter?
Gonna give up already, guys?
[YAMCHA growls]
No way!
Heeey! Why don't we
take a little break?
[ALL] Huh?
Piccolo's already over there
taking a nap under the tree.
You guys might
as well too.
Hey, we're not
like Piccolo.
We came here to work!
Let's get going!
Okay, big shot!
[KING KAI] Well, I could
sure use a nap too.
[thinking] He knows what
we're up against here...
This Frieza is somehow
even stronger than Vegeta,
and all he's doing
is wasting our time!
How is he?
[APOOL] He's holding steady.
I've managed to stabilize
his vital signs for now,
but he's still in
critical condition.
He may never
regain consciousness.
He's got to make it!
You revive him at all costs!
Do you understand?!
Yes, sir...
[thinking] If he
doesn't recover,
Frieza will have my head...
[FRIEZA] I want that
Dragon Ball...
[KING KAI snoring]
[BUBBLES quietly snoring,
KING KAI snoring]
[GREGORY panting]
[CHIAOTZU humming]
[CHIAOTZU laughs]
Oh yeah!
Chiaotzu! Home run!
C'mon! Keep your
eye on the cricket!
Right!
Here we go, it's two outs,
bottom of the ninth--
Hey, all right!
Full count.
We've got runners
on the corners
and we're down by two...
This for the win!
[GREGORY] I'll teach you
to give me some respect!
Just see if you can
keep up with me!
[CHIAOTZU] Okay.
All right, then.
Here I come, Doll-boy.
See if you can even
swing the bat!
Ready when
you are!
You asked for it.
Here comes the heat!
[GREGORY giggling]
[GREGORY screaming]
[YAMCHA] It's goooone!
[BUBBLES whooping excitedly]
Ah! We're under attack! Abandon
ship! Batten down the hatches!
He knocked it out of the
park. A grand-slam home run!
Huh? Gregory?
What are you doing in here?
It's not his fault. Chiaotzu
knocked him a good one.
We all did!
Really? All of you?
Is this true, Gregory?
No... They
didn't catch me.
They can't prove a thing!
They're lying!
Goodness! Well that
was really fast.
It only took you about an
hour and five minutes.
[YAMCHA] That's right. And
we're ready for the next lesson.
[KING KAI] Now, I
hope you guys know
what you're getting
yourselves into!
For the next exercise,
we'll start with some basics
in the ancient
art of grappling!
You ready for some
one-on-one, Tien?
You got it!
Yeah!
[KING KAI] Hold on, now!
Not so fast there!
Ah- ahh! I'm in charge
of picking the opponents.
[PICCOLO] Count me in.
[KING KAI] Oh, so you've
finally decided to join us.
Well, how 'bout
Piccolo against--
[PICCOLO] Against them all.
[BOTH] What?!
You three weaklings
had to struggle
just to catch a monkey
and a grasshopper.
I could take
on 10 of you,
and it still wouldn't
be a challenge.
Oh yeah? We'll
see about that!
Wait, now. I'm not
so sure about this...
The odds do seem
unfairly stacked.
[PICCOLO] Heh.
[KING KAI] But, if this is
what you boys want to do...
Heh! We'll handle him.
I certainly
hope so.
You three have done
such excellent work
in your training
exercises so far.
It's time to see whether
or not it's paid--
[PICCOLO] Enough talk!
I'm ready. Let's see
what you've got.
[BOTH growling]
Come on!
Attack me!
Ready?
[BOTH] Hmph.
[CHIAOTZU] Uh-huh.
Ready?! And go!
[shouting, grunting]
[PICCOLO] Hrr... Raah!
Oh yeah?!
Nice try!
[CHIAOTZU laughing]
[growling]
[PICCOLO yells]
[GREGORY] If you had
a headache like mine,
you wouldn't be
laughing. Ooouch!
[PICCOLO growling]
[TIEN &amp; YAMCHA shouting]
[PICCOLO yells]
Now... you're mine!
[PICCOLO growls]
[CHIAOTZU screams]
[PICCOLO roars]
No!
Chiaotzu! Chiaotzu!
Hey, don't worry.
You're forgetting...
You're already dead.
You can't die a second
time, you know.
You give him a minute or
two and he'll shake it off.
Just you wait.
R-Really?
Three... Two...
One... See?
[CHIAOTZU grunting]
Viola!
[YAMCHA chuckles]
[PICCOLO thinking] I can't
believe how much stronger
they've already
become.
It can't be because of
this stupid training
they've been doing...
[KING KAI] Resume the match!
[PICCOLO thinking] ...or can it?
[grunting, shouting]
[YAMCHA] Raaah!
[TIEN] Hrrgh!
[blows landing]
[PICCOLO yelling]
[TIEN] Hyaaah!
[PICCOLO] Uggh!
[YAMCHA] Gotcha!
[PICCOLO] Arrgh!
[YAMCHA] So...
How's that for you?
Yeah, have you had
enough yet, Piccolo?
[PICCOLO] Hmph.
I haven't even
gotten started.
[ALL] Hah!
[KING KAI] Nope, sorry guys.
That's enough
for now.
I've decided we should all
take a break for lunch.
[ALL] Huh?
[KING KAI] Hmm... Stop!
[ALL] Hm?
What's the only kind of dog in
the world that doesn't bark?
I'll tell you...
A hot dog!
[KING KAI laughs]
[ALL] Oh yeah...
[ALL laughing]
[PICCOLO] Pathetic...
[APOOL] Frieza's not
going to be happy.
At this rate,
he'll never recover!
I don't know...
But it looks to me
like the high and
mighty Prince Vegeta
really isn't so mighty
after all, now is he?
[APOOL laughs]
[APOOL] Well, I hope
you do pull out of it.
'Cause I'm gonna really
enjoy watching Zarbon
torture you
to death!
That oughta' keep
you for a while.
Tell you what, I'm gonna
go take a little break.
Just promise you'll sit
tight 'til I get back.
I wouldn't want you to
wander off and get hurt.
[APOOL chuckles]
Huh?!
[APOOL screaming]
So, then.
How is he?
[ZARBON] He... He should regain
consciousness any time, now.
Good, then I won't
have to kill you.
Yes, lord...
[distant explosion]
What? What in the
blazes was that?!
Find out!
[VEGETA chuckling]
They just keep underestimating
the true powers of a Saiyan.
Huh?
[ZARBON panting]
[distant explosion]
Damn! It came from
the recovery room!
Well, don't just
stand there!
[ZARBON gasps]
[ZARBON] He's gone!
He must've flown off!
[FRIEZA] So go after him!
[VEGETA thinking] Excellent.
Everyone's here...
Go now! Do you
hear me, Zarbon?
I'll...
I'll find him!
[FRIEZA] You'd better!
Because if you don't find
him within the hour,
you'll wish you'd
never been born!
[VEGETA laughing]
[thinking] They're almost
making this too easy...
[VEGETA laughing]
[thinking] Oh, Frieza.
You're so overconfident
in your abilities
that you've left even
your precious
Dragon Balls unguarded.
Well, I assure you, it
will be your last mistake.
[VEGETA chuckles]
You lose, Frieza!
[NARRATOR] Vegeta is back
from the brink of death,
and five of the magic Dragon
Balls are now within his grasp!
Can anything stop him from
fulfilling his sinister wish?
Find out, next
Dragon Ball Z!