[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragonball Z,
the androids that invaded Earth
went head-to-head
and fist-to-fist
with Vegeta, Piccolo,
Tien, and Trunks,
and left them bruised,
battered, and broken.
Frozen with fear,
Krillin watched in horror
as his friends took
it on the chin.
And Goku continued to battle
the illness that has
him in its clutches.
[KRILLIN] Stop!
You leave Goku alone!
No. I am programmed
to destroy Goku.
[ANDROID 17]
There you go.
16 has been programmed
to destroy Goku.
So that's what
we're going to do!
[KRILLIN] What is this?
Some kind of game?!
That's right, friend.
And finding Goku is
part of the game.
[KRILLIN whimpering]
Good luck!
Bye!
[NARRATOR] The good guys
are down for the count
and the androids seem
to be getting stronger.
Now that Krillin
is on his own,
can he revive his friends
and intercept the androids
before they reach Goku?
[KRILLIN thinking]
They're going after Goku!
If they find him, he's history!
Oh no! I forgot
the other guys!
[VEGETA groaning quietly]
[KRILLIN] Let's see now...
We should have six
beans left beteween us.
I hope it's enough for
everybody to have one...
[KRILLIN] Hey! Tien,
can you hear me?
[TIEN grunting]
[KRILLIN] Are you alright?
[TRUNKS growls]
Here, take this.
[KRILLIN] Hmm?
Vegeta looks like he's
in pretty rough shape.
I guess I need to give
Vegeta a couple of beans.
[PICCOLO] What?!
You mean they even knew
about the Senzu beans?!
[TIEN] I don't get it!
They know everything about us!
Why didn't they
just finish us off?!
Those two could have squashed
all of us like flies!
They were just toying with us!
Man, this is
all Vegeta's fault!
Hey, don't blame him!
We all underestimated
their strength.
Which was a mistake!
But we can't afford
to make any more.
The androids may not
be so forgiving next time!
[VEGETA growling]
Vegeta!
[PICCOLO] Trunks!
Let him go! Stop!
[TRUNKS] Huh?!
Leave him alone.
Ever since Vegeta
became a Super Saiyan
his ego has been
out of control.
Honestly, I think what
that Android hurt
the most today
was his pride.
He is very ashamed
of his defeat.
[TIEN] I know how he feels...
We worked so hard...
But they were still stronger
than all of us put together...
No, Tien. I'm sorry.
I should've been
fighting right
alongside with you guys,
but I was just too scared...
Don't sweat it.
Trunks is a Super Saiyan
and it only took one punch
from those androids to
take him out of the fight.
Even if you'd
joined us, Krillin,
we would not have won today.
Oh, man!
I wish Goku was here!
Trunks, you were able to take
out Frieza single-handedly.
You're one of the strongest
people I've ever met.
But those Androids
tossed you aside
as though you were nothing!
[TRUNKS growls]
Goku is strong.
But in all honesty,
I don't see how he can be
that much stronger
than Trunks or Vegeta.
And if that's the case,
we're done for!
[KRILLIN whimpers]
No!
I don't get it...
It's strange...
These androids
are much stronger
than the ones
I fought in my time.
[KRILLIN &amp; TIEN gasp]
Wait, Trunks,
what do you mean?
The androids I fought
were stronger than me,
but not this much.
The kind of strength these new
androids have is off the charts!
[TIEN] Then we really
are out of luck!
What should we do?
You three go to Goku's and
move him some place safe.
He'll be able to join
you once he's well.
It's obvious that
we're going to need
all the help we can get
to defeat these androids.
Good idea!
But, Piccolow, what are you
going to be doing, huh?
[PICCOLO growls]
I don't know.
[KRILLIN] Come on.
I know you've
come up with a plan.
Why don't you just tell
us what your scheme is
Come on we're
buddies now, aren't we?
Listen to me!
Stop asking questions!
It's none of your concern!
This is something
that I have to do alone!
[PICCOLO yells]
[TIEN grunts]
[KRILLIN grunts]
[PICCOLO yells]
[TRUNKS gasps]
[PICCOLO growls]
[KRILLIN] Piccolo! What do
you think you're doing?!
I'm leaving!
And anyone who tries to
follow me will be sorry!
Just find Goku!
And forget about me!
What's with him? Did I
miss something here?
I haven't seen
Piccolo act like that
since back in the old days
when he was trying to destroy
Goku and take over the world!
[TIEN growls]
It doesn't make sense!
Last I heard, Piccolo
was fighting on our side!
Don't worry, Tien.
Piccolo just has
a lot on his mind.
He's still one
of the good guys.
This is one fight
we can't afford to lose.
And if we want to
beat these Androids,
it's going to take
everything that we've got!
Piccolo is just doing what
he thinks he has to do to win!
Don't worry. He'll be okay!
Krillin! "He'll be okay"?
What are you talking about?!
You saw Piccolo fly
in that direction right?
Try and guess where
you thing he's going.
[TIEN] Is this a trick question?
Uh, gee...
How am I supposed to know?
Come on, tell me where he went!
To Kami's place!
To Kami's place?!
Piccolo and Kami are
one and the same.
Piccolo is
the embodiment
of all the negative energy
that's inside Kami.
They were once one being,
but split in two.
That's why they'll always
share a common bond.
[TIEN] Yeah?
I remember Master Roshi
telling me something long ago.
He said that if Kami and
Piccolo hadn't split into two,
they'd be the strongest being
in the entire universe.
Hell-oh? Get it?!
The reason Piccolo has
gone to Kami's place
is so that he can
join with him again.
Really?
If those two unite
again into one being,
they'll become the
ultimate Namek warrior!
And Piccolo is stronger
than he's ever been before,
so together they'll
be an unstoppable force!
Look! You know what
a Super Saiyan is!
Piccolo and Kami will
become a "Super Namek!"
You say a "Super Namek," huh?
We could sure use that!
Wait a minute,
if they unite,
Kami will disappear and
the Dragon Balls will too!
Yeah, that may be true...
But it's no better if Piccolo
is destroyed by the androids.
In either case, the
Dragon Balls will disappear!
Think about it.
There's no other way to defeat
these androids on our own.
If Piccolo's thinking of uniting
with Kami, he must be desperate,
and he figures that
this is our last chance
to get out of this mess!
It's too bad...
Piccolo and Kami
really don't get along.
My father,
I mean Vegeta.
We can't forget about him!
There's no reason for you
to hide it anymore, Trunks.
We all know about
Bulma and Vegeta
and the fact that
they had a baby.
And that baby is you;
you're their son, right?
[TRUNKS gasps]
I guess Vegeta's the only
one who doesn't know.
[TRUNKS] I kept it
a secret... I'm sorry.
[TIEN] You don't
have to apologize.
As for Vegeta, I'm sure he'll
be back once he cools off a bit.
I know he's too proud
to run away from a fight.
He just needs some time
to work some things
out for himself.
Then I'm sure he'll be back
stronger than he ever was!
Yeah!
I'll show those androids!
No one makes a fool of me!
They'll pay for this!
They should have finished me off
when they had the chance,
because I will
show them no mercy!
[TV MAN] I'm sorry, Beverly.
There's someone else.
I don't love you anymore.
So, goodbye...
No...
No, don't leave me...
What about our love?
Please don't go...
Come back! Rex, come back!
[MARON sobs]
It's such a sad story...
Love... It's a game...
Some win and some always lose!
[ROSHI cries]
[BOY A] Yo, Maron!
Who's that?
I wasn't expecting
Krillin to be back yet?
[BOY A] Yo, baby!
[MARON giggles]
Mack! Hi there!
[BOY B] 'Ey, Maron!
Oh! Tommy!
[BOY C] Howdy!
[BOY D] Hey, Maron!
[BOY E] Hey, Maron!
[BOYS chattering excitedly]
[MARON gasps]
[chattering continues]
[MARON] You all came
to see me? How romantic!
What?! What's going
on out there?
[MARON]
Wait right, here okay?!
[ROSHI] Hey, Maron?
What's up? What's happening?
[MARON] Oh,
I was bored
so I thought I'd call
a few boyfriends.
[ROSHI] These guys are
all your boyfriends?!
Oh, what's a girl to do?
All these boys are so cute;
it's hard to pick just one!
[ROSHI yells]
Say "Hello" to Krillin for me!
And I'll see you guys
later, okay? Buh-bye!
Looks like she's
gone for good.
Oh yeah, she's
gone alright.
Maron's a nice girl
but I don't think she's
the right type for Krillin.
Now, listen... When
Krillin gets here,
don't tell him
Maron was around.
I don't think the
boy could take it.
Right!
What a darn shame...
If only I were a younger man...
Then maybe I could have been
one of Maron's boyfriends too!
It's not fair! It's not!
Trunks, tell me something...
That medicine that
you gave to Goku,
how long will it take
before it makes him well?
In Goku's case...
I'd say it'll take
about ten days or so.
Ten days, huh?
We should be able to hide him
somewhere safe for ten days.
[TIEN] Yeah... No problem.
Of course there's no guarantee
that we'll be able to beat those
androids once Goku gets well.
But as long as we
can manage to stay
a couple of steps ahead of them,
we might just have a chance!
Right!
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU yells]
Goku! Try to relax!
[GOKU pants, grunts]
[YAMCHA] Here!
Quick! Get his medicine! Now!
Right!
Oh, darn! Where is it?!
ChiChi! It's right over there!
[CHICHI] Okay! Got it!
[GOKU pants]
Here... Now take this.
[GOKU panting]
[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH sigh]
Goku... Please get better soon.
[MRS. BRIEF hums]
[GOHAN] Look, Bulma!
There's your mom!
[humming continues]
[MRS. BRIEF gasps] Oh my!
Welcome home! Hi there!
Hi, Mom!
Oh... Look at you all!
Gohan, you sure have
grown into a big boy!
[GOHAN stammers]
[BULMA raspberries]
[MRS. BRIEF] Hey,
Trunks! Who's there?
[TRUNKS and
BULMA's MOM giggle]
You look bigger
every time I see you.
Why don't you
make yourself at home
and I'll get some of
those cakes and cookies
you like so much!
[MRS. BRIEF giggles]
Come on. Don't be shy now!
[MRS. BRIEF laughs]
No, wait!
[MRS. BRIEF] It's no
trouble, dear. Just relax!
But I want to go
see my father now.
No way! Cake and cookies
first! Then we go!
[GOHAN groans]
No! I'm sorry!
Oh! Wait, Gohan! Come back!
He's long gone, Mom.
[MRS. BRIEF] Oh...
was it something I said?
Bye-bye, Gohan!
[BABY TRUNKS giggles]
[thinking] Some cake and cookies
would've been nice...
But I have more
important things to do!
[thinking] Uh-oh!
Something's not right.
[thinking] So Piccolo has
decided to come back...
I could feel an uneasiness
stirring inside him.
He seeks the power that we once
had when we were still united
such a long time ago...
Yes, I remember...
Long before Piccolo
was separated from me,
I came to this
place to face
the former guardian of Earth
and to ask for his throne.
[KAMI] The former
guardian was not impressed
by what he saw in me, a brash,
young warrior from Namek.
He was not willing to relinquish
the guardianship of Earth
to any creature
he felt unworthy...
[FORMER GUARDIAN]
There is a great evil
deep in your heart...
If you wish to take my place,
you must rid yourself of it...
Rid yourself of the evil
before it consumes you!
[KAMI grunts]
[KAMI] The former
guardian's words
stirred something
within me...
Although I had done
my best to suppress it,
I had always sensed a darker
nature lurking in my heart.
The guardian confirmed this
beyond a shadow of a doubt...
Only through intense
training was I able
to separate myself
from this dark force.
The dark force that
became Piccolo!
With my heart pure,
I was able to take the
guardian's throne...
But King Piccolo,
fueled by his evil ambition
to control the world,
escaped to Earth.
[KING PICCOLO laughing]
[KAMI] Before he could carry out
his insidious plans, however,
a mysterious boy appeared...
That boy was Goku!
[KING PICCOLO] No one
will stand in my way!
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU growls]
[KING PICCOLO laughing]
[KING PICCOLO yells]
You're mine!
This planet belongs to no one!
No!
[GOKU yelling]
[yelling continues]
[GOKU grunts]
[KING PICCOLO gasps]
What?!
You're finished!
I'll squash you, insect!
[GOKU &amp; KING PICCOLO growl]
No! You're not
welcome here!
[crashing]
[KAMI] As his final,
desperate act,
King Piccolo sought
to preserve himself
by transferring his
essence into a single egg.
[KING PICCOLO grunts]
[KING PICCOLO screams]
[GOKU screams]
[KAMI] And that is how the
Piccolo we know today was born.
[PICCOLO chuckles]
And now the time has come
for the two of us
to unite as one
to face the
consequences together.
[KORIN thinking]
Uh-oh... There goes trouble.
[MR. POPO whimpers]
[PICCOLO thinking] You have
something I want, old man...
[KAMI thinking] You still have
a lot to learn, Piccolo.
[NARRATOR] While the
three killer androids
carry out their search
and destroy mission,
Piccolo is determined
to unite with Kami
in a last-ditch effort to stop
the three mechanical monsters.
But is he too late?
Find out next time,
on Dragonball Z!