[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Zl
it was Namek against machine
as Piccolo spear-headed the
battle against the Androids.
[NARRATOR]
After reuniting with Kami
and becoming a Super Namek,
the mighty Piccolo
was the only one on Earth
with enough strength to
challenge the Androids.
[NARRATOR]
As Piccolo fought,
Goku waited for
Vegeta and Trunks
to finish their task
in the Pendulum Room
so that he could
take his turn.
[GOKU] And, Son,
I know how you feel.
[NARRATOR]
Their mission:
To go beyond the level
of Super Saiyan
and achieve a new and
higher level of power.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, Bulma
wasn't wasting any time.
Using her extensive
knowledge of electronics,
she invented a remote control
that could cripple
the Androids' circuitry
and render them helpless.
[TIEN] That's great!
Now we can destroy them!
[NARRATOR]
Back at the battlefield,
Piccolo was
proving himself
to be an equal match
for Android 17.
But his bid for
victory was cut short
when a much more formidable
adversary arrived!
[NARRATOR] Cell!
The android nemesis
that was cloned from
the cells of the greatest
fighters in the galaxy.
His purpose:
To integrate Androids 17
and 18 into his body
and become the most
powerful creature
in the entire universe.
[CELL]
Hello, Piccolo.
Thank you for
bringing 17 and 18 here.
It pleases me greatly.
Aahhh...
[PICCOLO] Oh, great. I thought
I'd have more time than this.
Man! Now what?
If he merges with those
two, it's all over!
Hey! What is that thing?
[thinking]
He doesn't know!
They don't even
know who Cell is!
[CELL sighs]
I have been aching to
behold this for so long.
It's almost as if
I've seen them before;
I recognize them somehow.
Android 17!
Amazingly efficient!
And 18!
Poetry in motion!
[CELL] Wha...?
Who is this one?
He bears the
Red Ribbon insignia,
he must be one of Gero's
earlier, less efficient models.
I have sniffed the bouquet,
and now it's time to drink.
[CELL] Ah. Hello. Greetings.
[PICCOLO growls]
[CELL] Hmm...
Ahhh...
[CELL yells]
Huh?
[thinking] What's he doing?
This can't be!
[CELL yells]
[CELL cackles]
[SOUL moans]
[SOULS scream and moan]
[moaning &amp; screaming continues,
CELL growls]
[PICCOLO thinking] There
must be thousands of them!
[ANDROID 17 gasps]
[CELL growls]
[yelling]
[PICCOLO whimpers]
[CELL] Well, now, let's
get started! Shall we?
What's wrong?
You frightened?
Don't be ashamed.
It's hard, I know.
You feel my power
and it's hard to bear!
Awww...
[CELL chuckles]
What do you mean?!
It's not your power!
You stole it by taking
the lives of innocent people!
What? Fool! Stole it?!
They're part of greatness now!
I've given them all a purpose.
You're nuts!
[PICCOLO growls]
[ROSHI] What a horrible energy!
Cell must have powered up!
Piccolo must be flipping out!
I'm flipping out!
O-Oh, dear! I think I over
did it on the coffee, guys!
[KRILLIN]
I didn't have any
and I'm still about to
jump out of my skin!
Man, this just isn't natural!
It's driving me nuts,
hanging out here
in the bleachers
while a fight is going on!
Yeah! You said it!
This is nuts! There must
be something we can do!
I appreciate that you're
both eager to help, guys,
but I think our best
bet is staying put
until Bulma gets over here
with her new remote control.
Right!
Can't you guys fly faster than
Bulma can get here in her jet?
One of you guys could save time
by flying out to meet Bulma
and bringing the remote back.
You're right!
Of course I'm right.
You can solve problems
without your fists, you know.
You should write
that one down, ChiChi!
Now, if you'll
excuse me, Einstein,
I'm gonna go meet Bulma!
[ROSHI]
Good luck, Krillin!
I can't take this anymore!
Huh?!
I'm not sure if
I can help or not,
but I'll never find out here!
[TIEN growls]
[TIEN yells]
[ROSHI]
Tien, no! Don't do it!
[ROSHI] Darn it!
Doesn't anyone listen?!
Their heads are
too thick! Ohh, poo-pee...
What am I talking about?
My goodness...
If I was in his shoes,
I would've probably
done the same thing.
My gosh!
It seems like yesterday
when I was just like them.
I was considered the strongest
in the world back then.
Now I'd do anything just
to be able to help out again.
[thinking] Goku, please!
We all need you...
[thinking] Come on! What the
heck is going on in there?!
[ANDROID 17] Hey! I was
in the middle of something.
You're intruding.
[CELL] Yes, I see that now.
How rude of me!
There must be some way
I can make it up to you.
No need for long-winded
apologies. Just go away.
We have some business
that we're trying to settle.
[CELL] Yes, yes. I see
your point, but...
I have a little business of my
own that I need to take care of.
17! He came here
to kill you and Android 18!
Watch it! Look out!
Huh?!
[ANDROID 17 grunts]
[CELL growls,
ANDROID 17 yells]
[CELL laughs]
[CELL grunts]
[PICCOLO growls]
[CELL chuckles]
Thank you, Piccolo.
That was close!
So what's the deal?
You said this creature
is here to kill us?
His name is Cell!
He was spawned by
Dr. Gero's computer
and he came here to
absorb the two of you!
If he succeeds, and
he's able to integrate you
and Android 18 into his being,
his evolution will be complete!
What a creep!
[CELL] Rejoice my
brother and sister!
The three of us are
like pieces to a puzzle,
designed and destined to fit
together and form one whole.
Unite with me
and fulfill Doctor Gero's dream
to create the ultimate warrior!
It's a nice offer,
but no thanks.
Besides, it seems a little
crowded in there already.
I don't need you.
This is what I am.
[CELL] It doesn't matter
what you think you are!
You are part of me and
I am going to absorb you.
[ANDROID 17] Hmph. Go ahead and
give it your best shot, Cell!
[CELL]
Yes! I will.
[ANDROID 16]
17!
I would not fight him!
It is extremely risky!
It would be best for
the both of you to run.
This is a creature
that has great power.
Escape is
highly recommended.
[ANDROID 17]
Now you speak.
Well, go ahead and
take-off if you want.
Don't you worry.
I'll take care of
the big, bad monster.
[ANDROID 17 chuckles]
Ready?!
[ANDROID 17 yells]
[ANDROID 17 grunts]
--Huh?
--[ANDROID 16 growls]
[PICCOLO yells]
[yelling continues]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[CELL] Hyaah!
Darn!
[CELL] You shouldn't have
interfered, Piccolo.
[CELL chuckles]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[PICCOLO] Oh boy,
that one really smarts...
[ANDROID 18] Come on, it doesn't
seem like 17 and Piccolo
are even trying.
They are.
The creature has a much bigger
power than them though.
[ANDROID 27 grunts]
You should leave here...
while you can.
Huh?
If the creature absorbs 17,
we will not be able to stop him.
He will be too strong.
You should go.
What would you do?
Stay or go?
[PICCOLO pants]
[PICCOLO]
That's it! C'mon, Piccolo!
You can do this!
[PICCOLO] Alright!
Steady now! Steady as she goes!
[thinking]
This one's for Gohan and Goku!
[PICCOLO growls]
[PICCOLO yells]
Now, Cell!
No...
[PICCOLO yells]
[PICCOLO pants]
[ANDROID 18] Wow.
I think Piccolo did it.
[ANDROID 17] What a
bizarre creature that was!
Brilliant!
What an attack.
Don't be fooled.
It's not over. He's not dead.
Huh?!
[PICCOLO whimpers]
[ANDROID 17] Hey. What's the
matter, Piccolo? What is it?
[PICCOLO]
I-It's him! Cell!
[PICCOLO whimpers]
[CELL growls quietly]
[CELL] Are you finished
playing games, Piccolo?
[CELL chuckles]
[TIEN] Piccolo just gave
Cell everything he had
and it didn't even phase him...
What now? He can't win!
Not against a power like that!
[CELL] You can't stop me,
Piccolo! It's useless to resist.
[CELL] I am amused by your
little one-man army,
but I have run out of patience.
The road of life ends here for
you. You've reached a dead end.
[ANDROID 17]
Piccolo...
[CELL] Hmm...?
Ahhh...
Run, 17! Now!
--[CELL yells]
--[PICCOLO grunts]
[CELL]
All too easy, Piccolo...
[CELL grunts]
[PICCOLO gurgles]
[TIEN gasps]
Piccolo! That fiend!
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL] I could
absorb you, Piccolo.
But I have all that
I need of your being
in my cell structure already.
You are of no
value to me anymore!
You are just... refuse.
Goodbye.
[PICCOLO grunts]
[PICCOLO screams]
[TIEN gasps]
[GOHAN gasps]
[GOKU gasps]
[PICCOLO rasps]
No! What a beast!
[ANDROID 18 gasps]
[PICCOLO rasps]
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL] Haah!
Oh, my gosh!
Piccolo! No, guys,
we've lost him!
[GOHAN]
Oh, no! Piccolo!
Kami...
[GOHAN whimpers]
[GOKU growls]
[GOHAN]
I can't take this anymore!
Gohan?
Gohan, no! Wait!
No! Let go!
It's not fair!
Let go of me!
Piccolo needs me! Let go of me!
[GOKU] Gohan, listen!
You've got to listen to me!
I know it's not fair!
But we only have one chance
to beat that monster
and we have to play to win!
If we don't, Piccolo's
sacrifice will be in vain...
[GOHAN]
But it hurts, Dad...
[GOKU]
I know, Son. I know...
[GOKU thinking]
Vegeta! Trunks! Come on!
We're out of time!
We can't keep this
up much longer.
[CELL]
Alone at last.
It seems that Piccolo will
no longer be joining us.
[CELL growls]
[CELL]
Don't be afraid, Android 17.
This is your destiny.
It has always been.
You are part of me.
You, too, my little peach.
I am going to gobble you up!
[ANDROID 18 gasps]
[CELL laughs]
[NARRATOR]
With Cell in their midst,
the androids now have
much more on their minds
than how to defeat Goku.
It seems that the hunters
have become the hunted.
Is the combined strength
of the androids enough to
prevent Cell from absorbing
them into his being?
Stay tuned for scenes
from the next episode
of Dragon Ball Z!