[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z...
After Bulma, Krillin and Gohan
crash-landed on Planet Namek,
two friendly local
inhabitants were waiting,
ready to offer
a helping hand...
Showing more hospitality than
the three were accustomed to,
the Nameks decided to
help their new friends
find the missing
Dragon Balls.
[RAITI] Got it!
[NARRATOR] But even
such dedicated help
couldn't keep the
road to discovery
from being littered
with obstacles.
[BULMA screaming]
Flashing Attack... Haah!
[NARRATOR] The search for
the remaining Dragon Balls
continues on today's
episode of Dragon Ball Z!
[VEGETA thinking]
Kakarot!
[NURSE yawning]
Phew!
[GOKU yelling]
[CHICHI gently snoring]
I think we should
find the Dragon Balls
as soon as possible
so we can go
and sleep in our
own beds for once.
Well, that sounds great,
but this planet is so huge.
I kinda get the feeling
this is gonna take a while.
Don't worry. We'll
find them in no time.
There's nothing I like more
than a positive attitude.
Hey, how come Raiti
didn't come with us?
Unfortunately,
he had to stay home
and finish some
work in the garage.
This is strange...
The radar is telling
me that a Dragon Ball
is approaching
us dead ahead!
[BULMA]
See what I mean?
[GOHAN] It's
moving pretty fast.
What's that?
Wha--!
What are you doing?
Don't just stand there,
get the Dragon Ball!
[ALL] Uhh.
Come on, Krillin! Hurry up and
get it before it blows away!
W-Wait, hold up!
Why don't we wait for the
tornado to disappear?
[ZAACRO chuckling]
You're gonna have
to wait a long time.
On this planet,
tornadoes have been known
to wander the
plains for ages.
Zaacro and I are
gonna take cover.
Don't waste any more
time, okay? Go!
What are you doing?
Don't stare at it!
Go get it!
Man... She's bossy.
Are you ready to go
head-to-head with a tornado?
Yup.
Let's do it!
Desctructo Disk!
Yaah!
Masenko...
Wait, guys! Stop!
Don't do that!
You'll destroy the Dragon
Ball if you attack it!
Oh yeah. I forgot.
Where are those
fools going?
Why don't they
ever listen to me?!
It's coming right
for us! Quick, run!
This is exactly the kind
of thing that makes me
want to never come back
to this horrible planet!
Keep running!
[GOHAN whimpering]
I'm just a technical
girl who works in a lab
tinkering with
robotics and microchips!
How do I end up
running from tornadoes
and flying all over the galaxy
looking for Dragon Balls?!
Just don't stop!
[thinking] I've got to get
that Dragon Ball back!
Piccolo's life
depends on it!
[thinking]
Whatever it takes!
There it is!
All right!
Masenko...
Ha!
Gohan!
Are you okay?
Look what
I got!
Nice going!
[GOHAN] Woo-hoo!
That makes
three left!
[GOHAN laughing]
[thinking] It sure feels good
to be out of that hospital.
I was so sick of these
bandages tying me down.
The only way
to get better
is to get out there
and keep training!
Hyaah!
[GOKU grunting painfully]
[GOKU groaning]
[beeping]
The next one is that
way. I'm sure of it.
I hope we can find our
way in this dense jungle.
I'm gonna make a torch
so we can see better.
[strange screeching]
That didn't sound
very comforting.
[strange screeching]
[ALL screaming]
[birds screeching]
[screeching continues]
[GOHAN]
Wow! What a view!
[BULMA] Help! Grab me,
I'm about to fall off!
[BULMA screaming]
[KRILLIN] There.
[KRILLIN chuckling]
Look! It's a castle!
[bird screeching]
[ALL screaming]
[birds screeching]
So, what do you think
we should do now?
We have no other choice.
We'll have to jump.
You can't be serious!
That's crazy!
Either we jump, or we become
this bird's next meal.
[screeches]
Fine! I'll jump!
But only if you
promise you'll catch me
before I hit
the ground!
[KRILLIN] Don't worry!
I'll catch you!
[BULMA screaming]
[GOKU screaming]
[GOKU yelling]
You're all going
to suffer...
And when you beg
me for mercy...
I'll stare into your
eyes as I crush you...
[GOKU grunting]
[yells]
[GOKU screaming]
I won't stand a
chance against Vegeta.
Not like this!
[snoring]
[snoring continues]
[snake hissing]
I'm getting a
strong reading
from the Dragon Ball
right in front of us.
[BULMA screaming]
[muffled screaming]
[snoring]
Bulma, we're
gonna check it out.
You stay here
and stand watch.
This thing wouldn't wake up
if we screamed in its ear.
[GOHAN] Hey, Krillin!
Any luck finding it yet?
No, nothing yet. Hey,
Zaacro, what about you?
I haven't
found anything.
Tell me: where did you
hide the Dragon Ball?!
[BULMA screaming]
[whimpering]
[grumbling]
[BULMA] Ah! I found it!
[GOHAN] Here we go.
[ALL grunting]
[grunting continues]
[grunting]
Safe!
Now, let's leave this
oversized nightmare.
[KRILLIN whimpering]
[growling]
[CHICHI] Great! First
my son, now my husband.
[ROSHI] Hmm. Come on, don't
take it so hard. You know Goku.
I'm sure he had a perfectly
good reason to leave.
What?! A good reason to
leave? Yeah, right!
Those two go running off at
the first sign of adventure,
leaving the rest
of us sit around,
pay the bills,
and worry about them!
Woah, woah, woah!
Hold on now, ChiChi!
We both know very
well that they
can take care of themselves
just fine without us.
Are you out of your mind?!
Goku even forgot to
pack his sweater!
I go through the trouble of
making this, and he forgets it!
Why, I could strangle
him with it!
[BULMA] Okay,
here's the throttle...
Check the
fuel gauge...
I think I found what
I'm having for lunch!
Bulma, I don't
mean to rush you,
but I don't
wanna be lunch!
I could work
a lot faster
if you would stop being
such a backseat flyer!
[roaring]
You know, taking the stairs
would be faster than this!
Instead of
whining so much,
why don't you try and do
something with the angry giant?!
[roaring continues]
All right,
Bulma. Fine.
You ready, Gohan?
[GOHAN] Yup!
I'm gonna tear
all of you apart!
[BOTH growling]
[BULMA] I don't
get it.
How can there not be
an oil pressure gauge?
And what
does this do?
[BULMA growling]
I have had it
with this thing!
[engine sputtering]
I did it!
I knew my genius,
scientific mind
would come in
handy at some point!
Destructo Disk!
Yaah...
Hyaah!
[GIANT groaning]
Masenko Ha!
Haah!
[BOTH] We did it!
[GIANT growling]
[GOHAN and KRILLIN whimpering]
[BOTH] Hyaah!
[GIANT roaring]
[BOTH gasping]
[GIANT snarling]
[GOHAN laughing]
Nice catch,
Bulma!
Maybe you'd like
to apologize
for the comments
you made earlier?
You always second-guess
my abilities,
yet I seem to be the one
saving you all the time!
Is that really true?
Now, we only
have two left!
We should be able to go home
much sooner than I anticipated.
I'm all for that plan.
Uh? Eh?!
Eh? Eh?!
[GOKU grunting]
[thinking]
Boy, it sure is nice
to feel the wind
through my hair again.
Aahhh...
He looks strong.
[DOCTOR] I think he
may be ready.
But, let's keep emergency
equipment on standby,
just in case the
worst happens.
I'll initiate the draining
procedure, right...
Now.
You are fully healed now.
You can open your eyes.
Unfortunately,
we weren't successful
in reconstructing
your tail.
[VEGETA] No matter.
I don't need it.
[NARRATOR] Vegeta's
recovery has finally ended
and his next terrifying
battle with Goku
is waiting on
the horizon!
Don't miss it as the
adventure continues
on the next
Dragon Ball Z!