[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Frieza decided to test
Goku's agility and speed
by bombarding him
with boulders.
Now! It's my turn!
[NARRATOR] Goku proved to be
up to the challenge though,
and he easily
vaporized the remainder
of Frieza's projectiles.
[NARRATOR] But after
a sneak attack,
Goku found himself trapped
in a ball of energy.
[NARRATOR] Then Frieza launched
him like a Saiyan Warhead,
set to explode
on impact.
[NARRATOR] Just when
it was looking like
Goku wouldn't
make it out alive,
the Saiyan emerged
from behind the smoke.
[NARRATOR] Not only
had Goku survived,
but he appeared unharmed.
They're monsters...
One good, one evil...
[NARRATOR] It was then
that Frieza proposed they
stop pulling their punches
and use their true power.
No more sandbagging,
what do you say?
Sounds good, sure.
[NARRATOR] The fight
rages on... today!
[KRILLIN] So... this is it. The
calm before the storm, huh?
[PICCOLO]
Yeah, you got that right.
[KRILLIN gasps]
[GOHAN screams]
[GOHAN]
Wow! Check out that splash.
[KRILLIN] Yeah. That
was a pretty big chunk.
Look... Just look at 'em...
It's hard to believe,
but the outcome of this fight
will influence the future
of the entire universe.
[KRILLIN] And we're the only
ones who get to watch it...
[PICCOLO] Hopefully we'll get
a chance to do more than that.
[GOKU] What d'ya say
we get down to it?
I've got better things to do
than stare at you all day.
[FRIEZA] You are
a case, aren't you?
Killing you is going
to be sheer delight.
[GOKU] Alrighty, then.
It's now or never.
Sure, what do you prefer?!
Ground? Or up in the air?
Ground's good. Yeah,
sure, why not? Ground.
I'm a "ground"
kind of guy.
If that's alright
with you of course.
[FRIEZA giggles]
[FRIEZA]
I like your attitude.
Let's see...
[GOHAN]
There they go!
[KRILLIN]
What? They're landing already.
[PICCOLO]
They're choosing a battle site.
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN]
Huh?!
Frieza must fight better
when he's in the air.
Goku's call. This is it...
Go, Dad...
[GOKU]
So this must be the place.
[FRIEZA] Yes, this will make
a fine site for your grave.
It's perfect! Now, would you
prefer cremation or burial?
Daisies or chrysanthemums?
Whatever! You pick. I trust ya.
[FRIEZA giggles]
For that, I'm going to give
you a little break. Ah, I know!
I'll fight without
using my hands!
Well, how does that grab you?
That's your call...
Fine then. This way I won't
break my nails. Alright?
It's up to you. But I
don't recommend it.
[FRIEZA] You're too
cocky if you think
I need to use my
hands to beat you.
I don't want you
to die believing
that you ever really
had a chance to win.
Okay, I'm not going to
argue with ya, shoot.
Very well, then.
No hands, it is.
[FRIEZA]
Hmm...
[GOKU] Haaaah!
[DR. BRIEF]
Whoooaa!
[DR. BRIEF coughs]
[DR. BRIEF] Ohhh...
[coughing continues]
Well, she's good as new. Great!
[DR. BRIEF]
There we go!
Perfect! Now let's crank her up.
[DR. BRIEF]
Yes!
[CHICHI growls]
[CHICHI] I can't believe
my Dad broke the ship
just so I couldn't leave.
It better be fixed by now!
[CHICHI screams]
[DR. BRIEF] The repairs are
coming along slowly this time.
[ROSHI]
Good. Let's keep it that way.
So, that's the plan, huh?!
[DR. BRIEF]
Hm?
Schemer! How dare you
make light of this situation
when my son's life is at stake!
Your daughter's up there too!
Doesn't that mean anything to
you?! Don't you have a heart?!
ChiChi! That's enough
now! Come on!
[CHICHI growls,
ROSHI grunts]
[ROSHI grunts]
Picking on a helpless girl!
You should be ashamed! Hmph!
Look, I can't win here.
If I fix it fast, your dad
and the others jump on me.
If I fix it slow,
well, let's just say
it's best not to fix it slow.
You got it! So get the
lead out and fix it!
My dear lady, it takes time
to re-energize a reactor.
[CHICHI] Hmm?!
In layman's terms,
these yellow lights
have to be all the
way up to that "F",
but, as you can plainly see,
they're not even close.
So what?!
Huh?!
Who cares?! Just fix it!
I'm a scientist, not
a magician. Use your head.
[CHICHI]
What did you say?! How dare you!
[OOLONG] Why do I have to go to
Namek?! I'm just a regular pig!
One karate chop and my
hand aches for days. Man.
My stategy is kick 'em
in the shin and run,
but that won't work.
We should forget about
going to Lizard-Ville and head
to the Bahamas. Huh?!
[PUAR sobs]
[PUAR] We were so happy
together. Just the three of us.
I'm not going to take in
anymore of this sitting down.
Forget it.
Let's kick booty!
Calm down there,
tough guy. Kook...
Now, you just need to train at
a hundred times normal gravity,
Puar, and you'll be set.
[PUAR]
Okay!
[OOLONG]
Hey! Haaa!
[YAJIROBE yells]
Gotcha. "Coward" is my
forté. You can't fool me.
[YAJIROBE groans]
Hm?!
[FRIEZA giggles]
[GOKU grunting]
[grunting continues]
[GOKU] Not bad, Frieza.
[FRIEZA] Hmm...
Wha--?
[GOKU grunts]
♪ Fool. I made you look! ♪
♪ You dirty crook. You stole
your mother's pocket book. ♪
And one more for the road.
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU screams]
[FRIEZA]
Hmm...
[FRIEZA] Well, well. A little
slow getting up, are we? Hmm.
Oh, THERE he goes.
You had me worried.
I thought you were giving up.
No way. You're dreaming.
This fight's not over. Trust me.
[FRIEZA]
Ooooh! I see!
Come on, Goku...
Yeah, Dad!
[PICCOLO thinking]
He's faster than Goku...
I don't like this...
[FRIEZA] Don't tell me
that you still actually believe
that you have a chance to beat
me. You poor dope.
[FRIEZA giggles]
How strange. The chips are
down, but for some odd reason,
the challenge of trying to beat
this monster exciting to me!
Alright! If you won't move
then I'm coming to you!
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU grunting]
[FRIEZA]
Ta-ta.
[GOKU]
Whooaa!
[GOKU shouts]
[FRIEZA] Hmm?!
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU] Man... When's the...
last time you had a... bath?
Yeah, no foolin'! Whew! It's
downright unpleasant back here!
[FRIEZA] First you grab my tail,
and then you insult me.
You're going to pay
dearly for this.
[GOKU grunts]
[FRIEZA]
Let go!
[GOKU]
Okay! You asked for it!
[GOKU shouts]
[FRIEZA] Whoa!
[shouting continues]
[GOKU]
Huh...? Huh?!
[GOKU grunting]
[FRIEZA grunts]
[GOKU yells]
[FRIEZA]
Rrrgh! I'm going to kill you!
[GOKU] Man, I think
I'm having a deja' vu!
[FRIEZA]
Rrrgh! You are so dead!
BULMA Did I mention to you
that I'm a genius? Yep!
I'm not just
another pretty face.
Y'know, I'm almost as smart
as I am beautiful. It's scary.
Hey there, bud. You're so quiet.
I hope you're not bored.
Now, where was I? Oh yeah,
now I remember. It's true.
I'm a genius.
But you're pretty smart too,
considering how we met.
[GINYU] Ribbit.
[BULMA muffled] Hey!
[BULMA]
Hmmm...?
[FROGS croaking]
[BULMA gasps]
[BULMA] What are you
laughing at, huh?!
[BULMA whimpers]
You little jerks! Can't a
girl even die in peace?!
[BULMA screams]
[BULMA] How did my life
turn into such shambles?
I should have never
taken this trip...
What a nightmare.
Frogs. How gross.
[GINYU] Ribbit.
Hmm...?
Ribbit ribbit.
[thinking] Wow, what's up
with this little guy?
Man, there's something
special about you, bud.
Yeah, for real.
[GINYU laughs, yells]
[BULMA] I always told
my Dad he was silly
for stashing emegency food
on the air-bikes,
but, man, what a lifesaver!
[GINYU whines]
Hm? You're hungry, too?
[GINYU] Mm-hmm!
[BULMA]
There you go.
Wow. The poor little guy
was starving to death. Man.
Hey, how about desert?
[GINYU whimpers]
Oooh!
[BULMA giggles]
There!
Whooaaa...
[GINYU laughs]
[BULMA laughs]
Man, it's like he
understands what I'm saying.
Hey, can you shake your
head if you understand
what I'm saying? Two shakes.
Wow, hey, he does! Hey, I
could be the next Jane Goodall
except with frogs!
Maybe he's really a Prince!
[GINYU] Uhh...
[BULMA]
That should do it...
Not too bad. Here you go!
One universal translator.
Mm-hmm. Now I should
be able to understand
what you're saying
to me. Cool, huh?.
Ready? Here we go!
Say something silly.
It's working now.
[GINYU growls]
Huh...?
Ah! Change now!
[BULMA] Hey, what's up?!
What's going on?!
[GINYU grunts]
[BULMA screams]
[GINYU sighs]
[GINYU chuckles]
[GINYU] At last!
I was getting a little
claustrophobic in that frog.
What luck! I never
thought I'd find a body
in the middle of nowhere.
[BULMA] Huh?! Hey! What did
you do to me, you fiend!
[BULMA screams]
[GINYU]
Come here, little guy...
[BULMA wails]
Ribbit?!
Oh, yes. Much better.
No more blabber-mouth. Adios.
[GINYU chuckles]
What dispicable, slimy,
little creatures they are!
[BULMA growls]
Hey, instead of complaining, you
should be learning how to hop.
[PICCOLO growls]
[grunting]
[grunting continues]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU shouts]
[FRIEZA] There! Now I've
got you. It's all over.
[FRIEZA] What a pity.
You've gotten yourself
into quite a fix.
[FRIEZA] Huh? Not bad...
But don't get tired and let
go or your head will pop off
like a champagne cork.
[FRIEZA laughs]
[FRIEZA] Oh, my!
What's the matter, big guy?
Did you expect a
Fairy Tale ending?
Well, don't lose
your head over it.
You can't always
have it your way.
[GOKU wheezes]
[FRIEZA cackles]
[GOKU screams]
[cackling continues]
[screaming continues]
[FRIEZA squeals]
[FRIEZA whimpers]
[FRIEZA] Hmm?!
[GOKU yells]
[FRIEZA grunting]
[GOKU shouting]
[FRIEZA grunts]
[GOKU grunts]
So, I guess you had to
use your hands after all!
[FRIEZA gasps]
[FRIEZA giggles]
[GOKU chuckles]
Okay, from now on,
the deal's off.
[GOKU] Yeah, well, I sort of
gathered that much already.
[FRIEZA]
Oh, my. I'm so sorry.
Yeah, I'll bet. Well,
please don't go losing
any sleep over it.
Shoot, I'm sure that it
was an honest mistake.
You're welcome to try
it again if you want to.
Thanks, but no thanks.
[NARRATOR] All bets are
off as Frieza decides
to stop playing games.
And with each fighter knowing
it's going to take everything
he's got to win,
the action intensifies.
On the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z.