[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z!
With Krillin and Gohan
closing in fast,
the outmatched
Guldo had no choice
but to launch his
attack of last resort...
the paralyzing
"Mind Bind" technique!
Once snared in
Guldo's psychic web,
Gohan and Krillin
were forced to endure
every cruel and
unusual punishment
the evil green mutant
could think to dish out!
[GOHAN grunting]
[GULDO laughs]
[GULDO] Whee!
What's wrong?
You don't like me
pulling on your cheeks?
So how 'bout I try
pounding instead?!
[NARRATOR] And just as
it began to seem Guldo
had covered every
possible method of torment,
he found yet another way
to stick it to our heroes...
this time
permanently.
It's no use! I still
can't move a muscle!
[GULDO laughs]
Ready or not...
Time to die!
[NARRATOR] Though Krillin
and Gohan struggled
with all their might,
there was no escape.
Krillin prepared himself
for the worst, when suddenly,
like a bolt out of the
blue, a savior appeared!
[NARRATOR] It was Vegeta!
The Saiyan Prince burst
in from the sidelines
to head off
Guldo's attack!
And in one bold stroke,
the villain was defeated.
I had my own reasons for
wanting to destroy that freak.
I saw my moment to strike,
and I acted on it.
That's all. It had nothing
to do with saving your lives.
[NARRATOR] But Guldo was the
weakest of the Ginyu Force!
Three powerful members still
remain on the battlefield!
Do Krillin, Gohan and
Vegeta have any hope
of surviving the
onslaught to come?!
Hope is a luxury none
of us can afford...
[NARRATOR] These three
unlikely allies continue
the fight for their
lives... today!
[BIRDS cawing]
[RECOOME chuckling]
[VEGETA growls]
[KRILLIN whimpering]
[RECOOME chuckling]
[RECOOME] All right, kids, this
fight's between me and Vegeta.
But if you feel like
jumpin' in to help him out,
go ahead and try it.
I'll take you all on at once.
[JEICE] Hey, not so
fast there, Recoome!
That wasn't
the deal!
We're just not gonna stand here
and let you have all the fun!
Save the two little ones
for us like we agreed.
[RECOOME] Yeah,
yeah. Whatever...
Man!
Either way,
we're toast!
And now! Feel
the power of...
Recoooome!
[KRILLIN] Unbelievable...
[VEGETA growls]
[shouting]
Ah...!
Huh?
What the--? Why that
sly little devil.
Looks like Vegeta's
been hiding
his true power
level from us!
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN grunting]
[VEGETA shouting]
[shouting continues]
[RECOOME] Ugh!
[VEGETA] Raagh!
[RECOOME groans]
Yaah!
[VEGETA growling]
[RECOOME] Gwugh!
[RECOOME yelling]
[VEGETA growling]
[VEGETA shouts]
[KRILLIN] Duck!
See you in
hell, Recoome!
Raaagh!
[VEGETA panting]
He... He did it!
[KRILLIN] Incredible... That big
oaf never even saw it coming!
I never thought I'd
hear myself say this,
but, I'm sure glad
Vegeta's on our side!
[JEICE sputters,
BURTER growls]
Ahhh, man,
that was close!
[VEGETA gasps]
No... I... I can still
feel his power level.
He's... He's
still there!
[KRILLIN] There's... no way!
He couldn't be!
[RECOOME chuckling]
Hi!
[VEGETA growls]
[KRILLIN whimpering]
This is crazy! He's not
even breathing hard!
Wh-What the heck
are we gonna do?!
[RECOOME laughs]
Nice try! But
now... It's my turn!
[JEICE] Oh, this
is just great!!
You know how long
it's gonna take me
to wash all this dust
out of my hair?!
Complain all you want,
at least you've got hair!
[KRILLIN] We can't
beat these guys...
The only thing that's
gonna keep Frieza
from getting those
Dragon Balls now
is some kind
of miracle!
[GINYU humming]
[GINYU gasps]
[GINYU] The Dragon Ball!
Frieza wouldn't
be too happy
if I let one of
these get away.
Well, then no more
fooling around!
[COMPUTER] Now analyzing:
Planet Namek.
Environmental
Quality: fair.
Mineral Resources: low.
Civilization Advancement: low.
Industrial and
Commercial Potential: zero.
[FRIEZA] Hmph! I thought so...
It's just a useless rock.
There isn't anything
here worth developing.
But that's good.
As long as there's no
profit to be made here...
Well, then... There's nothing
to stop me from blowing it up.
[FRIEZA chuckles]
Huh?!
Once I have
the Dragon Balls,
it will make a nice
fireworks display,
to celebrate
my immortality!
Ah yes... I'll write the
name of Frieza in lights
across the galaxy!
You're kidding, right?
[FRIEZA] I'm not, how do you
say, the "kidding" type?
It will be...
glorious!
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[FRIEZA] What are you staring
at?! See if there are any other
nearby planets
worth conquering!
Right! As
you command!
[thinking] I think I'm going
to enjoy eternal life...
Now, this is one of my
favorite little moves.
Recooooooome... Kick!
V-Vegeta!
[VEGETA] Hah!
Whu--?
[VEGETA shouting]
[blows landing,
grunting]
[RECOOME] I gotta hand
it to you, I'm impressed!
But let's see if you can
bounce back from this one!
Recooome... Boom!
Heh, heh...
[VEGETA] Raah!
Oh!
[BOTH] All right!
[RECOOME laughs]
[RECOOME] What'd I tell you,
Vegeta? You're all washed up!
[RECOOME laughs]
[KRILLIN} Oh no...
This... This could be it...
All right!
It's about time!
[RECOOME] Yeah!
[RECOOME chuckles]
Yeah, no sweat!
[KRILLIN] I don't think
he's coming up, Gohan...
V-Vegeta...
[RECOOME] Hey, Vegeta!
What's the deal?
You didn't go and die
on me, did you?
Come on! I didn't get a chance
to do all my best moves!
Ah!
[RECOMME chuckles]
[VEGETA yells]
Oogh!
[RECOOME yelling]
[VEGETA shouts]
[RECOOME groaning]
[blows landing]
[RECOOME groans]
[chuckles]
I'm glad you're back, Vegeta!
[RECOOME grunts,
VEGETA yells]
[both yelling]
[VEGETA yelling]
[GOHAN yells]
[KRILLIN yells]
[RECOOME laughs]
Hey, now!
What do we have here?
[RECOOME grunts]
Looks like a vegetable
ready to be picked!
[RECOOME guffaws]
[RECOOME] Oh?!
[RECOOME yells]
[VEGETA pants]
[whimpering]
I don't
believe it!
[RECOOME shouts]
[whimpering]
[RECOOME guffaws]
Now that was low...
Even for a Saiyan!
You are ruthless, Vegeta...
No wonder you were always
one of Frieza's favorites!
[RECOOME] It's almost
too bad you had to go
and turn traitor on us.
[JEICE laughs]
That Recoome...
He's just having a laugh!
He loves his work...
[KRILLIN] This
guy's too much...
[RECCOME] Go ahead!
You got any more sneaky
tricks you wanna try?
Or should I just kill you now
before this gets too boring?
[thinking] Damn it all!
I knew from
the outset
that this battle would
be difficult to win...
But this
is insane!
I'm fighting at the
limits of my ability,
but he's just
toying with me!
Brushing off my attacks
like they were nothing!
[thinking] If this
keeps up, I don't know
how much longer I can last!
[KRILLIN] G-Gohan...
Yeah?
Look... It doesn't
matter anymore...
Whatever we do, we're
still gonna die...
We... We can't
beat these guys...
None of us!
Not even Goku...
[KRILLIN] There's nothing left
to lose... I'm goin' in!
You with me?
[GOHAN] Right!
You ready
for this?
Haaa!
There he goes...
I think we've just
come to the grand finale!
[BURTER chuckles]
You better take a
last look at Vegeta...
'Cause after this there
won't be anything left!
[RECOOME guffaws]
Yeah! Now I'm
gonna rub you out!
All right. Here
it comes, Gohan...
As soon as he
starts his attack,
you get Vegeta
out of here quick!
I'll see if I can't
blindside that big gorilla!
Got it!
Recooome...
Eraser Gun!
Haaaa!
[BOTH shout]
[GOHAN] Hang on,
Vegeta!
[GOHAN grunting]
[BOTH grunting]
What are you doing?!
Could you be any more stupid?
[GOHAN] W-what?
[KRILLIN] Whew...
Too close!
[VEGETA grunts]
Fool! Instead of
coming after me...
You should have both used the
opportunity to attack Recoome!
Dammit! Do you
really think
he's going to let his guard
down like that again?!
He sure made a
heck of a dent...
Guess he wasn't kidding when
he called it his "Eraser Gun".
It just wiped
everything out!
[RECOOME grunts]
Huh?
[KRILLIN gasps]
[RECOOME] That was
pretty crafty, twerp.
You made me slam my mouth
shut on my own blast. Ow.
I would be pissed...
But, lucky for you I
know a good dentist.
[KRILLIN whimpers]
Hey! Jeice!
Burter!
How about you guys let
me kill this one too?
Whadda ya say?
Yeah? No?
Well... I guess
you owe him one.
All right! You've
got yourself a deal!
He's yours! But as soon
as we get back home,
you're treating us
to lunch for a week!
Yeah, yeah... You just cost
me big. Now I'm pissed!
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[VEGETA gasps]
[GOHAN whimpers]
Hoo... yaahh... too... hnn...
Raah!
[GOHAN screams]
Krillin!
[RECOOME] How'd you like that?
Speak to me,
Krillin! Please!
I... I'm sorry, Gohan...
But I think I broke
every bone in my body...
[KRILLIN] We knew this
is how it would end...
They're just
too strong...
We never even
ha-had a chance...
But at least I got
in one good shot...
No! You've
gotta hang on!
You can't give up!
Just hang on, Krillin!
It's... all right... It's-It's
time to face the facts...
The... Dr-Dragon Balls
are... gone...
So, please... Save
yourself while you can...
[GOHAN growls]
Man! I don't
believe it!
My wind-up pose must
be off or somethin'!
That kick shoulda'
sent his bald head
skidding at least
twice as far!
Agh... Oh well, I guess
I'll have to try again...
I will.
[GOHAN growls]
G-Gohan...
You stay away!
I... I'm not gonna let you
hurt my friend any more!
[RECOOME laughs]
Oh, is that so?
[RECOOME guffaws]
[RECOOME] You hear
that, everyone?
[guffawing continues]
[GOHAN growls]
[VEGETA pants]
[RECOOME] That was funny.
[RECOOME guffaws]
[GOHAN growls]
[BURTER chuckles]
[NARRATOR] With Krillin and
Vegeta no longer able to fight,
young Gohan is left to face
the towering Recoome alone!
Can the pint-sized
Saiyan warrior
stand up to this
monstrous foe?
Find out, in the next
action-packed episode
of Dragon Ball Z!