[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
the fighters began to gather for
the start of Cell's tournament.
And who better
to arrive first
but World Famous
Champion-Of-Show, Mr. Satan!
And he was quick
to announce his plans!
Cell was not amused.
[ANNOUNCER laughs]
[ANNOUNCER] Hey, Cell,
get a load of this one!
[NARRATOR] While Mr. Satan
and his announcer sidekick
continued their moronic taunts,
Vegeta appeared at ringside.
And judging from
his cold expression,
he was determined to
make up for his last defeat.
[NARRATOR] Next to land was
the newly rebuilt Android 16.
And the others
were soon to follow.
Flying in close formation,
It was an impressive entrance
that had even Cell reacting
as he saw for the first time
all the competition
he would be up against.
[NARRATOR] And as far
as Cell was concerned,
only one question remained:
who would fight him first?
Goku seemed like a shoe-in,
but the hard-headed Mr. Satan
was quick to demonstrate
that he would start things off.
Goku and his friends
were baffled,
but a choice must
quickly be made...
Because, as Cell
has made it clear...
[CELL] It's time!
[NARRATOR]
The fight begins today!
Who will be the
first to challenge?
You're looking at him,
let's get it on!
There's no use in trying to stop
him, Goku. He just won't listen.
I've gotta try!
Listen, Mr. Satan,
if you fight Cell,
you're going to get killed!
[MR. SATAN sighs,
ANNOUNCER chuckles]
Okay, Lionel, get a close-up
of the guy with the big hair.
[LIONEL] Right!
[ANNOUNCER] Are we on? Good...
Just moments ago this
long-haired guy
had the audacity to tell the
people's hero, Hercule Satan,
to back down
from the tournament!
Imagine, telling the Martial
Arts Champion of the World
he was going to be beaten!
Having followed Mr. Satan's
amazing career over the years,
I have one question to
ask this know-it-all brat...
Who do you think you are?!
Sir, that blonde guy's quite
the dummy, wouldn't you say?
I know him.
Or someone who looked...
like him.
Many years ago, there was
a young lad who saved the Earth
from the Evil King Piccolo.
I've never forgotten
the innocent look
on that boy's face.
Hmm...
[KING FURRY] But his eyes,
his eyes were different,
and so was the
color of his hair.
Oh, maybe I'm just
getting old
and my memory isn't
what it used to be.
And yet, somehow
I know it must be him.
Ahh, look at the green one.
I'm sure he looks
just like King Piccolo!
If that doofus wants to
fight Cell first, then let him!
If he packs it in
we can just revive him
with the Dragon Balls.
Well, there seems
to be no other choice...
[ANNOUNCER] They've finally
decided not to interfere!
And for those of you
watching this unfold,
you've got to be ecstatic!
It's time for our champ!
You're gonna LOVE this!
[ANNOUNCER] So let's
set the scene!
The first up will be Mr. Satan,
who, of course, will win,
and then the Earth will be
saved from total destruction!
[WOMAN] Hold on, everybody!
It's time to get happy!
[ANNOUNCER] Oh, could it be?
[WOMAN] That's right!
The fabulous duo is here!
One's got strength,
one's got grace,
and EVERYBODY'S got the love!
Love? For what?
[WOMAN giggles]
It looks like we have
new challengers to take on Cell!
But who are they
and where are they from?
Must be National Goofball Day!
[MAN A] We are the
students of Maestro Satan!
Yes...
Gaze upon me. I am Caroni.
[CARONI hums seductively]
[grunting]
[PIROZHKI] And I am the
stupendous power-man Pirozhki!
Could these
possibly be
the often talked-about
Satan's apprentices?
[WOMAN] That's right,
my friend!
These two are the senior
disciples of Mr. Satan's
World-Renowned
Martial Arts Dojo!
So let's pave the way for our
raw man of muscle, Pirozhki.
And our dashing
speedster Caroni!
That's great! And who are you?
I am their spectacular
manager, Miss Piiza!
Mwah!
Maestro, please
let us take care of him.
There's no point in your
fighting this... sissy.
[PIROZHKI grunts]
[PIROZHKI] I will crush him up!
Hmm, you're right...
It could be a little
embarrassing for me
to take on such
an amateur as Cell!
He's all yours!
[ANNOUNCER] Whoaah Nellie!
You heard it right here, folks!
We have some new challengers!
And this dynamic duo will
replace their mentor
in round one.
What a turn of events!
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is great news!
With the help of Mr. Satan's
devoted students,
how can we fail?!
We can't lose!
I've seen those
two in a magazine!
From what I understand,
as a tag team, they've
never lost a match
in their whole career!
This is awesome!
[thinking] A pair of fools!
I'd say... they're toast.
[ANNOUNCER] And now,
let the Tournament begin!
Introducing Cell's
first challenger,
in the white spandex jump
suit, the lovely... Caroni!
As this is the first chance
we've had to fight or what not,
I'll be gentle.
[CARONI moans]
[CARONI chuckles]
Those are for you.
A bouquet for your funeral.
Man, he's good!
And I'll bet you this
won't go more than one round!
For the home viewers,
Caroni's special
skill is being able to
eradicate anything in the air
with his fabulous
speed and agility!
Thank you, Piiza.
Well, there you have it, folks!
Now let's see him in action!
He's giving me... a headache.
[thinking] Hmm,
I wonder how many women
are watching me right now?
[ANNOUNCER] The tension
is beginning to mount
as Caroni warms up for the
first round of the Cell Games.
The rules are simple:
You lose if you fall
from the ring, give up,
or [gulp] if you die.
Are you nervous?
Don't worry, it will
only hurt for a moment.
Beautiful, flying, rose!
♪ Attack! ♪
Wow! Would you look at that?!
That's the greatest move
in Caroni's repertoire!
Just wait 'til you all
see how it ends!
Let's finish this.
[CARONI yells]
Ooooh! That's some attack!
[CARONI screaming]
You, uh, think he's coming down?
He's in much better
shape than I thought!
Hmm? What's that noise?
[CARONI screams]
[ANNOUNCER &amp; PIIZA scream]
Huh?!
[CARONI groans weakly]
Well, Piiza, you're right!
That WAS a big ending!
Yeah, too bad he couldn't
land INSIDE the ring!
Huh?
In my Fighting Dojo,
I always considered Caroni
to be the son I never had...
But he never quite
measured up to his father.
[PIIZA giggles]
You're the best!
I agree!
[CARONI sobs]
[CROWD murmurs]
[ANNOUNCER] Caroni, the first
challenger in the Cell Games,
has lost by falling
out of the ring!
How terrible!
[PIROZHKI grunts]
[PIROZHKI] Now it is my turn!
[PIROZHKI yells]
Isn't he something?
Pirozhki has the strength
of twenty elephants,
and he absolutely
loves to crush things!
I'd say he came
to the right place!
[PIROZHKI growls]
[grunting, creaking]
[ANNOUNCER] Look at
his brute strength!
I've never seen
anything like that!
It looks like Cell's
met his match!
Get ready for round two!
There's no way Pirozhki will
mess things up like Caroni did.
I feel sorry for Cell.
[PIROZHKI yells]
Yes!
It seems Pirozhki
can smell a victory!
And he's doing
his special attack,
called the "Megaton
Bull Crusher!"
And no one has
ever survived it before!
[PIROZHKI yelling]
Huh?!
[PIROZHKI grunts]
[ANNOUNCER] What's going on?!
It appears Pirozhki's feet
weigh fifty tons each!
[PIROZHKI grunting]
[grunting continues]
I give up!
[ANNOUNCER] Oh, great goodness!
[PIROZHKI whimpers]
[PIIZA gasps]
So how are we supposed
to explain this one?
Mr. Satan?
Another trick!
[BOTH] Huh?
You don't see the
forest for the trees!
It's obvious to me that he's
somehow rigged the ring.
Case in point!
Maybe Cell rubbed himself
down with jalepeno peppers,
which Pirozhki is allergic to!
Or maybe he planted
magnets underneath the ring!
But I am gonna find out
what sort of tricks he's up to!
Yes, I see, so it was Cell's
dirty tricks that beat them!
And I think Mr. Satan's
got a few tricks
of his own up his sleeve!
How thick can they really be?
Cell's energy flicked them
away, not some stupid trick!
It's like talking to a wall!
[ANNOUNCER] This is it, folks!
Mr. Satan has had enough!
He's stepping into the ring
and is about to
finish Cell off himself.
He's taking off his cape,
and he's holding up
his champion fighting belt!
Now it looks like the
real battle's about to begin!
In the next few minutes,
the fate of the entire Earth
will be decided between Cell,
and the undisputed Martial
Arts Champion of the World!
And I'm not too worried
because Mr. Satan promised
to give Cell a hand
through the stomach!
[ANNOUNCER] What's this?
Mr. Satan is reaching into his
robe and pulling something out!
It looks like a... a capsule!
[ANNOUNCER] Look! A travel bag!
What will those clever folks
at Capsule Corporation
think of next?
Well, here we go, everyone...
Mr. Satan is unzipping
the bag and reaching in.
A-ha!
They look like ceramic tiles!
The champ is now carefully
piling up the tiles.
[KRILLIN sighs]
[KRILLIN] That guy's
a real moron.
This guys... an idiot.
[ANNOUNCER] He's now making
a stack fifteen tiles high!
[MR. SATAN yells]
[lauging]
You don't suppose he's going
to break all fifteen tiles
at once, do you?!
[MR. SATAN chuckles]
Oohhhmmm...
[ANNOUNCER] He's now gone
into a trance-like state...
I believe he is focusing his
energy for something incredible!
Let's see what happens...
[MR. SATAN] Oohhhmmm...
Mmmmm...
Oohhhmmm...
[MR. SATAN growls]
[yelling]
[ANNOUNCER]
Oh no! One tile is left!
But-But what a
mind-blowing power!
Fourteen tiles all at once!
I'm sure any other man would
struggle with two or three!
Incredible!
Phew!
[MR. SATAN yells]
[CROWD cheers]
[yelling continues]
[thinking]
His ignorance is painful.
Cell! You see these pieces of
busted tile on the ground?!
[MR. SATAN chuckles]
Well, that's...
what I'm gonna do...
to your face!
[CROWD cheers]
[chanting] Mr. Satan! Mr. Satan!
[chanting &amp; cheering continues]
[ANNOUNCER sobs]
There's no question!
Hercule Satan
is the undisputed
Martial Arts Champion
of the World!
[thinking] Yeah, I am that good!
I'm just glad I remembered
to set the VCR at home
to record this special moment!
[ANNOUNCER] Oh, it looks like
Cell is getting worried!
But, then again, who wouldn't
after seeing such
an amazing display of power?!
This is getting good!
It's payback time, folks!
Cell's made his ring and
now he's got to sleep in it!
Let's go!
It looks like our hero
is ready to fight!
It's hard to believe
that Mr. Satan's iron hands
are finally going to
have their revenge on Cell
for what he's done
to the people of Earth!
In mere moments
it will all be over
so don't you
dare blink an eye!
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER] It's all
up to you, Mr. Satan!
We're counting on you!
[MR. SATAN yells]
[ANNOUNCER] Nice move!
I can't believe it!
It looked like the champ
went straight for
his tried and true
patented "Dynamite Kick!"
[MR. SATAN growls]
[MR. SATAN yells]
[ANNOUNCER] Mr. Satan
is absolutely amazing!
The man never rests!
He just keeps on attacking!
Look at his speed!
His agility!
It's a veritable
ballet of punches!
He's too fast for Cell
to even fight back!
This is amazing!
[MR. SATAN laughs]
Now for my finish!
[MR. SATAN screams]
Uhhh...
[KRILLIN chuckles]
To be honest, Gohan,
I was cheering for Cell
to win that little scrap.
[MR. SATAN groans]
[PICCOLO] Hmph. Look,
he survived...
I guess Cell didn't want
to waste any energy
on that weakling.
He... He landed
outside the ring...
That means... our hero...
has lost the battle...
So... let's get the
tournament underway.
Who will be first? Will it
be Goku to start things off?
Let's do it!
[NARRATOR] After all the talk,
all the training,
all the idle threats, the
hour has finally arrived.
It's Goku versus Cell next time.