[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
Frieza kept dishing out blows
against our hero Goku
and Goku got all choked
up when Frieza revealed
he'd only been using 1%
of his actual strength.
In other words, Frieza's still
got a few tricks up his sleeve.
[FRIEZA] You should strike.
Why not, my back's turned.
What's wrong?
Don't tell me the
great Super Saiyan
is throwing in
the towel already.
What a disappointment.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
back at King Kai's place,
Tien said not to sweat it.
Because Goku had a
surprise of his own:
The awesome Kaio-Ken Attack!
[NARRATOR] Unfortunately,
only King Kai knew
the disastrous truth...
Goku had been using
the Kaio-Ken all along!
And Frieza was still batting him
away like a pesky, little fly...
[KING KAI] And even if he
was 100 times stronger,
he would still be no
match for Frieza...
[NARRATOR] Can anything
stop the evil Frieza?
Find out today!
[GOKU growls]
Huh?!
[GOKU grunts]
[PICCOLO growls]
[GINYU chuckles]
--[BULMA] Ribbit! Ribbit!
--[GINYU laughs]
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU yells]
[GINYU laughs]
Huh...?
[GINYU laughing maniacally]
[GINYU] Just look
at those moves!
That kid's toast
against Frieza!
Oh, I'm going to enjoy this!
Huh?!
[high-pitched GINYU gasping]
[PICCOLO] Hey, who are you?
[high-pitched GINYU]
Oh, you mean me?
[BULMA] Ribbit! Ribbit!
[BULMA croaking]
[GOHAN gasps]
Uh...?
Change... now!
[GINYU chuckles]
So... this frog...
this frog must...
...must... be Bulma!
[BULMA croaking angrily]
[GINYU] It's payback time!
[GINYU yells]
--[GINYU shouting]
--[KRILLIN] Ow! H-Hey! C'mon!
--[shouting continues]
--Cut it out!
[KRILLIN grunting]
[GINYU] Aw, th-there's no way
I'm... going to beat 'em
with this body!
[GINYU stammers]
Now I got it!
I pick you!
Huh?!
Change... now!
Piccolo! Look out!
But... I...
I-I can't move!
[GINYU chuckles]
[BULMA screams]
Then it's up to me!
[PICCOLO screams]
[growling]
Are... you okay, Piccolo?
[PICCOLO] What... What
just happened, Gohan?
[GOHAN laughs]
[BULMA gasps]
[BULMA] My... hands...
And both of my feet...
And my body...
Ouch!
I'm not a frog!
[BULMA giggles]
Ohh! Hurrah! Hurrah! Hurrah!
I'm back to normal!
[BULMA laughs]
I'm really happy for
you Bulma, but this place,
it's not safe for a girl.
Especially with all the fighting
that's going on around--
[BULMA &amp; KRILLIN scream]
Huh?!
[GOHAN] Dad!
[GOKU screams]
[FRIEZA giggles]
[FRIEZA growls]
[GOKU grunts]
[ALL grunting]
[BULMA screams]
Bulma!
[BULMA] Help me,
pleeeeeaaaase!
[GINYU] Ribbit ribbit ribbit
rib-rib-rib-rib-rib-rib!
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU shouts]
[blows landing]
Oh, please... Is that
the best you can do?
Where's the sport if
you don't fight back?
[GOKU grunts]
[FRIEZA giggles]
Huh...?
[GOKU screams]
[GOKU] Huh...?
[GOKU gasps]
Wha... What an attack!
[FRIEZA] And I'm
just warming up.
I told you I could
destroy this planet
in the same way I
destroyed Planet Vegeta.
And please don't think me vain,
but are you impressed
by my handiwork?
No...
What if I can't...
...can't beat him...?
Wha...
What did Frieza just do?
He... He...
He split the planet
into two halves...
But what I can't figure
out is how come Goku
isn't even fighting
back against him?
Something isn't right here and
we've gotta find out what.
[PICCOLO] Goku's just
realized the truth.
Regardless of how powerful
Goku thinks that he is,
Frieza is a hundred
times stronger
and Goku can't
defeat him!
I can do this
one of two ways.
Your end could be fast
or painfully slow.
Well, if you're not
going to answer,
maybe I'll make the
decision for you.
What's happening
down there, Tien?
It's not looking good.
From what I can make out,
Goku tried using his Kaio-Ken
but it wasn't enough
to overpower Frieza.
Isn't that right King Kai?
[KING KAI] Precisely!
And it seems Frieza hasn't even
shown half his strength yet...
No! It can't be!
Yes... I'm afraid it's
like I predicted...
Goku won't... win
against Frieza...
[KING KAI sobs]
[KING KAI] Goku can never win!
[FRIEZA] My dear friend,
how can I make this even
more painful for you?
I could crush
your hands,
rip off both
of your ears,
or maybe I'll just smash in
your tiny little cranium.
[FRIEZA laughs]
You might be stronger,
a hundred times stronger
than me Frieza, and
you may have me down,
but I'm not about
to give up now!
[GOKU growls]
And, I will do whatever it
takes, even if it destroys me,
to finish you off
once and for all!
To give you what you deserve!
Your speeches
put me to sleep.
But, everyone has
to have last words...
[FRIEZA laughs]
[FRIEZA] Before they're shredded
into a million, little pieces...
[blows land,
GOKU grunting]
[FRIEZA] Oh, what's wrong?
Poor baby got a boo-boo?
Well, I'll make it better.
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU groans]
After all those
things you said,
I thought you hated me.
[GOKU] Huh...?
Well, I've really enjoyed
prepping you for death.
[FRIEZA giggles]
[FRIEZA laughs]
Oh, and don't forget to
scrub behind your ears.
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[GOKU] Krillin!
[CHICHI] Goku!
[ROSHI] Gokuuuu!
[CHICHI] Gokuuu!
[OOLONG] Goku!
[GOKU] ChiChi!
Master Roshi!
Oolong...
Where are you?!
[GOKU] Master Roshi...!
[CHICHI screams]
[GOKU] ChiChi!
[CHICHI] Goku...
[CHICHI giggles]
[GOHAN] Daaaadddy!
[GOKU] Gohan?!
--[GOHAN] Where are you?
--[GOKU] Gohan!
[GOHAN] Where are you...?
[FRIEZA cackles]
[ROSHI laughs]
[OOLONG laughs]
[PUAR giggles]
[BULMA laughs]
[YAMCHA laughs]
[TIEN chuckles]
[CHIAOTZU laughs]
[KRILLIN laughs]
[DR. BRIEF laughs]
[MRS. BRIEF laughs]
[OX-KING laughs]
[LAUNCH laughs]
[KORIN laughs]
[MR. POPO laughs]
[KAMI laughs]
[PICCOLO laughs]
[CHICHI laughs]
[GOHAN laughs]
[FRIEZA gasps]
[PICCOLO whimpers]
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU snarls]
It's my Dad!
You're right,
it's Goku!
[GOKU] The future of Gohan...
...of ChiChi...
Not to mention the future
of the entire Universe...
It all depends on me!
[GOKU yells]
And I don't care if you're
a million times stronger
than me, mark my words, I'm
not going to let them down!
So get ready, Frieza,
'cause this time,
you're going down!
[GOKU yells]
[growling]
[FRIEZA growls]
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU] Hyaah!
[GOKU] Ka-Me-Ha-
Me-Haaaaaaaa!
[FRIEZA gasps]
[FRIEZA growls]
[GOKU growls]
[FRIEZA grunts]
[FRIEZA yells]
[FRIEZA] Why, you little...
You're mine, Frieza!
[NARRATOR] Was that
Goku's final attack?
And if so, what will
happen to him now?
Not to mention the
rest of our heroes?
Find out on the next
exciting episode of...
Dragon Ball Z!