[NARRATOR] Previously
on Dragon Ball Z...
Majin Buu made
a terrifying escape
from the
Hyperbolic Time Chamber,
and set his sights
on the unprotected
friends atop the Lookout.
[SUPER BUU] No more talk.
I've heard too much of that.
Now, let's just eat.
[NARRATOR]
With the same horrific method
he used to wipe out
the people of planet Earth,
Buu transformed the remaining
crew into chocolate,
and devoured them.
[SUPER BUU yells]
[NARRATOR]
Meanwhile,
trapped inside the
Hyperbolic Time Chamber,
Gotenks ascended
to Super Saiyan 3.
And using his newfound powers,
he forged his own amazing
escape back to the Lookout.
Buu, you'll pay for each one!
[NARRATOR] And it's there
that the battle raged on!
Piccolo could
only watch in shock
as the hallowed Lookout
was smashed into pieces.
[GOTENKS] Hold on to
your socks, Majin Buu!
[NARRATOR]
And Gotenks,
using the incredible
powers of Super Saiyan 3,
was able to subdue the monster
with another
peculiar technique.
[NARRATOR] But a giant
blast of energy now shows
that the true struggle
is only beginning.
Can the two best fighters
left on Earth prevail?
[GOTENKS yells]
[PICCOLO yells]
[GOTENKS] Wow, check
that out. Some light show!
Don't drop your guard
just yet, Gotenks.
There's going to be
more where that came from.
Arrogant jerk.
I'll give you
something to smile about!
Try this.
[yells, grunts]
[PICCOLO]
Slow down, Gotenks!
You'll destroy
the entire planet!
Make up your mind.
Do you want me to get
rid of this guy or not?
[PICCOLO] Of course,
but not at the expense
of the planet
you're trying to save!
The Dragon Balls
are scattered all over.
Destroy even one of them
and we can wish nothing back.
Oh, I forgot.
[GOTENKS] You know,
I don't wanna
toot my own horn or anything,
but look at
the size of that hole!
If he can still walk after that,
I'll be really surprised.
[GOTENKS chuckles]
Huh? Oh, no!
Huh...?
[SUPER BUU growls]
The guy's barely even bruised.
Man, this is getting old!
[SUPER BUU grunting]
[PICCOLO]
No, Gotenks, look at him.
You did hurt him, but it's not
his body that's suffering.
You've damaged his ego.
As a fighter,
you're his equal.
He's never fought anyone
as strong as himself.
[PICCOLO] This creature has
never faced a true challenge,
and I suspect he doesn't
know how to handle it.
[laughing]
You mean Majin Buu
is a little scaredy-cat!
But how can you blame him?
He's up against the
best fighter in the world,
don't you think?
Give me five more minutes
with him and he's toast!
Do you even have five minutes?
Your fusion will not
last forever.
Then he'll attack
with unrelenting force!
I really doubt that!
He's too scared!
[laughs]
--[SUPER BUU grunts]
--[GOTENKS laughing]
[PICCOLO]
Ah! Watch out!
That boy should
learn some modesty.
Fine then.
You wanna fight dirty?!
Look at that kid!
One tough fighter!
He's so resilient.
Finally, a warrior who
can truly fight with Buu.
[thinking] This seems like
it's taking forever.
Guess I just have to
trust that this Old Kai
knows what he's doing.
[OLD KAI laughing]
[GOHAN thinking]
I can't believe this.
[grunts]
[SUPER BUU groans]
[GOTENKS] Now for
the clean-up crew!
[laughs]
[GOTENKS groaning]
--[SUPER BUU chuckles]
--[GOTENKS groaning]
I'm hungry.
Gotenks!
[GOTENKS yells]
[screams]
[yells]
--[GOTENKS] Ah!
--SUPER BUU yells]
Buu... you creep. You
shouldn't have done that!
Control your anger, Gotenks.
[yells]
[bellows]
[PICCOLO grunting]
[GOTENKS groaning]
That really hurt.
[chuckles]
Take this!
Eeeh!
[yells]
Look at him go!
Gohan may not
have to fight after all!
Huh?!
[SUPER BUU groans, gasps]
[GOTENKS chuckles]
Now that you're worn out,
let me tell you
what I'm gonna do.
First, I'm gonna
cut you into tiny cubes.
Then I'll blast
those cubes into ashes.
Sorry to have to tell you this,
but your time on
this planet is over.
[gasping]
Power--
This is bad.
Uh, help?
[gasping]
[chuckles]
[GOKU]
Oh, I was afraid of this.
The power was
too high to sustain.
He's gone from Super
Saiyan 3 back to normal.
[BOTH] Aah!
[GOHAN]
Huh?
--[SUPER BUU] Boy?
--[GOTENKS] Heh!
[GOTENKS chuckles nervously]
[chuckles]
[grunts]
[laughs]
Now, normal fighting!
My best trick yet.
[PICCOLO]
No, we were so close!
The fusion's
nearly over. Over!
Hey, you guys
better hurry up.
Gotenks' Fusion doesn't look
like it's gonna
hold up much longer!
I don't know
how much we have left.
Ah, this is taking too long.
Oh, it's fine, you can go.
It should've been
finished a while ago.
[gasps]
[ALL]
A while ago?
Exactly, how long ago
was my training complete?
Eh... maybe five
or ten minutes.
I've been sitting around for
ten minutes for no reason?!
People are fighting
and dying right now,
we're doing nothing?!
Stay focused.
Now take that anger
swelling inside you
and use it to your advantage.
Eeh!
[ALL gasp]
Okay, I will.
But we've got to hurry!
[whimpers]
[GOTENKS]
Hhheeeh!
[thinking] I guess when
things get this desperate,
anything will do.
Here goes nothing!
Hmmm?
A Super Ghost
Kamikaze Attack!
[SUPERGHOSTS laughing]
[chuckles]
Just when you
thought you were safe,
the superghosts
come back even stronger!
Now! Superghosts!
Get over there
and turn that guy inside out!
[SUPERGHOSTS]
Huh?
[GOTENKS]
Uh...
[SUPERGHOSTS chattering]
Stop flapping your lips!
Get over there and attack!
[ALL holler, chuckle]
[ALL chuckle]
[SUPERGHOSTS yelling]
All right, it's time to run.
[GOTENKS groans]
[gasps nervously]
[exhales]
[GOHAN] Now that
my training is over,
how do I make sure
what you did
comes through in my fighting?
Well, you just do
that Super Saiyan thing
you always do
and stop worrying.
It'll happen.
Just make sure you let it.
All I have to do is become
a Super Saiyan and believe.
Try believing someplace else!
[GOHAN yelling]
[bellows]
[yells]
[GOHAN bellows]
Take a look at that.
[panting]
I can't believe he couldn't have
waited for me to move first.
This is awesome.
Hey Dad, are you
checking this out?
[GOKU] I sure am!
That's incredible, Gohan!
I'm so proud of you!
Perfect, Gohan has ascended
past his previous limitations.
But look at him,
he's... normal.
Incredible! He's stronger than
he ever was as a Super Saiyan,
but he looks like
he hasn't changed a bit.
I didn't know sitting
still for a long time
could do that for you.
Hm, I'm the one who
works hard and trains the boy,
and no one even
bothers to help me up.
We should leave
here immediately.
Gotenks can only stall Majin Buu
for a short period of time,
so we have to get to Earth
quickly for this to work!
Not us. Gohan will make his
journey to Earth alone.
Huh?
What about my obligations?
I am completely responsible
for that planet's fate!
Your going with him
will not help his chances
of defeating Majin Buu, master.
Your presence would
only present a danger
and impede his concentration.
I will take him back
and then return here
to wait for the good news.
So what's the plan?
Time to go. And you will
be traveling without me.
Kibito's right.
Good luck, Gohan.
I wish there was a way
I could go with you.
But I belong here now.
Make your father proud, son.
I have faith that
you can beat this guy.
Thanks, Dad.
This is the last time
I'll get to see you,
until you make your
journey over to this world.
[gasps]
You ready? Show him
what a Saiyan's made of!
Yeah!
Okay, go be a hero.
I'm gonna do my best, Dad!
[OLD KAI] He left
without saying a word.
Not a goodbye,
not a thank you,
after all the work
I did for him.
That's kids these days.
No respect!
Now, you're on your own.
The lone Saiyan.
[GOHAN]
Hey, Kibito?
Yes?
I need your help.
I wanna change clothes
but I don't have
exactly what I want.
My father is the
greatest fighter ever.
And I wanna fight in
the same clothing as him.
Of course.
You're quite respectful.
Now, explain to me exactly
what the outfit looked like.
What color was it?
Uh, how 'bout the one
he was just wearing.
That's the one.
Thanks, Kibito.
Anything for a savior.
We anticipate great things
to come from you, Gohan.
Please don't leave us,
and the world, disappointed.
No way. I'm not gonna start
disappointing people now.
All right, this is it.
Aah-uh!
[yells]
Let's not be too hasty!
[BOTH]
You're dead! Huh?
Hey, wait! You're there!
The Fusion must be over!
[NARRATOR] It looks
like Gotenks' powerful
fusion technique has come
to an untimely end.
[SUPER BUU chuckles]
[NARRATOR]
Now separated,
Goten and Trunks are no match
for the fury of Majin Buu!
[NARRATOR]
Their only hope,
and the only hope
for all of planet Earth,
lies in the newfound
abilities of Gohan.
After raising his powers
to unheard-of levels,
he returns to his home
planet as its hero once again.
But will he arrive in time
to save Goten and Trunks
from the impending
wrath of Majin Buu?
Find out, when
Dragon Ball Z continues.