Wait!
[NARRATOR] Last time,
on Dragon Ball Z!
Gohan's transformation
brought the battle with Vegeta
to its crushing
conclusion!
With his body and his
pride seriously wounded,
the evil Saiyan had no
choice but to retreat.
And Krillin had little
choice but to watch him go!
When, I come back
to this planet...
you're all
going to suffer,
and when you
beg me for mercy...
I'll stare into your eyes as
I crush the life out of you.
[NARRATOR] Krillin proved
himself the bigger man
by showing
Vegeta mercy.
But will this decision
come back to haunt him?
There's only one
way to find out...
Stay tuned for more
Dragon Ball Z!
[thinking] Go... Just go!
Don't come back...
[KRILLIN]
Gohan...
Hey there,
little guy...
Come on... It's
gonna be all right.
[GOKU] Krillin... Bring him
over here. Let me see him.
How're you, Yajirobe?
Oh, I'm fine...
Don't bother to give
me a hand or anything.
[GOKU] How...
How is he?
Oh, he's a
little banged up,
but mostly I think
he's just exhausted.
Transforming into
a giant ape
isn't exactly as easy
as it looks, you know.
[BOTH] Huh?
[engine roaring in the distance]
Great. Now what?
[ROSHI] Hey! Hello down
there! Krillin! Goku!
[ROSHI laughing]
[KRILLIN laughing]
[CHICHI] Gohan!
ChiChi?
[CHICHI] What are
you waiting for?!
My baby needs me!
Open that door!
[CHICHI] Gohan!
[CHICHI]
I'm coming, son!
[CHICHI] Mommy's here!
[KRILLIN]
Wait, Chichi!
[CHICHI] I was so
worried... It's okay...
I'm here now! I won't let
anything happen to you...
Oh, Gohan...
Please, say something...
He'll be all
right, ChiChi...
But, did you see
Goku over there?
I don't want to scare you,
but he's in pretty bad shape.
If you're going to worry
about anyone, well...
My poor little boy... What
did those bad men do to you?
I promise, I'm never letting
you out of my sight again!
Oh, Gohan...
[thinking] Sheesh! It's not like
he's her husband or anything.
[BULMA]
Goku?
Hey, boy...
Oh, no...
[BULMA] How are you?
Can you move at all?
[ROSHI] Easy now, Bulma...
Sorry if I can't
get up to say hello...
That's all right...
Rest now...
You've done enough
for one day.
Oh, Master Korin...
[KRILLIN] Uh, I'm afraid I've
got some bad news, guys...
Bulma, you know, there's
no easy way to say this...
But, Yamcha,
well, he...
He didn't make it.
Yes, I know... He fought
bravely, didn't he?
Oh! So then, uh, I guess you
know about Piccolo and Kami...
They're gone, too,
and that means,
so are the
Dragon Balls.
We won't be able to
wish anyone back...
[BULMA] Shut up!
I said I already know!
[BULMA sobbing]
I-I'm really sorry...
Yes, me too...
It's too bad. If only Piccolo
and Kami had survived...
Hey, I'm still here!
[BULMA] Yeah?! Well, I hope
you're proud of yourself!
You were hiding
the whole time!
Sneaking around like a coward
while everyone was dying!
Hey! That's
not true!
[BULMA] You're useless! Where
were you when they needed you?!
You should have died!
Not Yamcha! You!
[BULMA wailing]
You should be
thanking me!
I'm the one who cut off that
Saiyan creep's tail, y'know!
Jeez, you stick your
neck out for people...
And this is
what you get!
Now, now.
This is no time
to start fighting
amongst ourselves.
We need to get Goku
to the hospital...
I'm all out of
Senzu beans.
Hmmph.
[ROSHI] Okay, up we
go... Gently...
[BULMA crying]
[engines roaring to life]
[BULMA sobbing]
Where are the
others at, Krillin?
We need to go
pick them up, too...
That way... We were
fighting just over there...
Huh?
[BULMA sobbing]
[KRILLIN] Listen, um, Bulma?
I've been thinking...
And I don't know.
It's probably
impossible, but...
But still... as long
as there's a chance,
I gotta say
something...
Huh?
I can't get it
out of my head.
It's--It's
something that...
Well, it's something that
the Saiyans told us...
There might still be a
way to bring Yamcha back!
[ALL gasping]
What? What do
you mean?
Are you sure?
I-I don't know. It's
a shot in a million...
That's okay,
Krillin...
One chance in a million is
better than no chance at all.
Don't be afraid...
Tell us your idea...
Well, you see, uh... Hey,
hold on. This is the spot.
Yamcha and the others
are down there...
We'll talk later, okay?
[ROSHI] Mm-hmm...
Krillin...
Where's Chiaotzu?
I thought we'd find
him here, too...
[KRILLIN] No.
You won't find him.
Chiaotzu blew himself up.
He was trying to save us.
[KORIN] What a tragedy. Such
a shameful, senseless loss.
It's never easy, seeing
such brave young men
cut down in their
prime of their lives.
I know... I wish there was
something I could have done.
I should have
been with them!
[BULMA] Here...
You better let
me fly...
Really,
I'm okay now.
Oh... Are you?
[thinking]
Oh, Yamcha...
[BULMA] Would you mind closing
your eyes for a second?
[YAMCHA] Is she
really gonna kiss me?
[BULMA] You are so dead!
[YAMCHA yelling]
[YAMCHA] I know I let
you down. I'm sorry.
[BULMA] Don't say that.
You didn't let anyone down.
You did your best.
Everybody knows that!
[BULMA whimpering]
[YAMCHA] I'm really
anxious to show these guys
what we're all about
down here on this planet!
[YAMCHA screaming]
No... I failed!
[PICCOLO screaming]
Oh, Gohan! Good!
You're awake!
Uh... Uwaah!
It's okay...
You're safe now.
I've got you.
Uh? Mom? Is that really you?
[CHICHI wailing]
That's right! Mommy's here!
My sweet, little boy!
I never thought
I'd see you again!
Don't worry about a thing,
son... It's all over now.
Yeah. We did it, Gohan.
[GOHAN] We did? So,
what happened to Vegeta?
Well, I guess you could
say he... he got away.
But, listen!
The important thing is,
we ran that creep back
to wherever it is
he came from!
That's all that
matters, right?
What about Dad?
[GOKU] I'm okay, Gohan...
I'm right here...
You did great
today, son.
We really showed
him, didn't we?
[GOHAN and GOKU chuckling]
[YAJIROBE] Hey, ChiChi...
What the heck's goin' on here?
Goku just came back from
the dead and saved the world,
and you've hardly
even looked at him!
He's your husband!
Aren't you at least
gonna say hello?
What? Say hello?
Oh no...
I don't have a single thing
to say to that man right now.
It's his fault my baby
almost got killed!
Mom! But the Saiyans were
gonna destroy the Earth!
They can blow up the
universe for all I care!
That's no excuse for putting
my little boy's life at risk!
[YAJIROBE] Man, Goku...
Your wife is crazy!
Hey, Krillin... What were
you going to tell us?
About the Saiyans?
Oh, yeah, okay...
Eh?
The way I understand
it... Well...
The Saiyans found out
about the Dragon Balls,
and they wanted to use
them to make a wish.
That's why they
came to Earth.
They were ready to
kill all of us...
Except they wanted
Piccolo alive.
They were convinced
he was the only one
that could lead them
to the Dragon Balls.
What, really?
Yeah... And the whole time,
they kept calling him this..
This really
weird name...
They called
him a Namek.
[ALL gasping]
I think Namek is
where they're from...
I mean, Piccolo and Kami,
they're aliens!
Well, I always said
they were funny lookin'.
Then when Goku was coming,
they said something else...
Nappa! Quickly!
Kill them all!
[NAPPA] But, what about
the Dragon Balls?
[VEGETA] We don't need
those fools to find them!
It's clear
to me now!
A Namekian is all we need
to make the Dragon Balls,
and Planet Namek is
loaded with them!
And you believed
them? You dope.
[GOHAN] No, you're
right, Krillin!
I mean, if Kami made the Dragon
Balls, and he's a Namek,
why couldn't other Nameks
do the same thing?
Exactly, and maybe
they already have...
Vegeta said he'd heard legends
about Dragon Balls on Namek...
He never
believed them.
But what if they're
really true?
Then, that's it!
If you can somehow
get to Namek,
you can use their Dragon Balls
to wish your friends back!
And we can wish
Piccolo back first!
Now, Gohan, you shouldn't
get too excited...
That's a great idea!
And if Piccolo comes
back, then so will Kami!
And that means we'll have
all the Dragon Balls
here on Earth
back again, too!
Well, it's definitely
worth a shot!
Besides, what have we got
to lose? Let's go to Namek!
[KRILLIN]
All in favor, say "Aye"!
[ALL] Aye!
[ALL laughing]
[BULMA] Just stop it,
you guys! It's pointless...
I wish it was really
as simple as that,
but it just isn't!
It won't work.
[KRILLIN] What? What do you
mean? What's the problem?
Krillin, think about it...
For starters, do any of you
have even the slightest clue
where Planet Namek is?
[GOKU] Hey, wait...
I have an idea...
King Kai, are you there?
I hope you're
listening...
We could really use
your help right now.
[KING KAI]
Yes, Goku. I'm here.
So, you're looking
for the Planet Namek?
Well, of course I
know where that is!
Um, say you guys... Is anyone
else hearing voices?
Or is my old age finally
catching up with me?
Thanks, King Kai...
I knew I could count on you.
Go ahead,
we're listening.
Sure, but as long as I have
the podium for a minute...
Let me congratulate you all
on a battle well fought.
I was worried
there for a while.
It looked like that Saiyan
really had you guys
on the ropes!
But you pulled through!
[GOKU] I hate to say it,
but he even had me
a little scared.
I mean, even a Kaio
Ken times four attack
wasn't enough
to stop him!
Yes, and those were my
best techniques, too.
I hope you can
think of something
before you have to
face him again...
I'm sorry, but I'm
all out of tricks.
Yeah, I was afraid
you'd say that...
Maybe I shouldn't
have let him go...
Only time
will tell...
What? What are they
talking about?
You mean you actually
let that Saiyan go?
Oh, well, I'll tell you
the whole story later...
[KING KAI] Hmm...
Now where is it...
I'm sure I have
the coordinates
for Planet Namek in
here somewhere...
'Kay... There's Planet
Nambo, Namcheck, Namcheno...
Planet Namee...
Ah yes! Here it is!
The co-ordinates are SW-66.
Or maybe SU-83...
No, no!
9-0-4-5 XY, definitely!
What? Is he serious?
9-0-4-5 XY? But that's...
Um, what's
the matter?
We know where it is
now... That's good!
Hey! Master Roshi! I need
to check something out...
Take the wheel
for a minute!
You could say please...
9-0-4-5 XY... Hmm...
[KING KAI] I remember...
Planet Namek was once a
very beautiful place.
It was very much
like the Earth...
Lush and green, with
an abundance of life.
But that was
long ago...
Before a catastrophic event
caused the climate to change.
The effects on the
planet were devastating.
It has recovered over
time, little by little.
But I'm not sure there
were any survivors...
But... Oh no.
See? Told ya'...
It's just a pipe dream.
There's no
Dragon Balls.
Can it!
Let's not give
up hope yet...
There's really only one way
we can know for sure...
I'll have to feel it out...
Just give me a moment...
Oh! There it is!
Say... You know... If what
King Kai says is true,
this might explain how it
is that Kami ever came
to live upon
the Earth...
Yes... It must've
been so long ago
that Kami
couldn't remember.
But perhaps his
people sent him here
after the climate
on Namek changed,
so that at least one of
their race would survive!
I don't get it...
If these Namekians really
had a set of Dragon Balls
like you guys say...
Don't you think they
woulda' used 'em?
I mean, they coulda'
just wished their planet
back to normal.
Problem solved.
[ROSHI] No...
Maybe they couldn't.
The Dragon is not
all-powerful...
We found out when we
tried to destroy
the Saiyans
with a wish,
Shenron told us it
wasn't possible.
You see, the Dragon
Balls are tied
to the one
who created them.
And, they cannot
grant a wish
that exceeds their
maker's power.
Oh, that's a
load'a hooey...
You're makin'
it up...
You just don't wanna admit
that you're wrong. Yeah...
Urgh!
Hey! I thought I told
you to can it, stupid!
[KING KAI]
Good news, everyone!
I found the Namekians!
I can sense about a hundred
of them still on the planet,
alive and well!
You call that good news?
You're talkin' about a
hundred Piccolos here!
Even if the Dragon
Balls did exist,
you'd have to fight all
those guys to get 'em!
[KING KAI] No, no, no.
It's not like that at all!
The Namekians are basically
peaceful by nature, like Kami!
Piccolo was the
exception to the rule.
[KING KAI]
You have to remember,
Piccolo was born
there on Earth.
And during his
formative years,
he witnessed firsthand all of
the horrors of that world...
War, tyranny,
murder...
These experiences
took their toll...
Piccolo was
not born evil.
Rather, it was the evil
of men that corrupted
his otherwise peaceful
Namekian heart.
I guess that
makes sense..
People can be pretty
disgusting sometimes...
You said it...
Well, I can't think
of a better way
to show Piccolo
the good in people
than by using the Dragon
Balls to wish him back!
[BULMA]
Not so fast, guys...
You just don't
get it, do you?
Nothing's changed. So what if
we know where Planet Namek is.
How do we get there?
[KRILLIN] Is this a
trick question?
I mean, we just take a
spaceship! Easy as that!
Oh, easy as that? Well,
I've got news for you!
I just calculated how long it
would take us to make the trip
using the best Capsule
Corp spaceship available!
And do you wanna take a wild
guess what I came up with?
What's that? No idea?
Then allow me to show you.
Here... See?
The numbers don't lie.
Your little cruise to Namek
is gonna take 4339 years!
That's one way!
[GOHAN] Wow. That's long.
What do you think,
King Kai?
Any ideas on how
we can get there?
No, I'm afraid I'm
stumped on that one...
Sheesh... They expect
me to know everything?
[KRILLIN laughing]
Okay. So you got me there,
Bulma. It's impossible...
But, hypothetically
speaking,
what would happen if we
used a Saiyan spaceship?
Hm?!
There's an idea. But where
are we gonna get one of those?
I thought the
Saiyans left.
[KRILLIN]
Well, Vegeta left.
And it looked like his ship was
only big enough for one person.
There's absolutely no
way that Nappa guy
could've squeezed
in there with him.
He had to've had
a ship of his own!
Hey! That's right!
And what about my brother
Raditz? He had a ship, too!
But I think it's prob'ly broken
after what Gohan did to it...
Okay! So there's one
spaceship left out there!
Now, all we have to do is
figure out where it is,
and we're
in business!
Well, then... I bet I know
just where to start looking.
It's most likely
not too far
from where the
Saiyans first landed,
somewhere in
East City!
[KRILLIN laughing]
Hey, I think I have
something that might help.
Check it out!
Vegeta dropped it...
I saw him punch a couple a'
buttons... And then boom!
His spaceship
came right to him!
I think it's a remote
control or something...
[BULMA]
Lemme see that!
Hmm...
[BULMA giggling]
Pack your bags!
We're going to Namek!
[ALL laughing]
[BULMA] We'll have Yamcha and
everyone back in no time!
[ALL laughing]
[ALL] Namek! Here we come!
[laughing continues]
[NARRATOR] A day of sorrow has
become a bright day of hope,
as our heroes prepare to embark
on a bold, new adventure!
It's Planet
Namek or bust!
Next time on
Dragon Ball Z!