[TRUNKS] Vegeta,
Krillin, Yamcha...
[NARRATOR] Last
time on Dragon Ball Z,
[TRUNKS] They're all going
to lose their lives!
Huh?!
[NARRATOR]
Trunks' ominous warning
left Goku and his friends to
ponder a mind-bending question.
What could they do to alter
the course of a future
that had already been written?
[TIEN] Man, I'm going
to train, you guys!
[NARRATOR] And soon after Trunks
departed to face the dangers
that awaited him in his
own time, train they did!
Because with only three short
years to prepare themselves
for the arrival of
two deadly androids,
there wasn't a minute to spare!
Day in and day out,
Gohan, Goku, Piccolo,
and all of the others
worked harder than ever
to get their bodies into
the kind of shape needed
to take on these
powerful new enemies.
But in the blink of an eye,
three years came and went.
[CHICHI] How about a little
lunch before you go?
Mom, we don't have
time for that!
Thanks. Bye!
[NARRATOR] The day has finally
come for Goku and his friends
to put their
training to the test!
Can they put an end to the
androids and save the world
from the terrible fate
that Trunks predicted?
It's a date with destiny,
today on Dragon Ball Z!
[GOKU] Slow down, Gohan!
We'll get there
in plenty of time!
You'd better save your
energy for the fight!
[GOHAN] Oh...
Right, Dad!
For three years...
Three years, we've trained
just for this moment.
But was it enough?
Why don't you ask me
again this afternoon?
I think we'll know by then.
If only we'd had
more time...
I feel like there's so much more
I could have done to prepare.
I could've gotten faster!
I could've gotten stronger!
Don't say that.
You did as much as
you could, Piccolo.
We all did.
Ha-ha!
Hey, Dad! Look!
I can see Krillin!
[GOKU] Huh?
[GOHAN] Hey, Krillin!
Hey, bro!
Long time no see!
[GOHAN] Hey, Krillin!
[KRILLIN] Hey, Goku!
So buddy, think you're
about ready to tackle
a couple of androids today?
Well, I suppose
I'm as ready right now
as I'm ever going
to be, you guys.
I just wish things didn't
have to be this way...
[GOHAN]
Hey, look up ahead!
That must be the
island, right there!
[GOKU] Boy, there's a lot more
people here than I thought!
[KRILLIN] Yeah!
I didn't even know
this city existed!
It looks like we'll have
to divert the Androids
away from the city.
'Cause if we don't,
too many innocent people down
there are going to get hurt.
I agree.
Let's try not to get too far
ahead of ourselves you guys.
We have to find them first.
[GOKU] Then we'd
better start looking!
I told you, Tien! It's him!
Hey, Goku! Down here!
[YAMCHA]
Hey, over here!
[BULMA laughs]
[KRILLIN] Huh...?
[YAMCHA] You're late!
What took you guys so long?
Bulma!
It is Bulma!
Hey, guys!
Wow! You all have been
working out, haven't you?
[BABY coos]
Bulma!
What in the world do you
think you're doing out here?!
[BULMA] I've come to
watch you fight, silly!
Oh, don't worry.
I'll just stay for a while
and then I'll go home.
Heh... I hope you don't
think I'm nuts for asking,
but what's the deal
with the baby, Bulma?
Is he your son, Yamcha?!
I'll bet he is!
Hmph. He's not MY kid!
Huh?
Well if you think that's
a shock, just wait...
Wait until she tells you
who the father really is...
[GOKU laughs]
I'll bet it's Vegeta, isn't it?
Right, Trunks?
--Huh?!
--Uh?
Now, who told
you that, Goku?
I wanted to keep it a secret.
I was going to
surprise you guys!
[GOKU laughs]
Well, actually I just
thought I'd take a guess!
I mean, he kind of
looks like Vegeta...
[GOKU laughs]
[BULMA] You guessed
his name too?
[GOKU] Yeah! What are
the chances of that, huh?
Maybe I'm psychic!
Outrageous...
Who would've guessed?
Bulma and Vegeta?!
[YAMCHA groans]
Well, since we're
on the subject,
where is Vegeta?
I don't have a clue.
I really haven't seen
him around lately.
I know he was
training to come here,
but, what, with
the baby and all,
well I guess I must have
lost track of him...
He'll show.
He wouldn't miss a fight.
I left Chiaotzu
at Roshi's.
To be honest with you,
I didn't think the little guy
would stand much of
a chance out here.
Hm.
[GOHAN] Bulma?
What time is it?
Well, it's...
let's see...
According to my watch it's 9:30!
Bulma, you better get out
of here before it's too late!
Those Androids are going
to be here in half an hour!
[BULMA laughs]
Don't worry!
I just want to see what
these things look like
and then I'll go.
[TIEN] Well, it's
almost show time.
[TIEN sighs]
Only thirty minutes to go...
[DR. BRIEF] Hello!
Grandpa's home!
And I've got a new
toy for you, Trunks!
[DR. BRIEF] Now, where
did Bulma take him?
Huh?
I guess that
daughter of mine
must be showing him off
to the neighbors again.
I'll just sit here and wait.
Hm... Now then...
Let's take a look
at this thing.
I hope it works!
Hah, hah! To get the
cute little thing out,
all I've got to do is
press this button and...
[DR. BRIEF screams]
[GOHAN]
♪ Coochy-coochy-coochy-coo! ♪
♪ Goo-goo-goo-goo-goo! ♪
Bwaaah!
[BABY TRUNKS giggles]
[GOHAN laughs]
[GOHAN] Hey, Krillin, let's see
you try making the kid laugh!
[KRILLIN] Alright!
So...
You new in town or what?
[BABY TRUNKS laughs]
Yeah... I crack
myself up too, kid.
[ALL laugh]
[PICCOLO] Quiet, you guys!
[ALL] Huh...?
Someone's coming...
Hey... you...
think it's them?
I can't tell yet...
Yep. They're all right here,
just like Korin said.
[GOKU] Yajirobe!
[YAJIROBE grunts]
Hey, you came to help us
fight the androids!
[YAJIROBE] Hm?
Huh?!
[YAJIROBE] No way!
I... just brought
these Senzu Beans...
from Korin.
Ahh, thanks a lot!
And give my best to Korin.
[YAJIROBE]
Yeah, yeah, whatever!
I'm outta here.
Hey, are you sure you don't
want to stay and help us out?
If you guys want to stay here
and get yourselves killed,
that's your own business.
But I'm taking off
while I still can!
Don't you think
it's a bit strange?
[GOKU] Huh?
It's already
after 10 o'clock.
And there isn't a single
sign of those androids!
Yeah, I forgot
all about the time!
I can't believe that I
actually listened to that kid!
Androids!
That's a good one!
Don't be so literal,
you guys!
It's only 10:17...
I wouldn't jump
the gun just yet!
Excuse me, but I think
we would have sensed
their power levels by now?
Sorry to disappoint you, Bulma,
but those androids
just aren't coming!
[explosion]
[gasping]
Whoa!
What was that?!
[KRILLIN]
It's Yajirobe!
[PICCOLO growls]
You guys!
It's the androids!
Up there!
I see them!
[ALL gasp]
[TIEN]
They flew into the city!
But where'd they go?!
[KRILLIN] I don't know, Goku...
Did you see them?
I'm not sure.
One second they were
up in the sky and then...
Poof, they just vanished!
I didn't even sense
their power levels!
Well... they're both...
androids aren't they?
So maybe we can't!
[YAMCHA gasps]
That's crazy!
[YAMCHA] How are we supposed
to find these androids
if we can't even
sense where they are?!
[KRILLIN] Aww, man...
[PICCOLO] Well, if we can't
sense their power levels,
we'll just have to find them
the old fashioned way:
with our eyes!
Right! Let's
spread out, you guys.
Bulma!
Look after these!
[BULMA] Huh?
[GOKU] Now remember!
If you find the androids, don't
try to take them on by yourself!
Wait for the others!
Gohan, go check
on Yajirobe.
See if he's okay.
Right!
[PICCOLO growls]
Let's go!
[BULMA sighs]
[BABY TRUNKS coos]
[GOKU] Krillin!
Let's check down there!
[GOKU] Now then...
If I were an android,
where would I be?
[GOKU growls]
Man, I wish Trunks
would've at least
shown me a picture of them!
[SKYBOARD DUDE hums]
[SKYBOARD DUDE] Huh?
[SKYBOARD DUDE yells]
All right...
Let's see...
Aahh! Dude,
you were flying!
[PEOPLE gasp]
[KRILLIN] Nope!
No androids!
[SKYBOARD DUDE whimpers]
[KRILLIN] Hey, buddy,
you seen any strange looking
characters around here lately?
Yeah, maaan...
[KRILLIN] Huh?
You, flying dude!
[KRILLIN gasps]
[PICCOLO growls]
[WOMAN gasps]
Are you okay, Yajirobe?!
[YAJIROBE coughs]
Do I look "okay," kid?!
[YAMCHA] Huh...?
[YAMCHA growls]
[YAMCHA] This is nuts!
I don't even know what
I'm looking for here!
[MAN] Did you see that?!
I doubt if anyone
would've survived it!
[MAN] Hmm?
Man, that Sky Car blew up!
Wow, that was some awesome
explosion! You guys see that?
[MAN whimpers]
[MAN] What's up
with you two?
Hey, back up!
[MAN gasps]
--[MAN yells]
--[MAN B gasps]
[giggling]
[MAN B grunts]
[car horn honks]
Hey, get outta
the road!
Yeah, that means you,
you circus freak!
What, are you stupid
or something?!
Move it or lose it, pal!
I'm not kidding around now!
[MAN C squeals]
[MAN C] C'mon! D'oh!
[engine sputtering]
[MAN C] Start!
[MAN C gasps]
[MAN C whimpers]
[MAN C rasps]
[WOMAN B gasps]
[WOMAN B screams]
[YAMCHA] Huh?!
[YAMCHA gasps]
[WOMAN B screams]
I am detecting a human
with extraordinary power.
What do your sensors
indicate, 19?
[ANDROID 19] It is close.
Coming closer.
Perhaps the one we seek?
[ANDROID]
Perhaps.
This one far surpasses
the average human.
We will destroy it, yes, 20?
I think I just found them!
[YAMCHA gasps]
[YAMCHA] Where?!
Where are they hiding?!
[ATTENDANT whimpers]
[YAMCHA gasps]
[YAMCHA] Hey, you!
[ATTENDANT yelps]
--[YAMCHA growls]
--[MAN D] What the...?!
Hey, you two!
Did you see what
happened to these people?!
Who did this?!
[MAN E] There were two of them!
[MAN D]
They came out of nowhere.
They zapped everyone and
then just... disappeared!
They...
disappeared?!
[YAMCHA growls]
[YAMCHA] I must have
just missed them!
I better go back
and tell the others!
[ANDROID 19] This is not
the human we seek.
I will identify it.
[beeping]
Human is designated male,
warrior sub-class B,
identified as Yamcha.
Excellent.
He will provide us
with ample energy.
Wait a second!
What's the point of
telling the others?
I haven't found them yet.
Huh?
You two better
be careful!
There's a couple of
Androids on the loose
and they mean business!
No... No!
You can't...
We are they.
I found them!
[YAMCHA grunts]
[YAMCHA grunting]
[grunting continues]
[TRUCK DRIVER] Huh...?
[TRUCK DRIVER screams]
[screaming]
[GOKU] Huh?
[GOKU gasps]
[TIEN] Huh?
[PICCOLO] Oh no...
What was that?!
[CROWD murmuring]
[YAMCHA grunts]
[bones crunching]
[BULMA gasps]
[BULMA] Oh no...
[BULMA whimpers]
[BOTH gasp]
[NARRATOR] The Android's
reign of terror has just begun
and it looks like Yamcha
is their first victim.
But is there time to save him?
Find out on the next
exciting episode
of Dragon Ball Z!