[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball Z...
Vegeta made an explosive return
to the Tournament Arena...
The hatred in his
heart reawakened
by Babidi's magic,
the Saiyan prince
had become a servant
to the forces of evil.
[GOKU] Babidi! Transport us to
a place away from these people!
If you give me that,
then I will fight Vegeta!
[NARRATOR] Babidi willingly
granted Goku's request,
and zapped the Z Fighters
from the stadium floor.
Now, miles from civilization,
the two Super Saiyans are free
to fight without restraint,
which is just what the wizard
wants, for every blow
they land is a boost
for Majin Buu!
Unless Gohan and the
Supreme Kai act quickly,
Buu will soon have the
energy he needs to emerge
from his cocoon!
[GOHAN thinking] I've never
sensed anything like this.
So cold, and empty.
[BABIDI]
Welcome, friends!
I'm glad you could join us!
[GOHAN breathes heavily]
[SUPREME KAI breathes heavily]
[BABIDI cackles]
[SUPREME KAI]
Listen.
There is still time before Majin
Buu reaches his full power.
We have to strike.
Together, on my mark.
Hold nothing back, Gohan.
This creature must never
see the light of day.
The fate of your
world depends on it.
[GOHAN]
I know.
[GOHAN, SUPREME KAI grunt]
Wait, Kai.
[gasps]
Let's take this outside.
It seems a bit cramped
in here, doesn't it?
Yes, and when Buu wakes up,
I have a feeling he'll agree.
He's sure to be restless.
I hate to think what would
happen if we were trapped
with him in this
cozy little place.
Wizard...
You need not worry what
your monster will do to you.
Not when you still have
me to contend with.
[cackles] Squeak. Squeak. He's a
noisy little rat, isn't he?
Rraaah-mm... Papparapa!
[GOHAN]
Huh?
[gasps]
Now, Dabura...
You are feeling up to this?
I'd hate for you to wear
yourself out and quit
in the middle of the fight...
Rest assured.
These two will be easily
removed from your sight.
They're rubbish!
I'll clean them up easily.
[cackles]
[cackles] Good, you can dispose
of them any way you like.
Maybe you could even
turn them into stone!
Two more statues to
add to our collection.
No.
I have something far
more painful in mind.
[GOKU yells, groans]
[VEGETA, GOKU grunting]
So, you've still got
plenty of fight left.
Yeah.
Heh. Impressive. I didn't
think you'd last this long.
Really? I could say the
same about you, Vegeta.
You've learned a few new
tricks while I've been away.
[laughs, grunts]
[gasps]
[VEGETA, GOKU grunting]
[VEGETA yells]
[BABIDI] Did I mention how
glad I am to see you, Kai?
Now I can finally avenge
my father... can't I?
You remember, don't you?
The way you murdered my father?
I suppose he let his guard down.
I won't make that mistake.
I won't be done in
like my father was,
especially not by you. I learned
from his shortcomings.
I've made his
weaknesses my strengths!
For example, I've learned
to keep better company.
Father never did have a
knack for spotting talent.
[SUPREME KAI grunts]
[SUPREME KAI thinking] He's
right. He's completely on guard.
A direct attack would play
right into his hands.
There must be a way!
I have to get to Majin Buu!
We're running out of time!
[GOHAN thinking]
Come on, Gohan! Snap out of it!
You shouldn't be
afraid of these guys!
What's holding you back?
[GOKU]
Let go, son! Let go...
[GOHAN thinking]
Uh, Dad?
You've got all the power
you need to beat these guys,
if you can just
remember how to fight
with your feelings,
like you did against Cell.
Just remember all the
people you're fighting for
and how much you
care about them.
And then let that
be your weapon.
[GOHAN thinking] I'm trying,
Dad. I'm trying to remember!
But... But the
fight with Cell...
That-That was so long ago...
[YOUNG GOHAN]
Ka... me... ha... me...
Haaa!
[CELL cackles]
[GOHAN grunting]
[CELL yelping]
[groaning]
[CELL]
I'm perfect!
[GOHAN grunting]
[GOHAN thinking] I have to
do this! I can do this!
[GOHAN grunts]
[BABIDI whimpers]
Dabura...
[GOHAN grunting]
[GOHAN grunts]
[BABIDI gasps]
[yells]
Huh?
[gasps]
[BABIDI, DABURA]
Hm?
Could it be...?
But... So soon...
I don't believe it!
[gasps]
[SUPREME KAI gasps]
No, we're too late...
[gasping]
Master Babidi, what's happening?
[stammering] It's, he's...
He's full, he's full power...
[SUPREME KAI]
No!
Majin Buu is at full power!
[cackles]
His full power!
[gasps]
[BABIDI]
It's really happening!
Buu is coming back to life!
[cackles]
[DABURA chuckles]
I don't understand!
It's too soon!
Goku's damage energy alone--
it certainly couldn't
have been enough to...
[BABIDI cackles]
[GOHAN thinking]
Dad...
[gasps]
Huh?
That must be it!
Dad's been fighting at a
level beyond a Super Saiyan!
Dad and Vegeta both!
And when two powers
like that collide,
with as much energy
as they're putting out...
The damage must be enormous!
[gasps] No!
We did it, Dabura!
Yes, Master Babidi.
Buu!
How could I let
this happen?!
I've miscalculated at
every turn! I should have...
I should have foreseen this!
It's all my fault!
[GOKU grunts]
[VEGETA grunting]
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU]
Huh?
[VEGETA grunts]
[GOKU yelps]
What's the matter clown?!
[GOKU grunts]
--[VEGETA grunts]
--[GOKU groans]
Die!
[GOKU]
As I was saying, Vegeta.
You've learned a few new tricks
while I've been away.
But then, so have I.
[REPORTER A] Mister Satan,
on a more positive note,
your victory today...
You had some big
obstacles to overcome.
It must've been difficult.
How'd you do it?
Well, I haven't run
into an obstacle yet
that I couldn't smash down.
But you're right,
winning is never easy.
Good thing I've had
a lot of practice.
Thank you, sir.
But I was mostly referring to
your final opponent, Number 18.
Looked like she gave you
some trouble out there.
[MR. SATAN grumbles]
--[REPORTERS gasp]
--[REPORTER A] Hm?
[laughs] Maybe to the
eyes of an amateur...
I could've won that
fight in five seconds
if I'd wanted to,
but if I had...
...that wouldn't've been fair
to all the people who paid
good money to see
me in action today.
I make sure that my
fans get plenty of
bang for their buck!
So I intentionally
took my time.
[REPORTERS gasp]
Mister Satan!
Putting the fans first!
It's great to have such
a considerate champion!
"Considerate champion."
Really, guy, you flatter me.
But make sure you
write that down.
Mister Satan, could
you repeat the name
of that last technique you
used to beat Number 18?
[MR. SATAN] Uh, well...
Let's see, it was the
Satan Miracle Very
Special Strong... Uh...
Mighty Mega-Punch.
Oh, but... I thought I heard you
call it something different
out in the ring...
Ha, ha. Is that so?
[REPORTER D] Oh, you're right.
How silly. My mistake!
But back to what
happened after the match.
Do you know who those men were
that attacked the stadium?
I guess they were
a couple of posers
who wanted to challenge
me for my title.
But they should've known better.
I'm an old pro at
dealin' with flashy tricks
and light shows,
explosives and stuff.
Naturally, when they
saw I wasn't
backin' down, they got
scared and ran off.
[REPORTERS]
Ooh!
I wanna send out a message!
To all you would-be-challengers
of the world, Mister Satan says:
"Bring it on." Use all the
flashy tricks you want!
I still gonna send
you home with my fist!
--[CROWD cheers]
--You tell 'em, Mister Satan!
Those punks can't
touch you, champ!
[MR. SATAN laughs]
Yeah!
[gasps]
[MR. SATAN thinking] Why is she
still here? I told her I'd pay!
For 20,000,000 zeni,
she could at least stop
starin' at me like that!
[TRUNKS]
You feel that energy?
There's some real fighting
going on out there.
Not like at that
stupid tournament.
I know. Who do you think it is?
My dad? Or your dad maybe?
[TRUNKS]
It might even be both of them!
Feels like it's happening
in more than one place.
I wanna find my dad first,
then we can go watch your dad.
Doesn't matter. It'll all be
over before we get there.
We might as well turn
around and go home.
No! No! No!
I wanna see the Buu monster!
And the wizard!
[TRUNKS] All right! All right!
I wasn't being serious!
I'm just sayin' hurry up, or we
really will miss everything!
[GOTEN]
Oh, okay!
--[GOKU grunting]
--[VEGETA groaning]
[GOKU grunting]
[gasps]
[VEGETA]
Ha!
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU, VEGETA grunting]
[VEGETA]
Final Flash!
[gasps]
[VEGETA] You've become
quite the escape artist!
[GOKU] Maybe you just need
some better finishing moves.
[VEGETA]
I doubt that.
[yells]
[panting]
I'm amazed, Vegeta...
These last seven years
in Other World,
I've been through the most
intense training sessions.
But we're still
completely even...
I guess this whole time,
you've been pushing yourself
even harder than I have.
[VEGETA]
That may be true.
I've pushed myself to the edge
of my limits and beyond.
But you've been born
with a natural talent
far beyond my own.
No amount of training could
have closed the gap between us.
I realize that now.
It was made painfully
obvious to me today
as I watched your fight
with Babidi's monster.
[GOKU grunting]
[gasps]
[GOKU grunts, yells]
[VEGETA]
Imagine my shock.
To see the undeniable proof.
To discover that no
matter how hard I tried,
I would never be able
to catch you.
A warrior prince forever
living in the shadow
of a low-level clown!
So that's when I secretly
made up my mind.
You mean you-- You fool!
You deliberately let yourself
fall under Babidi's spell.
Yes. I saw the power
of Babidi's magic.
At the World Martial
Arts Tournament,
those two henchmen he sent...
--[SPOPOVITCH grunts]
--[VIDEL groans]
[VIDEL groans]
[VIDEL yells]
When did Spopovitch
get this strong?
It's like he's a
different person!
[VIDEL groaning]
The people who had
seen those fighters
in the previous tournament
couldn't understand
how they'd become so powerful.
But you and I know, don't we?
It was Babidi's magic.
And I knew that what his magic
had done for those fighters,
it could also do for me.
I knew that if I allowed myself
to fall under his control,
the difference in our
power would disappear.
I'm quite pleased
with the results...
...even if they do
come at a price.
I'd say the end more
than justifies the means.
Vegeta... I don't understand.
You've never allowed anyone to
help you before in your life--
Why start now? Why Babidi?
[VEGETA]
Because I wanted him to reawaken
the evil in my heart...
I wanted him to return me
to the way I was before!
I was the perfect warrior!
Cold and ruthless!
I lived by my strength alone!
Uninhibited by foolish emotion!
But slowly... over the years...
I became one of you,
my quest for greatness
gradually giving way to
this life of mediocrity.
I awoke one day to find
that I had settled down...
...formed a family...
I had even grown
quite fond of them.
Would you believe,
I almost started to think
the Earth was a
nice place to live.
Do you understand now, Kakarot?
That's why I needed Babidi!
To set me free! By releasing
the evil in my heart...
...he has freed my of
these petty attachments.
And I'd have to say
it feels pretty good.
Do you really believe
what you're saying?
[grunts, growls]
[GOKU grunts]
[DABURA] At last,
success Master Babidi.
[BABIDI] Oh yes!
Sweet, beautiful, success!
He's gonna come out!
Majin Buu's coming out!
[SUPREME KAI grunts]
[GOHAN grunts]
[gasps]
[NARRATOR]
After centuries of plotting,
Babidi's plans are finally
coming to fruition!
Majin Buu is going
to be set free!
And the Earth's best hope
for stopping the monster
has his hands full elsewhere.
Hurry, Goku!
Time is running out!
Human kind's darkest
hour is at hand!
[NARRATOR] Stay tuned
for scenes from the next
exciting episode
of Dragon Ball Z!