Right!
[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z,
Spopovitch and Yamu attacked,
armed with a mysterious device
that drained Gohan
of his energy.
[SPOPOVICH laughs]
Hey, that was
easier than we thought.
[NARRATOR] Shin, now revealed
to be the Supreme Kai himself,
flew from the arena in pursuit
of Gohan's assailants.
The Z-Fighters also
took to the skies,
where they learned
the true nature
of the danger they
rushed to face...
[SUPREME KAI] I'm glad
you decided to come.
And thank you.
Without all of your help I would
not be able to defeat them!
You need us...
to beat those two?
No, it's not Spopovitch and
Yamu that concern me...
It's the wizard
that controls them!
[NARRATOR]
Back on the stadium floor,
Kibito used his powers to
restore Gohan's energy...
Gohan may be back
in fighting shape,
but will he be ready to meet
a powerful new enemy?
Today on Dragon Ball Z!
We did it!
Once we give him
this pure energy,
Babidi should be very pleased...
[chuckles]
Our reward is sure
to be great.
Yeah.
[PTERRY PARENTS roar]
[BABY PTERRYS squeak]
[PTERRY FAMILY squawks]
[BABY PTERRYS screech]
[PTERRY MOM sighs]
[PTERRY DAD gasps]
[PTERRY MOM screeches]
[PTERRY PARENTS whimper]
[SUPREME KAI]
Hmm...
There...
That's it, drones,
lead the way.
So, it's obvious
you were able
to defeat
this wizard Bibidi
before he could unleash
Majin Buu on the Earth.
But you didn't
destroy Majin Buu.
You chose instead to leave him
here, lying dormant.
That's right...
We thought it best that way.
We believed that Bibidi
was the only one
who could free Majin Buu...
We were mistaken in that belief.
Bibidi has a son--
also a wizard.
And if he isn't stopped,
Majin Buu will live again.
So I guess Bibidi's son is
controlling the guys
from the tournament?
[SUPREME KAI]
Yes. His name is Babidi.
And as is often the case
in this universe,
the son is as evil
as the father.
[KRILLIN] Great.
Why does that not surprise me?
It's simple. All we have
to do is stop Babidi
from waking up Majin Buu, right?
Yes, that's right...
But I'm afraid that it won't be
as easy as you make it sound...
Babidi's abilities as a wizard
are not to be underestimated.
It may take all of us
to defeat him.
[GOKU]
Wow...
It sounds like this
guy's pretty strong...
Babidi's strength
lies in his magic.
Physically, he is
not very powerful...
Nor was his father.
But a wizard does
not need to be...
Instead, his magic enables
him to harness the evil
that exists in the hearts of
people like Yamu and Spopovitch,
and thereby control
their actions.
Imagine what would happen
if someone truly powerful
came under his spell...
[GOHAN]
If Yamu and Spopovich
didn't enter the
tournament to win,
then why were they even there?
I mean, what did they do to me?
Babidi intends to
resurrect Majin Buu,
but before he can do this,
he requires a tremendous
amount of pure energy.
So they came after me?
Babidi sent them
to the tournament
because he believed that it
would be the easiest place
to gather such a large
amount of energy...
Only after they saw you
transform into a Super Saiyan
did you become their target.
The Supreme Kai
and myself knew
that Babidi would send
someone to the tournament.
We also entered.
The ball containing
Majin Buu has vanished...
We journeyed to where it laid
before, but found no sign of it.
So we believe it is
in Babidi's grasp,
and he waits only for
the energy to open it...
And upon his success...
...the world will
slip into darkness
the like of which has never
been viewed by human eyes.
Videl, what's wrong?
[GOHAN]
You okay?
Yeah...
I'm... I'm fine.
I don't think
I understand.
I mean, you had your chance
to finish off Majin Buu
when you were fighting
Babidi's father.
Why didn't you take it?
It wasn't worth
the risk...
We feared that any
external stimulus
might accidentally
set him free...
The ball in which
Majin Buu was confined
was hidden deep
within the earth,
where no human
could ever find it.
So we allowed him
to lie dormant.
If our actions had
caused him to be released,
we would have been
powerless to stop him...
[CROWD shouting, yelling]
Everyone...
please, calm down!
We're trying our best to
find a way to continue
with no contestants!
Am I going crazy,
or did I just see Videl and
Gohan fly out of here?
It's all so weird.
Videl gets clobbered
in her match and then
gets up without
a bruise on her.
And then she just flies away!
C'mon, it's just
a trick, you know.
Just like Mr. Satan says,
with the smoke and the mirrors
and, um...
Yeah, whatever. I-I guess it
could be some magic trick.
I mean, I know Videl can't fly,
so what else could it be?
[ERASA]
Maybe she actually can fly.
I doubt it, she's
never flown before.
Maybe I'm just gullible, but
that didn't look like a trick.
It looked like it was real.
[CROWD yelling,
ANNOUNCER, FRIARS whimpering]
Hey, announcer!
How 'bout you get in the ring?!
[ANNOUNCER] Ah, Ah! Please!
Stop throwing the cans!
Ow! Ow! Do--!
They're really painful!
Hey... What are they
doing down there?
I dunno.
[VIDEL grunts]
[KIBITO] The Supreme Kai
and the others
are farther ahead of us
than I thought...
We'll have to move
faster to catch them.
[GOHAN]
No problem!
But... hold on
just a second.
How are you holding up
back here, Videl?
[VIDEL] I wish I were as
good at this as you are.
I can't go on.
[GOHAN gasps]
Gohan... I can't
keep my eyes open...
I'm just holding you guys back.
You're just not used
to the wind yet,
you'll get there with practice.
Don't worry about it.
But you're probably right,
it'd be better if you go back.
It's starting to look
like one of those days
that could get dangerous.
If it turns out like that...
...then I want you to
take care of yourself...
...for me, okay?
Yeah, you've got it...
Be careful flying back,
and when you get there,
could you be sure to tell my mom
and my brother what's going on?
They're probably worried.
No problem...
but tell me something.
The Gold Fighter.
It was really you, right?
[GOHAN]
Uh...
Yes. I-I'm sorry I lied to you.
I-I-I just didn't want
everyone to know...
So, seven years ago,
that strange group of people
that showed up during
the fight with Cell...
That was you guys...
And you were the little boy
that was with them, weren't you?
[GOHAN]
Mm-hm.
Then... My father wasn't the
one who beat Cell, was he?
No, it was you.
Yes... It was.
I knew it!
I always had a
feeling about that.
It just seemed strange
to me that my father
was capable of that
kind of strength...
And now it all makes sense!
I'm glad that I know the truth.
Thank you, Gohan.
Now go.
Go and be a hero again...
[GOHAN chuckles]
Good luck, Gohan!
I'll be waiting for you
when you get back!
Bye!
[KIBITO]
Are you finished?
Yep...
Thanks for waiting up.
We need to hurry, Gohan...
We have a lot of
ground to cover.
Right!
[VIDEL]
Wow, they're fast.
You better come back...
Because I'm not finished
with you yet, Gohan.
Hey, there they are!
Hey, Dad!
We're here!
Look, it's Gohan!
It's about time you caught up!
[PICCOLO]
We've been waiting for you.
[GOHAN]
Thank you.
Glad you're here.
Looks like we've got our work
cut out for us again, Gohan.
I heard.
[GOKU] But, hey,
let's have some fun this time!
It's been way too long.
[GOHAN]
You got it!
They both sure seem relaxed.
But, then again, Goku said
it was gonna be an easy one.
[CREATURE grunts]
[chuckles]
They're here.
We made it.
[SPOPOVICH chuckles]
Look, they're landing.
[GOKU gasps]
But there's
nothing out here...
This is odd. We have searched
this entire area before.
[SUPREME KAI]
Everyone, suppress your energy.
We don't want them
to know we're here.
Not just yet.
[GOHAN grunts]
[PICCOLO gasps]
Is that Babidi?
The one on the left?
[SUPREME KAI]
No, it's not.
It's one of his minions.
Hey...
That ground looks like its
been disturbed recently,
like it's been all
dug up or something.
It's so obvious now!
That's why we couldn't
find his spaceship
when we were flying over...
He buried the whole
thing underground!
And that means...
There's a chance Babidi has
learned that Kibito and I
have followed him here to Earth.
Otherwise...
there would be no reason
for him to hide his ship.
I say we attack them now.
The longer we wait here,
the more time we give them
to resurrect Majin Buu.
[SUPREME KAI]
No. We will bide our time.
They will release Majin Buu
outside the ship.
They wouldn't want it
completely destroyed...
We will wait for the right
opportunity to present itself.
[GOHAN gasps]
[GOHAN growls]
Hey! Someone's coming out!
[SPOPOVICH, YAMU grunt]
[BABIDI] So, boys.
What have you brought me?
[SUPREME KAI gasps]
[BABIDI chuckles]
[DEMON chuckles]
[KIBITO]
Dabura!
What is he doing here?!
That cursed wizard...!
He's even managed to ensnare...
the King of the Demons!
[KRILLIN gasps]
Which one?
Which one is Dabura?
[SUPREME KAI]
The tall one.
I see...
Is he strong?
Of course he's strong...!
He is the King of
the Demon World.
Wait a second.
What is this Demon World?
It is a shadow world that exists
on the other side of this one...
like two sides of the same coin.
One of you may be the
strongest in this world...
but in his dark Demon World,
Dabura is the strongest by far.
Um, guys!
I'm beginning to feel just a
little bit outclassed here...
I mean, I'll still help you out
if you think you need me,
but why don't I, uh...
How 'bout I take
the little guy?
[GOHAN]
The little guy...
So that's... Babidi?
[SUPREME KAI]
Yes, it is...
And he is the most
dangerous of them all.
Remember, it is not his size you
must concern yourself with.
It's his magic.
If he is able to keep a being
such as Dabura
under his control...
Just imagine the horror
he could inflict on this world.
So if this Dabura is that
strong and Babidi has him,
what's going to keep us from
falling under his spell?
A wizard seeks out the evil
desires in a person's heart.
Once discovered, he manipulates
them, enhances them...
And ultimately uses
them to control.
This is how Dabura was captured.
Once Babidi infiltrates
a person's heart,
his influence is complete.
All he needs is to find
but a trace of evil
to bring someone
under his power.
Only those pure of heart
and free of evil desires,
like us, have a chance of
fighting him successfully.
Well, that works
for most of us...
But what about Piccolo?
He hasn't always been one of
the good guys, you know...
This is not the time!
[GOKU, GOHAN whimper]
[YAMU]
For you, master.
So, this has the energy
stored inside?
Yes, it does... sir!
[DABURA grunts]
I never anticipated that
Dabura would be here too.
I'm afraid that this
changes everything...
Surely, the Supreme Kai
isn't afraid, is he?
[SUPREME KAI growls]
[VEGETA]
Hmph! Fine.
You can cower up here behind
the rocks if you want...
I'll take them on myself if you
don't have the stomach for it.
[KRILLIN] I may just
let you do that, Vegeta.
Krillin... these guys
seem pretty tough...
Don't you think you should
get back to your family?
Well, I'd like to
stick around, but...
...it looks like
you guys pretty much
have everything
covered without me...
And I'd hate to think of what
your wife would do to me
if I let anything
happen to you.
Yeah. Ha, ha... She does
have a bit of a temper.
But, hey! [laughs]
...I love her!
[BABIDI laughs]
[DABURA grunts]
[SPOPOVICH laughs]
You've done well...
We are now one step closer
to achieving our goal.
[SPOPOVICH laughs]
When you're as
strong as us,
this kind of job is like
taking baby from a candy.
[BABIDI]
It's such a shame
that your business
with me is finished.
[BOTH gasp]
[BABIDI] I'm afraid I have
no more use for you!
[laughs]
[SPOPOVICH gasps]
[screams]
[BABIDI chuckles]
--[SPOPOVICH grunts]
--[YAMU whimpers]
[GOKU whimpers]
[SPOPOVICH gurgles]
[BABIDI chuckles, squeals]
[GOHAN gasps]
[YAMU gasps]
Too bad...
You know, I really
liked him, too...
Yes...
A terrible loss...
Now, for our other... "friend."
[YAMU gasps]
Pui Pui...
would you please kill him?
Gladly.
[PUI PUI]
Hmm...
[PUI PUI growls]
[YAMU screams]
Ahh...
Nice shot.
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[SUPREME KAI whimpers]
[KIBITO whimpers]
[PICCOLO whimpers]
Ah! What kind of people...
kill their own parners?!
[NARRATOR] At last, the ruthless
wizard Babidi has been revealed.
And with the combined
powers of the villains
he's brought under his control,
his opportunity to resurrect
Majin Buu might just be at hand.
Stay tuned for scenes from
the next Dragon Ball Z!