[ANNOUNCER] Heyyyyyy!
All you crazy fans!
[NARRATOR] Previously
on Dragon Ball Z,
It was time at last for the
World Martial Arts
Tournament to begin.
And who better to lead off the
opening ceremonies
than the reigning
champ himself, Mr. Satan?
The big day kicked-off
with the Junior Competition.
The event started in
promising fashion,
but all the fans
cheering for action
were soon struck speechless as
these young warriors
showcased their rather
unconventional techniques.
--[wailing]
--[grunting]
[screaming]
[NARRATOR] Yes--despite
some heavy competition,
the tournament was
quickly shaping up
to be more farce than fight.
--[KORI-YU grunting]
--[ANNOUNCER yells]
[NARRATOR] That is, until
Trunks entered the arena!
[IDASA] Come on! Fight!
Don't you worry...
You'll feel it soon
enough, big-mouth.
[NARRATOR] The contest took a
serious turn as the young Saiyan
expertly defeated his
opponent with a single kick!
[IDASA'S MOM screams]
[IDASA grunts]
[NARRATOR] Trunks easily set the
standard for the competition,
but there was one other
fighter who could match it.
In a brilliant display of skill
and determination,
Goten rapidly advanced through
the ranks of the tournament.
[GOKU] Alright, Goten!
Woo-hoo! Yeah!
Aww! What a little guy, huh?
And handsome, too!
[NARRATOR] It was a proud
moment indeed for Goku,
who watched from the stands as
his son took center stage.
[ANNOUNCER] Allright!
Fighters, are you ready?!
Let's do it!
[IKOSE yells]
[IKOSE yelling]
Gosh... This is it?
This isn't any fun...
[NARRATOR] The competition
tried, but fell by the wayside,
until only the final
two fighters remained.
[TRUNKS] Just to let you know
I am going to win. Understood?
Yeah! I'm going
for the win, too.
[GOTEN chuckles]
[BOTH grunt]
[growling]
[grunting,
blows landing]
[BOTH grunt]
This... isn't happening!
Who are they?!
[CROWD gasping,
murmuring]
[CROWD cheering]
[grunting,
blows landing]
[CROWD cheering]
[ANNOUNCER laughs]
[thinking] I can't believe it!
This is the match I've been
waiting for all of these years!
Just when I was starting to
give up hope, it came!
This is too good to be true!
And this is only
the Junior Division!
[KRILLIN] Check those
two out, would ya?
Staring each other down
in classic stance!
I love it!
They're really doing
well! That's for sure!
[KRILLIN] Awesome!
Way better than I expected!
This match could get
really interesting!
[CHICHI] Come on, Goten!
You can do it, Son!
Yaye, Trunks!
You're doing great, Son!
Pretty impressive. Somehow
you've managed to get
a lot stronger than the
last time we faught.
Ha, ha! Gee, thanks, Trunks!
I owe it all to Gohan though!
He's the one that's been
training me all this time.
[TRUNKS] Well, he did good.
But... not good
enough! Try this!
Huh?
[TRUNKS growls]
Oh no!
This place is way too crowded
to be firing energy blasts!
He... could really
hurt someone!
We can't let him do it!
Ahh, it'll be okay!
[KRILLIN] Huh?
Really! Just look at him...
The kid's in complete control.
[TRUNKS yells]
[ANNOUNCER squeals]
[CROWD screams]
It's gonna hit!
[TRUNKS grunts]
[CROWD gasps]
Wow! What in the
world was that?!
I don't know! It looked
like some kind of rocket!
[MAN 1] But isn't rocket
fire against the rules?!
[MAN 2] Oh, yes!
Most definitely!
[CROWD murmurs]
Whew... That was close.
--See?
--[KRILLIN chuckles]
[MR. SATAN whimpers]
I... I've seen this before!
At the Cell games!
[CROWD gasping,
murmuring]
Nice, huh? What did you think?
That was really cool!
Gohan taught me a little
bit of that stuff too!
Watch! Check this out!
Ka... Me... Ha... Me...
[TRUNKS giggles]
Oh! Did he teach
you how to control it?!
Goten...?
[GOTEN] Haaaa!
[ANNOUNCER screams]
Hey! Not bad!
--[KRILLIN squeals]
--Oh well...
I guess, Goten still has a
little bit of practicing
to do on that one...
--Ahh... Gohan?
--Hmm?
--[CHICHI whimpers]
--Wow! Cool!
[OLD FELLA] What in
tarnation's going on?
Are those little tikes from
another planet or something?!
Whoa!
I-I-It... can't be!
They have the
same kind of powers
as those guys
who faught Cell!
[GOTEN laughs]
Oops! I blew up the roof!
You sure did! We better
cool it! No more beams!
We don't want to blow
the whole place up!
[GOTEN laughs]
Look at you! You're
lovin' it, aren't you?!
Uhh... Uh-huh!
[TRUNKS grunts]
[TRUNKS] Let's do it!
Yeah!
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER] It looks like
they're starting up again!
Wow! What a match!
This bout promises to
be the most exciting
Junior Championship of all time!
[IKOSE] Mom, I want
to go watch the final!
[IDASA] Me, too, Mom!
Can we?!
[IDASA'S MOM] What?!
Absolutely not! Keep working!
You two should be
ashamed of yourselves,
losing to those little runts!
[grunting, sobbing]
Boys! My boys!
How could you?!
I've never been so
embarrassed in my entire life!
This can never happen again!
But dear... please!
Those boys, they were special!
They beat all of the
other kids as well!
Oh, pooey! I'm not
buying that rubbish!
Fool!
I'm raising champions! I'll make
champions out of you two yet!
Stop giving them the excuses
they need to be weaklings!
Oooh! Well... Next
year! They're mine!
Now get to work!
[IDASA &amp; IKOSE grunting]
[CROWD cheering]
Here we go!
It's been fun, but I'm afaraid
I'm gonna have to finish it.
[cheering continues]
I'm gonna win this
thing, Goten!
Oh yeah? We'll
see about that!
[TRUNKS yells]
[BOTH grunt]
There! Going up?!
[GOTEN screams]
[GOTEN] Uh! Where'd he go?!
That's strange... There's
nowhere for him to hide...
--Huh?!
--Gotcha!
Hey! Let go of me, Trunks!
How did you do that?!
No fair! Let me go!
[GOTEN grunts]
[ANNOUNCER] Ladies
and gentlemen!
It's difficult to see
from down here,
but it looks like Trunks has
young Goten in a stranglehold!
Come on! Hang tough!
[GOTEN growls]
Give it up, Goten! I don't
want to have to hurt you!
[GOTEN yells]
[FAN 1] Look at those two!
They're floating!
How are they doing that?!
[FAN 2] This is crazy!
[FAN 3] Impossible's
more like it!
[GOTEN yells]
[TRUNKS] Give up, Goten!
You're only making this
harder on yourself!
[GOTEN] I can't! I won't!
No! No! Never!
[GOKU] Oh, man...
This does not look good!
Sure it does! If you're
rooting for Trunks, that is!
[GOKU] Hmm?
Yo, Goten! Brace up, bro!
[GOTEN yells]
Just say it! Give up!
[GOTEN grunting]
[GOKU gasps]
Wow! Goten's already
a Super Saiyan!
[GOHAN] Oh no!
Kakarot! That's not fair!
Well, hey. Don't
look at me. He did it.
[VIDEL whimpers]
[ANNOUNCER] Ladies
and gentlemen...
If I hadn't seen it with my own
eyes, I wouldn't believe it!
After a terrible
airborne struggle,
Goten broke the stranglehold!
Amazing! What a
match! What a match!
[MAN 1] Where did
those two come from?
[MAN 2] I know that kid's
hair turned yeller!
[WOMAN 1] I don't know if
we should be watching this!
[BOY 1] Aw, c'mon, Mom!
This is awesome!
Who would've guessed?!
This is better than wrestling!
[MR. SATAN] How can this be?!
It's him! It's them!
The ones with the powers!
[MR. SATAN whimpers]
He's just like the
guy who beat Cell!
[VIDEL] Unbelievable!
[TRUNKS] Yo!
Hello? Goten? Did you forget?!
We're not supposed to turn
into Super Saiyans, dummy!
Oh, yeah! Oops! Sorry!
I won't do it again, I promise!
Hmph!
You-- Gimme a break!
You didn't forget!
You knew darn well what you
were doing, didn't you?!
[GOTEN laughs]
Maybe...
[TRUNKS] Well, now I'm gonna
embarrass you, Goten!
--Huh?
--Yep! That's right!
Now! Look, you...
You're cooked!
I'm gonna win this thing
without using one of my arms!
Ah?! There's no way!
You're trying to trick me!
Nope! Dead serious!
Come on, Trunks!
You wouldn't have a chance!
Rrghhh! You-- You can't
beat me with one arm!
No left arm!
[TRUNKS grunts]
[growling]
[TRUNKS yells]
[GOTEN grunts]
--[TRUNKS grunts]
--[GOTEN] Haa!
[TRUNKS gasps]
[grunting,
blows landing]
Alright! Go, Trunks!
Yaye, Son! Go! Do it!
[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER] Look at them go!
What a Championship!
These two juniors are giving
it everything they've got!
Wow!
[CAMERA MAN] Hey, I think
I got it! Wait! Ahh, darn!
Don't got it!
Hey, guys! Yo! Still down!
[TECHNICIAN] I don't get it!
I can't find anything
wrong with these units!
They should be
working just fine!
Gosh, sir!
I hate to say it, but I
don't think I can fix this!
Ahhh... darn it!
Don't we have some
back-ups or something?!
Sir! We tried those already!
The back-up units
aren't working either!
Yeah! It's crazy,
and it's not just us!
Every single camera in
the stadium is broken.
Right down to the disposables
in the gift shop!
[DIRECTOR growls]
You've got to be kidding!
The fight of the
century is going on
and we can't even
take a snapshot!
[grunting,
blows landing]
[GOTEN grunts]
[TRUNKS grunts]
[grunting,
blows landing]
--[GOTEN yells]
--[TRUNKS grunts]
[GOTEN yells]
[TRUNKS grunts]
[TRUNKS yells]
No fair!
Trunks, you cheater!
You said no more energy beams!
That's not fair!
[TRUNKS] Sorry, Goten!
Sorry, it didn't
hit you, that is...
Mister Super Saiyan...
Give me a break!
[WOMAN 1] What the heck
does he think he's doing?!
People can't just fly!
Not where I come from!
That's impossible.
Wow!
I can't believe how strong
Goten is at his age!
He must be eating all
of his vegetables...
[KRILLIN] Yeah! That's for sure!
[VIDEL] This is
absolutely crazy!
[VIDEL whimpers]
Huh?! Now I get it!
You lousy bum!
You've been giving Goten
special training sessions
and leaving me out!
Huh?! No way! It wasn't special!
Just the normal routine!
Yeah, right! Huh.
No way! This is
anything but normal.
Here I come!
[TRUNKS growls]
[GOHAN growls]
[TRUNKS thinking] Alright,
Goten. What's on your mind?
You know you can't
hide anything from me.
I'll have it figured out
before you get here.
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[VIDEL whimpers]
[GOTEN yells]
What?!
[GOTEN gasps, yells]
[CROWD screams]
[GOTEN grunts]
[GOTEN] Huh?!
[GOTEN screams]
Aww... darn.
Oh no! He lost!
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[VEGETA chuckles]
[CROWD murmuring]
[ANNOUNCER] Ladies and
Gentlemen, we have a winner!
The new Junior Division
World Champion is... Trunks!
Yipeeee! Yeah!
--[TRUNKS laughs]
--[CROWD roars]
Yaye! Way to go!
Alright, Trunks!
Poor Goten...
He tried so hard...
--[BULMA cheers]
--[ROSHI] Well...
Both those boys
did their best!
And it looks like I'm
not doing so bad myself!
[ROSHI chuckles]
[ROSHI grunts]
[VIDEL whimpers]
Trunks too?
You mean they're
both Super Saiyans?
Wow! What's up with
this generation?!
[VEGETA laughs]
[VEGETA] Cheer up, Kakarot!
There's always next year!
Your son put up a good fight!
But there can only
be one champion!
[ANNOUNCER] Let's hear it for
these two young warriors, folks!
Trunks and Goten!
What happened?!
I don't know! They moved
too fast for me to tell!
[ANNOUNCER] Remember those
two names, people!
I'm sure we'll be hearing them
for a long time to come
at future Championships!
[GOTEN growls]
So what's the big idea, Trunks?!
That wasn't fair
at all! You lied!
You said you wouldn't
use your left hand
OR transform into
a Super Saiyan!
But you did both, you jerk!
Hey! It's just a game, right?!
Besides, you transformed once
so, that makes us
even-steven! One time each!
As far as using the
left hand goes,
I did slip up a little bit,
but I still didn't use
it to punch you! Right?!
Come on! Don't be mad at me!
I'll tell you what!
You can have
three of my toys!
You pick 'em!
What?! Really?! Cool!
I get to pick! Wow!
I know which ones too!
Thank you, Trunks!
[GOTEN laughs]
[ANNOUNCER] Ladies
and Gentlemen,
before get started with
the adult competition...
we're going to have
our special exhibition match
between the new Junior
World Champion, Trunks,
and Mr. Satan, the reigning
World Martial Arts Champion!
--[CROWD cheers]
--[MR. SATAN whimpers]
[ANNOUNCER]
That's right! Mr. Satan!
The most renowned Martial
Artist in the world!
The hero who saved
the world from Cell!
What a treat, to see this
veteran Master of the arts
in a friendly match with Trunks,
the rising, new rookie star!
Ha! This isn't going to be
much of a fight, you know?
Right! You better not
blink, or you'll miss it!
[KRILLIN laughs]
[VEGETA chuckles]
Trunks is going to
pulverise this noisy fool.
World Champion? I've known
stronger house-plants.
Oh, yeah right, Vegeta!
[GOHAN laughs]
Come on, Jokester!
Uh-huh...?
[GOHAN] What a crazy,
funny guy, huh?!
[GOHAN laughs]
[GOHAN] Oh, man!
That's a good one!
Vegeta! He should be a comedian!
He's got a million of 'em!
[ANNOUNCER] Alright, folks!
The reigning World Champion
should be coming out
any minute now!
[GOTEN laughs]
Wow, cool! I wish I was champ!
[ANNOUNCER] I know he's
around here somewhere, folks!
How about a big cheer
to lure him out?!
--Give it up for Mr. Satan!
--[CROWD cheers]
[ANNOUNCER] Alright! Now that's
what I call a hero's welcome!
[cheering continues]
[ANNOUNCER]
Unbelievable! It didn't work!
--Can we get it a little louder?
--[cheering grows louder]
[ANNOUNCER] Come on!
You can get louder than that!
One more time! Give
it everything you've got!
Ready! One, two, three... Go!
[CROWD roars]
[ANNOUNCER] Alright! Alright!
Nobody can resist
a welcome like that!
Where are you, Mr. Satan?!
--Come on out!
--[MR. SATAN wails]