[NARRATOR] Previously
on Dragon Ball Z...
The Ginyu Force faces up to Goku
in a mighty showdown,
and Goku turns up the heat
revealing his true strength
to the ruthless warriors.
An astonished Captain
Ginyu realizes
that he has come face-to-face
with the power Frieza fears
most: that of a Super Sayian.
[NARRATOR] Elsewhere
on the Planet Namek,
Frieza pays a visit to the aging
Guru to uncover the password
needed to call forth the
dragon and grant his wish.
Namek warriors try to intervene,
but Frieza launches into
an attack and easily
disposes of them.
[NARRATOR] Now, with
the Namekian warriors
out of the way,
only Nail can defend Guru
and keep Frieza from
getting his password.
[NARRATOR} Can this
brave fighter hold off
the evil tyrant?
Find out today.
[FRIEZA cackles]
[FRIEZA] Oh, please, Nail,
do you really believe that
you could possibly harm me?
Why, I would have thought you
were much smarter than that,
but I guess I
misjudged you!
[FRIEZA chuckles]
By the way, Guru,
once I'm finished
with your friend here,
I'll be back to see
if you've reconsidered
giving me the password. Hmph.
[NAIL growls softly]
[FRIEZA] So, you see,
it's really quite simple.
I'll spare his life for
the Dragon Ball password.
His fate rests in your hands
so I suggest you choose wisely!
I guess that answers
that question, doesn't it?
Oh well, let's
get on with it.
And now my friend, any last
wishes before I kill you?
[NAIL growls]
[NAIL] You want to fight?!
Fine! But not here!
I don't want Guru to see what
I'm going to do to you!
[NAIL] You see, he doesn't
have much time, Frieza,
and I want to spare him
the unpleasantries.
So, c'mon, let's do it!
I admire your courage,
but let's be honest.
Once I'm done with you, then
I'll deal with your friend here.
[NAIL] Follow me!
[GURU] Such horrible evil.
Nail, my son...
I know it's grim.
Still, you must battle on.
For the Earthlings...
They need more time.
[GURU sighs heavily]
They may be
our last chance
to save the universe from
that hideous Frieza.
[JEICE] I... I think
he's laughing.
[GINYU laughing]
Capt...
C-Captain Ginyu?
[GINYU laughing]
[GINYU chuckles]
What are you
laughing at?!
[GINYU laughs]
[GINYU growls]
Yaah!
[GINYU chuckles]
You crack
me up, bucko.
I've never seen someone so
cool in the line of fire!
I'm warning
you to go home!
[GINYU] Oh, I know you are!
But I think we should
just turn it up a notch!
[GINYU growls]
Yaah!
Hyaah!
[GINYU laughs]
For a peace-loving
do-gooder like yourself,
I'm pretty impressed!
[GINYU laughs]
Ladies and gentlemen,
let's get it on!
[GINYU laughs]
That's right, folks!
It's time for the grand
finale of grand finales!
No one can survive the awesome
power of the Ginyu Force!
Rrraaagh!
[JEICE grunts]
[GINYU chuckles]
Huh...? Wha...?
Hey, Jeice!
Yes, Sir...?
[GINYU] Hold on to that.
But... Cap'n,
you'll need the scouter!
I think not! The stronger
this guys is, the better!
I hear you
loud and clear!
[GOKU] Hmm?
[GINYU snickers]
[laughing]
So, where are we going?
I said, where
are we going?!
This is far enough! It's
time to put up or shut up!
This way.
[FRIEZA] Before you begin your
pathetic struggle to survive,
I should warn you, your chance
of winning is non-existent!
[NAIL growls]
Oooh.
[growling continues]
[NAIL yells]
Oh my. According to my
readout, I may have
underestimated
your strength!
But no matter.
Your power pales in comparison
to what I have in store for you!
[FRIEZA] Not to say the
light show wasn't impressive,
but you see, I'm probably five
hundred thousand times stronger
than you are!
So, in order to keep
this a fair fight...
I promise to
refrain from using
all of my powers on you,
for they are obviously
powers which you,
my green little friend,
do not possess.
Observe my left hand...
Its strength alone
is enough to crush you
like the little bug you are.
So as a special
one-time bonus...
Huh?
[NAIL growls]
Today, I will fight you while
my other hand is behind my back!
So, now that we've got the
ground rules settled,
shall we begin?
[NAIL growls]
[NAIL] I've had enough of
you! It's time to fight!
[NAIL shouts]
[FRIEZA laughs]
[FRIEZA] Oh my, oh my! You
still don't get it, do you?
You see, the bottom line
is you don't stand a chance!
I'll show you...
And like I said before,
I'll only use my left hand!
[FRIEZA laughs,
NAIL squeals]
[NAIL screams]
[NAIL pants]
[FRIEZA] Oh my,
that has got to hurt!
[FRIEZA laughs]
[FRIEZA] Here!
You might want to keep
it as a back scratcher!
[FRIEZA cackles]
A back scratcher!
Where do I come up
with this stuff?!
Enough idle chit-chat.
I should really get back to Guru
and see if he's changed his
mind about that password.
[NAIL growls]
[NAIL shouting]
Hm?
[shouting continues]
That didn't show up
in the readout!
The ability to re-generate
one's own anatomy!
I'll just have to make
a copy of that power,
because you never know
when it might come in handy.
Well, now...
Most of the warriors
I know would have
surrendered by now, but...
I don't think you've learned
your lesson, have you?
Alright, let's try it again.
Yeah, let's try it.
[FRIEZA chuckles]
This time you'll lose.
Agh! why can't this
thing go any faster?!
And just my luck, Dino here
isn't even breaking a sweat
Oohh...
[DINOSAUR roars]
[BULMA squeals]
[BULMA screams]
Huh?!
Oh no! Now what
am I gonna do?!
[thinking] The cave!
Just a little further!
C'mon girl, you can make it!
Ah! I made it! I-I made it!
[DINOSAUR B roars]
[BULMA screams]
[BULMA shrieks]
Whew. My industrial
strength... hairspray...
Huh?!
[BULMA wails]
[BULMA screams]
Oh, this is just great!
Why did I have to start
biting my nails again?!
[BULMA screams]
[DINOSAUR B roars]
Okay, I'll
close my eyes...
and he'll just disappear.
Who am I trying to kid?!
[BULMA yelps]
[grunts]
Huh...?
What... What...?
What in the world?!
[BULMA screams]
No, no, no! Don't
you come near me!
Get away from me
you hideous creature!
Get away and leave me alone
or I'll be forced to--
Huh?
Is that...
you Gohan?
But...
[BULMA gasps]
[KRILLIN growls]
[GOHAN chuckling]
Hey... Give
me a break...
It's not funny!
Man, you try and
give somebody a hand
and this is the thanks you get!
Well, look who
finally shows up!
Last time I saw you two was
when you were going to get the
Dragon Balls and you
said you'd be right back!
Do you realize how many
times I've heard that one?!
Well, I'm sick and tired
of waiting by myself!
From now on, I'm in charge
and if you don't like it,
that's tough! Any questions?!
Come on, it's not like
we were avoiding you.
Look, we were just
busy that's all!
[GOHAN] That's right!
We've been working real hard
to get the Dragon Balls back.
And we'll get them soon.
Why, you...!
You don't even have
the Dragon Balls?!
And here I am waiting,
being chased by every
wild beast imaginable,
I haven't showered in weeks,
not to mention I ran out
of lip gloss a month ago,
and you come back empty handed?!
So then... what do you
have to say for yourself?
We... We are sorry...
At least I think?
Krillin, I found it.
According to this,
they're not far away
They're over in that direction!
[KRILLIN] Let's go!
[BULMA] Wait! Where
are you going?!
You can't just leave
me here again!
Don't worry, we'll
be back in no time!
Just go back
to the campsite
and we'll meet you there, okay?
Hey! This is
plain ridiculous!
I'm not just going to wait here
again! Wait! Come back here!
What'd expect me just to
walk to the campsite?
Oh, yeah! I almost forgot!
I saw my father!
What? Are
you serious?!
You saw Goku?
Well, did he ask about me?
[GOHAN] Uh-huh!
[GOHAN laughs]
[BULMA laughs]
[KRILLIN] Gohan, we'd
better get going!
Gotcha!
[BULMA] Ahh... Goku.
[BULMA] Now, let's see...
I don't remember exactly
how long it's been
since I last saw him...
It's been so long, I wonder
what he looks like now?
[BULMA] Hmm...
[BULMA] Oh, Goku, when
will I see you again?
[GINYU chuckles]
[GINYU yells]
[GOKU gasps]
[GINYU grunts]
This guy... is nuts!
[GOKU] What the...?
Now... it's time...
to reveal the ultimate strength
of the Ginyu Force...
Watch... because the show...
is just... about to... begin!
Wow! What's he doing?
[GINYU growling]
[growling continues]
[JEICE] That's it,
mate! Good work.
Now let's pull it
together... and... It's done.
[GINYU shouting]
[shouting continues]
[thinking] C'mon, give me your
best shot you crazy kook!
Yaaah!
Yeah... that's it!
You're... miiinnnee!
[GOKU grunting]
[GINYU laughing]
[GINYU] Yaaah!
Haaaughh...
[GOKU grunts]
[GINYU laughs]
[GOKU gasps]
Why, you... Hey...
What kind of powers
did you use?!
[GINYU chuckles]
[GINYU] The power to
metamorph into your body and
fool your men!
[GOKU ] It's impossible!
No... It can't be!
[JEICE] Captain Ginyu...
Here's your scouter back!
Good... Now let's
head back to the ship.
I'm sure Frieza will be glad to
hear that I've defeated Goku.
Yeah!
[GINYU laughs]
Hey, this new body
is pretty quick!
[GOKU] Hey, wait! W-Wait! You
can't leave me like this!
Arrgh! The pain's too strong
and I don't think I can go on!
But I must summon
the strength...
Nooo! I... will
not... be defeated this way!
Even if it takes the last ounce
of strength in my body!
You will not get away with this!
[GOKU groans]
I just... wish there was a way
to warn Krillin and Gohan
about what's coming their way!
[thinking] You can run and you
can hide in my body, Ginyu,
but mark my words, this
battle is not over...
NOT by a long shot!
Count on it Ginyu...
It's not over!
[NARRATOR] Now that Captain
Ginyu possesses Goku's body,
will he be able convince
Krillin and Gohan
that he is who
he appears to be?
Will he be able
to trick them into
giving him the Dragon Balls?
And can Goku get his body back?
Find out on the next
exciting episode of...
Dragon Ball Z!