[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Cell had a surprise for Goku!
[CELL] You almost
fell out of the ring!
If you had, I would
have been declared
the winner of this
little match of ours.
Huh?
Is the game too hard for you?
Should I make it easier?
Perhaps this will make
things more interesting!
[NARRATOR] In a reckless move,
the genetically-engineered
villain destroyed his own ring
so that he could fight
Goku without any boundaries.
[NARRATOR] And so,
across the desert landscape
the battle waged on.
Cell's attack was relentless,
but the valiant Super Saiyan
matched the attack
blow for blow.
It seemed the fighters had
been thrown into a stalemate,
and the bout
would last forever.
[NARRATOR] But after dodging
a string of lethal blasts,
Goku unveiled
a daring new strategy.
Soaring high into the air, he
gathered up tremendous energy
for his most famous move--
The Kamehameha Wave--
and aimed it
directly at the Earth!
[NARRATOR] Cell was quick
to call Goku's bluff,
knowing that he wouldn't
risk firing the blast
and exploding the entire planet.
But, Goku had
something else in mind...
[GOKU] Haaa...
No, he wouldn't?!
[NARRATOR] At the
last moment, Goku used
his Instant Transmission
technique to appear below Cell
and deliver the bang
before the vile android
could put up his guard.
[CELL] NOOO!!
Haaa!!
[NARRATOR] Goku has
scored a direct hit!
Is this the final blow
that will win the tournament
and rid the Earth of Cell?
Find out... today!
[YAMCHA] Did you see that?!
Goku blasted Cell into pieces!
Nobody could survive
the Kamehameha Wave
at that close range!
[TIEN] You're right, Yamcha!
That little maneuver may have
just won Goku the tournament!
Yeah, he's won!
[VEGETA growls]
Uh, say, Champ, what
just happened down there?
Yeah! Goku did it, alright!
That Instant Transmission
Technique really did the trick!
Hey, everybody,
Goku won the tournament!
[YAMCHA laughs]
[YAMCHA gasps]
[YAMCHA] Come on, you guys!
This is good news!
We don't have to worry
about Cell anymore!
Huh...?
Man! I wish those guys
would lighten up a bit.
So, Mr. Satan, could this really
be the end of the Cell Games?
Hello, Earth to Hercule!
Oh! Uh? Of course!
Uh, this new guy
has some good moves,
and he might have
done a number on Cell,
but that's nothing compared to
what I would have done to him!
[MR. SATAN laughs]
[PIIZA giggles]
Oh, Mr. Satan,
it's such a pity you
never had a chance to fight.
Now the world will never get to
see what a great hero you are!
[PIIZA giggles]
[ANNOUNCER] Huh.
Well, there you have
it, ladies and gentlemen.
To our great regret, Mr. Satan
won't be able to demonstrate
his bone-crushing
moves in the Cell Games,
because this unknown contestant
has somehow turned Cell
into a pile of cinders.
Who is this insanely-hair-styled
hero and how did he do,
well, whatever he did?
Stay tuned, I'll try
for an exclusive interview!
What? You mean it's over now?
You know what I think,
the whole thing was fixed!
Come on, Mama! Let's go!
--Let's go! Come on!
--Wait!
I want to find out
who this young man is!
[thinking] Something's not
right... It's not over yet!
I can still sense a lot
of energy left in Cell's body.
[KRILLIN gasps]
Get away from him, Goku!
Cell is going
to regenerate himself!
[YAMCHA gasps]
Huh...?
[GOKU] Regeneration?
--[GOKU gasps]
--[ALL gasp]
Whoa! Leaping Lizards!
The headless Cell
is back on his feet!
[GOKU gasps]
[CELL grunts]
Oh my! Cell has just
sprouted another head!
Is this another one of
the monster's dirty tricks?!
Of course it's a trick!
It has to be!
[CELL grunting]
[GOKU] I should have known
that you'd be able
to regenerate yourself.
[CELL] Of course.
Thanks to Piccolo's cells.
He just won't die!
[GOKU] Hah!
I may not have beaten
you with that blast, Cell,
but I can sense that
your power level
has gone down sharply
because of it.
[CELL] Perhaps, but you're
the one who seems
to have trouble
catching his breath.
I know what you did.
You pushed most of your energy
into that last attack, Goku.
But I'm still standing and
all your power's drained,
which means your fight is over!
That's not true!
I'll show you.
[ANNOUNCER] Flaming fish sticks!
The Cell Game will go on!
Who will take the tournament
title now is anybody's guess!
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU grunts]
[yelling]
[GOKU] Hngh?!
[CELL grunts]
[GOKU yells]
[grunting,
blows landing]
[grunting continues]
Cell has come out swinging,
and the unknown challenger seems
to be using his face to block!
That's gotta hurt!
[grunting,
blows landing]
The power! They are both so
strong! I can't believe it!
The whole world
seems to be shaking!
I can feel the Earth
moving under my feet!
[ROSHI grunts]
This looks bad... very bad...
Hello, everybody! Hi!
Oh, hello, Bulma!
Am I too late? I hope
I haven't missed anything.
Little Trunks and I
just wanted to come over
and watch the tournament
with you guys, okay?
[BABY TRUNKS wails]
Oh... there now...
[wailing continues]
[grunting,
blows landing]
[GOKU growls]
[CELL yells]
[CELL] Huh?!
[GOKU grunts,
CELL yells]
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU gasps]
[GOKU screams]
[PICCOLO] Goku was counting
on that last attack
to finish Cell off.
I don't know how much longer
he'll be able to keep this up.
[VEGETA growls]
[thinking] I know you're
losing strength, Dad,
but you have to keep going.
[grunting,
blows landing]
[BOTH grunt]
Is this battle
too much for you, Goku?
NO!!
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU grunts]
[CELL chuckles,
GOKU growls]
[CELL yells]
--[CELL] Huh?!
--[GOKU yells]
[CELL grunts]
Yeah! Go get 'em! Ha!
[CELL screams]
He's got him!
Goku's going to win!
[GOKU shouting]
[CELL yells]
Yeah he's got
him now! That's it!
Finish that monster
off for good Goku!
Yeah, get him!
[whimpering]
[ANNOUNCER] The golden-topped
titan is attacking Cell
with everything he's got!
This could really be it, folks!
It looks like Cell is in
really big trouble now!
I can't believe what I'm seeing!
I'm almost too
scared to open my eyes!
Come on, now! This is important!
Fix it, you bums!
There's nothing wrong
with our equipment!
I set this station up myself
and I know everything works!
[phone rings]
[screaming]
[OPERATOR] That's it,
no more phone calls!
Alright, Cell is going down!
It's about time!
We won, guys!
[VEGETA growls]
Do it!
[thinking] Finish him off, Dad!
[GOKU shouting]
[CELL grunting]
[CELL yells]
[growling]
[CELL screams]
[shouting]
[ANNOUNCER] I don't like
the look of that!
[MR. SATAN screams]
[MR. SATAN grunts]
Maestro, are you okay?
Shall I give you a hand?
[MR. SATAN] No! No problem here!
Just getting
warmed up, that's all.
[MR. SATAN grunts]
Whatta man!
Hercule, you
are something else
getting warmed up
for battle like that!
So that's how you do it!
That's how you keep
in such great shape!
[MR. SATAN] You know me,
always ready for action!
As hard as this is, I will
hold on and continue my report!
But what is this ball
of energy Cell has created?!
It sort of looks
likes static electricity,
but where would he find
a conductor this large
and where was he hiding it?
Maybe now you can see
how completely hopeless
you really are, Goku!
[CELL] This is my game
and I make the rules!
[GOKU] Hmph.]
[MAN] Oh no! That monster
can't be stopped!
Hey, look at that!
It won't be long now,
that guy's history!
Mama what's going on?
I can't see! Is it over yet?
I'm not sure, but that
golden-haired young man
looks a lot like
ChiChi's husband to me.
What on earth
is he doing
on television fighting
that monster?
Don't ask me!
Don't know why ChiChi lets
her husband run wild like that!
It's shameful!
Ha-choo!
[CHICHI] I think I'm
worrying myself sick!
Come on, Goku!
You gotta do something!
[BULMA] Oh, Goku was so close to
winning the tournament!
What a rip-off!
No, I don't think so.
I don't think Goku has
any chance of beating Cell.
He's running low
on strength. It's obvious!
[BULMA gasps]
You think he'll lose...?
I know it's hard
to believe, Bulma,
Goku is looking tired
and I think he knows he can't
win the tournament either!
I don't know what
he's planning,
but whatever it is,
he'd better do it soon!
[PICCOLO]
Both of their power levels
have dropped tremendously,
but Goku's is...
dropping much faster!
[PICCOLo] If he doesn't act
soon, Goku is going to lose!
[CELL] Are you
feeling tired, Goku?
You've lost a lot of strength.
[CELL laughs]
Why don't you take a breather?
Perhaps one of those
Senzu beans would help you.
Hey, this is our chance!
If Goku eats a Senzu Bean,
he can get his strength back
and take Cell down!
That's right!
Cell said he could!
Come on, Krillin!
[PICCOLO] We will wait...
We'll wait for what?
He needs a Senzu Bean!
[VEGETA] Quiet, boy!
Where is your honor?!
Like all pure-blooded Saiyans,
Kakarot would rather
die fighting than win
with one of those disgraceful
Senzu Beans as his crutch!
Kakarot trained in the
Hyperbolic Time Chamber
just as we did.
Now let's see what he can do!
Oh no! We can't!
Goku doesn't have the strength!
Don't you see what'll happen
if he keeps going like this?!
If this goes on,
then he will die.
[TRUNKS gasps]
[gasping]
[KRILLIN growls]
But, that will be his decision!
It is painfully
clear at this point
that no one among this group
is stronger than Kakarot is.
Not even... myself.
So he deserves to have
the fight of a true warrior!
And that means to the death!
While we all just stand here and
watch?! I won't be a part of it!
Aren't you the one who
has never stopped talking
about how great a
hero Kakarot is?!
[VEGETA] If you have
so much faith in him,
then wait and see
what he will do!
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL] I can feel your
power slipping away, Goku.
I don't think you
can last much longer.
[CELL chuckles]
You know, it's hardly worth
my effort to finish you off now.
But I wouldn't
want to disappoint
the television audience
because I know they
want to see a real champion.
The next battle we engage
in will be your last, Goku!
[CELL laughs]
[GOKU] You're right
about one thing, Cell,
the world does want
to see a real champion!
[VEGETA gasps]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
[GOKU] It's over, Cell.
You win!
[GOHAN gasps]
I give up, I know
how strong you are.
There's no point in continuing
this fight. I can't beat you.
[CELL gasps]
You coward!
No! Goku!
No, don't do it!
What! No way!
Goku never gives up!
What! Goku's turning
his back on us?!
No... Don't give up...
Rrrgh! No, you can't
let Cell win, Goku!
[OX-KING gasps]
No! Come on, Goku!
You can't end it this way!
You can't let Cell win!
[NARRATOR] Has Goku
lost his mind?
If he gives up now,
what will prevent Cell
from terrorizing
the Earth once again?
Has Dr. Gero's cruel
creation proved
that he is even more powerful
than our greatest hero?
The answers are coming,
next time on Dragon Ball Z!