[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z...
After a lengthy rest,
Goten and Trunks awoke to
some strange new surroundings,
unaware that Piccolo
had carried them
to the Lookout
for safe keeping.
[TRUNKS]
This place is huge!
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
the loss of Gohan and Vegeta
weighed heavily on the
remaining Z Fighters' minds.
Little could they know,
far away on the
Supreme Kai's planet,
a glimmer of hope
still remained.
[SUPREME KAI] Kibito,
revive Gohan with your power.
Whoa! What's the...?
[NARRATOR]
Gohan has been revived!
The injuries he sustained from
Majin Buu have been healed.
But for what purpose has
he been transported
to the World of the Kais?
[SUPREME KAI] I brought Gohan
here to get the Z Sword!
It's the only way that
Majin Buu can be defeated now.
[NARRATOR] Sheathed in stone
atop a pillar of rock,
the Z Sword has lain dormant
for untold centuries,
waiting for the
arrival of a warrior
strong enough to
harness its hidden power.
Many have tried,
but so far, none have
succeeded in pulling it free.
[SUPREME KAI]
Now try to pull it out!
[NARRATOR]
Is Gohan strong enough
to remove the Z Sword
from its resting place?
And if he is,
will this legendary weapon
really give him the edge he
needs to beat Majin Buu?
There's only
one way to find out!
Stay tuned for Dragon Ball Z!
[thump]
[BULMA growls]
[BULMA] It's just too hard...
for me to believe...
How could Gohan
beat something like Cell,
but he couldn't stand up
to that fat, disgusting...
[BULMA sobs]
Yes, it is hard to
believe, but it's true.
Gohan is dead,
and my poor ChiChi...
Now she's lost her
husband and her son!
Dead, dead, dead! I'm so tired
of hearing you people say that!
We haven't even found
a body yet, and you just...
...stand around here
acting defeated
like we've...
already buried him!
[VIDEL growls]
Videl, I'm sorry.
I lost a friend, too.
But if we can't sense
his life force anymore,
then that... means that,
well... That he's passed on.
[VIDEL]
Stop saying that!
I don't believe it...
[VIDEL] I absolutely
refuse to believe it.
[VIDEL] He can't be gone before
we ever had a chance together.
[VIDEL thinking]
Gohan...
Here goes.
Huh?
Uh, I was wondering exactly...
I mean... Ha, ha. What's
supposed to happen when a person
actually manages to
pull this thing out?
[KIBITO] The sword draws on its
master's deepest hidden powers.
The two become one weapon,
capable of cutting down
even the mightiest of foes.
Oh wow, it sounds like this
sucker must be really sharp!
Guess I'll have to be careful.
Don't worry,
you can't free it.
[SUPREME KAI] Kibito,
we've all had our chance,
now give Gohan his.
If you're ready,
give it a try.
[GOHAN]
Here goes nothing.
[grunts]
[yells]
[grunting]
[screams]
[GOHAN groans]
Ahh, stupid hands.
Gohan, I think you
should try it again.
You guys weren't
kidding about this thing!
C'mon, hands, be strong,
be strong, be strong!
[yells]
Not even your
Super Saiyan strength
will be enough, I'm afraid.
[grunts]
Your effort is in vain.
If the Supreme Kai was
unable to extract the sword,
how can a simple mortal like
yourself ever succeed?
[grunts]
[GOHAN yells]
[yells]
[GOHAN grunts]
Gohan, you did it!
The Z Sword is free!
[SUPREME KAI]
Well, Kibito,
it would seem that you have
underestimated our young friend.
[KIBITO growls]
How does it feel, Gohan,
to hold the legendary Z Sword?
Let's see.
[grunts]
[GOHAN yells, grunts]
[SUPREME KAI gasps]
Don't worry, I've got it.
[grunts]
Hey, you know what?
I think I figured out
how I can use this thing
to beat Majin Buu.
Is that so?
[GOHAN] It's so heavy, if I
could just get him to hold it,
he won't be able
to move his arms!
[gasps]
How dare you make jokes?!
Have you no respect for the
power that is in your grasp?!
This sword is the ultimate
weapon, and you removed it.
Now you must master it.
You must work harder
than you ever have,
because if you continue
trembling the way are now,
your battle with Majin Buu will
be over before it's begun!
Well, Kibito, maybe you'd
like to give it a try?
For you, this
should be no problem.
[GOHAN]
Ready?
[yells]
[SUPREME KAI]
How embarrassing.
See? Like I said, it's heavy.
[KIBITO grunts]
[growls]
[BOTH gasp]
[KIBITO]
Uh, it's not that heavy.
You couldn't even
lift it off the ground...
[KIBITO] Well, I'm not the
one who has to use it!
You are! So you
had better get started!
[GOKU] Now remember, even if
the fusion is successful,
it will only last
for 30 minutes.
Once that time's up,
your bodies will separate
and you guys
will return to normal.
And then you won't be able to
do another fusion for a while.
You follow me?
Ah, 30 minutes isn't long
enough for this kind of fight.
Actually it is,
as long as they do
the fusion correctly,
a half an hour is all they'll
need to take down Majin Buu.
This technique
really is that powerful!
Okay, now, the two of you,
I need you to become
Super Saiyans for this.
What's wrong?
[growling]
Huh...?
Listen, we wanna know.
You're supposed to be
the strongest guy in the
universe or something, right?
So why why weren't you there?
Why weren't you there
to save Gohan? Or my dad?!
I'm sorry, Trunks.
What? You're sorry?!
You could've helped!
"I'm sorry" isn't
gonna bring back my dad!
Gohan always told me
that you could do anything!
So why didn't you save
him from that Buu monster?!
Why didn't you save him?!
Don't just stand
there, say something!
What can I say?
Look, I wish I was the
strongest guy in the universe.
Then I could have helped. But
I'm not. I can't beat Majin Buu.
But, with the fusion technique,
I know the two of you can!
If you'll trust me,
and you're willing to learn
what I have to show you,
we can still get that monster
for all of the
terrible things he's done.
I'm game.
Okay.
[BABIDI laughs]
[BABIDI using ESP] Your
attention please, Earthlings!
It's me again!
The great wizard Babidi,
along with my faithful
counterpart, Majin Buu.
The two of us have been out
doing a little
bit of sight seeing.
And what a glorious
site we've found.
A perfect place for Majin Buu
to grab a little snack.
[BUU]
Mm-hmm!
[BABIDI] I hear the local
cuisine is to die for!
Of course, what he
was really hungry for
was some Majunior Trunks,
and Goten a la mode.
[BABIDI laughs]
[BABIDI using ESP] Alas, I guess
we'll just have to make do.
I can't tell where he is.
What city is that?
Trust me guy--
you don't wanna know!
[PEOPLE screaming]
Why is that wizard
guy talking about us?!
I don't know, but if you close
your eyes you can see him, too!
Don't do it!
Don't close your eyes!
[yells]
[BABIDI] You all know what
I want. I'm lis-ten-ing!
Which means you still have time
to tell me where
my quarry is hiding.
I'll give you until I finish
speaking this sentence.
To late! Ha! It looks like
Buu gets to have that snack.
Yes! But what should he eat?
I'm sure he's had more than
enough candy for one day.
Hold on, I think
I know just the thing
to hit the spot, chocolate!
Oh-ho!
[screaming]
Ooh.
[laughs]
Whoa-ho!
[screaming]
Buu want chocolate!
[screams]
[screaming]
[laughs]
What's happening?!
[GOTEN] He's really gonna
eat all those people!
[GOTEN, TRUNKS scream]
Hey, uh, was that Cindy
and Janet I just saw?
Yeah, I think it was.
What's going on out there?!
[MR. SATAN] What are you
guys whining about?
[growls]
[MR. SATAN]
A true martial artist
is never distracted
from the task at hand.
Only a fool
dwells on foolish things.
Now get your minds focused
and back to my training!
Yes!
Human beings can fly,
it's just that our bodies
have forgotten how to do it.
We have to re-teach ourselves,
just like Videl did.
Okay, let go!
And release me now!
Come on, body of mine, wake up
and remember your lost powers!
[screams, grunts]
[screams]
[grunts]
Mr. Satan, hurry,
we need your help!
[gasps]
I've told you over a dozen times
never to open that door
when we are training!
I'm so sorry, sir,
but you have to see this!
[gasps]
What's all this?
--[chanting] Mr. Satan!
--[WOMAN] It's our hero!
--Mr. Satan! Mr. Satan!
--Our savior! Please protect us!
--[chanting continues]
--Yo, Mr. Satan!
--Mr. Satan! Mr. Satan!
--I gotta challenge for you!
--[chanting]
--Won't you defeat Majin Buu?!
[chanting]
Mr. Satan! Mr. Satan!
It's certainly
easier said than done.
Mr. Satan, you rock!
Please, save us!
You are truly an
example to us all!
[CROWD cheers]
--Mr. Satan! Mr. Satan!
--[MR. SATAN growls]
[yells]
[MR. SATAN]
My people, my people!
You have nothing to fear.
It can be revealed now.
I have been secretly training,
and am now in the
middle of developing
a devastating
new fighting technique.
Once I have mastered
this new method,
I will possess strength
far beyond that of anyone.
And then, like the mighty lion
hiding in the shadows,
I shall pounce on
and completely destroy
this evil beast
called Majin Buu!
[MR. SATAN laughs]
[thinking]
Oh no, what am I doing?!
[burps]
No, they'll destroy it all!
[BABIDI]
Well, the fun is over here.
It seems that Majin Buu
is actually full for once.
I guess that means the next city
will have to settle for being
pummeled into oblivion.
Okay, time for us to move on.
[TRUNKS using ESP]
Babidi, Majin Buu!
Huh?!
Can you hear me? This is Trunks!
And I'm Goten!
So, the two of you have
decided to find some courage.
No, we've decided to find you,
and you don't wanna know what
we've got in store for that day.
It won't be pretty!
You two stop talking
to him or he'll find us!
[BABIDI] Hello? Where are
you boys? Where'd you go?
Come out, come out,
wherever you are.
[BABIDI laughs]
I think it's time we got
started. What do you say?
[BOTH]
Mm-hmm.
[NARRATOR] Having witnessed
Babidi's horrific spectacle
of mass destruction,
Goten and Trunks are ready
to do whatever it takes
to stop the wizard
once and for all.
And if Goku is right,
these young Super Saiyans may be
the only ones who can do it!
Can they master
the fusion technique
before Majin Buu claims
any more innocent lives?
Stay tuned for scenes from
the next Dragon Ball Z!