[NARRATOR] Previously
on Dragon Ball Z,
Goku's battle with Cell
came to a stunning conclusion!
But the Cell Games
were far from over.
The fighters waited
with bated breath
as Goku prepared to
name the next challenger!
Someone he claimed
would put the evil
android down for good!
But who could it be?
[GOKU] That someone is you, Son.
[NARRATOR] Gohan!
[CELL] Ridiculous!
[NARRATOR] Has Goku
lost his mind?
[GOKU] Whadda you say, Son?
Go out there and win
this one for me, okay?
[NARRATOR] It seemed our hero
was asking the impossible!
But young Gohan was determined.
[GOHAN] Okay, Dad. I'll do it.
[NARRATOR] With a
dazzling display,
the pint-sized Super Saiyan
took the Cell Games by storm,
unleashing incredible energy
that far surpassed
anyone's expectations.
Well, almost anyone...
Frustrated by Gohan's
extraordinary abilities,
Cell's attacks appeared to grow
increasingly out of control.
[BOTH grunting]
[CELL] Well, I'm impressed!
You're pretty fast, aren't you?
What do you say we try
speeding things up a notch?
[NARRATOR] But the vile
creature quickly regained
his handle on the situation,
and soon had the rest of the
Z Fighters fearing the worst.
[TRUNKS] He's losing!
Don't you even care? Huh?
Goku, if you don't do something
right now, Gohan is gonna die!
[NARRATOR] Does this
brave young warrior
really stand a chance
against Cell?
Get ready to find out
today on Dragon Ball Z!
[GOHAN growls]
Well, Gohan, I see
you're ready for round two.
[KRILLIN] Will somebody
please tell me
we're gonna get
Gohan outta there?!
Somebody? Anybody?!
Oh man, I don't believe this!
Are we really gonna just stand
here and watch him die? Are we?!
Gohan!
Gohan, darling! Please!
You don't have to do this!
Oh... I don't want you to die!
[CHICHI sobs]
ChiChi...
Darn you, Goku!
You promised me you wouldn't let
our baby boy fight that monster!
Oh, my Gohan!
My precious baby
boy is going to die!
[CHICHI sobs]
I'm never going
to see him again!
ChiChi, don't say that!
[ANNOUNCER gasps]
[PIIZA] Is that little boy
really going to fight with Cell?
I am thinking
this kid is hamburger!
[GOHAN] I'm ready when
you are, you creep.
[CELL chuckles]
[GOHAN gasps]
[CELL growls,
GOHAN yells]
[CELL yells]
[GOHAN screams]
Hold still!
[CELL growls]
Unreal! Ladies and gentlemen,
I can hardly believe my eyes!
It seems that
the delivery boy has
resumed his fight against Cell!
But I'm afraid our
young hero may be
in over his head this time!
Dude, that kid
is gonna get nuked!
[WOMAN] That poor boy!
[KING FURRY] Mmm...
Your majesty!
I have a division
of troops ready to deploy.
We'll stop that creature.
Nonsense!
I won't allow it.
Your troops are no
match for that monster!
But... But sire!
No. I will not send
any more men to their graves.
Look, General...
Already this young
boy has proven himself
more effective against
Cell than our entire military.
It would seem that all
of our hopes rest with him now.
I only pray that he is
able to do, what my army cannot.
[CELL laughs]
[GOHAN gasps]
[grunts]
[CELL yells]
[CELL growls]
C'mon, hang in there, Gohan!
Cell's too strong!
[CELL growls]
[GOHAN gasps]
[CELL yells]
[GOHAN screams]
[GOHAN grunts]
[screaming]
[ALL gasp]
Gohan!
Good fight, kid.
But I'm afraid to say,
like all good things,
it must come to an end.
[CELL yells]
[GOHAN screams]
[PICCOLO] No, Gohan!
It's... It's over.
He's gone!
That was almost too easy.
[CELL chuckles]
Then again, it always is.
[CHICHI sighs]
ChiChi! Oh my gosh!
[whimpering]
Ah... Oh, the horror,
ladies and gentlemen!
Our valiant young delivery
boy has surely met his end!
Buried beneath tons
and tons of solid rock!
[CROWD gasping]
[MAN B] He's dead?!
[WOMAN B] That's just awful!
[CROWD gasping]
[VEGETA growls]
[PICCOLO growls]
Goku, you fool! We told
you this would happen!
We told you! But you
wouldn't listen to us!
Well, maybe you'll hear this:
Your son's dead, Goku!
HE'S DEAD!
You're wrong, Piccolo. Can't you
sense his energy? He's fine.
[PICCOLO] Huh?!
Huh?
Wait! I feel it, too!
Well, Goku! It would
appear that I have won.
Now, are you going
to fight me or not?!
Nope! Take a look behind you!
What now?
[GOHAN screams]
[TRUNKS gasps]
Gohan!
Ha! Way to stay alive, bro!
[CELL growls]
[CELL] Well,
maybe I misjudged you.
It seems you've
got a lot more nerve
than I gave you credit for!
We don't have to do this.
This fight, Cell.
It's meaningless.
Huh?
[CELL chuckles]
[laughing]
You sound just like your father!
Do you honestly think
I'll stop my Cell Games
just because you
think they're meaningless?!
Yes.
Well, think again!
Let me explain something
to you: you have to fight!
Unless you beat me here today,
I'll destroy the Earth!
Now how's that for "meaning"?
I'm telling you I don't
want to fight anymore, Cell.
Even though you're evil,
I really have no
desire to kill you.
Wow, check it out.
Gohan looks intense!
Wish I knew what he was saying.
Hey, can you hear him
through that mic?
No, they're
talking way too quiet!
You don't have to continue
this senseless violence.
You can put an end to all
of it right now. I don't want--
You don't want to fight.
Yes, I understand that!
Now, correct me if I'm wrong,
but did I just hear you
threaten to kill me?
Interesting.
And what makes you think
you can carry out this threat?
Really, do tell.
I know now what my father meant,
I know now why I'm the
only one who can take you down!
Don't make me laugh.
You can't touch me, kid.
No, maybe not right now.
But I think it's
important that you know
exactly what's going
to happen if you push me.
[GOHAN] When I
was just a little boy,
a Saiyan warrior named
Raditz came to the Earth.
He was a lot like you, Cell.
He enjoyed hurting others.
Especially my dad.
[GOKU screams]
[GOHAN] Raditz continued
his ruthless torture,
and I was trapped,
helpless inside
of his spaceship.
But I could still
hear my father's screams.
[RADITZ] Just a
sentimental dope!
You're way too soft to be
a Saiyan Warrior anyway!
No fair!
I suppose you're right, Kakarot,
but I'm a first-class warrior,
and I won't hesitate to even
kill my own brother if need be.
Now, say goodbye!
[RADITZ grunts,
GOKU screams]
[GOKU screams]
[CHILD GOHAN] Daddy!
[GOHAN] Each time
he cried out in agony,
my heart cried out
along with him.
The pain I felt at not being
able to help him was maddening.
[GOHAN] Then something happened.
Something snapped.
[RADITZ] Huh?
[GOHAN] The pain that I felt
became so great that I,
I lost myself in it.
The furious blinding force
began to surge through me,
and I knew only one thing:
I had to help my dad,
no matter what.
[RADITZ gasps]
[RADITZ] Power level
one thousand
three hundred and seventy?!
Impossible for a kid!
And yet, it's going up!
[CHILD GOHAN growls]
Leave my dad ALONE!
[CHILD GOHAN screams]
[RADITZ yells]
[GOHAN] That was the
first time I discovered
that I had a hidden power,
but I still had no idea where it
had come from or how to use it.
Fortunately, those
were things that
Piccolo was determined
to teach me.
[CHILD GOHAN wails]
Quiet! I can't take that
noise anymore, you hear?!
[CHILD GOHAN gasps
Perhaps you don't
even realize it yourself,
but there is an enormous
power within you, Gohan.
The purpose of
your training will be
to teach you to
control your power.
My power? What
do you mean by that?
Heh!
Let me show you!
[CHILD GOHAN screams]
[CHILD GOHAN] HEY!
What are you doing?!
[GOHAN] I think Piccolo
recognized my power
for what it was.
He knew the only way
it would surface was
if I was faced with a crisis
so great that I had
no other choice but to use it.
This wasn't a voluntary
decision on my part.
It was more like a feeling,
a gut reaction to a
situation beyond my control.
Once again, I lost myself,
and the power emerged.
[GOHAN] Piccolo knew
this would happen.
Wow! No way!
[GOHAN] But I don't think
even he expected
my power to be as
great as it was.
[GOHAN] I would learn even more
about my hidden abilities
while we were on Namek
fighting against Frieza.
Krillin!
[CHILD GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN]
Krillin was hurt really bad,
but I knew that there
was still a chance to save him!
I tried to get to
him as fast as I could,
but before I had
a chance to do anything,
Frieza was right
there... laughing.
[FRIEZA laughs]
Do you really
think you can save him?
Sorry. it's too late!
[GOHAN] Krillin, my friend,
was sinking to the bottom
of that lake dying.
And Frieza, that
cold-blooded monster,
was actually enjoying it!
I couldn't control what
happened next. I attacked!
I didn't care that Frieza
was the most powerful
fighter in the universe.
I didn't care
that he had the ability
to destroy entire planets
with a single finger.
All I knew was that
I had to help my friend!
And the only way to him
was through Frieza!
[CHILD GOHAN yelling]
[CHILD GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN] I still don't
know how it happened.
My memories of those moments
aren't really all that clear.
I was lost in a
raging storm of emotion,
unable to control my actions.
It's like a switch
had been pulled.
Something opened
up deep inside of me,
and once it opened,
nothing could stop
my power from
raging to the surface!
For those few moments,
I was an unstoppable force!
[CHILD GOHAN] Masenko... Ha!
[GOHAN] Once unleashed,
the hidden power within
me was enough to bring Frieza,
the most terrible tyrant
the universe has ever known,
crashing to his knees!
That was a long time ago
and since then I've
gotten much stronger.
My dad even thinks
I'm as strong as he is now!
He took that
into account, I think.
I think he realized that
if I were to be pushed too far,
if I were to lose control,
there's no telling how
powerful I'd become.
And there's no
telling what kind of damage
a power like that might cause.
[CELL chuckles]
[laughing]
[CELL] An interesting story!
But it didn't work.
Huh...?
Well, not in
the way you intended.
But you have given
me something to work for.
You see, Gohan, this "hidden
power" of yours intrigues me,
and now that I know about it,
I'm determined
to see it for myself!
[CELL grunts]
[GOHAN groans]
[CELL yells]
[CELL growls]
[CELL laughs,
GOHAN grunts]
Oh no!
[KRILLIN] Goku,
you can't let this go on!
Cell doesn't wanna fight Gohan,
he wants to fight you!
Goku!
Don't worry, Krillin.
Gohan's going to win.
Trust me, 'kay? He's fine.
Go on! What's stopping you?
Give in to your anger!
Lose control!
Show me your hidden power!
It's the only way
to save yourself!
[CELL] You stubborn
child! Get mad!
[CELL snarls]
[yelling]
[CELL] Do you hear me?!
I want you to be FURIOUS!
[CELL grunting,
blows landing]
[GOHAN screams]
[GOHAN grunts]
And Cell has just
delivered the delivery boy
another ferocious attack!
How much more abuse
can this noble lad withstand?
Mr. Satan, what
are your thoughts?!
I think this boy doesn't
even have a chance!
He oughtta let
a man finish the job!
Oooh! Does this mean
that the champ's gonna fight?!
[MR. SATAN squeals]
Get ready! Mr. Satan, the
greatest fighter in the world
is about to enter the ring!
[MR. SATAN gasps]
[ANNOUNCER] That's right!
Oh! The pain! It's my
stomach again! Oh... aahhh!
[PIROZHKI] Maestro!
Once again, the champ
has fallen victim
to a strange stomach pain!
[screaming]
Huh...?
Ladies and gentlemen,
this fearless announcer
continues to risk
life and limb
to bring you the action!
[GOHAN growls]
[BOTH grunt]
[CELL] Come on!
Show me your power!
Defend yourself!
[CELL grunts]
[GOHAN yells]
[CELL yells]
[GOHAN shouts,
CELL grunts]
Yeah! Way to
stick it to him, Gohan!
[PICCOLO growls]
[VEGETA growls]
[CELL grunting]
[CELL growls]
[GOHAN growls]
Well then. It looks like I may
actually get through to you yet.
[thinking] That's right, Cell.
Keep pushing.
Once you back
Gohan into the corner,
he's not going to have anywhere
to go except right through you.
[NARRATOR] While the others look
on anxiously from above,
down on the battlefield,
the test of will rages on!
Cell has fixed
his icy stare on Gohan,
but the young Super
Saiyan stands firm!
His iron determination,
the only thing between the
Earth and total annihilation!
Will Gohan awaken his
incredible hidden power
and put an end to the
evil android once and for all?
There's only
one way to find out!
Don't miss the next
exciting episode of
Dragon Ball Z!