[NARRATOR]
Last time, on Dragon Ball Z...
The efforts of Gohan
and the Supreme Kai
to destroy the ball encasing
Majin Buu proved useless.
[NARRATOR] And the magic
creature that had lain dormant
since human kind's
infancy was unleashed.
[NARRATOR] Both sides were
perplexed when nothing appeared
from the ball but a
barren cloud of smoke.
Sighs of relief were
short-lived, however,
as the spiraling cloud soon took
the shape of the
bizarre Majin Buu.
Buuuuuu!
[NARRATOR]
Make that very, very bizarre...
Pudgy, pink,
and with a wide grin
that seemed incapable
of leaving his face,
it was easy to doubt Buu's label
as the single-greatest
threat to the universe.
Awww...
[NARRATOR] But despite doubts
from Gohan and the others,
the horrified
Supreme Kai was certain
this was the Buu of the past.
Yes, that's Bibidi's
creation without a doubt.
I could never forget that
disgusting creature's face.
Buu!
[NARRATOR] Long ago,
Majin Buu was responsible
for the destruction
of entire galaxies...
But what is the extent
of his power now?
Could a creature so
simpleminded and childish
really pose a threat to the
battle-hardened Z Fighters?
Buu! [giggles]
[NARRATOR] Gohan stands
ready to face this new threat,
while Dabura and Babidi,
after their long struggle
to resurrect a creature
they'd never seen,
remain speechless
at its curious result.
[NARRATOR] Is it possible
that Buu's strength
has weakened during
his centuries in captivity?
Has he become
outdated in his time away?
Or is there still some unknown
horror hiding behind that smile?
Buu!!
[pants]
[grunts]
Uh... Huh?
[GOKU]
Vegeta, wait!
Uh?
There, I felt
that power surge again.
Huh...? [pants]
We know that it's Majin Buu.
What we don't know is how the
others are faring against him.
[pants]
[snickers]
[VEGETA laughs]
It's as I thought, there is
nothing to worry about, Kakarot.
This Majin Buu has been
revealed as a weakling.
At least, by the measuring
bar you and I have set.
[VEGETA] Is it too hard
to understand, clown?
The Saiyan race has evolved
since that creature
was entrapped!
Think of what
the Supreme Kai said!
He's been constantly
surprised by our strength!
On Babidi's ship we conquered
what were supposed to be
the strongest
fighters in the universe,
and we barely broke a sweat!
Think about it Kakarot.
We Saiyans have taken
a ruling place in the universe
that even its greatest
overseer couldn't predict.
And Majin Buu may
have ruled in his time
but now he's sorely outclassed.
You're... wrong... I can... feel
something deeper inside him.
Enough of your feelings!
You're just stalling because
you know I'm going to beat you!
No Vegeta, I know you
can sense the same thing.
[GOKU] You're just too
proud to admit it.
[BUU hums]
[BABIDI giggles]
Look at my face, Buu!
I'm the son of Bibidi,
your creator! See?
You can call me the Great Wizard
Babidi or just Wizard or Master,
since that's what
I am to you now!
Hmmm?
[chuckles]
[nervously] See if it weren't
for me you'd still be trapped
inside of that ball forever!
Eh... Uhhmm...
[giggles nervously]
[BUU]
Hmph!
[shocked] Nyaaa?
Hey... What's the
meaning of that, Buu?
You can't turn your back
on your master like that!
At least give me a proper
greeting! Turn around!
I command you!
[BUU grumbles]
What's wrong?
Is something incorrect
with your body, Buu?
Hahahahaha!
[pants]
[growls]
He is but a fool!
[GOHAN]
What's happening over there?
Is he playing with them?!
What nerve!
It is difficult to say why.
But his revival has
clearly been incomplete.
I had great hopes
for this Majin Buu.
But this deformed
version is nothing
but an idiot and a waste.
Hmm?
Oh, what's wrong? Do you have
a problem with what I've said?
Buu!!!
Huh?
Pow! Pow! Pow! Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
Pow! Pow! Pow! Pow! Pow! POW!
A pity; he's not even aware
enough to know he's outmatched!
Run along Buu!
Or shall I turn you into stone?
Guess Babidi made a real
mess out of reviving him.
He's acting like an infant.
There has been no mistake,
Buu has always been this way.
Huh?
[steam whistle]
Hmm?
[snickers]
Aaa!
[chuckles]
My, what a charming trick.
[gasps]
Owww!
[gasping]
[groans]
Whoaaaaaaa!
[BUU giggles]
Buu! That was just fantastic!
[BABIDI] Oh, did you see
the way he bounced!
Why, I think
you may have killed him!
That's wonderful!
You're every bit I knew
you'd be! Every gorgeous bit!!
[GOHAN]
His... his power!
It was like he reached into a
well of energy that doesn't end!
But it felt, empty!
I just don't know
how to describe it!
You had to have
felt that one, Vegeta.
I don't think we can
take this guy for granted.
Not anymore...
[TRUNKS]
Huh?
[GOTEN]
Ah!
Hey, did you feel
that too Goten?
It's like it went
straight to my belly.
Uh-huh.
Uh, I wonder if that's
what evil feels like?
Yeah... So should we go there?
Well let's think
this through, Goten...
That way feels scary,
so it's probably more fun.
I bet it's where
that Buu monster is!
Yeah! And if he's
a real live villain
I want to see
what he looks like!
Yeah!
[TRUNKS] Last one
there is a monkey brain!
--[GOTEN] Hey!!
--[TRUNKS laughs]
[MR. SATAN sighs]
Hmmm...
[thinking] Oh man, what on
earth happened out there today?
[MR. SATAN thinking]
Those were the guys, I know it!
The ones from seven years ago.
But, I thought they
were gone, or dead,
or at least staying
away from tournaments.
Heh heh heh heh...
[MR. SATAN thinking]
And that one fellow...
How could he have done that?
He killed those people---
My fans!
And with some
kind of explosion trick.
It was just like
Cell all over again!
[crowd screaming]
[snickers]
[thinking] I wonder if
the whole thing was staged?
Some promotional gimmick
that they didn't tell me about?
Hmph.
[thinking]
It felt so real, though...
And one thing I know
is that real things
usually mean something bad.
[REPORT A] Mr. Satan!
Congratulations on your victory!
[REPORTER B]
You were fabulous!
[REPORTER C] What will
you do with the prize money?
[REPORTER D]
Can you give us your angle
on what happened today?
[REPORTER E]
Do you have a plan?
Heh. Well you know I wouldn't
keep anything from my fans!
Hahahaha!
Oh...
[ooos; ahhhs]
We don't have any
time for this now Vegeta.
We're the ones who
let Buu out of his shell!
It's because of us!
[VEGETA]
Buu is just a side-show!
You are my only concern!
Everyone on Earth
will be killed!
You hear me?!
Bulma, Trunks, everyone!!
Shut up!!!
Shut... up!!!
Remember I've sold
my soul to Babidi.
I keep no loyalties.
I have a Saiyan heart
that depends on strength alone!
They're nothing to me!
Liar!
[gasps]
I don't... buy it!
Talk all you want Vegeta
but you better convince
yourself of it first.
[VEGETA]
Fine.
You win.
Our battle is postponed.
I want you at your fullest when
we fight and you're obviously
too distracted by
that ridiculous Buu.
Vegeta.
[VEGETA] Well don't just stand
there, get out your Senzu Beans!
We should be at full
power when we face him.
With all of us working together
I'm sure we can beat this guy.
[VEGETA] So Kakarot,
even you can prove helpless
when you drop your guard.
[VEGETA roars]
[VEGETA thinking] I'll take
care of this Buu myself.
The last thing I need is for
this clown to play hero again
and dangle it over my head.
We'll finish this fight
when I return, Kakarot.
Enjoy your sleep.
And should your time
run out before I'm done...
Heh heh. Then we'll have to
continue this another day.
[VEGETA]
When I see you in hell.
[BABIDI] Your revival
was a complete success!
Now we mustn't waste a second.
You must obey my every command!
With you as my tool this entire
universe will be cancelled out!
Nyaaaa!
[growls]
Lalalala!
So, do you think
it's wise to disobey me?
I'm well-versed in all
my father's incantations, Buu.
I can put you back in that ball
with a phrase if you like.
Buu?
[BABIDI] Now you
don't want to be trapped
in there again, do you Buu?
Huuuuh?
Huh? Ohhhh! Hohohoho!
--[BUU] You master!
--[BABIDI laughs]
--You! You!
--Yes, I think this...
...arrangement
will do just fine!
[GOHAN]
Supreme Kai.
Buu's definitely strong
but he's only acting
because he's afraid
of getting sealed up.
If we could just take
Babidi out of the picture...
There won't be anyone
commanding Buu
and maybe we could control him!
We mustn't, Gohan!
Babidi is the only
living being who knows
how to put Buu back
inside his ball.
Without him we'd be doomed!
That creature
might appear innocent,
but he has a deep-seated
need for destruction.
Eventually, Babidi will
lose control of him too.
When he does, he will be
forced to seal him up again.
And that will be
the time to strike.
I'm afraid we have no choice
but to wait for that moment.
Unfortunately Gohan...
The two of us probably won't
be the ones to make that move
as it looks like we will be
the first in Majin Buu's path.
I'm sorry. This isn't the
way it was supposed to be.
I was confident I could stop
Babidi before Buu was revived.
If, only I had known.
If only I had watched this part
of the universe more closely
and seen there were people
like you whose physical strength
has the potential
to far exceed my own.
Then the method
might have worked.
What method are
you talking about?
No, it's too late.
The two of us won't be
able to escape Majin Buu
to carry it out.
We'll have to rely
on Goku and Vegeta.
[GOHAN]
Oh, listen to yourself!
Are you just gonna stamp dead
on your forehead and give up!
[BABIDI]
Your attention, please!
Huh?!
Here is my first command!
Kill those two idiots.
And let's try to be
quick about it, huh?
Huh?!
Ah!
[BUU]
Buuuu!!!!
Huh?
[GOHAN]
Come on!
Don't you worry! I'm pretty
confident about my speed.
Hey what are you
standing around for?!
You're letting them get away!
[coughing]
I sure hope he comes back.
[GOHAN] Well it looks
like no one's behind us yet.
Huh?
[gasps]
Ah!
Laaaaaa!
How could he??
You drop dead!
[BUU giggles]
[NARRATOR]
To the Earth's great misfortune,
it seems Buu's revival
is a complete success!
He's put Gohan out of
commission with a single blow,
leaving the Supreme
Kai totally open to attack!
The losses are already starting,
and the anger-blinded Vegeta
is the only Z Fighter
still on his feet!
Does the side of good
even stand a chance?