[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball Z...
Majin Buu reached an all new
level of maliciousness.
He had already absorbed
Gotenks and Piccolo,
taking their power and wisdom
and transforming
into a mighty villain.
But when he sucked
up Gohan as well,
it gave him a virtually
unstoppable edge!
Goku planned to fuse with
Gohan using the Kai's Earrings,
and so had to watch
his best chance at
victory be taken, too.
And then came another.
[GOKU]
Vegeta!
All right! It's you! I knew it!
[NARRATOR] Thanks to
King Yemma's intervention,
Vegeta was back
from the Other World.
Immediately, Goku
tried persuading him
to join in a permanent fusion.
But Vegeta bore just
as much resentment
toward his old Saiyan
rival as ever,
and firmly refused.
[GOKU]
Everyone is gone!
[NARRATOR]
But in a passionate speech,
Goku asked Vegeta to lay down
their troubled Saiyan history
and look towards
a future on Earth.
And a bold decision was made.
[VEGETA]
Here, give it to me!
You bet!
To the end of the Earth!
All right! It's on!
Great! Thanks, Vegeta!
[NARRATOR]
And so, the last living Saiyans,
whose bitter rivalry has
stretched over a decade,
have dropped their swords
and fused permanently
into a new warrior.
The great battle begins.
Would you look at me?
I'm setting records.
He's dropped his guard! Great!
[gasps]
[VEGITO chuckles]
[VEGITO] Sorry about that.
Did I catch you by surprise?
What do you call a
Vegeta and a Goku?
Vegito sounds all right!
I was a little worried about
the two of us sharing a body,
but it looks like it
came out pretty good.
I guess I can live with this.
Those two I fought before
were starting to bore me.
Maybe now, I'll have
some decent competition.
[growls]
[chuckles]
Yoo-hoo!
[growls]
Cut that out!
[SUPER BUU yells]
[VEGITO yells]
[SUPER BUU groans]
[SUPER BUU grunts]
[yells]
[SUPER BUU cackles]
[chuckles]
[growls]
Thanks a lot!
That was a good warm up!
Nice bravado!
I bet you won't talk so tough
once I get my hands on you!
--[SUPER BUU cackles]
--[VEGITO yelps]
What a shame, dropping like
a fly, and I'm not even trying.
Ha...
Nice shot! That one really
got the blood flowing.
Can you throw me another?
Sorry about this,
but the body's rather new.
I'm sure you understand.
You've been stealing
people's bodies all day!
[SUPER BUU] The only thing
this two-man fusion has done
is make you twice
as foolish as before!
Funny, you think
that up yourself?
[grunts]
[gasps]
[SUPER BUU groans]
[SUPER BUU gasping, groaning]
[SUPER BUU] Curse you!
What have you done to me?!
[VEGITO] Pull yourself together,
would ya? It's humiliating.
[gasping]
[SUPER BUU cackles]
Now, that's more like it.
[MR. SATAN]
It's okay, Bee. I got ya!
[MR. SATAN] Let's just
hope this guy's got me!
Hey, buddy, uh, where
exactly are we goin'?
[DENDE]
Please, just be patient.
What? Where is that
rumblin' noise comin' from?
That's the sound of Goku
fighting with Majin Buu!
Yikes! We're not goin' over
there, are we? Say we're not!
[DENDE] We have to!
Goku might need our help!
Impressive.
So it's true that
you can do more
than just talk trash, after all.
Trash talk, huh?
Interesting phrase.
Must've picked that up
from my sons you stole!
[SUPER BUU] I don't know what
you're trying to suggest.
There's no shame in taking what
you need to hold your position.
I'm the terror of the universe!
[VEGITO] That's old news.
And, just like you,
it's about to be replaced!
[KIBITO KAI] Look at them!
They're extraordinary!
Despite all the power
Majin Buu has gained
from the other fighters,
they still fight evenly!
Evenly, you say?
Come, young Kai!
Which crystal ball have
you been looking through?
Huh?
Open your eyeballs,
and look closer!
I see! Majin Buu is
actually at a disadvantage!
In fact, that monster
can scarcely land a punch!
Oh! Our victory
is at last secured!
No, I'm afraid not!
[KIBITO KAI yelps]
There is the luck
of the moment, though!
Anything could happen
until this is through!
Honestly, I worry
about these Saiyans.
Seems their love of battle
might work against them.
But, if anyone is to defeat
Majin Buu, it will be them.
You can bet a nickel on that!
What's happening now, Elder?
I can't take the suspense!
[SUPER BUU groaning]
[grunts]
[SUPER BUU gasping]
Ugh! You fool!
You haven't beaten me yet!
[laughs, growls]
[SUPER BUU grunting]
[yells]
[CHICHI] What's the word?
Is there any news?
Did you heard from him yet?
[BULMA] Sorry, Chichi, there's
no sign of him anywhere.
Videl, have you seen
or heard anything?
No, nothing. Nobody seems
to know where he is.
I have searched many
places. But nothing!
Oh, I can't stand this!
Obviously, Gohan
must be somewhere!
[gasps]
Oh! You don't think
he was sent down below
with all of the
bad people, do you?!
Don't even think it, ChiChi!
Of all the nice guys in
the world, Gohan is--
[DABURA]
Videl is right!
Your boy has a
heart of fine gold!
I know he's around
here somewhere!
[BULMA giggles]
Huh?
Well! You certainly
have pulled a 180
since you came up here, Dabura!
If someone told me now you
were Babidi's right hand man
and the king of demons,
I'd crack up!
Thank you, Bulma.
There was a time when
evil filled my heart
and all I wanted to do
was control the universe.
But Majin Buu revealed
to me my folly.
And I intend to prove now
my heart is filled with
nothing but love.
Uh, that's so good to know.
Uh... Yeah, anyway, I'm sure
that Gohan is gonna show up
really soon, ChiChi!
After all, it's a
really big place.
To try and find one person among
a hundred trillion people
isn't exactly an afternoon job!
It's gonna take a little time!
But we're all in this together.
So, we'll split into groups
and report back
every hour on the hour
until we find him, okay?
That's right.
And we promise,
we won't stop looking
until Gohan is safely
back in your arms again!
You mean it? Thanks a lot, guys.
Ah! This is a cruel,
cruel world!
I don't want you to
give up hope, my dear.
No matter what it takes,
I will make sure they
bring your boy back to you!
It's the least I can do.
[yells]
[cackles]
[VEGITO grunts]
You wouldn't? Dumb question.
Yes, isn't it, though?
Every time I have
destroyed a planet,
I have taken a piece
of its energy with me.
This orb is the culmination
of eons of destruction!
[growls]
[SUPER BUU]
We're going to play catch!
If this falls to the ground,
you can say goodbye
to this planet as well!
Are you up for the challenge?
It's all in your hands now.
Don't drop the ball!
[laughs]
I'm gonna set you
down right here!
Uh, but--
--[MR. SATAN yelps]
--[BEE yips]
[MR. SATAN thinking]
Wait! I'm the champ!
[screams]
Shh!
Please be quiet, Mr. Satan!
Or else Majin Buu will find us!
[MR. SATAN groans]
Oh, wow!
W-Who is that person?
He kinda looks like that
Goku guy, but different!
Yes, that's Goku, all right!
Except that...! Yes, I thought
I sensed Vegeta's energy!
And so, there's still hope!
Huh? What'd you mean by that?
I mean, with those
two fused together,
the Earth has a very
good chance of survival!
[laughs]
Two, right!
[MR. SATAN chuckles]
So strange...
Huh? Wait!
Come back here, Bee!
[BEE yipping]
You shouldn't be goin' off
on your own like that, boy!
[whimpers]
--[gasps]
--[MR. SATAN] Mr. Guardian...
[gasps]
How did Buu create such
a giant energy ball?
He could split the Earth
in two with that power!
[cackles]
So, are you ready to play?
Ready? That all depends
on what you mean.
If you mean, am I superior
to you in every way, then yes!
What's that?
I'm ready! Go for it!
I'll make you a wager.
You see this spot?
I won't move from it!
You're awful confident
for someone so small.
But if that's the way you
want to play this, then fine!
[SUPER BUU yells]
[ALL yelp]
[ALL whimper]
This time, you lose.
[DENDE]
Oh, no!
[VEGITO grunts]
Here! Your turn!
[gasps]
[MR. SATAN grunting]
[MR. SATAN yelps]
[MR. SATAN]
Dumb wind!
Dumb pebbles!
[MR. SATAN groans]
Mr. Satan!
[gasps]
I dare say you've been
toying with me all along!
If you could have sent that
energy ball into space,
you could've inflicted much
more damage to me earlier.
But you still don't compare.
No one compares to me!
You're wrong, Buu.
I'm destined to destroy you.
[yells]
I'm kinda stuck here, pal!
Can you lend a hand?
[yelling continues]
Huh?
Call me Super Vegito!
[growls]
[NARRATOR] Could this be
the beginning of the end
for Majin Buu?
The combined powers
of Goku and Vegeta
have proven to be
nearly unlimited.
But now, as a fused
Super Saiyan,
will they be able to
deliver the final blow?