[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
the now-teenage Gohan
set out for his
first day of high school!
There's been
no need for warriors
in the last
seven years on Earth,
so the former child hero
has been hitting his books
and training his mind instead!
[NARRATOR] Now he's trying
school with other kids,
in none other than Satan City!
[NARRATOR]
But on his way to class,
Gohan encountered a gang
of ruthless bank robbers!
[POLICEMAN gasps]
[NARRATOR] Never missing
a chance to help,
Gohan charged up
to Super Saiyan status
and stopped
the thieves himself!
[ROBBER grunts]
Amazing!
[NARRATOR] It was
a valiant step, indeed.
But when Gohan
made it to school,
he found that students were
already talking about this
mysterious "Gold Fighter!"
[NARRATOR] And the girl most
likely to discover his secret
turned out to be
a very famous daughter.
[ERASA] She's the
daughter of Mr. Satan!
What?! Mr. Satan?!
[NARRATOR] High school
may not be as simple
as Gohan thought,
since hiding his amazing powers
is proving to be
quite a tricky play!
Is it possible
for the half-Saiyan
to live a normal life?
[VIDEL] Now this is strange.
Huh. So basically,
you don't want anyone
to recognize you, right?
Yeah. That's right.
I'm just scared my
new friends will think
I'm a little weird if they
see me fighting criminals.
You think you can
help me, Bulma?
[BULMA] Well now... you could
always not fight the bad guys,
but I guess playing superhero
is too much in your blood.
So, I'll just have to
make you a disguise then.
Oh wow! You really
think you can do it?!
Gohan, remember you're
talking to a girl who
designs and builds
space capsules for a living.
I don't think a little
crime-fighter costume
is out of my reach!
Thanks, Bulma.
You're the best!
This is gonna make
school so much easier now.
Hey, don't mention it!
Oh, and Bulma!
Do you happen to know
where Trunks is?
And would you mind if I
hung out with him
while you're working on it?
Sure! Just go on back
to the gravity room!
Last I checked, he was
still training with Vegeta.
Isn't... he kinda young?
Well, I said the same thing,
but as far as
Vegeta's concerned--
if you're old enough to walk,
you're old enough to train!
He's just so dead set on making
Trunks stronger than you!
Heh heh.
Well isn't that nice...
Hey, Trunks!
[TRUNKS gasps]
Gohan! Watcha' doin'?
Eh. Just stopping by. Heh.
Looks like you've been having
a pretty tough workout!
[TRUNKS] Yeah!
Uh.
[GOHAN]
Good afternoon, Vegeta.
Long time no see!
[VEGETA scoffs]
Well, well.
Aren't you looking dull?
A true warrior should be ready,
even in times of peace.
Right...
Now, let's go have some fun!
Huh? Sure!
[BULMA] There you go, Gohan!
[TRUNKS] Ooh...
So I just press this
red button to make it work?
That's it.
Awesome! Hey, can I
have one too, Mom?
[GOHAN laughs]
This is just amazing!
Does it fit?
Yeah! Why...
it's a super fit!
No, Mom. I don't need one.
[GOHAN]
I'll see you guys later!
Thanks again, Bulma!
[TRUNKS] Bye, Gohan! Come back
to play whenever you want!
Like tomorrow, maybe!
All right, Nimbus!
I think you'd better
take me home now at full speed!
[GOHAN chuckles]
We're about to pass right over
good old Satan City!
Hey, wait...
If I go make an
appearance in my new suit,
they'll all forget
about the Gold Fighter!
I think it's about time
to give the city
something new to talk about!
I'll race you, Nimbus!
[GOHAN] Ready...!
Set...! Go!
♪
Oh come on, Nimbus!
I know you're
faster than that!
[GOHAN chuckles]
I left that cloud in the dust!
[GOHAN thinking]
The hero is on call!
Huh?
Crazy driver!
Hey, porky!
Stop hogging the road!
Drivers today
are so inconsiderate!
[GOHAN thinking]
Now say something heroic.
Stop, you fiend!
Very nice...
[RIDER] Aah, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Slow down! Slow down!
[DRIVER and RIDER yell]
[DRIVER] Aah... Aah!
What kinda' meat-head are you?!
Get out of the way!
Hey, why don't you watch
where you're goin'?!
It is you who
should be more careful!
Use your turn signals!
Follow the rules of the road
and always buckle
your safety belts!
What is this?! A public
service announcement?! Huh?
You got a name for yourself,
there, little funny man?
Huh? Do ya?!
Huh...? What? A name?
Hm, let me think...
Hmmm...
What is he doing?
He's thinking...
Got it!
Guardian of the city!
I am the one and only...
Great Saiyaman!
The... Great... Saiyaman?
[DRIVER] Uh-huh.... Hm?
[BOTH laughing]
I... I don't know
what's funnier!
Your name or your outfit!
[BOTH laughing]
Love those helmet antennas!
Does it get good reception?!
Stop... laughing!
[GOHAN yells]
[BOTH gasp]
[DRIVER and RIDER gasp, yell]
I put some thought
into that name!
[BOTH whimper]
Oh I--you misunderstood me.
I-I said it was a
very nice name and costume!
I wish I had one of my own!
[DRIVER and RIDER gasp, groan]
Thank you,
mister Great Saiyaman!
[DRIVER]
Yeah! You have a good day!
[RIDER] Drive carefully.
Drive carefully!
[GOHAN thinking]
What promising young citizens!
[CHICHI] Oh, Gohan! I've been
worried sick about you!
You could've called!
[GOHAN] Sorry, Mom.
[CHICHI] Great. Look at you!
One day with those teenagers
and you're already
coming home late and
wearing silly clothes!
[GOTEN] I'm back, Mama!
Oooh... Gohan!
Now that's a cool uniform!
Hey, thanks, Goten!
I knew you'd be on my side!
[birds chirping]
[GOTEN] Come back soon, Gohan!
Listen. Don't fly too fast.
I just want you safe.
I know.
[GOTEN] Oh wow...!
When I get big...
I hope I'm as
cool as you, Gohan!
[GOHAN chuckles]
Well, for now...
why don't you just make sure
to help Mom
around the house, okay?
See ya later, guys!
[GOHAN] And Goten!
Flying Nimbus is all yours now!
He looks so happy!
I guess I could
get used to that outfit.
Thank you, Gohan!
[GOTEN laughs]
[NARRATOR]
The young and cheerful Goten.
He is Gohan's little brother,
who Goku left with ChiChi
just before
his fight with Cell.
He's the son
Goku never got to see.
[GOHAN laughs]
[GOHAN thinking] Man...
school sure seems closer
when I fly there myself!
[GOHAN thinking] At this rate,
I'm gonna have a lot of
free time on my hands.
Hmm... Guess that means
more time for Saiyaman
to save the day!
[SCIENCE PROFESSOR] So you see,
the new energy molecule
is very complex.
In fact, well, I'm not even
sure that I understand it.
You know another
hero appeared yesterday.
Yeah, and-and stopped
some Kamikaze drivers!
Yeah. But they say
he's not the Gold Fighter.
Yeah, I heard. He's not.
[GOHAN thinking]
Yes! The news is spreading!
They say he looks kinda' funny,
but he's super strong!
Yeah, uh, they call him
the Great Singing-Man!
Saiyaman!
The Great Saiyaman!
[CLASSROOM] Huh?
How... in the world do you
know that, Gohan? Tell me.
[GLASSES BOY]
Yeah, how do you know that?
You should--
you shouldn't know that.
Because... I know someone
who really saw him.
Well now, is there something
you'd like to share
with the class, Gohan?
Uhhh... No!
[beeping]
[VIDEL] Huh?
Yes! Go ahead, Captain.
[CAPTAIN] Videl.
There's been a hijacking
in the City Bus Terminal!
A trio of hooligans
have taken over a tour bus
full of senior citizens and
are holding them all for ransom!
Aah!
You coppers better
stop your stalling
and bring us the money
or these old folks
are going to be retired!
[CAPTAIN] Videl!
You've got to help us!
[VIDEL]
Stay calm! I'm on my way!
[VIDEL] May I be excused,
Professor?! Thank you!
[SCIENCE PROFESSOR]
Well, actually I--
Okay, on ya go then.
What's wrong with her?
She sick?
No silly! She went to
fight the hijackers!
Aah! All by herself?!
Of course!
I mean she is the daughter
of Mr. Satan you know!
She's always going out there
and saving us from the nasties!
But... that's not safe!
[SHARPNER chuckles]
There's really no need
to worry, Gohan...
Videl can lift even
more weights than I can!
She's been training
her whole life
and some say she's as
strong as her father now!
[GOHAN thinking]
As strong as her... father?
[MR. SATAN growls]
[MR. SATAN yells]
[GOHAN thinking]
Ooh. Well I'm more worried
she's as weak as her father!
Hm.
And where might you be--
[GOHAN] Bathroom!
Uh...
Hero time!
[GOHAN thinking]
Guardian of the city.
I am the one and only...
Great Saiyaman!
Gosh, that sounds cool!
[GOHAN thinking] Ummm...
Where's the bus terminal?
[HOOLIGAN 2 grunts]
[HOOLIGAN 3] All righty, Boss!
We're locked and loaded!
[HOOLIGAN 1] Hmph!
We have given you the money
exactly like you asked!
Now you give us
something in return!
[HOOLIGAN 1 laughs] Gladly!
[ALL yell]
Now floor it!
[bus engine runs]
[POLICE yell]
[ALL] Freeze!
[ALL shout cheerfully]
Hold your fire!
There's hostages!
[HOOLIGAN 3] Oh yeah!
Rulin' the freeway!
Oh, this is all very exciting!
Where do you suppose
they'll be taking us?
Well... I don't have a clue.
I've never been
hijacked before!
[OLD MAN 2] This is much
better than the normal tour!
I just have to
have a picture of this
for my scrapbook!
[HOOLIGAN 3] Hey! Keep it down!
You're ruining my moment!
Now... say "cheese!"
[HOOLIGAN 3] Cheese!
[HOOLIGAN 2] Ha!
[HOOLIGAN 3]
Turn around, you goof!
Who tought you how to drive?
[HOOLIGAN 2] Sorry.
[police sirens]
[HOOLIGAN 1 laughs]
[growls] Rats!
Huh?
Look! It's Videl's helicopter!
[ALL cheering]
[HOOLIGAN 3] Huh?
[HOOLIGAN 3]
Boss! Boss! It's a copter!
[HOOLIGAN 1 grunts]
[HOOLIGAN 1 laughs]
Oooh! Now get a
picture of that, Sue!
It's Videl! She's famous!
Ha! There they are!
[VIDEL grunts]
She sure is brave!
[grunts]
Aah!
Huh?!
[VIDEL grunts]
[HOOLIGAN 1] Aah!
I just love to
watch that girl fight!
I'll have the
best scrapbook ever!
Huh? Uh.
[HOOLIGAN 2 groans]
[VIDEL yells]
[HOOLIGAN 1 and 3 groan]
Oooh! And Videl
is the winner
with three knuckle-
smashing knockouts!
[OLD WOMAN 2] Let me
take your picture, dear.
[VIDEL giggles]
Videl! Hold on!
[OLD MAN 3]
Who's driving the bus?!
Stop it!
[PASSENGERS screaming]
Ooooh...
[screaming, yelling]
Huh?
[VIDEL] What... happened?
[PASSENGERS gasping, murmuring]
[PASSENGERS cheering]
Haven't screamed
like that in years!
This was a very good tour!
Like a roller coaster! Heh.
Who are you?
Hm-hmmm! I am...
guardian of the city!
The one and only!
The Great Saiyaman!
[GOHAN thinking]
Oh yeah! That was perfect!
[VIDEL thinking]
What a weirdo...
Is this the hero
they've been talking about?
See ya later, Videl!
[GOHAN grunts]
[VIDEL thinking] Ah!
How does he know my name?
[PASSENGERS cheering]
[NARRATOR] A new masked hero
has saved the day!
Not to mention his
high school reputation.
Let's just hope Gohan
can keep his double life...
in one piece!