[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z!
When a violent aftershock
sent her Dragon Ball
tumbling
into the sea,
Bulma had
no choice
but to confront the
dangers of the deep!
[BULMA screams]
[NARRATOR] And with monstrous
creatures lurking at every turn,
Bulma quickly found
herself in deep trouble!
But the ever-resourceful girl
would not be sunk so easily!
Thanks to some
quick thinking,
and some equally
impressive piloting skills,
Bulma was able to
out-maneuver her fishy foes
and reclaim her prize!
[NARRATOR] But no sooner
had she reached the safety
of the beach that her
troubles really began!
[BULMA whimpers]
[BLUEBERRY] Where are the
rest of the Dragon Balls?!
[BULMA screams]
[RASPBERRY] Where's Vegeta?!
[BULMA whimpers]
Okay. If you don't
want to talk to us,
you can talk to
Lord Frieza instead!
F-Frieza...!
[NARRATOR] The adventure
continues today!
[BULMA] Put me down! I already
told you everything I know!
Vegeta's the one who's
got all the Dragon Balls!
Don't you get it? It doesn't
matter what you do to me!
I can't help you! I don't have
the information Frieza wants!
A-and that means...
[BULMA screams]
It means I'm
done for...
[BULMA sniffs]
This is really it,
and there's no one coming
to save me this time...
[BULMA sobbing softly]
[BULMA] I can't
believe it's over...
After all the crazy adventures
I've had in my life...
Meeting Goku and
the gang...
Finding out about
Goku's powers...
And the strange transformation
that Saiyans undergo
at the full moon...
[BULMA sobs]
[BULMA] And taking on
that awful Emperor Pilaf
and his evil
sidekicks...
[BULMA sobs softly]
[BULMA] I've had so
many close calls
searching for
the Dragon Balls...
So many close calls...
But this time...
This time...
No! Stop! Pleeeease!
I told you for the last time!
I promise I don't know
anything! Please!
[BLUEBERRY] Ah, shut up.
[BLUEBERRY gasps]
Yaah!
[BULMA screams]
[BULMA shouting]
[screams]
[BLUEBERRY] Girl, you're
getting to be a major pain!
[RASPBERRY] And don't think
all your tears and moaning
are going to get
you out of this!
We're taking you to
Frieza, and that's that.
How many times do I
have to tell you goons?!
I don't know where
the Dragon Balls are!
[BULMA sobbing]
Yeah, yeah.
We heard you already.
But I'm sure a little
visit with Frieza
will help jog
your memory.
[BULMA squeals]
[BULMA panting frantically]
[BULMA wailing]
I really wanna know.
Just what are
these Dragon Balls
that they're worth puttin'
up with all of this?!
Who knows?
And who cares?
It's not like it's our place
to ask questions, now is it?
[BULMA panting]
You mean to tell me that
you two muscle-heads
don't even know what those
Dragon Balls can do?!
Uhh... Hey, what if I
told you the Dragon Balls
could make you the most
powerful beings in the universe?
Hmph. Yeah, right.
[BULMA squeals]
[BULMA] Honest!
I'm not lying!
All you have to do is
gather the seven Dragon Balls,
and any wish you
make comes true!
Save it,
would ya?!
[BULMA whines frustratedly]
No! You don't
understand!
I'm saying
the two of you
could be even more powerful
than Frieza himself!
What?!
[BULMA] I'm telling you!
Just think about it!
Why do you
think everyone
wants to get their
hands on them so badly?
Hey...
Shut her up!
We've wasted enough time
listening to her babbling.
Yeah...
He's right!
Why are you guys standing
around wasting your time on me,
when you could be
out there collecting
Dragon Balls
for yourselves?
[RASPBERRY] Hey...
What're you doing?
Think! You can have
everything you ever wanted,
anything in your
wildest dreams!
Just one little wish,
and it's all yours!
Can't you see
the girl's lying?
[BLUEBERRY]
And what if she isn't?
[BULMA giggling]
[BLUEBERRY snickers]
[BLUEBERRY] Very interesting...
Huh? What?
Here's what I say:
If we find all the Dragon
Balls, at the very least,
Frieza's sure to
give us a big reward.
Of course... Before
we bring 'em back,
we'll try
making a wish
of our own and see
if it comes true.
Oh, and it will!
Take my word for it!
Okay then, I say it's time
we got started looking.
[BULMA gasps]
Wait... just
a sec, please...
Don't you think I'd
just slow you down?
[BLUEBERRY] You
got two choices:
You can come with us,
or I can kill you here.
[BULMA screams]
No...
[BULMA squeals]
Now, tell us
where they are.
[BULMA whimpering]
They're in the sea! They
sank to the very bottom!
[BULMA yells]
If you're lying,
then so will you!
Well, are you
coming or what?
As if I have
any choice!
[GOKU panting]
[grunting]
Kaio-ken!
Hmm!
[GOKU grunting]
There...
[GOKU growling]
Rraaugh!
Ka...
Me...
Ha...
Haaaaaa!
[GOKU screams]
[GOKU grunting]
Wow, I'm
still here...
Well, I guess
that's a good sign
that I'm making progress
with my training.
[BULMA] Ugh!
[BULMA whimpers]
[BLUEBERRY]
Oh, no you don't.
[BULMA] Hey, what do
you think you're doing?!
You can't treat
a lady like this!
You're ruining
my outfit!
We're gonna take
a little swim
and see if we can't find
those Dragon Balls.
A little swim?
Weren't you listening?
I told you, they're at the
very bottom of the sea!
Yeah, so you said.
[BULMA] Well, I hate
to spoil your plans,
but here's a
news flash:
I have a hard time
breathing underwater!
Not to mention, I'm not
wearing waterproof mascara!
Hmm?
[BULMA laughs]
Oh, yeah...
Ugh. Now what
am I gonna do?
Once they find out there
aren't any Dragon Balls here,
I'll never see
dry land again!
[BULMA screams]
[BULMA] All right,
all right!
I'm going, already!
Knock it off!
Oh, come on. Just think,
Bulma! Think!
There's gotta be some
way to outsmart these guys.
Where are they?!
[BULMA chuckles nervously]
N-Now I remember!
They're just a little
further! Over here! Come on!
[thinking] This
is the place...
I just hope they're both
stupid enough to fall for it!
[BULMA] Right this way to the
Dragon Balls, gentlemen!
Right down
the middle!
[BULMA] No, please,
after you...
Ah! Hey! What
are you doing?!
[BULMA screams]
[BULMA] So this is it.
The place I'm gonna die.
[BULMA] Wait a minute!
Let's not do anything rash!
We're almost there!
As a matter of fact,
it's just inside that cave
there... Yeah, the cave!
[BULMA]
Ah! What the...?
[BLUEBERRY] Huh...?
[BULMA] Ha, ha! See?
Just like I said!
Dragon Balls!
Hundreds of Dragon Balls!
[BULMA] Well, what the
heck are you waiting for?
An invitation!? GO!!
C'mon boys, take as
many as you like!
Then you can
make your wish!
[BLUEBERRY grunting]
[BOTH grunting]
[BULMA gasps]
Nice...
[grunting continues]
[BOTH] Huh?
[BULMA giggles]
[BLUEBERRY screaming]
[RASPBERRY] She's getting away!
[BOTH scream]
All right, Mrs. Crab,
do your stuff!
[RASPBERRY yells]
[BULMA whimpering]
[BULMA sighs]
[panting]
[BULMA screams]
[BLUEBERRY &amp; RASPBERRY growling]
Oh, I don't believe
this! I just can't win!
[BULMA gasps]
[BOTH grunting]
[BULMA screams]
Oh, man... I almost wish
I'd never heard of these
stupid Dragon Balls!
Huh?
[BULMA] Noo!
[BULMA] Krillin? Gohan?
Please hurry...
[BULMA wails]
[GOHAN] Krillin, we've
been flying for days now...
How much
farther is it?
Well, I don't
know exactly...
But I'd say we still
have a ways to go yet.
[GOHAN whines]
[KRILLIN] All right.
I guess we can risk
picking up the pace a bit.
We should be far enough
away from Vegeta now
that he won't be
able to sense us.
Yeah, and not
only that,
my dad should be getting
here any minute now!
He'll need
our help!
Well, when you put it that way,
we've got no time to lose!
Right!
[KRILLIN] Let's go!
The good news is,
at top speed,
we'll probably be
there in an hour or two.
[GOHAN chuckles]
Yeah!
[VEGETA] Hmm?!
[VEGETA] Ah! I've
found them at last!
Interesting...
Those meddling earth fools
are halfway across
the planet.
I was sure they'd
make an attempt
to steal my
Dragon Balls.
But it seems they've got
something else in mind...
Whatever they're up to,
if I lose them now,
I may not get another
chance to make them tell me
where they've hidden the
final Dragon Ball.
And if I take this
one with me,
even if their woman friend
manages to find this place
with their tracking device,
they won't get all seven.
They'll get no
mercy from me!
This time
they're dead!
[SUBORDINATE]
Lord Frieza!
We've just received a report
from the Ginyu Force!
They are currently passing
through Sector 9-0-3-4 XY.
We can expect their arrival
on the planet within the hour!
[FRIEZA]
Excellent...
And considering the
fact that Vegeta
has been keeping his
pointy little head down
for the last
few days,
I think it's
safe to assume
that he still hasn't
managed to collect
all seven of
my Dragon Balls.
Too bad for him.
Because now that the
Ginyu Force is arriving
with their scouters,
there won't be anywhere
on this miserable planet
left for him to hide.
[NARRATOR] With the
fearsome Ginyu Force
only moments away
from Planet Namek,
it seems Frieza is but
one small step away
from achieving his
ultimate goal!
But if Gohan and Krillin
can somehow elude Vegeta
long enough to reach Guru,
the Eldest Namek,
a sliver of hope
may still remain!
It's do or die!
Next Dragon Ball Z!