[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z...
The two Saiyans, the strongest
fighters in the universe,
continued their intergalactic
journey towards Earth...
Their goal, torment
the population
and wreak havoc
on the planet...
That is unless Goku and
the other Z warriors
can stop them...
But they'll have to move fast
because time is running out.
Oh man, how far does
this road go on?
It seems like there's
no end to it at all.
I've been running
for days and days...
I hope this is worth it because
it's been almost a year now
and I still haven't
found King Kai!
[NARRATOR]
Hang in there Goku,
remember you've got
Gohan and on your side.
And right now he's being
trained by Piccolo,
who is a great martial
artist in his own right!
[PICCOLO] Haaa!
[GOHAN yells]
[NARRATOR] Piccolo's methods
may seem a little rough
but compared to what
the Saiyans will do,
this training session
is a walk in the park.
If Gohan can master these
new fighting skills in time,
Earth still might
have a chance...
If he can't, then
it's all over!
Come on, Gohan!
You can do it!
It's in your
hands now...
'Cause if you can't save
the day, then who will?
[COMPUTER] Wake up, Kakarot...
Destroy all life forms...
Wake up, Kakarot...
[GOHAN yells]
[groans]
[GOHAN] Ow! My head
really hurts.
Let's take a break
for awhile, okay?
[PICCOLO]
You don't need a break!
Now stop whining and
let's get back to work.
No, really, I don't
think I can move.
Heh, heh. Yah!
[PICCOLO]
Huh?
[GOHAN laughs]
Fooled ya!
[PICCOLO] Can't you jump
any higher than that?
[PICCOLO yells]
[GOHAN]
Aaaahhh! Piccolo!
I'll make that kid
stronger than all of us!
[GOKU panting]
[hooting]
[wind blows]
Ahh...
[GOHAN giggles]
Mmm! Pineapple!
Aaaahhhhh!
[GOKU screams]
So... I think I'll
finish you off!
Aaahhhh!
Say good-bye!
[GOHAN] Nooo!
[whimpers]
Oh, man...
It was just a dream.
Don't...
hurt my Daddy!
[GOHAN grunts]
Daddy!
[PICCOLO] Hm?
Gohan!
[COMPUTER] Wake up, Kakarot...
Destroy all life forms.
Wake up, Kakarot...
[PICCOLO growls]
[footsteps]
Huh?
[growling]
So, there you are.
What are you up to?
[COMPUTER]
Wake up! Destroy!
Wake up, Kakarot!
Destroy all...
Aahh!
Huh?
[GOHAN yells frantically]
Aahhh!
[GOHAN groans]
[grunts]
Haaaa!
Huh?! Rrrgh!
Gohan!
Alright!
Split Form!
[PICCOLO]
C'mon, Gohan! Let's go back!
For your own sake, don't
try anything foolish, Gohan!
[grunts]
[PICCOLO] There's nowhere
you can go, Gohan!
Now stop this foolishness
and go back to camp!
Huh?
[GOHAN yells]
[gasps]
[OTHER PICCOLO] Oh no!
Gohan has changed!
Whaaa?!
A tail?
[frantic yelling]
His tail has grown back!
Be sure to make a
note of that, would ya?
[PICCOLO]
No problem!
I just hope he doesn't
transform again!
Not without the moon...
The moon!
[gasps]
[OTHER PICCOLO] How did
that get back up there?!
[PICCOLO]
I don't know!
Maybe some one wished it
back with the Dragon Balls.
[OTHER PICCOLO]
I don't think so!
[GOHAN growls]
[PICCOLO yells]
Darn that kid!
[GOHAN screams]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[PICCOLO yells]
[PICCOLO chuckles]
[GOHAN groans]
Huh?
[GOHAN screams frantically]
[GOHAN growls]
[grunting]
[gasps]
[GOHAN growls]
[GIANT APE GOHAN roars]
[roaring continues]
No! He's free!
[roaring]
[rumbling]
[PICCOLO]
If I don't stop him,
he's going to rip
this planet apart!
[snarls]
[roaring]
I don't know how that
moon got back up there!
But it's got to go!
[PICCOLO grunts]
[PICCOLO yells]
Impossible!
[GIANT APE GOHAN roars]
It's not real!
It's a projection!
[BULMA, OOLONG, and ROSHI]
Cheers!
[laughter]
[ROSHI] Ahh! Well, I must say
things went pretty smooth.
[burps]
We got all seven Dragon Balls
with two months to spare,
that's pretty good!
[OOLONG] Pretty dangerous,
if you ask me!
[BULMA]
Oolong, your such a coward.
I'll bet you think taking
a shower is dangerous!
Well, it is unless you have
those gritty little stickers
on the bottom of the tub
that keep you from slipping,
but no, we were
in real danger,
I hope Goku appreciates
what we did for him!
Oolong, can't you think of
anyone but yourself! Oh my?
Sorry! The pressure of
all this has gotten to me!
How 'bout
some coffee? Huh?
[OOLONG]
Huh?
Oh, no thank you,
I'm fine.
[BULMA and OOLONG]
Huh?
Nice moon tonight,
isn't it?
Yes, it's beautiful.
A full moon!
Hey, is it just me or
does something look
different about it...
Just there's
no moonlight!
[BULMA] Ah.
[roaring]
Ahh!
[PICCOLO grunts]
Now! Eat this, ape!
Aahh!
Yeah! You're definitely
a Saiyan, Gohan!
[roaring]
[thinking] I don't think
I can beat a Saiyan yet,
I need more training!
Aaahh!
[PICCOLO yells]
[thud]
[roaring]
[groaning]
[roars]
No way! How on Earth
am I going to stop him
if I can't even
get near him?
[roars]
[PICCOLO] Aaahh!
Huh?
Huh? That's it!
The projection!
It's coming from that
Saiyan space-craft!
[COMPUTER] Wake up, Kakarot!
Destroy all life forms!
Wake up Kakarot!
Goku's ship! What a legacy
to leave for his son!
Let's see if I can't bring
Gohan back down to Earth!
[PICCOLO grunts]
[grunting continues]
[roaring]
Special Beam Cannon.
[PICCOLO grunts]
[PICCOLO] You're turning out
to be a lot more trouble
than I bargained for...
And there's the root of
the problem right there!
It's this tail
of yours!
Look at him!
Sleeping like a baby.
[GOHAN snores lightly]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[PICCOLO] There!
That should take care
of you for a while
'cause I'm getting
too old for this, kid!
Sleep well, Gohan...
You'll need it.
[GOKU pants]
Whew! Hm?
No way! I must be
seeing things!
It couldn't be! It is!
It's the end!
[GOKU laughs]
I don't believe it!
Ha, ha! Ha, ha!
Woo-hoo!
[laughing continues]
[yells frantically]
Huh?
Is this some kind
of bad joke?
There's nothing here!
[GOKU] I just can't
believe it! Nothing!
Oh, wait a second! There!
That's it! King Kai must live
on that tiny little planet!
Woo-hoo!
I hope King Kai has lots
to eat! I'm starving!
[GOKU chuckles]
Check that out!
Nice wheels!
Huh?!
[straining sound]
[GOKU yells]
[grunts]
Man! I'm getting
squashed down here!
[grunting continues]
This is nuts! How could
anyone live in a place
with this
much gravity?
Ah!
Wow! Intense!
You've got to be super strong
just to stand up here! Ah!
[grunts]
I made it, now just
one... step at a time!
There's a house...
That's got to be
King Kai's place.
Almost there!
I can make it!
[grunting continues]
Wait a second!
I thought I smelled food!
Well, first things first!
[grunts]
[chuckles]
If that's like King Yemma's
fruit, I'm in for a treat!
[GOKU grunts]
I hope I can
make it up there!
Wow! Goodness gracious!
Hey, there! Are you King Kai?
[MONKEY chatters]
[thinking] Whoa! I never
woulda pegged this guy
for the ultimate
martial arts master!
[GOKU] Uh, excuse me
King Kai, my name is Goku.
I'd like to train under you,
if you'll accept me.
[GOKU's stomach growls]
[GOKU laughs]
Listen, I'm kinda
hungry, sir,
could I have a piece of
that fruit before we start?
[chatters]
Wow! That's amazing!
This strong gravity doesn't
bother you at all, does it?
[MONKEY chatters]
[loud crashing sound]
[GOKU] Hoo-boy!
Sir Isaac Newton would have
never lived to tell about it
if one of those
apples had hit him!
Hey, King Kai!
Would you mind throwing
one more apple down?
I promise I'll catch
it this time! Honest!
[MONKEY chatters]
'Kay! Ready when you are!
Aaahhh!
[loud thud]
[GOKU grunts]
Wow! I got it!
[MONKEY chatters]
Sorry, King Kai!
I was starving!
I am ready though.
Please teach me.
[chatters]
Huh?
Oh? I guess I'll follow.
[MONKEY chatters]
Wow! That'll make you
strong in this gravity!
[MONKEY chatters]
[GOKU and MONKEY chatter]
[GOKU] Hey, this is a lot harder
than it looks! Boy-o-boy!
[chattering continues]
[GOKU chatters]
[STRANGER] I thought
I'd seen it all!
Huh?
Uh, hey,
who are you?
[NARRATOR] Could Goku
have finally stumbled upon
the real King Kai?
Or has he been made
a monkey of again?
Will this mysterious character
be the one to teach him
his new martial arts skills?
To find out, don't miss
the next exciting episode
of Dragon Ball Z!