[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball Z...
I'm getting a terrible feeling.
[NARRATOR] The Supreme Kai's
fears were realized
when the seal around
Majin Buu was broken,
and the doomsday
creature from the past
materialized into life
from a strange cloud of smoke.
Buuuuuuuuuu!!!!!
[NARRATOR]
To Gohan, Buu seemed harmless
with his childlike behavior,
but the Supreme Kai knew better,
and any doubts about Buu's
powers were soon squashed...
Aaaaah!
[NARRATOR] ...when he
attacked the taunting Dabura!
The powerful King of
Demons had insulted Buu,
unimpressed by this new arrival.
And with the greatest of ease,
Buu gave Dabura a one-way ticket
into a distant cliff wall.
Oh! Did you see the
way he bounced?! Ha!
[NARRATOR] Rather than be upset
about losing his right-hand man,
Babidi was ecstatic!
To this creature
without loyalties,
it was merely a
changing of the guard.
[NARRATOR] With Majin Buu's
terrible strength confirmed,
Gohan and the Supreme Kai
made a desperate escape.
For they had become
Buu's next target.
The chase began,
and Gohan was confident he
would buy them time to regroup,
but Buu displayed another of
his talents, unmatchable speed!
Ah!
[NARRATOR] And with one
mighty hit, Gohan was out.
[NARRATOR]
Meanwhile...
It seemed Goku had convinced
Vegeta to postpone their fight
and stop Majin Buu,
[NARRATOR] But the Saiyan
Prince preyed once again
on Goku's trust.
Vowing to destroy
Buu without any help,
he has knocked Goku unconscious,
and taken the last Senzu Bean.
But the immediate concern is
this: The Supreme Kai is alone,
and must face his greatest fear!
Ah... Ah...
[snickers]
Yes, now torture him Majin Buu!
Make that purple
rat scared like a baby!
[GOHAN grunts]
[thinking]
Gohan...
Haha. Haha. Buuu!
Huh?
[BUU giggles]
[SUPREME KAI]
Do you remember me Buu?
Hyaaaaaahh!
Haahhh...
[snickers]
[BUU]
Down! Down!
Pow! Pow! Pow! Pow!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
Huh?
It's no use!
Aaaaaaugh!
He's getting butchered!
[laughs]
Oh Buu, you are a beauty!
[cackles]
Yes! Yes!
[GOHAN]
Aaaaaah!
[GOHAN groans]
I'm not letting you down!
[BUU] You grounded drop dead!
Nya! Nya! Buu has win!
Pow! Pow! Pow! Pow!
Pow! Pow! Pow! POW!!
[SUPREME KAI groans]
[BUU]
Hello! You back!
Huh?
Woo! Hoohoohoo!
[BUU]
I drop you down you went dead!
Now you back!
I drop you more! [laughs]
Buu!
You'll stop this!
[BUU]
No stop!
[grunts]
No stop! No stop!
No stop! No no no no!
Hyarrrgh!
[BUU]
Whoa!
[SUPREME KAI thinking]
Yes. That should hold him.
Eh heh! Hahaha! Wooo!
Uh...?
[BUU]
Haha! Me try!
Ah hahaha!
[screaming]
Aaaaaughh!
Hmmm...
--[screaming gets louder]
--Huh?
[BABIDI]
Watch out! Not this way!!
Ow!
[exhales]
Huh?
Well what do we have here? Has
the rat Kai come back so soon?
That's funny. [snickers]
I thought you were running away!
Oh look! You seem to be
in a great amount of pain!
Oh, what a
terrible misfortune!
Buuuuu!!
Huh?
No, Buu! Watch out!
[screams]
What's going on here Kai?
You taking a nap on the job?
I don't know how a guy like you
got so high up
on the food chain!
[BABIDI laughs]
He's out folks!
Can't go another inch!
Maybe I should be polite
and give him a mercy killing!
Hahahaha!
[distant cry]
Huh?
It's me, Supreme Kai.
Let's get out of here.
Darn it! Mocking him
was just getting fun!
[gasps]
Hohohoho!
[GOHAN thinking]
What is this thing?!
His skin just absorbs
everything I give him!
You a big pest! You leave!
Watch out for his blast!
[screams]
[SUPREME KAI]
He'll.. die...
[cackles]
And that's the end of you!
You're headed
straight into outer space!
[SUPREME KAI thinking] Stay
down, Gohan they won't find you.
Hey, you didn't do
something tricky now, did you?
[SUPREME KAI thinking] You
have to keep on living, Gohan...
You could be our best hope.
[MR. SATAN thinking]
All right all right,
so, uh, the guys from
the Cell Games are back.
Well, a couple of them, and...
But where did all those
other weirdos come from, and...?
And why was my Videl acting so
chummy with that pretty boy one?
And he had the nerve
to go off and start flying,
which means he
must've been a trickster,
or some kind of evil alien!
And Videl is
absolutely not allowed
to go out with evil alien boys!
No way!!
Ah, huh? Huh?!
Oh, hold on a second!
Something doesn't add up here!
Huh? If only tricksters
and aliens can fly,
then how was my daughter
up in the air with them?
Hey! Now I understand it!
Human beings must've been
capable of flying all along!
Obviously it's just a matter of
sufficient upper body strength!
So of course the world
champion can do it no sweat!
[MR. SATAN]
All right! Here I go!
[MR. SATAN] Well, uh,
it's kind of cold out there.
[clears throat]
[chuckles]
Those know-nothing
losers think they're so cool,
but it probably took
them a couple decades
just to build up the
arm muscles it takes to fly!
Too bad they're not here
to watch me learn in one day!
Hyaaaaahh!
Uhhhff...
[grunts]
I must have just slipped. Yeah.
Doh...!
[MR. SATAN]
Huh?
Oh... Uh, hi... I'm the second
vice president of your fan club.
We said we'd come by.
Oh yeah of course,
just come on in!
I was perfecting my world-famous
carpet-diving attack technique!
Yeah... Carpet...
Heh heh... Yeah...
[chuckles]
What a wonderful day this is!
Though I fully plan
to rip you into pieces.
Let me first say thank you.
After all, if it weren't for all
the incredibly strong
fighters you brought me
I wouldn't have been able to
bring Majin Buu back to life!
[BABIDI laughs]
Normally I'd let my one of
my slaves do the dirty work...
But to show you my appreciation
I think I'll kill you myself!
See what a marvelous
circle this is?
You killed my father
and now I kill you!
[groans]
Huh?!
Bah! Forget the circle.
Hey Buu, what do you
say you finish off this rat
for me like you were supposed
to do in the first place?!
Buu! I'm ordering!
--Ooooh... Ordering...
--[stomach growls]
Hah?!
I have hungry now!
Buu eat him now yes?!
Huh?
[giggles]
That's just terrific.
Eating him up!
[cackles]
What an appropriate
end! Lost in your belly!
Yes! What are
you waiting for Buu?!
Eat every single bit of him!
Don't even let a strand
of his hair escape
your gorgeous stomach!
[giggles]
♪ Ha haha ha ha! ♪
Oh!
Augh!
Wha... What in the
world is that thing?!!
Oh...
Aaaagh!
Wha...?
[DABURA pants]
[BABIDI] Dabura! Have you gone
absolutely insane over there?!
I just really hope for your sake
that you were aiming
that spear at the Kai!
Arrgh!
We must be really close now.
That weird feeling's
stronger than ever.
[GOTEN]
It makes my stomach feel funny.
Look Goten!
There they are straight ahead!
Huh?
Hahaha!
Landing time!
Yeah!
Goten, let's rest
from being Super Saiyans
and try to find them
like we're secret agents!
Yeah!
[TRUNKS] Mysterious... I don't
know any of the guys down there!
Wait... Isn't that
Mr. Shin there on the ground?
[TRUNKS]
Mr. who?
[GOTEN]
Shin!
I saw my brother talk
to him at the tournament!
Oh! Yeah that's right!
He looks pretty torn up.
I wonder if he's done for!
[GOTEN]
Hmmm...
Which do you think
is the Buu monster?
The red guy, or the pink guy?
Well.. I'm not exactly sure.
It's hard to tell when
we're this far away.
So Goten... you think you're
brave enough to get closer?
Well maybe...
Hey, where are you going?
[BABIDI] Oh, of all
the stupid mindless...
Gee, I don't
understand any of this!
If all the
bad guys are over here
then where did
everybody else go?
I don't know.
Uh... Could that
be them, Trunks?
[TRUNKS]
What do you mean that?
That that right
there! Just look!
Huh?
It looks like a person.
Then, let's go and check it out!
Oh!
It's Piccolo.
[TRUNKS] I see!
It's just a statue of him!
Oh, that scared me for a second!
Haha!
[TRUNKS] Whoever did
this was really good!
It looks just like him!
They even got his cape!
[GOTEN]
Ohhh...
Hey Trunks, it looks like they
made a statue of Krillin too!
Well that's weird.
Uh...
Uh, oh... Whoopsie!
Trunks! That looked expensive!
Uhhh...
[TRUNKS]
Do you think they heard us?
[GOTEN]
I guess not.
[TRUNKS]
Whew...
Good. I thought I
was gonna get in trouble!
[GOTEN]
You still broke it.
[growls]
Babidi...
Don't be such a fool.
This Majin Buu creature
is far too powerful
to be kept under
your control for long.
If, he is allowed to keep
reaching into his power.
It will only be a matter of
time before he destroys you.
Make the best
decision of your life
and help me crush
him while we can!
Dabura, Dabura, Dabura,
Dabura. Are you CRAZY?!!
Huh?
There is no us anymore,
don't you understand?!
He has been my life ambition
and now that he's here,
you are nothing!!
Master Babidi.
And you hurt him!
Oh! Majin Buu! Do you
think that you'll be okay?
Huh?
What is this thing??!
Oh! Ahahahaha!
Yes! It's incredible!
My father was a genius wizard
just like I've always said!
Now new plan... Now I eat you!
[NARRATOR]
The situation on Earth
is looking
increasingly hopeless!
The Supreme Kai has his
face pressed in the dirt,
and could be
killed in any moment!
While Dabura's surprising
mutiny has turned up shallow!
And Buu plans to
somehow swallow him whole!
[NARRATOR]
Elsewhere, two of the Saiyans
most likely to stop this menace
have been knocked unconscious!
[NARRATOR]
And what of Vegeta?
When will he make
his promised move?