[GOKU yells]
[NARRATOR] Last time,
on Dragon Ball Z!
Having spent the
last of his strength,
Goku was powerless to free
himself from the clutches
of Vegeta's
death-grip...
But help was
on the way!
It's just up ahead!
[NARRATOR] Gohan and Krillin
returned to the battlefield,
in the hopes of saving Goku
from this crushing defeat.
Goku's in pretty bad shape.
Come on! We have to move fast!
Put my dad down,
right now!
[NARRATOR] While Gohan
distracted the giant ape,
Krillin readied
a surprise attack!
Destructo Disk!
[NARRATOR] But despite
Krillin's heroic effort,
the blast intended to
slice off Vegeta's tail
and end his monstrous
transformation missed its mark.
Suddenly, an unexpected
hero burst onto the scene
with a surprise
attack of his own!
In one fell swoop,
Vegeta's tail was gone,
and so was his
grip on Goku!
[APE VEGETA groaning]
[NARRATOR] Now, as Vegeta
returns to normal once more,
his powers
drastically reduced,
Goku has one final plan
to defeat the evil Saiyan.
He has passed the
remaining energy
from the Spirit
Bomb to Krillin.
The question is, can
Krillin hit his target?
Another miss
spells disaster...
Today, on
Dragon Ball Z!
Rraaugh!
Clear your mind, Krillin.
Don't try to force it...
Let it flow
through you...
Wow, I did it!
Um... what did I do?
[GOKU] It's a Spirit Bomb.
King Kai taught me...
Listen, you
can do this..
I know you can...
But, you have to be careful.
We only get
one... one shot.
Right. Got it!
I promise... I'll do my best!
He's just
way too strong.
If my dad couldn't
beat him,
then how am I supposed to
do it? I'm just a kid!
[KRILLIN] All right... This
should be a good vantage point.
[thinking] It looks like
this brat's almost used up
all his energy...
Hah! He's mine.
[ROSHI]
This is amazing!
Gohan's running stride for
stride with that alien!
Gohan's going to
win! Isn't he, Dad?
Well, uh, you know,
it's possib--
Honey, I can't say
that for sure, but...
Let's yell!
It helps!
[OOLONG] Yeah!
C'mon, Gohan!
[ROSHI] C'mon, son!
Hey, ChiChi...
[CHICHI sobbing]
ChiChi...
[sobbing continues]
[OOLONG] Look!
They're at it again!
[BULMA]
They're moving so fast!
[CHICHI] What happened?
They disappeared!
You! Do your hocus-pocus!
Change the channel!
Whatever it takes to get
them back on, do it!
Do you hear me,
old woman?!
Oh... Oh...
My aching back.
What's gotten into you?
Put me down this instant!
You people are crazy,
that's all there is to it!
Alright now, let's
see what we can do!
Hoya, boya, boo!
Rrgh... Hraagh!
Masenko... HA!
Ha! That trick
again, huh?
One more!
Haa!
[GOHAN] Haah! Yaah!
Hyaah! Haah!
Man, how am I ever
gonna hit him?
He's moving
way too fast!
[KING KAI] Don't use your eyes
when throwing the Spirit Bomb!
Feel it out!
Trust in your senses!
You'll know when
the moment is right!
Hey! Who's there?
[KING KAI] I am the one
who trained Goku!
I taught him how to
use the Sprit Bomb!
Wow, it's King Kai!
[KING KAI] I did not expect
this turn of events,
but you are now in
control of the Spirit Bomb!
Remember, it
contains the hope
of every person
on your planet!
The fate of the entire planet
is resting in my hands! Whoa...
[VEGETA laughing]
I've got to
hand it to you,
your strength
is surprising!
Yes, you should be proud...
You fought well...
But, unfortunately for
you, it wasn't well enough.
[KRILLIN] Oh, man!
He's got his back turned!
Maybe I should
throw it now!
[thinking] No...
[thinking] King Kai said I'd
know when the moment was right!
[GOHAN whimpering]
It's time we put
an end to this.
Rraaaugh!
[VEGETA growling]
[GOHAN shouting]
[growling continues]
[shouting continues]
You can't
run forever!
[thinking] Damn!
Gohan's in trouble!
But, I can't throw
it yet... Not yet!
[VEGETA growling]
[GOHAN screaming]
[YAJIROBE thinking]
Krillin, you idiot!
That's some nice
energy you got there,
but you might as well
stand up and shout:
Here I am!
Doesn't anyone know
how to sneak around?
[VEGETA laughing]
I hope you're watching this,
Kakarot! Get a good look!
Because it's the last time
you're going to see your son!
That was it!
Krillin, what are you
waiting for you dope!
Just throw the darn
thing, will ya?
Here goes nothin'!
What... is that thing?!
C'mon, hit!
Ahh! I missed him!
[OOLONG] Look!
[ALL gasping]
[screaming]
My crystal ball's gone!
I think I'm going to be sick!
Ahh... but...
Gohan!
[KING KAI] Goku! Try a rebound!
[thinking] Gohan!
It's Dad! Can you hear me?
Huh?
[thinking]
Bounce it back, Gohan!
That ball won't hurt you if
there's no evil in your heart!
You have to
bounce it back!
No!
Huh?!
Ahh! No!
[VEGETA screaming]
[screaming continues]
[KING KAI] Oh, my...
I... I don't believe it...
They did it!
Yahoo!
Yeeaah!
Ha, ha, ha! Goku!
He did it! He did it!
[KRILLIN laughing]
Ahhh...
[BABA]
That's just great!
I come here to help
and look what happens!
Roshi... You don't have any
of that Turbo-glue, do you?
Turbo-glue? Wait... I must
have something you can use.
[CHICHI]
What about my Gohan?
Isn't there anything
you can do, Baba?
Don't you have
another crystal ball,
a spare one
or something?!
ChiChi, stop that!
But, Daddy, little
Gohan's still out there...
So is Goku!
I know that...
But, honey, there's
just nothing we can do
to help from here.
Well, in that case, I guess
we'll have to go to them!
Ah! You mean it?
But, how will we get there?
In the air boat!
Great idea, Bulma!
Thanks a lot!
You're welcome, ChiChi.
Now, we'd better get moving.
I'm not sure if there's
anything we can do to help,
but, at least it's better than
sitting here doing nothing!
All right,
I got some glue...
[KORIN] But is
it Turbo-Glue?
[ALL gasping]
It's...
It's Korin!
[KORIN chuckling]
[ROSHI] Good thing Ox
King decided not to come.
We'd never
have enough space!
[BULMA] Well, I'm just
glad I don't have to sit
next to that pig, Oolong...
He's such a coward.
[GOHAN] Dad... are you
going to be okay?
Yeah, but I'll probably
be sore for a while.
Well, I gotta admit, I have
seen you look better...
[GOKU] Maybe so. But it
could be a lot worse.
Yeah... You could
be that alien!
[ALL laughing]
Huh?
[GOHAN] What in
the world?
No! It can't be!
Hey, maybe now
he's harmless.
Heh... Now I can
claim my prize.
[KRILLIN] He looks
finished, alright...
I guess that blast
really did him in...
Good thing, cause he
was bad to the core.
At least now we won't
have to look at
his ugly
face any more...
Whose face
is ugly?!
[KRILLIN whimpering]
[GOHAN yells]
[GOKU gasps]
Aahh!
[KING KAI] Ah! The
Spirit Bomb didn't work!
No! I didn't
foresee this!
The Saiyan is tougher
than I ever imagined!
[VEGETA] I suppose you think
you're very clever, don't you?
Well here's a
piece of advice...
If you're going to shoot
someone in the back,
make sure and
finish them off!
It's going to be my
greatest pleasure
wiping you and your
worthless friends
off the face
of this planet.
[VEGETA] Raaugh!
How does it feel
knowing you had one chance
to save your precious Earth
and everyone on it,
only to fail miserably?
[VEGETA laughing]
Hey, come on now...
Keep it straight.
[BULMA]
Back seat driver!
Bulma! You could at least try
to show some manners here!
Don't you have any idea
who you're speaking to?
Hm? I dunno. He looks like
an ordinary house cat to me.
[coughs]
[ROSHI] Bulma!
This is it, Kakarot.
No more tricks. No more games.
No more chances for you
and your friends to escape.
[GOHAN whimpering]
I'm done
toying with you...
I'm going to do now
what I should have done
from the very beginning.
I'm going to blast all of you
insolent pests into oblivion!
[GOHAN whimpering]
Run, Gohan... Run!
Goku...
[VEGETA growling]
[VEGETA yelling]
[VEGETA] This is pathetic!
How could I be
reduced to this?
[VEGETA] I don't have enough
energy to complete the attack!
They're still alive!
That last attack must have
damaged me more than I thought.
I need to end this...
Aaugh!
It... can't be!
He has... He has a tail!
Yeah, his tail...
I forgot about that.
It must have
grown back...
[VEGETA] The Blutz Waves!
I can't allow this brat
to transform! I can't!
[NARRATOR] What startling
new development is this?
Gohan's tail has
suddenly grown back,
and its appearance has
sent a wave of terror
through the otherwise
unshakeable Vegeta!
All eyes are on the
evil Saiyan warrior
as he towers over
the unconscious Gohan.
For with Vegeta's
next move,
the fate of the
world will be decided!
[NARRATOR] Tune in next time,
as the epic battle reaches
its Earth-shaking
conclusion...
on Dragon Ball Z!