[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z!
[NARRATOR] The Androids have
picked themselves up a new van
and they're getting ready
to go for a little drive.
Their final destination:
Goku's house!
And if they have their way,
they'll see to it that Goku
is dead on their arrival!
[NARRATOR] However,
Piccolo might have something
to say about that.
He's returned to
Kami's Lookout in the hopes
of merging with the aging
Guardian of the Earth.
Once reunited,
these two powerful forces
will form a
single "Super Namek",
strong enough to stop
the Androids in their tracks!
Meanwhile, the gang
is moving Goku
to a safer location.
[YAMCHA] I think Goku
has packed on a few pounds.
[KRILLIN] Give him a break!
He hasn't been himself lately!
[NARRATOR] Can they keep
the ailing Goku hidden
from the Androids?
Find out today!
[ROSHI]
All right, Chiaotzu!
Let's see if
this soup of yours
passes the
"Master Roshi Taste Test"!
[OOLONG] Well it
smells good to me!
That's for sure!
[slurping]
[ROSHI] Not too bad...
[CHIAOTZU growls]
[slurping]
[CHIAOTZU]
Well, how is it?
Great!
[CHIAOTZU gasps]
[ROSHI] That was
delicious, Chiaotzu!
You really know how to
make a fine bowl of soup!
Thanks, Master Roshi!
[slurping]
[OOLONG] Mmm!
This might be the best
soup I've ever had!
Please tell me there's some
more where this came from!
I could go for a couple
helpings of seconds!
And maybe even
some thirds, too!
Where did you learn
to cook like that?
I used to cook for Tien
when he was training
and I came up with
a few of my own recipes...
Here's a thought!
Why don't you stay here
and train with us, Chiaotzu!
Huh?! Stay with you?
Sure, you could stay here
and train with all of us!
Train?! C'mon, admit it!
The only reason
you want him to stay
is so he'll cook for you!
[ROSHI] That's ridiculous!
I-I just thought it
would be nice if he--
[OOLONG] Nice if
he cooked for you!
[ROSHI] That's not true!
[OOLONG] Huh?
[CHIAOTZU] Tien!
[OOLONG] Oh... Hey there, Tien!
Chiaotzu... we're leaving.
Huh...?
[TIEN] We have to get
back to our training.
Hey, wait a minute!
Fill us in, at least!
Were you able to take
care of those Androids?
Well, what then?!
What happened?! Tell us!
Tien? Is everyone okay?
Everyone's fine...
You don't have
to worry about them...
Krillin is on his way
here now with Goku
and he'll
explain everything.
They'll be safe with you...
No, wait!
You can't go!
[CHIAOTZU] Hey, wait up Tien!
I'd say something terrible
has happened out there!
[ROSHI growls]
[KRILLIN] Look at it
this way, Gohan.
It's all just a game
to these Androids.
And until they've found
Goku and destroyed him,
the game's not over.
Are they really
that powerful, Krillin?
[KRILLIN] Afraid so, bro.
They're even more powerful
than the Androids
Trunks told us about!
Huh...?
[YAMCHA] But I thought
those were the Androids
Trunks told us about!
[TRUNKS]
No. They're different somehow.
[CHICHI screams]
[ALL gasp]
Oh no! What in the
world was I thinking?!
We don't have
a minute to waste!
We've got to hurry!
Before it's too late!
What are you talking about?
[CHICHI grunts]
Well, let's hit
those books, Gohan!
[GOHAN gasps]
I can't study now!
Don't you dare
talk back to me!
Now go to it!
Wow, Gohan!
And I thought I had it rough!
Hey! What do we do now?!
Beats me, Yamcha.
I'm all outta ideas...
Well, maybe there's
something I can do to help.
[CHICHI growls]
[TRUNKS] I could travel to
the past in my time machine
and destroy the Androids
before Dr. Gero has
a chance to activate them!
It shouldn't be that hard
now that I know
where his laboratory is!
Hey, yeah! That's a great idea!
Hold on...
I don't think I like
the idea of you going
after the Androids
by yourself...
No...
What if something goes wrong?
Besides, didn't you once
say that your time capsule
only had enough energy
to make one more trip?
I mean, how would
you make it back home?
You could be trapped
in the past forever!
Maybe...
Hey, if you go
back to the past
and destroy the Androids
before Dr. Gero wakes them up,
what happens to the Androids
that are here in this time?
They wouldn't just
vanish, would they?
Because if changing
the past makes them vanish,
what happens to the re--?
Gohan, that's none
of your business.
You mind your studies!
No! He's right!
What was I thinking?!
Huh...?
If I go back in time
and destroy the Androids,
I can only save
the future of that world!
But I can't change anything
that they've already done
once they've been activated!
Which means there's really
no point in me going back!
Can you try that in English?
Ah, alright... let's see...
You know how Goku is alive now
because of the medicine that
I brought back from the future?
Well, in the future world
that the medicine came from,
Goku didn't make it!
That's because I can only
change one reality, not both...
Huh?
In other words, there are
two realities out there.
In one of them Goku survives,
in the other, well...
Let's just say
he wasn't so lucky.
Let me try to understand this.
[KRILLIN] You're saying
that even if Goku
beats the Androids
in our world,
they'd still be alive in
your world of the future?
Boy, that sounds
like some kind
of a parallel
universe or something!
[TRUNKS] Exactly!
So then, why'd
you bother to come
back in the
first place, Trunks?
You just said you
couldn't change anything.
--Hm?
--Huh?
My mother...
You see, it was my mother's idea
to send me back to the past.
She didn't think
there was anything more
we could do to help
the people in our world...
But she knew there were
others we could help!
Maybe we can't change
what the Androids have
done to this world, Trunks,
but I think I know of a way
we can make a better world.
A peaceful world,
free of the Androids forever!
[TRUNKS] I agreed with my mother
that I should travel
back in time,
but I had my own reasons
for wanting to go.
I hoped that in the past,
with Goku's help,
I would find the Androids
had some weakness.
That way, I could
go back to the future,
and even though
I still wouldn't be able
to bring back all
those already gone,
I might be able to save
the people who are left!
Huh...?
[WOMAN cries,
GIRL whimpers]
[TRUNKS whimpers,
MOTHER sobs]
[KRILLIN] Trunks!
Trunks! Trunks!
[TRUNKS gasps]
[KRILLIN] Are you okay, man?
Ah... Sorry about that.
Anyway, I thought this whole
plan would work out perfectly,
except that
I didn't count on
there being such
major differences
between the timelines
of my world and this world.
I thought Goku's
heart problems
would come much
earlier than they did.
And I only thought there
would be two androids,
but instead there's three.
And now everything's
going wrong!
[TRUNKS yells]
[VEGETA grunts]
[VEGETA] No, don't!
[TRUNKS yells]
[TRUNKS &amp; VEGETA grunt]
[TRUNKS growls]
But... there's still
something that bugs me.
How could you have
miscalculated so--
I don't know...
I wish I did!
I guess something...
changes when you travel
back from the future?
[CHICHI] Try not
to worry, Trunks.
If you hadn't come
when you did,
Goku wouldn't
be alive right now.
And, that's all
that really matters.
Yeah, she's right,
you know. We all owe ya!
Yeah... we owe you big time!
[KRILLIN laughs]
[KRILLIN] So I guess
we all should look
on the bright side
once in awhile, huh?
I mean, we're all safe
and sound thanks to... me!
[KRILLIN laughs]
[KRILLIN] Hey, Trunks,
lighten up!
I was just kidding! Really...
[ANDROID 18] I'm enjoying
the scenery 17,
but, one question:
Where is Goku?
Relax, 18, we'll be there
before you know it.
That's no answer.
Admit it!
You have no idea
where we're going!
Goku's house is in
the mountain village,
East District 439.
Wow! I'm impressed!
Did Dr. Gero tell you that?
He did.
We will get there
faster if we fly.
You're right! That's
what I've been saying.
It makes no sense
for us to drive.
What a complete waste of time!
Chill out, 18.
It's not a waste of time
if we're having fun.
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU] Who are you?
What do you want?
Wait... I know you...
Androids! How did
you find me here?!
Easy!
All we had to do was listen
for your whimpering!
We came to put you
out of your misery!
Why, you...
[KRILLIN] Hold it right there!
[GOHAN] One step closer
and you'll be sorry!
Gohan! Krillin!
It looks like these
two mean business!
Let's get
this over with.
No, don't!
[GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN grunt]
[GOKU gasps]
[GOKU growls]
You! You're going
to pay for that!
Perhaps... although
it's highly unlikely.
[ANDROID 18 giggles]
[GOKU growls]
[yelling]
Huh...?!
[CHICHI] Stop it!
Stop it right now!
ChiChi!
[ANDROID 18] Stop?
I don't think so.
[CHICHI grunts]
What did you think
would happen?
[GOKU yells]
[bones crack]
[GOKU] ChiChi! No!
[GOKU sobs]
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU yells]
Huh?!
No, Trunks!
[ANDROID 18]
Well, look who's here!
[TRUNKS growls]
[GOKU] Wait! Trunks! Stop!
[bones crack]
[TRUNKS gasps,
slicing]
[TRUNKS rasps]
[GOKU yells]
You monsters!
[ANDROID 17] Look!
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU gasps]
[GOKU] What's... going on?!
[ANDROID 17 chuckles]
That's enough!
[GOKU screams]
[GOHAN] Dad!
Just hang in there, Goku!
Get out of the way!
[GOKU yells]
[KRILLIN] Phew... Well, it looks
like he's resting again...
How intense... Even in his
dreams, he's still fighting.
Yeah... you're right.
But then--
that's Goku for you.
[ANDROID 18's voice echoing]
Tell me, Vegeta,
what is it like to feel
this kind of pain?
He'll be cleaning
you up off the highway...
How sad... to work
so hard for so little...
How sad...
Such a little man...
He'll be cleaning you
up off the highway...
To work so hard for so little...
He'll be cleaning you
up off the highway...
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA screams]
[screams echoing]
No...
The Super Saiyans of legend
were an invincible warrior race!
I am their son!
And at long last I have
risen to claim my birthright.
I have stepped into the
ranks of greatness!
All my life I have worked
toward this goal, and for what?
To be brushed aside as easily as
a common housefly by an Android?
A true Super Saiyan
would not have fallen.
Maybe I'm not
who I think I am...
[VEGETA] Perhaps there are still
new plateaus for me to reach.
Far greater heights
to which I must ascend!
Yes!
I will ascend!
The universe will marvel to see
the ultimate Saiyan
potential once again realized!
And I will be... legendary!
And then Kakarot...
Then I will see you bow
before your prince...
[YAMCHA] It looks like we'll
be at Master Roshi's island
in no time.
Oh, and Krillin?
Don't you think we'd better
tell Bulma what we're up to?
Good idea...
Wait, are you saying
that I should call her?
No way!
C'mon Krillin,
I'm flying the plane here.
Thanks, buddy.
Alright...
No offense, man.
Your mom's just hard
to deal with sometimes.
[TRUNKS laughs]
Believe me,
I know what you mean!
[receiver rings]
[OPERATOR] Capsule Corp.
Oh, hello? This is
Krillin speaking.
I was wondering if I
could speak to Bulma.
[OPERATOR]
Bulma? Yes.
Please hold while
I transfer your call.
Thank you.
[receiver plays music]
[BULMA] Krillin?! What's wrong?!
Is everyone alright?!
Talk to me!
I've been so worried.
Where are you calling from?
I've tried calling Gohan at
his house and there's no answer.
It just rings and rings.
By the way,
is my son there?
I-I mean Trunks?
You know, the one
from the future...?
Huh?
Yeah, ah, he's sitting
right behind me.
He is?!
Well then, put him on the line!
He can hear you on the speaker
so go ahead and say whatever
you need to say, Bulma!
[BULMA] Well, tell him
we received a call today
from this guy who lives out
in the middle of the country,
somewhere to the
west of here.
He claims he found
some sort of weird,
old abandoned vehicle
and wants to keep it.
But he doesn't know
how to fly the thing
so he phoned us and
asked us if we knew.
Yeah, go on...
He tried to explain what
kind of vehicle it was,
but he didn't make any sense.
Well, we didn't know for sure
if it was one of our
products or not,
but he swore to me that it had
"Capsule Corporation"
written right across it.
So we asked him to
send us a picture of it.
I couldn't believe my
eyes when I saw it!
It was a picture of the time
machine Trunks came in,
and I've got some
bad news for you:
It was a wreck!
Huh?!
B-But that can't be true!
Here, look! I put it up!
I put it back into its
capsule when I landed!
He says the time
machine's right here!
Seriously?
But then... well, the time
capsule in the picture...
It's the same... but I guess
it does look like it's been
sitting there for a while.
It's almost completely
overgrown with moss and stuff.
So exactly how
many time machines
did we make in the future?
H-How many?
Well, we barely
managed to make one.
[BULMA] What? That's strange.
I'm sure this is a time
machine in the picture.
But I want to make sure.
Hang on. I'll just send
you a copy of the photo
through the fax.
Trunks, I want you to
take a good look at it.
Here. Check it out.
Huh?!
That's my capsule!
There's no mistaking it, guys!
That's the one
I came back in!
Wait a second...
What's going on here?!
[NARRATOR] Is this in fact the
time capsule Trunks arrived in?
Or is someone playing a
cruel joke on our heroes?
There's only one
way to find out:
Tune in next time for
another exciting episode
of Dragonball Z!