[NARRATOR] Previously
on Dragon Ball Z,
finally pushed to his
limit by Cell's evil antics,
Gohan was able to restrain
himself no longer.
In an awesome
explosion of energy,
Gohan's power
raged to the surface,
and left the other Z Fighters
gasping in it's wake.
[NARRATOR] Even the
impish Cell Jrs.
were frozen in fear
as they witnessed
the event Goku had
predicted from the start.
That's right, at long last
the sleeper had awakened!
Gohan was reborn!
[GOHAN] Cell!
I can never forgive you
for what you've done.
[CELL laughs]
[CELL] At last, you've
come out of hiding!
Now the game will
really get exciting!
[NARRATOR] But Gohan had
no more time for words.
He snapped into action,
and in a flash,
recovered the stolen
Senzu Beans from Cell.
Then, the mighty young
Super Saiyan set his sights
on the seven Cell Jrs.
still on the loose.
[CELL JR. grunts]
[screaming]
[GOHAN yells]
[CELL JR. gasps]
[NARRATOR] As Goku
watched his son with pride,
Gohan taught the
pesky Cell Jrs.
what it was like to take
on someone their own size.
And in no time at all,
Gohan had ground every one of
the devilish dwarves into dust.
[GOHAN] Here, pass
these around, Trunks.
Sure.
[NARRATOR] Now that
Gohan's friends are out
of immediate danger,
the valiant young warrior
has turned his attention
to the source
of all this suffering.
And as Cell braces himself
for the conflict to come,
Gohan stands the calm
center of the raging storm,
a look of deadly
determination in his eyes.
Don't miss the
ultimate showdown,
today on Dragon Ball Z!
[CELL growls]
Hey! Hey, Krillin! Are you okay?
Don't worry,
I'll fix you right up.
[KRILLIN grunts weakly]
Huh...?
[KRILLIN] T-Trunks,
G-Gohan is...
...is amazing!
He's transformed
into a whole new person.
[KRILLIN whimpers]
Wow! I can't believe
how much he's changed!
It's like he
suddenly became a man!
Yeah! You got that right.
Listen up, guys.
I think that it's time
we all cleared out of here!
I'll stay behind and give Goku
and Piccolo each a Senzu Bean.
[TRUNKS] Go!
Now...
--[GOHAN growls]
--Yes!
Huh?!
[CELL growls]
[GOHAN grunts]
[TRUNKS] Huh?!
[BOTH gasp]
[CELL yells]
[CELL grunts]
Aargh! Stop mocking me!
[CELL growls]
--[GOHAN grunts]
--[CELL grunts]
[CELL growls]
[blows landing]
[CELL snarling]
It's... It's like
Gohan isn't even trying!
[PICCOLO] Ha! Now I get it!
Yes! I was wondering
why you fought Cell first,
when you knew that
you couldn't win.
You went first because
you wanted Gohan
to see how Cell
fought, didn't you?
Is that true, Goku?
[GOKU chuckles]
[CELL yells]
[CELL growls]
[BOTH scream]
Holy cow!
I apologize we can't
show you any pictures,
ladies and gentlemen,
what, with our only
camera still on the fritz,
but I sure hope
you can hear me!
The battle between
the pint-sized kid
and Cell is really
heating up, and so far,
it looks like
the kid is on top!
What a pro!
That's right, folks!
It looks as though
this tiny titan
may take Cell down
once and for all!
You're not holding the mic!
[ANNOUNCER] Hah?!
Agh! Noo!
Argh!
[CROWD murmuring]
What's going to happen to us?!
Don't you get it?!
There isn't anyone who can
beat Cell except Mr. Satan!
What if he's
not strong enough...?
Oh, it's all over!
I think you're right, lady...
We're doomed.
Hey! Let's get out
of here, Pirozhki!
I'll simply die if I
lose any more teeth!
[PIROZHKI whimpers]
I can't move my legs!
Ohh-kay, I admit this
kid is good, but still.
He owes me big time!
I mean, if it
weren't for me,
there's no way he'd
be winning right now!
[CELL growls]
[BOTH grunting]
[CARONI screams]
[PIROZHKI whimpers]
[PIIZA whimpers]
[CELL snarls]
Huh...?
You're mine!
[CELL yells]
Mama...!
[yelling continues]
[CELL growls]
[CELL grunting]
[PIROZHKI grunts]
[CELL growls]
How did he do that?!
[ANNOUNCER gasps]
[CELL growls]
Why, you...
That's it, Gohan.
Well, it looks like watching
your fight with Cell
has really helped him out.
Thanks, but I doubt that.
Right now, Gohan's
way beyond needing my help.
He is?
Yeah, I'd say. He's winning.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, it's almost
too good to be true!
[thinking] No,
this is maddening!
It's bad enough that Kakarot
has surpassed me in power,
but now his son has too?!
Hm?!
[TRUNKS] Here, take this.
Ragh!
I hate when I'm
forced to take these!
[VEGETA growls]
[CELL snarls]
[GOHAN grunts]
[CELL growls]
[CELL yells]
Why do my punches
always miss you?!
[CELL growls]
Enough of this!
[yelling]
[CELL gasps]
[CELL] Huh?!
[CELL growls]
[CELL] You!
[CELL yelling]
[CELL growls]
I've had it!
Don't get too confident!
For I have yet to show
you, young warrior,
what I'm truly capable of!
But you will see soon enough.
Can it.
[CELL gasps]
Ahh... A cheeky one.
Well, then, let's see
how you fair against me
when I fight at full strength.
No!
What? You mean he wasn't
even trying up 'til now?!
Oh, great!
Where is that fiend
hiding all of his power?
He's only bluffing.
He's trying to scare Gohan!
[PICCOLO growls]
[CELL yells]
[VEGETA grunts]
[MR. SATAN grunts]
[screaming]
[yelling continues]
Th-Th-This is just another
one of his tricks!
That's it! Just a horrible
illusion a-and n-nothing more!
I've been waiting
for you to turn it up.
[TRUNKS] Well, I guess this
shoots my theory
out the window!
Incredible!
Don't give up now, Gohan!
[BOTH grunting]
[TIEN] I don't believe this!
[YAMCHA] It seems like
it's getting stronger!
[KRILLIN grunts]
The whole planet's
gonna explode!
[CROWD gasping, murmuring]
What's happening?!
I-It's all over!
This is it, we're doomed!
I knew this would happen!
I-It's the end of the
world! It's really here!
[CHICHI] Oh no! Gohan!
What happened to my baby?!
[CHICHI whimpers]
[CHICHI] Dad!
[CELL roars]
[VEGETA grunts]
[screaming]
[CELL yells]
[yelling continues]
[MR. SATAN grunts]
It looks like it's time to find
out what Cell can really do.
It's amazing! He's making
the whole Earth shake!
This freak's totally
out of control!
But how d'ya stop
something like that?
[CELL yells]
Go! Do it, Gohan!
So, kid, are you
impressed by what you see?
Is that all you've got?
Huh...?
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL growls]
Man, he's quick!
His speed has increased as
much as his power! Incredible!
Huh?!
[CELL gasps]
[CELL snarls]
[grunting]
[CELL rasps]
[CELL grunting, wheezing]
[CELL growls]
[CELL yells,
grunts]
[grunting]
This... can't be...!
[CELL groans]
He only had two punches
that made contact!
So why am I su... so damaged?!
[CELL groans]
[VEGETA growls]
I've got a feeling that
Gohan just won it all, you guys!
Remember, Krillin: it's
not over 'til it's over!
I don't want to jinx him, but
I think Krillin might be right!
[NARRATOR]
With two mighty blows,
Gohan has brought the
once seemingly invincible Cell
to his knees!
But as Piccolo says, "It's
not over until it's over."
And while Gohan may
be in control of the moment,
he has yet to win the day!
Don't miss the
next Dragon Ball Z!