[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
a wish to the
Eternal Dragon of Earth,
was used to revive all
of Frieza's victims
on the planet Namek.
[NARRATOR] Even Guru
was brought back to life
which meant that Porunga,
the Eternal Dragon of Namek,
would also rise again,
since it was interrupted
before it was able to
grant a third and final wish.
[PORUNGA roars]
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, Goku and
Frieza were going head-to-head
in a vicious clash of energies!
It seemed that the
winner of this battle
was going to win the whole war.
Goku was holding his own when
Frieza launched a sneak attack
that buried the Super Saiyan in
the rocks and molten lava below.
Has Frieza managed
to defeat our hero?
Find out today!
Why am I not surprised?
You Saiyans are
like a stubborn virus.
And now the virus has
mutated to preserve itself!
But I know how to treat it!
I know how to blot
it out for good!
You should have never
come back here, you know.
I really thought you were dead.
You could have left
this place and escaped.
I would have never known it!
No way! Why run from somebody
that you're not scared of?
Huh! Just for that one...
I'm going to blow you to pieces!
Just like that little bald guy!
[FRIEZA giggles]
That little bald guy
was my best friend!
His name was Krillin!
Yeah, how could I forget that?
[GOKU growls]
Now, die!
Fool! I'm not the one
who's going to die here!
Catch my drift?
[GOKU grunts]
[FRIEZA growls]
[GOKU yells]
[blows landing,
grunting]
Yaah!
Haah!
[GOKU growls]
[FRIEZA growls]
[GOKU] haah!
[KING KAI] Guru! I know
we don't have much time,
so let me get
straight to the point!
Am I correct in seeing
that the Dragon of Namek
has been revived, and is
waiting to grant a third wish?
[GURU] Yes, King Kai...
It is just as you say.
[KING KAI] Guru, please have
someone ask the Dragon
to transport everyone on
Namek to the planet Earth
except for Frieza!
[GURU] Hmm! It will be done.
Thank you for your
thoughtfulness!
It is clear you have the
well-being of my people in mind.
We are indebted to you.
I will have someone make the
wish as you have directed.
But there is no time
to lose! We must hurry!
[GOKU] No! Don't do it!
[KING KAI] Huh?!
[GURU] Huh?
[KING KAI] Goku, is that you?
[GOKU] King Kai, please make
a change in your wish!
[KING KAI] Goku, how can
you be listening to us
and fighting at the same time?
Huh?!
[GOKU] King Kai, don't have the
Dragon send me back to Earth!
[GOKU] Ask the Dragon
to send everyone to Earth
except for Frieza and me!
[KING KAI] Goku!
You can't shoulder
the whole load by yourself!
Get out of there for now!
We'll make a plan!
[GOKU &amp; FRIEZA grunting]
[GOKU] I can promise you
that any plan we made
would boil down to
this in the end anyway!
Let me face him now! It's
already happening, why stop it?
[KING KAI] Goku, I just don't
want to see you get hurt!
[GOKU] King Kai, let
go of what you want!
This is bigger
than that! Please!
[KING KAI wails]
[KING KAI] Goku!
King Kai, what's wrong?
Is something up with Goku?
Is Goku in some kind of
trouble? You can tell us!
[KING KAI growls]
Huh...?
Yo! King Kai?
[TIEN] Maybe he's
in a trance...?
[YAMCHA] King Kai?
[TIEN] Hey, King Kai?
Can you hear me?
Will you please stop
that, you silly fools?!
[KING KAI] Goku, I can't do it!
I'll be signing your
death warrant!
[GOKU] Don't let your emotions
cloud your judgement!
Search your feelings! You know
what's right deep down inside!
Feel it out and do it!
[KING KAI] Guru! I want
to change my wish!
Please have someone
ask the Dragon
to transport everyone
on Namek except Frieza
and Goku to the planet Earth!
Wow! The Dragon is back, too!
Then, I guess that
means I really am alive!
[GURU] Heh, heh, heh, heh!
What a smart boy! And so brave!
Dende! How are you, my son?
[DENDE] Guru, is that you?!
[GURU] Yes, Dende. It is I!
[DENDE] But how? I thought you
were... I thought we were...
[GURU] Dead? I've never
felt more alive, my son!
But we have work to do!
Do you see the Dragon
before you, my son?
[DENDE] Yes, Guru!
It's right in front of me!
[GURU] Good, now listen
carefully, Dende.
The lives of all of our
people are in your hands now!
[DENDE] Yes, Guru. I'm ready.
[GURU] Go to the
Dragon, Dende!
I have a wish I would
like you to make.
[GURU] Listen carefully.
Wish that everyone on Namek
be moved to the planet Earth
except for Goku and Frieza!
[DENDE] Yes!
Thanks, King Kai!
You're the greatest!
Alright, Frieza! Let's do it!
Now you're gung-ho
What's the deal?
Is your phone call over?
Good thing they reached you
before I disconnected
your number!
[BULMA] Why am I doing this?
I must be losing my mind!
Gosh, Gohan! Why'd you have
to leave? How long can I wait?
I hate being unselfish!
It's always such a drag!
Oh, kid, I would do anything
for you, you know that!
But it doesn't make sense
for us to sit here and die!
I can't take it anymore!
I've got to get out of here!
That wasn't too hard!
Here we go!
See ya later, kid.
Good luck...
Oh, man! I can't leave!
I wouldn't be able to
live with myself, would I?
Don't you have anything
to say about all this?
[thinking] Come on, Dad!
[thinking] Maybe I
didn't come back to life
Maybe this is hell...
[thinking] But my wound is
healed! How can that be...?
[VEGETA gasps]
[VEGETA chuckles]
[VEGETA grunts]
Yes, it's true! It's
true! I'm really alive!
[VEGETA laughs]
[VEGETA gasps]
Wait!
That means...
There they are...
Yes...
Just look at them go.
Astounding!
[thinking] We still
have a chance!
[KING KAI] Goku! How
many Super Saiyans
does it take to screw
in a lightbulb?
[GOKU] How many?
[KING KAI] There's no telling,
but it only takes
one to beat Frieza!
[KING KAI laughs]
[thinking] What's
he smiling about?
[KING KAI] Come
home alive, Goku!
[GOKU] Don't worry! I intend to!
Thank you, King Kai...
[thinking] The Dragon of Namek!
Excellent!
It looks as though everything's
going according to plan!
What?!
There is no plan!
[FRIEZA gasps]
[FRIEZA] Isn't that the Dragon?!
Yes!
[thinking] But how...?!
Those rotten schemers lied to
me! They tricked me somehow!
Wait a second! Maybe
it's not too late! Yes!
It's wish time!
Hm? Uh-oh!
[FRIEZA growls]
[GOKU yells]
[blows landing,
shouting]
You dirty dog!
Takes one to know one!
[blows landing,
shouting]
[VEGETA gasps]
Is that the dragon?!
[GURU] Hurry, my son!
[KING KAI] Yes! Yes!
He's almost there!
Dragon!
[PORUNGA] Yes, boy, speak!
[DENDE] I want to
make a wish now!
I can do that,
can't I?
Yes, you can!
One wish still remains!
Right! Thank you, sir!
Just make the wish, young one!
Yes, okay! I can do this!
[blows landing,
grunting]
Eternal Dragon, I'm ready
to make my wish now!
[FRIEZA yells]
[FRIEZA growls]
Oh, no! Frieza!
No, no!
Dragon, I wish for eternal
life! Grant me immortality!
[DENDE speaking in Namek]
Huh?!
Yes, very well,
I will grant it!
I will move everyone on Namek to
Earth Planet except these two!
[GOKU chuckles]
[FRIEZA gasps]
Why, you little runt!
[FRIEZA yells]
[FRIEZA growls]
[VEGETA] Frieza!
Huh?!
Wha...?
Hey! Yeah!
Welcome back, Vegeta!
I guess it's a good thing
I didn't bury you
that deep after all!
[VEGETA laughs]
[VEGETA] Well, well, well!
Kakarot, you dog!
You did it, you actually did it!
You're a Super Saiyan,
I can see it!
Now what? I-I killed you!
You must be a ghost!
[VEGETA] Can a ghost
do this? Huh, Frieza?!
[VEGETA yells]
My work is done.
[PORUNGA roars]
[FRIEZA] The Dragon Balls...
What? No! Come back!
[FRIEZA whimpers]
[FRIEZA] I waited so long...
[GOKU] You actually beat that
little guy to the punch!
But it looks like you
have to say the wish
in their native tongue!
But that was great!
You almost had it!
[FRIEZA growls]
You were so close,
I could feel it!
That green kid, I could've
sworn that I killed him!
[GOKU] Yeah, I almost forgot!
We used the Earth's Dragon Balls
to wish back everyone
that you killed!
What?!
Wait 'til I tell you the
wish we just made here!
You mean you orchestrated this
whole thing telepathically?!
I had help!
We wished that everyone
on this planet
would be moved to the planet
Earth except for the two of us!
[FRIEZA growls]
[FRIEZA screams]
[YAMCHA] King Kai!
Did it work?
Did they make the wish?
[KING KAI] Yes, everyone is
on Earth, safe and sound!
Yeah!
Right on! We did it!
[KING KAI] But Goku elected to
remain on Namek with Frieza!
Wait, what?
He insisted on
finishing his fight
with Frieza, so I
changed the wish!
What? That's crazy!
Uhh...
[GOHAN] Bulma!
Huh?!
[BULMA] Hey! Wow! Alright!
[GOHAN grunts]
[BULMA] Gohan! Why, you
little runt! You left me!
I waited, and
waited, and waited!
I'm sorry, Bulma!
Hey, no biggy,
kid! Forget it.
Where are we? This isn't Namek.
Yeah, that's for sure!
Maybe we're dead?
Maybe! But I don't
think so though...
[NAMEKS murmuring]
Hmmm...?
You're... Dende?
Yes!
Where...
Um, you're on Earth, sir!
On Earth? Where's Goku?!
[PICCOLO] Oh, no!
Hey! Goku?!
Oh, wow! Piccolo! It's me!
Gohan!
Wow! It's really you! And Dende!
That means that...
Ow! Nope, I'm alive!
Me too! I think that
someone wished us back!
[GOHAN] Wow! What about
Krillin?! Is he back too?
I'm not sure...
Yeah, right...
I guess he can't be wished back
by the Dragon more than once...
[NAMEKIANS] Guru!
--Wow! Guru's here too?!
--Oh, neato! It's Guru!
[DENDE] C'mon! Let's go!
[GOHAN] Bulma, Piccolo, come on!
[NAMEK 1] Where are we, Guru?
Yes, that's a good question.
We are on a planet
called Earth, my son.
Huh?!
What in the world? How
did we get back to Earth?!
Did Goku win, or
did Frieza beat him?!
[GURU] The two of them
are fighting as we speak,
writing the final
chapter to a story,
that neither you nor your
children will soon forget.
The Super Saiyan could
have come with us
but decided to
remain on Namek.
You see it's like this...
I can't believe this!
I was so close to Frieza
I could have
spit on him!
That Dragon was there, too!
Somebody must have wished
for this to happen!
[KING KAI] There's hardly
any time left!
Stubborn, thick-headed--!
Why are you doing
this to me, Goku?
I'm too old for
this sort of thing!
Most planets would
have blown by now!
But this is a tough, old bird,
I'll give her two more minutes!
[thinking] That's not much time!
You sealed your fate
with that stupid wish!
There's no way out for you now!
Either you perish in battle
at the hands of yours truly,
or you win, and then: Kaboom!
You die anyway because there's
no more air to breathe in space!
Sounds bad!
But I've actually been looking
forward to this moment!
Now I can fight you
without worrying
about the safety of the others!
Fool! Why worry
about such trifles?
Those peons can't even fathom
what's been taking place here!
[GOKU] I know I'm strong,
but that doesn't make
my life more important
than anyone else's!
A rare fighter indeed!
What a treat!
I'd forgotten how
exhilarating it can be!
[NARRATOR] With the Planet Namek
teetering on the
edge of destruction,
Goku and Frieza are poised
to begin the final round.
[NARRATOR] But will Goku
be able to take down Frieza
in time to make it
off the planet?
On the next
Dragon Ball Z!