[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
Majin Buu continued his
all-out assault on Vegito!
But whenever Vegito found
himself in a tight squeeze,
he always seemed
to have the answer!
[VEGITO] Hey! Don't get
so down in the dumps!
You've won every
fight you've been in!
Everyone meets their
better sooner or later!
No! I won't lose! You'll see!
[NARRATOR] When it became
clear that brute strength
would not work against Vegito,
the desperate Buu
gave up the ghost,
and resorted to a
more unorthodox method!
[SUPER BUU]
Fool! Mock me while you can!
Super Kamikaze Ghost Attack!
[VEGITO gasps]
[NARRATOR] With ghostly
Kamahameha Waves on one side
and the Gallic
Gun on the other,
it looked like
curtains for Vegito!
[SUPER BUU cackles]
So it's a silly kid's
game, huh? Well, bug off!
Too bad it's not permanent!
It's a nice improvement!
You're using your eyes
instead of feeling where I am!
[yells]
You don't like
to lose, do ya?
[NARRATOR] It was a
hurting time for Majin Buu
who couldn't even land a
blow on the mighty Vegito!
[VEGITO] It's up to you!
Do you want to continue or not?
[NARRATOR]
But was the fight really over?
[SUPER BUU]
I like your style!
You're going to
make great candy!
[gasps]
[NARRATOR]
In a flash,
the devious Majin Buu
played his trump card,
and Vegito, the seemingly
invincible Super Saiyan tandem,
was reduced to a
coffee-flavored sucker!
Buu had managed to turn
the tides once again!
[KRILLIN]
What? Goku and Vegeta!
The two greatest fighters?
Reduced to a candy drop?!
What are we gonna do now?
[KRILLIN]
There's no one left...
[KING KAI gasping]
Huh?
[gulps]
M-M-M-M-M-Me? Are you crazy?
You want me to go
and fight Majin Buu?
[KING KAI]
Well!
It's a tough call!
But you're the only
ones left! You and Yamcha!
It's not ideal, I admit!
But when the first string fails,
you've gotta send in the B-team!
But this isn't sports!
This is life!
And I lost that game
not too long ago!
I was eaten!
Do you know what it's like being
eaten by a monster like that?!
Well, do you?!
Mmm! Not really!
Well, I do! And it's bogus!
I'm not food! I'm a person!
Forget it! Hmph!
[growls]
[YAMCHA] Hey, guys!
What's up? You look tense!
Huh?
Man! This place is great!
[KRILLIN] Yamcha, what do
you think you're doing
taking a steam bath
at a time like this?
Huh?
[YAMCHA] Dude! Just chill out!
I just got all relaxed!
I don't need that
right now! Come on!
You know! Shoot!
If this place had
some pretty girls,
I wouldn't even care
about going back to Earth!
Let Majin Buu have it!
All we lack is the chicks!
[gulps]
Oh, boy! So this
is the B-team, huh?
We're in big trouble!
[SUPER BUU]
Look at the mighty warriors!
[SUPER BUU cackles]
Yes! You're both so sweet!
[cackles]
Talk to me, Buttercup!
Chastise Majin Buu!
Yes! Tell me that I'm cooked!
That it's all over!
What else? Oh, yeah!
You wanted me to admit that
I was wrong and surrender!
Oh, yes! Remember?
[cackles]
[SUPER BUU]
Time to die!
[groans]
[VEGITO] You shouldn't
hurt yourself like that!
[ALL gasping]
[SUPER BUU] H-How is this
possible? You can still speak!
[VEGITO]
I can do more than that!
It seems I've retained
all of my power!
[VEGITO grunting]
[SUPER BUU yelps]
[VEGITO] I'm no ordinary
candy! I'm a jawbreaker!
The strongest piece
of candy there is!
Don't be a fool, Majin Buu!
You can still surrender!
It's not too late!
You're nuts!
Why would I want
to surrender to you?
You're just a little sucker!
[VEGITO] You want some of this?
Well, come and get it!
But I warn you!
Attacking something so
small and fast won't be easy!
Attacking?! You've got to
be kidding! No arms! No legs!
I'm not going to attack you!
I'm going to eat you!
[VEGITO]
All right, then! Eat me! Hiya!
[groans]
[SUPER BUU groans]
[VEGITO] I told him he shoulda
given up! How embarrassing!
[SUPER BUU, VEGITO grunting]
[SUPER BUU panting]
[VEGITO]
I guess you don't have
much of a sweet-tooth
today, huh?
Well, if you're
not going to eat me,
let me show you
one of my new moves!
Pinball Attack!
[gasps]
[SUPER BUU groans]
Chow time, sweety!
[SUPER BUU groaning]
Will you stop that!
Fight like a man!
Do you see a man around?
[SUPER BUU groans]
[VEGITO] Hey! What's the matter?
I thought you wanted to eat me!
I went right into your mouth!
What else do you want? Come on!
[groans]
[VEGITO] What now, Buu?
Shall we do it again?
Or would you rather fight
me in my original form?
[VEGITO]
Huh?
Mommy?
Oh, it's me again!
Lost your appetite, huh?
Sometimes too much candy
can be a bad thing!
It's not good for ya!
[KIBITO KAI] Look! He's normal!
Whew! Oh, boy! Thank goodness!
We can breathe easy again!
Can we? As long as that
beast is still alive,
the entire physical
cosmos faces extinction!
[sighs] You're right, sir!
It's far from over yet!
All right! All right! We know
how strong you are now!
Please! Just finish
him off while you can!
[KING YEMMA grunts, sighs]
That was close!
I thought it was all over!
Those two are something else!
[BABA]
They're too cocky if you ask me!
[BABA] It must be that Vegeta!
Goku's certainly not like that!
Yes! But Vegeta is
a better tactician!
He's smart, I'll give him that!
Hopefully they'll
balance themselves out!
If we're lucky that is!
How did you get
Vegeta to cooperate?
After all, the Yemma
Lock wouldn't work
on a guy like him, would it?
[KING YEMMA]
Mmm? Well, no!
I had to rely on my charisma
and great personal magnetism!
Don't give me that look, Baba!
I am the great
King Yemma, ya know!
[KING YEMMA] Although
enormous physical strength
is my trademark,
this time, I had
to rely on my wits!
--[VEGETA] Well?
--[KING YEMMA] Hm?
Ah! You're here!
That's right!
Now what do you want?
Well, I'm sure
you've noticed by now
that you've gotten
your physical body back!
This is a rare privilege
which is reserved
for very special souls!
Usually, very good souls!
So what? Get to
the point, Yemma!
How would you
like another chance
to fight Majin Buu, Vegeta?
What?!
Of course, it's tricky!
A guy with your record!
Returning to Earth!
It's unheard of!
But, given the
extreme circumstances,
we can bend the rules!
Second chances! They're so rare!
Especially in combat!
Wouldn't you say?
But there are no guarantees!
Fighting Buu will be no picnic!
But then, you know that!
Waaaah!
[cackles]
You are a fool!
I'm going to crush you!
And throw you into the wind!
[growls]
[yells]
[screams]
That was a waste! He lived!
Darn you!
[ATTENDANT 2 screams]
Uh-oh! Look out!
[yelling]
[VEGETA panting]
Oh, dear!
[grunts]
Count me in!
I can't wait to have
another crack at him!
[VEGETA] When do I leave, King
Yemma? I'm ready when you are!
[BABA]
Well, now it all makes sense!
[KING YEMMA] It does?
What do you mean by that?
[BABA] Take a look! The walls!
The new renovations!
It's all a result
of your charisma and
personal magnetism, isn't it?
[BABA] Too bad you can't
bottle it and sell it!
You silver-tongued devil, you!
[growls]
[yells]
[SUPER BUU yells]
[SUPER BUU groans]
[SUPER BUU screams]
[chuckles]
[screams]
[SUPER BUU groans]
[VEGITO] You're coming
apart on me, Majin Buu!
Is this how you
want it to end? Huh?
So much for the tough warrior!
[SUPER BUU cackles]
[MR. SATAN] Uh-oh! I'm
afraid that's not good!
Vegito!
Ah?
[VEGITO]
Break a leg, Buu!
[gasping]
[VEGITO yells]
[screams]
[yelps, groans]
[yells]
[panting]
There, good as new!
Okay... If you say so!
Say what?
[gasps]
[SUPER BUU]
Darn you!
Fighting on an empty stomach?
I guess you don't have to worry
about those painful
punches to the gut!
[SUPER BUU growls]
Well!
[yawns] This is getting boring!
It's time to finish things up!
You think it's that
simple? Wake up!
[gags]
[VEGITO]
You wake up!
Are you so blind that you
still can't see the difference
between your power and mine?
Man! The nerve!
[VEGITO chuckles]
Yeah!
[gasps]
[VEGITO] Take ten! I'm going
to count to ten, Buu!
Say a prayer! Get something to
eat! Whatever you wanna do!
Then, you will die!
One...
Two...
Three...
You don't have to wait
if you don't want to!
Please! Charge me now if
you'd prefer! It's your call!
[VEGITO]
Four...
Five...
Six...
[SUPER BUU thinking] There's got
to be a way to kill this guy!
But how?
He's too strong
to fight head-on! Mm!
[SUPER BUU thinking]
My head tentacle!
Good. Now, listen.
This could be our last chance.
[VEGITO]
Seven...
Eight...
[VEGITO thinking]
All right, Majin Buu.
You've cursed the Earth with
your presence long enough.
Your time's about to expire.
[SUPER BUU thinking]
Yes... That's it...
Lie still.
Nine...
[VEGITO thinking]
Okay. This had better work.
[gulps]
Ten!
[gasps]
[SUPER BUU]
Now! Close!
Blast it!
[cackles]
[yells]
[cackling]
Bye-bye.
[MR. SATAN]
He-He's gone!
We're alone!
Goku, no! Vegita, come back!
[KIBITO KAI] Great galaxies!
It's over! He had it in the bag!
[KIBITO KAI] There's no one
left! It's... the end!
[laughs]
This is too good!
I beat you, fool!
No more loud mouth!
Majin Buu won!
Yes! I did it!
I did it! I did it!
[laughing]
[NARRATOR]
Down, down, down!
Deep into the bowels
of Buu they go!
Goku and Vegeta,
the two most powerful
warriors in the Universe,
have been toppled by
the infamous Majin Buu
and sealed in the wretched
slime of their living tomb!
Stay tuned for scenes from the
next episode of Dragon Ball Z!