[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
an incredible force
descended from the sky!
Piccolo and the boys
thought it was Goku,
but it was none other
than his son, Gohan!
[GOTEN]
Gohan!
[NARRATOR] And with the
confidence of his father,
Gohan arrived at the
scene to fight Majin Buu,
the seemingly invincible enemy
who had annihilated the entire
population of the Earth!
[SUPER BUU chuckles]
So, hot shot,
you want to fight Majin Buu?
[GOHAN] Fight you?
No, I wanna kill you!
[yells]
[SUPER BUU groans]
[GOHAN yells]
[NARRATOR] And without
even transforming into
a Super Saiyan, Gohan took
control of the battlefield
in commanding fashion!
[GOHAN]
Hi, nice day!
[NARRATOR] Yes, it was a nice
day to subdue the subduer,
to destroy the destroyer!
Majin Buu's evil deeds had
finally come back to haunt him!
But is the battle really over?
[gasping]
[GOHAN]
What's the matter, Booboo?
Buu! Not Buu-buu! Fool!
I'll kill you all!
[GOTEN]
Did you hear that?
Yeah! I wish he
wouldn't have said that!
Be careful, boys! He looks
like he's about to blow!
[SUPER BUU growling]
You! You're dead!
No one mocks me!
[screams]
[chuckles]
[SUPER BUU screaming]
[TRUNKS, GOTEN, PICCOLO scream]
[grunting]
[GOHAN gasps]
[ALL gasp]
[growls]
[GOHAN grunts]
[SUPER BUU gags]
[screams]
[chuckles]
[groaning]
[ALL cheering]
[TRUNKS, GOTEN]
Oh, yeah!
Give it up, you can't win!
[SUPER BUU]
So, it's you.
Huh?
[SUPER BUU]
I've known about you all along.
[GOHAN] What? What are
you talking about?
[SUPER BUU chuckles]
I mean I've been expecting you,
ever since I started
fighting those little brats.
[SUPER BUU]
Even while I was fighting,
I could sense your power
in a far away place.
Could feel it growing!
I knew you'd be coming here.
Opposites attract one another.
[SUPER BUU laughs]
Yes! Yes!
I've been waiting
for you the whole time!
I can't let a power
greater than mine exist.
Oh, yeah? Well, I understand
your feelings are hurt,
but I don't think
you have much of a choice.
It would seem that the scales
are tipped in my favor.
[SUPER BUU grunts]
He's known about
Gohan all along.
He was merely using his fight
with Gotenks as a warm up.
Uh, oh! What if he's
hiding his real power?
Goodbye. Enough is enough!
[growls]
Now you'll see what
happens to those I hate!
Stupid boy, you will pay!
[screams]
Yes! You're going to pay
for everything you did to me!
[screaming]
[continues screaming]
Go ahead, make me pay,
but if that's all
the power you've got,
you're gonna have a lot
of trouble collecting.
You're missing the point.
Huh?
[SUPER BUU chuckling]
[laugthter continues]
Oh, no!
[ALL gasp]
[SUPER BUU yells]
[BEE whimpers]
Just hang in there, Bee!
Uh... Hm?!
Bee, look! A saloon that
hasn't been destroyed!
[BEE barks]
Yes! Whoohoo!
Ahhh! Pure gold!
[BEE whines]
That's right, boy!
We did it!
We found the old
oasis in the desert!
[MR. SATAN] Aw, you're next,
pup! Don't worry!
[sighs, yells]
Now what?!
[sighs]
[sobs]
[BOTH sigh]
[sputtering]
[MR. SATAN] He... He hasn't
stopped destroying things yet?!
[BEE barks]
Whoa, look at that hole.
Thanks, Gohan.
Sure.
Oh, wow, we would'a died!
No kidding! It's gigantic!
That was really awesome, Gohan!
How did you know that he
was gonna to blow himself up?
[GOHAN]
I'm not so sure he did.
[TRUNKS, GOTEN]
What?!
[PICCOLO]
Quiet!
--[BOYS] But we thought--
--[PICCOLO] Quiet!
Well, what do you think?
Is he dead?
No way.
[TRUNKS, GOTEN]
Huh?
But he blew himself up! He was
trying to take you with him.
Yeah, that's exactly what he
wanted us to believe all right,
but that freak is still
out there somewhere.
[PICCOLO]
Are you positive?
I can't sense him.
There's no signal.
That's true, but he
must be masking it.
Hey, that means
he might be ambushing us.
Could be. He's obviously
planning something.
Hey! It doesn't matter
if he's alive, Gohan's here!
What are we worried about?
--This here's the man!
--[GOTEN] Mm hm!
Even we were stronger than Buu
when we were Super Gotenks!
[TRUNKS laughs]
[GOTEN]
No, we were about the same.
Really? Yeah,
I guess you're right!
Well, at least
Gohan can beat him.
[GOTEN]
Yeah!
Oh, by the way, how did you
manage to get so strong?
[PICCOLO chuckles]
[PICCOLO]
So breaking the Z Sword
turned out to be a
blessing in disguise.
[GOHAN]
Exactly.
[PICCOLO] It's strange how
things work out sometimes.
[GOHAN]
Yeah.
Hey, I just realized,
we're gonna be needing
the Dragon Radar.
Oh, well I had it, but then
I gave it to Piccolo. Right?
Yes, that's right, but I think
it's in my other pants pocket.
Only it doesn't make a
bit of a difference, guys.
Dende's gone, remember?
The balls are inert.
Uh! Does that mean
that they don't work?
[PICCOLO]
Mmm!
Wait a second, I think
we're jumping the gun a bit.
Feel it? It's faint,
but it's still there.
What?
Ahh! You're right,
Gohan! I sense him.
Mm! I can, too!
--Yeah! Me, too!
--[BOTH laugh]
Great! Whatd'ya say
we go track down Dende,
before our friend
Majin Buu beats us to it?
Sounds good, let's go.
[TRUNKS] Did you get
a whiff of that? Ugh.
[GOTEN]
Smells like BO.
It's Piccolo!
We shouldn't have to fly at the
back just because we're younger.
It's not fair.
Hm?
What's up? Do you see something?
Yeah, there's a man, and a dog.
[grunting]
[panting]
This must be the punishment for
all the lies I told in my life,
of fame and fortune and women!
Sorry you have to
be here with me, Bee.
Oh, it's him, huh? We're not
gonna help that guy, are we?
He's a cheater,
and he lies a lot, too.
Yes, but I think that
he's paid his dues.
Deep down, he's a decent guy.
I've been keeping
tabs on the man lately.
I don't think I can
go on anymore, Bee!
I give up. Angels,
just take me away.
[screaming]
[groaning]
[MR. SATAN] No, angel of death,
I take it back!
[MR. SATAN sputters]
[MR. SATAN]
Huh?!
Hey! It's you, Videl's friend!
Hey there Mr. S!
[MR. SATAN]
Uh, hi. Uh, thanks for the lift.
There's still one thing
that I can't quite figure out.
[GOHAN]
What's that?
How Dende managed to survive.
Buu had ample time
to hunt him down.
Huh?
[PICCOLO]
When Buu gave us the slip,
it was quite some time
before we managed to
catch up with him again.
So, even if Dende got away,
it seems Buu would've found him.
I see, but you guys
were fighting
in the Hyperbolic Time Chamber,
weren't you?
So to you, a good while
passed before you got out,
but on the outside,
that same amount of time would
equate to a couple minutes,
would it not?
[PICCOLO]
Yes, that's it!
It's obvious! Why didn't I think
of that myself? I'm such a fool!
I guess I let the stress
get to my head.
[MR. SATAN screaming]
Sorry, my friend
got carried away.
Whew! Thank you.
[TRUNKS] Don't worry about it,
it was nothing.
Huh?! Oh, wow! There he is!
[MR. SATAN screams]
[TRUNKS]
You guys, it's Dende!
[gasps]
[GOHAN]
Hey!
[DENDE]
Hi, everyone!
[PICCOLO]
Dende!
[DENDE]
Hi, Piccolo!
You're alive, I don't know how
you did it. You did well, kid!
--[GOHAN, TRUNKS laugh]
--[MR. SATAN groans]
Thanks, but if it
wasn't for Mr. Popo,
I never would've escaped.
Buu came out of the Time
Chamber through a small hole.
He was in liquid form.
--[BULMA whimpers]
-- Gross!
--Huh?!
--[DENDE gasps]
How 'bout chocolate?
[POPO]
Quickly!
No guardian, no Dragon Balls!
[DENDE]
Huh?! Ah!
Mm. Brave, Popo.
Let's just make sure that
his sacrifice wasn't in vain.
You two should be
proud of yourselves.
It was a very wise move.
You're a fine guardian, Dende.
--[GOTEN laughs]
--[DENDE] Thank you, Piccolo.
That scrawny, green elf-boy,
is he some kind of
bodyguard or somethin'?
You oaf! He's no bodyguard!
He's Guardian of the Earth.
Huh?! Really, I'll be darned!
So, where's the radar now?
Piccolo's other pants!
[GOHAN, GOTEN, TRUNKS laugh]
[inaudible]
Phew!
Goku! What do they
intend to do with the balls?
How will they
utilize the wishes?
[GOKU]
I'm not sure.
Hm. Doesn't this generation
know how to plan?
My goodness!
Do I have to do everything?
[MR. SATAN]
What?!
M-M-M-My sweet,
little Videl is dead?
[BEE whines]
[MR. SATAN]
My poor Videl!
How could Buu do that
to her? Darn him!
He was my friend!
[cries] Huh?!
What's wrong with you?
Why didn't you protect
my little girl, huh?
What kind of boyfriend
are you, huh, pal?
I wasn't there!
Hey, don't worry, Sir.
She'll come back to life.
Huh? What are you talkin' about?
She's dead, you little imp!
How you gonna bring
her back to life?
[laughing]
No joking around. This is my
daughter we're talking about!
[GOTEN]
I'm not joking!
[GOHAN]
Hmm?
[surprised grunts]
Buu! He's coming back!
[GOHAN]
That didn't take long.
What? Majin Buu's here?
It's him! But why? Surely he
doesn't want to fight Gohan.
Unless he's managed to
improve in the last hour.
[ALL gasping]
Alright, I'm gonna go see
what he's up to.
Don't get sucked into
the fight, you guys. Stay here.
[GOHAN]
Why is he back so soon?
What could've changed?
[TRUNKS]
Come on!
[MR. SATAN]
Huh?!
Hey! Majin Buu!
How dare you hurt my daughter!
What's wrong with you?
You promised not to
kill anymore, remember?
[SUPER BUU laughing]
What? Don't you
know who I am, Buu?
Wake up! The Buu you made
friends with is gone.
Huh? Oh, hey! It's Bee!
You remember Bee, don't ya?
This is the puppy you saved.
[SUPER BUU chuckles]
All right, you gave it a try,
now back off. Let Gohan
handle it from here.
[growls] Huh?!
We'd better be quiet, Bee.
[chuckles]
[GOHAN thinking]
I don't get it.
I'm not sensing any
difference from before.
What's he up to?
His power level's
still the same.
Hey, I'll bet he's
bluffing, guys.
Ten to one, he runs away again.
Come on then, little worms.
I want to fight you now!
No way!
[ALL gasp]
That is not gonna happen.
You're fighting me, Buu.
You got it?
[SUPER BUU laughs]
I have a score to
settle with them first!
Then I'll take care of you,
stupid boy!
Sorry, pal,
but you're not the one
making the rules around here.
If you wanna fight someone,
then I'm your man.
What happened boys? Don't tell
me you're scared to fight Buu.
[TRUNKS, GOTEN growl]
You were raring to go before,
but now that your friend showed
up, you're acting like cowards.
[SUPER BUU]
Come on!
[NARRATOR] Ignoring the
obvious rematch with Gohan,
Majin Buu has challenged
Goten and Trunks to do battle!
What tricks does the insidious
Buu have up his sleeve,
or rather, under his back?
Stay tuned for more
of Dragon Ball Z!