[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
Mr. Satan was plotting
to blow up Majin Buu
and become the
savior of the world!
[MR. SATAN] I'm not
quite finished cooking
your dinner yet, sir.
[NARRATOR]
But when his target returned
with a newly found
friend in distress,
Mr. Satan discovered a
compassionate side of Buu
and decided to make an appeal.
Why do you
keep flying around, uh,
ya know, killing people and
destroying all of our cities?
Buu was told to.
Watch football.
Anything as long as it
doesn't involve destruction!
Hm?
Ah! I'm just kidding!
You can do whatever
you want to the world!
Just don't hurt me!
Is to kill people a bad thing?
Yes, it is a bad thing.
Then no more.
Huh?!
You're not going to
kill people any more?
[BUU]
Mhmm!
[MR. SATAN] And you won't
destroy any more cities?
[BUU]
Mhmm!
[MR. SATAN thinking]
I did it!
I got this guy to
change his ways
and I didn't have to throw
a punch or blow him up!
Oh, Mr. Satan,
you are truly the greatest!
[NARRATOR]
But just as soon as Buu's heart
began to be softened by
the love of his new friend,
tragedy struck when
a deranged madman
ended the puppy's life in
a senseless act of hatred!
[gasps]
Ohhh!
[NARRATOR] It was the end of
a new beginning for Majin Buu!
[MR. SATAN thinking]
Good heavens! This is terrible!
Who did this?
[growls]
[SMITTY laughs]
A Bull's eye!
How could they? Fools!
It was just a pup!
I-I'm sorry, Majin Buu!
Hm! Hey!
Yes, now I'm sure of it!
That's the World Champion
standing next to him, all right!
I'm positive!
But what would a
hero like Mr. Satan
be doing palling
around with Buu?
[VAN ZANT]
Trophy hunting no doubt!
The same as us, my old friend!
But Mr. Satan's not
getting the glory this time.
No sir-ee! That's the
joy of Armageddon, Smitty.
[VAN ZANT]
Everyone gets their turn.
Fire!
[cackles]
[VAN ZANT]
Yeah! Hahaha! Yeah!!
I did it! Yes!
The trophy is mine!
Remarkable! My word!
I've just stopped
the world from ending!
Guess that means more time
to have my fun! Ha, ha, ha!
[SMITTY] Ah! Look! In the
smoke! Someone's there!
[VAN ZANT] Stop being paranoid,
you old fool! Where?
There!
[VAN ZANT]
Huh?
What? I missed! But how
could I...? I shot right at him!
[BUU growls]
[gasping]
[SMITTY] He... He's coming!
What are we going to do?
[VAN ZANT] We're going
to kill him, you fool!
[SMITTY screams]
Huh?!
[VAN ZANT]
Idiot! What the heck happened?!
[MR. SATAN]
I happened!
What? You! Darn you!
[growls]
Go ahead! Pick it up!
Now it's your turn!
There! Hyaaaa!
[MR. SATAN] You! How could you?
It was just a little puppy!
You killed a little puppy!
You tried to kill us, too!
[pants]
Heartless monster!
Poor guy!
You didn't deserve this!
Majin Buu, quick!
He's still alive! Hurry!
Huh? Buu come!
He moved!
[BUU]
Buu here.
Can you help him? Like before?
[BUU]
Buu try! Try help pup!
[MR. SATAN] Yes! He's alive!
Ha, ha, ha! You did it, Buu!
You did it! He's alive!
[BUU] Buu do!! Buu do!
[BOTH] Buu do! Buu do!
Buu do! Buu do!...
[PICCOLO] I don't get it, Dende.
It doesn't make sense.
What's that show-boat
Mr.Satan doing
hanging around with Majin Buu?
Well making friends!
Hey, maybe Buu will
change if he has a friend!
Maybe we won't have
to fight him after all!
[PICCOLO]
Huh?
I don't like Mr. Satan!
But I don't want
him to get hurt!
He's in grave danger!
[barking]
[MR. SATAN] That a boy! Get the
ball.
Bring it back! Ah, good puppy!
Yeah! Aren't you smart!
Yes, you are!
Ahhh! Buu finish house!
[MR. SATAN] Oh, my goodness!
What a work of art!
That's incredible, Buu! Really!
Buu make house like Bee!
Aw, you named him Bee?!
[BUU] Buu pat-pat! Make house!
Buu make room for you, too!
[MR. SATAN]
Oh, really? Thank you!
[BUU]
Look! House for Bee!
[MR. SATAN]
Hey! He likes it!
[barks]
[MR. SATAN]
Awwwww...
[BUU chuckles]
[INSTRUCTOR]
Okay, girls! Here we go!
One and kick and two
and kick and three and kick!
That's it! Stretch it out!
Feel that burn!
Keep it up girls!
[GOHAN]
Hmm?
[INSTRUCTOR] Up, down! Up, down!
Up, down! That's it ladys!
Now you're doing it!
Okay, up, down, stop!
[OLD KAI cackles]
[GOHAN thinking]
This is absurd! What a kook!
Heh? You know!
When people succeed,
they're geniuses,
until then, they're kooks!
Huh?!
Look, I told you that
the awakening process
would take twenty
hours, didn't I?
And has it been
twenty hours yet?
Well, has it?
[GOHAN]
Uh-uh.
Shall we continue?
[GOHAN]
Mhmm.
Now!
Huh?
[OLD KAI] Tell me a little
about this Bulma lady!
I hope that she isn't
too old now, is she?
Well, as long as she's
got plenty of spunk left,
she'll do for me!
After being trapped
in that sword,
I'll settle for
just about anything!
Know what I mean? Hehehehe!
I know what you mean!
But don't you think we should
concentrate on the task at hand?
[OLD KAI]
Concentrate? How dare you!
What, you don't
think a Supreme Kai can
attend to a small matter like
this without losing his focus?
Concentrate? You're the one
who needs to concentrate!
So, what's she like?
Well, she's very beautiful!
Hm? Oh! I see!
But you shouldn't
be talking like this,
it's slowing down the process!
We must finish soon!
Yes! That way I can get my kiss!
Oh, my! He's putting Gohan
through the ringer, isn't he?
Well, I guess!
[SUPREME KAI]
It must be working! Excellent!
[barking]
[BUU]
Bee hungry! Bee think Buu food!
[MR. SATAN]
Uh, oh! Don't eat him, Bee!
Lunch will be ready
in just a minute!
[MR. SATAN thinking]
This is too good to be true!
Buu is like a little child!
He just needed a good friend!
That's me! Uh, huh!
The good friend!
[BEE barking]
[BUU]
Yeee! Help! Bee eat Buu!
[MR. SATAN]
Hey! Hold on! Here it comes!
[chuckles]
Uh! Oh...
[MR. SATAN]
Here we go!
Uh, don't mind the
curly black things, boys!
It's my, uh, special spice!
[BUU]
Will you eat with Buu?
Huh? Uh, yeah! Sure!
[PICCOLO]
And where have you two been?
[TRUNKS]
Uhhh... What do you mean?
We went to fight Buu! Remember?
[PICCOLO]
I told you to come back
as soon as your
fusion dissolved!
But we're here! We came back!
Fusion lasts for
about a half an hour
and you two have been gone
for more like half of the day!
Now how do you explain that?
It's time that you two
realized the seriousness
of this situation!
Do you understand me?
--Yes!
[BEE barks]
[BUU]
Bee paddle with feet! Good Bee!
[BUU laughs]
[MR. SATAN]
Excuse me, Majin Buu!
Would you like your
back scrubbed?
Hahah. Huh? Yes!
Come play! Get in tub!
Who, me? Gosh, that's
awfully nice of you!
Are you sure, Buu?
Buu sure! Come play!
[MR. SATAN]
Thank you! I could use a bath!
I'm smelling a little too
manly if you know what I mean!
Ahhh!
Forgive me! Please!
Come closer!
Closer? Okay, Buu! Uh.
Ha!
Gotcha! Play! Play!
[laughs]
Tadaaaa!
Funny fun!
Funny fun.
[MR. SATAN]
Besides almost drowning,
that was a really nice bath!
Uh, huh? My prize photo!
I almost forgot!
What a perfect picture to go on
the book jacket of my memoirs!
Uh, we're starting
to become friends,
so I think we should
preserve our new friendship
with some pictures. Yeah.
[MR. SATAN] If you wouldn't
mind lay down on your belly
with your hands
out in front of you.
[BUU]
Like this?
[MR. SATAN]
I know it seems strange,
but this is the latest
style of picture takin'.
[MR. SATAN thinknig]
He's so innocent
I could get him to do anything!
But that's the nice
thing about Majin Buu.
Grrr. I should be
ashamed of myself!
I don't need to fake it anymore!
If I've really convinced
Buu that killing is wrong,
then I truly
have saved the world!
[BUU]
Hey! Buu hungry!
You make yummy for Buu's tummy!
[MR. SATAN thinking]
But he just stuffed himself!
I'm coming!
Be right there, Buu!
Yum, yum! Tum, tum!
Whoa, Nelly!
That smells good! Mmm!
[BUU] Hey! Buu want sweety
sweet chocolates for desert!
Right! Huh? Mmm!
Some hero!
He's destroying our world
and you're cooking
him meals like a nanny!
You riffraff! [growls]
[BUU]
Bee want chocolate, too?
Hey! Bee want chocolate, too!
[VAN ZANT chuckles]
Now you die!
Hero!
[VAN ZANT]
Hehehehe! Numbskull!
Oh, no!
No, no!
[sobs]
[VAN ZANT] Come on out here,
you pink sack of blubber!
You're next!
Buu hurting!
[sobs]
Bad man make friend dead! No!
[BEE barks]
Aaaaaaah!
[gasps]
What? Whoa! Buu!
You saved me! I'm alive!
Thank you! Thank you! Huh?
Buu! Are you okay?
[MR. SATAN] Buu! What's the
matter? What happened to you?
[BUU] Go away! Go!
Quick! Take Bee and go!
Now! Please! Go!
Go? What? Buu, I won't
leave you! I'm your friend!
GO NOW!!!
Got it! Right!
[MR. SATAN]
Buu! Let me try and help you!
[BUU]
GO!!!
[BUU whimpers]
[pants]
[BEE barks]
[PICCOLO]
Yes, Dende! I feel it, too!
Something wicked
is brewing down there!
What is that thing?
[BEE barks]
[MR. SATAN]
Bee! Keep quiet!
Whoa! Are you seeing
what I'm seeing, boy?
[BEE barks]
Bad Buu!
Aaaaugh!
[VAN ZANT]
Wh-Wh-Wh-What are y-y-you?
They've separated!
Evil from good! This is awful!
[NARRATOR] What strange
personage is this that has been
expelled from the inner
workings of Majin Buu?
Is this really the evil
that was within him
manifested in physical form?
And if so, how will
this new threat
affect the fate of the Earth?
It seems the two Buu's
have a bone to pick!
Stay tuned for confrontation
on Dragon Ball Z.