[NARRATOR] Last time,
on Dragon Ball Z!
[ZARBON roars]
[NARRATOR] Zarbon underwent
a shocking transformation!
[VEGETA yells]
[ZARBON roaring]
[NARRATOR] Along with
his horrific new appearance,
Zarbon gained an equally
terrifying level of power!
And in this
monstrous form,
he quickly took control
of the battle with Vegeta,
unleashing a relentless
barrage of attacks
that brought the high
and mighty Saiyan prince
crashing down!
I'm through
toying with you.
It's time to end this
little game right now!
[NARRATOR] With Vegeta utterly
powerless to defend himself,
Zarbon was determined to finish
him off once and for all!
Ah, how perfect.
If he was still breathing
after that impact,
he won't be
for long.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
Krillin and Dende
completed their
dangerous journey
to the home of
the Eldest Namek.
Welcome...
[NARRATOR] Will he be able
to aid them in their quest
for the Dragon Balls?
Find out today!
[GURU snoring softly]
Um, do you think
he fell asleep?
Don't know...
Excuse me...
Great evil has
come to Namek...
Frieza and his
wicked men...
Because of them, nearly
all my children have...
...have been murdered.
[DENDE whimpers]
It seems they will
stop at nothing
until they have gathered
all seven Dragon Balls...
[KRILLIN] Right.
To Nameks, the Dragon Balls
symbolize wisdom and power.
But this Frieza sees them only
as a tool to serve his greed.
[KRILLIN growls]
Forgive me for being
blunt, Mister Guru,
but that's exactly
why we came here...
To ask for
your Dragon Ball,
so we can hide
it from Frieza.
[GURU] Hmm...
I won't let him get his hands
on it and that's a promise.
I see. So then you, too, are
collecting the Dragon Balls?
Yes, but my motives
are for good,
and not evil
like Frieza's.
Krillin lost several
of his friends.
He wants to wish
them back.
They died fighting these
evil men on Earth,
and if they return, they
may be able to help us
drive them
from our planet.
How is it you know
of the Dragon Balls?
[KRILLIN] We used to have
another set on Earth.
Impossible!
A long time ago, when
the terrible storm hit
that devastated
your planet,
there was one Namek
who managed to escape.
He left Namek
in a spaceship.
It took him halfway across
the galaxy to my planet.
He was only a child
when he got there,
but he grew up to become
the guardian of Earth.
He's the one who
created the Dragon Balls.
Ah, yes, I remember now.
The child of Kataas... Kami.
I'm pleased to hear he
made the journey safely.
He was a gifted child
from the Dragon Family.
He had the power to
create the Dragon Balls.
Kami was killed during our
battle with the Saiyans.
And the one
responsible was Vegeta.
The same one who's
here on Namek.
This Saiyan must be
horrible, indeed.
What an
awful power.
One who could defeat
a Namek like Kami
must've been
a Super Saiyan.
Eh?! A Super Saiyan?
What's that?
You mean you
don't know?
Hmm...
Please, come closer, and
we will solve this puzzle.
[KRILLIN stutters]
Now, clear your mind,
so I may feel your past.
Uh... 'Kay...?
[KAMI groaning]
[GURU] What a terrible thing.
A Namek at war with
himself, torn in two...
[KING PICCOLO laughs evilly]
[KING PICCOLO growls]
[KING PICCOLO] Raaah!
[KING PICCOLO laughing]
Before he could become
Guardian of the Earth,
Kami first
had to purge
even the smallest trace
of evil from his heart...
Thus, he split into two,
and Piccolo was born.
In doing so, his powers
were also split equally
between these
two halves.
If they had reunited, they
would not have been defeated
by any
normal Saiyan.
Uh... Really?
Now, I have
seen your mind.
Your heart is pure, and
your intentions are true.
Your bravery and your
loyalty to your friends
are beyond
question.
You have
proven yourself.
Worthy to receive
this Dragon Ball.
Krillin!
Wow, thank
you, sir.
You don't know what this
means to me... Thank you!
Ugh, will you look
at these split ends?
Aahh!
Is someone coming?
Uh, no, I was just getting
up to go to the bathroom.
[BULMA sighs]
I knew that...
That's one down,
six to go.
I only hope there is still
time for you to make your wish.
Wh-What do you mean?
Unfortunately, I'm
afraid I only have
a few days
left to live.
[KRILLIN gasps]
[DENDE gasps]
If your wish is
to be fulfilled,
you will have to gather
all seven Dragon Balls
before I go. However...
if this cannot be
accomplished, then...
[GURU coughs]
[GURU sighs]
Then the Dragon Balls will
disappear along with me.
I'll do my best!
And I promise:
Whatever happens, I'll guard
this Dragon Ball with my life!
And if I can't get all seven
in time to make my wish,
then neither will
Frieza or Vegeta!
Thank you... You do my people
a great service, young man.
Any time!
Indeed,
you are brave.
And there is much
strength in you.
Even more than
you realize
for much of it is
still sleeping...
"Still sleeping"?
Come again?
[GURU] Allow me to awaken
this power for you.
Really, I've already
trained myself to my limits.
I don't have any
sleeping powers.
And to tell
you the truth,
I'm amazed I even
made it this far.
[KRILLIN chuckles]
[KRILLIN whimpering panickedly]
[GURU] You see? This power
has been within you all along.
Oh, wow... S-So you
mean... I've got...
[KRILLIN cackles]
Power! A lot of
power! It's great!
[GURU chuckles,
KRILLIN laughs]
Aw, man! You were right!
I never knew I had it in me!
Whatever you did,
thanks a lot!
Uhh...
Um, excuse me,
Mr. Guru, sir?
One question... Can you
release anyone's power?
If they have the power within
them, then it is possible.
But, if you do this
thing too many times,
doesn't it drain
your own power?
I appreciate your concern
for my personal well-being,
but the short
answer is no.
Well, in that case, would
you mind trying this trick
on a friend of mine?
He's a really great
kid, and I tell ya',
if anyone I know has
hidden powers, it's him.
Bring him to me,
and if I can,
I will unlock
his potential.
Great! I'll be right back.
Uh...
But, what should I do
with the Dragon Ball?
I entrusted
it to you.
Its fate, along with the
fate of this entire planet
now rests
in your hands.
[gulps]
Alright Dende,
you wait here.
I'll come back with
Gohan as soon as I can.
Please be careful, Krillin.
Hm.
[GURU] Hmm...
[GURU coughs]
[BOTH gasp]
[NAIL] Guru!
[DENDE] Guru!
[coughing continues]
[GURU chuckles]
Ha! Oh yeah!
This'll be a cinch!
With all this new speed,
I'll make it back to
Gohan and Bulma in no time flat!
[KRILLIN chuckles]
Hmm?!
I don't believe it!
I finally find a
village to destroy,
and somebody already
beat me to it!
Huh?!
[growls]
[grunting]
[VEGETA] This should
do nicely...
[VEGETA laughs]
[VEGETA] Frieza can tear
this planet apart looking
for that ball, but
he'll never find it.
[thinking[ I must...
recover the Dragon Ball...
Tell me...
What happened here?
A-A Saiyan took
the Dragon Ball.
It was Vegeta...
Please, help me...
[grunting]
[screaming]
You worthless
Namek trash!
Miserable
Saiyan monkeys...
[ZARBON] Lord Frieza,
it's Zarbon.
The door's open.
[FRIEZA] So, did
you find the village?
No, I've come to tell
you that I found Vegeta.
You won't have to worry
about him troubling us again.
Oh? So you say.
What makes you sure?
Did you use your power
of transformation?
Right.
[FRIEZA] I see. And you know
for a fact that he's dead?
[ZARBON] Well, I
didn't check his pulse
if that's what you mean.
But I'm telling you,
it's highly unlikely
that he survived.
A chance in a
million, maybe...
So, in other words, you
don't really know, do you?
I know that I saw him
fall into the water
and not come get
back up again.
You should have gone
in after him, Zarbon.
Now, we can't
confirm anything,
just because you didn't want
to get wet! That's careless.
And it was careless
to try and kill Vegeta
before you'd even
questioned him.
How do you know he
hadn't already found
a Dragon Ball
and hidden it?
I-I'm sorry, Lord Frieza.
I'll go back and look for him!
Lord Frieza! I found another
one of the villages!
But it was completely destroyed
by the time I got there!
And the Dragon Ball
was missing!
[FRIEZA] Missing?!
[ORLEN] There was
one villager left...
He said a Saiyan took it!
[ZARBON] You were right.
Vegeta must've hidden it.
So, I took care
of the Namek,
and I got back here
as fast as I could!
So, you're saying you
killed the only witness?
Ah! Lord Frieza!
[ORLEN screaming]
Take note, Zarbon.
Because you can expect
the same to happen to you
if you don't find out
where that Dragon Ball is!
Do you understand?!
That is the price of
careless mistakes!
You had better
hope for your sake
that Vegeta
is still alive.
[FRIEZA] Apool!
Yes, my Lord!
[FRIEZA] Open a line
to the home planet.
Send word to
the Ginyu Force
that I want
them readied
and on their way
to Namek immediately.
And tell them they had better
not forget their scouters!
[ZARBON gasps]
[FRIEZA] I'll be expecting
them in five days.
Yes, Frieza.
[ZARBON] The Ginyus?
Lord Frieza,
are you sure that's necessary?
There's no telling what'll
do once they get here.
I've got the situation
under control.
I can handle
this without them.
I have a feeling we'll need
them sooner than you think.
Why? Is there something
I should know about?
I destroyed the Saiyans'
planet because I felt that,
if left unchecked, they might
one day pose a serious threat.
And it's beginning to
look like I was right.
[ZARBON gasps]
[FRIEZA] Vegeta isn't the
only one that concerns me.
There are others...
What? What others?
Surely you don't mean the
one Saiyan and his son
that Vegeta
fought on Earth?
I don't see how they
could possibly worry you.
Even combined, they were
hardly a match for Vegeta.
They're certainly
no match for you.
[FRIEZA] Zarbon, are you
telling me that I am wrong?
Is that what
I'm hearing?!
[ZARBON] No!
[FRIEZA] That's what I thought.
Now, go find Vegeta.
I want that Dragon Ball!
[ZARBON] Yes, Lord.
[thinking] The Ginyu Force.
Frieza isn't taking any chances.
[FRIEZA thinking] These
Saiyans are proving to be quite
a thorn in my side.
It seems the more they fight,
the stronger they become.
Of course, I'm still much
more powerful than they are,
but if they keep
multiplying their strength,
then who knows what they might
be capable of in the future?
Best to eliminate them now,
before they get any stronger...
[GOKU snoring]
[snoring continues]
[GOKU grunting]
[yawning]
Boy, am I exhausted.
I can barely move a muscle.
[grunting]
Actually... I can't
move a muscle!
[VEGETA grunting]
I... won't...
die like... this...
The... Dragon Balls...
are... mine!
[grunting continues]
Well, well... So you're
still alive, after all.
Lucky for me.
But then...
I guess it's not such a lucky
thing for you, now is it?
I'm going to have so much
fun making you talk.
[GOHAN grunting]
[beeping]
Hm? Hey, Gohan,
check it out!
It's moving!
[BULMA] You see?
And according to this,
it looks like it's
heading right for us!
Maybe it's Krillin on
his way back here.
[GOHAN] He must've
gotten the Dragon Ball
from the Eldest Namek!
All right! Way to go, Krillin!
I just knew he'd come through!
Mm-hmm. But, come here.
Look at this.
There's just something
that's been bugging me...
[GOHAN] Huh?
[BULMA] We know
one ball is moving.
And those five together are
the ones you say Frieza has.
So then, what's this one
doing up here all by itself?
[GOHAN] Huh? Well it's nearby.
It actually looks like
it might be... Uh...
Over in that direction.
[GOHAN] That's not too
far from here, is it?
That's where we sensed
Vegeta attacking that village!
That must be
where it is!
[BULMA gasps]
[GOHAN] But, I don't
think he's there anymore.
I can't sense him now.
I wonder why he
left it there.
I got it! If he couldn't
make the Namekians
tell him where
it was hidden,
maybe he never found
it in the first place!
Hah!
When he got tired
of searching for it,
he must've gone
away thinking
there wasn't a Dragon
Ball there to find!
Let me borrow the radar
for a while, Bulma.
I better go to
the village
and get it before
someone else does.
[BULMA] Good idea!
It's all yours, kid!
But be careful, okay?
[beeping]
[GOHAN laughs]
Okay, straight ahead!
And the coast is clear!
I still don't sense Vegeta!
Well, let me know
when he's ready.
I want him to be healthy
before I start torturing him.
[beeping]
[NARRATOR] With Gohan and
Krillin speeding across Namek,
and Vegeta in
Frieza's custody,
the race for the Dragon
Balls is heating up!
But who will win
the ultimate prize?
The forces of good?
Or the forces of evil?
Don't miss the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!