[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z,
the fearsome duo of Babidi
and Majin Buu took off,
seeking revenge for
Piccolo's failed attempt
to end the dark wizard's life!
Buu's penchant for annihilation
caught even his
master off guard!
Yet, the reckless destruction
left in their wake
is merely a sample
of what the evil twosome
has in store
for the Z Fighters,
whose defenses have
been severely thinned!
With Vegeta dead and
Gohan missing in action,
it seemed the world's
only hope for survival
would be Piccolo and Krillin--
at least until Goten
and Trunks recover.
[NARRATOR] But then Goku, after
being knocked out by Vegeta,
finally arose, along with the
Z Fighters' chances for victory.
Unaware of recent events,
Goku attempted to intuit the
status of his teammates.
[GOKU]
I can still sense Buu,
but I can't sense Vegeta or
Gohan either! This isn't good!
How long was I out
for? Too long...
Something's happened,
something terrible!
It feels like Piccolo and
Krillin are back in action!
They probably know
what's been going on.
Gohan... I'm sorry I
wasn't here for you.
[NARRATOR] Goku returned to the
Lookout in search of answers,
much to the surprise of
Piccolo and Krillin,
who had all but
given up hope of ever
seeing their friend again.
Reunited, they must
now find some way
to overpower the evil forces
of Babidi and Majin Buu!
[GOKU]
Hi!
He's real! He talks
and everything!
[laughs]
[PICCOLO] We're unaware of the
Supreme Kai's whereabouts,
though we faintly
detect he's alive.
We'd just brought the little
ones back here to recuperate,
when you showed up.
[GOKU] Gohan, Supreme Kai,
even Vegeta, all gone...
What kind of monster
are we dealing with?!
Majin Buu's power level
continues to increase at a rate
unlike any enemy
we've encountered before.
If we can't stop him from
destroying this world,
there will be nothing to
prevent him from wiping out
every last trace of
life in the universe.
Don't be such a downer, Piccolo,
of course we can stop Buu
now that Goku's alive.
Sorry! The halo! What I meant to
say is that you may be "dead",
but at least
you're not dead-dead,
like Vegeta and Gohan.
Oh! Stupid, Krillin,
think before you speak!
Goku, you're the only one left
who can take on Majin Buu.
So what are you waiting for?
Him to shove his pudgy,
pink face up in yours?
Come on, show that creep
a little of the ol'
--Ka-me-ha-me-haaa!
--Krillin.
It's impossible, I just
can't beat him alone.
Huh?! But why not?
He's simply too
powerful an opponent.
E-Even for you?
Look, when Vegeta
and I were fighting,
the two of us were
evenly matched.
He gave it everything he had,
even his life, and he still
couldn't beat that thing.
So what chance do
I have against him?
[ALL gasp]
If you can't, what hope
do we have? Goku...
[GOKU] If only Vegeta
hadn't been so arrogant!
Thinking he could
take on Buu alone...
He'd still be alive and
we could work together!
No. Don't punish
yourself like this!
It wouldn't have made
any difference.
Not even an army of
Super Saiyans could have--
[GOKU]
I was going to say that if
Vegeta or Gohan
were still alive,
we could've done a fusion!
Uh? Fuchsia? Like the
color of my shirt, sort of?
No, fusion.
[gasps] Fusion?
You mean a merger?!
Yeah, that's it, Dende!
Oh, I've heard of such a
skill, back on Namek.
A man from Metamor
once told me about it.
Their people are quite
proficient at the technique.
That's true! The Metamorese
I met in Other World
are the ones that
showed me how to do it!
So what is it, already?!
It's an ancient merger art
that can be performed between
two people of similar size
and physical ability.
You wanna try that again?
It's when two people combine
to form an entirely new being
that's able to do things
neither could do alone.
Like stopping an evil creature
that's out to destroy the world
and everyone in it.
[gasps]
Now that I think about it,
you and Nail were a sort of
fusion, too, weren't you?
[PICCOLO]
Mm-hmm. Yes, we were, of a sort.
[PICCOLo] Nail had been
badly wounded by Frieza
when I found him.
He was dying.
And as his final act,
he wished to impart
his powers to me.
I was reluctant to
join with him at first,
but his promise of
greater power proved...
quite persuasive.
[PICCOLO grunts]
[PICCOLO] When it was over,
Nail's body had vanished,
though I could still sense
his presence in me.
I felt his strength
and his wisdom,
so fresh and invigorating,
yet familiar, as though it had
been at my fingertips all along.
I stood up, reborn, knowing
that I was fully capable
of avenging Nail
by taking on Frieza,
or any other villain that
dared to cross my path.
Wow. Unreal. My gosh.
This is amazing!
I feel incredible!
Yes! Yes! Yes! I can win! I
feel great! I can do this! Yes!
[PICCOLO] Yes! I'm home! I'm
alive! This is all a miracle!
I'm awake! I'm wide awake!
[PICCOLO laughs]
[GOKU] The Namekian fusion
that you experienced, Piccolo,
is actually quite different
from the Metamorese variety,
Which is the process
I learned in Other World.
The way I know is
only temporary,
and instead of one body playing
host, a new hybrid is formed,
made up of characteristics
from both people.
They transform into
a single warrior,
capable of incredible
power and strength!
Yes, that is different.
But it seems the
end result is the same.
I know when I fused with Nail,
my power increased
exponentially.
So if Gohan or Vegeta
were still alive,
you could perform one of those
temporary fusions with them,
couldn't you?
And then in your new form,
you would have been able
to defeat Majin Buu.
Nah, it probably wouldn't
have worked out so nicely
even if Gohan or
Vegeta were alive.
It would take about a week to
show them what to do,
but I'm only here on
Earth for this one day,
not to mention that
even though I know how
these fusions work in theory,
I've never taught
somebody else how to do it.
And believe it or not,
I've never actually been able to
try out a fusion in practice.
No one in Other World is similar
enough to me to be compatible.
[groans]
[DENDE sighs]
[growls]
So yeah, so much for that!
It was just a crazy idea!
[KRILLIN]
Wait, Goku! No it's not!
[GOKU] What are you
thinking about, Krillin?
You said you're about to go
back to the Other World, right?
And if Gohan and Vegeta
are really dead,
then that's where they
must be too, correct?!
So you can do a fusion with
them when you get back there!
Oh, right!
Now that's a great idea!
Impossible. Once Goku
leaves this world
he won't be able to return.
The fusion would
still do us no good.
[BOTH sigh]
The young ones, sleeping.
Goten and Trunks
are almost exactly
the same size, aren't they?
Could they do a fusion?
Is that possible?
Yeah!
Thank you, Mr. Popo!
You know, that just might work!
[gasps]
Really, Goku?!
Mr. Popo, I love you!
You're a genius!
Let's all give it up for
Mr. Popo, the genius!
But Goku, do you think there's
enough time to teach them?
No. I'll work with them
as long as I can,
but they're gonna need
more time than I've got.
Someone else will have
to pick up the slack.
Piccolo, do you think
you'll be able to finish
instructing the boys
after I've gone?
I'll try.
Woo-hoo-hoo!
Goten and Trunks will
show Majin Buu who's boss!
He won't even know what hit him!
[PICCOLO]
Not so fast, Krillin.
Huh?
According to Goku,
it will take some time
before they've mastered
the art of fusion
and are ready to
make their attack.
Meanwhile,
many innocent people
will be lost in the wake of
Majin Buu's destruction.
I'm talking about
total annihilation.
Everything and everyone
on this planet, wiped out.
It's a gamble.
So we must prepare ourselves for
anything that comes our way
until the boys have mastered
fusion and are ready to go.
You're right,
but I'm confident these two
can learn how to do this.
And we can always use
the Dragon Balls
to clean up the
damage at the end.
[KRILLIN] You think we
still have a chance?
We can't ever give up
hope, you guys.
And right now,
Trunks and Goten are
the world's best hope.
We should know by now not to
underestimate the young--
especially when they're
a couple of Super Saiyans.
[BABIDI] Ah, Buu! So many places
to blow, people to scream!
[BUU giggles]
[BABIDI]
Buu?
[thinking]
He's a smooth flyer,
but as a conversationalist,
he's sort of a bum.
[BABIDI]
Hel-lo.
Buu?
[BABIDI] Ah yes, this location
is full of potential!
Or should I say,
"was" full of potential.
[BABIDI giggles]
[RIDERS scream]
[BUU squeals]
[BABIDI] Wait! Buu!
What are you doing?!
We're not here
for your amusement!
We're here for mine! Stop!
I'm not wearing
a safety belt! [screams]
[BABIDI]
No, no, not the loop!
[BABIDI screams]
[BABIDI] Stop, Buu!
I don't like this ri--!
[screams]
[BABIDI]
I command you to stop!
If you don't save me fast,
I'll put you in your shell until
the next ice age passes over!
I can't fall! Geniuses like
me are highly breakable!
Cool puppets.
They're way life-like!
Your playtime... is over!
[BUU grunts]
[RIDERS scream]
[BUU]
Buu!
Bulma, why don't you just get it
over with and summon the dragon?
Does he just pop
up out of them?
She may have a
pretty enough face,
but her skull sure is thick!
Mind your
manners, Oolong.
Not everyone is as
worldly as you.
Videl, just keep your
eyes on the balls.
I'm not so naive, you know.
I've just never seen
a magical dragon before.
Okay, now do you remember
the spell to release him?
You know all the words?
Of course,
I'm not gonna pull a Frieza
and screw it up, Yamcha!
Bulma, I think Frieza failed
because he wore
too many clothes!
--[PUAR sqeauls]
--[OOLONG yells]
Hey, now!
Put it to rest will ya?!
Now's not the time for your
shenanigans! Chauvinist pig.
So, there's a spell
involved, huh?
Oh, I guess that
would make sense.
Bulma, go ahead, dear.
Call the dragon so we
can wish all those poor people
who your Vegeta destroyed at the
Tournament today back to life.
That is the plan.
Eternal Dragon, by your name
I summon you forth! Shenron!
[gasps]
[KRILLIN] All right,
I'm gonna go get everybody
and bring 'em back here.
[PICCOLO]
Good.
[GOKU]
Take care, Krillin!
[ALL]
Huh?
[KRILLIN] Is it Daylight
Savings Time already
and someone forgot to tell me?!
Oh no, why has it
suddenly gone dark?!
Not good.
Someone's released
Shenron! Who and why?
My money's on Bulma.
Who else could gather those
Dragon Balls so fast?
But she can't know about
everything that's happened.
So why call the Dragon now?
[gasps] She knows
Vegeta slaughtered a lot
of innocent people at the
martial arts stadium today!
Bulma must be trying to
bring them all back to life!
Oh no! That'll ruin everything!
Once two wishes are fulfilled,
we'll have to wait a whole year
before we can make another one!
[gasping]
[GOKU] All right, then. I'll
just have to go and stop her.
[GOKU using telepathy]
Bulma? Bulma?!
Bulma, where are you?
Darn! Bulma's life-force
is difficult for me to trace.
Everything feels just so
clouded right now on Earth.
[SHENRON growls]
Ah! I'm dreaming...
This can't be real, can it?
[CROWD gasping, screaming]
You who have disturbed
me from my slumber,
speak and name your first wish.
[VIDEL] I think that... I'm
going to have to faint now.
[SHENRON]
You try my patience! Speak!
[BULMA] Hmm, now how exactly
should I phrase this wish?
[YAMCHA] I thought you had
this figured out!
How about, "Bring everyone
who died today back to life!"
Except for all the
really, really bad ones!
Will that do, Bulma?
That'll do.
Oh man, can people
actually be brought back
from the dead like that?
It has been set in motion!
Now, name your second wish!
[gasping, muttering]
[gasps]
Ah! I've got her!
I must have
your second wish now!
Did he say second wish?!
Oh no, I'm too late!
Huh, Goku?!
Goku?!
Goku, where on
Earth have you been?
[gasps, growls
And where is Gohan?
And Goten?!
ChiChi, there's
no time to explain.
Please trust me.
Dende, can you hear me?
[DENDE using telepathy]
Yes!
I arrived too late.
The dragon has already
fulfilled their first wish
and now he wants to know
what their second one is.
What should I do?
Then there is still hope.
Tell Shenron
that you want to save
the other wish for another time.
If only one has been granted,
then we can
use that wish again
when only four
months have passed.
[GOKU using telepathy] All
right, I'll take care of that.
Oh, and you guys. I can't
believe I almost forgot.
I'm bringing you
all back with me,
once I'm finished with my
business here. So get ready.
[DENDE using telepathy] We'll
prepare for your return, Goku.
Thanks. Shenron!
You don't have to grant any more
wishes today. Thank you!
We'll call you again sometime!
As you wish. Farewell.
You wanna tell me what's
gotten into you Goku?
We still had a
perfectly good wish
we could have used to help!
[KIBITO thinking]
I don't understand.
My body appears to be in
perfect physical condition.
And this place,
something's wrong.
I shouldn't be here! Wait...
I remember now.
I was attacked by Dabura.
Now, let's begin.
[gasps]
Haaa...!
[KIBITO screams]
Have I been brought
back to life? A miracle!
[gasps]
[KIBITO] The Supreme Kai!
I must find and protect him!
Where could he possible be?!
Master!
[thinking] I must seek out
help to prevent Majin Buu
from wreaking any more havoc.
My only hope is...
As long as there's the slightest
possibility that he's alive,
I still have a chance.
[SUPREME KAI thinking] Wherever
you are, Gohan,
I hope to find you. And I
hope to find you breathing.
For your sake, and for my own.
You are my last hope!
And that makes you, perhaps,
the last hope of the universe.
[GOKU]
So, there you go.
Now, if you'll all come back
with me to the Lookout,
we can start
making preparations.
That's fine,
I'll just have to
track down seven Dragon Balls
again in four months, which
shouldn't be any problem!
That's the spirit!
Now, everyone.
As long as you're
connected to me,
we can all travel by
"Instant Transmission!"
[VIDEL thinking]
This is like some wonderful
fantasy land where,
just when I think
it can't possibly get
any weirder, it does!
[GOKU] Please remain standing
in an upright position,
fastened to the
person next to you.
[BULMA] Mom, Dad,
what are you waiting for?
Hold onto my hand, quickly,
or you'll be left behind!
Your mother and I just
can't bring ourselves
to leave the little ones.
We'll wait here
for your return.
[gasps]
Will you two stop being
naive and open your eyes?!
Is it really worth
risking both your lives
just to stay here
and feed and clean
your stinking
precious pets?!
Remember, even if we meet our
horrible, tragic,
gruesome and grotesque end
at the hands of this Majin Buu,
you can always bring us back to
life with the Dragon Balls!
Don't try to argue,
we've made up our minds.
But, Mom!
Goku! Say something!
Bulma, you're pretty good
at finding Dragon Balls
when you really need to,
so don't worry!
Oh, you don't want to
transport with us, Videl?
Oh no, oh no, oh no! I'm
going, I'm going, I'm going!
We're ready for liftoff!
[MRS. BRIEF] Shall we feed all
of our little darlings now,
before it gets too late?
[DR. BRIEF]
But, I'm hungry.
How very peculiar, Buu.
First it's day,
then suddenly it's night,
then it's back to day again.
Hmm... [giggles]
Doesn't make much
difference to me anyway.
Soon, my pet, there will be
only permanent nightfall.
[giggles]
[NARRATOR] Dark skies loom ahead
for the people of the world,
as long as the evil Babidi
and Majin Buu
float among them.
Can anyone put a stop to
their mission of terror?
Right now, the Earth's best
chances for survival
lie resting in bed.
When they awaken,
will they be up to the
challenge before them?