[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z...
As the two evil Saiyan
warriors hurtled towards Earth
in their space pods,
the Z warriors
were busy
beefing up their
martial arts skills.
Goku had made it to
King Kai's planet
but he was finding the gravity
a little tough to take.
And it didn't
help matters
when he mistook the
King's pet ape Bubbles
for the mythical
martial master...
Once the proper
introductions were made,
Goku was put to the test to
see if he was worthy enough
to train with the
legendary King Kai...
His first assignment,
catch Bubbles,
and then he would be
permitted to move on
to the next phase
of his training...
It all seemed easy
enough at first,
but it proved to be a lot
harder than Goku imagined.
That little monkey
sure could move!
And don't forget the intense
gravity of King Kai's planet.
It can really
bring a guy down!
While King Kai watched with
amusement from the sidelines,
Goku did his best to grab
the speedy little monkey!
Time and time again they
traveled around the planet
and before long they
were going in circles!
Then Goku made one
last leap of faith
and managed to get
a grip on Bubbles!
[GOKU] Heh. Gotcha! Yeah!
[NARRATOR] It was then that
King Kai realized that Goku
could indeed be
a worthy student.
But things are only going to
get harder from here on in...
And one question
remains...
What kind of
bizarre training
does the King have in
store for Goku now?
[GOKU] Woo-hoo! I did it!
I caught him! Ha, ha, ha, ha!
Look King Kai!
I caught the monkey!
[BUBBLES chatters]
I'm ready for the next phase
of my training King Kai!
Okay... If you say so.
Let's see now...
Phase two, huh?
Yeah!
No more
monkey business!
[snickers]
Heh!
[kissing sounds]
Can I do my next training
session without Bubbles?
He'll just
get in the way!
Hey! Don't be so rude!
All right then!
Let's start training!
Yeah! Let's get to work!
[long inhale]
[intense yelling]
Hm?
What did you do?
I yelled at the
top of my lungs!
Yeah, I'll say...
Um... Am I missing
something here?
Why did you do that, King Kai?
You'll see...
[GOKU] Uh...
[intense yelling]
That, my boy, is a
long distance call!
[snickers]
Don't you get it?
He can't be a
martial arts master!
[GREGORY]
Hey! I heard that!
Huh?
[GOKU yells]
What is it?
[GREGORY] I'm not an
it, you lunk-head!
Hey! It's a little
grasshopper man!
Yeah! So what?
Little grasshopper man?
[KING KAI snickers]
Be quiet!
And listen up!
My name's Gregory!
And I'm King Kai's most
trusted attendant!
So you watch
yourself!
Uhh...
That's right!
I'm also a fearless
martial arts master
with no equal!
Except for King Kai!
[KING KAI snickers]
[KING KAI] I think it's
your ego that has no equal!
A-hem. Yes, now
where was I?
Right! Who do you
think you are?
I heard what you
said about King Kai!
So you don't think
he's for real, huh?
No! His methods
just bug me!
[KING KAI growls]
[KING KAI] Heh! Oh, I get it!
My methods bug him!
[KING KAI snickers]
King Kai? Please! It's hard to
concentrate with you laughing!
Yes, of course!
Sorry about that!
Goku, Gregory will be your
next test! Are you ready?
The bug?
Hey, buddy,
I'm a grasshopper!
But King Kai...
I thought you were going
to train me personally?
You'll take on just about
anyone these days, won't you?
How am I supposed to work
with a guy like this
who doesn't know
the first thing
about showing respect
for his elders?!
You'll manage!
Now let's
get started!
What's that for?
That's kinda big! Are you sure
you're not overdoing it, sir?
Of course not!
Goku, catch!
[GOKU yells]
How's that?
Heavy enough?
[GOKU grunts]
[GREGORY giggles]
Now Goku.
Take that hammer
and see if you can
hit Gregory with it!
Hit him? Uhh...
And if you can
complete this task
I will allow you to
train under me directly!
Hey, all right!
Don't get your
hopes up, buddy!
There's no way I'm gonna let
you hit me with that hammer!
[GREGORY]
Heh, heh! Catch me if you can!
Ahhhh...
Ahaa!
All right!
Here I come!
[GOKU yells]
[GREGORY chuckles]
Man! What speed! Ahh!
Creep!
[KING KAI thinking] Hmmm? I've
never given a trainee a hammer
as heavy as that one!
Good luck, Goku.
C'mon Bubbles, this
could take a while!
I'll get him
this time!
[grunts]
Aahhh! He's all mine!
[GREGORY] Bye now!
Come back here!
[GOKU] I'm going to squash you
like the bug that you are!
[GOKU yells]
[glass shatters]
Be careful!
Huh?
Aaaahhhh!
[GREGORY laughs]
And I just finished
the wax-job, too!
[whimpers]
[BUBBLES chatters]
[GOKU yells in distance]
[yells]
[GOKU]
Slow down, would ya?!
[BUBBLES chatters]
[NARRATOR] While Goku
plays bug exterminator,
on Earth, Piccolo is busy
trying to push Gohan
to the next level of
martial arts training!
[PICCOLO yells]
[PICCOLO] Heh! You're too
easy a target for me!
[GOHAN and PICCOLO yell]
Aahh!
[GOHAN laughs]
[PICCOLO chuckles]
So you've figured out how to
dodge my punches and kicks.
Now try this!
Uh?
[PICCOLO yells]
[footsteps]
[GOHAN groans]
[GOHAN] Aw, come on Piccolo!
Gimme a break!
[PICCOLO chuckles]
[GOHAN screams]
[PICCOLO] Get up here!
We've got work to do!
[GOHAN breathes heavily]
[PICCOLO scoffs]
[grunts]
[thinking] At this rate
he'll never be able
to face those
two Saiyans!
[GOHAN grunts]
[GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN breathes heavily]
Hey! I'm stuck!
Piccolo! Come on!
Help me! I can't get out!
Please Piccolo! Help me!
Just this one time!
Please...
I'll do better next time...
I promise!
Help me Piccolo...
Please!
[NARRATOR High above the
Earth on Kami's lookout,
the other Z
warriors continue
their intensive
training regime!
Tien and Yamcha
seem about equal!
They're
looking good!
[KAMI]
Mm-hm...
[TIEN yells]
[YAMCHA yells]
[TIEN chuckles]
[YAMCHA chuckles]
[KRILLIN yells]
Hey come on!
Stop kidding around!
[YAJIROBE] Heh!
[KRILLIN yells]
[KRILLIN yells frantically]
[GOKU] Aw, come on,
slow down a little!
I won't hit you that
hard... I promise!
Time out!
[GOKU] Huh?
Whoa! Hey!
What's the deal?
It's break time!
Dinner!
[GOKU laughs]
Woohoo!
Uh--Don't feed him!
[eating noises]
[GOKU belches]
[eating noises continue]
You worked up quite an
appetite, didn't you?
[GOKU] Boy, oh boy!
I sure did!
Will it slow
him down?
Oh, no, it makes
him much faster...
And it won't give
him a cramp!
[GOKU] You betcha!
[KING KAI] The Saiyans
are remarkably fast too!
But you are
not there yet!
Huh? Ah, the Saiyans!
What do you know
about them, King Kai?
What do you mean, what
does he know about them?
King Kai knows
everything!
There, there, Gregory!
Goku, you told me earlier
that you too are a Saiyan,
am I correct?
Huh?!
Yeah! But I don't know
anything about the Saiyans...
You see, they sent me to
Earth when I was just a baby!
Ah, well then... I can probably
tell you a few things
about the Saiyans
that you don't know!
[GOKU]
Wow! Really?
[KING KAI]
Mm-hm!
[GOKU]
Hold on!
Ah! How kind of you!
Ah, I feel like a king!
[GOKU] Mm-hm...
Mm. Yes... Now a long time ago,
before you were born...
There were two tribes
that lived on Planet Vegeta.
There were your
ancestors, the Saiyans...
And the other tribe was
known as the Tuffles.
[GOKU] The Saiyans
and the Tuffles, huh?
[KING KAI] That's correct.
Now, the Tuffles
were a so-called
advanced civilization...
They had cities much
like the ones on Earth
and enjoyed all of
the modern conveniences
such as air-travel
and mini malls.
They had long ago
outgrown energy sources
which polluted
their planet
and were enjoying
health and prosperity.
Not far from the big cities, in
the arid wastelands of Vegeta,
the Saiyans lived in
primitive fashion.
They were much larger in
size than the Tuffles
but much smaller
in number.
One thing all Saiyans
had in common
was that they
all had tails.
Another was their brutal
and violent nature...
They loved to fight.
But because they were
so few in number,
the Tuffles never worried
about the Saiyans.
That is until the day...
...they attacked!
And so the great war for
planet Vegeta began.
With the element of
surprise in their favor,
the Saiyans quickly
gained a strong foothold
in the war against
the Tuffles.
The Tuffles had
technology on their side.
They had devices that measured
their enemies fighting power
and advanced
weaponry
which they used to hold
the Saiyans at bay.
Though few in number,
the Saiyans strength
was so incredible
that they too won their
fair share of the battles.
[SAIYAN #2 laughs]
[KING KAI] And just when it
seemed that there was
no end in sight to
this horrible war,
something
happened on Vegeta
that only happens there
once every eight years.
There was a full moon!
A decisive factor in the
war for planet Vegeta!
As you must know, Saiyans
have the ability to transform
into huge ape-like creatures
when the moon is full.
[roaring]
[TUFFLE #2]
Let's get out of here!
[roaring]
[KING KAI] It didn't take long
for these monsters to destroy
the Tuffles and their
advanced civilization...
But then a new problem
began for the Saiyans.
Without the technology
of the Tuffles,
the Saiyans couldn't
travel in space.
This meant they couldn't
satisfy the one desire
that they all shared,
the desire to fight.
I'm sure you've
heard the joke,
how many Saiyans does it
take to build a rocket-ship?
[GOKU] Uh? No...
[KING KAI chuckles]
It's a really good one!
[GOKU]
Later King Kai!
[KING KAI] Fine!
Well, not far away,
the Saiyans met
the Archosians...
Now, the Archosians had
money and technology,
but the planet
Archos was a dump.
So they hired the Saiyans to
conquer a planet for them!
An unholy partnership
was formed.
With Saiyan might and
Archosian ingenuity combined,
they formed a fleet
of planet pirates.
The plan that these
two sinister races
hatched meant that
there was nothing
they wouldn't do to
achieve their goals...
An armada of space pods
was designed to travel
the vast distances
of the universe.
They even sent babies like
yourself to distant planets.
The Saiyan leaders were more
than happy to send specimens
of their race into
the great unknown.
They knew that when
the babies grew up
they would extinguish
any and all inhabitants
of the planet
they landed on.
I'd like to
extinguish them!
Well, all misdeeds gather
their just rewards.
You see, like Earth, the planet
Vegeta also had a guardian.
This good man
used his power
to attract a vast system
of meteors to the planet.
He could no longer tolerate
the horrible burden
of the Saiyans'
dark deeds.
So he brought destruction
upon the planet,
which was plagued by the weight
of its inhabitants' evil.
Planet Vegeta
was demolished!
It kind of got a major
spanking you could say,
except with meteors.
Only four Saiyans
survived the destruction
of planet Vegeta,
and you are
one of them.
No!
I'm not one of them!
I'll never be!
[KING KAI]
Easy now...
Listen you might despise your
heritage, but at this point
the fact that you are a
Saiyan is a great asset!
Channel your anger. Use it
to enhance your training.
You're right! I can't wait
to start training again.
I'm in! If it's okay
with King Kai of course!
[KING KAI]
Mm-hm! Mm-hm!
[GOKU] I am really
anxious to get started,
but uh, let me wolf
this down first!
[eating noises]
[GOKU thinking]
C'mon... C'mon...
[GREGORY] Huh?!
[GOKU thinking]
Missed him!
[KAMI] Gentlemen, Mr. Popo
and I are both very pleased
with the progress
you have made here.
Each of you has
reached a new level
of strength
and technique.
But the time has come for you
to go back down to Earth.
The future of the planet
is in your hands.
May you fight
with honor!
[ALL] Right!
Kami, can I take these
weighted clothes off now?
You may do
as you please.
So what are you guys
going to do down below?
Well, I say we go somewhere
and continue training.
That's a
good idea.
[thinking] Hm. I wonder how
much Goku has improved...
[GOKU]
Ha, ha, ha! I got you now!
[GREGORY]
Oh, no you don't!
[clanking]
[KING KAI]
What a mess!
I hope my insurance covers this!
[GREGORY laughs]
[thinking]
I almost got him!
Hm. That was a close one!
Yeah!
That oughta do it!
Aahh!
All right!
Here goes!
Gotcha!
[BUBBLES chatters]
That wasn't too bad
now was it, Gregory?
What is that, a joke? Come on
my body is in super condition!
You couldn't hurt me with
that thing if you tried!
Really? Well, is
that a lump I see?
Oh! What did
you do to me?
[GOKU laughs]
[thinking] Goku is
indeed a rare man.
Perhaps he
is the one!
There are seventy days left.
He could do it!
He could master Kaio-Ken and
defeat those Saiyan warriors!
No one's ever been able
to master Kaio-Ken.
It's been like a
dream in my head.
Like a horse that's
too wild to ride!
But now,
there is a chance!
King Kai you
promised remember?
Do you really think
you're ready to learn
the mystic art of Kaio-Ken
from me as you are?
Well, do you?
Yes, I do!
All right, first I want
you to visualize yourself
at your very best! Both in
body and in spirit! Got it?
Got it!
Now that you understand, uh...
let's go take a lunch break!
[ROSHI] Well sis, I should
know better then to ask but,
can you tell us what
your crystal ball says
about the future?
Who's future?
Be specific!
Our planet's future...
Mother Earth's!
Hm. What's up?
You heard something?
No matter!
If it's going to
happen, I'll see it!
I always do!
[incantation vocalization]
Huh? Oh no!
As things stand right now,
the Earth has no future!
Eh?!
No! Attack! Don't just dodge!
Use your strength!
[GOKU yells]
[KING KAI snickers]
[NARRATOR] While our heroes
push themselves to the limit
with their
martial arts training,
on the outer edge
of the solar system,
a great evil
approaches.
The Saiyans, who are intent
on destroying Earth,
are already
passing by Jupiter.
Only one day remains
until their arrival.
Have the Z warriors properly
prepared themselves
to face
their wrath?
And will Goku make
it back in time
to fight side by side
with his son Gohan?
All these questions and
more will be answered
on the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!