[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Frieza set his destructive
sights on Planet Namek itself!
[FRIEZA] Die, planet! Die!
[NARRATOR] It was a strategy
born of desperation...
Overwhelmed by
Goku's new power,
Frieza was attempting
to destroy Goku
by taking away the very
air that he breathed.
[NARRATOR] Miraculously,
Planet Namek didn't explode,
but it was only
hanging on by a thread,
due to blow up in just
five short minutes.
[GOKU] Five minutes
is all that I need.
It won't even take me
that long to beat you
and leave with my
friends on my spaceship.
You underestimate me.
The true depth of
my power escapes you.
Well, it's time you experience
the ultimate Frieza!
[GOKU growls]
This battle
ends right now!
[GOKU yells]
[yelling continues]
[FRIEZA yells]
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU growls]
[FRIEZA screams]
[FRIEZA yells]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU] Hey, yo!
What's the matter?
You're the one who started
this battle, remember?
[GOKU growls]
[FRIEZA screams]
[FRIEZA growls]
[GOKU yells]
Huh...?
[FRIEZA yells]
[GOKU grunts]
[FRIEZA] Well, well,
well, look who's back.
I didn't think that I'd
get rid of you that easily.
But that little break in the
action is all I really needed.
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[FRIEZA] While you were
down there spelunking,
I was gathering
precious energies.
[FRIEZA laughs]
[FRIEZA] I'm just moments
away from achieving
my maximum right now.
Aren't you curious?
You're a Saiyan, right?
Then, no doubt, you must be
burning to see my true power!
Well, watch and see.
[GOKU growls]
[thinking] Excellent.
Like a typical Saiyan,
he's going for the bait.
This victory is
going to be mine!
Ugh... This is crazy!
I don't know what's holding
this planet together anymore!
Bulma...
Where are you...?
I should be able to
sense your presence
but for some reason, I can't...
[GOHAN] Dad, I can't
leave you in this place!
This whole thing
could blow any second!
We're going to have to make
it out of here together!
[BULMA] Oh, no!
I'm stuck!
I-I can't move, I'm frozen!
Somebody help me!
Those rotten skunks!
This is it!
I'm one ticked-off
damsel in distress!
[BULMA gasps]
[BULMA screams]
Yikes!
Oh no! Help me!
[FRIEZA growls]
[GOKU] Huh?!
[growling continues]
[GOKU] Woah...
He's actually reaching the
true pinnacle of his power!
[FRIEZA growls]
[GOKU] I sense his desperation.
He's scared that I'm going
to attack before he finishes.
[FRIEZA yells]
[thinking] Just a
little bit longer...
Yes...
Yes!
[KING KAI] Goku?
This is King Kai.
Can you hear me?
Goku?!
Please answer me!
This is King Kai calling!
Now, look!
I know you can hear me, Goku!
You're just like all the others!
You learn what
I have to teach you
and then you forget
about the teacher!
If you don't
answer me,
I'm going to start
telling jokes!
And I've got a million of them!
Okay then, here goes:
What did the penguin
say to the astronaut?
[GOKU] Alright, alright!
I'm here, King Kai!
What is it?
[KING KAI] Goku, why aren't
you attacking Frieza?!
He's about to reach his maximum!
This could be your last chance!
[GOKU] I want him
to reach his maximum!
I want to fight him
when he's at his best!
What?! That's crazy!
[KING KAI] Goku!
Is it possible
that your new power
has altered your judgement?
Think about it!
[thinking] My true
power is close...
Yes! I can feel it!
[KING KAI] Goku, I want you
to know that I'm here for you.
If you need to talk...
I'm fine!
For some reason,
this is the way I want it!
[FRIEZA growls]
[KING KAI] Goku,
please! Attack now!
No!
[FRIEZA yells]
[GOKU growls]
I will not forget
what you did to my
best friend, Frieza!
You took from him what no one
has the right to take: Life!
[GOHAN] Krillin! No!
[GOKU] I won't let your
sacrifice be in vain, Krillin!
I can still see the
look on your face...
Help me! Aah--!
[GOKU] He had no right...
[KING KAI] I understand
how you feel, Goku!
But how is letting Frieza
achieve his maximum
going to help?!
[GOKU] If I face him now,
at his best, and beat him,
he'll never come back
to haunt us again!
It will be over for good!
[KING KAI] But it's
too risky, Goku!
What if you lose?
I won't lose! I can't lose!
[KING KAI] But what about
Gohan? And Piccolo?!
If Piccolo doesn't make it
then the others can't be wished
back with the Dragon Balls!
They'll survive!
I know that!
Somehow...
[FRIEZA giggles]
Oh, man!
Bulma! Where are you?
[BULMA] Help!
[BULMA screams]
Please, I don't want to die!
[BULMA gasps]
[BULMA screams]
[BULMA] Oh, no!
This is really it!
I can't believe it!
[BULMA sighs]
[BULMA screams]
Hey, thanks! Wow!
But, hey, what took you
so long, you big jerk!
And you could
have left yourself
more than one second
to spare, you know?!
This is my life that
we're talking about here!
Hello? Wake-up call?!
Where are Goku
and Krillin anyway?!
Those scoundrels!
Can we talk about
this later, Bulma?!
This whole planet
is about to blow!
Yeah, things are
a little unstable here
to say the least...
But we're going
home, aren't we?
Oh, my gosh! I can't believe
it! We're actually going home!
Yay!
I hope so...
All right!
[CHICHI] Gohan, this is mommy...
Gohan, why won't
you answer me...?
I'm sorry for yelling at you.
You're not grounded. Please...
Just say something, anything...
[CHICHI] Oh, no!
This is terrible!
What in the world
is going on up there?!
[DR. BRIEF] There are
only three things
that could cause this
transmission to fail.
One: the darn thing's broke.
Uh... Two: the whole ship
has been destroyed somehow.
And then there's three:
Interference from a series
electro-magnetic waves.
Which means the planet's axis,
it's being stretched
or compressed.
Goodness!
What does it mean when
the axis distorts?
Mmmm...
Uh, well, it means... Hmm...
Well, a sudden
change like that
could mean only one thing:
I'm afraid that the planet's
core has become unstable.
It's... um... gonna... blow...
--[CHICHI gasps]
--[ROSHI] Wha--?!
[FRIEZA growls]
C'mon! Just a bit more!
Almost there!
Frieza, let's do this
while we're still young.
I will let you reach your
maximum so there's no doubt
who the strongest
was when this is over!
I could have already
beaten you by now!
But when you lose, I want
you to know for certain
that you gave it
everything that you had!
That even at its fullest, your
power was no match for mine!
[FRIEZA] Alright, big guy.
Whatever turns you on.
[FRIEZA giggles]
[YAMCHA] King Kai!
What's the matter?!
When I was young,
I did what my master told me!
I don't understand this
thick-headed generation!
[FRIEZA grunts]
[FRIEZA growls]
[FRIEZA yells]
Bingo!
Ahh, that feels so
good. I'd forgotten.
Now, time to squash
you like a bug!
All that waiting and this
is how you thank me?
[KING KAI laughs]
[KING KAI] Oh my!
Maybe he hasn't
lost it after all!
[GOKU grunts]
[FRIEZA grunts]
[blows landing,
GOKU grunting]
[FRIEZA grunts]
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU growls]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[blows landing,
GOKU grunting]
[GOKU growls]
Huh?!
Huh?! Unbelievable!
This has never happened before!
They're moving so fast that even
I can't follow their motions!
Huh?
[FRIEZA yells]
Huh...?!
[yelling continues]
What the--?!
[GOKU] I can't even sense him!
Darn!
[GOKU] Alright! Where is he?!
[FRIEZA yells]
[GOKU grunts]
Bullseye!
[GOKU] Oh, man!
[FRIEZA yells]
[GOKU grunts]
Huh?!
[blows landing,
grunting]
[FRIEZA yells]
[BOTH grunting]
Let go of me,
you no-good, stinkin',
dirty Saiyan!
[FRIEZA growls]
Not today!
[BOTH grunting]
[GOKU] So this is it, huh?
Your true power?
Rrrgh!
Well, I'm not impressed!
[FRIEZA] Why, you...!
[FRIEZA] You'll be much more
impressed when you're dead!
[GOKU] I wouldn't count on it!
[BOTH grunting]
[FRIEZA laughs]
[FRIEZA growls]
[GOKU grunts]
[FRIEZA chuckles]
Well, fancy that!
One shot and he's
throwing in the towel.
Strike-up a dirge.
[FRIEZA chuckles]
[GOKU] Don't get too
excited, Frieza...
[FRIEZA growls]
Because this battle...
...is far from over!
[FRIEZA growls]
[NARRATOR] The battle between
Goku and Frieza continues.
But with each passing minute,
Planet Namek gets
closer to destruction.
Does Goku have time
to beat Frieza
and escape before
the explosion?
The clock is ticking...
on the next
exciting episode of
Dragon Ball Z!