[VEGETA chuckles]
Well, five Dragon Balls...
[NARRATOR] Last time,
on Dragon Ball Z!
Vegeta found the Dragon
Balls Frieza had collected
and threw them
into hiding...
Then, the sinister Saiyan
made his own daring escape...
[VEGETA} There now.
That ought to do it.
[FRIEZA] My Dragon Balls!
Where are my Dragon Balls?!
[ZARBON screaming]
Vegeta!
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, on the
other side of Planet Namek,
Krillin returned
with the Dragon Ball
bestowed on
him by Guru.
But it wasn't long
before others
were able to
track it down.
[BOTH] It's Vegeta!
[NARRATOR] And Zarbon,
sent to bring Vegeta
and the Dragon Balls
back to Frieza...
[Bulma] He's here
to rescue us!
Not even close!
[NARRATOR] Elsewhere, Goku
had problems of his own,
as a magnetic
storm played havoc
with the gravity
inside his ship,
leaving him
helpless and weak,
trapped on a
training chain...
Can our hero withstand
this interstellar onslaught?
Find out today!
[GOKU grunting]
[thunder crashing]
[grunting continues]
[GOKU grunting]
[thunder crackling]
[GOKU shouts]
[thunder crashing]
[ALL scream]
Goku!
The magnetic storm!
There's no way Goku can
take another hour in there!
It's killing him!
Doctor,
do something!
[OOLONG] Yeah! Use that brain
of yours for something! Please!
[DR. BRIEF] Wait! I think
I've figured it out!
[OOLONG &amp; PUAR] Huh?
[DR. BRIEF]
Well, maybe not...
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU] Come on...
just a little... farther...
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU screams]
[GOKU grunting]
Ka... Me...
Ha... Me... HAAA!
Huh?!
[GOKU grunting]
C'mon! Cut the chain!
[grunting]
[GOKU screams]
[bones snapping]
[GOKU screaming]
We're in trouble...
I'm in trouble!
Yeah...
'Cause I'm in love...
Uh?!
Bulma, I... I really don't
think he's here for a date!
You think he'd go
on a date with me?
Come on! Snap
out of it already.
I wonder if
he's noticed me?
He has, but not in the
way that you're thinking...
Vegeta, did you really
think that you could
escape me for long?
[VEGETA] Heh...
Ahh... Another
Dragon Ball.
How nice of you to
track it down for me.
[KRILLIN gasps]
[ZARBON] Don't tell me
you've joined forces with them?
[BULMA] Yoo-hoo!
Thank you for
coming to rescue me!
[VEGETA chuckles]
Idiot...
Those two don't
concern me.
All I want to know
is what you did
with the rest of
the Dragon Balls.
You can either tell me
or you can tell Frieza.
Your choice!
Try to make
me talk!
[ZARBON giggles]
With pleasure...
Well, get on with your
little transformation then.
You know perfectly well that
you can't possibly defeat me
unless you change into
that hideous creature.
Alright...
Now you've done it!
No one insults me
like that, Vegeta!
And for someone who
looks like you,
you have no right
to call me hideous!
I'd kill you
where you stand,
but Frieza wants me
to take you alive.
Consider
yourself lucky...
Ha! The only thing I'm going
to consider is how much pain
I make you endure before I end
your pathetic little life.
Come on,
let's go... Ugly!
[grunting]
Ah...!
My hero...
Bulma!
Haah!
[ZARBON laughs]
[VEGETA] Rrrgh!
Hah!
Guh!
[BULMA screaming]
Hey, Bulma! Now's our
chance! Let's run!
But he said he'd kill us
if we tried to escape!
We're dead anyway if we don't
get outta here! Come on!
[BULMA screams]
Going somewhere?!
Rraaugh!
[BULMA screams]
Oh well! Looks like
we're stuck here!
Huh?!
Nice try, Saiyan!
Ah!
Hyaah!
[FRIEZA] Stop apologizing
and start doing things right!
[FRIEZA] You're a
disgrace of a warrior!
You're not fit to serve me!
Now my Dragon Balls are
stolen and Vegeta is missing!
[FRIEZA growls]
[FRIEZA] You have
one hour to find them.
Don't disappoint me again!
Ah!
[thinking] He's stronger
than he was before!
Ha! Your power
is pathetic...
[VEGETA laughs]
What a waste
of time...
[laughing]
[ZARBON laughing]
[ZARBON roars]
[BOTH squealing]
[ZARBON laughing]
He changed
into a monster!
And he's become
even more powerful!
[BULMA] So much for
that date...
Congratulations!
You're the first to see
this form a second time!
I wonder why
the villagers
threw this Dragon
Ball in the lake...
Maybe they knew that
Vegeta was coming
so they hid it
down there!
Wait a minute... I'm sensing
two big power levels
back where I left Bulma!
I'd better hurry!
[VEGETA growling]
[ZARBON grunting]
How do I get myself
into these things?
Oh, Goku, where are
you when I need you?
Goku, be careful! Easy!
[GOKU grunting]
[thinking] Almost there...
Just a few more swings...
That's it! You can almost
make it to the Gravitron!
Come on!
You can do it!
[GOKU grunting]
[shouting]
Goku! Stop!
Control the swing!
The gravity will
rip you apart!
[shouting continues]
[GOKU growling]
Kaio-ken...
Haaa!
[GOKU growling]
[cheering]
[GOKU screams]
[ALL] Huh?
[GOKU groaning]
[grunting]
That took a
lot out of me...
I think all my
bones are broken...
But I've got to cut
this machine off...
[GOKU grunts]
[thunder crashing]
[ZARBON roars]
[VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA] Haah!
[VEGETA shouts]
[ZARBON laughing]
[roaring]
[OOLONG] Goku!
[PUAR] Goku! Are you
alright? Say something!
[OOLONG] Goku!
[thinking] If I don't cut off
that Gravitron, I'll die!
Well, that's easier
said than done...
[GOKU grunting]
[ALL whimpering]
[GOKU shouting]
[grunting]
You can do it!
Higher!
Yes, Goku! You're almost
to the control panel!
[GOKU grunting]
Huh?
[cheering]
Hey, I did it! The
gravity's back to normal!
And now that I've experienced
100 times gravity,
I know that that's
what I have to train in.
It's the only way I'll
stand a chance on Namek.
[ZARBON roaring]
[growling]
[ZARBON] Hyaah!
Hm?!
[ZARBON roaring]
[VEGETA chuckles]
[ZARBON whimpering]
[VEGETA growls]
[screaming]
Haaah...
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
[BULMA screaming]
[GOKU grunting]
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
[ZARBON growls]
[blows landing]
Vegeta, you're dead!
[VEGETA chuckles]
Face it, Zarbon,
you're no match for me...
I'm far stronger!
Now would be a good
time to start
begging me to
spare your life.
Begging you?!
[ZARBON laughs]
Your smart mouth won't be so
noisy once I crush your skull!
The first and last
mistake you made was to
underestimate the power
of a Saiyan warrior...
[ZARBON growls]
While so many
others grow weaker
during battle, we Saiyans
become stronger...
[GOKU grunting]
[thinking] Senzu Beans!
I'll have to thank
Yajirobe for these
next time
I see him...
[bones popping,
GOKU sighing]
[grunting]
[GOKU] Woo-hoo!
Alright! Time to
turn that machine
back up to 100
times normal gravity!
Huh?
Well, guess there's no harm
in having a snack first!
[GOKU giggles]
Bye!
You can bleed us to
the brink of death!
Crush every bone
in our bodies!
It only makes
us more powerful!
[ZARBON gasps]
He's just like Goku...
No matter how much of a
brutal beating Vegeta takes,
he gets stronger every
time that he fights!
I don't care how powerful
you think you've become,
you'll never defeat me while
I'm in this form, Vegeta!
[VEGETA laughs]
[ZARBON roaring]
You're wrong, I can kill
you in any form, Zarbon!
[blows landing,
grunting]
Haah...
Hyaah!
[ZARBON groaning]
[VEGETA chuckling]
[BULMA squeals]
[screams]
Vegeta!
I was just...
following... orders...
Please...
Don't... kill me...
Is it just me or
does it sound like
you're begging for your
life after all, Zarbon?
Vegeta... spare me...
and we'll be... a team...
We'll defeat
Frieza together...
[BULMA screams,
VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA] Haah!
[KRILLIN gasps]
[VEGETA chuckles]
[VEGETA] Once I have all
of the Dragon Balls,
I will be the one to
defeat Frieza... alone!
[VEGETA chuckles]
Well, now that we've taken
care of that little problem,
the three of
us have some
unfinished business
to attend to...
[KRILLIN growls]
I sense that you're
quite a bit stronger now
than you were
back on Earth,
but you're still
no match for me.
Hand. It. Over. Now.
No way! I'm not giving
up that easy, Vegeta!
You just try and take it from
me and we'll see what happens.
[VEGETA chuckles]
Then we're back
where we started!
Hand over that
Dragon Ball right now,
or the girl beside you
will pay for your actions!
No... Please,
don't hurt her...
Don't worry...
I don't think you'll
be around long enough
to see what happens to her.
Hand it over or you both die!
[KRILLIN] Here...
K... Krillin!
[VEGETA] The last Dragon Ball
is finally in my possession!
Now all that remains is
calling forth the Dragon!
Then I'll make my
wish for immortality
and become the Supreme
Ruler of the Universe!
And Frieza
will die!
[VEGETA laughs]
[BULMA sighs]
[thinking] I don't
think so, Vegeta...
You'll never get to
make that wish...
[Thinking] Hurry, Gohan!
We need that last Dragon Ball!
[NARRATOR] With the lone
Dragon Ball he recovered
from the Namekian village
in his possession,
Gohan holds the fragile hopes
of the planet in his hands.
But how long can the
young hero keep the ball
from Vegeta's
evil clutches?
Find out next time,
on Dragon Ball Z!