[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z,
energy clashed against energy
in the remote
fighting ground where
Goku and Vegeta
continued their duel,
a battle that had brewed
in the Saiyan Prince
for nearly a decade.
Vegeta, I don't understand.
You've never allowed anyone to
help you before in your life.
Why start now? Why Babidi?
[NARRATOR] And Vegeta revealed
he'd intentionally fallen
under Babidi's spell.
Just to gain more strength.
I was the perfect warrior!
Cold and ruthless!
I lived by my strength alone!
Uninhibited by foolish emotion!
Huh?!
[VEGATA roars]
[NARRATOR] And so the
struggle wages forward
with Vegeta's rampage of hate
perhaps too strong
for even Goku to stop.
[NARRATOR] But the fight
between the Saiyans
has left unexpected
consequences.
[NARRATOR]
Absorbing the enormous energy
that Goku had lost
in his fight...
The seal around
Buu was finally broken.
[NARRATOR] And unless
Gohan can act quickly,
the Supreme Kai's careful
plan will end in failure.
Ooo! It's really happening!
Majin Buu is at full power!
[laughs]
[NARRATOR]
Because now, the magic creature
that nearly destroyed
the universe
centuries ago is ready
for a second try.
[rythmic pulse sound]
[hysteric laughter]
[laughs]
[BABIDI chuckles]
Dabura, he's coming
out! It's really real!
Yes, Master!
He's going to come
out and when he does,
Everybody's going to run
around and suffer 'til they die!
My father will be avenged
by his own creation,
and I'm the one who
made it all possible!
Yes, you do him a great honor.
You have no idea how long
I've waited for this!
Counting down minutes
for centuries!
[BABIDI giggles]
Ahh! Ohhh! Ahhh!
[grunts]
[GOHAN thinking] Dad's energy
has gone beyond Super Saiyan.
Guess he had to do
it to stop Vegeta.
[SUPREME KAI gasps]
[GOHAN thinking]
But their stupid fighting
is gonna make this
Buu thing hatch!
Too late we must
retreat and quickly.
Huh?
We have no choice,
Run when I signal!
Wait! We've got to try and stop
this thing before it hatches
and starts hurting people!
There must be a way!
I mean, you are the Supreme Kai
for goodness sakes!
Yes, and unlike you I've
seen what Buu is capable of!
And it's more than
our present state can handle!
This is a time for strategy,
Gohan, not blind heroics!
We must regroup and
wait for a better opportunity!
We have to wait!
I'm sorry, but
I still have to try.
Please listen to me Gohan!
We need you alive!
But there's people I care about!
Gohan!
[growls]
And this time around,
I'm not going to just stand by
and let them all get hurt.
Hyaaaaagh!!
There's no stopping him!
Now what do you
suppose got into that one?
Fool!
Well at least I'll make
them work for it Ka-me...
[GOHAN]
...ha-me..
Haaa!
[gasps]
No!
Ka-me-ha-me HA!
Amazing!
Hold on Trunks! Hold on!
Huh? What, Goten?
[GOTEN] Something over
there feels really weird...
Do you think that could be
where the grown-ups are at?
[TRUNKS]
Yeah, but that's weird.
I still feel something from up
ahead of us, too. Don't you?
Uh-huh.
So which way is right?
Man! I wish they would have
left us some directions!
[GOTEN]
Whoa! Birdies! [laughs]
Why so many?
They sound kind
of frightened to me.
I don't know what
scared birds sound like
but I bet they're coming
from some kind of trouble.
Oh...
[TRUNKS] And that means
we know which way to go.
[frightened screams]
Why are they all running away?
Well...
[MR. SATAN]
Don't they know I'm here?
Well you didn't
exactly stop that guy
from blowing up
the arena earlier.
But...
Yeah it's a pity things had to
end like this sort of a downer.
I mean we didn't even have time
to give you the prize money.
Hey! Cheer up!
I say we continue the ceremonies
to keep up the morale!
Start by giving me the money!
Well I would but no one's
paying attention right now.
Hey! Everybody!
If you're looking
for a safe place,
then you're running
in the wrong direction!
You're under the
watchful eye of Mr. Satan!
Proven champion for all that
is good! Guardian of the world!
That's right! It's Mr. Satan!
[cheering]
[MR. SATAN]
Yaaaaah!! Haha!
[MR. SATAN thinking]
That's better.
Now I can get my cash
and hurry back home.
It's dangerous around here.
Hmmm... I'm feeling very strange
disturbances in the distance.
Can't tell what it is, exactly,
but it doesn't belong.
If things are wrong
then I just know Goku and
Gohan are mixed up in it!
And my little Goten
is missing too
and nobody can tell me anything!
What is going on?
This isn't helping, ChiChi!
Curse that boy.
Master, we must stop
this interference
before he ruins the hatching.
Oh, let him have
his fun, Dabura!
That level of attack is like
a flea bite to Majin Buu!
There! You see?! All that and
he can't even budge it one bit!
Haaaaaa!
Ah!
Hmm?
Oh!
Uh...
Here goes.
Ka-me-ha-me HAA!
Oooh! We did it!
He's really alive!
Our time has come.
It's empty!
Huh?
But... how? I did
everything correctly...
Followed every step...
Said every word...
Come out! Yes, come out
and destroy them all, Buu!
We're all waiting!
[SUPREME KAI laughs]
All your efforts, for nothing!
You've made a
fatal mistake, Babidi!
Just like your father!
Fooled by overconfidence!
Underestimated
your opponents!
And so this Earthling has
destroyed your sacred Buu!
Years of captivity in that shell
must have made him defenseless.
And not even the energy from
this planet could revive him!
Now.. the story of
Buu finally comes to an end.
Don't let that old
fool discourage you Babidi
even without Buu we can
still continue our plan.
And I'm sure that
with a little persuasion
the Saiyan Prince
could be put
more completely
under your control.
Oh it's no use!
Don't you understand?
There isn't any
plan without Buu!
To think I'd see the great
wizard of evil brought to tears!
Hahahahahaha!
Well galactic
domination may be ruled out
but what do you say we get rid
of this annoying Supreme Kai?
Sure. [chuckles]
[SUPREME KAI] All right
Gohan, let's work together
and put an end to this entire
ordeal as quickly as we can.
I'll get Babidi
to the ground
and prevent him from
casting his spells.
That way you can fight
Dabura without distraction.
I hope you realize the
significance of this day, Gohan!
You've released
your full powers
just like your father said
and now look what its done!
We're only one battle away
from bringing everything
back to normal!
No, Supreme Kai... We're not.
Huh?!
My last attack still
wasn't strong enough
to destroy the energy
I felt in there.
There's something... Huh?!
But, I don't sense
anything, Gohan! It can't be!
All I know is that something
did come out of that shell
and it's up there now!
Dabura...
What is the boy looking at?
[DABURA] Clouds...
No, it's some kind of smoke.
I can't feel anything
from it but emptiness.
[SUPREME KAI]
But what is it?
Hyaaargh!
[GOKU thinking]
His moves are incredible!
[VEGETA thinking] Finally,
I'm going to rip him apart!
Hyaaaaaa!
Ugh!!
[snickers]
[GOKU chuckles]
I'm getting a terrible feeling.
Hey look!
Something's forming!
I'm beginning to detect...
Aaah!
Buu!
Awww...
Tell me, Master. Is this the...
the great Majin Buu?
[BABIDI]
Well...
To tell you the truth
I'm not quite sure.
See. The only person
who's actually seen Buu
is that annoying rat,
Kai, over there.
So, what's the
verdict, Supreme Kai?
Is this the guy
you're so afraid of?
Yes, that's Bibidi's
creation without a doubt.
I could never forget that
disgusting creature's face.
[gasps]
Oooh! Look how scared
the Kai is! It must be him!
Are you positive?
Hey! Majin Buu! Come to me!
[GOHAN] Strange...
The way you talked
I thought he'd be much larger.
[SUPREME KAI] I can't bear to
look at him! We have to retreat!
I'm not so sure about that.
You may have been
right about him weakening
from his years in captivity.
He's obviously tough, but
I don't think he's unbeatable.
Wha... But don't you sense
his power? His strength?!
Yeah... But I'm also
well aware of what I can do.
[gasps]
Buu!
[BUU giggles]
Oh, ho haha. Woop.
[BUU hums]
Ohhhh...
That's right Buu,
come to your master!
[giggles]
Uh...
[BABIDI]
Hey... Where are you going?
[pants]
[grunts] Hyaargh!
Hey! Wait a second!
[VEGETA]
Huh?!
I just felt a
tremendous surge of energy!
While we've been
fighting each other,
that Buu creature must
have been hatched!
[pants]
[growls]
[BUU laughs]
Whooa! Woop. Woop. Woop.
Woooo....
Buu... Buu...
Buu! [laughs]
[NARRATOR]
At long last,
despite the heroic efforts
of the Z Fighters,
Buu has been unleashed!
But does this pudgy,
pink, infant-like creature
really have the power to
put the planet in jeopardy?
Don't miss the next
episode of Dragon Ball Z!
Buu!