[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z!
Evil descended
from the skies,
as the Ginyu Force made
their explosive landing
on Planet Namek!
With no time to spare,
Krillin, Vegeta, and Gohan
raced to gather the
seven Dragon Balls
in order to combat
these deadly foes.
[KRILLIN] Sorry... No
time to explain, Bulma!
I need the Dragon Ball!
[VEGETA] Quickly, now!
Follow me to the others!
Hey, hang on a
second! Come back!
What's going on?!
You could at
least fill me in!
Come back here!
Youuu!!
Why those...
What the...?
What was Krillin
doing with Vegeta?
[NARRATOR] As startling
as it seemed,
allowing Vegeta to
wish for immortality
was our heroes' only hope
for surviving the onslaught
of Frieza's
unstoppable henchmen!
I'm Recoome!
Burter!
I'm Jeice!
Guldo!
Captain Ginyu!
Now! You! See! The! Power!
Of the Ginyu Force!
[FRIEZA] At ease, men. I have
an important errand for you.
Thank you, Lord Frieza.
Glad to be of service.
So let's get
down to business.
What is
our mission?
[FRIEZA] It's quite
simple, Captain Ginyu.
Your mission is to
recover my Dragon Balls
and bring me Vegeta!
Vegeta...?
Ha, ha! Stupid Saiyan.
I always said he was
too cocky for his own good!
Looks like that ego of his
finally got him into trouble.
So, you've finally shown
your true colors, Vegeta...
You can expect
resistance.
Vegeta's strength has
grown considerably
since last
you saw him.
Woah!
Huh...?
[FRIEZA] Now, you know what
to do. Get those Dragon Balls,
and bring
me the Saiyan!
Oh, and before you go getting
carried away: I want him alive.
Consider it done,
Lord Frieza.
Vegeta doesn't
appear to be making
any efforts to
conceal himself.
He should be an easy catch.
You'll have him kneeling at
your feet within the hour.
Hmm...?
[FRIEZA] What is it, Ginyu?
[GINYU] Who are these
other two he has with him?
Both of them
seem to have
fairly significant
power levels as well.
Others? Ah,
that's right.
It's probably those
two meddlesome pests
we encountered
earlier.
Vegeta must have
formed a little gang!
And what
of them?
I suppose you
can kill them.
Yeah!
Right!
As you wish. It will be
our pleasure, Lord Frieza!
[ALL chuckling]
[GULDO] Hmm...
[GULDO] Hey!
Watch it, Vegeta...
You'd better start
remembering your place,
you arrogant
Saiyan monkey.
You're nothing
compared to us!
We make the rules around
here, and you follow!
The only reason you're
even still breathing
is because Lord Frieza
has taken a liking to you.
[VEGETA] Hmph!
[GULDO gasps]
[VEGETA chuckles]
Who do you
think you are?
The last I checked,
you took orders from Frieza
the same as I do.
Just because Frieza's put
you on the Ginyu Force,
it doesn't
change a thing.
You'll always be a
sniveling four-eyed freak.
What?! Why you
insolent little--!
[VEGETA] Now, if I was calling
the shots instead of Frieza,
you'd be licking my boots.
Urgh... Now you've
pushed me too far!
[GULDO growls]
Raah--!
[FRIEZA] That's enough fun
and games for one day, Vegeta.
Playtime is over.
[FRIEZA] I have
a job for you...
There's a nice
little planet
I've had my eye
on for some time.
Why don't you join me, and
we'll conquer it together?
As you command, Frieza.
Get used to that spot, Guldo.
I'll see you there again.
[VEGETA laughs]
[GULDO growling]
Damn you,
Vegeta!
Yo, what's wrong?
You got something in
one of your eyes there?
Snap out of it!
I see
revenge.
Here you go, Lord Frieza,
the scouter you asked for.
The newest model.
Ah, good work.
[GINYU] Ginyu Force!
[GINYU] Let's get busy.
[ALL] Hut! Hut! Hut!
Hut! Hut! Hut!
[BURTUR &amp; RECOOME] Haa! Haa!
[GULDO &amp; JEICE] Haa! Haa!
[ALL] Hoo! Hoo!
Hoo! Hoo! Hoo!
[ALL] Ginyu Force! Hoo!
Hoo! Hoo! Hoo! Hoo!
[ALL screaming]
[ALL growling]
[ALL] Gooo!
[thinking] The Ginyu Force!
They're coming!
We have to go faster!
[KRILLIN growls]
[thinking] Vegeta's right!
And it feels like
they're gaining on us!
Oh, Dad, where are you?
We need you!
[COMPUTER] Attention.
Destination alert.
Now on final approach
to Planet Namek.
ETA, 20 minutes.
[alarm ringing]
[muffled rining,
GOKU grunting]
[GOKU yawns]
Huh...?
Wait a sec...
[GOKU] Hope I've got
a change of clothes...
Huh...?
[GOKU chuckles]
[GOKU] Well, I guess Dr. Brief
really thought of
everything, huh?
[GOKU] There's a lot of trouble
waiting for me down there...
Hang on, guys... I'm coming.
Ten minutes left.
Strange, but, I don't
feel the least bit scared.
Maybe it's the calm
before the storm.
I've just got to try
to keep myself focused.
Gotta stay alert...
because there's no
more time for training.
It's time to get out
there and help my friends!
[VEGETA] Ah! It's down there!
[VEGETA laughs]
[VEGETA] Come on!
Here th--!
Huh?
What are you
waiting for?!
[BOTH whimpering]
What is it?!
Y'know, suddenly this doesn't
seem like such a good idea.
We might be better off
taking our chances
than letting him
have his wish!
This isn't a game!
Give me that ball!
I'm losing
my patience!
You ignorant fool!
You'll kill us all!
[KRILLIN gasps]
Raah--
Huh?!
[BOTH gasp]
[GINYU] Hello, Vegeta.
[JEICE] Hi, mate!
[BURTER] It's been a long time!
[ALL laugh]
Dammit! Not now!
I was so close!
[ALL laughing]
[KRILLIN whimpers]
Aw, man! How'd they
get here so fast?
I thought we'd
have more time!
[laughter continues]
[GOHAN whimpering]
We've come to collect you
and the Dragon Balls, Vegeta.
Hey, Cap'n...
Looks like we got the
other five balls right here.
[GINYU chuckles]
[ALL laughing]
If you only would
have listened to me!
How was I
supposed to know?
[GOHAN whimpering]
[GINYU] This is going to be
even easier than I expected...
I should thank
you, Vegeta,
for having all
seven Dragon Balls
packaged up so
neatly for us.
But you'll
understand if I don't.
[thinking] Rrgh!
Vegeta was right!
There's no way we can beat
all five of these guys!
Their power levels...
They're terrifying!
Especially that one...
The leader...
Don't get too
cocky, Ginyu!
You haven't
beaten me, yet!
[GULDO chuckles]
Oh, you think you're
pretty tough don't ya?
Well, this time you
won't have Frieza
to save your
scrawny carcass!
Oh, I've
waited for this!
Really?!
Yeah, that's
right! Come on!
Huh?
[thinking] This little guy has
lots of eyes, but no brains!
He's the one
guy in the group
Vegeta could beat with both
arms tied behind his back!
[GULDO chuckles]
Guldo...
You're still a freak.
[GULDO growls]
Raah!
Now, hold up
there, Guldo...
Frieza wants him
back alive, remember?
[GINYU] Vegeta,
don't be silly.
You'll save us all
a lot of trouble
if you hand over the
Dragon Ball... Come on, now.
[VEGETA] Heh!
Yeah, right!
And next you'll ask
me to surrender
so you can take me
back to Frieza!
Is that the plan?
Something like that...
[VEGETA] Rrgh! Go to hell!
Uh... Huh...?
[BURTER] Nice try!
[JEICE] You're
so quick, mate.
Ahh...!
[ALL laughing]
[BOTH gasp]
Yes, a valiant
effort, Vegeta...
But, as you can see,
my friend Burter here
just loves a good
game of catch!
[BURTER] Mm-hmm!
H-how... How'd
he do that?!
And now, the
other one please.
Destroy it!
[KRILLIN yells]
Wuh--! Eh?! Huh?!
Hey, where'd it go?
[GULDO sighs]
What happened?
[VEGETA growls]
So, then it's true
what they say...
Well, you gonna tell
us what they say?
I never believed it,
but Guldo has the ability to
freeze an instant in time.
[GULDO chuckling]
No way!
Impossible!
Yeah, just keep
thinking that!
[GULDO chuckles]
All right, we have
what we came for.
Now to deal with
these three.
Make sure you treat
them nicely, boys.
Yeah, an' when he
says treat 'em nice,
that don't mean we're
gonna buy you flowers
or nothin'
like that...
No, it means we're
gonna kill you!
Oh, would you
please shut-up!
[JEICE] Right, right.
Sorry 'bout that.
[KRILLIN] Come on! We can
still make a run for it...
It's no use.
We can't run from this.
We have no choice
but to stand and fight.
[VEGETA] If we
combine our powers,
we might hold out long
enough to discover
some weakness
we can exploit.
I'll handle Vegeta.
The rest of you can do that
"rock-paper-scissors" thing
to decide who
gets the other two.
[ALL whining]
[VEGETA growling]
[GOHAN whimpering]
Come on, Captain! Let me
have Vegeta! I owe him one!
All right,
fine. You win.
Have Vegeta. But you'd
better make sure
he's still
breathing when you
bring him back to Frieza.
Are we clear?
[ALL cheering]
[GINYU] And who are we?!
[ALL] We are the
Ginyu Force!
And don't forget it,
or you will regret it!
[JEICE] Yeah, mate!
You are so in trouble now!
Okay, who
gets who?
[BOTH whimper]
You ready, boys?
[VEGETA growls]
[GINYU FORCE] Rock,
paper, scissors!
Are you sure we shouldn't
be trying to get away?
[GINYU FORCE] Rock,
paper, scissors!
Ha-haaa! Yes!
I get Vegeta!
You always win!
Now, don't be a sore
loser. Fair is fair.
[RECOOME] Awwh,
tell you what...
I'll let you have a few
hits if you want, Guldo.
[GULDO giggles]
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I have to take these
Dragon Balls to Lord Frieza.
[GINYU laughing]
Take this,
you big bully!
Stop! He's gone!
Save your energy!
Concentrate on the
four who are still here.
If we can defeat them,
we'll catch up to him later.
[GOHAN growls]
You... Come over here.
I think they're making
some kinda plan!
It looks like you two
will be fighting Guldo.
You'll have to
use your heads.
A direct assault won't work.
Do you understand?
Yeah.
Didn't you say
earlier that Kakarot
was supposed to be coming
here to save everybody?
Don't know
about you,
but he's coming to
save Gohan and me.
I'm not trying to win
a popularity contest here!
All I'm saying is we could
use his help right now!
[thinking] I can't
let Piccolo down!
We've got to get the
Dragon Balls back!
Frieza can't be allowed to
make his wish! He just can't!
[GULDO &amp; RECOOME chuckling]
[ALL growling]
Hey there, Guldo,
why don't you ahead and
take your turn first?
Yeah, now that
you mention it,
I suppose that is
the best thing to do.
After all, we gotta get
the trash outta the way
so we have plenty of
room to crush Vegeta!
All right. It's time to
see what you're made of.
Gohan... Just remember
the power you have within!
Awww... I was hoping
they'd be begging for mercy.
Ready, Gohan?
Hm.
[KRILLIN] Then let's
turn up the heat!
Huh?!
[BOTH shouting]
[RECOOME] Oh...
Wh-What in the--?!
[NARRATOR] The battle against
the Ginyu Force has begun!
And as Gohan and Krillin launch
the first powerful volley,
it appears they've caught
their opponent off-guard!
But Vegeta knows victory
will not come so easily...
Our heroes will have
to use every ounce
of their strength
and courage
if they hope to
win this fight...
On the next
Dragon Ball Z!