[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball Z...
Hidden deep underground, the
sleeping Majin Buu
was closely monitored by Babidi
and the demon king Dabura.
Their goal: to collect enough
energy to free the monster
from his cocoon and unleash him
upon the unsuspecting Earth.
[NARRATOR] Krillin and Piccolo
learned the hard way
just how dangerous Babidi could
be, but that didn't scare Goku.
[NARRATOR] He led Gohan,
Vegeta and the Supreme Kai
boldly into
Babidi's spacecraft.
But the evil wizard had stocked
his ship with warriors
waiting on each level
to do them in!
[NARRATOR] Using his
Super Saiyan strength,
Vegeta made
short work of Pui Pui,
the fighter guarding Stage One
of Babidi's spaceship.
But Stage Two would prove
much more difficult.
Standing in Goku's way
was the monster Yakon.
A beast with a sweet tooth for
light who found the energy
of the Super Saiyan
extra tasty.
[YAKON roars]
[NARRATOR] Yakon planned to
make a meal out of Goku,
but he bit off more
than he could chew,
and that caused the gluttonous
ghoul to burst at the seems.
Once the smoke cleared,
Goku and his friends
would be free to
advance to Stage Three.
A proposition which made
Babidi rather nervous.
[BABIDI]
...Who will protect me?
[DABURA laughs]
For Stage Three, I will be the
warrior they must battle.
I am Dabura.
I am the Demon King!
And you will have my word that I
will fill Majin Buu
with their energy when
I destroy every one of them.
[GOHAN] You'd think Babidi
could have at lest
varied up the
décor a little bit.
All these Stages
look the same...
[VEGETA]
Get used to it.
I have a feeling we're going
to be here for a while.
Well, hopefully the next
fighter through that door
will be worth the wait.
Gohan! Your next!
Goku! Listen to me!
This is not a game.
Babidi's henchmen come from the
four corners of the universe and
every one of them is
incredibly strong.
We've all been lucky so far,
but I think from now on
we should all fight together.
Nah. Don't you worry
about it, Supreme Kai.
Gohan doesn't need any help.
Besides, that would be unfair!
[gasps]
Unfair?!
Well... Vegeta and I
both got to fight alone,
so don't you think Gohan should
have a turn for himself, too?
[GOHAN] Yeah!
I can take care of myself.
Just wait, I'll show you!
[whimpers]
Yes! Go and get them!
[chuckles] Master,
I am going to crush them all!
Ah! Where are you going, sir?
Level Three is the other way!
[BABIDI] Dabura's going to get
into the fighting spirit
in the meditation room!
The meditation room?
[grunts]
Ah, I see!
That's how he focuses
his incredible power!
[BABIDI laughs]
Guard! Listen, I don't
want you to open that door
until Dabura tells you to.
Yes sir!
[BABIDI] I'm glad he's
taking this seriously.
He can be such a devil!
Oh, I just can't wait to see the
look on all of their faces
when Dabura walks
through the door.
[giggles]
[GOHAN]
Boy, it's getting late...
How long is Babidi
going to keep us waiting?
Relax, Gohan.
He's probably just having
trouble finding anyone
strong enough to fight you.
[GOHAN]
Yeah...
So, uh, I wonder
how they're doing
back at the World Martial
Arts Tournament?
[GOHAN]
I don't know, Dad.
I mean, we did sorta
leave 'em in a bit of a bind.
I would have preferred
to fight you there, Kakarot,
than come to this place.
This has been a waste of my time
battling these cretins.
[GOHAN chuckles]
I know what you mean, Vegeta,
I was looking forward to
duking it out in the ring
with my Dad, too.
[GOKU]
Oh yeah?
I'm ready for the both of you!
Anytime, anywhere!
[SUPREME KAI thinking]
These Saiyans are impossible!
They enjoy the thrill of a
challenge so much
that they ignore the
dangers of fighting!
Reckless!
[CROWD shouting, yelling]
Hey! What's the hold up?!
How long do we have to wait?!
You better start the
match or else!
[ANNOUNCER whimpers]
So you want to disqualify them?
[FRIAR D] Well, they
haven't come back yet!
[FRIAR E]
It's our only choice!
[OX-KING]
Did I miss anything?
Are they ready to start?
No way.
They can't start until Goku and
the other guys come back.
Bulma, I'm worried. Where
do you think they could be?
[growls] They're pretty
far away, wherever they are...
And I sense that they're in
some sort of trouble, too.
[YAMCHA]
Huh...
Okay, if they're not back within
the hour, they're disqualified!
[FRIAR D] But that leaves
only five fighters
in the whole tournament!
[FRIAR C]
Hmm...
That'll never work.
[TRUNKS] Oh no, did we miss the
start of the competition?
[GOTEN]
I think we're just in time!
[MR. SATAN] Hmph.Those sissy
cowards haven't come back yet.
I guess I scared them off.
Oh well, the show must go on!
At least the four of you
have enough guts
to stick around and fight me.
[KILLA talks incoherently]
[TRUNKS grunts]
Well, it's time!
Look, it's Mr. Satan!
Hey, Mister Satan!
[CROWD cheers]
[CROWD] Mr. Satan!
Mr. Satan! Mr. Satan!
Thank you my friends!
I know you came to see
a show of strength
and I'm gonna give it to you!
Mr. Satan always comes through
for his loyal fans! Yeah!
[CROWD cheers]
You the man, Mister Satan!
Yeah! Come on, show us
what you got, Mister Satan!
[MISTER SATAN]
Yeah-ha-ha!
[growls, chuckles]
That old guy's a clown,
isn't he?
[GOTEN]
No. Clowns are funny.
[MR. SATAN]
Now, listen here, guys.
The only thing that's gonna
satisfy this crowd
is some action.
[FRIAR E] There are only five
fighters. What do you suggest?
A battle royale!
[FRIARS]
A battle royale?!
[MR. SATAN]
Yes!
Disqualify the cowards
who took off
and have all five remaining
fighters duke it out
in the ring at
the same time.
The crowd will go wild!
They'll love it!
In fact, this'll probably be
the single greatest
moment of their lives!
And you can take that
all the way to the bank!
Ha-ha!
Hey! Great idea!
Leave it to Mr. Satan to come up
with a great plan like this!
Uh, Mr. Satan?
It's just that...
Well, I'm a bit concerned...
Yeah? Speak up!
It sounds like you got a problem
with my great idea or something.
Uh?
All right, if you don't like it,
I guess I'll just go home...
No don't do that!
I-It's a wonderful idea, sir!
Good! It's settled!
Tell the crowd!
Right!
Ladies and gentlemen!
Sorry to keep you waiting, but
I now have some terrific news.
At the suggestion of
Mister Satan,
we have decided to
hold a battle royale
among the five
remaining fighters!
All five will take to the
ring simultaneously,
and the last one standing
will be the winner!
[CROWD cheering]
Yeah! Three cheers
for Mister Satan!
Oh my! I think I'm in love!
Mister Satan it looks like your
battle royale idea is a hit.
It was very courageous
of you to suggest it.
Uh. What?
Well, yes. Of course.
Defending your title against
four challengers at once
is no easy feat.
To be honest, if you were anyone
else, I'd say you were a fool!
[laughs] The last thing a
champion like me
ever worries about is
the competition!
Yes, of course.
Everyone knows that you're the
best fighter on planet Earth.
Right? He's great!
[MR. SATAN thinking]
I'm done for!
A battle royale, huh?
Oh no, do you think
it's going to start
before Goku and Gohan get back
from where ever they are?
[ROSHI growls]
That's "if" they come back!
What are you saying, old man?!
Of course they'll be back!
[sighs] How else will
I win my prize money?
Now let me tell you the
names of the participants
in the battle royale,
and I'll start with
the most important
fighter first!
You know him, you love him!
It's Mr. Satan!
[CROWD cheers]
[MR. SATAN thinking]
This is it! It's showtime!
[MR. SATAN grunts]
[squeals, whimpers]
--[MR. SATAN yells]
--[CROWD cheers loudly]
[ANNOUNCER]
Now, here's the blonde bombshell
with the wacky name! Let's hear
it for beautiful Number 18!
[Yo! I got your number, baby!
[ANDROID 18]
Hmph.
[OX-KING]
Hey, Number 18!
Good luck!
Go, Mommy! Get 'em!
--[ANDROID 18 giggles]
--Next, we have a guy
who was defeated in the first
round of the last tournament!
Say hello to Mighty Mask!
This is it, Goten!
Let's give the people a show!
[GOTEN]
Let's do it!
[BOTH wail]
Now meet our next contestant.
He's a force to be
reckoned with! It's Killa!
[grunts]
And last but certainly
not least...
This fighter made it
all the way to the finals
last time he was here...
The ladies love him!
Here he is! Jewl!
[FEMALE CROWD MEMBERS]
We love you, Jewl! [giggling]
[ANNOUNCER]
There you have it!
The battle royale will be among
these five skilled fighters!
[grunts]
Are you ready, Goten?
[GOTEN]
I'm kinda nervous.
We never fought in the
adult division before...
Nahh.
[ANNOUNCER] There you have it,
ladies and gentlemen!
One of these five fighters
will be our next World Champion!
So don't move a muscle,
this colossal brawl
is about to begin!
[KILLA talks incoherently]
Ah! No thanks.
It's not Mr. Satan I'm
worried about, it's Number 18!
And once she's down, I'm coming
after you, stupid. Right?
[GOTEN]
Yeah!
[KILLA gasps, stammers]
Man, you talkin' funny!
Hi there... Do you
come here often?
You sure are beautiful...
Why not throw the fight
and have dinner
with me instead?
Whatta ya say, sweetheart? Come
on, it'll just be the two of us.
I promise.
Get lost...
...you insect.
[JEWL] What?! What'd you say?!
Don't you know who I am?!
All right! It's time!
So... Glue your eyes to the ring
and your backs to your seats!
Get ready, 'cause here comes
the Battle Royale!
[CROWD cheers]
[ANDROID 18]
Hm?
[growls]
[CROWD] Mi-ster Sa-tan! Mi-ster
Sa-tan! Mi-ster Sa-tan!
[MR. SATAN thinking]
Come on! I'm ready.
What are they waiting for?
Let's get this over with!
[JEWL thinking]
I'll show her!
No girl has ever turned
down a date with me!
[KILLA thinks incoherently]
Now! Begin!
[CROWD roars]
Haaa...!
Killa!
Haa!
[JEWL grunts]
[KILLA squeals]
[MR. SATAN whimpers]
[KILLA groans, mumbles]
[JEWL groans]
[MR. SATAN whimpers]
Wow! I never would
have guessed it!
Both Killa and Jewl are
out of it! They're both history!
Look at that!
Number 18 kicks butt!
Well, I'll tell ya, that
Mighty Mask is pretty good, too!
Yeah! Go, Mom! Get 'em!
[CROWD cheers]
[OX-KING]
Hang in there Number 18!
You can do it!
[CHICHI]
Give it all you got!
[MR. SATAN thinking]
Those two went down easy!
Maybe if I'm lucky, the next
two will take each other out!
Yeah... But I'd better
keep my guard up!
These guys look kinda tough...
[thinking] At least I still
got the crowd on my side.
[ANDROID 18 thinking]
That guy with the mask
is no ordinary fighter...
He's got an unbelievable punch!
How does he do it
with those tiny arms?
Hey, Goten. Listen! Krillin's
wife is a whole lot stronger
than he is so we
better be careful, okay?
[GOTEN]
Yeah, I got ya!
[MR. SATAN]
Who wants some of this, huh?!
I got two fists of fury and
there's one for each of you!
[TRUNKS]
We'll take care of him later.
[GOTEN]
Yeah...
[MR. SATAN grunts]
[growls]
[ANNOUNCER] Ladies and gentlemen
only three fighters remain
in the battle royale!
Mighty Mask, Number 18, and our
current champion Mister Satan!
It's come down to this!
And only one of these three
will emerge the victor!
[MR. SATAN chuckles]
[thinking]
First, I'll get that Mighty Mask
with a few of my
flashiest moves...
[MR. SATAN yells]
[CROWD] Mis-ter Sa-tan!
Mis-ter Sa-tan!
[thinking] Now what would
be the best way to knock
that 18 girl out of
the competition?
[MR. SATAN yells]
[MR. SATAN] Quick and painless!
After all I am a gentleman.
[thinking] Those poor saps
never knew what hit 'em!
Yeah! I showed them!
[MR. SATAN]
Yeah!
[ANNOUNCER] Wow, Mr. Satan is
already declaring victory!
That's what I call showmanship!
[thinking] Yeah, I won again!
Aw, it was all too easy...
He's such a blockhead.
[GOTEN]
That's for sure.
You! You with the mask on!
Are you ready to get the
pummeling of your life?!
Pay attention!
I'm gonna teach you
real martial arts!
[laughs]
Number 18 first,
then Mr. Satan.
Got it?
[GOTEN]
Okay!
[yells]
[TRUNKS, GOTEN growl]
[MR. SATAN yells]
[yells]
[TRUNKS growls]
Yaah!
[MR. SATAN gasps]
[gasps]
[ANDROID 18 grunts]
[TRUNKS grunts]
[ANDROID 18 gasping]
[MR. SATAN whimpers]
Wow!
Whee!
Since Goku isn't in the fight,
I guess I'll just have to
cheer for Number 18!
Get 'im! Number 18! Go!
[OOLONG]
Oh! Oh! Oh!
Yay, Mommy!
[ROSHI]
Hmm...
[ROSHI thinking]
Eh? What was that?
[TRUNKS]
Not that way!
To the right. To the right!
[GOTEN]
I'm trying! I'm trying!
[TRUNKS]
Whoa!
[TRUNKS gasps]
[GOTEN] Trunks!
It's no good! It's time to fly!
[gasps]
[ANNOUNCER]
And they're off!
Their fists are flying
and so are they!
[BOTH grunting]
[GOKU]
Aw, man! What's the hold up?
Let's smash
the door in!
No, stop! Don't do that!
I'm sick of all this waiting!
Please!
Whatever you do, Vegeta,
you mustn't create a shock!
[BABIDI laughs]
Ah, good...
How's Dabura doing?
Sir! He's still meditating.
[BABIDI]
Good!
Soon he'll be ready to go
crush the three intruders.
I can hardly wait!
[chuckles]
[NARRATOR] The meditation
chamber has served Dabura well.
Now, with his
mind and body focused,
his power at its maximum,
the Demon King
is ready for battle.
But so are the Z-Fighters!
They know that they've got only
one more opponent to beat
before reaching the
heart of Babidi's ship
and the evil wizard himself.
And Gohan's itching for a fight!
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
the Battle Royale rages on!
Number 18 and Mighty Mask
vie for the top prize,
and while they exchange
volley after volley
high above the Earth,
Mr. Satan's chances of winning
the Tournament are
crashing to the ground!
Faced with not one,
but two challengers
of incredible
strength and speed,
it seems the champion
will have no choice
but to relinquish his title...
Which of these fighters
will win the day?
Stay tuned for scenes
from the next Dragon Ball Z!