[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Goku took a snooze and
was haunted by nightmares
of the two terrifying Saiyans
who are making their way
towards planet Earth...
That got him
back on his feet
and moving even faster
along Snake Way...
He came across a castle that
he thought was King Kai's,
but it turned out that it
belonged to the charming
but deadly
Princess Snake...
And oh boy, did she ever
live up to that name!
Once the Princess
shed her skin,
Goku realized he was in
the belly of a beast.
So he made a
hasty retreat...
But it turns out that the
Princess never lets her guests
leave her with
an empty stomach,
and Goku almost became
the hot item on the menu!
Not wanting to
end up snake food,
Goku shook the
Princess off his tail
by setting a trap
of his own...
Using himself as bait,
he tied the Princess up
and left her
tightly tangled
and got back
on Snake Way...
Now he's on
track again,
still in search
of King Kai
and the special
martial arts training
that he so badly needs...
Meanwhile, Gohan is doing
his own training on Earth...
It won't be long until
those two evil Saiyans
arrive on the planet.
I sure hope Goku and Gohan have
what it takes to stop them!
[NARRATOR] Every good
martial artist knows
that you have to train your
mind as well as your body,
and Gohan is no exception...
With his daily
training completed,
he keeps his mind busy with
his school homework...
But all the arithmetic and
language lessons in the world
can't keep memories of
his mother and father
from creeping
into his head...
[GOHAN hums]
[GOHAN] Let's see...
Carry the one and add two...
No... X equals one and
carry the one... Hm...
[CHICHI] What a smart
boy you are, Gohan!
You just solved one of the
hardest problems in your book!
Thatta boy!
You keep studying like that
and you're going to be
a great scholar one
day. I just know it!
Yup! He's a chip
off the old block!
[GOHAN] I miss my Mommy
and Daddy so much...
[NARRATOR] On the other
side of the planet,
Piccolo works on his own kind
of intensive training...
Recalling his near-disastrous
battle with Raditz,
he works out new
fighting strategies
and attack
combinations...
[PICCOLO] Here it comes!
Special Beam Cannon!
[PICCOLO]
Hraaah!
[RADITZ grunts]
[GOKU gasps]
[PICCOLO roars]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[GOKU yells]
[PICCOLO shudders]
[RADITZ snarls]
He... He dodged it...
He's faster than the...
the speed of light!
You took a chunk
out of my armor.
I guess even you can
get lucky sometimes...
[RADITZ chuckles]
I won't let it
happen again.
[PICCOLO] Ha. You won't even
see the next attack coming!
You don't even come
close to my power level.
Give it up! You're through!
Your life will end today!
I don't think so!
[PICCOLO roars]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[PICCOLOS grunt]
[OTHER PICCOLO grunts]
Ah! Great!
[GOHAN grunts]
[GOHAN stammers]
[GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN laughs]
It works!
Yeah!
[GOHAN laughs]
[GOHAN]
Yahoo!
That... snake... lady sure
wasted a lot of my time!
I've really got to
pick up the pace
if Earth is
going to be saved!
[GOHAN]
Woo-hoo! What a ride!
If only my daddy
could see me now!
[GOHAN laughs]
[GOHAN]
Uh-- Uhh...?
[EAGLE squawks]
[GOHAN stammers]
[GOHAN] Nah-nah!
You won't catch me!
[GOHAN laughs]
Bleh!
[GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN shudders]
[EAGLE shrieks]
[GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN shudders]
[GOHAN grunts]
[GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN shudders]
[GOHAN yells in the distance]
[TIGER grumbles
inquisitively]
[GOHAN yells]
[TIGER growls]
[EAGLE shrieks]
[TIGER grunts
inquisitively]
[GOHAN makes
muffled noises]
[TIGER grunts
inquisitively]
[GOHAN chokes, coughs]
[TIGER growls]
Hi! How are you?
[GOHAN sighs]
Hm?
U-Uh...
Oh... Ah...
[GOHAN]
Whoa! Where am I?
This sure is
a big place...
[GOHAN &amp; TIGER
grunt inquisitively]
[GOHAN] I wonder if I can
find my house from here...
I hope so...
[TIGER growls]
[GOHAN laughs]
[TIGER grunts]
[TIGER yells]
[TIGER groans]
[GOHAN snores]
[TIGER pants]
[TIGER grunts]
[TIGER snarls]
[TIGER roars]
[TIGER groans]
[TIGER's stomach rumbles]
[TIGER grunts]
[GOHAN snores]
[GOKU snores]
[GOHAN laughs]
[TIGER grumbles]
[GOHAN] Ha ha ha!
Mommy! Here I come!
[GOHAN laughs]
[TIGER shudders]
[TIGER trembles]
[GOHAN laughs]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[OTHER PICCOLO yells]
[PICCOLO yells]
[PICCOLO]
Hraaah!
[TIGER grumbles, yawns]
[TIGER barks frantically]
[OX KING] ChiChi?
Are you in there?
Open up! I've brought
some porridge for you.
It'll make you feel
better! Come on!
[CHICHI]
I'm not hungry...
ChiChi... You haven't eaten
anything in the last week.
Have some food.
Come on... Open up now!
[CHICHI]
Leave me alone...
Eh... Oh...?
[thinking] The poor
girl really misses
Gohan and Goku...
[GOHAN grunts
rhythmically]
[GOHAN laughs]
[TIGER growls]
[GOHAN]
Yahoo!
[GOHAN laughs]
[GOHAN] Hey...
This looks familiar!
I came back to the
same place I was before!
Oh, no...
[TIGER pants]
[GOHAN]
This way, Mr. Tiger!
[GOHAN grunts
excitedly]
[GOHAN exhales]
An... island?
I'm on an island?
[GOHAN] I must be a long,
long way from home...
That means I'll have
to figure out a way
to get off of this
island... somehow.
I can do it...
I have to!
Mm hmm... Well, I guess
that might work, maybe.
[thinking] My greatest
opponent is myself...
If I can discover
what my weaknesses are,
then I will be an even stronger
fighter than I already am...
Hm?
[OTHER PICCOLO roars]
Special
Beam Cannon!
[GOHAN] This should
do the trick.
Guess I'll have to
chop it down!
[GOHAN]
Hyaaa!
Hi-yaaa!
[GOHAN grunts]
[TIGER grunts]
[GOHAN]
Thank you!
Ahh...
[GOHAN] Whew! That was hard
work! Now it's time for a snack.
[hammering]
Finished!
I did it!
[GOHAN laughs]
Okay!
[GOHAN grunts]
[GOHAN]
I'm going home!
[TIGER groans]
[GOHAN] Don't worry,
Mr. Tiger, I'll come back!
I just need to go home
and see my Mom first, okay?
[TIGER groans]
And stroke... and stroke...
and stroke... and stroke...
And stroke... stroke...
stroke... stroke...
[TIGER howls]
Good... There's
some wind!
[GOHAN laughs]
[GOHAN]
Whoa!
[GOHAN laughs]
[GOHAN]
Whoa-ho-ho!
[GOHAN laughs]
[GOHAN]
Yahoo!
[PICCOLOS grunt]
It's the kid!
Gohan?
[PICCOLO roars]
[GOHAN snores]
[GOHAN] Oh, no!
A storm is coming!
[GOHAN lurches]
[GOHAN shudders]
[GOHAN coughs]
I've gone too far to go
back now, and just in case,
I better eat this food
while I still can!
Uh-oh! I'm taking
on water! Oh, no!
Maybe this wasn't such
a good idea after all.
Boy, I wish
I could swim!
[thinking] Where is he? I sense
he's around here somewhere!
[GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN grunts]
[GOHAN]
Help me, Daddy!
[GOKU pants]
[NARRATOR] All alone
on a stormy sea!
How will Gohan get
out of this one?
Hopefully Piccolo
will find him in time.
If he doesn't,
you can say bon voyage
to the pint-sized Saiyan...
Hang on Gohan, hang on!
And don't you miss the
next exciting episode
of Dragon Ball Z!