[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z,
Garlic Jr. and his henchmen
watched with delight
as Piccolo, under the spell
of the Black Water Mist,
set upon Gohan in
a vicious attack.
[PICCOLO growls]
[PICCOLO grunts]
[GOHAN grunts]
[blows landing]
[NARRATOR] Gohan had
no choice but to submit
to this brutal beating;
unwilling to defend himself
against his friend
and former teacher.
Piccolo, however, had
no such reservations,
and he launched himself
at Gohan in full force.
[grunting,
blows landing]
[PICCOLO growls]
[NARRATOR] Despite
his best efforts
to evade Piccolo's
onslaught, in the end,
the young Saiyan was
finally overwhelmed.
--[PICCOLO grunts]
--[GOHAN yells]
[NARRATOR]
Unconcious and helpless,
it seemed he too would become
one of Garlic Jr.'s victims...
[PICCOLO] Hmm?!
Wait! I think I will
finish him off after all.
[NARRATOR] ...when suddenly:
[PICCOLO] Oh, the
pleasure is all yours.
[NARRATOR] Piccolo
sprung his trap!
[PICCOLO] Krillin! Catch!
[NARRATOR] Kami is free!
And hope for saving
the Earth returns.
Today!
[GARLIC JR. growls]
You'll pay for that!
Yeah, well I don't think that's
going to happen, garlic breath!
[PICCOLO grunts]
[PICCOLO groans]
[GARLIC JR. growls]
Hey! That was one heck
of a plan, Piccolo! But...
Gohan here is
pretty messed up...
[PICCOLO] Ha! He's
fine. Don't worry.
I know I've trained Gohan to
withstand a lot worse than this.
[GOHAN grunts]
Hey!
[GOHAN gasps]
[GOHAN] Mr. Popo...?
Huh...?
And Kami?
[POPO chuckles]
[KRILLIN chuckles]
[GOHAN] Piccolo... I-I
thought that you were...
[PICCOLO screams]
[PICCOLO hisses]
[PICCOLO chuckles]
The Black Water Mist had
no effect on me at all.
Oh?
[KRILLIN] Yep! We fooled ya!
Piccolo was one of
the good guys all along!
[PICCOLO growls]
[PICCOLO yells]
[PICCOLO] Listen carefully
to me, Krillin.
I'm going to attack Gohan now.
[PICCOLO] Garlic Jr.
would like nothing more
than to see me fight Gohan,
so I must make
this battle look real.
And... when he drops his guard,
I will grab the bottles
that contain Kami and Popo!
I guess it's true what they say:
you can't trust anyone anymore!
[KRILLIN laughs]
[GARLIC JR. growls]
Krillin, you and Piccolo
are really good actors.
I didn't suspect a thing!
You two were acting,
weren't you?
[KRILLIN chuckles]
With Kami and Popo
as hostages,
that was the only way
I could get close enough
to Garlic Jr.
to release them safely!
[KAMI] Thank you for
freeing us, Piccolo.
We are eternally grateful!
Spare me your thanks.
I didn't rescue the two of you
because I wanted to, Kami.
[KAMI] Hmm...
[PICCOLO] The only
reason I did it
was because with
you captured,
I can't fight
at my maximum power.
Yes, of course.
[VINEGAR chuckles]
I'll take care them!
Deliver the Sacred Water
before it's too late!
Yes, I will.
Garlic Jr., your plan
is going to fail!
I'm going to send you back
to the dark world
that you came from!
[PICCOLO chuckles]
Well, you ready?!
[GARLIC JR. growls]
[growling continues]
[GARLIC JR.] It's not easy
taking over the universe.
Huh?
[GARLIC JR.]
But it's days like this
that make it all worthwhile!
[GARLIC JR. laughs]
Don't you fools realize
that it's too late
to use the Sacred Water?
What's that?!
[GARLIC JR.] It will be
dawn long before you can
spread your Sacred Water
over the planet,
and by then it will be too late!
By that time, every
living thing on Earth
will have succumbed
to the effects
of the Black Water Mist!
They will all belong to me!
So no matter how hard you try,
you will never
be able to defeat me!
[GARLIC JR. giggles]
You are about to witness
the birth of a new world
of darkness and evil!
And I will be the ruler
of this beautiful new world!
[GARLIC JR. laughs]
[KRILLIN growls]
You monster!
No, don't! Please don't!
[laughter continues]
Kami...?
[KAMI growls]
Quiet. We'll be all
right if we stay here.
I can't believe what's
happening to everyone.
Why are they acting so violent?
[running footsteps]
[MAN] It's that evil mist!
It changes them!
[CROWD growling &amp; snarling]
[meowing,
hissing]
[screaming]
[screaming,
yelling]
[GARLIC JR. chuckles]
[GARLIC JR.] With an army of
darkness under my control,
Earth will become the most
feared planet in the universe!
And every second that ticks by
brings me closer
to realizing my dream!
[GARLIC JR. laughs]
Piccolo?
[PICCOLO growls]
[SPICE chuckles]
[VINEGAR chuckles]
[POPO] We might still
have a chance, Kami!
There is a way we can spread
the Sacred Water
everywhere quickly!
Tell me!
Huh?
[POPO] You can take the Sacred
Water through there, Kami!
It leads directly to the
seven air currents of the world!
Are you certain, Mr. Popo?
[POPO] Yes, Kami.
The air currents flow
just below your lookout!
It's the best way for you
to spread the Sacred Water!
Then let's go!
I must warn you that
if you choose this path,
it will be dangerous
and there's a chance
you will never
be able to return!
Yes, I know...
Ahh... Okay, you know
we'll have to pass through
the place where the spirits
of the former guardians
of the Earth go
to their eternal rest!
There is a risk that
your spirit could be
trapped in there, Kami!
Then you would no longer be
guardian of the Earth anymore!
You could die!
I understand!
Kami!
[KAMI] If this is the last
chance we have, then I must go!
Come on, there's no time
to waste, Mr. Popo!
We must get the Sacred Water
to the people of Earth
before it's too late!
Of course, I'll drive!
Magic Carpet!
[POPO] Hop on! Quick, Kami!
Ready!
Come back here!
[GARLIC JR. growls]
[POPO] Kami, we're
not going to make it!
[KAMI] We've got to keep going!
[VINEGAR chuckles]
[VINEGAR] Huh?!
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN growl]
[VINEGAR grunts]
[SPICE grunts]
[GARLIC JR. yells]
[PICCOLO grunts]
Come on! You can do
better than that!
[GARLIC JR. yells]
[PICCOLO growls]
[GARLIC JR. grunts]
[PICCOLO shouts,
blows landing]
[KAMI] Piccolo!
[GARLIC JR.] You're finished!
[PICCOLO grunts]
[KAMI] We've got to
hurry, Mr. Popo!
[screaming]
[VEGETA] Now you know what
happens to those who do not
pledge their loyalty
to the great Vegeta!
[SOLDIERS chuckle]
[VEGETA yells]
[SOLDIERS gasp]
[screaming]
Please, Sire!
Please forgive us!
Forgive us for ever doubting
the incredible power of Vegeta!
[VEGETA] A lesson
learned too late.
Ha! Did you poor fools
actually believe
you had a chance against me?
[VEGETA] When will
they ever learn?
Those who do not
bow down before me
shall suffer my wrath!
Out here
I have no equal!
Not even Frieza was
enough of a match for me!
[VEGETA] But there is one...
Kakarot! Where are you?
[PICCOLO grunts]
[GARLIC JR. growls]
[PICCOLO growls]
[KRILLIN grunts,
blows landing]
[VINEGAR grunts]
[KRILLIN grunts]
You're history!
[VINEGAR yells]
[VINEGAR grunts]
[KRILLIN grunts]
[SPICE grunts]
[SPICE laughs]
[GOHAN grunts]
[blow lands]
[SPICE giggles]
[GOHAN grunts]
[PICCOLO] Over here, you dwarf!
[GARLIC JR. growls]
[PICCOLO yells]
[GOHAN rasps]
[SPICE giggles]
[SPICE laughs]
[crashing]
[VINEGAR growls
[VINEGAR chuckles]
[KRILLIN grunts]
[KRILLIN growls]
Destructo Disc!
[KRILLIN yells]
What's this?
[VINEGAR] This game is over!
[KRILLIN gasps
[VINEGAR growls
[KRILLIN grunts]
No, Krillin!
[GOHAN yells]
[VINEGAR chuckles]
[GOHAN shouts]
Huh?!
[VINEGAR grunts]
[VINEGA screams
Hang in there!
[SPICE giggles]
[SPICE grunts]
[groaning]
[beams firing,
crashing]
[blows landing]
[GARLIC JR. grunting,
blows landing continues]
Give up! You can't win!
[GARLIC JR. growls]
So, Piccolo! Aren't you
worried about Kami?
I'd be worried
if my mind and body
were linked to
that decrepit old prune!
It would be such a tragedy
if something
happened to him, huh?
You'd certainly have a tough
time surviving without him!
And with Kami gone, I bet
you wouldn't talk so tough.
[PICCOLO] Ha!
If I were a coward like you...
your words might
scare me... But I'm not!
What?
[GARLIC JR. growls]
You want to see
what real strength is?
Then I'll show you!
[PICCOLO &amp; GARLIC JR. grunt]
Mr. Popo, how much
farther is it?
We'll be there soon!
[GARLIC JR. grunts]
[PICCOLO] It's over, Garlic Jr.!
[GARLIC JR. chuckles]
Huh?!
I want to show you something!
My source of power!
[GARLIC JR.]
Behold the Makyo Star!
My home!
It's warm glow
revives me and fills me
with incredible strength!
And after 12,000 years,
it's made it's way to Earth!
Can you feel it?
Now that the Makyo Star
has finally arrived,
I will become
ten times more powerful
than I've ever been before!
There's nothing
you can do to stop me
from taking this
planet for my own!
[GARLIC JR. growls]
Oh! Now what?
I wish Garlic Jr.
would give it a rest
for a little while!
[growling continues]
[SPICE gasps]
[GARLIC JR. growls]
He's changing? Krillin!
Gohan, get out of here!
What?
[GARLIC JR. growls]
[GARLIC JR. yells]
[PICCOLO gasps]
[distant rumbling]
[BOTH gasp]
[POPO] This is the doorway that
leads to the seven air currents!
Open it! Go on!
[POPO] I'm trying...
It's just that...
It's open, Kami!
[GARLIC JR.] Heh...
Ow. I think my brain shifted!
[GOHAN] Piccolo?
Go! Leave this place!
[BOTH growl]
The last time we fought,
you got lucky, kid!
But now you're
about to find out
how powerful we really are!
Yeah, so be afraid.
Very afraid!
[VINEGAR guffaws]
[GARLIC JR. growls]
[PICCOLO growls]
[KAMI] This is it,
Mr. Popo. Let's do it!
[KAMI gasps]
[KAMI yells]
Who are you?
[NARRATOR] It doesn't look good
for Piccolo,
Gohan, and Krillin.
With the Makyo Star
in Earth's orbit
increasing his power,
Garlic Jr. seems unstoppable!
Meanwhile, in the depths
of their mystical lookout,
Kami and Mr. Popo have found
yet another obstacle
standing between them
and saving
planet Earth.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z!