[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball Z,
Majin Buu absorbed Gotenks
and Piccolo into his body,
transforming himself
into a new, Super Buu.
[NARRATOR] Possessing
the strength of Gotenks,
and the wisdom of Piccolo,
it was a form
that not even Gohan's
awakened powers could stop.
[NARRATOR] With both physical
and psychological attacks,
Majin Buu chipped away
at Gohan's Achilles heel:
his confidence.
But Gohan knew the
weight of Earth's survival
had been placed
on his shoulders.
And like a true Saiyan,
he refused to give up.
[GOHAN groaning]
[SUPER BUU]
Still alive...
Well I guess I'll
have to make sport
out of smacking you around!
[NARRATOR] But Gohan could not
hold out for long,
and elsewhere, desperate
new strategies were made.
[NARRATOR]
On the Supreme Kai's world,
the elder Kai
gave up his own life
so that Goku might
live and fight.
[NARRATOR]
And that's not all he gave him.
[OLD KAI]
Now simply have Gohan
snap this one onto
his right ear.
Immediately your bodies
will be bound together,
and much stronger,
my type of fusion!
[NARRATOR] What is the secret
to this new fusion?
Could it really be the
answer the Z-Fighters need?
[gasp]
Are you sure people
can be fused together
just by using some earrings?
Don't be difficult. I'm a Kai,
of course I'm sure!
And it's much more effective
than that fusion dance
you must've picked up
from the Metamorese.
Why, didn't I know that?!
[OLD KAI]
That's a very great question.
Seems you missed out
on a good deal of training
when Majin Buu
eliminated the other Kais.
[SUPREME KAI]
Kibito, have you heard of this?
[KIBITO]
No, master!
Go on then,
you've got Kai earrings
don't you? Try it for yourself!
[SUPREME KAI] Oh, Kibito,
take off your left earring
and I'll take off my right.
We'll try and fuse our bodies.
Of course!
[SUPREME KAI, KIBITO yelling]
[SUPREME KAI]
I can't stop, Kibito!
[KIBITO]
Me neither!
[chuckles]
[gasps]
[laughs]
Look at us!
We're joined together!
Incredible!
Oh! Wow!
And now I'm ready to fight
alongside you Goku.
Let's go to Earth right now!
Hey! Don't get carried away.
Although you may
have become stronger,
your power is nothing
compared to Majin Buu's!
He could easily absorb you.
You'll stay right here.
Aw.
This earring trick
is just what we need!
Hey! How long will the people
stay joined for, Old Kai?
[OLD KAI] The power of the
earrings has no time limit.
It lasts forever.
Once joined, you can never
return to your original body.
You mean I'm stuck this way?!
That's good to know.
Boy, I'd better choose
the right person then!
[OLD KAI] Indeed, I wish I could
do it all over again myself.
What? You used the earrings
to fuse with someone, too?
[OLD KAI]
Uh, yes. Yes, I did.
[OLD KAI] I wasn't always
a can of ugly, you know.
I used to be dashing!
But foolishly I let an old,
power-hungry witch
sneak up on me.
My boy, why are you
wearing an earring?
Give it to me!
[gasps]
This will look much more seemly
on a pretty girl like me.
[gasps]
Y-You mustn't!
[BOTH scream]
[OLD KAI] That's why I look
like a misshapen prune!
But on the positive side,
it gave me the impressive
powers you've seen me employ.
Guess, there's no other way.
It's going to be strange
joining with my son.
I just hope ChiChi doesn't
make me go to school with him!
[SUPER BUU laughs]
[SUPER BUU]
Come out, come out, Gohan!
[energy blasts]
[grunt]
--[SUPER BUU yells]
--[GOHAN groans]
What's wrong,
are you frightened?
[laughs]
[GOHAN]
No!
[MR. SATAN] Can ya see what's
going on down there?
It looks bad.
Oh no, I don't think Gohan
can last much longer.
[SUPER BUU grunts]
[yells]
[gasps]
[DENDE, MR. SATAN, BEE whimper]
[GOHAN screams]
[GOHAN groaning]
[DENDE]
No, I'm coming Gohan. Hang on!
[groaning]
You're all right! I'll heal you.
[SUPER BUU chuckles]
[SUPER BUU] It's not as fun
when he doesn't fight back!
Perhaps it's time to
put an end to this.
Huh?
The little Namek.
[sighs]
That's better!
Thanks, Dende!
Now hurry and hide!
What's this? Gohan is
as good as new?
Would someone tell me
how that's possible?!
[SUPER BUU]
Ah yes, Piccolo knows.
[chuckles]
Dende's healing power.
He'll pay for that.
[growls]
[yells]
And now, for that
disgusting Namek.
[gasps]
No, Dende!
Take a bite out
of this, you monster!
Ha, ha! What'd ya think of that,
little guardian?
That's some pretty sharp
shootin', don't ya think?
[gasping]
What the--?
Tien! Is that really you?
Hardly recognize you, Gohan!
You've changed a lot,
inside and out. Good for you.
[grunts] But I see Majin Buu
did some changing, too.
[grunts]
Where's the hole these
pests are crawling out from?
Oh well, it's just
more fun for me!
Ah. [chuckles]
[gasps]
Tri-Beam! Ha!
[groaning]
[exhales]
Uh?!
[SUPER BUU laughing]
You're even weaker
than the others!
It can't be!
He didn't even flinch.
This is worse than I thought.
Hm. Why don't I show
you how it's done!
[SUPER BUU chuckles]
This one blast is capable
of destroying you all.
Can I get a volunteer
to stop me?
[gasps]
[groaning]
[gasping]
That's it Buu, our friendship
is officially over!
Hold it! Shouldn't I become
a Super Saiyan first?
Yeah, then this fusion
will be at its maximum.
No! That would be
dangerous, my boy.
Once you initiate the fusion you
may never be able to power down,
and if I remember
right about Saiyans,
they can't stay in their
powered up states forever.
The strain on your body
could shorten your life!
[GOKU]
Really?
Yes, but you will
find that once you fuse,
the additional power
won't be needed.
Now, are you sure you understand
that whoever you fuse with,
it'll be for keeps?
Yeah, I understand.
[OLD KAI] If for some reason you
need to go Super Saiyan,
you may do it after you fuse.
But trust me, you won't need it.
You'd better dispense
with the coaching!
Take a look at what's
happening on Earth.
[GOKU] Oh no! Well, thanks
for all the help you guys!
Yes, good luck.
[GOKU]
Thanks!
[SUPER BUU chuckles]
[SUPER BUU] So, not one
among you can stop me?
Then the end of the Earth
is on your heads!
[laughs]
I'm sorry, old Buu!
[SUPER BUU laughing]
[laughing]
[grunts]
[gasps]
What on Earth? Dad,
what're you doing here?!
[groaning]
[gasps]
[MR. SATAN] Buu's body
has been split in two!
I didn't mean to do that! No!
What a shot! Oh curse
my deadly aim!
I'm too powerful!
You forgive me, don'tcha boy?!
You're Goku! Where did
you come from?
You're smarter than the
others to try a sneak attack!
Too bad, that won't save you.
Not from me, I've
absorbed your friends,
and taken their powers,
and soon I will do
the same thing to you.
[GOKU chuckles]
[GOKU]
You're wrong, Buu!
For your information,
I've got something that'll
make you finally answer
for every crime
you've committed!
[SUPER BUU]
What?
[gasping]
[SUPER BUU laughs] Do I have to
prove myself once again?
[TIEN]
Huh?! Ah!
[grunts] He was off guard!
Uh-oh!
See what just one kick
did to your friend?
Now imagine what I'll do to you.
I'm sorry, I interrupted you.
You were giving a speech,
something about making
me answer for my crimes?
Honestly, I was finding
it a little cliché.
[chuckles]
But you sure were quick
to pull yourself back
together, weren't you?
I think you're starting
to get a little nervous.
You wish! Let me see what
you can do. I'm ready.
Sure.
Here, catch!
Huh?!
[GOKU]
Hurry Gohan! Get that earring!
[GOHAN]
Uh. Okay.
Go and pick it up and
put in your right ear.
Then we'll join bodies,
and beat Majin Buu.
[GOHAN]
What is he talking about?
[SUPER BUU]
That's what you're up to?
More fusion?
Don't make me laugh.
You obviously do not understand
the power I have
recently acquired!
I could crush both of you.
Uh! Wait! Time out! Can you
give us just a minute, please?
What is with these goofs?
[KIBITO KAI gasps]
Hurry!
Time's up!
Okay, here it goes!
[yells]
Gotcha!
Gohan, put that earring on!
I'm trying, Dad.
[yells]
[GOKU grunts]
[SUPER BUU yells]
Ah!
[yelling]
Ah?! Gr...
My turn now! [chuckles]
It's gone?
[yells]
[GOKU grunts]
[laughs]
[surprised grunt]
[groaning]
No! Not now!
Uh!
[yells]
Oh, of course. Gotenks!
The boys' fusion must have worn
off inside Majin Buu's body.
Now he's mostly Piccolo.
You were playing
against time, Buu.
And you lost, you don't plan
to beat me like that, do you?
[GOHAN grunts]
There you are! [chuckles]
I'm ready, Dad!
Still not sure what this does,
but I'm putting it on.
Right ear, right?
[GOKU]
No.
[SUPER BUU growls]
Uh, left?
[GOKU]
Forget about it, Gohan.
There will be no need for us
to join bodies anymore.
Majin Buu has lost over
a third of his power.
[growling]
Ha. For your sake,
I hope you brought
some insurance
to back up your claims!
[SUPER BUU]
But knowing you, Goku,
you probably don't even know
what insurance means.
[squelching]
It's not finished yet,
or didn't you notice a certain
piece of me was missing?
Uh?!
[chuckles]
Uh?
[gasps]
[GOHAN groans]
Gohan!
[grunts]
Uh. Missed it!
[growls]
[gasps] That monster! No.
Oh, dear me. This is bad!
Please, help them!
I've done all I can.
[sighs]
[chuckles]
Awesome, I have way more
power than I did before.
Now, the only problem
is you. Right, Dad?
Oh, I should've used this
when I had the chance.
[GOKU] Guess I'll have to
fuse with someone else.
[GOKU]
Tien's down for the count.
[gasping]
[GOKU]
Can't afford to use Dende.
[gasps]
It has to be Mr. Satan.
[NARRATOR]
With the absorption of Gohan,
Majin Buu is stronger than ever,
and Goku's plan of fusing
with his Super Saiyan son
has been ruined.
The earring given to him
by the elder Kai
could be the only way
of defeating Buu,
but where is a suitable partner?
Is Goku so desperate
that he will join bodies
with the bumbling Hercule?
Choices must be made,
on the next Dragon Ball Z!