[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Krillin was spared
a three-fisted face lift
when the trio
of evil androids
decided to go after
larger prey-- Goku!
And it looks like Vegeta's ego
will take a long time to heal.
[VEGETA] No one makes a fool
of me! They'll pay for this!
They should have finished
me off when they had the chance,
because I will show
them no mercy!
[NARRATOR] It seems Piccolo has
turned his back on his friends,
just when they need
his help the most.
[PICCOLO] I'm leaving,
and anyone who tries to
follow me will be sorry!
Don't worry, guys.
Piccolo just has
a lot on his mind...
He's still one
of the good guys!
Piccolo has gone
to Kami's place
to join with him again!
Together, they'll
be an unstoppable force...
...a Super Namek!
[NARRATOR] The androids must be
stopped before it's too late.
But can Piccolo convince Kami
to make the ultimate sacrifice?
FInd out today!
[PICCOLO thinking] I know Kami
senses something is wrong...
Why doesn't he say something?
[KAMI thinking] Things must be
more serious than I thought.
Uh? Kami...?
This isn't a social call it's
business! I think you know that.
Yes, I know...
Of course, I do.
The bond we share is of the mind
as well as the body, remember?
I know exactly what's
on your mind, Piccolo.
Hmph! Good! That
saves me some time.
What an unexpected
honor this is.
I never thought that you and
I would ever be united again.
Stop smiling!
I'm not doing this
because I want too.
It's because I need our
combined powers. That's all.
To be perfectly honest,
I'm not sure how
I'm going to tolerate
being so close to you.
Your mere presence sickens me!
Oh... Kami!
[PICCOLO] Trust me,
I'd have preferred it
if I never had to
look at you again!
[KAMI growls]
[KAMI thinking] Piccolo's
attitude angers me,
but I can't blame him...
He is a part of me.
I have watched him fight
one formidable enemy
after another...
And he has beaten
the odds every time.
[PICCOLO yells]
No! You can't!
[RADITZ yells]
[GOKU &amp; RADITZ grunt]
[NAPPA yells]
[GOHAN yells]
[PICCOLO yells]
Yes... unite
with me, Piccolo...
[PICCOLO grunts]
[KAMI] My power is nothing
compared to Piccolo's...
He has developed
strength and abilities
far greater than I
could have ever imagined.
[KAMI] Perhaps my time
as guardian of Earth
has come to an end.
No, Kami! You are
still needed...
The people of Earth still
need you to watch over them.
[KAMI] You are too kind,
Mr. Popo...
but I must act for
the good of the Earth.
This is about
the continuing struggle
for power between the
forces of good and evil.
And the danger that
looms over us now
poses a greater threat
than anything we
have faced in the past.
Even Vegeta
with all of his strength,
was no match for these androids.
[KAMI]
Super Saiyan or not,
he was tossed
aside like a rag doll!
These androids will
be difficult to beat.
Even if Goku recovers
from his illness,
he will provide
little resistance
against these
powerful new foes.
In our combined form,
Piccolo may be the only one
strong enough to win this fight!
We agree.
The force that threatens Earth
is bigger than both of us.
But at least when
our powers are united
we still stand a chance.
And no matter how slim that
chance is, we must take it!
[KAMI] Hold on...
I haven't agreed
to anything yet!
Time may still
be on our side.
Listen, I would
like to let things
play out further
before I make my decision.
You want to see
how things play out?!
Have you lost your mind?!
[KAMI] Silence! Sometimes
things are not always
what they appear
to be, Piccolo.
[PICCOLO growls]
[KAMI] And I am
not entirely convinced
that the aim of these androids
is to destroy the Earth.
Is this a joke?!
You've sat
here and watched
everything that's
gone on below
and you're still going
to let it continue?!
Don't you remember
what Trunks said?!
The future will be
destroyed by these androids!
Yes, but Trunks
made a mistake.
He told you that the androids
you encountered today
are not the same ones
that he fought in the future.
[PICCOLO chuckles]
Yeah, right. And these androids
are a real great bunch of guys
once you get to know them.
I'm serious.
I know you may
not agree with me,
all I'm saying is I still need
more time to make up my mind.
[PICCOLO]
Have it your way!
You're scared! I know...
[PICCOLO] If you
need time then take it.
I'll be waiting right here.
Hmph.
You can wait as
long as you want.
But remember, the
clock is ticking.
Hey, Krillin!
[KRILLIN] Yeah?
I think I'm going to
go pick up Chiaotzu
so we can get back to training.
Sure! Sounds good!
As soon as things
get dicey again,
we'll be there to help!
Although, I'm not sure
how much good we'll do.
Okay, go get Chiaotzu
and meet up with us later.
We're going to move Goku
over to Master Roshi's house.
That should buy us all
a little bit more time.
Yeah, that's
a good idea, but...
Be careful.
And take care of Goku!
[KRILLIN] We will.
Good luck, Tien!
We'll need it...
That's for sure.
Hope we're not too late.
[TRUNKS] I don't know why
the future I predicted
changed so much...
The androids I fought
weren't as powerful
and there were
only two of them.
I don't get it!
It doesn't matter now...
If we don't get out
of this mess soon,
we're all gonna be history.
[birds chirping]
[CHICHI] I think the worst
is over now, Yamcha.
Don't you?
[YAMCHA] Yeah... Let's hope so!
[GOKU grunts softly]
[ANDROID 17] 18, check it out.
Looks like we found some wheels.
[ANDROID 18] It's about time.
Let's take it for a spin.
[ANDROID 17] All right!
But let me take
care of the driving.
Okay.
[MAN A] Whoa! This coffee
doesn't look very fresh to me.
[MAN B] Well, it's not!
It's older than
my mother-in-law!
[MAN A chuckles]
[MAN A slurps]
[gasps]
Let's clear this out
and make more room.
[MAN A] Hey, pal!
Get away from there!
Right now!
[ANDROID 16 grunts]
[MAN A gasps]
[engine starts]
Right. We're all set.
Now let's go find Goku.
Step on it. Come on, let's go!
[ANDROID 17] Quiet now, or
I'll make you ride in the back.
[MAN A] Well,
say... something...
[MAN B] Something...
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA] Wait till I get my
hands on those androids!
[VEGETA growls]
I will prove once
and for all that I am
the strongest warrior in
the universe! It is my destiny!
[BIKERS laughing]
[motorcycles roaring]
Hey! You! Get moving!
You're in my way!
Hey, hey, hey!
[BIKER A laughs]
[BIKERS laughing]
[BIKER B] Hey, babe!
Why don't you ride with us?!
Come on! Take a
ride with the Toad Warriors!
It'll be fun! I promise!
Hear that?
Yeah, this should
be interesting.
[BIKER C laughing]
[BIKER C yells]
[tires squealing]
[BIKERS screaming]
[BIKER A] Heads up!
That's it!
Nobody messes with the Toad
Warriors and gets away with it!
Let's get 'em!
[BIKERS cheering]
[BIKER D screams]
[RINGS] Oooh!
These chumps are
gonna pay for that!
[ANDROID 17] Why don't
you take a new outfit
from one of
these goons, 18?
No. Theere's nothing
in my size.
[ANDROID 17] Hmph. Picky.
[BIKERS laughing]
[BIKER A] Yipee! Ha, ha, ha!
[tires squealing
[train horn blaring]
[BIKERS yelling]
[BIKER E screaming]
[train horn honking]
[BIKERS gasp]
[BIKERS panting]
After them!
[ANDROID 17] Impressive...
They still haven't given up.
[BIKER B] This'll fix ya.
[BIKER E laughs]
[ANDROID 17 growls]
They want
to play chicken.
Play chicken... heh!
[BIKER E laughs]
[BIKER E screams]
Huh? You're dead!
[BIKER A yells]
There! You like
your haircut?!
[BIKERS gasp]
[BIKERS scream]
[sirens wailing]
Rats! If the cops
weren't coming
we'd have you guys for lunch!
[BIKERS scream]
[sirens wailing]
[SHERIFF] Secure the
perimeter, deputy!
[DEPUTY] Yes sir!
[SHERIFF] Let's round
up these hooligans!
[DEPUTY] It looks like the rest
of their gang got away, sir!
[SHERIFF] That's okay!
I've got the ring
leaders right here!
Hey! Whoever's in the van!
Come out now!
[DEPUTY stammering]
Y-Y-Yuh, uh...
You are under arrest!
That's not good...
Sir! He broke my handcuffs!
Shall I take this one?
[ANDROID 17] Be my guest.
Now... Pay attention.
I'm only going
to do this once.
Hey! Hold it!
[SHERIFF whimpers]
There.
[ANDROID 17 chuckles]
[ANDROID 18 giggles]
[SHERIFF] Stop in
the name of the... law?
Follow me! We're close
to Goku's house!
Hold it... Trunks...
Just one question.
Huh?
Uh... The androids...
Are they... Uh...
Really as terrible
as you say they are?
They're ruthless
and cold-blooded.
I've told you that
before, Krillin.
Why even ask?
[KRILLIN wail]
Hey! I was just hoping that we
wouldn't all have to fight!
Really, that's all, man!
[TRUNKS] Well, hoping doesn't
get us anywhere, I'm afraid.
[KRILLIN] I know that!
It's just that I... well...
Oh, nevermind.
[KRILLIN whimpers]
Good luck.
Oh, Gohan!
Oh, it's you, Krillin.
[KRILLIN] Nice to
see you too, ChiChi...
That hurt...
Well, say hello.
Oh! Hello there.
Oh! Krillin! Hey!
Alright! I'm glad you
made it here safe!
And Goku?
[YAMCHA] He's okay...
He's sleeping right now.
Hey, welcome back, man!
So if you guys are here,
you must have defeated
the androids, right?
[BOTH gasp]
Not yet...
I can't explain now...
But we have to
evacuate this place
and transport Goku to
Master Roshi's right away!
Huh?
[KRILLIN] We're dealing
with a group of androids
that are a thousand times
more powerful than any of us!
[CHICHI gasps]
What? We can't stop them?!
[CHICHI] Be careful with him!
[YAMCHA] Boy, I think Goku
has packed on a few pounds.
Give him a break.
He hasn't been himself lately.
[KRILLIN] Hey, Yamcha,
where's Gohan?
[YAMCHA] He should be
getting home any time now.
Look! Gohan's back!
Here he comes!
[GOHAN] Hey, what's going on?
[CHICHI] You've come
home! Oh, my baby!
I'm so happy to see you!
Uh? Hey what are
you guys doing?
No time to talk.
On the plane, Gohan!
[thinking] Something's wrong...
Something I've missed...
[NARRATOR] Goku is on his way
to a safer hiding place
but his trail is warm and the
androids are in hot pursuit.
Krillin and the others can
only hide him for so long
before they are discovered!
And if that's not enough,
Bulma is about to
get a telephone call
that will add a whole new
dimension to this crisis.
On the next Dragonball Z!