[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z...
Tragedy struck, when Goku's
evil older brother, Raditz,
kidnapped Gohan!
Daddy! Help me!
Daddy!
[NARRATOR] Goku raced
after the sinister Saiyan
to take back his son.
But with little hope of
overpowering Raditz alone,
he had no choice but
to accept the help
of a most unlikely ally...
Goku has joined forces
with one of his most
dangerous enemies... Piccolo!
[RADITZ] Hm...
Well, well, well.
Look who's decided
to drop in.
It's little brother.
Oh, and he's brought
the green man with him.
I was wondering who that
second insignificant blip
on my scouter
might be...
[NARRATOR] Radtiz was
far from intimidated
when confronted by the Earth's
two greatest fighters.
In a flash, he gave
them a demonstration
of his own power that
proved, even together,
Goku and Piccolo had
little chance for victory.
Raditz's otherworldly
strength and speed
already make him the
most powerful opponent
Goku or Piccolo
has ever faced.
But this, it seems, is only
the tip of the iceberg.
If you think I'm strong now,
wait until I catch my stride.
The truth is, I'm just
getting warmed up.
[NARRATOR] Is there any hope
of defeating this deadly foe?
Find out, today!
[RADITZ]
I'll tell you what...
Seeing as how your power
levels are more or less equal,
why don't we make a
little game out of this?
We'll call it,
"Which of you can last
against me the longest."
The rules are simple.
I cause you both a
great deal of pain,
and you writhe
around in agony.
The loser is the first
to beg for mercy.
That's it... I don't
care how strong he is.
I'm not going to stand
here and listen to this.
I would
prefer to die!
[laughs]
Don't you worry
about it green man,
we'll get to that
in due time!
Hey, don't get
ahead of yourself.
You haven't
beaten us yet.
Trust me, Kakarot. I know
an easy win when I see one.
I'm a Saiyan!
It's what I do.
[PICCOLO] Come on, Goku.
Let's finish this guy!
We'll charge
him together!
Wait...
Not yet...
Not until he tells us what
he's done with Gohan...
Now, where is he?
Where have you hidden him?
Right...
Your little son...
You think you're
going to save him?
Who's getting ahead
of himself now?
This is the last time
I'm going ask you!
Where is my son?!
[RADITZ] Spare me the
fatherly dramatics.
You can have a last look
at him if you want.
He's locked inside my
space pod, behind you.
Ah!
[cries]
Gohan...
Daddy, help! Please, Daddy!
Get me out!
Be strong, Gohan!
I'll be down to help you
in a minute. Just hold on!
[RADITZ] Ha!
You'll be down all right...
But you won't be
helping anybody!
You should say
your goodbyes though!
You won't get
another chance.
No. I won't lose.
All right.
Let's do this!
[RADITZ chuckles]
[GOKU and PICCOLO yell]
Heh.
[chuckles]
[GOKU and PICCOLO yell]
Where did he go?!
Right here!
Heh!
[RADITZ chuckles]
[RADITZ] What's the
matter with you two?
You could at least try to make
better sport of it than this!
You don't want me to
get bored, do you?
[GOKU groans]
Piccolo, are you alright?
Ah!
[PICCOLO groans]
Don't worry about it.
It's not as bad as it looks...
I'm not out of
this fight yet.
[RADITZ laughs]
Oh, excuse me, has
anyone seen my arm?
[RADITZ laughs]
You can't miss it...
It's green!
[RADITZ laughs]
Uh... How we doin', Bulma?
We getting close?
[BULMA]
I think so.
But I'd need the Dragon
Radar to know for sure.
I just hope Goku's
doing all right.
I've got a terrible
feeling about all this.
Well, at least we know
that with Piccolo,
his chances are about
as good as they can get.
But the fact that
he's with Piccolo
is what worries
me the most!
I mean, he's one
of the bad guys!
For all we know, he's
already teamed up with
Raditz and blasted
Goku--Oh...
Goku can't beat
Raditz alone,
and I doubt any of us
could be much help...
So we might as well put
our faith in Piccolo.
If he can't help
Goku, or won't,
then there's no
one else who can.
[KRILLIN sighs]
[KRILLIN thinking]
Good luck, Goku.
Come on, now.
Surely that pathetic
excuse for an attack
wasn't the best
you could do.
Okay, Goku. If you have
any new techniques
you've been waiting
to use, now's the time.
Heh, heh... Sorry...
I wish I did!
Hmph! You slacker...
While you've been
taking it easy,
I've been developing
a new attack!
[RADITZ] Fools!
Haven't you figured it out yet?
All of your
planning is futile!
Whisper all you want, but
you're still going to die!
So you think this attack
of yours has enough power
to do some
damage, Piccolo?
Yes!
And can you do it
with only one arm?
[PICCOLO]
Yeah, that's no problem.
The problem is,
it takes me a while to
gather the energy for it.
[RADITZ chuckles]
So, you'll have to
last against him alone
for five minutes.
It's your decision.
All right... If you're sure
it'll work, I'll hold him off.
Well, the truth is
it's untested...
I've never tried it
against an opponent.
I was hoping to save it
for a special occasion.
It's the attack I planned
to use to defeat you.
[GOKU] I see, and now
you're using it to help me.
You must be terribly
disappointed.
[PICCOLO] No. This
will be a good test.
And if it works, I'll be
using it on you next.
Ha, ha. Figures.
You know, that wasn't actually
intended to be funny.
[RADITZ thinking]
What are they laughing at?
Planning something
clever, no doubt.
I guess I'll be sure to watch
out the next time we meet.
But for now,
wish me luck.
All right.
Do your best, Goku!
[GOKU yells]
[PICCOLO grunts]
Heh.
[RADITZ thinking]
It's about time.
[PICCOLO grunts]
Huh?
He's persistent!
Kaaameee!
Impossible! His power
level is sky rocketing!
900! 950!
Haaa!
But how?
He knows how to raise
his power level
by concentrating his
energy onto one spot!
[GOKU] Meee!
[beeping]
What?
His power level has
gone up as well!
It's over a thousand!
Unbelievable!
And it's still going up!
[GOKU]
Haaaa!
[GOKU grunts]
Enough of this!
[RADITZ yells]
[RADITZ grunts]
Ah! He cancelled it out!
Piccolo had
better hurry.
Brother! I'll show
you how it's done!
[RADITZ yells]
[GOKU whimpers]
Let... me... out!
[GOKU groans]
[RADITZ gasps]
[PICCOLO laughs]
Let's see you
stop this one...
[PICCOLO grunts]
How foolish!
I underestimated these guys!
Power Level 1330?
I can't block that!
[PICCOLO laughs]
Alright then, green man!
Let's see what you've got!
It's all yours!
Special Beam Cannon!
Ah!
[RADITZ grunts]
[PICCOLO grunts]
He... He dodged it!
He's faster than the...
The speed of light!
My, that was quite an
impressive little trick!
Look how easily it
pierced my armor! Heh.
It's lucky for me your aim
needs a little work.
[PICCOLO] Darn it!
All for nothing!
Now, I had a little trick that
I had wanted to share with you.
Remember?
It's the one I was going to
show you when we first met!
Yeah, I know...
Do you remember
the name?
Double Sunday!
[RADITZ yells]
[RADITZ grunts]
[GOKU laughs]
You were
careless!
[GOKU laughs]
I'll never forget
how much my tail hurt
when someone
squeezed it!
[RADITZ groans]
You shouldn't
do that!
Piccolo!
Do you think you can manage
that attack one more time?
[PICCOLO] Yes, Goku!
With pleasure!
I see you had a surprise
attack after all, you sly dog!
Now hold him tight, this is
the last time I can do this!
Kakarot,
please tell me
you're not going to go
through with this!
I am your brother!
Brother?
Don't be ridiculous.
You kidnapped my son and
you tried to kill me.
And, if I
remember right,
you said you were going to
exterminate every human
on this planet.
I was bluffing!
I would have done or said
anything to get you to join us.
I swear it!
[PICCOLO]
Don't listen to him Goku!
He'll say anything
to get loose!
[GOKU grunts]
[RADITZ] I was never going
to kill you or the boy...
Once I was sure that I couldn't
persuade you to join us,
I was going to leave
this planet, for good!
And that's the truth...
I could never hurt my own
flesh and blood, I swear...
I swear it, Kakarot!
Do you promise
to leave?
[RADITZ] Yes, of course!
It's over!
I'll tell the others
that you won't join!
No, Goku! He's trying to
trick you! Don't let him go!
I'll never come back to this
planet again! I promise!
[RADITZ groans]
No, Goku!
[RADITZ chuckles]
[GOKU groans]
[RADITZ laughs]
You've always been
way too trusting, Goku.
[RADITZ laughs]
Fool! Ha, ha, ha, ha!
How could you?
You're a rare breed
indeed, my brother!
Just a
sentimental dope!
You're way too soft
to be a Saiyan Warrior!
Ahh!
No fair!
You're right,
Kakarot,
but I myself am a
first class warrior
and I won't hesitate to kill
even my own brother if need be!
Now say goodbye!
[GOKU groans]
[GOKU screams]
[GOHAN]
Daddy?
Aaahhhhh!
[RADITZ] Come on! I want to
hear you beg! Beg for mercy!
[RADITZ laughs]
[GOKU screams]
[RADITZ] Hmph!
What are you waiting for?
Go ahead and try that little
trick of yours again!
Or can't you
handle it?
[PICCOLO grunts]
It's no use! I need more time!
[RADITZ grunts]
[GOKU screams]
Oh, daddy...
[CHICHI hums]
[CHICHI]
♪ La, la, la, la, la, la... ♪
♪ La, la, la, la, la, la,
la, la, la, la, la, la... ♪
Hm?
[giggles]
Gohan was supposed to
show me his test grade
the day
he got it back.
He's so good
at math,
I think I will push
him into the sciences.
It'd be neat to have
an astronaut in the family.
And who knows? If he
works hard enough,
he might even get to travel
to other planets someday!
Hmm.. That rice is going to
be ready in a few minutes.
I wish those two would
hurry up and get back.
[GOKU screams]
[RADITZ]
Come on, Kakarot!
I want to hear you beg!
Go on. Just say Uncle!
[RADITZ laughs]
Uncle! Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
Just look at that fool...
Why so blue,
Green Man?
Is it because you're powerless
to help your friend?
Or 'cause you're
just plain ugly?
[RADITZ chuckles]
Aaaahhhh!
[RADITZ] I guess your not
going to beg for me...
Aww... You're such a
disappointment, brother.
Time to die!
[beeping]
Huh?!
I'm picking up an
enormous power level!
[RADITZ]
There's nothing there!
Huh?!
What?!
[NARRATOR] Unable to bear his
father's torture any longer,
Gohan has erupted from
Raditz' space pod
in a sudden
explosion of anger!
But what is the source of
the boy's newfound strength?
And will it be
enough to help Goku?
Find out...
When Gohan attacks!
On the next
Dragon Ball Z!