[NARRATOR]
Previously on Dragon Ball Z,
the mighty Goku obliterated
Majin Buu with his Spirit Bomb!
The evil Buu was wiped out,
but the good Buu was left
to start a new life on Earth.
But, could he fit into society?
[GIRL]
Go get your own!
[PIT BULL PETE]
That's from Pit Bull Pete!
[NARRATOR] His quest for ice
cream, led him to challenge
a street fighter,
and his victory earned him
a sweet payday!
Buu had scored the mother lode!
Everyone was happy...
Except Bulma, that is!
But was shopping
the perfect cure?
It was until a pair of
desperate thieves barged in!
[BUU] Hey, you nice men!
Give Buu money for ice cream!
[NARRATOR]
But with Citizen Buu on hand,
even the most
dangerous situation
seemed like mere child's play!
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile, underneath
a starlit sky at Mount Paoz,
Goku, Trunks, and Goten
were demonstrating the old
saying that boys will be boys!
And these boys
were fighting back!
[GOTENKS]
Geronimo!
[GOKU] Ow! Hey! So you
wanna play rough, huh?
[NARRATOR] It was a
bathtub brawl to remember,
but the naked truth was that
Goku simply could not be beat!
[CHICHI] Hmm! Well, I like it,
but it doesn't like me.
It makes my bottom look big.
This one won't do either...
It's out of style.
[CHICHI]
Hey! Yeah! This'll work!
It's a classic,
but it's still alluring.
[GOHAN]
Mom?
Oh? Hey! Don't you
look stunning? Goodness!
Thanks, Mom.
But do you think we might
be overdressing a little bit?
We're not overdressed!
How could you say that?
[chuckles sheepishly]
Besides, isn't your future
wife going to be there?
I remember the first party
that your Dad and I went to!
Did I ever tell you about that?
You would think we
were going to the opera,
but we're just going to Bulma's!
It's a barbeque, isn't it?
[CHICHI]
Gohan?
What do you think?
This is more casual, right?
Yeah, it's cool.
I like it a lot better
than those other outfits.
Good, I-I guess a little
lipstick wouldn't hurt, huh?
What about my hair? Do you
like it better the other way?
[GOTENKS]
Hmm-mm.
Ugh. I'm glad
we got that settled!
By the way, where's your father?
Is he ready to go yet?
To go? I think he already went.
He was here a few minutes ago,
and now he's gone!
Ohh! I know where.
[CHICHI] Oh, great!
Where is he this time?!
[GOKU]
Hey! What in the world?
[GOKU] Oh, there it is! It fell
through! I'm glad I came!
[PTERODACTYL MOM screeches]
[screams]
All right! I get it!
I was only trying to help!
Give me a break!
[GOKU]
Not that kind of break, man!
I'm glad you're happy,
but if the egg hatches there,
your baby's going to fall!
[CHICHI] You mean
he deserted his family
to go look at some eggs?!
What kind of
lame excuse is that?
Yeah, but they're
gonna hatch soon!
He wanted to make
sure that they're okay!
[GOHAN] I looked all over, Mom.
He's not anywhere around here.
Hey, do you want me to check on
the other side of the mountain?
No way! Come on!
We're leaving without him!
Can't he stop saving
things just for one day
so we can be
together as a family?!
Is that too much to ask?!
Why can't someone else be the
egg man today?! This is absurd!
You're smart, but building nests
obviously isn't your forte.
[screeches]
Whoa! Easy! Sorry!
I just want to help you
so I can take off!
I have a family of my own
I need to tend to.
Two boys and a wife.
An extremely angry wife
who probably wants
to kill me right now.
[PTERODACTYL MOM screeches]
[GOKU]
Yikes!
Gotcha!
[GOKU] Sorry! Can't say
I blame you for trying!
Have a nice flight!
[PTERODACTYL MOM coos]
[GOKU thinking] Oh, boy!
How did I get myself into this?
[door bell rings]
Hey! Long time no see!
Yeah! You're really growing!
You're almost as
tall as I am, Trunks!
[chuckles]
Come in! Huh?
[KRILLIN]
Uh! Look out!
[PUAR screams]
[TRUNKS growls]
Thanks, Trunks! Sorry
about that! It's brand new!
I'm not used to it yet!
[KRILLIN]
Sweet ride, bro!
Yeah! Sweet!
This was made here!
It's got the Capsule Corp logo!
Indeed! Your mom gave me a great
deal on this little cruiser!
Wow! I could get used to this.
[GOHAN]
I'll bet you could! Hey!
Hi, everyone!
Hi! It's great to see you guys!
Ah, where's Goku?
Well, uh...
Goku? Never heard of him!
Who's he anyway?!
Gosh! What in the world
is he doing this time?
[CHICHI]
He's having a baby!
A what?
It's a long story.
I'll explain later.
[ROBOT A]
Ginger Ale, anyone?
[ROBOT B]
Club Sandwich!
[ROBOT C]
Fill 'er up! Thank you!
[ROBOT D]
Fill 'er up!
[TIEN]
Here you go, Krillin!
Ahhh! Thanks!
[YAMCHA] Yeah, that was taken
right before she dumped me!
[laughing]
[BUU]
Ah-ha!
So, then! Guardians aren't
forbidden to attend parties?
If they are,
it's a bit late now!
[GOHAN]
Thanks, Videl! Huh?
Piccolo?
Hey! I didn't even know
you were here! This is great!
[PICCOLO]
Yeah!
[GOKU sighs]
[GOKU thinking]
Sweet beginnings...
I started my life on
Earth on this mountain,
just like these
little ones are about to.
It's just that the egg
I hatched out of
happened to be a spaceship!
[BABY GOKU cries]
[GOKU] I don't remember much
about being in the woods
except that I was all alone.
Then he came. Gohan!
My very own grandpa.
[BABY GOKU cries]
[GOKU]
Once he picked me up,
I knew that everything
was going to be all right.
[GOHAN]
Ahh... Hey!
[GOKU thinking] Oh, Grandpa!
He was a stern old guy at times!
Of course,
he was dealing with some
highly unusual circumstances!
[GOKU] I had that
poor man climbing the walls!
Thank goodness he
had a loving heart!
[GOHAN chuckles]
[GOKU]
I was a mess!
I meant well,
but I wrecked
everything in sight!
He always managed to see
the humorous side of it though!
[GOHAN laughs]
Grandpa...
[DINOSAURS roaring]
Hey!
[roars]
[PTERODACTYL DAD screeches]
[GOKU
Hey, you two!
You're going to have to finish
this somewhere else, okay?
[GOKU] Have at it, guys!
Knock yourselves out!
Let's boogie!
[ALL laugh, whoop]
Go ahead, Gohan.
What do you call that one?
The chicken?!
Step aside and take notes!
[YAMCHA]
Oh, yeah, ChiChi!
[GROUP cheers]
[YAMCHA]
All right! Go, ChiChi!
[ROSHI]
Karate Mama!
Goten! Your Mom's almost
as cool as your outfit.
Is it cool, Gohan?
I wouldn't go that far.
It's different,
that's for sure!
But Mom obviously
thinks it's cool,
and I guess that's
all that matters!
[BULMA] You're right about that,
Gohan! It's all in the attitude!
Your Mom invented this kind of
dance! I call it Tai ChiChi!
[OOLONG]
Yeah! You go, girl!
--[CHICHI] Hyah!
--[bones crack]
--[GOTEN] Oh no, my mom!
--My gosh, Mom! Are you okay?
[CHICHI] Give me a
Senzu Bean and I'll finish!
[ALL cheer]
Awesome! Only Goku's wife
would say something like that!
[gasping]
Goku?
He should've been here by now!
[DENDE thinking]
Maybe this is why
guardian's shouldn't
be at parties...
It's just not the
same without him, is it?
Gosh! You really care for Goku.
Hey! I know! How 'bout we
trade mates! Vegeta for Goku!
[BULMA]
Uhh...?
Vegeta's not as sweet,
but he's certainly
more dependable.
I think it evens out!
[BULMA growls]
[ALL laugh]
Hey! I'm available, ladies!
What d'ya say, huh?
We're talking an even trade!
We don't want to downgrade!
[laughter]
I feel sorry for
your mother, Gohan.
Don't worry! He'll be here!
[GOKU thinking]
This could take all day.
[GOKU thinking] I used to
have a tail just like that.
[screeches]
Ahh...
[GOKU]
Oh! Hi!
Are you guys worried
about the new babies, too?
[GOKU] Wow! That's really nice
of you! What good neighbors.
[GOKU] Uh-oh! I don't
like the looks of this!
[MONKEYS gibbering]
[gasps]
[GOKU]
That's not gonna hold!
[screeches]
[GOKU thinking] If I try to
move the eggs to a safer place,
they're going to freak out!
But I can't just leave
them there like that!
Shoot! This is going to get
worse before it gets better.
I need to do something fast!
[PTERODACTYL DAD screeching]
[GOKU thinking]
Hold on, guys!
[GOKU]
Easy there, girl!
We're going to make
this nest stronger!
[GOKU] Don't be scared!
This is going to help!
[screeches]
[GOKU]
I know! Hold on!
[GOKU] I'm going to
try to reinforce it!
[GOKU] That's a little better!
I'll go get another one!
[GOKU screams]
[PTERODACTYL DAD screeches]
[yells]
[screeches]
[GOKU]
That's it! Stay with it!
[screeching]
[gasps]
[GOKU]
No!
Gotcha!
[GOKU]
Whoo! That was close!
[GOKU] Let's get this little guy
back to a warm, safe place!
[yells]
[PTERODACTYL DAD screeches]
[screeches]
[GOKU grunts]
[screeching]
[GOKU]
It's okay! I've got it!
[OOLONG]
Go fish!
[YAMCHA] Look at that grin.
He's hiding something!
[laughing]
Well, it's been great,
but I think we'd better
be heading out!
Thanks again, Bulma!
Sure! Any time!
--[YAMCHA] See you, guys!
--[GOKU] Hey!
[yelling]
[KRILLIN]
Ow! What the heck?!
--Goku?
--[ANDROID 18] Goku?!
[ALL]
Goku?!
What's up, Dad?
Well, obviously
not me! Hi, everyone!
Where's your mother?
[CHICHI] I'll tell you
where I am! On Lonely Street!
When you were dead
you had an excuse!
But now, it's just
shameless neglect!
Aw! But if you could have
just seen those... eggs!
[GOKU] They were so
helpless and fragile!
Ugh. You are so lame, Goku!
But you were protecting helpless
little babies! Lucky for you!
[GOKU giggles]
[CHICHI]
Have you eaten anything?!
Oh, I guess we have to
get everything back out now!
What a bothersome husband!
Come on, Bulma!
The king wants his food!
[GOKU chuckles]
[GOTEN] So did they
finally hatch, Dad?
Yep!
Tell us about it, Goku!
How many were there?
Well, it was really
something else, Krillin.
There were four
beautiful babies.
[GOKU]
And after the storm broke,
there was a
warm glow from the sunset
and all kinds of Moms and Dads
had brought their children
out to see the miracle!
[GOKU]
Nobody was making a sound!
We were all so intent
on watching those eggs.
[gasps]
[BABY PTERODACTYLS squawking]
Hi, guys!
So Dad! What was the most
weirdest part of the day?
Well, I'll tell ya!
I've eaten plenty of fish
but that's the
first time one ate me!
[ALL laugh]
Hmm? Hey, Vegeta! What
are you doing way over there!
Come on over here with us!
[BULMA]
Oh, come on!
[CHICHI]
Yeah, come Vegeta!
[ALL chattering]
[CHICHI]
Come on, tough guy.
[YAMCHA]
Silly guy.
[NARRATOR]
Now that Goku's at the party,
everyone is having a good time.
Whether it's conquering the
unjust or lifting the spirits
of his family and friends,
Goku is indeed number
one under the Sun!