Now what do I do?
Goku!
Get outta there!
[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z!
Goku took a very wrong turn on
his journey to Planet Namek!
But as he plummeted into the
fiery heart of a giant star,
it was our hero who
turned up the heat!
Kaa... Mee...
Haa... Mee... Haaa!
[NARRATOR] With the help of
a powerful Kamehameha Wave,
the ship blasted free
of the star's gravity
and resumed its
course to Namek!
It would seem
Goku's intense training
has begun
to pay off...
And he'll need every
ounce of strength
he can get if he
hopes to face Vegeta!
The evil Saiyan has
become even more powerful
since their
last meeting...
And he's only too
happy to show it!
Bang.
[NARRATOR] Can nothing
stand in Vegeta's way?
Find out today,
on Dragon Ball Z!
[NAMEKS murmuring]
[growling]
[whimpering]
[VEGETA chuckling]
[NAMEKS growling,
VEGETA laughing]
[growling and
laughing continues]
Oh, I see.
Sounds like you guys
had a rough
time out there.
Yeah, I'd say we're
lucky to be alive!
Huh...?
[sighs sadly]
I know it's
not very good,
but you should probably
try to eat something
to get your
strength back.
[BULMA]
Not very good?!
[BULMA growls]
Well, that sure
hasn't stopped you
from stuffing
your fat face.
Would it kill
you to show me
a little appreciation
for once?! Huh?!
I... I wasn't
talking about the food!
I swear! It's the
best I ever had!
[GOHAN laughs]
[KRILLIN] Shut up, Gohan!
[laughing continues]
I'm sure he's just
too upset to eat.
I mean, after
everything that's happened.
Please try. It might
make you feel better.
I'm sorry,
but we don't eat.
We Nameks only
drink water.
Uhh... Really?
But wait a second.
You guys had fields full of
vegetables out by your village.
I saw 'em myself.
The fields you saw
were Ajissa plants.
W-W-Whoa...
Ajima wha--?
Well, the elders say
that the Planet Namek
used to be a very different
place than it is today.
They say our world was
once lush and beautiful,
alive with
forests of Ajissa.
But one day, a massive
storm darkened our skies.
Violent winds tore
across the planet,
stripping the Ajissa plants
of their delicate leaves.
The forests
were destroyed.
In fact,
all life on our planet
was brought to the
brink of extinction.
The Eldest Namek remembers
how the Ajissa plants
brought beauty to our planet,
and helped make the soil rich.
That's why we're trying
to grow more of them.
We hope this will bring our
world back to life.
[NAMEKS growling]
Haah!
Raah!
Aah!
[NAMEKS panting]
He's gone!
[whimpering]
[yelling]
[VEGETA growling]
[growling]
Whyyy youuuu!
Yaaah!
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA grunting]
[yelling]
[grunting]
[VEGETA chuckles]
Raah!
[GOHAN] Y'know,
I just realized
you haven't told
us your name yet.
I'm sorry.
It's Dende.
And who are you? What
brings you to Planet Namek?
[BOTH] Hmm?!
Whatever that is,
it's... it's bad!
[BULMA] Hey!
What is it, you guys?
Did they find us?
Is someone coming?
No. It's a whole
bunch of power levels.
And they're all... fading!
Huh?!
It means somewhere out there,
the... Nameks are dying!
[DENDE gasps]
It's... it's Vegeta! He's
attacking one of the villages!
That bastard! Those Nameks
never even had a chance!
Why, he's just an
animal, isn't he!
Yeah, and from
the looks of it,
now he knows how to sense
power levels without a scouter.
So we're stuck. 'Cause if
we try to fly anywhere
he'll find us!
I don't know if he's
working with Frieza or not.
But if either one of
them gets their hands
on all seven
Dragon Balls,
we're gonna be in
some serious trouble.
I don't think anyone'll be
able to stand up to them!
We may not be able to
fight them directly,
but if we can manage to find
just one of the Dragon Balls
and hide it, we can stop
them from making a wish.
[GOHAN] No.
That's not enough.
It won't stop them
from looking for it.
They'll kill every Namek on
this planet until they find it!
[DENDE gasps]
Oh no!
[KRILLIN] What are
we supposed to do?
I mean, Vegeta on
his own is bad enough.
But... Vegeta and
Frieza together?!
Man, I don't even know
if Goku's strong enough
to fight 'em both.
Dammit!
[KRILLIN] I should've killed
Vegeta when I had the chance!
[DENDE] I... I still don't
understand... Who are you?
[BOTH] Huh?
[DENDE] You seem to
know everything about
the Dragon Balls
and these evil men
who attack my people.
Please... Please tell me that
you've come here to help us!
[VEGETA yelling]
[moaning]
[VEGETA] Hmph.
You killed them...
You savage!
You killed them all!
[VEGETA]
Well, well...
It's just down to
you and me, old man.
Are you ready to tell me
where the Dragon Ball is yet?
No, I won't do it.
You'll never find it!
[VEGETA laughs]
Oh, you think
not, do you?
Well, then.
We'll see, won't we?
Hm?
[VEGETA growls]
[ELDER NAMEK screaming]
Don't ever
try to stop me.
[VEGETA chuckles]
I should
have known.
Sitting right out in the
open for all to admire.
This should
do nicely...
[VEGETA laughs]
Frieza can tear this planet
apart looking for that Ball.
But he'll never suspect
it's hidden so close to home.
[VEGETA] So... six of the Dragon
Balls are now accounted for.
Only one
left to find.
It's been
too long.
Dodoria should have
been back by now.
Something must
have happened.
Maybe I'd better
go look for him.
[FRIEZA] Forget him.
If he isn't
capable of dealing
with two puny pests
and a baby Namek,
then I don't
want him back.
Continue your search for
the last two Dragon Balls.
[HENCHMAN] But, how will we find
the Namek villages
without our scouters?
We'll have to search
this entire planet!
And that's exactly
what we'll do.
Don't worry, Lord Frieza.
We'll find them.
[FRIEZA] I expect nothing
less from you Zarbon.
Now, leave all the
Dragon Balls with me.
I'll wait for you
back at the ship.
Come to me when you
have the final two.
And do hurry...
I'd like to make my wish
before I die of old age.
[BOTH] Lord.
[ZARBON] I want you to
search in that direction.
If you find
any villages,
note the position and
come get me at once.
Don't try and take on
the Nameks by yourself.
They're way too
strong. Understand?
Sir.
Otherwise, meet me back at
the spaceship in three hours.
Now, head out!
If Vegeta tries to
interfere with my plans
for getting all
the Dragon Balls,
he will soon
regret it.
I refuse to stop until I've
collected all seven of them.
But I imagine he'll be
on his way sometime soon
to try to steal
these five.
Well, that's fine with me.
I hope he does try it.
He'll just save me the trouble
of having to hunt him down.
[FRIEZA laughs]
Poor Vegeta has no idea
what he's getting into.
So, I can just
relax at the ship.
Ha!
[KRILLIN] So you see,
we thought if we came
to Kami's
home planet,
there might be another
set of Dragon Balls here.
We hoped we'd be able
to wish all our friends
that Vegeta and his
partner killed back to life.
That's all we're
trying to do.
Not only that, if
our wish is granted,
it means the Earth's Dragon
Balls will come back, too.
Oh. Thank you for
telling me your story.
So your world has been
terrorized by these men, too.
[DENDE growls]
Then we must fight
them! Together!
And I know
someone who can help.
I must take you to
see the Eldest Namek!
Huh?
And, who's that?
But how can
he help us?
Oh, he is
very wise.
He is the father
of all Nameks!
He alone survived
the terrible storm
that nearly
destroyed our world.
And he is the one
who is responsible
for repopulating
it so far!
We are all
his children.
I myself am
his 108th child.
But, um, well...
How exactly did your father
have a child all by himself?
What do you
mean "how"?
He spit the eggs out
of his mouth, of course.
Oh, right.
H-How silly of me...
Wait, so what
you're saying is
he is actually a she,
right? A female!
Female?
What's a female?
[BULMA] Well, there's
two types of people, right?
Males and females. And
they're... they're different.
So, like for
instance, say...
You have brothers,
and you have sisters!
What?
Different types?
Uh... No...
[BULMA gasps]
Can you believe this? There's
no different genders here!
They're all one type!
I'm sure glad I'm not a Namek.
Talk about boring!
'Kay. Anyway...
So you really think
going to see this Eldest
guy'll do us some good?
Yes... But, it's
important that we go quickly.
The ones who
attacked my village
already have five
of the Dragon Balls.
And, if another
village is being attacked
right now,
like you say,
unless the Nameks
can hold them off,
they'll be looking for
the Eldest Namek soon.
Sorry, kid.
I think it's all over.
[GOHAN] I'm not sensing
any more power levels.
It doesn't feel like
Vegeta left any survivors.
Oh, no...
If that's true,
then there are only a
few of us left alive now...
Wait a sec... So, if Vegeta
got the sixth Dragon Ball
in that village, and if
there aren't many Nameks
left out there...
Then, does that mean the Eldest
Namek has the last Dragon Ball?
That's right.
This is bad!
[ALL gasp]
[KRILLIN] It might take
Frieza's goons a while
to find him without
their scouters,
but that won't
stop Vegeta!
If he has any
kind of power,
Vegeta will sense
him from miles away!
For all we know, he could be
on his way there already!
Exactly! And we must warn the
Eldest Namek that he's coming!
Please! Please, you have to
help me! Come with me, please!
It's risky, but I'd say
we'll be in even more danger
if we let Frieza or Vegeta
get that Dragon Ball.
'Kay, let's go. You lead
the way. I'll follow.
Right.
With any luck, this
won't take too long.
But I want you to
wait here with Bulma
until we get
back, okay?
We can't let
Vegeta sense us both!
You're right. It'll be
better if we split up.
See ya! You guys
be extra careful.
You, too! Bye!
[thinking] Vegeta seems
stronger than he's ever been.
And the power I
sensed from Frieza
was even higher than his!
I don't know what kind of
training Goku's doing, but...
But whether he's strong
enough to beat them or not,
the only thing we can do now
is get the last Dragon Ball
from this Eldest Namek and
hide out for a few days
until he gets here.
Then I guess we just
cross our fingers
and hope we don't
all get creamed.
[KRILLIN thinking]
Ahh, who am I kidding?
I doubt any of us're gonna
make it off this planet!
I'm gonna die here...
And I've never even
had a girlfriend!
[GOKU grunting]
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU] Well, I guess that does
it for twenty-times gravity.
Good, then it's time to
start working on thirty.
[KING KAI]
Goku, can you hear me?
Helloooo...
Come in, Goku...
Hey, I sure hope
that's you, King Kai.
[KING KAI] No, it's the
chair talking to you.
Of course it's me!
How are you, Goku? I had some
trouble tracking you down.
You're moving at a
pretty good clip there
in that spaceship of yours.
But I guess it means
you're off to Planet Namek
for a little Dragon Ball
hunting, huh? Sounds exciting.
Wait a second...
You mean you
don't know anything
about what's
been going on?
It's a long story, but
there's a whole lot of trouble
waiting for
me on Namek.
You can fill me
in in a minute...
First, I have something
important to tell you.
You see, I've received
some unexpected guests.
[GOKU] Guests? What's the big
deal about having some guests?
[KING KAI] Well for starters,
they got down Snake Way
even faster
than you did!
Let's just say, they're
some pretty strong guys.
Stumped? Okay, I'll give you
a hint. There's four of them!
Huh? Four?
[KING KAI] Yup. Let's also say
you know these guys pretty well.
[GOKU] No way!
You don't mean...
[KING KAI chuckles]
You guessed it!
They're here, and they
want me to train them
harder than
I trained you!
You gotta be kidding me!
Everyone made it?
They all reached you
together? That's great news!
Hey, can I say
hello to him?
[KING KAI] Of course.
Just rest your hand
on my shoulder and speak.
He'll hear you.
[YAMCHA] What's up, Goku?
[GOKU] Yamcha!
Guess we just missed each
other at the check-in station.
But we saw Kami, and he
told us about this place.
Uh-huh.
[YAMCHA] Anyway, King Kai told
us you guys might try to find
the Dragon Balls
on Planet Namek
so you could
wish us all back.
That's really great, Goku.
You're a good friend.
Thanks, Yamcha.
So, who all's there with you?
What about Piccolo?
Did he make it?
[YAMCHA] Yeah,
he's here alright.
Heh. Like I'd let those
clowns train without me.
I don't want them
to start thinking
they can show me
up or anything.
[GOKU] And you said you ran
into Kami. Is he there, too?
No, not Kami.
He stayed back at the
Check-In Station.
It's Tien
and Chiaotzu!
[GOKU] Chiaotzu? That's
fantastic! How is he?
Is he doing okay?
[YAMCHA] He's doing
just fine, Goku.
In fact, I almost had
trouble keeping up with him
coming down Snake Way! Heh, heh!
[GOKU] Ha, ha, ha!
All right! Way to go, Chiaotzu!
[CHIAOTZU chuckles]
[GOKU] Wow, you guys.
This is great!
You don't know how glad
I am to hear from you!
[NARRATOR] Goku is
certainly relieved to learn
of his friends' safe
arrival on King Kai's planet.
However, still more of
his friends are in danger
on Planet Namek!
Can they escape the watchful
eyes of Vegeta and Frieza?
Don't miss the
next Dragon Ball Z!