[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Trunks jumped into a
one-on-one brawl against Cell.
With Vegeta beaten
and Goku still in training,
it was clear that Trunks
was the planet's last hope.
[KRILLIN] Hang in there,
Trunks... You have to beat Cell!
You're the only
one who can do it now!
[NARRATOR] Kicking
into second gear,
Trunks struggled to keep
Cell at bay long enough
for Vegeta to be rescued.
Now, alone on the battlefield,
Trunks is pushing his
powers as far as he can.
[TRUNKS] ...Come and get me!
I will, but show me some of that
wonderful power of yours first.
[NARRATOR] Cell,
loaded with confidence
after pummeling Vegeta,
is actually encouraging Trunks
to unleash his maximum power.
The evil android is
anxious for a good fight,
and by the looks of it, that's
exactly what he's going to get.
[NARRATOR] Get ready, it's
time for these two titans
to engage in the
fight for the future!
Today, on Dragon Ball Z!
[TRUNKS grunts]
[TRUNKS yells]
[yelling continues]
[ANDROID 16 thinking] I see now
why the boy was not scared.
[TRUNKS yells]
[TRUNKS yelling in distance]
Huh?
What's happening back there?
Hey, that's not a storm
cloud... that's Trunks!
How can I feel his energy
from this far away?
Yikes! I'm glad I'm
not a lightning rod.
[TRUNKS yells]
[ROSHI] Earthquake!
Run for your lives!
[YAMCHA whimpers]
That's no earthquake.
[ROSHI yelps]
[ROSHI] Hmm...?
That's quite a view!
[CHICHI gasps]
Watch the hands, old man!
[ROSHI] D'oh!
[TRUNKS yells]
[BABY TRUNKS babbles]
I've never felt energy
that strong before.
It can't be possible!
That's Trunks' energy.
He passed Vegeta? How can that
be? He'll beat Cell for sure!
[TRUNKS yells]
Nice light show, Trunks.
It's such a shame
Vegeta isn't here to see
that you have
surpassed his power.
As long as I have the
power to destroy you, Cell,
that's all that matters to me.
Your kind ruined my future,
and I'll sacrifice
everything to change it!
[WOMAN A shrieking]
[TRUNKS] The world
I grew up in
was devastated by
Dr. Gero's androids.
They took control of the planet
and terrorized the population.
Here they come again! Those
monsters are going to attack us!
What can we do?
There's no escape!
[MEN yelling]
[screaming]
I do enjoy destroying these
cities, and how about you?
Isn't it wonderful
that these humans
have so many buildings
for us to annihilate?
Yeah, but I think we
need to spice things up.
Mass destruction just
isn't fun anymore.
[TRUNKS] The androids
continued their path of terror,
and finally found the
excitement they were looking for
when they slaughtered my father!
[VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA groans]
No!
[VEGETA screams]
[TRUNKS] Thrilled by
the new challenge,
the androids tracked
down all of the Z Fighters.
Even Piccolo was
quickly overwhelmed.
[PICCOLO screams]
[TRUNKS] And Krillin
suffered a similar fate.
[KRILLIN screams]
[TRUNKS] Tien was
taken out next.
[TRUNKS] Then the Androids
went after Yamcha!
Poor Yajirobe never even
saw them coming...
[TRUNKS] One-by-one they
destroyed the greatest fighters
on the planet...
...until there was no one
left to challenge them.
No one except Gohan and me.
We were the last
fighters to survive.
Oh, look... it's Gohan.
You two are gonna pay for
what you've done to this planet!
[ANDROID 18 giggles]
Do you know Tien and Piccolo
said the same thing...
right before we destroyed them?
[GOHAN grunts]
Trunks! Stay back!
[TRUNKS] Right!
[GOHAN grunts]
[TRUNKS] Gohan!
[ANDROID 18 gasps]
You little brat! How dare
you do that to my hair!
[TRUNKS yells]
[grunting]
[GOHAN yells]
[ANDROID 18 grunts]
[ANDROID 17 snarls]
[ANDROID 18 growls]
Yaaah!
[GOHAN] Masenko-Ha!
[ANDROID 18] Curse those brats!
Where have they gone?!
Let's just bomb the whole area.
That will draw those
two out of hiding.
What should we do?
Stay here. We can't
let them find us!
I hate androids!
[GOHAN thinking] If my
father were still alive,
he'd know what to do...
[GOHAN] Oh, Dad, I always
thought you were invincible.
At least to a virus...
But I'll be brave for you,
Dad. I'll make you proud.
Well, Gohan?
What should we do?
[TRUNKS] Gohan fought
a long, hard battle
against the androids,
but he was too
overwhelmed by their power.
I survived and vowed to
find a way to break the grip
the androids had on the planet.
I helped my mother build a time
machine and traveled to the past
to alter the events that had
led to this disastrous future.
You see? That's why
I'm going to defeat you!
Cell... I will not let you
destroy the future again!
[TRUNKS growls]
[yelling]
That's the way, Trunks, keep
it up! Show me your great power.
You've held back
for far too long.
Let's see what you can do!
[TRUNKS gasps]
[CELL] I have grown so
bored with challengers
who are not worthy of
being in my presence.
But now that I am complete, it
will be a pleasure to do battle
with a Super Saiyan
at your level.
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL] Soon I will make
Dr. Gero's dark dream
of revenge a reality.
[COMPUTER] Subject, Cell.
DNA growth sequence initiated.
[CELL] There in my
development chamber...
I learned of my destiny
through the voice of
my creator Dr. Gero.
[COMPUTER] Voice
message activated.
[DR. GERO] Cell...
You must listen carefully.
You are my ultimate achievement!
I have spent years
constructing you from the cells
of the greatest
fighters in the world.
And soon, your first
evolution will be completed.
[DR. GERO] If you are
hearing this message,
it's because I have not
survived to see your completion.
And though that
saddens me greatly...
I know that my revenge will
be realized through you.
Nothing will stand in your way!
[COMPUTER] Warning!
Chamber breach imminent!
Warning! System
malfunction! Warning!
Warning! Warning!
[DR. GERO] Cell,
you will need to absorb
the bio extract of the living
to move into your next
stage of development.
You must feed to grow, but your
hunger will never be satisfied.
That is the beauty
of your design.
You will always have an
insatiable appetite for power,
much like my own.
My enemies will become yours.
Seek them out and
destroy all of them!
But never forget that your main
objective is to become complete.
The only way to do that is
to find the other androids
and absorb them.
Only then will you evolve
into your perfect form.
[CELL] And so it began.
My reign over this planet
was swift and relentless.
I set out to find
Android 17 and 18
by following the
trail of devastation
they left in their wake.
Along the way I absorbed
as much bio extract as I could.
At first there was resistance,
but I consumed all
who challenged me
and the rest fell in line.
There really is nothing better
than the cold taste of fear.
[WOMAN B screams]
[MAN C] The monster...
he's coming this way!
Don't be afraid...
stay together!
[MAN D] Let's get 'im!
[MAN D yells]
[MAN D squeals]
[MAN D screams]
Let's blast him!
Come on... FIRE!
[GROUP yelling]
[GROUP gasping]
[screaming]
Retreat!
[MAN F] Oh, please, no!
[MAN F grunts]
[screaming continues]
[MAN C rasps]
[MAN G groans]
[screaming]
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL] Dr. Gero was right.
No one stood in my way.
Every victim
gave me more strength.
I could feel the cells
in my body transforming.
As my power grew,
so did my hunger,
and I yearned to
become complete.
To do that, I needed to
absorb Androids 17 and 18,
but no matter how
fast I searched,
it seemed I was always
one step behind.
Finally, I learned why. The
androids had been deactivated.
I believe I have you
to thank for that, Trunks.
And really, I do thank you. For
it proved to work out perfectly.
By stealing your time machine...
I was able to absorb
the androids here
and become complete.
And now that I'm ready,
I have a world not yet
touched by the androids.
Which means, all the
more for me to devour.
I have achieved my perfect form.
Dr. Gero will have his revenge
and this pathetic
planet will be destroyed.
And you're responsible
for all of it!
[CELL giggles]
[CELL chuckles]
By traveling back in time,
you thought you could
change the events
of the future, didn't you?
Well, let me assure you
that you were successful,
though not quite
in the way you planned!
[TRUNKS growls]
[CELL] Rather than prevent
the world's destruction--
[CELL laughs]
[CELL] You've guaranteed it!
[CELL growls]
[CELL] Let me show you my
complete power.
Observe, my little friend.
[TRUNKS] Go on!
Show me what you've got!
And you'll be
the first to see the
true power of the Saiyan race!
[TRUNKS yells]
[yelling continues]
[TRUNKS shouts]
[TRUNKS] Give it up, Cell!
It's over!
What?! He's gone! I know he
can withstand more than that!
[TRUNKS grunts]
[TRUNKS shouts]
[blows landing,
BOTH grunting]
They move so fast!
Their speed is incredible!
[CELL chuckles]
You cannot win, Cell!
I'm going to make sure that
all androids are gone for good!
[TRUNKS yells]
[TRUNKS grunts]
[TRUNKS grunting]
[yelling]
[CELL grunts]
Huh?!
[CELL groans]
Huh?
[CELL chuckles]
Impressive... I must admit
you have exceeded me, Trunks.
At least in the area
of brute strength.
And yet, you have absolutely
no chance of defeating me!
[TRUNKS growls]
[TRUNKS] Listen to yourself!
What kind of logic is that?!
Oh, you'll see.
[CELL chuckles]
[NARRATOR] The battle between
Trunks and Cell is
well underway.
And after a
bone-breaking first round,
the young Saiyan seems
to have a slight upperhand.
But what secret does Cell know?
Why is he so relaxed?
Find out next time,
on Dragon Ball Z!