[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragonball Z,
Captain Ginyu managed to
switch bodies with Goku!
Yaaaah!
[GOKU grunts]
[NARRATOR] Now, with Goku's
stronger, less damaged body,
Ginyu seemed to
have the upper hand.
[GINYU chuckles]
[GOKU gasps]
Why you... Hey...
What kinda... powers
did you... use?
[GINYU chuckles]
[GINYU] The power to
metamorph into your body
and fool your men...
[GOKU] It's... impossible!
No, it can't be...!
Good. Now, let's head
back to the ship.
[GINYU] Hey, this new
body is pretty quick!
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
Vegeta, Gohan and Krillin,
and Jeice and Captain Ginyu, are
headed for Frieza's spaceship...
Can Goku muster up
enough strength
to follow Frieza and steal
back the Dragon Balls?
Find out today.
[LIZARD GUARD yawns]
[VEGETA chuckles]
Well... it looks like
Frieza's out on the town!
This is going to be
easier than I thought.
Hello, boys!
[SOLDIER A] Huh?
[SOLDIER B gasps]
[LIZARD SOLDIER screams]
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[VEGETA chuckling]
[SOLDIERS murmuring]
Huh...? What the--
What was that explosion?!
[SOLDIERS gasp]
Oh no, it's Vegeta?!
Ahhhh... it can't be!
[SOLDIERS whimpering]
[whimpering continues]
[SOLDIER E yells]
[SOLDIERS murmur]
Rraaauugh!
[LIZARD SOLDIER B groans]
[VEGETA] Where are
the Dragon Balls?
Where are they?!
[VEGETA growls frustratedly]
[VEGETA] Where are they?!
I want an answer right now!
[SOLDIERS whimpering]
[SOLDIERS growling]
Well?! What are
you staring at?!
And you call
yourself guards?!
[SOLDIERS growling]
Don't tell me that
your afraid of me?
[SOLDIERS gasping]
[VEGETA] Look! I've
even come unarmed!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[VEGETA laughs]
[SOLDIERS panting]
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[screaming]
Takes care of them.
Now, to find out where
those Dragon Balls are.
[VEGETA] They've got to
be around here someplace,
'cause why would Frieza have
left his guards
here if they weren't?
Hmm, now where
would he hide them?
The obvious place would
be inside this spaceship,
but that's way too obvious.
Gotta give Frieza
more credit than that.
I'll just take my
time and look around...
[GINYU laughs]
[GINYU] So fun,
hey, Jeice?
[GINYU] And now, I have an
unbelievable amount of power!
And, I gotta admit, this new
face doesn't look half bad.
What d'ya think Jeice?
Lookin' good, mate!
[GOKU grunts]
Ah man, I gotta hurry...
If I don't make it in time,
Gohan and Krillin are done for.
[GOKU grunts]
Where am I? I gotta
get my bearings
[GOKU grunts]
[GOKU yells]
Ribbit... Ribbit...
[GOKU] Ah, nuts!
I just can't get the
hang of this bulky body!
[thinking] I can't believe I
regained my strength so quickly.
Now all I have to do is
concentrate my power
and in no time, those hidden
Dragon Balls will be mine!
[VEGETA] Finally. These
dryers take forever.
Krillin, the Dragon
Balls are at 12 o'clock!
Right there!
Do you see it?
I'm locked on...
And ready to kick butt!
[VEGETA] Hngh?!
Hmm...
[thinking] I believe
I have company.
Yes, I think I'll just observe
them for a little while more.
And once they get the Dragon
Balls for me, I'll destroy them!
Let's get down there
and find 'em...
before anyone shows up!
Wait a sec,
Krillin! Will ya?
According to the
Dragon Radar,
the balls are down
there all right,
but they're not located
inside the ship!
Huh?
[KRILLIN] Which way, Gohan?
[GOHAN] It looks
like... This way!
The signals getting stronger!
Krillin!
I've found them!
Someone buried
them right here!
It looks like the ground
has been recently dug up.
But I wonder how
deep they're buried?
Well, what say
we start digging?
Uh-huh!
[GOHAN hums,
KRILIN chuckles]
Huh?
Look, Gohan!
A Dragon Ball!
[GOHAN laughs]
[GOHAN] Look, I found another!
[KRILLIN] One over here!
[GOHAN] I found two more!
[GOHAN laughs]
[thinking] Aagh, it would have
to be those stupid rugrats!
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN laughing]
Who'd have thought...
We found all seven!
[GOHAN laughs]
[thinking] Well, I suppose I
could look on the bright side.
After all, those puny little
punks just saved me the trouble
of getting my hands dirty.
Now all I have to do is nab
'em and make my wish!
[VEGETA chuckles]
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN laugh]
[GOHAN] Yeaah!
[BOTH laughing]
You got a dirty smudge.
Right there!
[KRILLIN laughs]
Well your face is
covered in dirt too!
[KRILLIN] What? It is? Where?
[GOHAN laughs]
[thinking] Come on,
you Nimrods! Move it!
[BOTH laughing]
[GOHAN laughs]
Well, they're all here.
It's been such a long
since we've started,
I don't know what
to wish for anymore.
[thinking] Oh, c'mon already!
Let's get this show on the road!
Well, I do. Let's summon
the dragon, Gohan,
'Cause we've got
some wishin' to do.
So, are you ready
to bring Piccolo back
to the land of the living?
Yes!
[KRILLIN growls]
I summon the Dragon,
I command you now! Hear my howl,
to make my wish come true!
I summon the Dragon,
I command you now! Hear my howl,
to make my wish come true!
[thinking] So that's
the password!
[KRILLIN laughs]
[BOTH laughing]
[thinking] Huh? How
come nothing's happening?
Isn't the Dragon
supposed to show up?!
[KRILLIN chuckles]
Uhh...
No... No... No... No... No!
Nothing's happening! But why?!
We have all seven Dragon Balls?!
[GOHAN] Wait! Didn't Dad
say there was a password?
[KRILLIN] Why didn't
we ask what it is?!
[VEGETA thinking] Oh, great!
Little chrome dome
can't even remember
the password!
[GOHAN] Well, you don't
have to yell at me!
[KRILLIN] Who's
yelling?! I'm not yelling!
Well, what now?
Huh? Krillin, I-I think
I hear someone coming!
What...?!
Gohan...
[GOHAN] Yeah...
[KRILLIN] There's
two of them!
You think the Ginyu Force
followed us here?!
[GOHAN] If they did,
that would mean they
defeated my father!
[thinking] Oh, great.
This just isn't my day.
I don't like this.
Something's wrong...
If they're coming here then what
happened between them Goku?
C'mon, Gohan!
I think you may be right
about those Ginyu guys.
[KRILLIN gasps]
[GOHAN gasps]
[VEGETA gasps]
What the...
Look Cap'n! It's all seven
Dragon Balls! Right there!
They're all dug up!
[GINYU] How convenient!
Jeice... Any ideas
on who dug them up?
[KRILLIN laughs]
[GINYU &amp; JEICE gasp]
Hey, Goku!
It's me, Krillin
Me and Gohan were
really worried about you!
What took you
so long, huh?
[JEICE snickers]
Boy, for a second there,
I thought you were that
Captain Ginyu coming,
but you must've
taken care of him, right?
First of all, Captain "Ginyu"
was a worthy opponent...
Now, how did you find the balls?
HA! Will you quit
kidding around, Goku?
You know good and
well that we used
the Dragon Radar to find 'em.
A Dragon Radar...?
What the heck is that?
So, "Krillin", have
you made your wish?
Well, we didn't
know the password!
Hey, do you know
what it is, Goku?
[KRILLIN] Uh... Goku?
Maybe... Why
don't I try?
Goku? Are you sure
you're feeling alright?
I mean, you sound kinda
strange. Is everything okay?
And am I missing something?
What are you doing
hanging around with Jeice?
Isn't he the enemy or
did he switch sides?
Good question...
Huh?
Hey, Krillin! That
guy isn't my Father!
Huh?
Huh...?
Look out,
he's behind you!
Uhh...
[GINYU chuckles]
[GOHAN gasps]
Noo!
Ah... I see you're
tougher than you look.
Hey, but I'm not interested
in you two runts.
Where's the challenge?
I could easily dispose of
both of you in an instant.
[KRILLIN] What're
you talking about?!
[GOHAN] Krillin!
He's not my Dad!
Believe me!
[GINYU chuckles]
What d'ya mean he's
not your dad...?
Take a look for yourself.
How can you be so sure, Gohan?
You gotta trust me.
When I look
in his eyes
I can just tell!
[GINYU chuckles]
[GINYU laughs]
Very perceptive, kid...
Let's just say I'm taking your
dad's body for a test drive!
[GOHAN gasps]
Wh-What did you say...?!
[thinking] That voice!
It's Captain Ginyu!
Surprise!
[JEICE howls]
[JEICE] Yoooww!
It's time to face the
fury of the Ginyu Force...
I'm Jeice!
[GINYU grunting]
[GINYU] And introducing...
The new and improved
Captain Ginyu...
[JEICE] Tell 'em what
time it is, baby!
It's time for you to die!
I gotta hurry...
If I don't, Gohan and Krillin
don't stand a chance...
Huh...?
But with this body...
I-I can't...
I can't lock onto their exact
position to find them...
and I'll never forgive myself
if anything happens to Gohan!
Wait a sec!
If you're not Goku, then
what happened to him?!
[GINYU] If I knew,
I'd tell you!
Let's just say...
I am going to do to you
two twerps what I did to him!
No! Please,
wait a minute...
Can we maybe discuss
this like gentlemen?
Or at least give
us a last meal?
[GINYU shouts]
[grunting,
blows landing]
[thinking] Okay, this
is starting to become
a little too complicated!
Even with Captain Ginyu
inside Goku's body,
it doesn't take away from
Goku's original strength!
This is nuts!
[shouting]
[GINYU] Having fun yet?!
'Cause I'm just
getting warmed up!
[GINYU laughs]
[JEICE chuckles]
Huh...
Huh?
[JEICE] Captain Ginyu!
Incoming at three
o'clock high, sir!
What? Huh?
[BOTH] Huh?
[GOKU] Must concentrate...
[thinking] Now what?!
[GOKU] Your trick
won't work, Ginyu...
[GINYU laughs]
[GINYU] Well, well, look
what the cat dragged in!
I must say, you are
one tough customer!
K-Krillin! Gohan!
Listen to me! Be careful!
Captain Ginyu has
taken over my body!
[KRILLIN screams]
No, that can't be Goku!
No... I can't bear to
see you this way, Daddy!
[GINYU laughing]
This can't
be happening!
Be brave, Gohan!
And listen very carefully.
You must defeat him right away!
Trust me, I know you can do it!
[KRILLIN] What?! Are
you out of your mind?!
[GINYU laughs]
[GINYU] I gotta agree
with baldy here!
I estimate my new body
and my strength at 180,000!
No one will stand a chance!
[GINYU laughs]
That's... what you
think, Captain Cocky...
'Cause I understand
that body you're in
a whole lot better
than you ever will!
And you'll never
get maximum strength
without knowing the secret
of uniting body and soul!
[GINYU chuckles]
Oh, bravo indeed.
That was quite the
impressive speech
But the first rule is
never kid a kidder...
Right, Jeice?
Yeah!
[GINYU growls]
[BOTH whimpering]
[GINYU growling]
[growling continues]
Hey, Jeice, give him a
readout of my strength now!
[thinking] 180,000...
and climbing!
[NARRATOR] Is
Captain Ginyu right?
Is his fighting power
really at 180,000?
And do Krillin, Gohan, and
Goku even stand a chance?
Find out in the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!
[GINYU laughs]