[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
Trunks was named the new
Junior World Champion!
As his prize, he was given
the chance fight Mr. Satan.
It only took one punch
from the new champ
to send the old one
flying into a world of pain!
[NARRATOR] And as the
Z Warriors were preparing
for the main event, the World
Martial Arts Championship,
they encountered two strangers.
Good afternoon. You wouldn't be
Goku by any chance, would you?
Well, your reputation as a great
fighter proceeds you!
I was hoping for a chance to
fight you during the tournament.
Uh...
Huh?
Gosh! Well, thank you!
[NARRATOR] These mysterious
newcomers are overflowing
with enormous power.
And they're eager to fight Goku.
Is this some sign of trouble
on the horizon?
Or are these just two more
contestants that will be
sent to the floor?
Today, on Dragon Ball Z!
Those two are
not to be trusted.
[chuckling]
Why?
[PICCOLO] I sense
something from them
and I'm not sure what it is.
They're very powerful,
but their power is... different.
[VIDEL] Huh?
Why can't we trust them?
They seem nice enough.
Uh... Well,
sometimes Piccolo is...
a little on the paranoid side.
I guess you're right.
He does seem a little
bit high strung.
[PICCOLO growls]
C'mon, guys,
let's get out of here...
I wanna find out who they got
fighting in the tournament.
Yeah, good idea!
[MR. SATAN groans]
[MR. SATAN] Darn that Trunks!
How does a
little kid like that...
pack so much power
into one punch?!
[TRUNKS] Goten,
you gotta check this out!
Yeah?
Okay.
Look at him...
That's a nice mask
and cape, huh?
[growling]
[GOTEN laughs]
[GOTEN] He looks like
he's wearing a dress.
[TRUNKS] Only people who've made
it through the elimination round
are allowed to be in
this area over here...
So, then... What d'ya see we
try and give it a shot?
[GOTEN] Huh...?
We can use that ugly mask
that he's wearing
to disguise ourselves.
Wait, I don't get it...
We very quietly sneak down
there, knock that moron out,
out, and take that
silly costume away from him.
Then the two of us can fight
in the championship.
Are you crazy, Trunks?!
We could get in so much trouble!
What's wrong?
You too chicken to go out
and fight with the grown-ups?
I'm not a chicken, Trunks...
Okay... So, let's do it!
No, wait!
Hello.
Yeah, what?
You want somethin'?
There's this guy over there
who bet he can beat you
at arm wrestling
for a thousand zeni.
Who?
don't know, but he's
really skinny and small.
That sounds like easy money!
[TRUNKS] C'mon, he's right
around the corner...
I'm telling you, you're
so much stronger than him,
it's embarrassing!
Where is he, kid?
I could... I could
really use that money.
Thousand zeni would
buy me that new cape
I've been eyeing all week!
[MASKED MAN yells]
Done!
What did you do?
We arm wrestled...
I won.
[MASKED MAN whimpers]
Pretty good job, huh, Goten?
Let's get this costume off.
[TRUNKS] Help me out, will ya?
[GOTEN] This isn't
going to fit you.
[TRUNKS] I know that.
[GOTEN] You're too small.
Everyone will notice.
[TRUNKS] I'm not
wearing it by myself.
You're wearing it with me!
What?!
With you?!
[MASKED MAN whimpers]
You don't think they'll
know that it's us?
Nah... don't worry about it.
Yeaaah!
[TRUNKS laughs]
Perfect! No one can tell.
We look great!
I'm not so sure...
Yeah. Oh!
Huh...?
They start drawing for
the pairings very soon.
[TRUNKS] Of course.
We're, er, I'm on my way.
Told ya!
Yeah!
I'm ready to fight--
Whoah, whu...
No, Goten, you're
walking the wrong way!
[GOTEN &amp; TRUNKS grunt]
[GOTEN] I can't see
where I'm going!
[TRUNKS] Then poke
out some eyeholes.
[GOTEN] That's a lot better!
Now we'll be invincible!
[KRILLIN] So, 16 fighters
in all, huh?
I sure hope at least one of them
is going to be worth fighting.
I don't want this
to get too boring...
Oh, you're here!
Hi!
Oooo... kay. Well, it
looks like everyone
who's supposed to
be here is here now.
Should we call in Mr. Satan?
[FRIAR #4] I'm sorry,
but Mr. Satan asked
if we would draw
without him.
He is a little incapacitated
at this time.
Okay, sure... I guess.
Okay, people!
This is how it works...
I will call your name,
and you will come up here
to draw a ball.
The balls you choose will
determine your opponent
in the match.
Okay...
I don't ask for much,
just please, please don't make
me fight any of my friends.
Krillin... destiny is not
something that you can control.
Hey, it never hurts
to try...
Especially not Goku!
[GOKU] Hmm...
Most of these guys look like
they're not going to
be much of a challenge...
But those two...
they really send chills
down my spine.
[BOTH snarl]
Uh... I wonder what's
making them so angry?
Maybe they didn't have
a good breakfast...
Huh?
[TRUNKS &amp; GOTEN grunting]
[GOKU] Who's that?
Euugh...
Is he actually going
to wear that?!
He looks so weird!
When I call your name,
please come up...
Uh... Mister Killa!
Yeah!
Turn of mine...
first off, 14.
Thanks... Number
14 goes to Killa.
Number 14 goes to Killa!
Lookie there!
They've already started pairing
people for the first round!
[CROWD cheers]
Next is... Kibito!
Kibito?
[KIBITO growls]
And... you're number 7.
Kibito is number 7.
[ANNOUNCER] And next up for the
drawing is, uh... Krillin.
Huh?
Guess it's my turn.
I hope my number's not
too late in the match.
What in the world
did I do to deserve this?!
[ANNOUNCER] It's time for
the Great Saiyaman.
Yes!
[GOHAN] Let's see here...
I'm number 8.
And that puts me up against...
Kibito.
Yikes!
He's a big guy,
but remember: a true warrior
fights with the mind.
Oh... right.
With the mind.
And now we have...
Miss Number 18?
[ANNOUNCER] Is, uh,
Number 18 your real name?
My father was pretty dull.
[ANNOUNCER gasps]
Now I'm number 9.
Shin's up next!
Ready.
[PICCOLO] Hm?!
[GOKU] Mm-hmm...
I'm number 3.
Shin and Kibito, huh?
I certainly hope that Piccolo
is wrong about those two.
[GOKU] He carries himself
with such grace...
like he hasn't got
a care in the world.
What's his secret?
We've got a lot of people out
there waiting for a good fight!
Hey, Goten...
What do you think
this guy's name is?
[GOTEN] I don't know.
Didn't you ask him?
Next in line we have
Spopovich...
You're up.
Hello?
Spopovich if you are here,
please step forward
for your number.
No one is answering.
This costume has gotta
belong to Spopo-whatever!
[GOTEN] Are you sure?
Yeah. Let's go.
[GOTEN] Alright.
[ANNOUNCER]
Is there a Spopovich here?
[TRUNKS] Coming!
I'm Spopo-hnnngh. Here I am!
I'm ready to draw now.
[TRUNKS grunts]
Give me a good one.
Excuse me, but aren't you
the one they call Mighty Mask?
Huh?
[SPOPOVICH]
Out of my way, you worm!
I am Spopovich!
Oh, yeah... hello.
[TRUNKS &amp; GOTEN grunt]
[TRUNKS] I can't believe this...
We totally made fools
out of ourselves!
[GOTEN] Don't blame me, Trunks.
This was all your idea!
Well, I must say...
You have changed a lot
since the last time I saw you...
Been drinking
that milk there, bud?
[ANNOUNCER] You're number 6.
[SPOPOVICH] Right!
Jeez...
Why didn't that big stupid oaf
just answer him
when he first called his name?
[ANNOUNCER] Next up
for the drawing is Jewl.
I am number 16.
[ANNOUNCER] Okay,
Jewl at number 16, then.
Oh yeah, Jewl's on
the board, man!
And I'm tellin' you that dude is
gonna take everyone else down!
[grunting]
Up yours! He don't stand a
chance against Mr. Satan!
Goku better get a good
spot on that board;
we need that grand prize!
It'll take a lot of luck to win
a competition as closely
matched as this one.
Father! Would you
watch your mouth?!
That is not the kind of support
I need from you today!
Do you understand that
if Goku doesn't win
we will be completely broke?!
We'll have no money at all!
And I refuse to raise
my son on the streets!
And if you don't
understand that,
then I'm really sorry for you.
Goku, your turn now!
Alright, here we go, Goku!
Which one will it be?
Ah!
It's number 11.
[GOKU laughs]
I wonder who
I'll end up fighting...
Well, I'll find out soon.
Next up is... Videl.
Yes!
Do you know
where my dad is?
Uh...
Mr. Satan is taking
a small rest right now.
Cool. Fifteen.
Hold it!
Did she just say that
Mr. Satan is her father?!
Yeah...
Keep your voice down, Dad.
Ah... I'm afraid I don't see the
resemblance between them...
She is quite the looker.
Really? I hadn't noticed...
You just throw on a
little bit of that charm
and I'm sure
she'll go out with you.
Shut up, Krillin!
I don't like her!
I never said that I liked her!
[KRILLIN laughs]
[KRILLIN] Right...
Pintar is number 2.
Huh?
That's my opponent?
And to think I was worried!
[PINTAR] You the one
they call "Krillin?"
Yep. That's me.
You may be a
scrawny little thing,
but I promise when we
get out in that ring,
you're gonna be
screaming for your mommy!
Yeah, you know...
That's just the sort of garbage
I expect to come out
of the mouth of
an incompetent fighter.
So, if you could just
go away now, thanks.
[KRILLIN sighs]
Ah! You brat!
You think that size
doesn't matter?!
Well, I'm gonna show you
otherwise, little man!
You should pick out a
coffin because you will die
out there today! You hear me?!
[ANNOUNCER] Vegeta, you're next!
[VEGETA] Hm?!
[VEGETA chuckles]
[GOKU gasps]
So, you're number 12?
Not the two of them!
Goku and Vegeta!
[FRIAR #5] Vegeta is number 12!
--[KRILLIN] Golly!
--[GOHAN gasps]
Vegeta and Goku
right off the bat!
That figures...
[VEGETA] A fight with Kakarot...
Perfect!
Just the opportunity
I've been waiting for
to prove my true
Saiyan abilities!
[TRUNKS] Cool! My dad's
going to fight your dad.
I wonder who'll win?
[GOTEN] I'm pretty sure
that my dad will.
Are you kidding?!
My dad is stronger and
faster than your dad any day!
But my brother told me
that my dad
is the strongest fighter
in the universe.
Mighty Mask... It's your turn
now. Why don't you come on down
here and make your draw?
Sorry... Coming!
Now, draw a good number.
Sure.
[TRUNKS] Lucky number 13!
[TRUNKS wails]
[ANNOUNCER] He doesn't look like
he's been working out much.
Majunior is up next!
[PICCOLO growls]
You're number 4.
[PICCOLO] I am the first
to fight Shin...
The first to know the
true extent of his power.
And seeing as Mr. Satan will be
taking some relaxation time
between bouts, I will
go ahead and draw for him.
And our Champion
is number 10!
Yes! Look, 18, you get to
fight Mr. Satan!
Great... I'm jumping for joy.
I wouldn't take it so lightly...
My dad's a dangerous man!
[ANNOUNCER] Last
but not least is Yamu!
[ANNOUNCER]
Safe to say that's 15!
There! We have a
full board of fighters!
[ANNOUNCER] In the first match
we have Krillin fighting Pintar!
Second match is
Shin versus Majunior!
The third match is
Videl and Spopovich!
Fourth match is Kibito
and the Great Saiyaman!
[NARRATOR] Match five is
Number 18 and Mr. Satan!
[ANNOUNCER] The sixth match
is Goku versus Vegeta!
The seventh match is
Mighty Mask against Killa!
And the eighth match
is Yamu versus Jewl.
[ANNOUNCER] The fighting will
commence immediately.
I will quickly show you all
to the waiting room.
I'm sure you know
the fighting rules.
You are the loser if you
give up, if I count to 10,
if you fall out of the
ring, or if you...
unfortunately...
kill your competitor...
Each match has a
time limit of thirty minutes,
and not a second more.
If there is not a victor decided
within the allotted time,
then that decision will be
left up to the judges.
Ah...
Thirty minutes
isn't long enough.
[PINTAR laughs]
Thirty seconds is too long
for you, tough guy!
Will you shut up?
[MR. SATAN] I'm in the
fifth match, huh?
Who am I fighting against?
[FRIAR #6] I'm not
really sure of her name,
but she is blonde
and quite attractive.
[MR. SATAN] Oh. Yeah!
Hey... Ladies and
gentlemen, are you ready?!
[CROWD cheers]
[BULMA] Yaaay! Ho-ho!
[cheering continues]
[PINTAR grunts]
This is so exciting!
I'm gonna totally cut loose!
Now...
Let the Martial Arts
Championship begin!
[CROWD cheers]
[NARRATOR]
With the lineup prepared
and the competitors ready
for their shot at glory,
the Martial Arts Championship
stage is set for battle
on the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!