[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
thousands flocked to
the small island where the
World Martial Arts Tournament
was scheduled to begin.
And the guest of honor
appeared as promised.
Goku is back! Permitted
to the living world
so he can fight
in the tournament.
[NARRATOR] It was a time for
hugs and laughter,
as friends were reunited
after years of silence.
[GOKU] And I've
missed you, ChiChi.
[NARRATOR] And a father met his
son for the very first time.
[GOTEN] I'm Goten.
[GOTEN] Daddy!
[GOTEN laughs]
Whoa, kiddo.
[NARRATOR] But like
many good things,
there were
strings attached.
[BABA] Listen up, Goku.
Remember that you only
have twenty four hours.
That's all I can do.
[GOKU] Mm-hmm.
Yeah, I know.
[BABA] I'll see you then...
[NARRATOR] Goku has just
one day to spend on Earth.
So as the tournament gets under
way, how will he make it count?
[SPIKED FIGHTER growls]
[SPIKED FIGHTER chuckles]
[SPIKED FIGHTER yells]
[grunting]
[CROWD gasps]
[FEMALE REPORTER] This way!
[CROWD cheering]
[SPIKED FIGHTER laughs]
[S FIGHTER grunts]
[S FIGHTER laughs]
Tell us where you're from, sir!
Satan City!
You know, I'm one of the top
students at Mr. Satan's gym.
[VIDEL] Where could Gohan be?
[SHARPNER] Oh, Videl...
[VIDEL] Hmm? Sharpner?
Hey, just wanted to
bring you some good luck.
No thanks.
[SHARPNER gasps]
[VIDEL] I bought an expensive
camera just for today.
I'm gonna take pictures of you.
[VIDEL] Oh. That's nice.
[SHARPNER] Hey! You're pretty.
I think your hair's shorter!
Aren't you observant.
[SHARPNER] Listen, Videl, I hear
there's this great juice shop
on the island... How 'bout we--
[VIDEL gasps]
Yeah, I can tell
you're excited...
I'll take you...
[whimpering]
Eh?
Videl?!
[TRUNKS] Goten... Your dead
father looks a lot like you.
You think?
But then he said
we were disqualified
because we both
touched the ceiling.
I don't think he looks
all that tough.
I bet you my father could
beat him no sweat.
But my brother says
Dad was the strongest
in the whole universe!
[GOKU] So what's with
the hair, Krillin?
I thought you were
naturally bald.
Oh, no. I just kept
it well-waxed.
I coulda sworn
I told you that...
Then why'd you stop doing it?
I mean you just don't look
like, y'know, Krillin anymore.
Guess love makes ya...
change some things...
Whoa, watch out everyone!
Android 18 is here!
Look, he noticed. How cute.
Someone please tell me
she's still not
terrorizing the planet!
Well, actually, uh, Goku,
18 and I have gotten married...
[GOKU gasps]
You mean you live in
the same house as her?!
[KRILLIN chuckles]
That's all part of it!
And we even had a kid together.
Whaa--?!
But... But how?!
Spare me...
How do androids have babies?!
As it so happens, she started
out as a human being!
Dr. Gero just remodeled
her a little bit.
[GOKU] Oh, okay.
Then, congratulations!
[KRILLIN] Thank you...
[VIDEL] You're lucky
I recognized you!
[GOHAN] Hmm? Hey, Videl!
Hey, Gohan...
So what's with the
turban and shades look?
Shh!
[GOHAN] I'm entering
as the Great Saiyaman.
[VIDEL] Well,
I won't tell a soul.
How about you? Have you
perfected your flying moves?
Now I'm twice as fast! Come on!
[VIDEL growls]
See? I won't hold anything back.
I am impressed.
[VIDEL] Huh...?
Videl! I've been looking
all over for you!
[GOHAN] I'll leave
you two alone.
[SHARPNER growls]
Slow down! What's your name?!
The Great Saiyaman.
Really? Is he a
friend of yours?!
Well, we do spend
a lot of time together
fighting all those
would-be criminals.
Right, Great Saiyaman?
That's right! I guess...
Who the heck is this guy?!
[VIDEL] You don't listen well.
No one knows his real identity.
Right, Great Saiyaman?
[GOHAN chuckles]
Right... Saiyaman?
Hmph. Spare me...
My... Did I hear jealousy
in your voice, Sharpner?
No! No way!
[LOUDSPEAKER VOICE] All
contestants for the
World Martial
Arts Tournament:
Please report to the
warm-up pavilion.
Preliminaries will begin
with or without you.
We better hurry over there!
Yeah! We better!
[VIDEL] See you later, Sharpner.
[SHARPNER growls]
Rragh!
I'll find you out!
Nobody steals MY girl!
[FEMALE REPORTER]
And I think it's clear
those stomach crunches
have paid off!
Good luck in the
tournament!
Here comes the last of them!
Good, 'cause I'm
tired of brown-nosing.
[FEMALE REPORTER]
That's not on tape, right?
Hi! Where are you guys from?
Hey, look... Don't those
two look familiar?
From where?'
I'm not quite sure-- Huh?
[laughing]
[FEMALE REPORTER] Hello there!
Can you tell us
where you're from?
Who? Me? Um...
I'm dead, just back for the day.
Oh?
Ohhh!
[FEMALE REPORTER laughs]
That's very funny!
No ma'am, it's not a joke.
[CAMERA MAN gasps]
[FEMALE REPORTER]
Alright... Uh...
Tell us where you got
that head accessory!
It's fabulous!
[GOKU] What? Oh, this?
It's not an accessory.
You see, when you die--
[screaming]
Well! I see that
Piccolo hasn't changed.
[KRILLIN chuckles]
Fool! What have you
done to our camera?!
That had an entire day
of brown-nosing!
I'm sorry!
I promise... This has
never happened before!
Hurry now...
The locker rooms
are right this way.
The preliminaries
are starting soon,
so you'll have to be quick.
Gee...
I can't believe they won't
let me fight with grown-ups...
[KRILLIN] Ah, you'll
get your chance, Trunks.
What I want to know is which one
of us gets to fight Mr. Satan!
It sure would be nice to finally
throw that goofball
off his high-horse!
[GIRLS squealing]
[TEEN FIGHTER] Next?
--[GIRLS murmuring]
--[TEEN FIGHTER laughs]
[TEEN FIGHTER]
One at a time, ladies!
You'll all get your turn...
Sir, is there anything
we can do for you?
You're looking a tad green.
Go away! I always
look like this.
[BOTH squeal]
[BOTH] Sorry! Our mistake!
[TEEN FIGHTER]
Now, girls, I have to go!
[SHARPNER] If I could only
get a good picture of him...
[TEEN FIGHTER]
No, girls! I'm leaving!
[SHARPNER gasps]
[screaming]
[GOKU &amp; GOTEN laughing]
[TRUNKS] We're ready!
[KRILLIN] Sorry for the wait!
[GOKU] No problem, guys!
Goten and I were just
having some play time.
So, let's go!
Darn! I'll unmask you
before this day is through,
Mister Saiyaman!
[GOTEN &amp; TRUNKS laughing]
[TRUNKS] Whoa...
[FIGHTER A grunts]
[FIGHTER B grunting]
[KRILLIN] Now this is a crowd.
[GOHAN] Are all these
people competing?!
[VEGETA] I say we
wipe them all out now.
[ANNOUNCER] Huh?! Is that...?
Yeah! It's you!
[GOKU &amp; KRILLIN] Huh?
--Oh, hi!
--Hey!
[ANNOUNCER] Wow. And
here I'd started to think
that I'd never see
you guys again.
I mean, how long's it been?
You haven't come out to compete
in the World Tournament in ages!
But hey, tell me something,
it wasn't Mr. Satan
who beat Cell, right?
C'mon, I know it was you!
[GOKU &amp; KRILLIN chuckle]
Listen, I can't tell you
how glad I am you're here.
Without you, these last few
tournaments have been nothing
but Capital-B Bo-ring!
Huh...?
Say, are all of
them with you too?
[GOKU] Yeah, you could say that.
Great! Even better!
So, you think you guys
can get through the fights
without blowing up
the ring this time?
We'll try.
And that's exactly
the kind of attitude
this tournament
has been lacking!
Ha-ha!
You haven't...
always had that gold ring
over your head, have you?
Well, actually I've been dead
ever since my fight with Cell,
but they let me come back this
one time for a day to compete.
Uh... Uhhh...
Well, that's weird! But, hey,
with all the things
I've seen you do, it'd be dumb
to start doubting you now
am I right, Goku, baby?
[thinking] Good.
At least one person knows
how great my dad is...
[ANNOUNCER] Well, I've got
business to take care of now
--but good luck to all of you!
--[GOTEN laughs]
--I'm expecting a super show!
--[KRILLIN laughs]
See you at ringside!
--[CROWD cheers]
--[ALL] Huh...?
Yeah!
Line up if you want an autograph
from the greatest fighter ever!
Cause I'm not charging
for the first fifty!
[MR. SATAN laughs]
--Hey, look!
--[CROWD] Go Satan!
--That's him!
--Go Satan! Go Satan!
--Yeah, the champ!
--Go Satan!
[CROWD chanting continues]
[CROWD screams &amp; cheers]
[KRILLIN] Hmph! People
will cheer for a goldfish
if you put a
champion belt on him!
[GOKU &amp; GOHAN laugh]
Here we go!
[GOTEN laughs]
[FROG ribbits]
[SHARPNER] Haah!
[SHARPNER groans]
Could've... sworn I had him...
Attention, please.
The prelims for the
World Martial Arts
Tournament now begin!
One hundred and ninety-four
people have entered
the adult tournament.
Unfortunately, there
are only sixteen spots.
And by the rules, the defending
champion, Mr. Satan,
is automatically qualified.
If you do the math,
that leaves fifteen spots!
So, here's the deal...
We're gonna to play a game
with Mister Saiyaman!
Got it?
No prob!
[KID B] Yeah!
Sixteen minus...
To ensure fairness,
we'll select the finalists
by way of punching strength.
The fifteen people with the
highest scores on the machine
will be given the fifteen spots.
Punch machine? Hmm...
Well, that's a new one!
[MONKS grunting]
Hey!
Here's the money shot!
[camera clicks]
[SHARPNER growls] Great!
Leave it to the big guy!
[PRELIM REF] Now, to test out
the new punching machine
and give us a score to go by,
we ask the defending world
champion to make the first hit!
Mr. Satan, would you
come on out please?!
[MR. SATAN chuckles]
[MR. SATAN] Heeeey!
Does anybody want this?!
[FIGHTERS cheer]
[MR. SATAN] Yeah!
[KRILLIN sighs]
I can't decide
what's worse:
Him or his fans...
Rrrrgghyyeeah!
[GOHAN] Videl!
Hey there, Saiyaman!
[VIDEL giggles]
[GOHAN chuckles]
'Scuse me!
[GOHAN] Hmm?
[KID A] Will you help me see?
[SHARPNER] Come on, kid!
[KID A laughs]
[camera clicks rapidly]
Perfect! I couldn't see
with the shutter moving,
but it's gonna be on film!
And as soon as I
develop these pics,
I can make him into
a laughing stock
and Videl will just
have to like me!
I'm sure you'll want
a picture of this!
Yeaaah. Oh yeah!
[MR. SATAN grunts and shouts]
[thinking] This has to stop.
[screaming]
Noo! No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
[screaming continues]
Piccolo?
A ring is a place for fighters,
not publicity seekers,
and I don't want you holding
back any of your strength
because you're afraid
of being discovered.
I want a good fight...
I see! Thank you!
That pose would've
made a great poster...
Oh well. I'll show
'em something!
[MR. SATAN yells]
Satan Punch! Raagh!
Incredible!
Mr. Satan has just scored one
hundred and thirty-seven points!
[CROWD gasps]
[MR. SATAN pants]
[VIDEL laughs]
Good luck to all you fighters!
I hope one of you at
least breaks a hundred
so we can have
a decent match!
All entries please
form a line in front
of the punching machine after
you've been assigned a number.
And anyone who is entering
the Junior Tournament
please gather over here by me.
Well, it looks like Mr. Satan's
gonna win again this year.
Okay, kids! Good luck!
Sure...
Where's Tien? Shouldn't
he be showing up?
I don't know, Goku.
I think he and Chiaotzu both
said they weren't coming back.
Next up, number six!
[FIGHTER D grunts]
Okay... Ninety-seven points!
[FIGHTER E grunts]
[PRELIM REF] Number sixteen...
Seventy-seven points!
[GIRL] Good luck, Videl.
We're rooting for you!
[VIDEL grunts]
[FIGHTER F growls]
[PRELIM REF] Ooh! Very nice!
One hundred and twelve points!
How absurd!
Next, please! Number eighteen!
Lookie there! That girl's
pretty cute for a fighter!
Yeah! But I bet
she scores a thirteen!
[KRILLIN] Now, 18,
remember to take it easy!
[ANDROID 18] I know.
Seven hundred
and seventy-four?!
[gasping]
Wha...?
It seems to be out of order...
Sorry about that...
That's what you call
taking it easy?!
It's not my fault these
guys are weaklings...
Okay, ma'am, would
you like to try again?
[gasping]
Two hundred and... three?
One hundred... and...
ninety-two points...
[gasping]
[PRELIM REF] One hundred...
and eighty-six points?
[gasping]
[PRELIM REF] Two hundred
and ten points?!
The pressure mechanism
seems to be broken...
See if you could fetch
the other machine?
[MONK E] Of course, sir...
[VEGETA] Now stand aside!
[PRELIM REF gasps]
[yelling]
Oh, wow...
[GOKU sighs]
So much for restraining...
[VIDEL whimpers]
[NARRATOR] It's safe to say
Vegeta and the other Z Fighters
have qualified for
the tournament,
in addition to destroying
a punching machine,
a dozen cameras,
and the speaking ability of a
couple hundred fighters.
Stay tuned for more
mayhem on Dragon Ball Z.