[NARRATOR] Previously,
on Dragon Ball Z...
Think again!
[NARRATOR] After a long
and grueling battle,
Vegeta was
finally defeated.
But, at Goku's request,
he was allowed to escape.
The Saiyan Prince
promised that one day,
he would return
for his revenge...
[NARRATOR] Though the day
had been won,
it wasn't without
its casualties.
As his fallen friends were
gathered from the battlefield,
Krillin thought of a way
to wish them back...
The Namekian
Dragon Balls!
Yeah, that's
a great idea!
And if Piccolo comes back,
then so will Kami!
And that means we'll have
all the Dragon Balls
on Earth back
here again, too!
Oh, it's that easy.
Well, I've got news for you!
I've done all the calculations,
and the numbers don't lie!
Your little cruise
to Planet Namek
is going to
take 4339 years!
Okay. But,
hypothetically speaking,
what would happen if we used,
say, a Saiyan spaceship?
[laughter]
[NARRATOR] So now, with a new
plan and restored hope,
Bulma, Krillin
and the others
prepare for the voyage
to the Planet Namek.
The quest begins today,
on Dragon Ball Z!
[INVESTIGATOR] Come on! Let's
get this thing outta here!
The sooner we do, the
sooner we can go home!
[GOKU screaming]
[KRILLIN whimpering]
[GOHAN whimpering]
Gohan, you've got to catch
up on your homework!
Keep studying!
[GOKU screaming]
[KRILLIN whimpering]
Why are you shaking
like that, Krillin?
Uh, because I'm cold!
[DOCTOR] Stop squirming! You're
only making it take longer!
All we're doing is
changing the bandages.
What is this
guy's problem anyway?
[GOKU screaming]
I just can't
take it anymore!
I've got to
do something!
I'm gonna find that
Saiyan spaceship!
Just leave that to Bulma.
You need your rest, Krillin!
Yeah, but...
Vegeta could return to attack
the Earth at any time.
You boys need to be
healthy and ready!
You just leave my little
Gohan out of this!
His fighting
days are over!
Next patient, please...
Don't worry about me!
I think I've recovered!
Me, too!
[CHICHI and ROSHI growling]
[KRILLIN] See ya!
[ROSHI] Oh, no you don't!
[CHICHI] Get back here!
[CHICHI] You've got to let
the doctor check you over!
[laughing]
Yeah... But the good news is
there's no serious injuries
and we'll be outta
here in no time!
Ohhh... Lucky you, but I
think I'm going to be stuck
in this contraption
for a good while...
But the worst
thing is,
this is going to slow
down my training...
Don't you worry, Goku.
I'll see if I can
grow some Senzu Beans
to help speed your
recovery up a bit.
Heh, heh. Hey Goku, you should
have seen Yajirobe fight...
Well, I didn't see you guys
doing any better...
It's hard to see
when you're hiding...
Yeah, he really showed
Vegeta. He was so brave...
I wasn't trying
to hurt you!
I was just playing around!
Ha... Nice one!
Heh, heh, heh. It was strategy!
I was distracting him!
[ALL laughing]
Well, I'm just so
glad that everyone here's
going to be
all right!
But I just hope that real soon
we can say the same thing
about all of
our friends...
Heh. We just gotta get the
Namekian Dragon Balls.
They'll be fine.
You'll see...
Hey, guys! Quick!
Turn on the TV!
Oh, it's Bulma! I thought
it was a hot new nurse!
Can't you be serious
for a change?
[ROSHI]
I was serious!
I am now standing in front
of the alien spacecraft
that was recovered
from the ruins
of East City
late last night!
For our safety,
it has been placed
inside this
isolation chamber!
The Saiyan
spaceship!
Right!
[GOKU] I can't see!
[MALE REPORTER]
Eyewitnesses at the scene
reported a second spacecraft
that mysteriously lifted off
and flew away during the
recovery operation...
What do we do now?
They've got that ship
under lock and key!
But, we need it!
And we'll
have it...
I'll fly it
out of there
using this remote control
that Vegeta left behind!
We'll be on
Namek in no time!
You know how that
thing works?
You've gotta be kidding me!
I can work anything!
I'll just take this and aim
it at the TV... No sweat!
[BULMA] It's just like something
my dad would make!
All I have to do is punch
in a few coordinates...
Here, these ought
to do nicely...
And then...
We watch...
[beeping]
[GOKU] Watch what?
I can't see anything!
What's going on?
[REPORTER screaming]
The spaceship
has exploded!
It powered up and went
into some sort of
self-destruct mode!
The building around
me is in shambles!
[BULMA] Wait!
It can't be! Nooo!
[screaming]
What happened? How could
it just blow up like that?
The remote was supposed to
bring it here, not destroy it!
Now what are we
supposed to do?!
We'll never make it to
Namek now! Never! Never!
Sure seems that way...
Good job with that
remote, Bulma...
[KRILLIN whimpering]
[BULMA]
C'mon, think, Bulma!
There's got to be
another way...
Just calm down...
I'm sure that we can come
up with something, Bulma.
[BULMA growling]
If we don't do
something soon,
we'll never get
our friends back!
Maybe we should ask Mr. Popo
and see what he thinks...
Mr. Popo?
Hello.
[BULMA screaming]
[KRILLIN laughing]
Hey, Mr. Popo!
[MR. POPO laughing]
[MAN screaming]
Did I hear that you are
looking for a spaceship?
[ALL gasping]
Yeah, why do you ask?
You don't have one, do you?
Maybe...
Uhh...
Who's that guy?
That's Mr. Popo...
Mr. Popo?
Yeah, that's right,
Mr. Popo.
He lives with Kami at The
Lookout, high above the Earth.
He and Kami have watched
over this planet for years.
Ooohhh!
So, where's this other
spaceship, then?
If it's a spaceship... I'm
not quite sure what it is...
But, I... I know that it's
not from this planet...
If it would help, I could
take one of you with me
and show you
where it is...
Hey, Bulma!
Uh, me?
Well, Bulma, you are the only
spaceship expert around here.
[BULMA whimpering]
Hey! What's wrong?
I... I can't do it...
That guy just totally
gives me the creeps.
[PATIENTS murmuring]
[PEDESTRIANS murmuring]
[KRILLIN] Bulma, please!
You're the only one who
can do this! Come on!
[BULMA] Oh, all right...
[ROSHI] Careful, Bulma!
Here! Let me help you...
[BULMA] Hmm?
[PATIENTS gasping]
[BULMA[ Aaahh! Get me off
this thing! Somebody help me!
I'm too young
and pretty to die!
[BULMA screaming]
Huh?
Uhh?
[CROWD murmuring]
Good luck, Bulma!
Take it easy, okay?
I mean, I've never ridden
on a flying carpet before.
Yes, alright...
[BULMA] I just hope all
this is worth it...
They... They
just... vanished!
I sure hope Popo's right...
We really need a spaceship!
We're here.
Huh? We are?
[BULMA] Are you sure
this is the place?
I mean, there's
nothing here!
[MR. POPO] Don't be so
certain... You'll see.
What's wrong?
I'm freezing!
Just where are we?
Yunzabit Heights.
Yunzabit? But how? That's on
the other side of the world!
[MR. POPO]
Follow me... This way...
Hey! Wait up!
So, where exactly is
this spaceship, anyway?
Boy, you don't
talk much, do you?
[BULMA] Hrrm...
[BULMA] Ah.
I'm beginning to
think you're lost!
We walked all
the way down here
and now there's nowhere
left for us to go!
It's a dead end!
Wait! Stop!
What now?
I'm no rabbit!
How am I supposed...
[MR. POPO]
Climb, I guess...
There it is!
[BULMA gasps]
What do you think?
It's a ship,
alright...
What is this? It's not
metal... How weird...
All right!
I've had it!
What exactly do you
know about this thing?
Well, I only know what
Kami told me about it
from the stories of when
he was very young...
It's hard
to remember...
The last time he mentioned
it was over 100 years ago,
but I'll do my best
to recall what I can...
One day, not too
long after lunch,
Kami began telling me about
his mysterious past...
You see, Mr. Popo,
when I was a child,
I used to live in a place
called Yunzabit Heights.
It was very
cold and lonely...
Why would you
live there?
I'm not sure... I was
in a strange accident
and somehow
lost my memory...
How awful...
Then what happened next?
He told me that
he remained here,
waiting for his
parents to return...
Staring out into
the distant skies...
[KAMI] I was certain
that someone
would come
looking for me...
I thought that if I wandered
too far from where I awoke,
no one would be
able to find me.
So there I stayed,
patiently awaiting the
arrival of my salvation...
But my light of hope
grew more and more dim
as the days
passed me by...
Days led into weeks,
weeks led into months,
and months
led to years...
Finally, after more years
than I care to remember,
I left Yunzabit
Heights behind me...
Sometimes I would
return there,
but I never found any
sign of my people...
Sad, but what does your story
have to do with this ship?
Because during his time
here, he found this ship.
One day, I discovered
something very strange...
It was round
and had four legs.
It looked like some kind
of giant alien insect...
As I examined the
strange sphere...
a word seemed to
appear in my head...
I found that if I spoke this
word aloud, a door would open.
Pic-co-lo...
What in
the world?
What are you
waiting for? Go.
So how do we
get up there?
You just say the
word again... Piccolo!
[BULMA] Wow...
Look at this place!
If this is some
sort of spaceship,
then how did
it get here?
I got it!
Kami was a Namekian!
King Kai told us
that a long time ago,
Planet Namek was in great
danger of being destroyed...
Yes, I believe I've heard
that story before as well!
They thought their
planet was done for,
so they started
evacuating everyone
on Namek to
other worlds!
If this ship really is
from the Planet Namek...
It kinda makes everything
fall into place!
When their planet
was in danger,
Kami's parents must have
put him on board and
sent him here to
save his life...
I'm sure they intended
to join him here later
but for some reason,
something happened
and they never made it...
The poor little fella...
Popo! If we can just get
this old thing working,
then maybe we can...
Hey, wait a minute!
If the door opened,
it is working!
But I don't know how
these controls work...
It's alien technology,
so I don't even know
where to start...
Well, uh,
when in doubt...
Just start pressing
some buttons...
[BULMA growling]
It's no use...
It... It won't work!
It must be
missing something...
Spaceship Expert...
Yeah, whatever!
I don't have the faintest
idea what I'm doing!
But I've got to keep trying.
Everyone's counting on me!
Man, I really hope they've
found that spaceship...
[ROSHI] If it's
a spaceship...
[ROSHI sighs]
[GOKU thinking] Please,
Bulma... Hurry!
[BULMA] Move,
you hunk of junk!
What will I
say to everyone?
Hmm?!
What is it?
It's what we say
that makes it work!
I don't think
I understand...
It must be run by
voice command,
just like before when you
opened the entry hatch.
But, that would mean all of
the commands are in Namekian!
[BULMA screaming furiously]
That's just great! Unless you
speak Namekian, we're stuck...
Wait a minute.
I'm pretty sure I remember
hearing some Namekian
back at the World
Martial Arts Tournament.
Did you really think
you could fool me
with that fragile
disguise?
Your skills
have improved!
But I don't remember
it enough to speak it...
Well, I don't speak
the entire language,
but I think I know
a word or two...
You do?
Sometimes Kami would
mix in strange words
when he would
speak to me.
I learned their meanings
by what context
he would
say them in.
Well, let's
try some of them!
If we can just figure out
one or two simple commands,
we'll be out of this
place in no time!
Can you think of any words that
might make this thing move?
[MR. POPO]
I can say fly.
Let's try it...
See if you can tell it
to fly us to Jupiter.
Topurukuppa Jupe!
[BULMA] Something's happening!
[MR. POPO] What's that sound?
[COMPUTER]
Topurukuppa Jupe.
[whimpering]
[whimpering continues]
Just hang on! We don't
have any safety belts!
[beeps]
[COMPUTER]
Sefte Bette.
Just what in the
world is that?
A toilet! You asked
for one in Namekian!
That's what sefte
bette means!
I didn't say that! I just
need a chair to buckle into!
[COMPUTER]
Juznee Achur.
Juznee Achur
means bedtime!
[BOTH] Huh?
We're here! We're already
at Jupiter? All right!
It works! We did it!
We did it!
Now we can fly this
thing to Namek!
Oh, Kami... Soon you'll
be with us again!
[NARRATOR] Now that
Bulma and Mr. Popo
have discovered Kami's
long-lost spaceship,
a universe of possibility
has opened up!
The search for Planet
Namek continues,
next time on
Dragon Ball Z!