[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragonball Z,
Ginyu Force members
Burtur and Jeice
launched a tag-team
assault on Goku!
Together, they fired they fired
the Purple Spiral Flash attack.
But, to their surprise,
it was a move easily defended
by our newly arrived hero!
Ah! What's happening?!
[growling]
[NARRATOR] As the smoke cleared,
Vegeta, Gohan, and Krillin
watched in awe as Jeice prepared
to fire a second attack!
Crusher...
Ball!
[NARRATOR] But this too was
deflected with little effort.
Goku looks unstoppable, which is
bad news for Burtur and Jeice!
Do two of the strongest warriors
of Frieza's fighting force
even stand a chance against
the Saiyan's new power?
Find out... today!
Darn it!
Where did he go?!
[BURTUR grunting angrily]
Burtur! Behind!
[BURTUR screams
Hey.
How... how the heck
did you do that?!
I mean...
How did you get behind me?!
No one's that fast!
[GOKU] Well, apparently I am.
[BURTUR growling]
[thinking] Man, I've
never seen anyone
get to Burtur like this before!
And he deflected my Fire Crusher
Ball like it was a beach ball!
This isn't good!
I don't like it one bit!
[BURTUR growls]
Who are you?!
My name is Goku
and I'm a Saiyan...
from Earth.
[BURTUR growling]
Liar!
I've defeated hundreds of
Saiyans and none of them
were faster than me!
[GOKU]
It must be my diet.
I eat really wholesome foods.
Your diet?
Your diet, huh?!
Well, you're about to make
my fist part of your diet!
Oh, I see. Playing
it cool, are you?
Well, you'll die even faster!
[BURTUR yellling,
GOKU grunting]
Why don't you stay still
and fight me like a man?!
[BURTUR and GOKU grunting]
Can... you see?
No way!
[VEGETA softly growls]
Hyaah!
That does it!
I've had enough!
No one makes a fool
of the Ginyu Force!
[JEICE yells]
[ALL grunting]
[BURTUR]
Outta my way!
[grunting continues]
[BURTUR] He can't dodge
us forever, Jeice!
He's gotta screw
up sometime!
[JEICE] Right!
[grunting continues]
[blows landing]
[JEICE] Gwaahh...
Idiot!
It's your fault,
ya dope!
[BOTH growling]
[JEICE] Wait, Burtur!
He's doing this to us, mate!
Don't you get it?!
He is...?
[JEICE] Darn right, he is!
[GOKU]
Hey, guys! Yo!
[GOKU] Well, do you want
to dance, or fight?!
[BOTH growling]
[BOTH yelling]
[GOKU]
Woah!
[BURTUR gasps]
[GOKU]
Hyaah!
[BURTUR screams]
[JEICE yelling]
[GOKU grunts]
[BURTUR yelling]
[blow landing]
[BURTUR groaning]
[BOTH gasping]
[groaning continues]
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU] You've been
deceiving yourselves!
This fight is fruitless!
[JEICE whimpering]
[GOKU] Listen!
It's not too late for
you to leave this planet!
Your choice. But if I were you,
I'd get out of here!
[VEGETA] Don't be a fool,
Kakarot!
He's destroyed more
men than you can count!
[GOKU] Don't you
remember, Vegeta?
We let you go on Earth!
Don't you think they
deserve the same chance?
[VEGETA growls]
Man o' man!
Burtur!
This is totally insane!
I don't know who this guy is,
or where he came from,
but he's good!
Geez, I've never
seen anything like it!
We never even
touched him!
Now, that's
one bad dude!
[JEICE growls]
I'm bad! But man,
I ain't that bad!
Sometimes you've got
to know when to go, go, go!
[GOHAN]
Hey, he's running away!
Gosh, he's some
friend, isn't he?
These guys might walk
funny for a while,
but they'll recover just fine!
[RECOOME moaning]
[BURTUR groaning]
[GOKU] Strong fighters,
but with weak characters!
[KRILLIN] Uhhh... Hey, uh,
you are Goku, aren't you...?
What? Of course
I am, Krillin!
Don't be silly!
[VEGETA growling]
[GOKU] Hm?!
[VEGETA yells,
BURTUR screams]
Hey, stop!
[GOKU] Vegeta, that's enough!
What are you doing?!
[VEGETA]
Rrrgh!
[GOHAN gasps, whimpers]
What's your deal?!
You know how to receive
mercy but you can't give it!
Too bad! I was hoping
you might have changed!
They don't deserve
any favors!
They're scum, Kakarot!
Believe me!
Would they have taken mercy
on your son and your friend?!
If you'd arrived
ten minutes later,
they'd be gone right now!
[KRILLIN whimpers]
You're too soft
to be a Saiyan!
That freak you let go
could cost you your life!
No way, not him!
[VEGETA] He doesn't have to be
stronger than you to beat you!
He could take your kid
hostage and make you walk
right into their
hands like a lamb!
These people are ruthless
savages, Kakarot!
They're warriors!
And they'll do whatever
it takes to win the game!
And here you are,
Mr. Nice Guy!
They're going to chew you up and
spit you out with that attitude!
[GOKU] We'll see...
I don't think having
a little compassion
is a disadvantage.
You poor fool.
A fight with Frieza
is a fight to the end!
And it will be your end!
Your nothing compared
to Frieza, Kakarot!
[KRILLIN] Uh, excuse me,
I hate to interrupt,
but, who's going
to beat who here?
You saw how Goku handled
those guys earlier!
[GOHAN chuckles]
He was in a league
of his own!
They couldn't even touch him!
And this guy's
supposed to beat him?!
Not likely!
[GOHAN] Yeah!
Kakarot's strong, but
he's not strong enough!
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN groan]
[VEGETA] And besides!
Frieza's been after
the Dragon Balls!
And if I know him, he's probably
already made his wish by now!
Which means you won't be dealing
with an all-powerful maniac!
You'll be dealing
with an immortal!
[KRILLIN] Hm!
[GOHAN] Huh?
No, I don't think
that Frieza guy
has used the
Dragon Balls yet.
[VEGETA] Huh?
Why not?! Explain!
Well, on Earth, when
you summon call the Dragon,
all kinds of crazy
stuff starts happening!
For one thing, the
entire sky turns pitch black!
[KRILLIN] Plus, there's
always a lot of lightning.
Radical lightning!
And high winds!
Nope, the sky's
been real calm.
[VEGETA] What! Then Frieza
hasn't summoned the Dragon yet!
But why not?!
He's bound to have had
them all for a while now!
Hey, I think I know why!
I'll bet Frieza doesn't
know the password, huh?
These balls aren't
like the ones on Earth.
Here you need to
know a password!
A password?!
Then there's still hope!
[GOKU] Hey, that means there's
still a chance to wish Piccolo
and the others back
to this dimension!
Alright!
[GOKU]
Whatd'ya say, Gohan?!
[GOHAN chuckles]
[GOKU] You guys
should be proud!
This means all of your hard
work might still pay off!
[GOHAN]
Woo-hooo!
[KRILLIN]
Everything's gonna be okay!
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN laughing]
[GOKU laughs]
[KRILLIN]
Right, Goku?
[GOKU] Yup!
Thanks to you guys,
we still have a chance!
[VEGETA thinking]
A very slim chance!
[GINYU] Do they think
they can just take
the rest of the day off?!
[JEICE] Uh, Captain,
I really need to talk
to you about something. It's--
[GINYU] What lovely balls.
[JEICE] I understand. Burtur,
Recoom are--
[GINYU] I thought you
knew better than to
interrupt me when I'm
talking, Jeice, hmmm?
[GINYU laughs]
When Frieza figures out
how to use these things,
and you know he will,
we'll be completely unstoppable!
Imagine working for the most
powerful man in the universe!
How's that for a 401k?!
[GINYU] Okay,
this is ridiculous!
Where are Burtur
and Recoome?!
[JEICE] Well... they
won't be coming back, sir...
[GINYU] Jeice, are you
saying that two members
of the most illustrious
fighting squad in the universe
have been defeated
by just one man?!
[JEICE] Yes, Sir!
That's exactly what I'm saying!
[GINYU]
And where were you?!
Well, I was right there
with them, and then I took off!
[GINYU] You idiot!
I know what's up!
You ran away, didn't you?!
How dare you show your
orange, little face back here!
You're such a disgrace!
Have you learned anything
after all this time?!
But this guy was
unbelievably strong!
I'm sorry, Captain.
[GINYU growls]
[thinking] Guldo, Recoome,
and Burtur... All gone!
Men, good news!
Your chances of making the
squad have just increased!
There are now four
openings on the team!
[RECRUITS cheer]
[JEICE]
But, Captain Ginyu!
I'm still here!
We only need three!
[GINYU]
Silence!
You no longer have a
place on the Ginyu Force!
[JEICE] Hmm?!
[GINYU]
That is, unless...
[GINYU laughs]
Unless you can strike a
pose that shows these guys
what being a Ginyu is about!
I'll try my best, sir!
[GINYU] Alright, men!
Look sharp!
This is your first mission!
I want you to dig a hole and
bury those Dragon Balls!
[RECRUITS] Yes, Sir!
[RECRUITS grunting]
Dig with style, mates!
You're not convicts!
You're the Ginyus!
[RECRUITS grunting
and murmuring]
[JEICE] The one on
the left has pinache.
And he's a heck of a lot
better looking than Burtur.
[RECRUITS grunting]
[JEICE chuckles]
[JEICE] Not too shabby, Captain!
This lot knows how to dig!
Yes. Yes, they do.
Now, men, I'll be
leaving you for a while
to take care of some business.
Line up!
[RECRUITS panting]
[GINYU] I want you to sit
this one out and watch
but pay close attention!
[GINYU]
We are...
the Ginyu...
--Wooah!
--Force!
It's just not the same
without the other guys! Ah...
We're like two puppies
that have been seperated
from their litter!
That guy is gonna
pay dearly for this!
Ya hear me?!
[JEICE whimpers]
[JEICE] I hear you, Cap'n!
[BULMA] My Dad couldn't
have been that far off
with Goku's arrival time.
He should've
been here by now.
Maybe Goku already
came and won the day
and they all went back
happily to Earth together
and forgot about me...
No, Goku wouldn't
forget about me!
He just couldn't!
Heck, I've known him since
he was just a little guy!
[BULMA sighs]
Those were the days...
What's the use?! Ugh!
[BULMA] Oh, Goku...
[BULMA sighs]
You won't forget me. I know.
[GOHAN]
What do we do now, Dad?!
[KRILLIN] Yeah, where
do we go from here?
[GOKU] Hey, Vegeta!
You know Frieza and the
others alot better than us.
How would you suggest we
approach the situation?
Oh, it's quite simple.
All you have to do
is finish Frieza.
You don't think
I can do it, do ya?
I know! King Kai warned
me about Frieza as well
and told me to stay
away from him at all costs!
[VEGETA] Good advice.
But, heck, if we could
get to the Dragon Balls
and wish our friends
from Earth back,
we might have a chance!
[VEGETA]
You friends from Earth...
If you think they're going to
tip the scales in your favor,
you're out of your mind!
But I have an idea.
Let me wish for immortality
and we'll win for sure!
You can forget that!
There's no way we're going
to create an immortal Vegeta
to go around terrorizing
the universe!
[VEGETA] Heh!
Huh?!
[KRILLIN]
Two big powers coming!
Oh, great! They're heading
right for us, aren't they?
You'd better believe it.
Jeice, the one your Dad let go,
is coming back with
Captain Ginyu!
[VEGETA] Oh, now
you've done it, Kakarot!
You're not having
any regrets, are you?
Hey, shut up!
We're here for you, Goku!
You just tell us what
to do, and we'll do it!
Wait a second! If those
guys are coming here
and I can't sense Frieza over
there, where their ship is!
Kakarot, quick,
help me locate Frieza!
[GOKU] Right!
No problem!
[KRILLIN] I don't get it.
What's the big deal?
[VEGETA] The big deal is if
the Dragon Balls are
at their spaceship
and Frieza isn't there
for some reason...
[KRILLIN] then Captain Ginyu
and the orange guy are leaving
the Dragon Balls
unguarded to come here!
[VEGETA] Precisely!
[GOKU] There's a huge
power in that direction,
but it's pretty far off!
That's him.
It's unmistakable now.
[GOHAN] Uh, oh.
That's Guru's place!
This is not good.
Guru's old, he can't
defend himself!
And that's not all.
That's right!
Guru created the Dragon Balls!
So, if Frieza destroys him,
then that means the Dragon Balls
are history as well!
Say what?!
You mean if some
old Namek dies,
the Dragon Balls will vanish?!
[GOKU]
All things must pass.
Not even the Dragon
Balls last forever!
[KRILLIN] Hey wait, Frieza
wouldn't hurt Guru if he knew!
But he doesn't know.
Poor Guru! He wouldn't
tell Frieza either!
He'd rather die than
let the Dragon Balls
be used for any kind of evil!
I wish there was some
way for us to help out...
[GURU] Yes, I see
you have been brave
and giving in your struggle.
I have a gift for you that might
help you in your endeavors.
He's so good he reminds you of
a Grandfather or something,
how could anyone want to
hurt such a great guy?!
[VEGETA] What world
do you live in?!
[GOHAN &amp; KRILLIN] Huh?!
[GOKU] Cool it, guys!
We've got company!
[VEGETA gasps]
Huh?!
Dad!
Meet the boss, Matey!
His name is Cap'n Ginyu
and he'd like to have
a few words with you
concerning our
encounter earlier!
[KRILLIN] Hey, uh, Goku,
I think now would be a good
time for a plan!
Krillin, you and Gohan
are going to take off!
Get the Dragon Radar
and see if you can get your
hands on the Dragon Balls!
Alright. Let's see...
housand!
[GINYU] The Scouter
says... five
[JEICE] That's impossible!
Somehow he can hide his true
level from the scouter!
Shut up, Jeice!
Huh?
evel,
Of course he's hiding
his true power
that's ridiculously obvious!
You're looking at a
rare fighter there!
A guy like this one can
quadruple his fighting power
in an instant!
I estimate when
he really gets going
housand or maybe more!
he'll have a power level of
sixty
What?! Sixty thousand!
But he said he was a Saiyan!
No bloody Saiyan that we've
ever met is that strong!
[GINYU] Well, this one is!
Think about it!
He might be a mutant like us!
I mean, he's
definitely different!
He's the first Saiyan
I've seen without a tail!
What a magnificent
opportunity to showcase
my fabulous strength. Heh!
A chance to reveal
the full extent
of my grandeur in battle.
You gotta love it.
Alright, guys.
It's time for you to leave.
You can do it!
Get the radar, and then
go get the Dragon Balls!
But what about you, Dad?
You know there's no way we can
leave you here all by yourself!
[GOKU]
I'll be fine, Gohan!
Just concentrate on
doing your part!
[KRILLIN] Goku, you're enjoying
this in some strange way,
aren't you?!
[GOKU] Kinda.
Let's get out of here and let
your Dad do his thing, Gohan.
Don't forget we've got
own mission to finish!
Piccolo and the others...
Now you're talking,
you guys!
You have a part
in the plan, too!
If that's okay with you.
I was hoping that
we could join forces
and work together
against those guys.
Well, how does that sound
to you, Vegeta, will you do it?
Yeah, sure. Why not?
You're gonna trust him?!
[GOKU] Guys!
There's no time!
Now, let's go!
We're on it.
You got it, Goku!
[JEICE] Hey!
There they go!
Let 'em go! Big deal.
I don't know why your dad
has to trust that guy!
I hear ya!
It's too risky!
[GURU coughs]
[DENDE]
Guru, are you okay?
Well, I guess
it's now or never!
And I'm right behind you.
[VEGETA chuckles]
[VEGETA yells]
Have fun, Kakarot!
[VEGETA laughs]
Man, you dirty dog!
Prepare to die!
[GINYU laughs]
[NARRATOR] With Vegeta leaving
our hero to fend for himself,
will Goku have the power to
defeat the fierce Captain Ginyu?
Find out on the next
Dragon Ball Z!