[NARRATOR] On the last
episode of Dragon Ball Z,
Gotenks, the super being
formed by the fusion
of Goten and Trunks,
had achieved the
level of Super Saiyan 3
and was giving Majin Buu
the fight of his life!
[SUPER BUU groans]
[NARRATOR] The seemingly
invincible Buu
had finally met his match!
But when the fusion
began to wear off,
and Gotenks had to power down,
the situation went
from bad to worse!
[GOTENKS yells]
Let's not be too hasty!
[NARRATOR] Until finally,
to their dismay,
the duo came unraveled!
[BOTH]
Hey wait! You're there!
The fusion must be over!
[NARRATOR] But when it
seemed that all was lost,
Gohan completed
his power raising
under the dubious
guidance of the Elder Kai,
and unleashed a sample
of his newfound ability!
[GOHAN bellows]
[OLD KAI hollers]
[SUPREME KAI yells]
[KIBITO grunts]
This is the last time
I'll get to see you
until you make your
journey over to this world.
You ready? Show him
what a Saiyan's made of!
Yeah!
[NARRATOR]
And just as his father had
so many times before,
Gohan arrived on Earth
in the knick of time.
After supplying him with a new
uniform identical to Goku's,
Kibito left
the new savior alone
to contemplate his mission.
[NARRATOR]
Look out, Majin Buu!
Here he comes!
[GOHAN]
This is it.
Great! We're done for!
Those imbiciles!
They had the chance
but they blew it!
[TRUNKS]
I don't know what to do!
Without the fusion,
we're cooked!
[GOTEN] Y-You mean
there's a chance
that we're gonna... die?
It's more than just a chance!
You and me are about to
bite the big one, Goten!
Ahh, that's bad!
Hey! Why don't we run away?
But do you think we can?
I guess not. It's over!
This isn't any fun! Shoot!
We're way too young to die!
Yeah! We're just little kids!
[SUPER BUU chuckles]
[BOTH whimper]
[SUPER BUU] It's time,
little trouble-makers!
[TRUNKS]
Piccolo!
You two can't have all
the fun. Now it's my turn.
I'll do the best that I can.
If it doesn't work,
at least we'll die together.
[TRUNKS] What do you mean
"the best that you can"?
We were both Super Saiyan 3's,
plus we were fused together,
and we still couldn't beat him!
[GOTEN] Yeah! It might
not matter to you
because you're old!
But we're just little kids!
We don't want to die!
[TRUNKS]
Unh-uh!
Do you have any ideas, Trunks?
Yeah...
I think it might work!
What is it, Trunks?
Come on! Tell me!
Well, we apologize.
[PICCOLO]
Uuh!
Yeah! We just tell him
that we're sorry. Why not?
And we'll give him tons of
candy and chocolate and stuff
as a peace offering!
Cool, huh?
Mm! It's a great idea!
Especially the part
about the candy!
Plus! It's a heck of a lot
better than Piccolo's idea!
What in the world are you--?
All right, Goten!
Go and get us some candy, pal!
[GOTEN]
Right!
[TRUNKS]
Hurry back!
Okay!
[TRUNKS]
What are you doing?
Get the candy first!
Yeah! But there aren't
any stores around here.
Hmm.
You're right. Darn it!
I guess we better figure out
some other way to get it, huh?
[GOTEN] Well, do you
think Piccolo would
materialize some for us?
[TRUNKS] I don't know!
It's worth a try!
[grunts] No!
It's not worth a try!
[yawns]
What?
[GOTEN] Hey! What's the
matter with Majin Buu?
[TRUNKS]
I don't know.
Huh? Do you hear that?
[BOTH]
Uh!
[PICCOLO]
Listen!
[snoring]
Wow! He is! Isn't he... Goten?
I don't know.
He might be. Let's go see!
[thinking]
Is he really asleep?
Or is he just toying with us?
Aah!
--[GOTEN] Come on!
--[PICCOLO] Wait!
We'll be right back, Piccolo!
Are you nuts? What in the world
do you think you're doing?
[GOTEN] We're seeing
if he's really asleep!
[TRUNKS]
Sshh! Stupid!
[SUPER BUU snoring]
[TRUNKS]
Come on!
[GOTEN]
I'm coming!
[snoring]
[BOTH scream]
[TRUNKS]
Is he awake?
[GOTEN] I don't know!
My eyes are closed!
[TRUNKS]
Let's look.
[GOTEN]
Okay...
[SUPER BUU snoring lightly]
He's sound asleep!
How can he sleep
sitting up like that?
You dummy! He's probably
faking it to trick us.
Oh. Right. Got it!
He's pretty sneaky.
But I think I can
surprise him.
If he's faking, we'll know.
Yeah! I'll just
squeeze his horn.
[TRUNKS] That's not
a horn. It's soft.
[GOTEN] Whatever it is
I'll just give it a little--
Aah! No!
[GOTEN]
Trunks, give me a boost!
[PICCOLO] No! No!
No boost! No boost!
Are you two insane?
[TRUNKS, GOTEN]
Huh?
We finally get a chance
to buy a little extra time
and you two
want to wake him up?
[PICCOLO] You two
are making me crazy!
Now listen up!
Let's use this time to
prepare for the next fusion!
Don't you get it?
It's our only chance!
Now come on!
--Yes, sir.
--Okay.
[PICCOLO] Uhh! I'm getting
too old for this!
Huh?
[BOTH gasp]
[grunts]
[PICCOLO] What is it?
I-It's mind-boggling!
It's a person!
[GOTEN]
Yeah! Someone's coming!
[SUPER BUU]
Mmm...
[PICCOLO]
But who is it?
I've never experienced
a power like this.
It's outrageously strong!
It could be a new enemy!
Boys! Stay close!
[growls]
[PICCOLO] What?! I don't
believe it! It's Goku!
No! It's my brother,
you guys! Gohan!
Are you positive?
Uh! Gohan?
[growls]
Hey, guys! What's happening?
Hey there, Gohan.
Hi, Gohan! What's up?
We all thought
that you were dead!
I would've been if it wasn't
for the help of Supreme Kai.
But that's all in the past.
I think it's time to
focus on the here and now.
[growls]
[thinking] I've known you
since you were a boy, Gohan,
but I hardly recognize you!
Your face,
it's changed a little
and your power has
increased dramatically.
But that's not it,
it's your attitude
that's so different.
You're so... confident.
Where are the others?
They're all dead!
He killed them!
Huh? What about Dende,
is he all right?
Him too! Mom, Videl,
everyone Gohan!
[grunts]
[thinking] Videl!
Mother! They're gone!
And without Dende, we can't
wish anyone else back!
And they were good!
I turned them all
into chocolate
and gobbled them up!
[growls]
[thinking] Wait! It's faint
but I can still
sense something!
Just barely!
[SUPER BUU growls lightly]
[chuckles]
So, hot shot. You want
to fight Majin Buu?
Fight you?
No, I want to kill you.
All right! Now we get to see
Gohan's new powers in action!
He is an extraordinary man!
Who would have
thought that a mortal
could have
progressed so rapidly?
It is amazing! And bringing
him here was a brilliant move!
Thank you!
I guess my recruiting instincts
were correct, were they not?
Yes! Finding a man who
could remove the Z Sword
was remarkable in itself!
But when Gohan
shattered the sword
and released the elder Kai,
I realized then that we were
witnessing a living legend!
Yes, well,
I guess if you can't
get the job done yourself,
finding someone who can
is the next best thing.
But I always thought a Kai
should have been
the one to set me free.
[SUPREME KAI]
Yes, venerable elder.
I understand your sentiments,
but I think it
all worked out well.
After all, in my
humble opinion,
the planet Earth should
be protected by Earthlings,
don't you think?
I agree.
The Earth's heroes just
can't drop in from the heavens.
Not now. Mankind has
to learn to rely on itself.
No dead guy from
the history books
is going to save them either.
Oh! Hey, come to
think of it,
I guess I fall into
that category myself now!
[chuckles]
Indeed so!
Heroes should be home grown.
[OLD KAI] Stop twisting up the
subject, kindergarten Kai!
Don't you think I know that?
I'm an ancient man!
I don't need a lecture
from you two whippersnappers!
Hm!
[BOTH]
Uh... uh... uh...
Youths! Know-it-alls!
No proper respect!
[SUPREME KAI] But sir!
That's not true!
Do your best, son!
The Earth's future is
resting on your shoulders now.
[laughing]
I recognize you now!
You're one of the
ones I've beaten before.
So you want some more?
Okay. But this is
going to be the last time.
Humph!
[grunts]
[thinking] Gohan.
What are you doing?
We should be trying to buy
time until the next fusion.
Not fighting him head to head!
This is bad! We can't
just stand here, Trunks!
We have to help him!
But how? It's too soon
to do the fusion again!
It's worth a try! I can't
watch Gohan get killed!
He's my brother! I love him!
Goten!
Hey. Let's try
the fusion anyway.
[GOTEN]
Yeah! Thanks, Trunks!
[BOTH]
Fu--!
[SUPER BUU grunting]
[grunting]
[bellows]
[GOHAN yells]
[groans]
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
[SUPER BUU groans]
[grunting]
You're making a mistake!
I'll make you dead!
[yells]
[SUPER BUU growls]
You! Stupid boy!
Cool! Huh, Trunks?
Yeah! Very!
[grunting]
[yells]
[groaning]
[yelling, groaning]
[TRUNKS]
Yes! All right, Gohan!
[chuckles]
[growls]
[GOHAN]
What's wrong?
I thought
you said something
about making me dead?
[yells]
Buu make you dead!
What Buu say, Buu do!
Now you die!
[screams]
Huh?
[groans]
[thinking] Amazing! He's
not even a Super Saiyan
and he's picking Buu apart!
A power increase
of this magnitude--
it--it's inconceivable!
Wowee! Gohan!
[GOHAN]
You can get up now.
I know you're not hurt.
Not from an attack like that.
Man! What a faker!
He's not hurt!
Uh!
Well! Let's go!
What are you waiting for?
Aah!
[groans]
[SUPER BUU groans]
[yells]
--[GOHAN grunts]
--[SUPER BUU yells]
[yells]
[GOTEN, TRUNKS]
Hit the deck!
[yells]
[SUPER BUU chuckles]
[GOHAN grunting]
--[SUPER BUU chuckles]
--[GOHAN grunting]
[BOTH grunting]
[yells]
[growls]
[SUPER BUU yells]
He, did that?
[SUPER BUU groaning, yelling]
[grunting]
[GOHAN]
Pst! Hey. Behind you.
[SUPER BUU]
Huh?!
Hi! Nice day!
[gasping]
[ALL gasp]
[NARRATOR]
After having his way
with the citizens of Earth,
it looks like Majin Buu
is getting his
own taste of justice!
With a steely resolve
never seen in him before,
Gohan is ruling the day!
But is the fight really over?
Stay tuned for more
of Dragon Ball Z!