[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z...
[FRIEZA] I hate to interrupt
a spirited conversation
such as yours,
but I'm running on a
bit of a tight schedule.
Now prepare yourself for
my final transformation!
[NARRATOR] The hideous
Frieza took everything
our heroes could dish out.
And retaliated by
transforming once more
into an even stronger form.
[FRIEZA yelling]
[yelling continues]
Well... now that I've
bercome a Super Saiyan.
It's time to let my
fists do the talking!
[NARRATOR] Vegeta and Piccolo
were restored to full strength,
thanks to Dende's
healing abilities.
But will their collective
powers be enough to stop this
ultimate transformation
of Frieza?
Find out... today!
What the...?
[DENDE whimpers]
Now wait just a second.
That's the new Frieza!?
Gotta tell ya, he doesn't
look so tough to me.
--I mean, he's so puny--
--[PICCOLO] Shut up!
Let me give you a
piece of advice kid:
Don't let that
creature fool you!
'Cause you know,
looks aren't everything.
What?
He's just too strong!
And even with our
combined strength,
there's no way we could
start to put a dent
in his shiny new armor...
[GOHAN whimpers]
[PICCOLO] I say we get out.
And then maybe one day
we'll return... and kick--
What are you saying?!
[KING KAI] Nooo!
[BOTH] Huh?
[KING KAI] Oh no!
Oh my, I sense Frieza has
manifested into his final form.
Drat!
This could mean all our hope
in Piccolo restoring your lives
may be for naught,
and the universe could fall
under Frieza's evil rule!
Huh?!
No. This just can't happen!
Piccolo, you must...
...stop Friezaaa!
[thinking] Frieza's power
is stronger than ever!
Ah man, I've gotta
get out of here!
Hm?!
Bang.
Noooo--!
[gasping]
What... happened?!
No... No!
[NAIL thinking] Dende?! No!
It can't be! It just can't be!
[PICCOLO thinking]
Frieza, you monster!
That's one down...
and I didn't even break a sweat.
[FRIEZA giggles softly]
No... Dende...
[GOHAN growls]
[giggling continues]
[growling]
[thinking] Oh no! This stinks!
But until I get my strength back
to 100%, I'm totally useless...
Dende? Dende!
Say something, Dende!
He... He saw Dende's power to
heal us and that's the reason
he decided to
take him out first.
[GOHAN growls]
Hey! He disappeared!
[thinking] Come back
and fight like a man.
Wait. What's that?
[FRIEZA] Hello, boys.
How dare you!
[FRIEZA] Now...
...it's time to pull
back the curtain
and let the third
and final act begin.
[GOHAN growls]
My, my, you're quite upset
about what I did
to your little
friend over there.
How touching...
Oh well, what's done is done.
[GOHAN growls]
You seem especially anxious
to get things started.
Shall we begin?
[GOHAN yells]
[GOHAN shouts]
I've had all I
can take from you!
Hmph.
[growling]
[ALL yell]
[grunting]
[grunting continues]
[PICCOLO] Masenko-Haaaa!
Right! That does it!
Kamehame-Haaaa!
Hyaaaa!
Did you get him?!
[KRILLIN] I-I'm not sure...
Yeah. I don't see him anywhere.
[VEGETA] You idiots! Behind you!
What!?
Here I am.
[VEGETA] Look out!
[GOHAN grunts]
[KRILLIN screams]
[PICCOLO growls]
[GOHAN screams]
But I-I didn't see
him move a muscle.
How does he move so fast? It's
like his moves are invisible...
[PICCOLO growls
[thinking] But somehow Vegeta
could see them! I wonder how?
Did Dende give him some
sort of special power?
[GOHAN] Thanks, Vegeta!
You saved us!
[GOHAN laughs]
I didn't save you.
You're not even worth it.
Huh?
[VEGETA chuckles]
I suppose you guys weren't
quite aware of my new powers!
What? New powers?
Huh?
So, what are you saying?
You think you can
take him on yourself?
Oh yes.
He-He's crazy!
[VEGETA] Why don't you
run back to your mommies,
I've got a little
business to take care of.
Your words may be tough, Vegeta,
but I wonder if you
can truly back them up?
I don't think you realize just
who you're dealing with.
So let me show you!
Introducing...
...for the very first time...
Super Saiyan Vegeta!
S-Super...
...S-Sai... Him...?
[thinking] Vegeta?
A Super Saiyan?
What's he talking about?
At last the power
is all mine, Frieza!
[VEGETA laughs]
[FRIEZA giggles]
Forgive me if I don't tremble
in fear, "Super Saiyan".
[FRIEZA giggles]
You don't believe me, do you?
Then I'll just wipe that grin
off your face, Frieza.
Are you ready to fight?
[FRIEZA growls]
[growling continues]
[thinking]
What's going on out there?
Now I sense Vegeta's
power building!
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA yells]
Wh-What's happening?!
[thinking] B-But where did
Vegeta get all this power from?!
[PICCOLO thinking]
He just stood by and watched
as I was fighting Frieza...
Did he have that type
of strength then?
[VEGETA growls]
[PICCOLO thinking] How
did this happen? How?!
[KRILLIN] Don't you get it?!
Vegeta told me that a Saiyan's
strength is at its peak
right after he recovers
from a mortal wound!
What?!
[VEGETA roars]
[GOHAN whimpers]
Gohan! I think we better get
outta here while we still can!
So you're saying it's
possible for Vegeta
to go from all-talk
to super-tough
in the wink of an eye?
Do you remember when Vegeta
asked me to beat him up?!
Well that allowed Dende to heal
him and give him his new powers!
Ah... Now I think I understand.
[VEGETA growls]
Look at Vegeta! Man,
he's really turning it on!
I've got a feeling Frieza's
going down this time!
What do you think,
Gohan?! Oh yeah!
[KRILLIN laughs]
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA roars]
[grunting]
[VEGETA roaring]
[GOHAN] Wha-What
happened, Krillin?
Oh no! That's not good!
Frieza's still standing!
Hold on, Gohan, there's
more fireworks to come.
I've got a feeling
we haven't seen
the full extent of
Vegeta's powers yet!
[GOHAN] You think so?
Yeah! I think you got that
right! I mean, just look at him!
Yep. It's like I said before,
Vegeta just might win
this battle for us after all!
Well, well, you
certainly surprise me
with your new found force.
And I'm just warming
up, you clown!
What you just witnessed was
only the beginning of my power!
If you had one of your
stupid scouters here
you'd realize
my true potential
and you'd run like the
coward you really are!
No matter. A Saiyan
loves a good fight,
and you'll discover
my powers soon enough.
So, let's stop talking
and cut to the chase!
This time you're going down!
Wha'sa matter? Is your brain
another one of your weak
and underused muscles?
Very well. You've
had your fun.
But I really do feel
sorry for you now.
Because now you have to
back up your delusional,
pathetic taunts, Super Saiyan.
[VEGETA growls]
Shut up!
[VEGETA grunts]
[VEGETA yells]
You're making me mad!
[VEGETA growls]
[VEGETA grunting]
[KRILLIN gasps]
[KRILLIN] He's winning!
Look, Vegeta's got him
on the ropes now, Gohan!
Hmm!
[PICCOLO] No!
Huh?
He... He won't win!
He... He can't!
Wh-What are you saying?
[VEGETA grunting]
[VEGETA chuckles]
[FRIEZA] Quit fooling yourself.
You're no match for my speed.
[VEGETA yells]
This is impossible! There's no--
There's no sign of him anywhere!
[FRIEZA giggles softly]
No! No! NO!
[giggling continues]
Well, it looks like you're not
that "Super" of a Saiyan
after all, huh?
[FRIEZA giggles]
In fact, I guess this
makes you the loser.
What does this mean?
It-It means Piccolo was right
and V-Vegeta doesn't stand
a chance against Frieza!
No one stands a chance
against Frieza...
Ah... Da-Daddy...
[thinking] I have to get out of
here! Must help... Gohan!
[NARRATOR] Is Vegeta
truly a "Super Saiyan"
or will this be his
"Sayonara Battle"
against the superior speed
and strength of Frieza?
Find out in the next exciting
episode of Dragon Ball Z!