[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z...
In a dramatic move using
the Fusion Earrings,
Goku and Vegeta joined
bodies to battle Majin Buu.
Permanently united as one,
they became the warrior Vegito.
And they focused
all of their strength
on Earth's ultimate threat!
A monster once
thought unstoppable,
Majin Buu at last
began to weaken
under the Saiyan combo's attack.
[SUPER BUU] But if that's
the way you want to play this,
then fine!
[NARRATOR]
Anxious to test the limits
of his new opponent's power,
Majin Buu created
a giant energy ball.
Made with energy fragments
from every planet
the monster had destroyed,
it was a blast capable of
splitting the Earth in two.
[NARRATOR] But for the
confident warrior, Vegito,
it was just another sporting
challenge to overcome.
[NARRATOR] Now, having
warmed up his new body,
and tested the fighting
abilities of Majin Buu,
Vegito has decided to turn
the battle up a notch.
Calling on the greater
powers of Goku and Vegeta,
the incredible fused warrior
has gone Super Saiyan.
[VEGITO]
Call me Super Vegito!
[DENDE]
Can you hear me? Hello?
[BEE yips]
[yips]
Is he gone, boy?
[BEE whines, yips]
What? You mean he's down there?
Oh, I shouldn't
have let this happen!
Hello!
[DENDE]
Can you hear me, Mr. Satan?
--Mr. Satan!
--[BEE howls]
[MR. SATAN grunts]
Ah! You're alive!
[MR. SATAN] Yeah, I sure am.
That was pretty close!
[BEE yips]
How did you survive that attack?
[laughs]
Did you forget who you
were talkin' to, guardian?
I'm Mister Satan!
The greatest martial arts
champian that ever lived!
Ha, ha! Aw...
So, uh, what happened
to Majin Buu?
Up there?!
[SUPER BUU]
Super Vegito.
So is that your
official new name?
[SUPER BUU laughs]
[SUPER BUU] We have such
great titles now, don't we?
Super Buu, Super Vegito,
we might as well just
say we're invincible.
But let's not forget the stats.
You have two Saiyans and I have
three, not to mention the Namek!
It's quality, not
quantity, my friend.
And our union wasn't
achieved by kidnappings.
But if you're sure you can win
this fight with petty theft...
Come prove it!
[growls] Enough!
You talk too much!
I'll make sure you never
speak to me again!
You're finished!
[SUPER BUU grunting]
[SUPER BUU growls]
[SUPER BUU grunts]
[gasps]
[growls]
[groans]
I'll give you a chance. Give up!
[VEGITO] Hey, did you know
your nose is bleeding?
Clean yourself off!
You're a disgrace!
Ha! I'm getting very
angry with you!
And for me that is a very
bad thing! So, watch yourself!
[yells]
Who could survive that attack?
[gasps]
[VEGITO] Ha! That wasn't too
bad. But your aim is lousy.
What were you shooting at?
[VEGITO] I guess I'll have to
show you how it's done again.
[yells]
What? Why, you...!
Still hungry, Buu?
Eat this!
[SUPER BUU gasping, yelping]
[MR. SATAN laughs]
[MR. SATAN]
He got him!
Ha! We're safe! Yeah!
[MR. SATAN groans]
Strange man.
Go ahead. Take your time.
[yells]
[SUPER BUU panting]
I'll get him! I must!
[growling]
[SUPER BUU cackles]
[SUPER BUU]
What're you going to do now?
You can't hit me
if you can't see me!
[VEGITO] Well, you're half
right, I can't see you.
--[SUPER BUU groaning]
--[VEGITO grunting]
[SUPER BUU panting]
How? Why?
[SUPER BUU gasps]
You villains never
really do take true pride
in your fighting skills.
It takes more than eyesight and
a strong arm to be a warrior.
I'll make you pay!
[SUPER BUU groans]
[VEGITO yells]
[SUPER BUU screams]
[KIBITO KAI]
I'm afraid to believe it!
Majin Buu can't
lay a hand on him.
The fusion has made him
stronger than I ever imagined!
Does everything
surprise you, youngin'?
What did you expect
when they joined together?
Goku and Vegeta were two
of the strongest fighters
in this world or the next.
Naturally, their fusion
would be impressive.
And the fact that
they were rivals
actually makes the
fusion more complete!
I'm sorry, but I've been
dreading Majin Buu for so long!
And now, seeing his defeat--
It's a relief I can't describe!
Give up, Buu!
[KRILLIN laughs]
[KRILLIN]
Isn't this great?!
That Goku-Vegeta combo's
got Buu in a real headlock!
[KING KAI] Yes. I asked King
Yemma to leave you boys with me
in case you needed to help.
But now I see
you're about as needed
as a can of salt at a slug farm!
Come on, King Kai.
How useful would Yamcha
and I have been, anyway?
I mean, if Goku and
Vegeta couldn't beat him!
No use now, I guess.
Wait a minute. What do
you mean by that?
Ah! We're not gonna
have to leave
this training
ground now, are we?
I mean, now that we're not
needed to fight with Buu?
Don't blow your top.
You boys have helped save
the galaxy plenty of times
to earn a spot
on the old A-list.
I'll talk to the Grand Kai about
giving you permanent positions.
Maybe you can help me
win the next tournament here!
[laughs] Thanks a lot,
King Kai! That's great!
Did ya hear that, Yamcha? Huh?
Yamcha? Yamcha?
[YAMCHA]
Hi-ya! Ha!
[yells]
Wow! What's gotten into him?
Ha, ha! This is great! Yeah!
Did ya see that, Krillin?
Those guys couldn't
even touch me!
I don't know what
it is about this place,
but somethin' 'round
here sure is pumpin' me up!
Great. If we were back on Earth,
you couldn't get him to train,
but here, he's a star.
[OLIBU, GORILLA groan]
What's wrong? Has your
confidence finally dropped?
[VEGITO] You know your
run can't last forever.
Not when I'm on guard.
It's not much fun being
hunted down, is it, Majin Buu?
Being hunted,
just the way you hunted down
our friends. Does it hurt?
[screams]
Curse you!
[SUPER BUU grunting]
Hm?
[SUPER BUU cackles]
[growls]
I warned you!
I warned you not
to make me mad!
[yells]
[gasps]
[screams]
[VEGITO gagging]
What the--?
[SUPER BUU cackles]
[SUPER BUU]
I have you now! I'm inside!
Increase your power
all you want.
I'll only get stronger!
If you thought you
were sick of me before,
wait till I start tearing
you apart from the inside!
[SUPER BUU grunts, cackles]
You must really think
I'm an amateur!
[SUPER BUU]
What?!
[VEGITO yells]
[yelling continues]
[SUPER BUU groans]
[SUPER BUU groaning]
[SUPER BUU panting]
[SUPER BUU] I don't understand!
You should be under my control!
It's simple!
You see, I've used my energy to
isolate you inside of my body.
And, as long as
you stay in there,
I have complete
control over you.
Which is fine,
if you don't mind it.
[VEGITO wretches]
[SUPER BUU panting]
[VEGITO chuckles]
I'd say add some spice.
But I don't think anything
will get your bad taste
out of my mouth.
I'm taking you off the menu.
You've got some nerve
making me into a joke!
I'll destroy you, I swear,
if it's the last thing I do!
[growls]
I'm not your entertainment!
[grunting, growling]
[SUPER BUU yells]
[gasps]
[SUPER BUU screams] You led
me to this, you mortal freak!
It's your fault!
[screams]
That's it, try
everything you can!
[screaming continues]
Oh, no! It looks like Buu
is really out of control!
Isn't he always?
Yes, to a degree!
But this is like when
was trapped in the
Hyperbolic Time Chamber!
Let me out!
[DENDE] Somehow, Majin Buu's
anger plunges him deeper
into his evil power
supply. In a rage,
he was capable of punching
a hole between dimensions!
Take a look!
[DENDE] If he's mad enough,
he could do it again.
And that would be disastrous
for the entire universe!
He could break through one
dimensional wall after another.
The imbalance could
cause a collapse!
Yeah, sounds awful.
[SUPER BUU] You make fun of Buu!
No one makes fun of Majin Buu!
[yells]
What? The whole planet's
energy is warping around us!
Is he trying to
destroy everything?
This has gone too far!
[yells]
[yelling]
[VEGITO grunts]
Stop this!
[yelling]
[yells]
[VEGITO]
Hmph.
He won, I lost.
[VEGITO]
Well! If you ask me,
that was a little too
close for comfort.
But have the decency
to learn your lesson.
There's no way you
can ever beat me!
Unless you'd like
to try that technique
you've been saving.
[growls]
[OLD KAI]
Oh, no.
Don't stop now! What could
he be waiting for?
Now! He must destroy
Majin Buu now!
[NARRATOR] The clash
between two great powers
has taken a darker turn!
Vegito seems fully
capable of defeating Buu,
and yet, he declines.
What secret is the
fused Saiyan after?
Find out next time
on Dragon Ball Z!