[NARRATOR]
Last time on Dragon Ball Z...
it looked like the whole
gang was getting together
for a Black Water Mist party!
[MARON screams]
[NARRATOR] Even Piccolo
showed up to take part
in all of the fun!
But somebody forgot to tell
him that the Spice Boys
were planning on serving
him as the hors d'oeuvres!
[groaning]
[growls]
[NARRATOR] Gohan and his
friends were headed straight
for Kami's Lookout,
to reverse the effects
of the Black Water Mist,
but they were cut off by
Piccolo and his new allies!
[GOHAN]
Piccolo!
[SPICE]
What took you two so long?
[SALT] We've been waiting
for you! So has he!
Man!
This isn't looking good!
[NARRATOR]
Friends become enemies, today!
[PICCOLO growls]
[SPICE] Well boys, what do
you think of Piccolo now?
He's all set to
serve Garlic Jr.!
That's because he's
become part of our family!
He's one of us, kid,
just like your mother is!
[GARLIC JR.] Ah, I see the
son of Goku has arrived.
I believe your name
is Gohan, right?
Welcome here, my friend.
I hope you don't mind but,
I have a question for you!
[KRILLIN whimpers]
I want to know where
your father is!
My father?!
Precisely! I must
find him in order
to carry out my revenge!
Once that is accomplished,
then both you and he...
will pay double for
your failed attempt
to defeat me!
No!
Even though I now
rule the Earth,
that isn't good enough
until I exact my revenge
upon you two!
[PICCOLO growls]
Huh?
[PICCOLO growling]
So, young Gohan, tell me where
your dear father is hiding.
And I warn you,
don't try to be smart!
My dad would never hide
from the likes of you,
and besides, where he is,
he doesn't even know
your evil kind exist!
Where he is...
What do you mean by that?
I'll never tell!
Huh?
So don't bother to...
ask me that question again!
[GOHAN yells]
[GARLIC JR.]
Have it your way, kid!
[GARLIC JR.] Once Goku
realizes that you're here,
it's only a matter of time
before he shows up!
[GOHAN grunts]
Huh?
[GOHAN growling]
[GARLIC JR. growling]
[GARLIC JR.] Now I remember!
That little kid has the ability
to nullify my power!
But I can't let
that happen again!
You pest!
How are you doing this?
[growls]
Into the void you go!
[grunting]
[yells]
Father!
[GOHAN growling]
[GOHAN yells]
It's time to finish you off!
Huh?
Go ahead and take
your best shot!
But if you shoot me,
then you'll also have
roasted Kami under glass!
[GARLIC JR. cackles]
Oh my gosh!
[GARLIC JR. cackling]
[SALT cackles]
[SALT grunts]
[GOHAN groans]
[SALT grunting]
[GOHAN groaning]
Gohan!
I gotta present for ya!
[KRILLIN groans]
[GARLIC JR. cackles]
Ooh, Master Garlic,
I was wondering,
can we play with our
newfound buddies?
Wait a second!
[GARLIC JR.] All right then, you
both may have sport with them
until Goku shows up!
However...
Hm?
[GARLIC JR.]
The coup de grace is all mine,
so be careful not to go
too far with them!
Yes!
All right, you heard him!
Why don't we get started!
Prepare to get whooped!
[GOHAN growls]
Hey!
Don't whoop him too bad!
Save some for me!
But two against one
wouldn't be fair!
Ah, like they say, all's
is fair in love and war!
[PICCOLO growling]
Huh?
C'mon kid, let's play.
I haven't got all day!
Oh, isn't this wonderful, Kami?
I've always believed
revenge is so sweet!
[SALT]
What are you waiting for?
Well, if you're not
gonna make a move,
then I guess I will!
[SALT growls]
[GOHAN groans]
[GOHAN groaning]
Gohan, I'm comin'!
Hey! Hold on! Where you goin'?
It's my turn to play with you!
[KRILLIN groaning]
[SALT grunting]
[GOHAN groaning]
What's wrong kid?
You don't wanna play with me?
[SALT grunting, yelling]
[GOHAN groaning]
Oh, please! I thought
the son of Goku
was a little tougher than this!
My sister can take a
punch better than you!
Gohan...
[KRILLIN yells]
[KRILLIN, MUSTARD grunting]
[KRILLIN groans]
Gohan!
C'mon! Let's keep
playing, all right kid?
Ah, that's more like it!
[SALT] Hey! I think it's
about my turn to win, pal!
[SALT yells]
[KRILLIN yells]
[KRILLIN yelling]
Krillin!
You want some!
[KRILLIN groaning]
No! Krillin!
One, two, three, four,
let's do it once more!
Five, six, seven, eight,
keeps up the heart rate!
Oh, exercising is not only
good, but good for you!
And people wonder how I
keep up my girlish figure!
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight...
Man, I don't think
I'll ever understand
how you chicks can
exercise so much!
Why, just watching
you is making me
break out into sweat!
One, two, three, four,
why don't you join
me on the floor?
[KORIN giggling]
Well then, Yajirobe,
I must say,
this girl doesn't
have a whole lot
of respect for us, does she?
I guess you can't blame
her, at least I don't!
Huh?
Hey! Yajirobe and the
talking cat!
Hey, hey, hey! The cat
has a name you know
and it wouldn't
hurt for you to
show a little respect!
Whatever! If it makes you happy!
[KORIN groans]
All that working out's
making me hungry!
Why don't you make me something?
--Huh?
--What? Make you something?
[MARON] Would you hurry it up
already! My body needs fuel!
Uh, but we've never cooked
anything before, right?
[nervous laughter]
For me, please?
Ah, sure...
Okay!
[KORIN]
We were talking the talk,
now we have to walk the walk!
[YAJIROBI]
Yeah, and like they say,
the way to a woman's heart
is through her stomach!
[KORIN] What? Oh, I guess
that pretty much explains
your strikeout record
with the women!
You know, I think Maron
is taking a shine to me!
[KORIN]
Ah, but once she tastes my
Coconut Cream Shrimp Casserole,
she'll be all over me!
[YAJIROBI]
In your dreams, catnip breath!
[MARON]
Oh boys, could you please hurry!
I'm simply starving!
C-coming my precious!
Poor cat's headed straight
for heartbreak city!
[KRILLIN yelling]
[SALT cackling]
[KRILLIN yells]
Krillin!
[GOHAN]
Wake up, Krillin! Wake up!
It's okay Gohan,
don't worry about me.
[KRILLIN] There're others
who need your help
a lot more right now!
B-but Krillin!
Go Gohan.
Go before it's too late!
Do it for your mother and Bulma!
[PICCOLO growls]
[KRILLIN]
Do it for Piccolo!
You see, you haven't breathed in
the Black Water Mist yet, so...
[cackling]
[GOHAN yells]
[VEGETA grunting]
Curses! Even with
all of my power,
Kakarot would
easily defeat me!
His power makes mine
seem insignificant!
[VEGETA]
How much more do I have to train
to become a true Super Saiyan?
Tell me!
[VEGETA panting]
[VEGETA gasps]
What the? What was that?
What's going on down there?
Kakarot?
[VEGETA]
Kakarot! He must be back!
I knew it!
[VEGETA]
I just knew it was him!
What?
[VEGETA grunts]
[VEGETA yells]
Come and get it!
Now, where did he disappear to?
Oh, now I understand!
[VEGETA] The answers were right
before my eyes all along!
But I was my blinded
by my own ambition!
[VEGETA cackles]
And now that I hold
the key to the secret,
soon I too will
possess the power!
The time has come,
for me to finally
meet my destiny!
Beware, Kakarot. Because I too
will become a Super Saiyan!
[GARLIC JR.] That kid's
building up his strength again!
But this time I'll be prepared!
[GOHAN grunting]
[GOHAN yells]
That kid's sure
gotta lot of moxy!
You're not kidding,
he's on fire!
[SALT] Well, I think you should
have first crack at him, okay?
[MUSTARD]
Remember what he did last time?
I say two against one is
our only option against him!
[grunting, cackling]
What's this!
[grunting]
Oh gosh, Gohan!
[MUSTARD gasps]
[SALT gasps]
Yeah, Gohan...
Ma-sen-ko
[GOHAN yells]
[yelling]
I'm gonna get you for this!
[MUSTARD yelling]
[GOHAN yells]
[MUSTARD screams]
[GARLIC JR. growls]
Why you rotten rugrat!
Let me at him!
Save some for me!
[PICCOLO growling]
What're you doing, Piccolo?
[PICCOLO yells]
[KRILLIN yelps]
[GOHAN grunting]
[PICCOLO growling]
[GARLIC JR. cackling]
Yes, my pet. Destroy him!
Then the entire universe
will be under my command!
No... Piccolo... no...
[PICCOLO growling]
[NARRATOR]
Is this "lights out" for Gohan?
And what's keeping our hero,
Goku from saving the day?!
The universe won't rest
until we find out...
on the next episode
of Dragon Ball Z!