[GOHAN yells]
[NARRATOR] Last time
on Dragon Ball Z,
Gohan began his training
in the Hyperbolic Time Chamber,
a room that defies the normal
constraints of time and space.
His mission: To achieve
the level of Super Saiyan
under the watchful
guidance of his father.
[GOKU] Use the pain of loss.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
Vegeta began his assault
on the evil super-power, Cell,
who was still one android short
of completing his evolution!
Even without
absorbing Android 18,
Cell had already gained a
enormous amount of strength
when he successfully integrated
Android 17 into his body.
And itt seemed that
he was now unstoppable
[CELL gasps]
That one was free...
Now I'm going to show you
what true power really is!
[NARRATOR]
But has Vegeta actually
surpassed him in strength?
[CELL] Vegeta!? You've changed!
You've... You've
become something else!
Yes... I am Super Vegeta.
[ANDROID 18] Cell's... scared!
[TRUNKS] Father has
him against the ropes.
He's won the game.
[CELL growls]
How did you acquire this
new strength?! Enlighten me!
I do a lot of
push-ups and sit-ups!
And I drink plenty of juice!
[CELL growls]
[CELL] Listen here!
I came from the future where you
were destroyed by Android 17!
And now I've
absorbed Android 17!
I have all of his power at my
disposal in addition to my own!
So tell me, how could
you be stronger than me?!
It's not possible!
You're bluffing!
Look! If you think
I'm bluffing, call my bluff.
Here, I know you're confused
so let me make it easier on you.
My back's turned. How's that?
[CELL growls]
[CELL] You will pay for
your insolence, Vegeta!
[growling continues]
[KRILLIN] Wow! Vegeta's
turned his back on Cell!
I don't see either of the
androids down there...
Man, that's not a
good sign at all!
That means that 18's
probably been absorbed already!
[KRILLIN growls]
Well, maybe it's all
for the best anyway...
I don't know if I
could have used this thing.
[VEGETA] Hmm?!
Hey, that's my
Father's Gallic Gun!
Remember: Some
of your cells compose me!
[CELL] Gallic Gun...
Fire!
Father!
[VEGETA laughs]
[CELL growls]
[KRILLIN grunts]
Oh, my gosh!
[CELL grunts]
[SQUIRREL squeaks]
[CELL chuckles]
[CELL gasps]
[KRILLIN] Phenomenal!
Vegeta looks awesome!
[SQUIRRELS squeak]
He is stronger.
[ANDROID 18] Wow!
Fantastic! Hm? Huh?
I must be going crazy...
[ANDROID 16] Do not be alarmed.
Our feelings sometimes
conflict with our programming.
So this is it, huh?
Now that's a joke!
I thought this was
going to be a challenge.
Ha! I can't believe
we were worried about you.
[CELL growls]
You will pay!
I don't think so, Cell!
I'm afraid you're
outclassed in every way!
No! Impossible! It's not true!
[CELL yells]
[CELL] Hrrgh?!
[CELL grunts]
[CELL yells]
[VEGETA] Haah!
[CELL  yells]
[KRILLIN] This is crazy!
Vegeta's radical!
I've never seen him like this!
He's bigger, faster... He's
even stronger than Goku now!
What's the matter?
You seem to be worried
about something,
but at least we're
winning, right?
It's Vegeta who's
winning, Tien, not us.
Yeah, I guess I know
what you mean.
I have a hard time
trusting in Vegeta as well.
[BULMA] Silly boy!
You like them, huh?!
Yeah! They're butterflies!
[BABY TRUNKS giggles]
[BABY TRUNKS coos]
[BULMA sighs]
Gosh. I wonder what's up?
Goku's taking so long in there.
And your Daddy, I wonder
how he's doing against Cell?
[BULMA] Come on, Goku!
It never feels right when
you're not on the scene!
We need you!
[GOKU] Now, Gohan!
Try it again! You can do it!
[GOHAN yells]
Yes! That's it!
You're doing it, Gohan!
[yelling continues]
You can do it! Push on through!
[GOHAN gasps]
[GOHAN] That was so real!
I almost had it...
Is he training me in my dreams?
[GOHAN] Hey, Dad?
Huh? He's gone.
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU] Kaa...
Mee...
Haa...
[GOKU growls]
[GOKU] Haaa!
[GOKU yells]
[GOKU growls]
[GOHAN] Dad! Are you okay?!
[GOHAN gasps]
[GOHAN] Dad!
[GOHAN] Dad! No!
[GOHAN screams]
[GOHAN] Dad, are you alright?!
[GOHAN] Wow... Awesome...
What's up? Sorry, I scared you.
I almost did it!
[GOKU] Huh...?
Yeah. But it was just a dream.
I see.
Hey, you're in there, champ.
It's only a matter of time
until you break through.
You're doing incredibly.
And besides, you're
way stronger than I was
when I was your age, Son.
You have to keep that in mind!
You're being too hard
on yourself! Let it all go.
Right. I'll try, Dad.
But I'm still ready to start.
Train me. I'm done resting.
Please, Dad!
I feel fine! I promise!
There was something
about that dream, Dad.
It was so real! I started
to transform! I could feel it!
Dad, please! Let me continue!
I can rest later! Please!
[GOKU sighs]
[GOKU] You know what your mother
would say if she were here,
but since she's not,
I guess it's my call...
Alright. Let's train!
Yaye Awesome!
[GOHAN laughs]
[GOHAN] You're the best
dad in the whole world!
[GOKU laughs]
[GOKU] Well, the best dad
in the whole world
would probably make
you stay in bed,
but I'm going to have to ask you
to do one hundred push-ups, Son.
[GOHAN] Oh, alright.
[GOKU] And then
one-hundred sit-ups!
[GOHAN] Okay, gotcha.
[GOKU] And then ten
Kamehameha Waves!
[GOHAN] Right...
[CELL wheezes]
[thinking] How could
he be so strong?!
It doesn't make sense!
I've tried everything on him!
[VEGETA] Cell?!
[thinking] This can't
be happening!
[CELL wheezes]
[ANDROID 18] He is amazing...
[CELL] "Super Vegeta"!
[CELL growls]
I am Cell! Do you hear me?!
[VEGETA] You are nothing.
[CELL yells]
[CELL roars]
[VEGETA yells]
[CELL screams]
[CELL grunts]
[thinking] Father,
you truly are strong...
But it's dangerous to
let it go to your head.
Hey, it's Trunks.
Man! What a change.
He looks totally different!
The Hyperbolic Time
Chamber must be a killer!
Maybe I should think about
spending a day in there!
I need to bulk up myself...
Come on, girls!
You can do it! One, two...
And that's the news, folks!
Ordinary journeys
become adventures
in a glass-bottom boat!
[YAMCHA] Man! Fifty
channels and nothing!
What's this world coming to?!
[CHIAOTZU] How can
you guys watch T.V.?!
I can't stop thinking
about Tien and the others...
Well, when Goku's your
husband and Gohan's your son,
you can either let it all go
or worry yourself to death.
So, I'm trying to let it all go!
[CHIAOTZU] I thought you
were just being heartless...
--[CHICHI laughs]
--[YAMCHA stammers]
Hey, look! Talk about worried!
Master Roshi's really
stressed out over there.
Pitiful! Just pitiful!
Yo! Hello in there!
[ROSHI gasps]
Oh! Sleep if you must.
I'll keep the vigil.
Heart aflame like
a lighthouse in the night
will my hopeful eyes
cast their searching light.
Man! You should
really write that down.
Why, thank you, sir.
That's very kind of you.
--[CELL yells]
--[VEGETA growls]
[CELL grunts]
[VEGETA shouting]
[CELL grunting]
[VEGETA yells]
[VEGETA laughs]
Hm?! Where'd he go?
[CELL growls]
Now this is more like it!
Super Vegeta, let's see
you get out of this one!
[CELL growls]
What a pity! Your tail's stuck!
You are detestable!
[growling continues]
[VEGETA chuckles]
[VEGETA growls]
[BOTH yell]
What went wrong? You had me!
[CELL growls]
[VEGETA yells]
[CELL yells]
My gosh! What an
extraordinary power!
I hope you're
being careful, Father.
You're in uncharted territory.
Please! Don't let
it consume you...
My gosh!
[ANDROID 18] Cell
doesn't know what to do.
Mama mia!
[CELL roars]
[CELL] I will find
a way to destroy you!
[VEGETA] Is that what you were
doing down there so long?
Trying to think
of a way to beat me?
Well, it's not going
to happen, Cell!
Face it! You were
dealt a bad hand!
[VEGETA chuckles]
[CELL growls]
Come on.
[KRILLIN] Vegeta! Now
why'd you go and do that?!
[CELL thinking] Now where is he?
[CELL growls]
[FISH roars]
[CELL shouting]
[shouting continues]
[thinking] He can't
harm you, Father!
[CELL growls]
Hey! Come out!
[garbled shouting]
[VEGETA yells]
[CELL yells]
[CELL roars]
[CELL growls]
[VEGETA chuckles]
You should see the
look on your face right now!
How would you feel if I told
you there's another like me?!
[CELL gasps]
Allow me to introduce you
to my son! His name is Trunks!
He, too, is a true Super Saiyan!
He's not quite
as strong as I am,
but it would be hard to tell
the difference between us!
He has incredible power!
[CELL] No! How can this be?!
[CELL whimpers]
Do you understand
how fruitless this is?!
I've been allowing you to
deceive yourself, that's all!
You never had a chance to win!
If by some miracle you
managed to get by me,
Trunks would've
finished you off!
Face it, Cell, you
took a gamble and you lost!
[CELL growls]
[CELL] It doesn't make sense!
How did you get all of
this power?! Curse you!
[CELL growls]
[VEGETA] You're the one
who started this game!
And now that you're losing
it's no fun anymore!
You're just a big baby!
[CELL screams]
[CELL] You wouldn't be
talking to me this way
if I had completed my evolution!
[CELL growls]
[CELL] You would be nothing to
me if I absorbed Android 18!
Woah! So he hasn't
absorbed Android 18 after all!
[CELL] Vegeta, allow me to
achieve my final, perfect form.
As a Saiyan, you can
appreciate the challenge!
[TRUNKS thinking] Father, no!
He's deceiving you!
[CELL] What do you say, Vegeta?!
[VEGETA] You still
sound like a baby
who's trying to get his way!
[CELL yells]
[CELL] This isn't happening!