( Singing in Japanese )
♪
♪ Fire
( singing in Japanese )
( Both gasp )
( Door creaks )
( Phil giggles )
Don and gilda: Phil?
- Phil: Shh.
- Don: Huh?
Phil: I’m playing hide-and-seek
with naila and Eugene.
( Both sigh )
Gilda: Oh, I see.
Norman: So...
Emma: The next thing
we look at is...
All: Outside.
Ray: We already got
lots of stuff done
on the inside.
Norman: Training’s going well.
The trackers can be broken,
which leaves...
Ray: Learning about the outside
and outsmarting the adults.
Once that’s done...
We can clear the wall for sure.
Emma: Next is checking out
the escape route.
Norman: The escape
we’ve planned out
consists of three steps.
One, we ascend the wall.
Two, we safely get
as far away as we can.
Three, we learn how to survive
and become self-reliant.
We have everything we need
to pass the first step.
As for the second...
The outside is key.
When we leave,
we should run as far as we can,
so let’s examine and prepare.
Ray: We need info
about the area outside.
Emma: Oh! When I climbed
up a tree, I saw a big forest!
Ray: Okay, but we’ve gotta
confirm stuff like that.
Norman: Let’s look into it
starting tomorrow.
( Emma grunts ) Oh, yeah.
There was one more thing
I wanted to mention.
Norman: Hmm?
Emma: I have someone
I want you to meet.
( Children chattering )
( Don sighs )
( Both gasp )
Don: Oh! Sorry! I’m in a hurry!
- Mark: Hey, mom, down here!
- ( Isabella chuckles )
Don: Look. I actually did it.
( Gilda gasps )
( Don chuckles )
Naila: Isn’t it cool?
( Children giggle )
♪
Emma: The person
I wanna introduce is...
Right here.
Norman: Mr. "William Minerva."
Really?
( Emma grunts )
- Norman: Who’s he?
- Emma: I don’t know.
All I know is that he’s
the former owner of these books,
but I think it’s possible
that’s he’s on our side.
Norman: What do you mean?
Emma: He’s been
delivering a message
through the books
in this library,
and not just a few books,
but lots of ’em!
- ( Lock clicks )
- ( Both gasp )
( Both grunt )
( Door creaks )
Norman: So this sticker is...
Emma: A bookplate.
Ray: It’s a label
that shows who owned the book
before it came here.
Norman: Okay,
but where’s the message?
Emma: Look closer.
Norman: They’re all
the same owl bookplate.
Wait.
The circle...
It’s morse code.
Ray: Correct.
( Both gasp )
Don: Eh?
( Gilda gasps )
( Foot clatters )
Don: Huh?
( Matches rattle )
- ( Door rattles )
- ( Gilda gasps )
( Don gasps )
( Both grunt )
Norman: It says, "run."
And this one says, "doubt."
Then there’s "danger."
And this last one is "truth."
Still, these don’t mean...
Emma: Hey, check these, too.
Norman: These ones
are "harvest"...
"Monster," and finally...
"Farm."
( Gasps )
This is...
Ray: It’s a message to us
from the outside,
hidden from everybody else.
I think we can
at least trust these.
Norman: You sure?
Ray: I tend to be more
suspicious than Emma, so, yeah.
It’s possible this Minerva guy
could be an ally to us,
but unfortunately we don’t
know if he’s dead or alive,
so we shouldn’t
get our hopes up too much.
Emma: You’re always so negative!
Norman: William Minerva,
he’s someone from the outside
who’s aware
that our farm exists.
And while it may be indirectly,
he’s definitely
trying to help us.
Emma: That’s right!
Norman: An ally on the outside.
He might even still be there.
In which case, it’s possible
a society of humans may exist.
Emma: Exactly!
( Don gasping )
( Gasps )
Emma: These messages are only
in books that belonged to him.
It’s hard to tell exactly when
these labels were put inside,
but at least
we know that this one
was done after the year 2015.
Norman: I see.
Are we aware of anything else,
like if the books
have some kind of similarity?
Ray: Nope.
The genres are varied.
Same goes for the publishers
and years they were published.
Emma: But what about...
Uh, which one was it?
We don’t understand
the morse code in these two.
Ray: One is a run-of-the-mill
adventure novel.
The other’s
a confusing mythology book.
Norman: There’s
no morse code here.
As for this one...
"Promise"?
Norman: What does that mean?
Don: Why is little bunny here?
Gilda: So what Emma
and the others said,
all of it was true, Don.
Don: Huh?
Gilda: Mom was lying.
No one was sent
to foster families.
Don: Stop it.
Gilda: Because if they
actually had been,
this wouldn’t be here.
It would have been delivered
straight to conny.
And it’s not
just little bunny, either.
Mom took
all of these toys from them
when they left the house.
Then they were taken
by the bad people.
( Don gasps )
Hey, would you cut it out?!
- ( Wheels squeaking )
- ( Gasps )
( Both gasp )
Emma: I’m pretty sure
there’s some kind
of meaning in these two,
a book with
the message "promise"
and one
that doesn’t have morse code,
but has
a few ripped pages in it.
Norman: So you think
these ones are special?
Emma: Yeah. If i’m right...
Then I think
it’s extremely likely
that these’ll become
an important guide for us.
Ray: Based on what?
Emma: A hunch!
( Ray grunts )
Emma: What’s with that face?!
Don: So who is mom
communicating with?
Is it the base
ray was talking about?
Are they the bad guys?
Ray mentioned that he
had mom under control
and we’re done for
if krone finds out.
What did he mean by that?
If either of them catch us,
will they punish us?
And what if mom
is really dangerous
and our siblings are--
gilda: Stop it! Norman told us
that he doesn’t know
what happened to conny!
Don: No, those three
are just hiding things from us.
Gilda: They must have
a reason for it. Maybe...
Don: I can’t
trust them like that,
not when they
obviously don’t trust us
enough to tell us the truth.
Norman: I think this is
all worth looking into.
Let’s learn more
about Mr. Minerva.
Emma: We’re not just escaping,
right, guys?
We’re gonna find a way
for us to survive in this world!
( Norman grunts )
Let’s run.
Let’s live,
no matter what things
are like out there.
( Clock ticking )
( Emma giggles )
- ( Door opens )
- ( Both gasp )
Isabella: Just a moment, Phil.
- I’ll be right there.
- ( Both shuddering )
Norman: I’m kind of surprised.
I expected ray
to find the bookplates,
since he reads a lot,
ray: But how the heck did you
manage to find them, Emma?
Emma: Oh, it wasn’t me
who noticed them.
Norman: Huh?
Emma: Phil was actually
the one who showed me.
- Norman: Really?
- Emma: Mm-hmm.
A kids’s book he was reading
happened to be Mr. Minerva’s,
and there was a part in it
that had morse code, so...
- ( Overlapping chatter )
- Emma: Huh?
Don and gilda...
Norman:
They’re not here, either.
Emma: Could they be...
( Both shuddering )
( Footsteps echoing )
( Chair scrapes )
( Papers rustle )
( Thump )
( Isabella sighs )
( Chair scrapes )
( Footsteps approaching )
( Both shuddering )
( Clock ticking )
( Isabella sighs )
- ( Gasps )
- Eugene: Mom!
Isabella: Oh, Eugene.
What’s wrong?
Eugene: This was on the floor.
( Isabella gasps )
Why, thank you.
( Eugene giggles )
( Door opens )
( Door closes )
( Emma gasps )
Don! Gilda!
Oh, good. I thought--eh?
Ray: Where were you?
♪
( Clock ticking )
Well?
Don: We were just
in mom’s secret room, okay?
Emma: But how?
Gilda: You see,
Don stole the key, and--
- Emma: He what?!
- Norman: Wait. Did she...
Gilda: I don’t think
she noticed,
and we already
put it back, so...
( Ray gasps )
That was a stupid move!
Did you not even stop to think
that the room could have
had a camera or an alarm?
What would you have done then?
If mom or krone found out,
you two--no, we’d all be--
Don: Tell us
what would happen, ray.
( Norman and Emma gasp )
Don: Would we all be killed?
When we searched
the secret room,
we found little bunny.
You kept us hopeful,
said we’d save them...
But we can’t save them, can we?
’cause they’re all--
conny and the others are...
( Shuddering )
Emma: Look...
I’m so sorry!
Gilda: Then, they’re really...
- ( Emma gasps )
- Don: You see, gilda?
They were lying to us after all.
What are you hiding?
Just tell us the truth.
( Emma sighs )
( Norman grunts )
( Inhales )
Don: Demons? A farm?
Gilda: You’re saying every one
of us was raised to be eaten?
Don: And ray is a spy?
No way.
Norman: He did it for us.
Don: Then you knew
what was going to happen
to conny that day, ray?
And Emma and Norman,
you guys lied
so we wouldn’t know
you were taking us
into a world full of demons?
( Sighs )
( Laughing )
( Laughing wildly )
- ( Norman groans )
- ( Girls gasp )
Don: Seriously?!
Ray: Wait, Don! Stop!
( Emma gasps )
( Don growling )
( Gilda shuddering )
( Don sighs )
Gilda: Don.
Don: Are we
that much of a burden?
Do you think gilda and I
are so weak and useless
that we can’t get by
without you three protecting us?
( Emma gasps )
Don: That time you asked us
to help you,
I thought you were
actually relying on us.
Was that a lie, Emma?
( Emma gasping )
Don: I know we’re not nearly
as smart as you guys,
but we’re family...
Aren’t we? ( Sobbing )
We’re siblings, right?!
I just want you to have
a little faith in us!
♪
Sorry. I need to cool off.
I’m going outside.
Gilda: Don, wait.
( Door opens )
( Door closes )
Emma: Did I not have faith?
Don: Honestly, that was just me
taking it out on them.
I’m not mad they treated us
like we were weak.
I have no reason to be.
I couldn’t do anything
for conny and the others.
I’m so ignorant and powerless.
I’m frustrated,
because I really am weak!
( Sobbing )
Damn it!
I hate this.
I wanna be stronger!
Gilda: Yeah, I know.
Emma: Don! Gilda!
Gilda: Emma.
Emma: Look, I was way too naive.
I was ready for you
to resent me,
but not at all ready
to believe in you!
( Both gasp )
Norman: Same here.
Sorry.
( Don stammers )
Uh, well, I...
I shouldn’t have
punched you like that. Sorry.
Are you okay?
You’re not, are you?
Norman: I’ll be all right.
Gilda: We realize that it was
a bad idea to act on our own.
Don: Yeah. Ray had
every right to get mad.
Don and gilda:
Please forgive us.
Norman: Well, will you?
( Ray sighs )
Yeah, I forgive them.
If the worst happens,
i’ll figure out
how to deal with it.
( Don sighs )
Ray: I should also apologize.
Sorry.
( Emma and Norman laugh )
Emma: Now that you two
know the truth,
I need to confirm something
before we continue.
The outside world
is full of demons.
If we mess up, we die.
Knowing that,
will you still come with us?
( Both grunt )
Both: Of course we will!
( Emma sighs )
♪
( Ray grunts )
( Overlapping chatter )
Emma: You know, I feel better
now that we’ve
told them the truth.
( Norman grunts )
One week until we escape,
and the preparations
are going well,
but how do we get out
with all of our siblings?
Emma: Oh, yeah.
- I should probably tell you.
- Norman: Hmm?
Emma: I think
I have it figured out,
a way to escape with everyone.
♪
( Wind blowing )
Is it reckless?
Norman: I’m afraid so.
Emma: Norman, we can catch mom
off guard with this plan!
It’s the only way to actually
escape with everyone.
Norman: Hmm.
( Chuckles )
( Emma chuckles )
Should we tell ray?
Norman: No.
Emma: Um...
Do you think he would
really escape with all of us?
Norman: Of course he would.
Everything ray has done
up to this point
has been for our sake,
all of it,
for me and you, Emma.
Emma: Huh?
Norman: Nothing.
Anyway, don’t worry.
I’ll bring it up to ray soon.
Emma: Oh.
( Children giggle )
♪
( Wood clatters )
( Norman gasps )
"All of this just to make sure
you both don’t die."
I see now.
Amazing, ray.
Don: I stole those things
you wanted, Norman,
some detergent and herbicide.
What are you
gonna use these for?
Norman: They’ll help out
with our investigation.
Gilda: We’re going
past the fence to climb the wall
so that we can inspect
the outside, right?
What about
the tracking devices?
Emma: Oh, well, we make sure
they don’t look at them.
Norman: It’ll be easy.
All we need’s a distraction.
We’ll create a situation where
they can’t check the trackers.
Don: But how do we do that?
Ray’s working
on stalling mom now.
He’s giving her false info
to throw her off.
Isabella: So you and Norman
got into a fight?
Ray: It was over something
we didn’t agree about.
Isabella: Now, what is it
you came here to tell me?
Ray: Norman’s working
on trying to kill you.
( Isabella gasps )
Of course he would go that far
to escape with everyone. And?
Ray: He’s collecting items--
a hammer, detergent, herbicide,
anything he thinks
he can use to get it done.
Isabella: Including
that rope from before?
Ray: Yup. I tried to stop him.
I told him
it was a stupid idea.
Isabella: And he
gave you that bruise.
Death by poison?
That could be troublesome.
Ray: Yeah, but don’t
ship them out because of this.
Let them live
in this house peacefully
until they’re
old enough to age out.
That’s all I want, okay?
Now, then, here’s the plan.
We just replace the chemicals.
Isabella: Do you know
where he hid them?
Ray: Yeah.
Isabella: Then let’s
deal with this tomorrow.
Is that all?
Ray: Yeah. Why?
Is there something else
bothering you?
Isabella: Not really.
- Oh.
- Ray: Hmm?
Isabella: I’ll let you in
on this early.
I received word from hq
during yesterday’s check-in.
They say
that the next shipment is set.
( Ray gasps )
There won’t be one in December.
Ray: January’s next, then.
It’ll happen
on my 12th birthday.
So the next shipment
is finally me, huh?
Don: But even if ray
manages to keep mom busy,
what about sister krone?
Gilda: Yeah, if she finds out,
then we’ll be shipped out
immediately, right?
Norman: Don’t worry.
I have an idea.
♪
Norman: Did you need something?
Krone: I saw it, you know.
- ( Emma gasps )
- Krone: That’s right, children!
I saw everything!
All of you
were talking last night
in the dining hall!
The ones who know
the secret about this house
are Norman, Emma,
ray, gilda, and Don,
five of you total.
( Chuckles )
So...
You want to join forces?
Emma: Huh?
( Krone laughs )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )