( Both sigh )
( Ray gasping )
Where are the kids
four and under?
Emma: I decided that we
should leave them all here.
( Ray gasps )
Emma: I thought about...
( Grunts )
What you said to me earlier...
One more time.
- ( Children grunting )
- Don: So far, so good.
I got everyone down to age five
on our side.
Gilda: They were
pretty surprised,
but I think things’ll be okay.
Don: We already
started training them.
Emma: Thanks, you guys.
Don: So what do we do next?
Should we tell
the kids under five?
( Clock ticking )
Emma: But do you think
they’ll believe us?
Don: Well, it’s more like
can they keep it a secret?
Gilda: It’s not
just that, either.
Is it really possible
to bring them with us?
- Don: Huh?
- Gilda: Don’t get me wrong.
It’s not like I don’t believe
in norman’s plan.
However, we are dealing
with a cliff in winter,
and norman’s not here to help.
Once we actually escape,
we don’t know what’s out there.
I’m starting to see ray’s point,
even though it may be
a little late to feel that way.
Don: So you’re saying...
Gilda: If we take them along,
they could get killed.
Don: Gilda, if they stay here,
they’re gonna get shipped out.
Gilda: I know!
I know that, but...
♪
Emma: I can’t bring myself
to leave them.
Ray’s correct.
So are you, gilda.
But I don’t want anyone else
to get shipped out.
( Don sighs )
Same here.
Emma: I wanna take everyone.
We’ll all run away.
Gilda: Yeah, but...
Don: What’s wrong?
Gilda: Well, um...
What about the kids
in the other plants?
( Emma gasps )
Gilda: Is it okay if we’re
the only ones who escape?
We’ve never seen them before,
but there’s a family
just like us
in the next plant over, right,
living life as if
everything’s normal?
( Gasps )
Oh! Uh, sorry!
( Don sighs )
What now, Emma?
( Emma gasps )
Good question.
After all...
Can you get Phil?
Phil: What’s up?
Emma: We need to talk
about the house and mom.
Phil: Hmm.
I knew it.
It’s just like I thought.
( Emma gasps )
Phil: When we all played tag,
sister said stuff
about a "harvest,"
and I wondered what she meant.
One time, I saw her
looking under ray’s bed.
And, when Norman left the house,
I could tell you were
really scared of mom, Emma.
It was all weird,
but I didn’t know why.
So then...
Norman got harvested, huh?
Conny, too. ( Crying )
And the others.
That’s why you guys...
( Crying )
Emma: Phil!
( Phil crying )
( Crying echoes )
Emma: I won’t take them yet.
Only Phil knows the truth.
The others don’t know
about the house or fire,
so i’m leaving it to Phil.
All right. Hear me out.
I don’t know which option
i should go with.
Do I take everyone,
including the babies,
or should I leave
the kids under five?
Both: Huh?!
Emma: We only get harvested
when we turn six,
and even though marnya’s
birthday is the earliest,
she’ll still have
a year and a half.
15 of the older kids’ll
be gone.
Since this house
focuses on quality,
the pace of harvesting
should start going down.
if they want to raise
high-quality kids here again,
they can’t kill
ones with potential.
that said,
you and the other five
who are four years old
all have good scores,
so it’s best to let you develop.
If I had to take a guess,
i’d say we have about two years.
( Don gasps )
Wait. You mean...
Phil: I can wait. Promise.
So just leave us here.
( Both gasp )
Emma: I don’t plan
on ever giving up.
I’ll return here
within two years,
and, when I finally do,
i’ll escape with Phil
and the rest of our siblings,
along with kids
from the other four plants.
( Nat grunts )
Isabella: Phil...
Where are the other children?
Phil: Mm.
This way!
( Isabella gasps )
( Grunts )
( Children panting )
Children: Mom! Mom!
Boy: Where’s Emma
and the others, mom?
Are they lost?
Isabella: I’ll go get them.
- ( Children clamoring )
- Isabella: Don’t worry.
I’ll be back soon enough.
while i’m gone,
make sure to stay together.
( Phil sighs )
Isabella: 73584 here,
from plant three.
Kids have escaped.
Sound the alarm.
( Alarm blaring )
Emma: They’re already
being alerted.
Ray: What now?
We’re still far from the bridge.
( Male over P.A.) We got
an alert from plant three.
All hands on deck.
There was a fire,
and 15 kids escaped.
Two of them are of top quality.
we are enforcing
maximum security from here on.
Demon: Kill those who aren’t
high-grade if you must,
but, whatever you do,
don’t damage any of their heads.
those who see them
are to capture them immediately.
They cannot get away!
isabella:
Now try and escape, Emma.
♪
Emma: We’re crossing here.
( Ray gasps )
Seriously?
But i’m pretty sure
Norman said...
Norman: That bridge
is our way out.
That’s what most people
would think, anyway,
but you won’t go to the bridge.
And even though
it’s a crazy idea,
you will use the cliff.
I checked the distance
and geographical features.
It’s dangerous, but there’s
a spot that’s crossable.
You have two months to prepare.
Good luck.
( Ray gasps )
( Gilda sighs ) It’ll be okay.
all of us
trained a lot for this.
Ray: You what?
( Don grunts )
( Children murmuring )
( Don grunting )
♪
( Chorus vocalizing )
( Emma gasps )
( Boys gasp )
( Don grunts )
- nat!
- Nat: Got it!
( Children cheering )
- Don: Yeah!
- Emma: Yeah! ( Laughs )
Ray: So then, we’re gonna...
Emma: It’s fine.
The first person
just has to cross.
- ( Ray gasps )
- ( Don grunts )
Ray: What?!
( Chorus vocalizing )
( Ray gasps )
- ( Brush rustles )
- ( Don yelps )
( Children gasp )
( Don grunts )
- ( Children cheering )
- Emma: Yeah!
It worked!
Lannion: Okay! We’re up next!
Ray: Huh?
( Lannion grunts )
Both: Ready. Go!
- Both: We did it!
- ( Children cheer )
Don: All right! We’re all good!
Nat: See you later, ray!
Ray: Wait a second.
- ( Children laughing )
- boys: Yeah!
Ray: When did you
train for this?
- ( Gasps )
- Norman: Well, ray?
( Ray gasps )
( Norman chuckles )
( Ray sighs )
What a smug face.
It’s irritating.
Norman: Just admit it.
We completely fooled you,
didn’t we?
ray: You’ll
"show me something cool,
so shut up and follow," huh?
Norman: And I kept my word.
Look.
We never thought something
like this was possible.
Ray: Yeah. Honestly,
taking everyone seemed
like a pipe dream.
i kinda figured
they’d all just hold us back.
Norman: You weren’t
the only one,
but I made my decision
in the end,
all because of Emma.
Thanks to her, everyone
joined without question.
She’s reckless and naive,
but true to herself.
She can say that we’re taking
everyone without wavering.
you don’t have
to give up, okay, ray?
( Ray gasps )
( Wind blowing )
- Male 2: Not yet.
Isabella: They haven’t
reached the bridge?
male 3: No.
Everyone, keep looking!
Isabella: How strange.
What if...
Don: Just five more!
( Hanger rattling )
Girl: Emma, my hands.
( Emma gasps )
Girl: Uh, sorry.
It’s too scary!
I keep thinking about the cliff!
Boys: Eh?
- ( Both gasp )
- Girl: Wh-what if...
I end up falling?
- ( Boys gasp )
- Lannion: F-falling?
( Girl crying )
( Isabella panting )
( Boys shuddering )
Ray: It’s okay, jemima.
I’ll cross with you.
Emma: Ray.
Ray: Emma...
You still have the rope
we used to get up here, right?
Emma: Oh! Yeah!
ray: All right.
Tie jemima to me with it.
Jemima: Huh?
Emma: You know
how to slide down?
Ray: Seemed easy enough.
What’s wrong, guys?
don’t tell me
that you’re chickening out.
( Both gasp )
Lannion: D-don’t worry!
we’ll be fine!
Thoma: Y-y-yeah! Piece of cake!
( Ray scoffs )
That’s what I thought.
It’s time to go, jemima.
( Young Isabella grunts )
Ray: Come on. Open your eyes.
We’re safe.
Jemima: Huh? Eh?
( Gasps )
( Girl chuckles )
( Jemima chuckles )
Ray: You got me, Norman.
congrats.
( Boys yelling )
Don: All right, Emma!
You’re the last one!
( Emma gasps )
( Children gasp )
( Isabella panting )
( Wind blowing )
Emma: Goodbye to our house.
Goodbye to the home we all
grew up in and loved so much.
And, of course, bye, mom.
Isabella: Please don’t go, Emma.
i don’t want
my darling children to leave.
( Gasps )
( Wind blowing )
( Isabella sighs )
( Wind stops )
( Mandolin playing lullaby )
( Gasps )
- hey!
- ( Boy shrieks )
Isabella!
- ( Isabella grunting )
- ( Boy sighs )
You scared me.
Isabella: Sorry about that.
I was climbing the tree
when I heard
a beautiful song playing, so...
( Boy sighs )
- Isabella: Is it an original?
- Boy: Yeah.
isabella:
It’s a beautiful melody.
Does it have a name?
Boy: Actually, it doesn’t.
Isabella: It’s so good!
Let me hear more of it!
- boy: Huh?
- Isabella: Mm-hmm.
boy: Fine,
but don’t tell anyone else,
’cause it’s embarrassing.
( Isabella grunts )
( Boy chuckles )
( Chuckles )
( Playing melody )
( Melody continues )
♪
( Isabella humming melody )
( Continues humming )
Woman: Starting next year,
i’m putting you in charge
of plant three, Isabella.
Isabella: Yes.
I look forward to it.
( Humming continues )
( Child humming melody )
( Isabella gasps )
( Isabella gasping )
( Stifling sobs )
Ray...
How do you know that song?
( Ray chuckles )
( Isabella gasping )
Ray: Hey, mom...
Why’d you give birth to me?
( Isabella sighs )
( Sighs )
( Isabella humming melody )
Well, ray, I...
Did it to survive...
Longer than anyone.
( Humming continues )
( Sighs )
I guess that’s it, then.
It looks like i’ve lost.
( Woman vocalizing melody )
( Wind blowing )
Run, children, and be careful.
♪
I pray that you can one day
find true happiness and light.
Phil: You’re back.
Isabella: Don’t worry, Phil.
They managed to escape safely.
( Phil gasps )
( Children panting )
Girl: Mom, i’m scared.
Isabella: I’m sorry, everyone.
You must have been
so cold and lonely.
Emma: We did it.
We did it, Norman!
( Woman vocalizing )
Emma: We actually made it
to the outside!
I’ll go back to get the others
as soon as I can.
Today’s a new beginning for us.
( Music ends )
( Wind blowing )
Our very first morning.
( Singing in Japanese )
♪
♪ Fire
( singing in Japanese )