( Singing in Japanese )
♪
♪ Fire
( singing in Japanese )
( Insects chirping )
( Norman sighs )
( Clock ticking )
Isabella: Are you
enjoying it here?
Krone: Oh, of course.
Your children are a delight.
They’re all so intelligent
and very well-behaved.
Isabella: Quite.
And speaking of which,
you’ve been
on your best behavior as well.
Krone: Uh...
- yes.
- ( Isabella chuckles )
It’s good you’re trying
to gain their trust.
you’ve even
played tag with them.
i was worried
you’d be too spontaneous,
but it’s been fine.
( Krone sighs )
Isabella: You’re just insurance.
The only reason I called for you
in the first place
was simply to make sure that
the products were protected.
( Krone grunts )
Isabella: So, you see,
those who know the secret
are not your concern.
All you have to do
is keep working hard,
pretend to be obedient to me,
and laugh about having leverage.
( Krone gasps )
I-I would never...
Isabella: Your sole purpose
for being at this house
is to act as my pawn.
But if you behave...
I’ll award you the mom position
that you so desire.
You have my word.
( Krone gasps )
♪
Now, I know you’re a smart girl,
so try not to make
any more errors.
( Door closes )
( Insects chirping )
( Footsteps approaching )
( Krone sighs )
( Sighs )
( Inhales )
( Growling )
How dare she?
( Grunting )
Just watch! You’ll see!
I’ll drag you down, you witch!
( Grunts )
( Panting )
( Chuckling )
and then,
soon I will be mom here.
- Norman: Emma!
- Emma: Huh?
Norman: We should
start playing tag
- in teams from now on.
- Emma: Why’s that?
Ray: Honestly? Most would die
if they escaped on their own.
Emma: Come on, ray!
Ray: Not to say that they
don’t have some potential,
but we shouldn’t
let them run solo.
Norman: We’ll make formations
and take off in teams.
ray: That way,
we can simulate the real escape.
Emma: The real one?
norman:
I had another idea as well.
- Ray: Hmm?
- Emma: Oh?
Norman: Let’s tell
Don and gilda.
If we get them on our side,
they can be team leaders.
Ray: And what if they turn out
to be mom’s informants?
Norman: Don’t worry.
I’ll basically be killing
two birds with one stone.
Just leave it all to me.
I’ve already made arrangements.
Emma: Ah.
- Ray: Emma.
- Emma: Mm?
ray: Listen up.
Memorize these formations.
There are 100 of them.
Emma: Wait. Do you mean by ear?
Ray: That a problem?
Emma: Easy peasy.
- ( Overlapping chatter )
- Child: ...So much fun.
Ray: The goal here
is to not get caught.
You have ten minutes.
Go!
♪
Emma: Everyone, follow me!
norman:
Let’s surprise ray by winning!
( Children laughing )
Don: We got this in the bag!
♪
( Emma chuckles )
( Phil laughs )
( Ray chuckles )
( Overlapping chatter )
Phil: That was so fun!
Emma: You did pretty amazing
out there, Phil!
Don: Hey, can we do that again?
and, this time,
I want to be the leader.
Gilda: Maybe we should
take a little break first.
Child: Let’s do it again.
Emma: This was a great idea!
I think it’ll work!
Ray: Hmm.
Emma, what’s phil’s score?
Emma: Huh?
His score, huh?
i’m pretty sure
he’s averaging about 203.
Norman: Pretty high.
Ray: When we played tag
with sister and now,
he was one of the last left.
How odd.
Emma: Hmm?
Ray: And, on top of that,
he and Sherry are always
looking for you two.
Emma: Uh...
Hmm. ( Gasps )
( Wails ) Stop it!
I don’t wanna suspect him!
There’s no way!
Ray: You’ve gotta start
being more suspicious
of everyone, you dummy!
This is life or death.
( Emma whimpers )
♪
( Grunts )
( Sighs )
- Norman: Hey, ray.
- ray: Hmm?
Norman: Are you any closer to
breaking the tracking devices?
How much time do you need?
Ray: Let’s see here.
About ten days.
norman: Right.
Then ten days from now.
- Ray: Huh?
- ( Emma gasps )
Norman: That’s when we’ll
break out of this place,
on November 8th.
( Both gasp )
Emma: W-wait!
That’s so soon!
Which is fine, but--
ray: Are you crazy?!
Conny was shipped two weeks ago,
and shipments go out
every two months,
so we should have
a month and a half!
weren’t we
supposed to use that time
to carefully prepare our plan?!
Norman: Yeah. But, see,
you’re only thinking that way
because mom is controlling us
to think that way,
so I say we outwit her.
( Emma gasps )
Ray: We’re likely to fail
if we rush. What then, Norman?
Norman: We need to escape
before winter comes.
Once we break the devices,
we’ll execute the escape plan.
Emma: Then we’ve got a little
over a week to do everything.
( Norman grunts )
( Ray scoffs )
Emma: So let’s talk to Don and
gilda about the plan tonight.
( Insects chirping )
( Footsteps clomping )
♪
( Stairs creaking )
Emma: Please, guys,
just follow my lead.
Ray: Huh?
( Norman grunts )
( Don and gilda gasp )
Don: Hey, Emma! What’s up?
( Gilda sighs )
Don: Human trafficking?
are you sure?
( Gilda gasps )
emma: Yeah.
All of our siblings...
were sold off
to some really bad people.
( Don gasps ) Uh...
( Laughs )
No, no, no! There’s no way!
Come on!
Norman: It explains
the walls and gate
and also why the kids
who get adopted
never send us any letters.
Don: All right, guys.
So what’s the punch line?
You almost had me there
for a second.
( Emma stammers )
Don: Uh, hey...
Why aren’t you guys
saying anything?
Ray: Because it’s true.
Don: What?
Wait, but mom...
Emma: She’s the one...
Who sells us to people.
Don: Huh?! There’s no way
mom would ever do that to us!
Take it back, Emma!
- Gilda: Don.
- Don: Huh?
Gilda: Emma loves mom
and this house
just as much as the rest of us.
Why would she make this up?
( Don gasps )
Emma: So, gilda...
Gilda: To tell the truth,
I did think it was weird.
The night that conny left,
emma and Norman
both went down to the gate.
Don: Wait. You did?
Norman: Yeah.
Gilda: In most cases,
even if you broke the rules,
you’d eventually
come clean about it,
and things
would go back to normal.
But you haven’t done that yet.
( Emma gasps )
( Don gasps )
gilda: Emma,
I wanted to ask about it,
but I always got too scared
to bring it up.
( Crying )
Emma: Oh, gilda,
oh, please don’t cry.
I’m sorry I made you worry.
Gilda: Did you see it happen?
Did you guys see conny being
sold off to the bad people?
- ( Emma grunts )
- Norman: Yeah...
But we didn’t make it in time.
Don: Okay, but is conny safe?
Norman: I don’t know.
( Ray sighs )
Don: Impossible.
This can’t be real!
Norman: I don’t know
if this proves much,
but Emma and ray
spent the last few days
looking into
everyone’s test scores.
Both: Our test scores?
Norman: According to this,
kids over six
are adopted in order
of lowest scores first.
Weird, huh?
Don: So not just conny’s scores,
but hao and ceddy.
Gilda: It’s just
like Norman said.
Emma: Don, gilda...
let’s all escape
so that we can help everyone.
we can do it
if we work together!
Please, help us.
( Don sighs )
( Both grunt )
( Emma chuckles )
( Gasps )
( Ray sighs )
♪
Ray: What was that?
Norman: Not to your liking?
Ray: "So we can help everyone"?
You should have told them
they died!
Norman: We did what we had to
so they’d join us.
Ray: If they end up
not being spies,
then that was a cruel thing
to do to someone.
Conny is dead. You shouldn’t
have given them false hope!
they need the truth.
When are you going to tell them?
Can you?
Norman: Maybe when
the time is right.
We still have to assume
they might be spies,
so then we should lay a trap.
Ray: A trap?
Norman: I’m going to tell them
where the rope is hidden.
( Ray groans )
Norman: I’ll tell Don
that it’s behind my bed.
Gilda will know that it’s
in the second-floor
bathroom’s ceiling,
and at that point
how’s mom gonna find out?
We’ll just have to see.
Ray: Okay, but what if
the ropes are gone
and it turns out that
neither of them are the spy?
Norman: I’ve already
considered that.
Ray: Seems like you’re
prepared for everything.
- Norman: Yeah, I told you.
- ( Ray gasps )
Norman: The key here
is to outwit.
( Ray grunts )
( Children chattering )
Emma: You remember?
It was so fun!
( Gilda giggles )
This is nice, Emma.
it’s been a while
since we talked like this.
emma: Weird, right?
Since we’re always together.
Gilda: Let’s keep it that way,
together forever.
( Emma gasps )
( Giggles )
Yeah.
( Clock ticking )
( Emma gasps )
( Footsteps shuffling )
( Isabella gasps )
( Sighs )
♪
I see.
the rope is
in norman’s bed, is it?
( Krone chuckles )
I’ve been waiting
for you, gilda.
( Emma gasps )
♪
Krone: We can talk now,
can’t we?
( Emma gasps )
Gilda: You mean about...
The issue, right?
( Stammering )
Well, there isn’t an issue!
i appreciate you
checking in on me so much,
but there’s nothing
to worry about.
krone: Are you sure?
I can’t help but be concerned.
Gilda: I feel better, I promise,
so please stop
worrying about me.
- Good night.
- ( Emma gasping )
Krone: Ah, I see now.
Emma told you everything.
Hmm? ( Laughs )
Am I right, gilda?
she told you
all about it, didn’t she?
( Gilda gasping )
( Krone chuckles )
( Emma gasps )
Krone: Ahh!
Too bad. I was really hoping
that we could eventually
become good friends.
( Chuckles ) So tell me.
How many of the others know?
There’s Norman and ray.
Anyone else?
( Gilda gasps )
krone: I will let you
off the hook if you cooperate,
so let’s work together.
♪
Gilda: Please stop this!
( Sighing )
What are you
even talking about?
Emma and I just had a fight,
but we were able to make up,
so everything’s fine now!
( Krone laughs )
well, it appears
that I misunderstood. Sorry.
( Gilda gasps )
Krone: If you think
Emma is lying to you,
feel free to come back
and talk to me.
( Gilda gasps )
Krone: Sweet dreams, gilda.
( Door creaks )
( Clock ticking )
( Gilda gasps ) Emma.
Emma: Gilda.
( Gilda whimpering )
( Krone groans )
I am not giving up.
If I can’t get gilda, then...
thank you
for all your help, Don.
Don: Yeah, no problem!
Gilda: You think
we should be worried?
Emma: It’s time to go.
Mom’s watching.
( Overlapping chatter )
Norman: According to what Emma
told me, we can trust gilda.
I’m curious. Why do you think
the traitor’s betraying us?
Ray: It’s obvious that there’s
gotta be some sort of advantage.
Think about it.
maybe they get spared
from being shipped or something.
( Norman gasps )
Guaranteed survival. Huh.
( Children panting )
Don: Oh, I get it now.
This was all escape training,
wasn’t it?
Emma: 1, 2, 3...
Norman: Emma.
Emma: Eh?
Norman: Can we talk?
I need your thoughts
on something.
Emma: Hmm?
Norman: If there
really is someone here
who’s willingly siding
with the demons
and is guaranteed to live
in exchange
for bits of information--
Emma: You mean that they’re safe
from getting shipped out
- because they’re spying on us?
- Norman: Mm-hmm.
Would you take them with us
or just leave them?
Emma: Hmm.
I’d take them.
( Norman gasps )
Even if they didn’t want that?
Emma: Mm-hmm. I’d force them.
Because if we end up escaping,
then that person’s life
might not be guaranteed anymore.
( Norman gasps )
emma: And plus
I wanna believe in everyone.
i realized that
after what happened with gilda.
Ray said to suspect everyone,
but even if one of us
is helping the demons,
none of our siblings
are truly bad.
We all grew up together!
Even if someone gets in our way
or says i’m naive,
I still wanna believe in them.
Right.
of course
that would be your answer.
♪
( Footstep thumps )
( Ray grunts )
( Norman grunts )
Ray: No rope?
Norman: It’s gone.
Ray: Really?
Well, then, guess it was Don.
( Norman grunts )
Actually, it’s you
who’s the traitor, ray.
( Ray gasps )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )