( Singing in Japanese )
♪
♪ Fire
( singing in Japanese )
Norman: It was a cliff.
Emma: What? Seriously?
Norman: And it wasn’t a height
we can easily jump from.
Krone definitely wasn’t lying,
and the demons
don’t take us lightly.
A cliff like that
needs no security.
( Ray gasps )
Emma: You mean we can’t
use the wall to escape?
- Norman: Well...
- ( Both gasp )
- There is a way.
♪
i ended up going
to the edge of the wall.
It split into two more.
One side still faced the cliff.
the other made up
a side of the house here.
They were both
at 60-degree angles,
and the two walls on the inside
were identical.
- I saw the same scenery ahead.
- ( Ray gasps )
( Norman grunts )
so basically
what i’ve learned from this
is that the house
is on a hexagonal property
surrounded by a cliff.
( Emma gasps )
Norman: And the lot
that’s directly west
of where we are in plant three
is likely the headquarters.
It was the only lot
with a bridge.
Since we can’t escape
by using the wall,
that bridge is our way out.
( Knock on door )
( All gasp )
phil: Norman!
Mom’s calling for you!
Norman: Tell her
i’ll be right there.
Phil: Okay.
( Door closes )
( Both sigh )
Norman: Well,
I should get going.
- Ray: Hey, just wait a minute!
- Emma: Norman!
Norman: Here. I didn’t use it.
( Ray gasps )
Seriously? ( Growls )
You were gonna come back
from the start, weren’t you?!
You said we’d survive together,
but, this whole time,
you were planning--
Norman: Yeah. Sorry. I lied.
( Both shudder )
Norman: I can’t risk
making any mistakes,
’cause I can’t let you die.
The plan might be ruined
if I run,
and that would be
a problem for me.
I don’t even want
a chance of losing.
You can’t change my mind.
i’ve decided.
( Ray shuddering )
Norman: So I did
what I could today.
I’m leaving the rest to you.
Make sure the escape succeeds.
Emma: Now, wait a second--
Norman: You’re warm.
Thanks, you guys.
Because of you two,
I had a good life.
I had fun.
I was happy.
I was fortunate.
( Ray crying )
No.
You can’t.
Damn it!
Emma: Hey, Norman,
it’s not too late to run.
Just go hide in the forest.
( Norman chuckles )
It’s like I already said,
i made my choice.
( Emma gasps )
Norman: Goodbye.
( Door closes )
( Clock ticking )
( Chuckles )
♪
( Child coughing )
Isabella: Another cold.
No snowball fights for you.
( Norman sighs )
( Wood clatters )
child:
Norman can’t play anymore?
Isabella: Not until
he gets better,
which means
I don’t want any of you
in the infirmary
for a while, understand?
Children: Yes, mom!
( Norman sighs )
Emma: Boo!
Norman: E-Emma!
- Emma: I came to visit.
- ( Norman coughs )
Yeah, but mom said not to.
Emma: I know she did,
but you’re all by yourself
when you get sick like this.
I thought you might be lonely.
( Norman gasps )
Emma: I’ll do the talking
so you don’t have to.
is that okay?
Norman: You can’t stay here.
You’ll catch my cold!
- Emma: That isn’t true!
- Norman: Huh?
emma: I was told
i’ll never, ever get sick!
Norman: Hmm?
- ( Isabella sighs ) Emma?
- ( Emma gasps )
Isabella: When did
you sneak in here?
careful,
or you’ll get sick, too.
Emma: Don’t worry, mom.
Ray said that i’d be fine.
Isabella: What?
ray: This book said
that idiots don’t get sick.
( Isabella sighs )
- Regardless...
- ( Emma gasps )
Isabella: You can’t
be in here, Emma.
You can play with him
once he’s better.
Do you understand?
Isabella: Yes, mom.
- ( Door closes )
- ( Norman sighs )
( Kids chattering outside )
( Norman sighs )
( Sighs )
( Gasps )
Emma: I’m back!
( Norman yelps )
( Coughs )
Emma, you can’t be--
Emma: Here. For you.
Norman: Huh?
A cup?
Emma: Ray taught me
how to make it.
- Isn’t it cool?
- Isabella: Oh, Emma...
You really don’t know
when to give up, do you?
Emma: He said we’d be able
to talk using the string phone!
( Norman gasps )
Emma: Are you there?
Emma: Norman, can you hear me?
( Norman chuckles )
Yeah, loud and clear.
( Emma laughs ) Ray!
How cool! Now we can talk even
though i’m out here! Hooray!
Ray: You know, if you
keep yelling like that,
you won’t even need
the string phone.
Emma: Oh, you’re right.
( Laughs )
( Norman laughs )
( Laughter fades )
- ( Door opens )
- ( Norman gasps )
( Door closes )
( Chuckles )
Thanks for waiting, mom.
Isabella: Sure.
Now let’s get going.
- ( Overlapping chatter )
- Isabella: Everyone’s waiting.
Child: I’m gonna miss you.
( Girl crying ) Norman!
Norman: Sherry,
please don’t cry.
You should say goodbye
with a smile, okay?
Sherry: ’kay. ( Giggles )
- Phil: Norman.
- Norman: Phil.
Do me a big favor,
and take care of Emma.
Child 2: I’ll miss you so much.
Phil: Uh-huh.
Isabella: Emma, where’s ray?
Emma: The infirmary.
He said he didn’t want
to say goodbye.
Isabella: I see.
- Norman: Don, gilda...
- both: Eh?
Norman: Take care
of Emma and ray, okay?
Don: You got it.
Leave it to us.
Norman: Emma...
All the rest is up to you.
It’s been fun, everyone.
i’ll miss you.
- ( Children chattering )
- Child 3: Write us, ’kay?
- Child 4: Thank you.
- Child 5: Bye, Norman!
- child 6: Bye!
- Child 7: I’ll miss you!
( Emma gasps )
Norman, wait!
( Silence )
♪
Norman: Emma.
- Emma: I’ll distract mom...
- ( Norman gasps )
Emma: So, please, run away.
( Norman gasps )
♪
( Grunts )
( Thumping )
( Gilda gasps )
( Children murmur )
( Norman gasps )
Look, I know you’re reckless,
but this is crossing the line!
This isn’t what you
should be doing right now!
Emma: Shut up! You can’t go!
( Norman gasps )
- Children: Aww.
- Girl: What’s wrong?
( Both gasp )
Norman: Why can’t
you understand, Emma?
i didn’t ask you to help
keep me from leaving this place.
All I want is a nice goodbye,
so please respect that.
Emma: No! That’s the one thing
I won’t do for you,
especially if you
don’t really want this!
♪
( Ray crying )
You’re crazy. You know that?
You’re so reckless,
naive, and immature,
but you’re true to yourself.
Honestly, that’s why I...
( Woman vocalizing )
( Emma gasps )
Isabella: It’s time, Norman.
( Norman chuckles ) Okay.
( Emma gasps ) No, wait!
Isabella: Emma,
there no need to yell.
I get that you’ll miss him,
but you’re being stubborn.
Keep causing trouble,
and i’ll kill you.
Just give up.
Norman: Before we go, mom,
can I say
my last goodbye to her?
Isabella: Oh, yes, of course.
Hear that, Emma?
( Vocalizing continues )
- Norman: Emma.
- Emma: Huh?
Norman: Thanks a lot.
Emma: Yeah.
Norman: Sorry I tricked you.
Norman: Make sure to heal up.
( Emma grunts )
Norman: And don’t be reckless.
Emma: ’kay.
Norman: Stay healthy.
Emma: Yeah.
Norman: It’s up to you.
Emma: Right.
Norman: It’ll be okay.
Don’t ever give up.
( Emma crying )
( Vocalizing continues )
( Norman chuckles )
( Door creaks )
( Children murmuring, crying )
( Gilda and Don gasp )
Gilda: Emma!
( Vocalizing ends )
Isabella: Your suitcase
is empty, isn’t it?
Norman: Well, for the most part.
No matter what’s in there,
it’s not like I can take it.
Isabella: You would
never run from here.
i knew that
from the very beginning.
rest assured,
you’re doing the right thing.
ray and Emma
can be shipped maturely now.
Norman: They’ll live
happily inside this house
until the very end, huh?
Isabella: Yes, just as intended.
( Norman gasps )
Hey, mom, are you happy?
( Isabella gasps )
( Lantern creaking )
Yes.
Yes, I am.
after all,
I was able to meet you.
( Chain clanking )
( Wind blowing )
( Footsteps echoing )
( Ray shudders )
- Isabella: Over here.
- Norman: Huh?
isabella: Please wait
in this room for a little while.
( Door creaking )
( Norman gasps )
( Door closes )
( Bell tolling )
Isabella: Good morning to you,
my darling children.
Now let us appreciate
that all 37 of you
are able to live happy lives
under this roof.
Thank you for the food.
children:
Thank you for the food!
( Children laughing )
Norman: Emma!
( Emma gasps )
- Boy: Huh?
- Phil: Hmm?
( Birds squawking )
( Fizzing )
- Children: Yeah!
- Boy: Whoa!
That one flew up real high!
( Laughing )
( Girl laughs )
( Birds squawking )
Phil: Emma looks sad again.
I’ve never seen her
look like that.
Gilda: Yeah.
Don: Me, either.
Boy 2: And it’s not just Emma.
Boy 1: Ray, too.
Boy 2: They seem so depressed.
Phil: They’re lonely
without Norman.
Boy 1: Well, the three of them
were really good friends.
( Don and gilda sigh )
Ray: So? What is it?
Don: We should start deciding
what we’re gonna do,
I mean, for our sake.
- Ray: Whatever.
- All: Huh?
Ray: Who cares?
Let’s just die here.
( All gasp )
ray: The cliffs
make it impossible to escape,
and the only bridge
is attached to headquarters.
Plus, i’m tired,
really tired.
( Both gasp )
Emma: Here. It’s yours.
Ray: Keep it. I don’t need it.
If you wanna escape,
then do it.
Sorry, Emma. I’m out.
( Emma gasps )
Gilda: Emma.
- ( Gasping )
- ( Door opens )
- ( Door closes )
- ( Don grunts )
Ray! Come on!
- Ray: Sorry.
- Both: Huh?
Ray: Gilda, Don, sorry.
( Both sigh )
( Crutches clatter )
( Thump )
( Emma sobbing )
♪
( Gasps )
Isabella: I did knock, you know.
Didn’t you hear it?
( Emma grunts )
( Isabella sighs )
You poor thing.
i can tell
you’re in pain and suffering.
Norman is dead,
ray has lost hope,
and you can’t do any of this
on your own.
You must be so despaired,
knowing you’ll never
be able to escape.
( Emma gasps )
( Crying )
Isabella: You should
have listened to me.
the best way for you
to end all of your suffering
is to give up,
so stop resisting. It’s easy.
You’ll feel better. I promise.
( Emma gasps )
Isabella: Hear me out,
emma, please.
I’ve been thinking about it,
and I would like
to recommend you
as the next mom candidate
for this farm.
Emma: A mom candidate?
Isabella: That’s right.
If you become an adult
and give birth,
then prove your abilities,
you can return to this house
and watch over it
as a mom or sister.
You have the right
to that option.
So, if you’re at all interested,
- I would love to recommend you.
- ( Emma gasps )
Isabella: I’m sure
you’re thinking,
"who would accept that offer?"
but what else
can you do to stop this?
It’s over. You have nothing.
Death awaits you.
You’ll continue suffering.
Live and strive to become a mom.
accept despair,
and free yourself of pain.
Emma: No. I refuse to do that.
Isabella: Fine, then.
You can writhe in agony
as you await your end.
You’ll never be able to escape.
You’ll come to realize it
sooner or later.
( Emma gasps )
( Crying )
( Rain pattering )
Girl: All done!
( Children laugh )
( Birds chirping )
( Boy panting )
- ( Overlapping chatter )
- boy: Ha ha!
( Chatter and laughter )
( Don and gilda gasp )
Phil: Emma.
( Both sigh )
( Clock ticking )
♪
( Ray humming a tune )
( Continues humming )
Emma: Ray.
( Clock ticking )
what are you
doing in here this late?
Ray: It’s my last chance
to say bye to the house.
emma: Oh.
Your birthday’s tomorrow, right?
ray: Yeah.
Tonight’s my last night,
and then I say goodbye.
Hey, Emma, did you give up
like mom told us to?
You haven’t actually given up
on running away, have you?
♪
( Emma chuckles )
( Singing in Japanese )