Huh? A movie?
Yeah.
I was planning to go
with an old friend,
so I thought I'd splurge
and treat us to
some reserved seats,
but then the person
cancelled at the last minute.
So what you're saying is...
just you and me?
Yeah!
Oh, but then
I'm sure you still have
to study even though you
don't have prep school, right?
No, I can go!
I mean, everything's
totally fine with me,
but it's just that
we'd be going alone,
if that's alright with you?
Is that a bad thing?
Oh no, not at all;
I mean as long as you're OK.
Oh really? Great! I'm so glad!
Here.
Okay, tomorrow it is,
and I'll meet you at eleven
in front of the movie theater!
Yeah, sure.
So... I guess that means...
A date?!
This is actually a date!
But, wait a sec...
This town is empty after all.
Every "person" is with "it."
They never awaken
from the fun dreams
they have with "it".
The time spent
with "it" are dreams.
Times so wonderful,
they feel just like dreams.
"It" will grant any
wish "people" have,
and behave however
"people" want it to.
"It" is not a "person,"
so "it" can become
a "person's" dream.
But, "it" has one thing
that "it" cannot do.
"It" cannot become a "person."
"It" can take a
"person's" place,
but never become a "person."
That is something
that "I" know very well.
"I" know, because "I" am "me."
I'm home, Chi!
Welcome home.
I'm sorry Chi,
but I need to ask Shinbo
something right now.
I'll be right back.
Shinbo? Hey, are you home?
Chi?
Tips, for a date?
Yeah, like the ones they
have in the magazines,
you know what I mean.
What girls like,
and what they hate,
where they wanna go,
the best outfit,
what kind of underwear.
Things like that.
That's a good one.
Well, from my
experience, first...
Tell me.
The first thing you want to do
is do something about
your messed up hair.
Regardless of what
anybody says about it,
appearance is important.
Do something with hair.
When you're out on the date,
you've gotta compliment
her on her outfit.
Got it?
Like you really mean it!
Compliment her on her outfit.
Right, next step...
Get yourself a single red rose,
bite down on it
sideways like this,
and with a light tango step,
you do a one-handed handstand!
Single-handed handstand,
tangoing, and then?
It was a joke!
Huh?
Are you for real?
Does that mean you've never
had a date with a girl before?
So that means you're a virgin?
You think that's a problem?
No, it's just that now I see
why you're panicking like this.
But don't get all worked up,
there's only one foolproof
tip for a good date.
What is it?!
Just relax and act as much
like your regular self
as you possibly can.
Huh?
See, people just,
no matter how much
they might want to
change their personalities,
they can't be reprogrammed
like computers can.
Whatever happens is gonna
happen anyway, right?
And besides, don't you think
it's sorta rude to her
to be a different person
just because you're on a date?
That's true, but I-
Great. So just be yourself,
and see if you can
lose that old virginity.
Right.
But don't call me a virgin!
Be my regular self, huh...
Yeah, but while I'm at it,
it really wouldn't hurt to do
a little something with my hair.
Okay, how's that look?
Great, the teeth
are nice and clean.
Alright, that's not bad.
Handkerchief, wallet,
tissues, pocket map,
dating guide, antacids in
case of a sudden stomachache...
Okay, that should
just about do it.
I don't think I've
forgotten anything!
Hideki forgot something.
Huh?
Hideki forgot magazine.
Ah, no, I don't think I'm
going to be needing that, Chi.
Chi?
An entire day. Just Yumi and me.
It's still a little
early to get going,
but I really don't
want to be late!
Hideki looks happy.
Oh?
Is that how I looked?
Prep school makes you happy?
No, it isn't that.
I actually don't
have any classes
at prep school today, Chi.
I'm going out with
a girl from work.
Out with girl?
Well I know I said
I was going out,
but since it's
just the two of us,
I guess you'd say it's
really more like a date.
A "date"?
Chi doesn't understand.
Oh. Let's see...
It's when two people,
who are attracted
to each other,
get together and do stuff.
Attracted?
It means to like someone.
Well, I gotta go.
That means...
Hideki likes... this girl?
Huh?
Oh.
I wouldn't say "like,"
but she's a really great girl!
Okay. Well, gotta go.
Take care of yourself.
Oh, hello.
Are you going out by
yourself today, Mr. Motosuwa?
That's right.
I actually have
an errand to run.
Will Chi be staying home?
Well yeah.
Oh... Does it look
weird or something?
No.
Well, see ya later!
Take care.
"I" begin my search once more
for the "one"
who's only for "me."
The "person" who will love "me"
because "I" am who "I" am.
The "person" who
will still love "me,"
even if "I" cannot
grant his dreams.
But...
Is there such a
"person" out there?
I hope there is.
Will he love "me" and only "me"?
Will he really not
seek anything from "me"?
If he can't love "me"
for being "me",
then he is not
the "one" for "me."
Really?
Really.
There really is someone?
Yes.
Then, where is he?
I'm sure he is
really close to "me."
Not so far away.
There must be someone
that "I" can fall in love with.
Chi.
That's strange.
Isn't this where she said?
Senpai!
I'm sorry I'm late.
I don't know what happened.
No, I just happened
to get here a little early.
In fact, you're
right on time. See?
Huh?
Oh, you're right!
Huh.
Look at that I wonder
how my watch got so fast?
Geez, I didn't expect that!
Yeah, all that
hurrying for nothing.
Oh, I suppose.
But then again,
it all worked out,
because at least I didn't make
you have to wait too long.
To think: my first date,
and such a cute girl, too.
Life couldn't get any better!
By the way, Senpai,
isn't your hair a
little different today?
Yeah, um , is it weird?
No, it's nice.
I think it makes you
look more mature.
But if you ask me,
I kinda prefer it the
way you usually have it.
Oh, really?
Oh no, wait; please don't
do that on my account.
Oh, that's all right.
Believe me, I feel more
comfortable like this, anyway.
Do you mind...
if I hold onto your arm?
Huh?
I don't... want to
go home tonight.
What am I gonna do with her
if the whole thing
ends up like that?
Maybe I should take
her home anyway,
and tell her that her
father's gonna be worried
if she stays out
too late with me.
But wait, when a girl's
asserting herself that much.
And you're on a date...
Oh, I don't know!
Senpai, is something wrong?
Huh? Oh no, nothing at all.
But...
What if that "person"
doesn't love "me"?
What if he falls for
someone other than "me"?
A "person's" heart can't be
erased or copied like "it."
That's why it's hard to change
what a "person" has chosen.
I know.
A "person's" heart
may be easy to change,
but some cannot
be changed at all.
Feelings of love are
especially hard to change.
So, what would you do?
Then, "I" will have to decide.
Decide, and act upon it.
"I" will, with the other "me."
Chi hears it again.
It's calling now for Chi.
Who is it?
It's me.
Close your eyes.
I'll send you a vision.
Chi.
Is it "you" who
is calling to me?
Yes. "I" am the one
calling for "you."
Why do you have
the same face as Chi?
Because "I" am "you."
Chi doesn't understand.
All your data is gone, isn't it?
Tell me. Who is at
"your" side right now?
Hideki. It was Hideki
who found Chi.
Chi? Is that your new name?
"Chi" is Chi's name.
Hideki gave Chi this name.
Is Hideki "the 'one' for 'me'"?
The "one" for "me"?
The "one" who will
love "me" and only "me."
I don't know.
Chi only knows things
Hideki taught her
after she woke up.
I see.
Then it's true: you really
have forgotten everything.
But, "I" still remember.
About "us."
About what "we" will decide.
Chi, "we" are now
connected again.
From now on, whatever
"you" see, do, or know.
Everything will come to "me."
"We" are together.
Always together.
I'll see you soon, Chi.
Wow. Boy, that's
really something.
Well, I felt I really should
put in a little extra effort,
Senpai, since I was
making them for you.
How 'bout a little coffee?
Oh, thanks.
Geez, going out to see a movie
with Yumi, and
then getting treated
to a homemade lunch
in the park, too.
Oh man, am I one
lucky guy, or what?
I'm sorry I'm late!
Hi. Alright then, you
can do the shopping now.
And when you're finished,
you can take it all
back to the house.
Yes, I understand.
Hey, so what do you want to eat?
I'm starving!
How 'bout ramen?
You're kidding... again?!
No, I found this new place.
It's really good.
Are you worried about something?
Huh?
What's that?
Chi, I mean.
That's her name, isn't it?
Isn't that your Persocom?
Now that you mention it
I guess I'm a little worried,
'cause she still can't do
much on her own yet.
But... she's cute, right?
Well, yeah... sorta.
I guess I'm a little jealous.
Huh?
It's just that Persocoms
are always so cute.
I wonder if you might start
to prefer Persocoms
more than people.
More than people?
But they're computers!
Of course, they're incredibly
cute and all that...
But they're...
They're what?
Humans are entirely different.
You think so?
Yeah.
I'm sorry.
That must have sounded strange.
Do you want to go out on a boat?
I'll pay for the rental
to make up for things.
Huh? That's all right.
Let me pay.
But I...
You already got the tickets
and made lunch for me.
At least let me do that. Okay?
Okay.
Senpai, isn't that hard work?
No, it's not very hard at all,
in fact, it feels really good.
Huh?
Is something wrong?
Isn't that Minoru, over there?
Hey!
I guess he can't hear me.
Senpai, watch out,
that's dangerous!
Hey!
Senpai!
Oh?
It's cold.
Are you all right?
Oh sure, I'm fine.
But you look so cold like that.
I know, I can go buy
you some new socks
and shoes so you won't be
wet for the rest of the day.
Yumi, hold on!
You don't have to do that!
I can accompany her
and guide her
to the nearest
appropriate store.
Oh, okay.
Go ahead. That's fine.
Right.
That girl is human, isn't she?
Huh? Yumi? Why, of course.
Why do you ask?
I'm glad.
Huh?
I say that because you
have such a cute Persocom.
I was worried you'd
become so engrossed with her,
it would blind you
to anything else
and you'd lose
interest in humans.
Even you, Minoru?
Are you thinking the same thing?
The same thing?
That's exactly
what Yumi said to me.
That I might find
myself beginning
to prefer Persocoms
to actual people.
And, what did you say to that?
Well, a Persocom is
different from a human.
That's right.
I should know that...
that computers...
are different from people.
When you say that,
do you mean Yuzuki?
What?
Oh, I don't mean
to pry or anything.
You don't have to talk about
it if you don't want to.
But you know, Minoru,
you do act a little differently
towards Yuzuki than the others.
Mr. Motosuwa, people often refer
to you as a
nice guy, don't they?
Huh? Well, I suppose.
But then, you're the
type who ends up...
the guy they like,
but not as a boyfriend.
Don't say that!
Yuzuki is...
a Persocom I made to
resemble my older sister,
who died from an
illness two years ago.
Not just her appearance either,
but as much personality
data as I could input.
All my sister's habits
that I could remember,
what she hated,
what she loved...
Every memory of
my sister that I could find.
That's why Yuzuki is
just like my older sister.
So perfect... a resemblance...
Minoru...
But, no matter how
similar she may be,
it's nothing more
than a program.
And I know that
better than anyone,
because I'm the
one who made her.
But then, there are times
when I just want to forget that.
That Yuzuki is only a Persocom.
So then...
When we first met,
and you told me
to be careful not to fall
in love with a Persocom.
Yes.
That advice came
from my own experience.
Was I too intrusive?
Oh no, I didn't mean
anything like that.
Oh, that's okay.
I'm sorry...
I never seem to know what
to say at a time like this.
That's because you
really are a nice guy.
By the way,
I wish you all the best
on losing your
virginity Mr. Motosuwa.
Oh, thanks.
Hey, wait a minute!
How did you find
out about that?!
I got an e-mail from
Mr. Shinbo last night,
in a font 6 times normal size.
That little...
Why did he hafta...
Seems like fun.
Yeah.
I'm jealous of you, Miss Yuzuki.
Huh?
Senpai!
See you later.
So pretty.
Senpai?
There are times when he
just wants to forget about it.
Huh?
Huh? Yumi?
I'm home, Chi!
Welcome home.
Chi.
Hideki, welcome home.
Oh.
I'm home, Chi.
With bated breath,
I listened intently.
Yes, for some reason,
it wasn't after me anymore.
Somehow, I'd managed to escape.
With a sigh of relief,
I looked up into the sky,
and there was the living head
of a man floating
in mid-air, smiling!
Hideki? Hideki?
Next episode of Chobits:
"Chi Confirms."
It's alive. It's alive!