It's hot.
I always heard summers were
a lot hotter down here,
but I didn't think
it'd be this bad.
It's not supposed to be
this hot right after
the rainy season.
Air conditioning.
Huh?
Hideki... no energy.
Are you sick?
Don't worry.
It's not like I'm sick;
it's just summer fatigue.
Summer fatigue?
Yeah, it's when the
heat totally drains you.
Hideki... no energy.
You could say that.
Well now I'm just wasting time.
At least it's air conditioned
at the prep school.
I can always go
in a little early
and try and get some work done.
Hideki.
Huh?
Do your best!
Yeah!
Why's it have to be like this?
They said that
they'll be all done
with the air conditioning
repairs in no time,
and that they'll have it
running by the next class,
so let's just get
through this hour!
Geez... What a bunch
of lightweights.
Okay, how about this?
I think it's time for a
little class participation.
I'll ask you a question,
and then you just answer it;
if you get it right,
then I'll treat
everyone to snow cones!
Wow, really?
You serious?
I want strawberry!
Huh?
Hold your horses,
I said if you could
answer my question first.
So I'll choose one person
as a representative
to answer it now.
So, let's see. Well... Motosuwa!
Huh?!
Everyone's counting on you!
Do your best!
Take a look in your
textbook at page 25,
question number three.
Uh, let's see.
This is...
Uh.
Something I don't know.
Aw man, no snow cones.
Oh, you're hopeless.
It's rudimentary.
All right then, anyway
I think the best way
to explain this
one would probably be
for me to use an
example like this.
Huh?
Now in this case,
you'll often find that
they use this form--
You're late.
Oh man, it's hot in here.
Yeah.
The air conditioning's broken.
Oh!
So I guess you're the
one who broke it then?
Why me?!
'Cuz you look depressed,
that's all.
Well, there's been
a lot going on.
Huh.
Hey, by the way,
do you have any
spare time today?
Yeah, a little before work.
Well, I'd like to
look at your notes
from English class
if that's alright with you.
I'll treat you to
lunch if you want.
Okay, that's cool.
I can't believe how
terrible your handwriting is.
Y-You think so?
What's this letter
here that looks like
an upside-down musical note?
Huh?
Oh, that's a "U."
You call that a "U"?
Come on, my handwriting
might not be great,
but I'm sure the
notes are still good.
Hm-hm...
Hey, Sumomo.
Aye!
I'd like you to translate
the English textbook for me,
starting with the sixth line
on page one-fifty-eight.
Roger, I understand!
Whether weakness should be
placed among the
causes of happiness
or among the
causes of unhappiness,
may perhaps be regarded
as a doubtful question.
It's just as I thought.
That's good, Sumomo.
Aye!
Hey, you got this all wrong.
What? Are you sure?
Sumomo is a
smart little Persocom.
Huh?
Oh, no, not really.
Sumomo's had English translation
software installed in her.
Huh, I didn't know
you could do that.
She can even give
sample problems;
it's very handy.
Wow.
Would you like to borrow her?
Huh?
I'd like to return
the favor for the notes,
so you could take her for a day.
No, I don't think so.
Huh?
You know how it is.
It's just that I'd rather
do it on my own, that's all.
Working with a computer
is just so different.
But thanks a lot anyway.
Oh, I see.
Time for me to go to work.
You can hold onto the notes,
just give 'em back to me later.
Well, thanks for the meal.
Hey, Motosuwa.
Hm?
In Miss Shimizu's class today,
did she say anything about
what she was going
to do tomorrow?
Huh? No, not really.
Oh, okay...
Well, see you later!
See ya.
I'm home.
Hideki, welcome home.
Oh, it's so hot.
Huh?
Oh, where'd you get that?
The manager brought it over.
She said to put it here.
I see.
That takes me back;
getting a whiff of that makes
me feel like summer's here.
Summer?
This is summer?
No, no.
I'm talking about the seasons.
The hot season is summer,
the cold season is winter,
and the warm season is-
Huh?
Who could that be
at this time of night?
Yes, who is it?
Well, good evening! It's me.
It's me!
What nerve, how could
you forget me?!
I'm sorry!
I apologize;
I didn't mean anything.
It's not like I forgot
you or, I was distracted.
The summer, well a memory
of summer, that's...
I'm not taking you for granted,
it's just, that
I'm serious, I was just-
Did I surprise you?
Huh?
M-Miss Shimizu!
What is it? I don't get it.
What are you doing
here so late at night?
Can I stay over?
Huh?
Stay over? Stay over?
So, this is what
Motosuwa's place is like.
Uh, she's fast!
It certainly feels like
a guy's room, all right.
Why are you doing
inside already?!
Hmm?
Oh, I see, so you
really ARE a guy.
Hm?
Hey, you don't have to
do that; I don't mind.
Yeah, great; well I do mind!
Hm...
Huh?
Chi!
Let's see, wasn't
your name "Chi"?
Chi?
Good evening.
Oh, that's great:
you got it right this time!
Good girl!
Now we're gonna get
down and drink tonight!
Hey, wait a minute,
how'd we get to
that all of a sudden?
Why, you've been
drinking already!
So, are you done cleaning up?
Yes, finally.
Hey, don't change the subject!
What are you up to?
What do you mean "stay over"?!
You mean I can't?
Well, it's not that you can't...
It's, well, it's more like
it's just not the
best idea in the world.
I guess there's no choice then.
If that's the way
you're gonna be.
I guess I'll just have
to spend the night
somewhere else.
What are you thinking?
That's even worse!
So, then you'll
let me stay here?
If anything happens,
it won't be my fault.
Motosuwa,
are you going to do
something with me?
No, I mean...
You really are a
nice guy. Aren't you?
Are you really going
to drink all this, ma'am?
Of course I am. Why do you ask?
Okay, so tell me this one:
Chi, what's that up there?
The moon! Hideki taught me that!
Good! And what do
you call that shape?
Chi.
It's a smiling moon!
Oh, she's so cute!
So anyway, what
I really wanted to do
was teach elementary school.
Elementary school?
So you really wanted to be
an elementary school teacher?
Yeah, as a matter of fact.
But then my husband...
He kept saying
that the work I had
to put in to teach all those
little kids would make it
so I wouldn't have
time for anything else.
Huh, your husband.
Huh?
Did what you just say
mean that you're married?!
Yeah, for the time being.
Uh, for the time being?
Hey, Motosuwa?
Yeah?
Do you find
Persocoms attractive?
Is it more fun to be
with a Persocom
than with a human?
But Ma'am, I...
Motosuwa, that look on
your face is so funny!
What's so funny about it?
Five, six, seven, eight, nine,
t-ten!
Wow, amazing!
Is Hideki all right?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Could you get off me?
Chi.
Uh, ma'am?
What do you say we just
stop and call it a draw?
Why?
Follow The King's a great game!
What's the matter,
aren't you having any fun?
I'm the one who keeps
getting ordered around,
so it's not much fun.
It's not my fault;
it's the luck of the draw.
Chi?
Now, onto the next round!
Come on, don't be chicken.
Here ya go: draw!
And you can play, too, Chi.
Chi.
And...
Who shall be the King?!
Me!
Chi?
Okay, let's see.
Whatta ya say we
try to, I don't know,
get a little excitement going?
Excitement?
Number 2: it's time to...
Kiss the king.
K-Kiss?!
Now, number 2, raise your hand!
W-What number was I?
What a relief that is;
yet somehow it's a letdown.
Wait, that means she's gonna...
All right, Chi, time to smooch!
Smooch!
No! Don't do it!
You again.
Oh, hold your tongue;
the king's the absolute monarch,
and subjects need to submit.
Ma'am, it's just...
you're glaring at me.
It's time for the king,
ready or not, Chi.
Close your eyes.
Chi.
Oh, she's just the cutest thing.
I'll just leave it at that;
after all, she is
Motosuwa's Persocom.
Try to keep the
surprises to a minimum.
Chi?
Huh?
Hideki, lots of
energy down here.
Huh?
Yes, well, uh, it's just...
Hmm...
It's not like I was thinking
about anything perverted,
it's just, well,
you know, it's just that...
Hideki.
It's not that I...
Huh?
Miss Shimizu...
she just fell down.
Huh?
Miss Shimizu?
I hope there's nothing wrong.
Huh?
Oh, that's right, I fell asleep.
Motosuwa.
Huh?
Miss Shimizu?
Shh...
You'll wake Chi up.
Huh?
Motosuwa...
Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh?
It was a dream.
But it was so realistic.
Mm...
Huh?
Morning already?
Chi.
M-Miss Shimizu...
in her lingerie...
just like in my dream.
That's impossible.
Oh, good morning, Chi.
Chi.
Huh?
Hideki, face is all wet.
Well, that attire of yours...
Attire?
Oh, don't worry about it,
I didn't take advantage you.
Take advantage of me?
It's better if it's
with the one you
love the first time.
Don't worry, Motosuwa,
you're still pure.
It was just a little hot,
so I took off my clothes.
Same as you, Motosuwa.
Me?!
It's too late for that.
I saw it all.
All?
It was average size.
No!
Average size. Hideki is average.
Chi! You don't
have to learn that!
Chi.
Is it okay if I use your sink?
S-Sure.
But don't you need a
toothbrush or anything?
Got one of those right here.
I sort of knew I was going to be
spending the night out.
Huh?
You mean you knew
that you'd stay here?
Of course not.
Then, why are you here?
Because I'm just
a coward, I guess.
Well, Chi, see you later.
Time for me to go too. Bye, Chi.
Take care of yourselves.
I'll be going now.
Oh, that's right...
I wonder if Shinbo left already.
Motosuwa, we'll be late.
Okay!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
Good morning, Mr. Motosuwa.
Good morning.
Oh, hello.
I believe we met at
the beach last week.
Huh? Uh, well, this is, uh...
Yes, I remember;
I'm Takako Shimizu.
Oh, so you teach
at the prep school.
Well, that's great:
you must have been able
to get a lot of
studying done last night.
Well, actually, you know...
Yes.
Huh?
T-That's right.
Well, I'm very
glad to hear that.
Hey, come on,
what's with all the heavy sighs?
I wonder if she misunderstood.
Are you still
worried about that?
Well, don't be.
If you're that concerned,
I'll just go talk to her.
I wouldn't want to mess
up your private life.
I'm sure you don't want
anyone to think we're dating.
What are you talking about?
Aren't you the one
who should be worried?
I mean you're the one
who's married, right?
I see.
Well, that's true.
Miss Shimizu?
I don't know what it is that's
bothering you so much,
but it certainly seems
to be something.
I just want to say that
if you ever need someone
to talk about anything,
I'll always be happy to listen.
Motosuwa.
It's just like they say,
you really are a nice guy,
even if you are a virgin.
Wha--?!
Why'd ya say that?!
What's that gotta
do with anything?
Oh, man, I'm tired.
Shinbo.
Shinbo, Shinbo!
Mm?
What's the matter?
Did you come to
class early today?
Huh?! Shinbo!
Huh?
You're a wreck.
Were you up all night?
Uh...
Oh, well, sorta...
Hmm...
You don't look so hot yourself.
Well, to tell you the truth,
last night, outta nowhere,
Miss Shimizu came to my room.
W-What?!
Geez, what the
heck's wrong with you?!
You don't have to yell. Huh?
Good morning, everyone!
Good morning!
Alright, please take your seats.
Time for class.
Oh, my notes.
Hey Shinbo, you got my...?
Oh?
What's with him?
Alright, everybody,
let's get started.
Okay, let's take out our
textbooks and open to page 26.
Miss Shimizu?
I'm exhausted.
Today was not the greatest day.
First, Shinbo
gets all weird in class
and won't talk to me,
and then I can't stop
thinking about it all night,
so I made all those
mistakes at work.
Huh?
And now, rain.
I'm going straight to bed.
Don't cry.
I'm not crying.
Really? Then why
is my chest so wet?
It's the rain;
what else will it be?
Can't you even be a
little bit honest, Takako?
I'm not honest!
I'm not attractive, either!
Yes, you are.
You're very attractive.
Tremendously attractive.
Look what I did;
I got makeup all over you.
That doesn't matter.
Just be quiet for a bit.
But why?
When women cry,
they just look so vulnerable.
All women?
You're the best, Takako.
I'm afraid someone
might be watching.
I don't care.
I told you, I've already
made my decision.
A person who teaches
at a prep school
is the instructor.
The people who study there
are the prep school students.
The prep school instructor
is Miss Shimizu,
and Miss Shimizu was locked in
an embrace with a
prep school student.
And that prep school
student is Shinbo.
Miss Shimizu is a married woman.
Shinbo is my friend,
and I, well I just...
Chi, what do you
think I should do?
Next episode of Chobits:
"Chi Doesn't Do Anything."
That's what I thought.