Good morning everybody!
Let's do the
wakey-wakey exercises
with lots of energy today!
Time to get those arms
stretched way up in the air.
Uh... Sumomo I think
you can skip that today.
Aye.
Canceling wakey-wakey exercises.
Good morning, Hideki.
Good morning to you too, Chi.
Oh?
Uh? What was that?
Miss Hibiya?
Oh, hello Mr. Motosuwa.
I hope I didn't wake you;
I guess I was making
a bit of a racket.
No, don't worry;
I was already up.
So what are you
doing with all this stuff?
I'm doing a big cleaning today,
and I'm airing
out the tatami mats.
Oh, I see. That's quite a job.
Chi?
Are you sure you
really don't mind?
After all you've done for us?
Of course not!
Chi!
It might be helpful to
have a guy like me around
if you're cleaning up
the whole building.
Chi!
So if it's okay with you,
just let me know
what I can do
starting right now.
Chi!
Thank you, that's
very nice of you.
Then, I guess
I will ask you for help.
Just leave it to me!
Chi? Chi, chi, chi.
Hooray, hooray!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Dust! I see dust, I see dust!
Huh? Where is it, Sumomo?
Right there! Right there!
Oh.
There we go.
Over there, too!
Chi.
And that's how you do it.
You want to give it a try?
Chi!
All right, let's do our
best to clean them!
Chi will do her best!
It's time to get cleaning!
Chi.
Okay, and now we do the outside.
You just stay right
there and watch.
And I-
Is Hideki all right?
He fell.
Pull it, pull it, that's
the way, that's the way!
Pull it, pull it, that's the
way, that's the way.
Pull it, pull it, that's
the way, that's the way...
Yay, you did it! You did it!
That's the way!
Chi.
Chi. Chi.
Here you are.
Ah, thank you very much.
Oh, that hits the spot!
Chi?
Oh...
Chi.
Are you having fun, Chi?
Wah! Danger, danger!
This is crisis situation!
I repeat: a crisis situation!
Sumomo!
Somebody help me!
Um, sorry about that.
Chi?
Mr. Motosuwa?
Yeah?
I, uh, came across
a perfect outfit for Chi
when I was going through
some of this old stuff.
Do you mind if
I have her try it on?
No, of course not.
Thanks, I really appreciate it.
This is great. Right, Chi?
Chi!
Well then Chi,
then do you have a minute
to come to my apartment?
Go ahead, Chi.
Just try not to cause
Miss Hibiya any trouble, okay?
Chi!
I think that just about
does it for this room.
All I have to do now is to bring
all those things
back in from the hall,
and I'd say we're done.
Hmm.
Come to think of it,
there's another door upstairs,
maybe that's a better place.
I'll be right back;
just wait here.
Chi.
Chi?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Would you like to try this on?
Chi.
Okay, since that's
the door to the roof,
maybe this is a closet.
Excuse me, I'm coming in.
We're coming in!
Huh?
All done.
I knew that would
look nice on you.
Chi?
Of course, that outfit
was yours anyway,
so it should.
Chi's outfit?
That's right, you've
forgotten everything.
Did Chi forget about something?
It's all right.
You should have; that's
the way he wanted it.
Chi?
What do you think is up
with all these cables?
Huh.
Well I guess I can
dust the place, anyway.
It could certainly use it.
Nothing strange is suddenly
gonna pop out at us, is it?
Time for your bath!
S-Sumomo!
Sumomo? Sumomo!
Come on, talk to me!
Sumomo! Sumomo! Sumomo!
Oh come on, Sumomo!
What do I do now?
It would be terrible
if Shinbo found out
that Sumomo was broken.
Uh, sorry, but it looks
like Sumomo sorta broke.
"Sorry" doesn't cut it.
Pay to have her fixed!
Hey, you gotta wake up,
Sumomo, come on!
Please!
Miss Hibiya! Miss Hibiya!
Mr. Motosuwa, is there
something the matter?
It's Sumomo:
she got electrocuted!
Oh!
I never know what to do
when things like this happen.
What do I do?
Mr. Motosuwa, please.
First you have to calm down.
Yeah. You're right
I gotta calm down.
That's right.
Now how about
some nice barley tea?
I know! I'll call Minoru!
He always knows what to do!
Mr. Motosuwa?
Oh, yes, hello,
is this the Kokubunji residence?
Uh, my name's Motosuwa,
is Minoru there?
He isn't home?
Oh, I see. Yes,
that's fine. No, no, no.
Thank you, thank you,
sorry to bother you.
Why now, of all times?
Is Hideki all right?
Oh , I'm all right,
but Sumomo...
Chi?
Aah, Chi!
What kind of an outfit is that?!
This outfit is bad one?
No, I wouldn't
call it a "bad" one,
as a matter of fact,
I think it's
actually quite pretty.
Chi is happy.
Oh.
So that must be the one
Miss Hibiya gave you just now.
Yes, Miss Manager handed to me.
I think it's all
right to actually say
that she gave it to you, Chi.
"Gave" is what you say
when you receive something.
That's right.
But this is Chi's.
It's Chi's outfit.
It's wrong to say "receive."
So what now?
Man, do I have to call Shinbo?
Yeah but the only one
who knows his number
is Sumomo, and she's...
Come on, Sumomo, wake up.
Um, Mr. Motosuwa?
If you don't mind,
I think I might be able to help.
Huh?
I can take a look
at Sumomo for you.
Let's see what's going on.
That's amazing.
Chi?
Well, that's good.
According to this,
it appears that
the surge protector
was functioning properly.
Surge protector?
She was designed to shut off
if there was any sudden
surge of electrical power.
So, as a result, all of
her data's still intact.
It looks like she just
passed out from the shock.
Sumomo? Does that
mean you're okay?
Good morning, everybody!
Let's do the
wakey-wakey exercises
with lots of energy!
Somehow her clock reset
itself when she started back up.
I can set her to the
correct time for you.
Thank you; I don't
know what to say.
You saved the day!
I'm a total nitwit when
it comes to stuff like this.
Oh, everyone's like that
in the very beginning.
There, everything's fine now.
I'm glad you're okay, Sumomo.
It wouldn't be
very funny if you were
to break while I was taking
care of you, you know.
Did Mr. Shinbo go somewhere
on vacation or something?
Well, yeah.
I guess you might say
that he's gone off
on a vacation of sorts.
I see.
Well, if you're planning
to keep her for a while,
I think it'd be a good idea
to set up a user password.
A password?
Yes. It's always a good idea.
That way, other
people won't be able
to use Sumomo
unless you let them.
As it is right now, she's set up
so that anyone can
use her, there's no way
for you to protect your
personal information.
Oh, I see what you mean.
Wow, you certainly know
a lot about Persocoms.
I suppose.
I used to deal with
Persocoms at my old job,
so I picked up a fair amount.
Oh, well that explains how you
could figure out what was
wrong with her so quickly.
So I guess that means that
you quit your other job?
That's right.
I see, and then
you became manager
of this apartment building.
I mean it's not like
this isn't important too,
but don't you think
you're wasting your talents?
There's a little more to it.
This building was originally
owned by my husband.
Oh, I see, your husband.
Miss Hibiya, you mean
you were married?!
Oh yes.
In fact my husband
and I used to work
in the same
Persocom-related field.
Miss Hibiya... married.
Chi?
My husband passed away.
I really wanted
to keep this place,
so I thought I'd
just manage it myself.
Because it was something
that he'd left behind.
Yeah, well, I can understand.
By the way...
If you're free tonight,
I'd love to have you come
over for dinner, Mr. Motosuwa.
Huh?
You were a big help today;
I'd like to thank you
for all the work.
Is that all right?
Well, sure!
I wouldn't want to pass
up an offer like that.
Chi.
I'm sorry.
This is all very ordinary.
Maybe to you, but
I only see this in pictures!
Do I actually get to eat this?
Please do.
Thank you; it's perfect.
Delicious!
Chi!
I'm so glad.
Hideki.
Oh, thank you very much, Chi.
Chi.
You know,
Mr. Motosuwa, I've noticed
that Chi seems to smile
a lot more these days.
Huh? You really think so?
Chi?
Oh yes.
And I'm sure the reason is that
you take such good care of her.
Well...
Chi.
Chi is getting cuter
and cuter with every day.
But, because of that,
it's going to be
that much easier
for them to find her.
Man, that was a lot
of hard work today.
And I ate way too much
of that wonderful food.
Oh, that's right.
I almost forgot:
Miss Hibiya said something
about a password.
Would you like to
set up a password now?
Oh, can I?
Yes, you can!
The mode is
currently set to public.
However, if you
register as a user,
you will be able to
block other people
from using Sumomo!
Would you like to create one?
It sounds like a good idea.
Fine.
Then please enter
a password now.
Well how about... "Motosuwa"?
I can't accept that password;
try something else.
How come?
Name, birthday,
telephone number, etc...
They're all bad.
It's imperative that
you pick something
that's not easy to figure out.
Yeah, I guess that makes sense.
But you know,
if it's not something
easy to remember
like my birthday or
my phone number, how'm I-
Password now!
Password now. Password now.
Password now...
Chobits.
Voice recognition.
Is that in hiragana?
Or in katakana?
Uh, what?
I don't recommend using
the same alphabet
for every letter.
I suggest you use
a mix of hiragana,
katakana, numbers,
and the English alphabet.
Oh, then let's use katakana
just for the "ch" part.
Your password is now registered!
Come to think of it...
I wonder if Chi has
a password, too?
Chi?
No doubt about it. That was it.
It's close.
It appears that
they're getting close,
just as I thought.
Why are Persocoms
shaped just like humans?
They can do almost
anything, they're helpful,
they're pretty, and
they're always by your side.
But then, they're
different from humans.
I don't get it!
Why's a guy like me
who couldn't get into
college and worries
all the time always finding
more things to worry about?
Next episode of Chobits:
"Chi Disappears."
Chi?
Chi. She's a
Persocom, too, right?