Thank you very much!
I don't like the looks of that.
Boy, I wish I'd never
listened to that story.
It was a cloudy, muggy day,
with a darkness that
threatened rain any second...
The day that she was murdered.
She was lured by her
lover's jealous wife--
with his usual signal-
but instead of the
arms of her lover,
she found a violent
end to her life.
Her aching fury lives
on in that apartment,
and sends out its beckoning
signal on those same muggy days.
The signal for their meetings
that the man had used...
flashing the light on
and off, on and off,
waiting, even now...
for the arrival
of her next victim.
Hideki, welcome home.
Chi?
W-w-w-was... that story
about this apartment?
B-b-b-but that's impossible!
That's impossible!
Flashing the room
light on and off.
That was the signal for the
passionate rendezvous
of a married man
and his mistress.
One day, when she went
to the room as usual,
she found the man's
wife standing there,
with a kitchen knife
in clutched in her hand.
It was a cloudy, muggy day,
with a darkness that
threatened rain any second,
The day that she was murdered.
The woman tried to get help
from the man by dragging
herself toward the hall,
but the man had
not come for her,
and only her ebbing blood
ever reached the door.
Yes, the woman was betrayed
by the man she loved.
The woman who fell to the
jealousy of her lover's wife,
lured by her lover's signal.
Her fury remains in
the room as we speak,
and sends out that signal
on those cloudy, muggy days...
days like the day
she was killed.
The signal for their
meetings that the man used...
Flashing the room light
on and off, on and off...
That is how she awaits for
the arrival of a new victim.
In room 104 of Apartment G.
Of course, most of the
stories on this website
are nothing but completely
unsubstantiated rumors.
But I'd have to say they do
sound pretty good
coming from a Persocom instead
of just some old monitor.
Wait, Mr. Motosuwa.
You asked me about the internet;
I thought you wanted to know.
Yeah, but I gotta go
to the bathroom...
Wait, that story's
just like the one I heard
over at Minoru's place.
Yeah, b-but that's impossible.
No matter how
cloudy it is today,
and even if the lights were on
in the empty room down there...
It just can't be.
Hey, Motosuwa!
Want to go to the baths?
Huh? Motosuwa?
Hideki over there.
Of all the things to do
on a gloomy day like this,
are you playing some
kinda creepy game?
Ready or not, here I come!
Master, he's scary!
You mean that spooky
old story about Room 104?
Oh, sure, I've
heard about that one.
I've even seen the
website and everything.
But it's just one of
those urban legends.
Oh, you think so, huh?
But I saw it with my own eyes.
It was a flashing light in
that vacant room beneath us.
And, it's apartment G.
This is Gub Jogasaki after all,
that's a bit of a coincidence.
It's all in your mind.
For starters, you said it
yourself: it's a vacant room.
And I don't see
any lights flashing.
It was doing it
just a minute ago!
Motosuwa.
You know, you're
a bigger lily-liver
than I'd ever thought.
Shinbo!
Wah! He's so scary!!
Will you stay here tonight?
Well, I'm not gonna stay
with a guy the whole night
just 'cuz he's a scaredy-
cat and can't take it!
Aw, come on, just tonight;
I won't do anything
weird, I promise!
I won't let you
do anything weird!
Oh god, it's morning already,
and I haven't slept a wink.
Hmm?
Chi?
Chi!
Hideki?
Hideki.
Chi?
I hear something.
No sound. Sound is all gone.
What's come over you;
what're you doing down here?!
I heard a sound here.
Huh?
What was that?!
What did I see?!
Did I just see that?
Hideki, what's wrong?
Are you sick?
Oh...
No, it's all right, Chi.
There's nothing there,
nothing at all.
It's gonna be fine, don't worry,
it's OK, don't be scared.
I gotta thing or
two to take care of,
so you just stick around here,
and I'll, just uh, right.
This is... it's getting
just like that crazy story.
Hey! And whatever you do,
don't go near that room!
Now what do I do?
Should I ask the
Manager about it?
But how do you ask
a thing like that?
"Excuse me, but is
this apartment haunted?"
I'm already behind on my rent,
that'll make it sound
like I'm trying
to blackmail her or something.
Oh, Mr. Motosuwa,
I was wondering if...
Gah!
Lovely weather
we're having, huh?
Big dark clouds and...
oh, no, nothing supernatural
going on around here.
Nope, nothing like that;
normal as rain!
See you!
Hey wait,
so was that all just in my head?
That's true.
I mean, what're the odds
it would be that place?
Sure, the name of
the building starts
with a "G," but so what?
It could be "Gonzales" or
"Garando" for that matter.
Besides, the story's
a little too good.
To have the "other woman"
standing there
with a kitchen knife in
her hand when you walk in...
Uh...
Senpai?! Are you
all right, Senpai?!
Oh, sure; that makes sense.
I'm sorry I surprised
you like that.
Oh no, it's nothing.
I'm sorry to bother you
with such a screwy story!
I mean it's really just
a silly urban legend.
I know it's pretty dumb
to believe in stuff
like that at my age.
Oh, I totally disagree!
Huh?
I don't think there's
anything wrong with it;
I'm scared of the color black!
Just black? How come?
I mean crows, black cats, bats.
They seem to be bad luck.
And, don't you think
they look a little scary?
Mm-a little bit.
I think everyone's
putting up a brave front
when in reality,
they're paranoid.
So when you think about it,
there's no reason to be worried.
Yumi, I...
Hmm?
I was just a little
surprised, that's all;
you really don't have to worry
about me so much, okay?
Okay, but that's
not what I meant.
The other day, after
going to the movies,
I felt really bad,
because I left
without saying good-bye
to you or anything.
Oh, well I didn't...
I'm really sorry about that!
Oh, don't let that bother you;
I just thought you must've been
in a big hurry to get somewhere.
And...
Maybe we could go out again
sometime, if you'd like to...?
My Pleasure!
Ahh!
Senpai?
Are you gonna be okay Senpai?
Sheesh! That's enough
cowardice out of you!
A spooky story's one thing,
but what about a
true friend who sacrifices
his back to carry
you all the way home.
Don't say things like that.
Hideki.
I'm sorry, Shinbo.
But you know,
my passing out didn't have
much to do with that story.
Listen to yourself.
Just think about it.
First of all,
I'd like to point out,
there's no room 104
in the building.
Huh?
There are only 3 rooms
on the first floor. Right?
Okay, when you come,
the manager's room's on
the left; that's room 101.
Then to the right,
there are only two rooms.
So, where would room 104 be?
Oh.
Once ya figure that out,
the story sorta falls apart,
doesn't it? See ya!
Hideki still hurts?
Huh? No, the pain's
all gone, Chi.
Hideki, is scared of that room?
Huh? Well, it's uh...
Chi will check it.
Huh?
But, Chi...
First of all,
I'd like to point out,
there's no room 104
in the building.
Chi, wait for me!
Let's see...
All right, then.
So if there really
isn't a room 104,
at least one part of the story
doesn't hold up.
There are 3 rooms
on the first floor.
Miss Hibiya's apartment
is off to the left,
that's room 101.
Then over here
are the other two...
102 and 103...
Just your basic
unoccupied apartment.
Looks pretty harmless to me!
I'm such an idiot.
Huh? Was that a blackout?
Didja hear the
thunder just then?
The storm's coming this way.
What's that?
Where's Chi?
Hey, Chi!
She wouldn't...
Chi?!
What are you up
to all of a sudden?
It's dangerous by that door.
Chi?
Ow.
Huh?
Just a dream... Thank goodness.
Hey, Motosuwa!
Rise and shine sleepyhead;
it's almost noon after all.
Time to go to prep school
and do our best again today!
Oh no, it's that late already?!
I'm gonna go on ahead!
See you later!
Chi.
Oh, Chi, sorry I woke you up.
I gotta get going!
I'm gonna be late!
Where is Hideki going?
What do you mean? Prep school.
But that's...
Room 104.
Here you go!
Huh?
I hope you like
vanilla ice cream.
But... How'd I...?
Hey, come on.
It was all your idea to
bring me here after all.
You said you'd like to go
out with me again sometime!
Oh, oh really?
And it is a
perfect day, isn't it?
Yeah.
Hey! That looks
like so much fun!
Let's get a boat!
This is great.
It's really nice to
do things like this
every once in a while.
Isn't it though?
I just love doing
stuff like this!
The light streaming through
the trees like that...
It's almost like
being back home.
You're in for a treat then.
There's an even
prettier place up ahead.
Huh.
It's an old apartment.
But the light in the
first floor window
flashes on and off! On and off.
Mr. Motosuwa!
Huh?
What do you mean, "huh"?
Be careful, it's dangerous
spacing out like that!
Oh, Miss Shimizu!
Thank you very much.
You know, you've been
acting a little strange lately.
Is something wrong?
Huh? No, not really.
Oh.
I get it, it's not something
you'd want to talk to me about.
I guess to you, I'm just...
an instructor at a prep school.
Huh?
Hey, do you want
to go get a drink?
Huh?
Come on, let's go!
Anyway, there's
something I've been wanting
to ask you about.
Uh, Miss Shimizu,
is this all right?
I mean, you know:
just the two us, and like...
Oh, don't be silly.
Come on; I know just the place.
See? It's right here.
I've been thinking just
how much I wanted
to bring you to
this place, Motosuwa.
M-Miss Shimizu.
Miss Shimizu, don't do it!
Do what?!
So then... It was a dream?
What's up with you this time?
From now on, try and have
your nightmares at home.
Now go wash your face.
Right... I'm sorry, thank you.
Hey, watch it!
This is the third floor!
Here.
Oh, thanks.
I haven't had a decent night's
sleep since I first heard it.
Ya look like it, too.
It's this Room 104.
Asleep or awake, I can't
get it out of my mind.
It just won't leave me alone.
Please, Shinbo!
You gotta sleep with me!
Right. Totally lost it.
Motosuwa! Time to exorcise
that demon of yours.
So...
What exactly brought
you to my place?
Are you saying that
Mr. Motosuwa's paranoia
is somehow my fault?
No, I wasn't saying that.
But I thought if we
could track down
the origin of the story, it
might just do a world of good
here to ease his troubled mind.
The origin of the story?
The best thing to do would
be simply to take
most of the spooky stories
on the web with a grain of salt.
I know, but humor
me this one time.
Room 104.
Why does it have to be Room 104?
Motosuwa, try and cheer up.
Life is filled with mysteries
and seemingly
supernatural happenings,
but the overwhelming majority
are just illusions
or natural phenomena.
Sure.
But not this; I know
I really heard it.
This tortured,
endless dragging...
Then I saw that thick,
dark puddle
of blood slowly seeping out.
I saw it with my own eyes!
I must say that
your witnessing of it
is one of the least
compelling facts.
Huh?
Humans are blessed with an
intriguing structural ability:
They tend to see things
they'd subconsciously
like to see rather than
what's really there.
As a result...
But, I really saw it!
It shouldn't have been there,
but I saw a Room 104
with my very own eyes.
You know, Mr. Motosuwa...
That story was about
Gub Jogasaki after all!
It was, it was, I know it was!
Then, let's go
look at it together.
Huh?
To Gub Jogasaki.
Looking at it like this, it's
definitely got that feeling.
Yeah, well I can do without
that kind of feeling!
And why'd we have to have
this kind of weather,
especially now?
If it's really a
supernatural phenomenon,
it's the perfect weather.
Hideki!
Hmm?
Chi!
Welcome home!
Oh, Chi!
You're all right after all!
I'm so glad!
Of course she'd be all right.
So which one is
the room in question?
Oh...
The one on the left here's
our Manager's apartment;
so that would be Room 101.
Then over there on the right,
there are the two empty ones.
And the one where Motosuwa
saw the lights flashing
would be that corner
one on the far end.
Excuse me, Mr. Motosuwa,
but when you saw it,
were you...?
I-I was alone.
Have you ever seen
it happen, Mr. Shinbo?
Uh, nope.
Sumomo hasn't seen it either!
Yes, well, all the more reason
to assume it's just
some kind of mistake.
It was just like that!
Shh!
Hideki, are you
scared of that sound?
This takes away the scary?
Enougha this, I'm gonna go
in and check it out myself.
You stay here and
keep your eyes peeled
in case somebody
tries to get away.
Hey, Shinbo!
Geez, talk about a tacky prank.
When I get my hands
on whoever did it...
Mr. Shinbo should
be back by now.
Do ya think...?
Let's go.
Shinbo?
We should check
upstairs. Come on.
Right.
Huh? Wait!
Chi?!
There.
T-There?!
Chi!
M-My body won't move!
Chi, don't go.
Move! Move!
What am I doing here?!
Chi... She's...
Chi!
Huh?
The closet?
Oh sure, you can get a lot
of mold this time of year,
because of the humidity.
So I thought it was a good time
for some serious cleaning.
But the light bulb
was about to give out,
and I needed to see
what I was doing.
I tried all sorts of things,
like a stepstool and a table,
so I could get up
high enough to change it,
but I just couldn't reach it.
And since I'm taller,
she called me over to
give her a hand with it.
And the replacement
is now complete!
But, I saw it; what
about that dark liquid
coming out from under the door?
Oh, well, you see
when I moved the table,
I happened to accidentally
knock the bucket over.
That was when I came
over to your place
to ask you for some
help, Mr. Motosuwa,
but you seemed
rather busy at the time.
Light bulb... Table... Bucket?
Okay, but it said Room 104;
anyone care to explain that one?
It's safe to assume they divided
the first into four
rooms at one time.
You'll notice the number
on the next apartment is 103.
Yes, I did a rather
extensive remodel
when I first
became manager here.
And that means that the missing
room number is apartment 102!
Hideki?
Are you all right?
Why do things like this
happen to me all the time?
I feel so dumb.
Hideki not scared now?
No, that's all ancient history.
Chi very glad.
Oh... Chi.
Well, wonder what he's getting
in the mood for now, huh?
That's not true!
But I am glad.
What really got me
scared though was
when I started to believe
that Chi might suddenly
become possessed
or something like that.
Lord Minoru, you look strange.
Is something wrong?
Hmm? No, I'm quite glad.
...that nothing really
happened after all.
Nothing like that
blue morning sky!
No, wait. Where's Chi?
Could she...?
Hideki! Good morning!
Ah!
Chi?
Hideki? Sleeps some more?
Good night!
Chi?
Chi hears it again.
Ta-dah!
This DVD player is great;
it can even play games!
And, of course,
anything you watch on it
has incredible picture quality.
Hideki, face is red.
Uh, okay then,
let's play a game!
Chi!
All software's 20% off at the
store by the train station.
Hideki, face is red again!
A game, right? A game!
Chi!
5 titles for just 10,000 yen.
Hideki, porno?
Yeah, porno!
Next episode of Chobits:
"Chi Plays."
A stewardess, a nurse,
and a housewife...