Good afternoon, may I help-
Oh, hello, Motosuwa.
Hey there, nice to see you.
I came by to get Chi.
Is it time?
Yeah. Thanks for coming.
Chi, come on out!
Chi.
Hideki!
Hey, Chi, calm down!
Hideki, look, look!
Huh?
Pretty good, huh?
Chi made it all by herself, too.
Huh?
Chi made that?
Chi is a very quick learner,
so I thought I'd let her try.
And I think she did
a really great job.
Yeah, that's great Chi.
Chi.
Please go ahead and
have some, if you'd like.
Huh?
Are you sure it's all right?
Of course.
Well great! Then I think I will.
Chi?
It's good!
This is delicious, Chi!
Chi!
This is really great!
Ah, you two seem to get
along so well together.
Oh, well...
Chi.
Oh, so she even learned
how to bake a cake, huh?
That's right!
Ya don't say...
You know, that could be handy.
Maybe we can find a way
to teach ours to
make the appetizers.
I think we should
be able to do that.
Well, ya gotta admit...
These things are an
incredible invention.
They look just like humans,
they're really cute, and they
follow instructions to a "t."
They never give you any guff,
and they can do
just about anything.
Pretty much.
Hey Manager, the truck's here!
Oh, okay, just put
it in the back.
Come to think of it...
hey Yumi, didn't you
say you had a Persocom?
Ah, yes.
Well, that's a small one.
Oh, I had a human-shaped
Persocom for a while,
but I found that it
made me sort of sad.
It's true that Persocoms
can do all sorts of things.
In many ways, they're better
than humans will ever be.
There're a lot of 'em out there:
people who think Persocoms
are better than humans.
But, at this rate,
no one'll want to stay
by anyone's side anymore.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to
get into all that.
Oh, it's okay.
"At this rate,
no one'll want to
stay by anyone's side."
Human beings and Persocoms...
It's morning!
It's morning! It's morning!
Aw man, is it really
time to get up?
Good morning, Hideki.
Oh, good morning.
Chi?
Let's start with the
wakey-wakey exercises today!
Why's this such a big
surprise to me every morning?!
I should've gotten
used to this by now!
She's a Persocom! A Persocom!
Chi.
You're so enthusiastic!
Ok! Leg exercises!
I'll be going now.
Take care of yourself.
Oh, yeah, about your
job at Tirol today...
Chi?
I have to go to the library
after prep school gets out,
so I don't think
I can make it in time
to walk you home.
You're gonna have to come home
by yourself this time
if you don't mind.
Is that okay?
Hideki.
Hm?
Hideki tired? Out of energy?
Huh?
Too much exercise?
No, I think it's a bit
more complicated than that.
Hideki sick?
No, it's not like that.
It's just a little early
for that much stimula-
No! I-
It's all right.
I'm not sick or anything.
Hideki sure?
Positive.
So don't worry
about it; I'm fine.
Chi is glad.
Oh, Chi.
That makes Chi very glad.
Uh, hey!
When Chi thought
Hideki was sick...
Chi's heart felt like
it was twisted tightly.
Chi.
Time to go; time to go!
Time to zoom out
of the house now,
gotta get going!
Yeah, um, well, at any rate...
I'll be going now!
Hideki.
What am I doing;
am I out of my mind?
But Chi is so
innocent and honest.
What am I supposed to do?
She looked like she
felt so badly, and...
Anyway, she's very--
In many ways,
they're better than
humans will ever be.
There're a lot of 'em out there:
people who think Persocoms
are better than humans.
But, at this rate...
But after a while,
her husband only seemed
interested in the Persocom.
Miss Shimizu's husband
got all obsessed
with Persocoms too.
At first, I wondered
if something
like that was really possible.
But it's happening
more and more.
I admit that Chi is really cute.
When I look at her,
my heart races,
and I can't help smiling.
But, she's not human.
Still, I- I can't think of Chi
as just a Persocom anymore.
So, how am I supposed
to think of her?
No one'll want to stay by
anyone's side anymore.
Chi goes to work,
making sure Chi isn't late.
Chi?
Continues from other book...
Ch-
I just can't take it!
I need to get ready
for my entrance exams;
I don't have time to
think about relationships
between humans and Persocoms!
Well, there's nothing I can do
about it now anyway.
Besides, if I let
myself get all worried,
I'm just gonna wind up
getting Chi worried too.
Hm?
I'm home.
Chi?
Well that's strange...
She should have gotten
off work ages ago.
Telephone! Telephone!
Please answer the telephone!
That's right.
I forgot that Minoru
helped me set it up
so my home phone
would forward calls directly
to Sumomo when I wasn't in.
Go ahead, Sumomo.
Aye!
I'm sorry to call so late.
Is this the Motosuwa residence?
Manager Ueda.
Oh, Mr. Motosuwa.
You've got great timing.
I was worried about Chi.
Huh?
Well, I was wondering
what had happened to her.
Huh?
Actually she never came
in to work today at all.
I was getting worried,
so I decided to call.
Wait a minute.
Are you saying she
never even showed up?
Yeah. That's right.
Hey, Mr. Motosuwa?
I'm sorry!
I'll call you back later!
Wah!
Mr. Motosuwa? Mr. Motosuwa?!
Miss Manager! Miss Manager!
She's not home.
It certainly looks that way.
Where are you going?
Where could she be?
I hope she's not
mixed up in something
like that peep show again.
She's just so innocent;
I can't help thinking
something's gotta be up.
Oh, hey, you're
the guy who bought
the other books of
that series, aren't you?
Uh, yeah.
Yeah, you were in a while ago
with that little
long-haired Persocom.
Yeah, that was me.
Well anyway, this morning,
I saw her taking
a look at the new one.
And I thought I might just
say "hi" and talk with her.
But I was in the
middle of something,
and before I knew it,
she was gone.
She was gone?
Well, actually to
tell you the truth,
I am missing one
of those books now.
Oh, that's right,
I almost forgot.
I found this, lying on the
ground right over there.
Chi.
Where is this?
Somewhere Chi doesn't know.
This is not Hideki's room.
Why is Chi in a
place Chi doesn't know?
You were kidnapped, that's why.
Chi?
Chi was "kidnapped"?
It means that you've
been abducted,
...taken against your will!
So Chi was abducted?
Should Chi like that?
What's that supposed to be?
Some kinda punch line
from a comedy routine?
Chi?
Is that a good thing
or a bad thing?
Boy, oh boy.
You really don't know much
of anything, do you?
Chi doesn't understand
many things.
Hideki always teaches Chi.
Hideki?
Yes, Hideki.
Hideki picked up
Chi from the garbage.
Hideki took Chi
back to his apartment.
Hideki teaches Chi
all sorts of things.
I knew you had to
be the same Persocom.
Who's that?
Yoshiyuki Kojima.
Just call me Yoshiyuki.
Where is this?
You're at my place.
Yoshiyuki's place?
That's right.
Just now this thing was--
How dare you!
What do you mean by
calling me "this thing"?!
I have a proper name, you know!
My name is Kotoko,
do you understand?
Chi understands.
This thing is Kotoko.
That's not right;
I keep telling you:
I'm not a thing,
so stop saying it!
I guess you really
don't understand
anything yet, do you?
Chi is here because
Yoshiyuki kidnapped Chi?
"Because you were kidnapped"?
I guess you could say that.
But why do you say that?
From the very first moment
that I found out you existed,
I've never stopped
thinking about you.
I finally found you.
And in the bookstore,
when I saw you standing there,
I knew immediately
that it had to be you.
I'm going to start
analyzing you now.
Because you must be
a more special entity.
Yes...
You could very well be
one of the Chobits series.
Chobits series? So Chi is...
What's Chi?
Chi is Chi.
Chi is the name
Hideki gave to Chi.
Yeah, but why "Chi"?
In the beginning,
the only thing Chi
could say was "chi."
That sounds like
the kind of name
you'd give to a dog or a cat.
Anyway, I'll analyze you
and tell you
what you really are.
If you need anything,
feel free to tell Kotoko,
and I'm sure she
can take care of it.
Okay, I'll see you later.
But...
Hm?
"Chi" is the name
that Hideki gave Chi.
Hideki gave this name to Chi...
Hideki gave, that's
why Chi loves this name.
Oh?
I'm sorry, Chi.
I made a promise that
I wouldn't do anything.
A promise I made to him.
I never expected that something
like this would come up.
Well, I failed again.
No matter how many times I trace
the sender of this image,
it's always a dead end.
Whoever it is, they've
done an awfully good job.
I'm sorry.
Huh?
I don't believe it's possible
for my present
configuration to handle this,
so I'll stop.
It's not your fault, Yuzuki.
I'm afraid I'm just not
experienced enough.
But then, I was made
to be helpful to you,
and if I can't do what
you ask me, I'm not.
To think that I can't
do what I'm asked to do.
Huh? Lord Minoru?
You are very helpful
to me, Yuzuki.
So much so in fact,
that sometimes it
actually troubles me.
When you were much
younger, Lord Minoru,
if anything ever made
you sad for a while,
your sister was
always right here,
to do something like this.
Yuzuki.
It's been a while
since the last
maintenance was done,
but there still hasn't
been any new data entered
regarding your elder sister.
In order for me
to be closer to her
and serve you better,
Lord Minoru,
please enter more
data about your sister.
You know I-
Lord Minoru?
A telephone call.
Who is it?
It's Mr. Motosuwa.
At this time of night?
Connect me.
Connecting.
Minoru! I can't
find Chi; she's gone!
She disappeared;
I don't know what happened!
That sounds serious.
Do you have any leads?
There was a guy at the bookstore
who found her hairclip,
but somehow she just
suddenly disappeared!
I looked all over for her,
and I can't find
any sign of her.
Shinbo's not around,
so I don't know what to do.
You're the only one
I can turn to, Minoru!
Okay, try to calm
down, Motosuwa!
I don't know.
I've just got a really
bad feeling about this!
Yeah, I understand.
Just meet me at the Duklyon.
I'll be right over.
The connection has
been terminated.
I'm going out now.
There's a chance I might
need to look something up
when I'm out with
Motosuwa later on.
Would you like to come with me?
Sure.
Yuzuki, you always seem
to have the same exact
smile on your face
whenever we're going to
do something together.
It's because I know I'll be
by your side, Lord Minoru.
Well, shall we go?
Yes.
Chi.
But after a while,
her husband only seemed
interested in the Persocom.
Do you find
Persocoms attractive?
Is it more fun to be
with a Persocom
than with a human?
No one'll want to stay by
anyone's side anymore.
That's beside the point;
I still have to look for Chi.
Let's go, Sumomo!
Aye!
Chi, please be alright!
Okay.
Let's say my wallet disappears.
The missing wallet's
not gonna be worried
or lonely or anything like that.
And, of course, contents aside,
I'm not gonna be worried
about the wallet either.
Chi is a Persocom.
She might not feel
doubt or loneliness.
But not me; I'm super
worried about her!
Next episode of Chobits:
"Chi Waits."
Is something wrong with me?