Hideki's special someone...
The one who is just for Hideki.
Chi?
But, if it isn't you, Chi...
If the same thing
happens this time,
we must do it.
We must do it.
You are...
Sorry to make you wait.
So, let's begin.
What does it mean? Begin what?
An analysis.
I'm going to analyze everything.
Where are you, Chi?
Telephone call
from Mr. Kokubunji!
From Minoru? Connect me, Sumomo.
Motosuwa, I just received
another interesting e-mail.
It's got a return
address that's identical
to the previous one that
had the image had on it.
Sumomo has it now,
so go ahead and open
it as soon as you can.
It's from the same person?
Yes, but it's an entirely
different kind of image
from the last one.
I don't have the slightest
idea what to make of it.
Okay, but I have
to look for Chi.
I know, and I'm still trying
to find her on this end, too.
Please, just open it up.
It's possible there's a
clue in it that might help.
I guess it's worth a try.
Extracting from
the compressed file!
So, it's true.
The guy who sent the other image
was the one who abducted Chi.
Does it show Chi
in some horrible
predicament or something?
What is this?
All right.
You're now connected to
every Persocom in the house.
The cords look like
ribbons coming down.
It's really cute.
Ribbons?
Yeah. And they look
great on you, too.
I've never stopped
thinking about you.
I knew you had to be an
extraordinary Persocom
for "M" to post about
you on the message boards.
It's amazing, I didn't think
they'd let you walk
alone like that.
I thought I'd never
get to meet you.
But there you were:
a Persocom just like
the one "M" described,
right at the bookstore.
I couldn't believe it.
It must be that your
owner doesn't have
any idea how valuable
you really are,
that's my guess.
The connection
terminals are normal,
as far as I can see.
All your special qualities
must be on the inside.
Chi is special?
Well, I would be
happy if you were.
So what is this thing?
It's not like the last photo;
it doesn't look
anything like Chi.
What am I missing?
Why would they send
something like this?
Sumomo, do you have any
idea what we're looking at?
This is...!
This is what?
This is known as
an attached image!
Thanks, even I know that!
Hey, don't expect so much!
Sumomo is a mobile unit;
she can't answer abstract
questions or things like that.
Shinbo!
A very good evening to you!
Oh, hi Sumomo!
Been getting along
okay with Motosuwa?
Aye!
So what brings you
back all of a sudden?
Takako got pretty worried
when I started to tell
her about our phone call.
Motosuwa always gets so
serious about everything.
He must be terribly
worried about her.
Yeah.
I'm sure he could use your help.
This is one of those times
when two rational heads are
better than one emotional one.
Miss Shimizu said that?
So what's the scoop?
You manage to find that
Persocom of yours yet?
No.
Well I'm sure you
must be worried
out of your mind by now.
I know that a Persocom's
memories can be erased.
Even so, I'll still remember.
Even if the other one's
not a living creature,
and even if she
doesn't remember,
I don't think it will
all be for nothing...
if I can remember.
I guess I am worried about Chi.
I'm very worried.
That's why.
I want to find her
just as soon as I can.
All right.
And I'm here to help ya!
Thank you.
All right!
It's time to show me
everything you got.
Interesting.
So you're saying this
image has something
to do with your
Persocom disappearing?
I don't know, or at least,
I can't make heads or
tails out of it, anyway.
Hmm.
Might be a map, whatta ya think?
Huh?!
Yeah, I'm thinkin' it's a
map from a navigation system.
You know, like for
cars or cell phones.
But why would anyone want to
send us something like that?
Beats me.
Do you know where this place is?
We can always have
a Persocom look it up.
Can Sumomo do that?
Well, yeah, in a pinch,
but it's definitely
gonna take some time.
I know, let's ask Kokubunji.
It doesn't make sense.
Who in the world
would want to send me
a strange image like this one?
Same thing with this image
that was sent to me earlier.
But then, even if
I were to find out
who sent these images,
I couldn't do anything about it.
Because that was the
promise I made to you.
So now there's
really no other way,
except of course, to draw.
What Chi lost...
What Chi lost before
she became Chi...
What I'd like her
to find again someday.
To help her a little.
So she can finally find
"The One Just for Me."
Oh, I get it. It's a map.
Yeah, but we don't know where.
I'll look it up on this end.
Wait just a minute.
Yuzuki, use the LAN
with the other Persocoms
and match up the image with
the coordinates on a map.
We need to know where this is.
Sure.
I'm afraid I'm at a
loss on this one too.
These images could have
been sent by anyone.
But I do think we're
on to something here,
and I think there's
a good chance
it'll lead us to Miss Chi.
So do you think
she's there, or...?
It would nice if she were.
Lord Minoru, we've
identified 12,568 locations
throughout Japan that
correspond to the map image.
12,568 locations?!
Well, ya gotta admit it is
rather abstract for a map.
How about Tokyo?
23 locations.
That's still way too many.
That's not too many;
we can check all those out!
Just a minute.
Yuzuki, if I'm not mistaken,
you still have the access log
from the custom-made Persocom
site, isn't that right?
Yes.
Good.
Then I want you to track down
the access points
using those IPs.
What I want to know is
if any of those
access points correspond
with any of the 23 locations,
so see what you can find.
There is one match.
What's the user ID of the person
who uses that IP address?
Dragonfly.
So it's him?!
W-Who is it?
This guy--
He might, ya know...
Hey, what is all this?
Tell me who this "Dragonfly" is?
Mr. Motosuwa.
I think we just discovered
the location of Miss Chi.
Huh?
Amazing.
Something...
I can hear a voice in my head!
This voice...
It isn't my master's, and
it isn't Miss Chi's either.
Yet somehow
I recognize this voice.
Is it around here?
Yes.
The map coincides
with the address
of the IP right
where you're standing.
Wow, it didn't even
take us ten minutes
to walk here from our place.
So you mean I've been
that close to Chi all along?
Dragonfly loves
the custom models;
I think he's got over
twenty of them at least.
Over twenty?!
So that means,
we need to look for
a house that's big enough
to hold over 20 Persocoms.
But all the houses
around here are huge!
He went and hired a
private security company
to look after his
Persocoms, too,
if I remember correctly.
Hey, that's right;
he posted about that!
That's it: we gotta
look for a house
with a security
company logo on it!
Uh, right!
It's already more
than an hour now.
Every single Persocom
in the entire house,
and I still can't
hack the protection.
But, not for much longer.
The program we're running is one
I created especially for you.
No matter how
much you resist it,
it'll find a way to
eat right through you.
It's hopeless;
you'll have to accept it.
This isn't it!
But how do both of you
know so much about this guy?
Who is this Dragonfly
character, anyway?
Let's just say he's a
pretty conspicuous guy.
It's sorta hard
not to notice him.
Conspicuous?
Yeah, pretty snotty,
likes to provoke people.
Always arguing with
"M" all the time, too.
"M"?
My user name.
The name I use as an
alias whenever I'm posting
on a website; it's
basically a penname.
This isn't it, either! Darnnit!
Chi, wait for me!
I was right, you are
very special after all.
You really might be one
of the Chobits series.
Chi!
No!
That's it!
So she's in there?!
There's another one over here.
Aw, come on!
Which is it?!
Shinbo, take Sumomo
for a moment
and go stand next
to the other house.
Sumomo!
Aye!
You're off the map,
so that can't be it.
This one!
I know you are
not the One for Me.
So don't try to come inside.
What's that?!
Chi!
Motosuwa! We can
get in over there!
Okay!
Motosuwa! Shinbo!
That's strange, Sumomo
doesn't respond at all.
Is there something wrong
with the connection?
Yuzuki, can you try
to call them again?
Yuzuki?!
I hear a voice.
A voice?
A voice.
A voice of someone
who knows me very well.
The voice of the one
who knows me best.
Yuzuki!
Chi, I'm here! Are you okay?!
Hideki.
Chi.
Chi wants only one person.
Just the one person-
the One who is Just for Me.
And only the One Just for
Me can ever touch Chi.
Only the One Just for
Me can ever come inside...
Motosuwa!
I don't know why, but
Sumomo's acting strange!
How's Chi?! Is she okay?!
Is it you, Chi?
Are you doing all of this?
Hideki, what is the
most precious thing
in the world to you?
The most precious thing?
The most precious thing...
For It... and for People.
If that can be figured out,
Chi might never have
to lose It again...
...the most precious thing.
What's going on?!
Chi!
Aye?
Sumomo!
Hey, are you alright now?
My consciousness.
Yuzuki?!
Are you all right now Yuzuki?!
Lord Minoru.
Chi.
Hideki.
Hideki! Hideki! Hideki!
Chi, is it you?
Chi is Chi.
Hideki said Chi,
so Chi is Chi's name.
Hideki.
Chi, happy.
Chi is happy Hideki came.
Chi.
Chi! Chi!
What's wrong?
I don't know what happened;
she just lost consciousness.
You must be the
guy called Dragonfly!
Uh?
N-No!
Hey, what did you do to Chi?!
I didn't do anything;
I just wanted to analyze her.
Shouldn't you at
least ask first?!
Um well she tagged
along with me.
Tagged along?!
Yeah, she just kinda
followed me home.
That's what it was.
You know how she is.
That's all.
Master, you said
before that you
had kidnapped her.
K-Kotoko!
The only thing I can
ever speak is the truth.
Even if it works to your
disadvantage, Master.
And after all, you programmed
me to be like this.
Do you still have
any recordings of
when he said he kidnapped her
and brought her here?
Yes, I do.
Good!
Here, I want you to
come with us for a while!
Hey, what do you
think you're doing?!
Just try and stop me.
The proof of what
you did is in her,
and I'm gonna makes
sure it stays there.
This is so you don't
erase it when we leave.
That's right!
And just so you
don't start tryin'
to claim that we stole her,
tell Sumomo you're lending
her to us for a little while.
Go on; say it!
Well that was a
close one, all right.
Uh.
What?
Nothing.
Just that you were so
incredibly cute there,
Dita, that you almost
fell right off the ledge.
What kind of nonsense is that?
I'm only speaking the truth.
So anyway, have you found her?
Nope, not yet.
Geez, where could she be?
I'm sorry, Dita.
I want to see
how things turn out
for just a little
while longer...
Chi.
She hasn't woken up since.
I got her back home
as fast as I could.
Chi, she seemed so different.
And was that...
Was that actually
Chi doing that?
And what about that time before?
Was Chi responsible
for that too?
Then maybe she is...
Maybe Chi really is a chobits.
Hm?
Are you changing the password?
Enter the password again.
Chi?
Hiragana, katakana,
English alphabet, numbers -
please state
one letter at a time.
That's not what I was doing!
It's wasn't?!
That's dangerous;
you shouldn't use
the password
unless it's necessary.
You never know
when someone could be
listening, so be careful!
Um, okay!
There wasn't any
response, was there?
Chi?
I'm talking about
the word "chobits."
When my master checked
your specifications,
your personality changed.
I had thought that
perhaps... but no.
When you finally get down to it,
chobits might be just
an urban legend after all.
Chi?
It's time for the
wakey-wakey exercises again!
Do we have to do this today?!
Chi!
My goodness what the heck
is up with these people?
Hideki, where are you going?
Well, first of all, I think
we need to let Mr. Ueda know
that we found you, and that
everything's gonna be fine.
While we're out, we
should pay for this, too.
Chi. You took this
book along with you
when you were
kidnapped, didn't you?
Chi.
Somehow, this book does
seem to be about Chi and me.
But who would want
to do that, and why?
Hideki?
Oh, sorry, it's nothing.
Let's go, Chi.
I'm glad that Chi
was able to come back.
Right, darling?
Hideki, what are memories?
Uh, well, let's see...
Happy things, fun things,
all jumbled together;
important things that
live inside your heart.
They are things you can't
easily re-enter, unlike data.
Do Chi and Hideki have memories?
Yes, we do.
Next episode of Chobits:
"Chi Answers."
Memories of Chi and Hideki...
Things that you can't
easily re-enter, hmm.