Well class, that's it for today.
And a reminder,
this Sunday will be
our first practice
college entrance exam!
I certainly hope you've all
studied and are ready for it.
It'll be a strong indicator of
how you'll do on the real thing.
With a good score,
you might even want
to change the school
you're applying to!
Now, this test is
really important,
so do your best!
And if you need a
little more motivation...
...those of you who don't do
too well on this examination,
will be the first
ones I start calling
on in class from now on!
No way!
Hey, no problem for me,
'cause I'm gonna ace that thing!
I know you'll all do your best!
See you Sunday.
So, it's time.
Our first practice
entrance exam...
So, here's the plan:
I'm gonna take
tomorrow off from work,
and if I'm able to buckle
down and concentrate all day...
Senpai!
Huh?
Yumi!
I couldn't help but hear you
talking to yourself again!
Gah!
I have to do something
about this habit of mine...
So you really need
to concentrate.
Mind if I ask on what?
Well, I have to study.
You have to study?
I have a practice
entrance exam in two days.
So, I thought I better
take a day off from work
and seriously hit the books.
Taking a day off from work?
Is this practice exam really
going to be that difficult?
Well, it's an important
one that'll let me know
if I'm on the right track
to get into college.
But the curriculum at the
prep school is pretty tough,
and it's really hard
for me to keep up!
And they really keep me running
so much around here,
by the time I get home
all I can do is sleep.
And so for tomorrow,
the day before the exam,
I'm going to stay home and
concentrate on studying!
Wow, you're serious.
Well, I know you're going
to do just great, Senpai!
Thanks, Yumi.
I, uh, I think you
made me blush, somehow.
All right, time to open up!
Oh.
My Pleasure!
I'm home!
Chi.
Hideki, welcome home!
Well, it's good to be home, Chi!
Chi. Chi.
Oops. I dropped my stuff.
Chi?
Oh, these are
the textbooks I use
for the prep school I go to.
And they're very important
things to study with, Chi.
To "stuh dee"?
Well, "to study"
means to-to work hard
at learning things
you don't know yet,
or things that are new
and unfamiliar to you.
Well, that's easy to say...
...but it's pretty tough to do!
Study is tough.
That's right!
So I'm gonna have
to really hit the books
and study hard all
day long tomorrow!
It'll help me a lot
if you cheer me on, Chi.
Chi.
All right! Let's get going!
Let's see.
Hmmm...
No! I'm not gonna lose focus!
Mmm...
Chi.
Hmm...
It's no good!
Chi!
No, no, no!
I've gotta keep working on this!
I just don't get it!
Chi-i-i-i!
One, two, three, four!
Two, two, three, four!
Now!
Hm, hm, hm...
Chi, chi, chi...
Well, I can't say that
it was too much fun.
But I feel pretty
good about that!
Hmm!
Chi!
Now for English.
I am definitely not
good at this subject.
And look at this textbook,
it's about as thick
as a cement block!
But right now,
my biggest roadblock is
this piece of work here.
If I can do half before dinner,
I think I can still
get it all done today.
Yes!
Wait a second, what's
this word "respect,"
what's the definition
of the word "respect"?
Argh! Where's my dictionary?
Chi, Chi.
You know, Chi,
I'm really not playing
around, right now.
Chi.
I'm looking for my dictionary.
Hm?
Come to think, I haven't seen
that dictionary
since I moved in here.
I haven't unpacked
these boxes yet.
Hmm... Guess that shows how much
I've been avoiding English.
Chi.
Let's see, dictionary,
dictionary...
Huh?!
That's impossible!
Gone, gone, gone, gone!
It's really gone!
I must've left my
dictionary back home.
This is the worst.
Arrrgh!
Why didn't I think
of this before now?!
Chi!
I can't possibly learn
English like this!
I'm such a stupid idiot!
Chi! Chi!
Geez, it's the day
before the practice exam.
What's the matter with me?
I can't believe
I'm so unprepared!
Let's see...
Here it is. Yeah, this one.
Dictionaries are
expensive, aren't they?
Well I know it's painful,
but now I can get back
to studying for the exam.
And I'm gonna do my best
with English,
just see if I don't!
Hmm?
What is it?
Chi?
Chi!
I see now. This must
be the first time
you've ever been in a bookstore!
Chi?
This place is a bookstore.
They sell lots
and lots of books.
"Books"?
Let's see, books are like...
paper databanks
with stuff in them.
There's all sorts of stuff
in them- amusing stuff,
useful stuff,
all kinds of stuff.
Bookstore...
Lots and lots of books.
Hm?
Chi?
Would you like this book, Chi?
That much for a picture book?
But I don't have enough
to get this and
the dictionary too.
Gah!
The dictionary...
English... The exam...
It's a present for you.
It's a present?
I'm going to buy this for you.
Buy for Chi?
Yeah.
There are all kinds
of useful things
you can learn from books.
You can learn a lot more than
from someone like me
trying to teach you stuff.
Hideki!
At times like this it's usually
considered proper
to say "Thank you."
Thank you, Hideki!
She's just so darn cute
when she's happy!
Uh?
Excuse me, Sir,
perhaps you could make
your purchase first,
and then do your love scene
from Romeo and Juliet?
Of course, yeah!
Ah-ha-ha-haa!
I'm embarrassed again. Huh?
Well actually,
that reminds me...
This is the first time you've
ever read a book, isn't it?
Chi. Chi.
All right, Chi.
Picture books are actually
really easy to handle.
See, over here on this page,
you've got some words, right?
Chi.
And then right over here,
you've got the pictures.
When you put them together,
the pictures and
the words tell a story.
So are you able
to read the words?
The town was completely...
Chi, are you reading
those words by yourself?
You are so smart!
Chi-i-i-i.
Okay, try reading a whole page.
Chi!
The town...
...was completely empty.
Hey, Motosuwa! How's it goin'?
Sh-Shinbo!
Oh, so now you're back
to being lovey-dovey again?
No! No, it's nothing like that!
Tch!
You're so boring.
Huh?
And here we came all
this way to cheer you up!
Came to cheer me up?
Sumomo.
Aye!
Motosuwa! Motosuwa!
Do your best!
Never gonna rest!
Study real hard and
you'll pass that test!
Ah!
I'm supposed to be studying!
But I can't, 'cause
I don't have a dictionary.
Dictionary? Whattya mean?
I forgot my dictionary
back at home,
and I haven't been able to study
for the English part of
the entrance examination.
Hey no sweat,
you wanna borrow mine?
Huh? Really?
But what are you going
to do about studying?
Well, it's like this:
I always make sure
I keep up with the assignments,
so I don't find myself
in that position, Motosuwa.
Oh there he goes,
being all unstressed again.
Hmm?
Oh, don't' worry,
it's nothing,
Mr. Shinbo, nevermind.
Well, come on over to
my place and pick it up.
I really appreciate this.
Chi.
It's all right, Chi.
I'll be coming right back.
Chi.
Here y'go.
Thanks...
Okay, let's see now,
"respect" from the Latin,
it's defined as
"to have a high regard."
Is somethin' the the matter?
How many ways am
I supposed to use the word?
That's not a problem, see.
Look, check it out.
It's the difference of
whether you're gonna use it
as a verb, or if you're
gonna use it as a noun.
I see.
Then, what about
as an adjective?
Then that would be
"respectable."
"The town with no people.
The town was...
...completely empty.
There were houses,
and lights could be
seen from the windows.
But, nobody was out
in the streets.
I tried peeking in
from the window.
There was someone there,
but he was together with it.
I looked in the other houses.
They all were together with it.
Because it's fun to be with it.
It's more fun than
to be with people.
So, nobody comes out now.
This town is empty.
I am going on a journey.
I am going to go
to another town.
I think it would be nice
for someone to find me.
But, if the one that is meant
for me should one day happen
to fall in love with only me,
that will be the day
when I will have
to part with the one
that is for me and only me.
Still, I want to meet the one
That is what I think as I walk
through the town with no people.
I... I... I...
Mm-hm.
I think I'm starting to
get it a little bit now,
so I guess I'm gonna
try the rest on my own.
Great!
Go, go, Let's go, Motosuwa!
Thanks for the vote of
confidence, Sumomo!
Hey, I'm back. Uh, Chi?
Chi! Chi!
Chi!
What's the matter with you, Chi?
Chi.
Chi?
What was that?
Are you all right, Chi?
Uh, what happened?
Chi.
Huhhh.
Well, I can't find anything
at all in the
easily visible areas.
I see.
But the thing is,
this is a very unique,
unusual Persocom.
To be honest with you,
I don't have even
the slightest idea
what happened to it.
Or what could even
cause something like this.
So you have no idea.
Anyway, don't stress over it.
Have her take it easy
for a little while,
and if nothing else happens,
she'll probably be fine.
She seems to be
working okay right now.
Thanks a lot.
You've got to be getting tired
of saving me all the time.
Hey, man, don't worry about it.
Do your best, Motosuwa!
Mm.
I'll go back to my place now,
so see you later.
G'nite, Shinbo,
and thanks again.
Hideki, is all right?
It's nothing.
I'm perfectly fine.
Chi.
Huh...
Wow, this is tougher
reading than I thought!
Chi, did you read this book?
The whole thing?
Chi.
Huh?
Ah! How could it be
so late already?! No!
I was planning to get
through at least half
the assignment before dinner!
I haven't gotten anywhere
at all in my studying!
Chi! Chi!
I have no concentration at all!
None! I'm such a chowderhead!
Even if I start right now,
I'm not going to make it.
I'm a failure,
I'm never gonna pass.
Huh?
Chi-i-i-i?
It's all right,
Chi, don't worry.
Chi?
Do your best!
Huh?
Hideki, do your best!
Chi, I-
Chi!
All right, I get it, Chi!
I see you're not gonna let me
give up just yet, are you?
Mm-hm!
Chi?
Umm... hmm... hmm... hmm...
Mmm!
Mm! Mm!
Hideki, do your best!
Huh?
Alright! I'll give
it another shot!
Chi.
Oh, I don't get this.
Chi, can you say it again?
Hideki, do your best!
All right, I've still
got the fighting spirit!
It's no use, Chi.
Hideki, do your best!
Right!
Chi, once more?
Hideki, do your best!
Chi!
All right, class, time's up!
Please pass your
exams to the front.
Ah! That was tough!
Whatcha gonna do now?
Well, I gotta go to work!
Good morning!
Oh, hey there, Yumi.
How are you doin' today?
So, how'd you do?
Uh...
Mm!
I'm home.
Hideki, welcome home!
Chi,
you really helped me out!
Chi?
I can't really say
that I did perfectly
on the exam today,
but I do think I'm going
to get myself
a pretty decent score.
Chi?
It's all because of the way you
wouldn't let me stop,
and kept cheering me on.
I'm really grateful
for all your help, Chi.
Chi.
Oh, that's right.
When I get my next paycheck,
I was thinking
that I'd really like
to buy you something again,
so please look
forward to it, okay?
Chi Look forward.
But, if the one
that is meant for me
should one day happen
to fall in love with only me,
that will be the day
when I will have
to part with the one
that is for me and only me.
Still, I want to meet the one
That is what I think as
I walk through the
town with no people.
Oh, my head hurts!
Hideki, did you hit your head?
No, no.
There are so many things I have
to worry about that
my head is spinning!
Head spinning?
No, no!
It's the electric bill, the gas,
the water, the rent, the food.
Ahh! What am I supposed to do?!
Chi is worried
about Hideki's head.
Somehow that hurts me
in a strange way.
Next episode of Chobits:
"Chi Weakens"
I wonder if Chi ever
gets a headache.