Mmm.
It's so bright.
I really oughta get
some curtains in here.
But before I fix this place,
I gotta clean it up.
Chi.
Oh, that's right!
I forgot, I found a
Persocom last night, didn't I?
Hm?
Chi. Chi.
Look at how cute she is!
I can't believe it;
she's so incredibly cute,
and she can do everything!
Oh, this is gonna be great!
Games! Online shopping!
Personal ads! And Internet porn!
That's right!
Now at last
I get to have it all!
Hey, what're you...
Yah! Why am I getting
so excited in the morning?
Motosuwa!
Hm?
Please pardon the intrusion.
Oh, well ah, this uh...
Well now, what have we here?
Hardly even settled in
and you've already
had a girl over for the night.
That's not too shabby,
I gotta say.
Not too shabby, I've gotta say,
not too shabby, I've gotta say.
It's not like that!
Oh really? Then what is it like?
It's, well, take a
good look at her!
She's a Persocom!
Hm?
Oh, I see what you mean.
See? No matter
how you look at her,
she's a still just a Persocom.
I see. But then again,
you gotta admit,
she's a really cute Persocom!
So this must be what
you were hiding last night.
Huh?! So that's what it was.
I thought you
were hiding something
when I came over.
Uh, well, uh, I uh...
You didn't have to
hide her, you know.
Yeah, you're right,
I suppose not.
Wait a sec.
Didn't you tell me that
you didn't have a Persocom?
Well, uh, it's because I...
Well, to find a computer
like this for free,
I'd have to say
you're nothing less
than incredibly lucky!
You really think so?
Oh yeah, absolutely,
and she's a really cute one.
I see, well I guess I did
get pretty lucky in that area.
So what exactly
can a Persocom do?
The real question is more like:
what do you want her to do?
Huh?
Well, I guess,
among other things,
I wanted to try
going on the Internet.
To get to the net, there's a
little connector right in here.
Chi...
That's all she says.
Hmm? Well, maybe she's broken.
Course, I don't know
anything about computers.
We can use that monitor there.
Monitor? This screen
right over here.
Oh! You mean the TV?
So far so good; it's got
ports for an RGB cable,
so at least we can make
the connection there.
Now in just a second here,
we should be able to
see the default specs
for the system as well
as the CPU speed
and what version the OS is.
I see. Hmm.
I didn't know
anything about that.
Actually, I don't have a
clue what he's talking about.
Oh wow, that's great.
You did it! What's "No Data"?
"No Data" can only mean
that it's all been lost
or there's hasn't been
anything installed on it yet.
Oh, I see.
I don't get it at all.
I don't get it. Huh?
It doesn't make sense.
If she doesn't have an OS,
how can she move?
So they need to
have this "OS" thing
or else they can't move?
Yeah, OS means Operating System.
And unless a computer has system
software installed,
it can't function.
It's a mannequin. I get it now.
And to get the right software,
I'm gonna have to buy it.
And it costs a lot? Yep.
But, which version of the OS
are we supposed
to install in this model?
Hey, can I mess with her?
"Mess with her"? Mess where?
Let's see. That's strange.
I wonder what brand she is.
If she's from PCN,
she'd have her model
number right here.
W-w-w-w-w-w-w-w-w-w-wait!
Now as I recall... Waah!
What are you doing?
No, it's: what are you doing?!
Finding the model number.
Hey, get a grip
on yourself, willya?
Are you gonna be able
to handle a Persocom?
What do you mean?
Hey, she's only a computer!
It's no problem;
I'm gonna be fine!
All right.
I'll let Sumomo check her out.
I'll just connect
them together here.
It's up to you, Sumomo. Aye!
Hm?
Ah! Wait, what's
the matter with her?
She's gone crazy!
Huh?
Oh, my poor little Persocom!
Sumomo's broken!
What's going on?
She's a goner. Oh Sumomo oh!
Oh I see.
This is turning into
a great big mess.
Anyway, I guess I should go meet
this guy that Shinbo
said I should see.
You can walk there;
it's really close.
Uh, by the way,
what do you mean
by "custom-made"?
I've never seen
anything like this model,
and she seems to have
a really monster CPU.
You have to figure that
someone made her by hand.
There are Persocoms
that are made by hand?
Yeah.
This guy's a really
top-notch Persocom specialist.
He might be able to
help you out somehow.
"Custom made," he says.
Anyway, we should go see him.
Chi.
Oh, hello, Mr. Motosuwa
and Miss Persocom.
Hi there.
Chi.
Oh dear, aren't those
clothes awfully loose on her?
Hm?
Well, I-I just got
her last night;
I couldn't get her
any clothes yet.
It's not like I'm a weirdo
dressing her like a man
like some pervert or something!
I see.
Well, if you don't mind
hand-me-downs,
I can let you have
some of my clothes.
Huh?
Are you sure about that?
Thank you very much!
Chi.
You're entirely welcome.
You can just drop by
my apartment any time.
Great!
Well then, we'll be on our way!
Chi!
Have a nice day!
Well that would
really be a big help.
I'll bet women's clothes
are incredibly expensive.
If they're Miss Hibiya's
hand-me-downs,
then that's also gotta mean
that she used to wear them.
Huh? Hah?! Oh no, no!
I can't think those things!
This Persocom is going
to wear these clothes!
Chi!
According to the map,
it should be somewhere
right around here.
Hm?
Is this is the place?!
Okay, now I'm starting
to get a bit irritated.
It's like they think
I'm gonna get all impressed
because he's rich
and everything.
Yes, Kokubunji residence.
Uh, my name is Motosuwa.
Um, is Mr. Minoru in?
Oh yes, we heard
you were coming.
Please come in.
Uh, excuse me.
Don't get a nosebleed
over just a few Persocoms.
You must be Hideki Motosuwa?
Uh, yeah. And you're...?
I'm Minoru Kokubunji.
How do you do?
Ah, Shinbo said
that he knew someone
who was an expert on
custom-made computers.
It can't be. You just look so...
You expected
someone a bit older?
Umm, sorta.
Yes.
Well then, enough
of the pleasantries.
Won't you join us inside?
Please attend to him.
Huh? Attend to--
Hello there.
We'll take off your shoes now.
Huh? Wha?!
Try not to get all hot
and bothered by my Persocoms.
Oh, whatever;
just don't soil them.
Wait, just a minute! Hey!
Wait! Stop that!
What are you...!
Chi!!
No Chi, you don't have
to do what they do!
Okay okay, that's enough,
just stop it already.
Willya knock it off?
I can't take it.
It's this girl.
Huh?!
The mysterious Persocom.
She's the one that
Shinbo was talking about.
Chi?
She's somehow moving
without an Operating System.
W-What's going on here?!
I hope you can repair them.
I thought you said
just a quick check-up.
Hmmm...
I guess my equipment's just not
powerful enough to analyze her.
Four life-size computers
aren't enough?!
Would you like me
to give it a try?
Huh?
Yuzuki.
Please excuse us.
My name is Hideki Motosuwa.
Welcome to our home.
How do you do?
My name is Yuzuki.
So, you would be
Mr. Kokubunji's elder sister?
Oh no. I'm a Persocom
who was custom
built by Lord Minoru.
Gah?!
Lord Minoru?
But.
You are curious to find
out her capabilities, right?
It's a pleasure to know you.
Chi.
Are those sounds
coming from her?
Chi?
That's enough! Yuzuki!
A portion of my data
seems to have crashed.
Which data?
Household chores,
some stock information.
Not your personality data?
No.
Hey, is she okay? Is she hurt?
Chi?
I'm just fine.
There are no ill effects.
Don't worry.
You may rest assured.
Well, that's a big relief.
Chi.
I guess there's not much
chance she'd break, huh?
For starters, she doesn't
even have one of
those OS things, right?
That isn't true.
Huh?
I can't tell you
with any certainty
whether there's been an
Operating System installed
in your computer
or not, Lord Motosuwa.
So you don't know?
No. Her data's
protected very well.
Huh?!
Protected? What's that?
Are you sure you're
going to be alright?
Thank you, I'll be fine.
Lord Minoru has made
the corrections already.
But you said some of
your data had crashed.
Since that data
was all backed up;
we can simply reinstall it
and it will be fine.
And that data in question
was a very small amount.
Oh, I see.
Hm?
Hm? What?
Oh, um, it's nothing at all.
Well, she might be a "chobits."
Chobits? And what
does that mean?
Hmm.
Chobits?
I guess you might call
them legendary Persocoms.
Legendary?!
It's like an urban
legend that's been
floating around on
the Internet for awhile.
Rumor is: there was a series
of Persocoms secretly developed
under the codename "chobits."
Lots of Persocoms are developed
all over the world, right?
After all, you make 'em too,
don't you Kokubunji?
Call me Minoru.
Oh, sure.
"Chobits" are
Persocoms that have
the ability to move entirely
of their own free will.
Huh? Can't Miss
Yuzuki do that too?
She volunteered to do the
analysis for us earlier.
Not really.
Yuzuki merely moved the way
I programmed her, that's all.
She followed the program
that I installed in her.
It tells her what's
right and wrong,
and how to perform various
functions effectively.
All of her actions are
based upon calculating
what she's been programmed.
Of course, she does have her own
automatic learning program.
But then, even those actions
that seem like free will
are actually dependent
upon the learning program.
She can break and on occasions
she'll even freeze up,
but without a program,
she can't do anything.
But, that's not how
the "chobits" are.
Yeah!
So then she's an amazing
Persocom, unlike any other!!
But I'm sure it's just a rumor.
Chi!
It's just one of
those urban legends.
It's comes from a
desire for something
human-shaped that
isn't actually human
and subject to
all our limitations,
yet has free will and emotions.
Is that so?
Chi?
Is she different?
Yes.
She doesn't resemble
any past or currently
produced computer model
in any available database.
Then she must be custom made.
I'll see what I can
find out about this.
There's also a forum for
custom-built computers.
I can always write in and see
if there's anyone who
might have a clue about it.
Thank you.
But what do you
mean by a "forum"?
What's your e-mail address?
I'll write you later on.
Uh, well I don't have one.
Why don't you call me?
Let's see, something
to write with...
Just can just tell Yuzuki
your phone number.
Please say it,
and I'll record it.
You may start.
Uh sure. Let's see.
It's area code 03-688-2852df3
Hm?
Recording completed.
That's amazing.
Mr. Motosuwa,
why don't you ask yours
to repeat your number for us?
Huh?
Why?
Just do it.
So tell me:
what's the number of
my telephone at home?
03-688-2852df3
She spoke!
She didn't just say "chi"!
Well that means
she's already had
her learning software installed.
Really?!
You said you found her
in a dumpster, didn't you?
I wonder if she was
formatted before that?
Either way, her learning
function seems to be working.
I'm sure she'll speak,
if you teach her,
and learn to do all sorts
of other different things.
You think so?
If you treat her
properly Mr. Motosuwa.
Me?!
Oh yes, Mr. Motosuwa.
Since you are her current owner,
she will move, relate, and
respond just as you teach her.
Respond just as I teach her.
So that means I won't have
to get any software then?!
No, you'll have to buy some.
I knew it.
Don't worry.
I don't know what
kind of software
you can install in her.
This'll take some time.
But as she continues
learning more,
I'm sure she'll wind up
telling you herself.
Ah, I get it now,
well thanks for everything!
No problem.
Sorry to bother you.
Please come again when you can.
Mr. Motosuwa!
Huh?
Even if she begins
to speak and manages
to learn various other things
you never thought were possible.
No matter how nice she is,
no matter how cute...
For your own sake,
don't fall in love.
Huh?
If you don't want to cry.
But, that's...
Chi.
Well, let's go home.
She's only a Persocom!
To fall in love, there's no way.
Chi.
She's just so incredibly cute.
Hmm. But, now to teach her.
How'm I supposed to do that?
Chi.
Here you are.
Well, I just hope they're
the right size and all.
Don't worry!
Thank you very much!
I hope I didn't
trouble you at all.
Uh, no, of course not.
What are you talking about?
It's exactly what we
needed, really. Right?
Chi!
That's great.
Oh wow. That's nice.
Why don't you try this one on?
Chi.
Hey, hey, wait a minute!
Chi?
If you go stripping
like that... oh man.
I'll just have to
look the other way!
Is it all right?
Chi.
You look great!
You're so cute.
Okay now, so how can
I start to teach you?
Hmm...
Chi.
Hey, that's it: your name!
Shinbo and Kokubunji, well,
they both have names for
their computers, don't they?
Chi.
Hey, that's the way. Right?
The first thing we've gotta
teach you is your name.
Chi.
Chi?
Chi, huh?
That's it! That's your name!
From now on, your name is Chi.
You understand, Chi?
Chi!
Nah!
Well, I might not know just what
the best approach
is for teaching,
but I promise
you I'll keep trying.
Well, let's do our best
together, right Chi?
Chi!!
For starters,
I guess we should get
you some underwear.
Chi.
Chi, what do you say
when someone's going out?
"Take care."
What's my name?
Hideki.
Good! Okay, and what's that?
Uh, no. It isn't. It's a kettle.
Hideki.
A kettle.
Hideki. Hideki.
That's a table
and a rice cooker.
Hideki. Hideki. Hideki. Hideki.
Chobits next episode:
"Chi Learns."
There are so many Hideki's here,
but the only Hideki that can
make money to live is me?