That's Hideki's magazine.
That's also Hideki's magazine.
Aye! Those are
Hideki's magazines!
Understood!
Oh, there are some
more behind you!
Look, they're all
over the place!
Chi.
Hideki will be home soon.
I see, then!
So he usually comes home
around this time of day!
Understood!
It's Hideki, he's here!
When he comes in,
we say "Welcome home!"
Understood!
Hideki, welcome home!
Chi?
Hideki has no energy.
I also could be in big trouble.
At this rate, I won't get
into college next year!
Chi?
Huh?
Hideki, what's wrong?
Something happen?
Yes, actually.
At prep school today...
No, it's nothing to get all
that worked up about, Chi.
That's right, telling Chi
won't really help anything.
Oh great.
And the summer session's
already started, too!
Chi.
Oh, it's the telephone!
It's the telephone!
Who is it?
It's a telephone call
from my master.
Shinbo? Great, put him on.
Aye!
Yo! So how's it goin'?
Everything okay?
Well you seem to
be doing just fine.
Hey, of course I am!
I'm with the person I love!
Oh, that's right.
You have no idea what
kind of day I'm having.
What's the matter?
You don't sound
all that chipper.
No, I guess not.
So what's going on?
Why'd ya call me?
Oh, right, just a minute.
Hello there, Motosuwa?
Miss Shimizu, is that you?
I wanted to ask you something.
I believe you should be
getting your grades
about now, right?
Oh, sounds like you've
already gotten them.
So, how were they?
I got straight Es.
I see. That's what I thought.
What you thought?
But what do you mean by that?
You're not a bad student.
It's just when
it comes to exams,
your grades tend to
drop off, that's all.
In other words,
you just don't test very well.
And it's a shame,
because you've got
the power to do it
when you really want to.
Really?
Motosuwa, why
don't you try taking
the national mock
exam that's coming up?!
Huh?
A national mock exam?
Yeah. It's just a practice run
to get ready for the real one.
A mock exam would probably
be a good opportunity
for you to check up on
your current skill levels.
Miss Shimizu...
Well, I'm happy you still
consider me your instructor.
Although it's only fair to say
that I wasn't always
an effective one.
Well, thank you
for all your help,
and I think I'll take your
advice about the exam.
That's great. Do your best!
Talk to you soon, man. See ya!
Okay guys, thanks for callin'!
All right! Nothing
is gonna stop me!
I'll show 'em what I can
do when my mind's made up!
Do your best!
Chi.
Let's see. If the
length of the tangent
to the circle from
point K, KT, is beta,
then beta must either
be both of them or...
Hideki.
Good morning, everybody!
Another day begins with
the wakey-wakey exercises!
From the front, reach up high!
One, two, three, four, two,
two, three, four, three-
Hey, Sumomo...
I'm sorry, no exercises today.
Really?
Are you really sure about that?
Oh, what a shame.
Chi.
Huh?
You're taking time off
starting tomorrow?
I have to.
The mock exam's coming up soon,
so I asked if I could
take about a week off.
Well, it's just seems so sudden.
W-what's this all about?
Is she thinking about me?
Well, you know, I...
Well I'll be rooting
for you, okay?
You just do your best, Senpai.
Huh?
Thank you, Yumi.
Hideki, taking time
off from work?
Yeah.
But don't worry,
I'll still be able to come
pick you up after work, Chi.
Chi.
All right!
From now on,
it's nothing but study!
Nothing can stop me!
I'm just gonna
go buy some dinner.
Chi.
Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh?
That's strange.
Hideki, something wrong?
My wallet... it's gone.
Chi.
Gone.
Vanished.
That was all I had,
I cleaned out
my bank account to make
it through the week!
Chi.
Here you go.
What am I going to live
on 'til my next paycheck?!
It's a whole week away!
Chi.
The exam's almost here,
what am I gonna do?
I'm so hungry.
I can't study when
I feel like this.
Hideki, still no energy.
My grades go down,
and my wallet goes
along for the ride.
Insult to injury!
Hideki.
It is now time for Chi to
go to work at the bakery!
Chi.
I'll be going now.
Okay. Be careful.
Thank you very much.
Very much!
Thanks for all the
hard work, you two.
Aye!
Chi, do you mind
telling me what's wrong?
Somehow, you don't seem
to be your usual
cheerful self today.
Chi doesn't understand.
But seeing Hideki not cheerful
makes Chi act like this.
Hideki lost his wallet.
His grades went down,
so he studies all the time.
But Chi can't do
anything for him.
Chi wants to do
something for him.
Chi wants to cheer him up.
Oh, Chi.
As long as you feel that way,
Motosuwa will know it,
and be happy no
matter what you do.
Chi?
Here, this is for the week.
Chi!
Got money for work.
If I give this to Hideki,
he'll be happy.
Aye!
Wha? You want
to give this to me?
Chi. This will make
Hideki cheerful.
Chi.
I'm very happy,
but I just can't accept this.
But why not?
It's like I explained last time:
you worked hard for this money
and it belongs to you
and no one else.
It just wouldn't
be fair if I were
to take this money
from you, Chi.
You have to use this money
for what you want, okay?
Chi.
But, thank you so much;
I really appreciate
what you wanted to do.
And now: study, study, study!
Good morning, Mr. Motosuwa.
Oh. I'm sorry I didn't see you.
Good morning.
Oh my, are you all right?
Your eyes seem awfully red.
I'm sure I'm just fine.
Thanks for asking;
I gotta go now.
I sure hope he'll be all right.
Hideki.
Okay everybody, now
here's a particular type
of equation that
you're gonna find
pretty regularly
on entrance exams.
It's a little tricky at first,
but I'm sure you'll
get the hang of it.
Somehow they seem to think
it's particularly hard,
which it isn't,
or particularly useful...
I wish I didn't always
put up such a big front.
But I guess I'm just like that.
Hey, there!
Where are you going now?
Hideki said Chi should
use her work money
for what Chi wants.
So Chi will use it for Hideki!
So what will you do with it?
I will give Hideki a meal.
The other day, Hideki
was eating these things
that went round and round.
Hideki will like this.
Wow; you're amazing, Chi!
Chi.
Whoa, warning, warning!
Dangerous gasses!
Ventilate immediately,
please ventilate immediately!
Huh?
What's wrong, Chi?
Is something the matter?
Chi.
I see, so it was
for Mr. Motosuwa.
Chi wanted to
work to help Hideki,
but Hideki didn't
want the money.
Is there something
Chi can do for Hideki?
What to do to make Hideki happy?
Hideki always looks very happy
when he reads his magazines!
Let's go buy some of these!
Magazines!
I'm sure you're
right about that.
But I know something he'd
like even more than that.
Chi?
I've never been
so hungry before.
It's impossible to study
when I'm like this.
Huh? Oh, that smell
makes my heart race.
This is no good.
I shouldn't even look at it.
This isn't gonna help me at all.
But if I don't get any
food into my stomach soon,
I won't be able to study.
No!
Mommy, look!
Come on, honey.
I'm so hungry!
Hey, I found the potatoes!
Potatoes go in. Next?
Carrots, red onions,
radishes, peppercorns.
That's right, that's the way.
Got that? The left hand
is a like a cat's paw.
Don't forget.
Chi remembers.
Be careful handling
knives and cleavers.
The left hand is a cat's paw.
I will now prepare the potatoes!
Sumomo, it might be best
if you look after the hot water.
Rice not ready yet.
Oh no, don't; you don't want
to open the lid until the
rice is completely done, okay?
Chi, Understand.
I can't do that!
Bad idea! What am I thinking?!
I can't ask 'em for time off
and then try to get an advance!
To the right! Then to the left!
Chi, Chi.
Oh... That's starting
to smell really good.
Mind if I have a taste,
to see how it's coming along?
Mmm, tasty!
Does this mean Hideki
will be happy again?
Will it cheer him up?
Yes, I'm certain he'll be happy.
Chi.
I haven't been able to get
any studying done at all.
What's gonna happen
if I have to take
the exam like this?
I've got no money.
I've got no food,
and I can't study.
What's gonna happen to me?
I guess Miss Hibiya
is having curry tonight.
Wait a second, what's
that wonderful smell?
Hideki, welcome home!
Chi, what is that smell?
But this is... How?
Chi and Sumomo
learned everything
from the manager;
she was very helpful.
Huh?
Hideki said Chi's
money should be used
for getting what Chi wants.
And so Chi made
a meal for Hideki.
That's what Chi wanted.
Chi.
Hideki hasn't been
very cheerful lately.
If Hideki isn't cheerful,
Chi isn't cheerful either.
So Chi wants to
give energy to Hideki.
Telephone! Telephone!
It's from my master!
From Shinbo?
Hey, how's the studying going?
Uh, well...
Huh?
Well, I guess I was just
a little worried about you.
Hey come on, it's not like
it's the first time I've ever
taken an exam you know.
Okay, maybe not,
but what about the first exam
we took at the prep school?
You forgot to even
put your name on it.
Just be careful
during the actual test.
You're the kind of guy who tends
to lose track of things
when the pressure's on.
Hmm...
Chi.
You're right; it's true.
I've been missing
all sorts of things
that are right in front of me.
See? Just stay calm on exam day.
Yeah.
Sorry about that.
Chi.
What are you apologizing for?
Oh, nothing!
Hey, thanks for everything!
Talk to ya later.
Well, yeah...
Left hand is a cat's paw.
Always skim the top.
Chi learned many things today.
Manager was nice;
manager said it was tasty.
Manager said that it
would make Hideki happy.
Oh, I see.
Hideki is smiling.
It's a long time
since Chi saw that.
Happy? Is Hideki happy?
Yeah, I'm happy, Chi.
Chi is happy when Chi
sees the smile of Hideki.
Wow, Chi it is tasty!
Chi.
Huh?
Oh, good morning, Hideki.
Good morning, Chi.
Chi! What are you
doing dressed like that?!
It's like the one Chi
saw in Hideki's magazine.
Hideki was very
happy looking at it.
Recorded into memory!
Sumomo will dress in the
same manner tomorrow!
Stop that!
Chi, please, listen to me:
you can't wear
something like that!
Chi. Is this bad?
Well no, it's not bad...
No, it's bad! It's really bad!
Chi.
Well. I'll be going now.
Good luck out there!
Do your best! Do your best!
Hideki , do your best.
Do your best!
Do your best! Do your best!
Chi?
Do you want to come with me?
I was thinking maybe we could
go somewhere after the exam.
Oh, and of course,
Sumomo could come with us!
Huh?
Chi.
Hm?
Doesn't this belong to Senpai?
Hideki!
Let's get goin'.
Chi.
O-souji!
Chi?
It makes it more important
when the prefix "o"
gets attached to a word,
even to cleaning!
Chi.
O-mori, O-iri, O-gomi, O-atari.
See, when you add the big "o,"
I feel like something
good happens.
Chi!
O-medama, O-gui, O-boke, OS,
Ole, O sole mio, Oh my god!
O-baka-san.
Eh?
Oh no!
Next episode of Chobits:
"Chi Helps."
By the way,
Miss Hibiya is O-ya-san.
O-baka-san.