Wow! For real?!
I can really borrow
your DVD player?!
Man, this is great,
thank you so much!
Yeah, well.
You're about that
age now, Motosuwa.
You have needs.
You know?
Huh...
But um, keep this
quiet from Yumi, okay?
I promise. I will.
The little shop near
the train station
has plenty of good titles.
And, all this week, they're
having a sale- 20 to 50% off!
For real?!
Also...
And...
Ohh!
That's not all.
Oh, Senpai!
Waah!
Oh, what's going on, Dad?
Are you lending
that to my senpai?
Uh, yeah. I am!
He-he said he didn't have
a DVD player, so I, uh...
Oh, I see...
So, what kind of
things you gonna watch?
Well, let's see, um...
Probably action flicks.
Or maybe they have those shows
to help me with English.
And all sorts of...
That's right!
You're going to be watching
all sorts of things!
Yeah. I am!
Hm?
Come to think of it,
if it's a DVD it ought
to be really easy
to choose the good scenes.
And, I guess I won't
have to rewind it.
Okay, which one should I go for?
Oh yeah. Oo-la-la.
This one looks good.
Mr. Motosuwa.
Wah!
It's good to see you
again, Mr. Motosuwa.
Well, if it isn't
Minoru and Yuzuki!
What a surprise!
What are the two of you
doing in a place like this?
We're here to buy a new net-game
that just came out today.
A new net-game?
It's an online game.
A game where you
use the Internet
to play with many
different people.
You can play games
on the Internet?
Yes.
You can play with
many other people,
and you can also play
along with your Persocom.
What?
So you mean that Chi
and I can play together?
That's right.
If you have the
hardware and software,
all you need to do is to connect
your Persocom and you can play.
Oh wow, imagine that!
To play a game with Chi...
Would you like
to play this game?
I'll give you one if you like.
This is a special promo package,
and comes with an
extra game disc.
Wow! Oh yeah, that's cool.
But I don't have any hardware...
You have a DVD player there.
You can play net-games on that.
Huh, really?!
Certainly.
I'll go on ahead to the checkout
and pay for these things.
You can look for
DVDs of that nature
as much as you want,
Mr. Motosuwa,
Thanks!
What?
Wait, I uh, you've
got it all wrong!
I wasn't really actually
gonna get one 'o these.
Oh, yeah.
Hideki, what is this for?
Oh, that's software
for a net-game.
I borrowed it today from Minoru.
Borrowed from Minoru?
Yeah. It's a game you can play
with all kinds of different
people using the Internet.
Can play with all
kinds of people.
Can Chi and Hideki play, too?
Oh, yeah.
He said you and
I could play together.
Together with Hideki.
Whew.
There, I'm all done setting up!
Alright, Chi, do you wanna
play the net-game with me?
It'll be lots of fun.
Yes!
Chi will play the net-game
together with Hideki!
Okay!
There you go!
And here we go!
Game, game, play with Hideki!
Whoa calm down!
Alright Chi, we'll get
started right away.
Chi!
Hm? Connect to the network?
Huh? Login ID?
Hm?
Hmm...
Chi?
Oh, Mr. Motosuwa...
Good to hear from you.
Have you tried out
that game yet?
Well I'm trying.
But when I look at
the instruction manual,
it's full of things I don't
understand.
So I can't seem to get started.
The screen says
something about needing
a login ID and some
sort of password.
Oh, I see.
Have you gotten yourself
an e-mail account yet?
Well, no.
I don't have anything like that.
Just as I thought.
Mr. Motosuwa,
I'm afraid you can't play
a net-game unless you sign up
with an internet
service provider
and get set up with
an e-mail account.
What?! Really?
Well, what do I do?
Where do I sign up?!
At the back of the
instructions manual,
they should have a phone
number for a service provider.
Just try hooking up
to that number directly
from your screen.
Got it!
Wha...? That's strange...
What do you mean? What's wrong?
It says, "unable to
connect due to user error."
Well, of course it does.
Mr. Motosuwa, you're
using your phone line
to talk to me right now.
Uh...
Well then, I guess
I'll just try to do it
by reading the
instruction manual!
All right. Good luck.
It looks like it's
going to be quite
a while before he
gets the game started.
Huh?
There's a license fee
to play this game?!
What the...?!
They want 1,000 yen a month?!
Oh!
It says right here that
the first month is free.
Huh? I don't get it.
I wonder what a
broadband adaptor is.
Oh, well.
Huh! Wrong password?!
I don't understand!!
Let's see now...
How about if I...
It's awfully bold of him
to sleep in class.
I really don't know what to say.
Agh! I got another
wrong password again.
You know you really
could've at least
done the basic network
set up by yourself.
I'm sorry!
I tried to read the manual,
but I just didn't
understand it at all.
Here you go. It's done.
Huh?
So you mean that it's
already connected up?
That's right.
Chi and Hideki can
play game together now?
It looks that way.
I should've asked
Shinbo to help us
right from the beginning.
Well, I guess we should go
ahead and get started then.
Chi.
Have fun! See ya.
Good night! Enjoy the game!
Hey! Wait!
Don't go back home yet!
You should stay and
play with us for a while!
What?
I was thinking about checking up
on the prep school course
materials for tomorrow...
One day off can't hurt!
It's just a little breather!
Come on, Shinbo, sit down!
Let's play, alright?
Uh...
Geez, you're really
hopeless, you know that?
You're really hopeless!
Chi, you ready?
Chi.
All right!
Start the game!
Wow! Here I am! How cool!
Jump! Jump!
Look- a sword!
Hey, it even changes
facial expressions!
This game is amazing!
Man, you're such a newbie.
This game reacts to the
sound our voices and changes
the facial expressions
and actions accordingly.
Waah! Miss Shimizu!
I'm so sorry!
I'll stop playing the
game right away! I promise!
You idiot. It's me. Shinbo!
Huh? Shinbo?
How come your character looks
exactly like Miss Shimizu?
It's just a coincidence.
I made this character in a rush.
Huh...
But, that face with that voice,
is really kinda weird.
I'm sorry you had to wait!
Now, let's head out
to the adventure!
Why's she so huge?
You get to choose your own size
when you create a character.
Yeah! I can see that!
Huh?
What's wrong?
Chi... Chi's not here!
Chi!
Where are you!! Chi!!
Hey, Chi?! What's wrong?!
Where did you go?!
She won't answer.
When a computer
is playing a game
it always shuts down every
other program and function.
I didn't know that.
Well then, tell me
what happened to Chi?
Why is Chi the only one
of us that's not here?!
I'm sure that she just somehow
got connected to a
different server.
Well, looks like you finally
got connected, Mr. Motosuwa.
Oh, Minoru.
Let me explain.
This game uses a whole
bunch of different servers
in order to limit
the number of people
that can play together
simultaneously in each city.
In other words,
the city we're in is
probably already full,
so there is a distinct
possibility that Miss Chi
was forced to enter
the game in another city.
That is a huge problem!
I have to hurry up
and find her then!
Calm down, would you?
Look, I said there
are other cities,
but you've got to
realize that there
are 20 servers always working,
and each server contains
at least 15 cities,
for a total of--
Listen, I don't care about that!
I can't leave Chi
wandering all by herself
through some game!
I've gotta to go!
Oh, sorry about that.
You know, you complete
newbies are so...
You're a guy?
It gets so much harder
to play this game
when people like you
decide to show up.
So, please, try not to do
anything strange, will you?
W-What was that?!
It's alright, Mr. Motosuwa.
After all, it's not
like this game
was created especially for you.
There should be freedom for
anyone who wishes to play it.
So, I suppose that you'll
always to be an idealist.
Right, Kokubunji?
Wait a minute.
Do you know who I am?
You are pretty famous
on the net you know.
Well, I'll leave you to
get better acquainted
with all the newbies!
Bye, bye!
What's up with that guy?!
Unfortunately there
are mannerless people
like that all over the net.
I hope I don't run into them.
Wait, I don't have
time for this right now.
I've gotta get going!
Chi! I'm coming!
Hey wait, Motosuwa, stop!
Chi! Chi, where are you?!
Chi! Where are you?! Chi!
Hang on, Chi!
I'm coming to find you!
Outta my way!
Huh?
Hey, wait! It's unfair
to attack me like that!
Huh?
I guess you didn't
know that swords
don't work against them.
You should read the instruction
manual more carefully!
Oh, so that was it.
Can it be that this
is the first time
you've played this sort of game?
That's right,
it's my first time.
When I was in high school,
I was busy taking care of cows
and didn't have time for games.
Then going out on
adventure by yourself
is way too much for
you! It's reckless!
You'd be a fool to try it!
Shut up!
Hey! That's why we're
telling you not to go alone!
I know that there
are plenty more
dangerous monsters around!
And that's all the more reason
I can't leave Chi alone!
But it's only a game.
That's right, it's only a game.
No! Get way from me!!
Leave me alone! No!
Hm?
Wah!
Aah! Hot!
Ah, he's really is
a newbie, isn't he?
This really is too much to bear!
It's totally reckless!
He's really acting stupid!
Shut up!
I-I couldn't find her
after all that work.
The game is now over.
Good job today.
Chi.
Chi?
Oh hey, Chi.
Where were you in the game?
Chi does not know.
But, Chi heard Hideki's voice.
You mean you could hear me?
Yes, but Chi was not
together with Hideki.
Hey I know!
How about we play
again tonight, Chi!
This time, I'm sure
we can play together!
Chi!
Good morning!
Oh yeah, right.
Good morning.
Have a good day you two.
Oh, I don't believe it.
They both have got some
nerve sleeping in class again.
Oh, Chi, where did you go?
This isn't good.
I ended up falling asleep
during class again today.
Am I really going to make it
through the entrance
exams like this?
Hey, Motosuwa.
Hm?! Yes?
It's my pleasure!
Mm-hm So, how was it?
Huh?
Are you enjoying it?
Uh...
What are you talking about?
You know, the DVDs!
You don't look like
you've had any sleep.
Have you been up all night
watching them you dog?
Uh, no! I haven't had
the chance to buy any.
You what?!
You haven't even
watched any yet?!
That won't do!
You can borrow these!
Sir, are these what
I think they are?
Yeah, they're from
my private collection!
You can return them
whenever you want.
Wow! Oh thank you!
Hey there! What are
you guys doing?
Waah!
Oh, I see you've got some DVDs!
What kind of movies
did you borrow, Senpai?
Action flicks!
Yeah, that's right!
I borrowed some action flicks!
Yeah! Those are from
my private collection
of special action flicks!
Hm?
Oh boy.
I'm sure that Chi
is looking forward
to playing that
game again tonight.
This time, I'm sure
we can play together!
Chi!
Of course I did say that.
I really can't be playing games
every single night of my life.
All right!
I feel bad for Chi, but I'll
get a good night's rest tonight,
and study hard
starting tomorrow!
Magical... Life Healing...
Player Items...
I'm home, Chi!
Welcome home, Hideki!
Play game again today!
This time, together with Hideki!
Uh... Yeah, okay I guess.
Uh, explain to me why
it is we're here again?
Aw, come on Shinbo,
it's gonna be fun!
I mean, the more
the merrier, right?
And today, Chi is going
to be with us, too.
Chi.
Okay, let's start the game!
Huh?
Ah!
Where is Chi! Why isn't
she with us again?!
This is pretty strange.
The server really isn't
all that crowded today.
Maybe it isn't the
number of people.
Then where is she?
Is she in some other city again?
There are cases
in which a computer
will not be allowed
to play the game
if the task-handling skills of
the computer are too high
and puts extra
pressure on the servers!
Darn!
Hey, wait!
Hey Chi! Hey Chi!
Where are you?!
Don't worry! I'm coming!
Warning, warning!
Danger! Danger!
Do not act alone!
Repeat: do not act alone!
Oh, shut up!
No, that's not it!
You can't go that way!
Darn it! Take that you...
Ugh!
That's why I keep telling you
to not to use magic so much!
Wait for me, Chi!
Hi... de... ki.
Wha...
What the heck is that thing?
That thing is the boss monster!
We'll never be able
to defeat him.
Why? Is he really that strong?
Yeah. I've seen info in
magazines and on the web.
Nobody has been able
to defeat him yet.
Warning, warning!
Danger, danger!
Everyone, please
evacuate immediately!!
But if we can
get by him somehow,
we can go on to
the next city, right?
Hey wait, are you serious?
Don't do it.
There's no way you can
win against this guy.
Yeah but...
Chi might...
Chi might be somewhere
waiting for me!
Motosuwa!
Oh man, that guy is hopeless!
Sumomo!
Aye!
Carbonara!
Chorizo!
Ahh!!
Ahh!
Ah, man. We're finished already?
Chi!
Chi? Is that you?
Chi? Chi? Is it you?
Dah! Hey! Hey wait minute!
Chi was right there!
I was touching her hand!
Hey, rewind it, will ya?!
What are you talking about?
This isn't a
videotape, you know.
But, that light.
I wonder what it was?
It sure did seem like Chi...
The game is over!
Good job everyone!
Chi?
That was great, Chi!
You totally defeated
the boss monster!
Chi doesn't remember anything.
Huh?
What do you mean by that?
Chi?
Chi, started out missing,
but then she appeared
as a different character
and defeated the
invincible boss monster.
Perhaps that means
that Miss Chi has
so much task-handling power
that she surpasses
the game servers?
Well, if that's really the
case, her CPU is on par
with the fastest
supercomputers ever built.
Hideki, no more games tonight?
No, Chi, we've already
finished this one,
and it would be really bad
if I lost track of
you in a game again.
Chi could not play game
together with Hideki.
Hey, how 'bout we play
a different game then!
One where we don't have
to connect to the internet!
Chi.
Chi?
Here. Different game.
That's not a game!
Hideki, let's play
this together!
C-Chi! Don't! Please!
That's not a game!
Not a game?
Um, well, no it's...
What is it?
Wah!
Don't make it into college
and you have no vacation!
It's study, study,
and study some more!
Hideki, what is this?
That's a beach parasol.
"The word 'parasol' is Italian."
And this?
An inner tube.
The buoyancy of an
object in water is equal
to the mass of the water
the object displaces.
This?
A swimsuit.
To wear, wears,
wore, worn, wearing.
Where is this?
The beach.
Wait a second!
Why am I at the beach?!
Next episode of Chobits:
"Chi Goes to the Ocean!"
This is a problem.
I'm having fun!!