My paycheck from Bakery Tirol.
Hideki said Chi could
buy anything she wants
with this money
because it's hers.
But then...
What Chi really wants is
to give something to Hideki.
This is a bookstore.
Lots of books.
Lots of study guides.
Lots of girlie magazines.
Hideki has this. He has this.
He has this. He has this.
This is one Hideki doesn't have.
Give this to Hideki.
I wonder if Chi's all right.
I know there's nothing I can do;
she insisted on
going by herself.
But I keep thinking about
what happened back
at that peep show.
No point getting
worked up about it.
She'll be fine; she's
learned a lot since then.
I hope she didn't get lost.
Maybe letting her
go out all by herself
wasn't such a great idea.
Hey!
Shinbo.
There you are.
You workin' today?
No, I've got today
and tomorrow off.
So, what's up?
I thought I'd see if you were
into goin' to the bathhouse.
A bath?
You mean at this time of day?
Hey, what are you talking about?
That's the whole
reason it's so great.
Huh?
Well I just took
a bath yesterday.
Yeah well it's not
like it makes it okay
because you had
a bath last night.
Here, anyway, let's get going.
Hey!
See?
Ya come this time
of day, and it's empty.
We got the place
all to ourselves.
I'm tellin' ya it's about
as good as it gets.
What's the matter,
are you still worried?
Well, don't go
being gloomy about it;
you're the one who let
her go by herself, ya know.
And she's starting to talk
a lot better too, isn't she?
Yeah.
Okay, so let's go in.
Oh yeah well since
we're on the subject here:
I don't suppose you
bathe your Persocom?
Huh?
Bathe my Persocom?
What do you mean?
Oh, right.
I guess you don't know
anything about that either.
You see that?
Persocoms - 200 yen?
Y-You're right.
So you're supposed to wash
Persocoms in the bath?
That's the basics, man;
it's just common sense.
Common sense.
Look, when I say
bathe your computer,
it's not a social thing;
I mean actually cleaning it.
Cleaning it?
Yeah.
It's something you
really shouldn't put off;
it's a part of your
routine maintenance.
So then, you bathe
your Persocom, too?
Sumomo?
Well, she's so small,
I just dunk her
in cleaning fluid and
she scrubs herself off.
Hmm...
But regular Persocoms
are human-size,
so you really need a bath.
After that, though,
she'll be as fresh as new.
I see.
So I just have to
bring Chi here, right?
Well, the thing is your Persocom
doesn't know how to
bathe yet, does she?
Huh?
You see, usually you buy
cleaning software
and install it.
That way, your Persocom
learns the proper way
to bathe and can wash itself
without needing any help.
But I don't have the
money to buy software.
Then, you've got no choice,
there's only one thing to do.
What's that?
You'll just have
to wash her yourself,
right here in the bath.
Me? You mean me wash her myself?
You mean here?!
That means I'd be naked, and...
and then I'd have to strip her,
and we'd be right here
with all the people watching,
and they'd all be and I'd be...
Are you completely
out of your mind?!
Come on, I was just kidding.
You'll just have to teach
her how to do it, that's all.
Teach her what?
How to take a bath!
Whadda ya think
I'm talkin' about?
She's already got learning
software installed somehow,
so ya just gotta teach her how,
and after that she can go to
the women's bath by herself.
That way, all ya have
to do is pay for her bath.
I see.
A bath, huh?
I bet a nice refreshing bath
would make Chi very happy.
I'm back!
Welcome home, Hideki!
Hi Chi, well it looks like you
were able to get home okay.
Hideki, Chi went shopping.
You know, Chi.
What is it Chi?
It's this.
Chi bought it for Hideki.
Huh?
So, you had to go alone,
'cause you were shopping for me.
Chi.
Thank you Chi; I can't
tell you how happy I am.
Chi!
No, Chi! Wait!
Hideki looks happy!
Hideki! Hideki!
When Hideki is happy,
Chi's face is happy too.
It makes Chi's mouth go up.
Well, that's called smiling.
Chi is smiling.
Is smiling a good thing?
Oh, absolutely.
It means that you're very happy.
Very happy.
I'm so happy.
That's right, Chi!
I've got something for you, too.
Well, it's not that big a deal,
but I'm gonna try to teach
you something really good.
Something good?
Yeah I'm gonna teach
you how to take a bath.
A "bath"?
Yeah, bathing is what
you do to clean your body.
You ready?
Alright, now when you
go to the bathhouse,
the locker room's the
first thing you're gonna see
when you step inside.
You got that?
So that's where you
take off your clothes,
and put them in an empty locker.
Oh.
Chi.
Oh, I'm sorry,
what was I thinking?
I should've opened
your present first.
This is great,
I wonder what it is?
Chi.
Hideki, you said you
wanted to get new magazines.
You like it?
Well, yeah, a bath,
as I was saying, uh...
Chi
Yeah, baths are where...
lions and hot water...
and water pouring out of their
mouths and you can just...
Hideki not happy with magazine?
I'm very happy with it, Chi.
As happy as I can be.
As I was saying,
a bath is like...
Hideki smiling. Chi happy.
A bath is...
You're completely hopeless!
I'm sorry, it's just that
after seeing
something like that,
there's no way I'm gonna
be able to teach her myself.
Ya gotta help me...
Please?
I've seen active
imaginations before,
but you take the cake.
Searching the web...
searching the web...
That's a hit.
I found the information!
Good job.
Now see if there's any
data you can download
from there that has instructions
for bathing procedures.
Aye!
Well this should take
care of it in just a minute.
She's downloading the
data from the website now,
and when she's done, she'll
perform the actions from it.
You just need to have your
Persocom mimic those actions.
Thank you.
Chi, I want you to do exactly
what Sumomo does, okay?
Chi.
All files are good,
and download is complete.
Very good, now go ahead
and run the data for us.
Aye!
Understood. Starting now.
Hot, hot, hot! Oh, it's hot!
What's that all about?
Ow, hot, hot, hot!
Oh, hot, hot! Ooh it's hot!
Hot, hot, hot! It's hot!
Oops, I guess it's some
kinda scalding bath website.
It's hot, it's hot!
It's hot! Ah!
S-S-Shinbo!
Sumomo, not that.
We need software on
taking a regular bath,
so you can get clean.
Hey, wait, I can't afford
to buy any software!
With any luck, we'll be able to
find some Freeware.
Try again, Sumomo.
Aye!
Download successful!
Running program now.
But Sumomo, isn't that-?
The program is named:
"The Appropriate Manners
for Taking a Bath."
Rule one: coffee-flavored
milk must be drunk
with your hand
resting on your hip!
Chi
No!
That one's just as bad,
Sumomo; now try it again!
Aye!
Download is successful!
Running program now.
That's not it! Try again!
Aye!
Download is successful!
Running program now.
So we couldn't figure
out how to teach her
to bathe last night after all.
Now what do I do?
Chi go to work.
Oh, hang on.
I'll walk you over
to the bakery.
The bathhouse Hideki mentioned
to Chi yesterday,
is Hideki going there?
Huh?
Oh yeah, that's right;
we'll go there
right after you get
home from work, Chi.
Understand.
Hmm?
Motosuwa here.
Hello, this is Kokubunji.
Oh! It's been a while, Minoru.
Um...
I don't suppose you have
some free time this afternoon?
Sure, I don't have
prep school today.
There's...
There's something I'd
like to talk to you about.
Talk? Hey, that's perfect!
I've got something that I'd
like to talk to you about too.
Where do you wanna meet?
How about 4 o'clock at Duklyon,
across from the train station?
Do you know it?
Yeah, that'd be fine.
Huh?
You want to know the best way
to teach your
Persocom how to bathe?
Yeah.
I thought I'd have Shinbo's
Persocom show her how,
but when we tried it yesterday,
it didn't work out very well.
What do you suppose would be
the best way to go about it?
There are many approaches,
but there's one simple way.
Yeah? Really?
What I mean is that it's
up to you, Mr. Motosuwa;
you'll have to teach
Chi how to bathe herself.
And down to the
very last detail.
I sorta tried doing that,
but all I can say is it
really didn't work out...
If you don't want
to buy the software,
you're just going to have to
accept that it's the only way.
Yeah, I guess that's
the only way after all.
Is Hideki going
to the bathhouse?
Well, she definitely
seemed happy about the idea.
All right! I can do it!
I'll give it everything I've
got and tryta teach her again!
And as long as
I don't let myself think
any bad thoughts,
it should be just fine!
Bad thoughts?
Oh no, I don't mean bad,
I mean not really bad,
you know, I mean...
Hot!
Oh, that's right...
So what did you want
to talk about, Minoru?
Yes, well it was
something about Chi.
About Chi?
I told you this
before, didn't I?
That I was going
to post something
on a BBS for
custom-made Persocoms?
Well I did, and
I got a response to it.
I thought it best to tell you
about it as soon as I could.
Wait a minute!
What's this BBS thing?
It's basically just an
electronic bulletin board
that people use on the internet.
All sorts of people
post things there.
I never realized such
useful things even existed.
So that might just be the place
to find the best way to
teach a Persocom to bathe.
Huh?
Oh no, nothing, nothing at all.
So did someone out there
have something to say about Chi?
Yes, I got some
replies all right.
Oh, a reply is a post written
in response to my post.
Most of them were things like
"That's the kind of
Persocom I'd love to have!"
or "I'd like to get a chance to
check out the specs on her"...
And I also got this one e-mail
with an image file attachment.
A "file attachment"?
I'm not sure if this
particular information
pertains to Chi,
but here, take a look.
But, this is...?
I agree.
It does appear to
be Chi, doesn't it?
Well, I'm not sure, but it
certainly looks like Chi.
But what's with these weird
things all over the place?
What's that all about?
They're some kind of connectors,
as far as I can tell, but
I've never seen them before.
Are you sure it's not a prank?
Maybe they think it's funny
and they're playing a game.
Or could be they saw
Chi out in public one time,
and they took a photo of her
and then doctored it up somehow.
It is possible.
But then... there's
something not quite right.
But don't you have any
idea where it came from?
You can't send an e-mail
without some kind of
return address on it, right?
So if you know what that is...
Yes, there was definitely
a return address on it.
But every time I send a reply,
it just bounces back.
Why?
Either the address
is no longer in use,
so it's just a mistake,
or somebody sent it with
a fake e-mail address...
on purpose.
What would make someone
want to do a thing like that?
Perhaps the sender
preferred to remain...
untraceable.
Look at this.
What if the letter hidden under
the arm right here is a C?
C-H-O-B-I-T, huh.
Chobits?!
I believe I told you about them.
About the legendary Persocoms
that go by the
codename "chobits."
They have real
feelings and emotions,
and unlike other computers,
they act on their own will.
They have human forms,
but aren't exactly human...
Is that photo really Chi?
Is she really some
super powerful computer
called "Chobits"?
That was pretty funny.
Yes, what would you
like to see next?
Let's see...
There are so many
Persocoms around here.
Hideki!
Chi!
Work is over!
So I see.
And now, a bath!
Are we going together
to the bathhouse?
Yeah, Chi; that's right.
Okay, I'm gonna teach you
how to take a bath right now.
Chi.
But, before we do that...
There that'll do it.
Alright, so the
first thing you'll do...
is to enter the
locker room, like this.
Locker room?
That's right: when you
enter the bathhouse,
the first room you go
into is the locker room.
And once you're there,
you take off your
clothes like this.
Chi
Ah-h-h-h-h-
No, you don't have
to do it right now!
Right.
Now to explain the bath
and how to use the tub.
The tub?
The bathtub's sorta
like a swimming pool.
It's a great big tub
filled with lotsa hot water
and it feels really good
when you get inside it.
Chi understands!
Huh?
The bath in Hideki's magazine!
Chi saw this before!
No!
Do you think you know
how to take a bath now?
Chi.
Don't forget: you have
to wash your body
with soap before
entering the bath.
Chi.
And if there's
something you don't know,
just look at the
people around you
and copy what they're doing!
Got that?
Chi.
Okay, see you later.
I wonder if Chi is all right.
But then again,
I think I've pretty much
taught her everything I can.
And anyway, things
like this always seem
to go a bit smoother
than you think
when you actually
get down to doing them.
Yeah! It's gonna be fine.
It's gonna be just fine.
Sir.
Excuse me, sir!
Hmm?
Over there.
Huh?
Chi, what on earth are you
doing in the men's locker room?
Hideki said Chi should watch
other people and copy them.
Huh?
Chi watched Hideki
and copied Hideki.
Hideki walked in here,
so Chi walked in here.
No, that's not it;
you can't follow me.
You hafta go into
the women's bath!
Chi, you go here!
Chi, together with Hideki.
Aww, geez, I don't know.
What am I supposed to do now?
Oh?
Oh, Miss Manager, hello.
That's good, and then
we'll wash this end.
Chi.
Wow, what a lucky break
to have her come by.
For a moment there,
I thought I was sunk.
Miss Landlord is
bigger here than Chi.
Huh?
Just like Hideki's magazine.
Oh... Oh, my...
I'm very sorry about all this.
And thank you for helping me
take care of Chi all the time.
Oh, that's all right.
And please feel
free to let me know
when you need to take
Chi to the bathhouse again.
Oh sure; thank you very much!
There we go, all done.
Doesn't she look nice?
There is nothing like a summer
kimono right after a bath!
Isn't it a nice feeling, Chi?
Hideki!
Huh?
Hideki is smiling!
Uh...
Wow, what a day.
At least the whole
bath thing worked out okay;
I'm glad that's over with.
Oh, that's right, I forgot.
I borrowed this from
Minoru when I saw him today.
Uh, hey...
This photo, is this
a picture of you, Chi?
No. This is not Chi.
All right!
Then it really was
just a prank after all!
Oh, I'm so glad.
I really am relieved.
There was no
need to worry at all.
That's right, Chi is...
Chi is Chi, and that's that!
Hey, look at that: there's
something else in here.
Oh...
It looks like a continuation
of that other book.
Very mysterious...
just like the first one.
That's right.
Chi bought that too.
Together with Hideki's new book.
Chi also wanted that one.
Well, I'm glad you got it.
It's your money; and you
earned it by working, Chi.
And you should use it to buy
whatever it is you
want from now on.
Chi.
Imagine you go out
on a date, Chi.
Bathhouse.
That's bad!
You don't want to go someplace
where you're separated
at the beginning.
On a date you want to go
where you can stay
together as long as possible!
Bookstore?
That's even worse!
You have to be so quiet there!
The real key to a date
is the conversation!
The more you talk,
the better the mood becomes!
Chi.
Well, at least that's
what the guidebook said.
Next episode of Chobits:
"Chi Meets."
Studying and dating both
require serious research!
Chi!