Are you The One
that is Just for Me?
I, uh...
Chi is in love with Hideki.
Is Hideki in love with Chi?
Chi, I...
This is the...
It's a voice.
What is it? Is something wrong ?
Yuzuki!
Miss Sumomo!
Hm?
That voice again.
Uh, what is it?
Hey, come on, you two,
what's going on?
Hey!
Chi.
Chi, I...
I...
I'm in love with you, Chi.
Hideki.
I found...
the person just for Chi.
Chi.
Chi?
I must do it. Myself...
and my other self.
Chi?
Chi!
Yuzuki!
Hey, are you guys okay?
H-Hey!
Chi has found.
The One Just For Me.
Chi's special person.
The one just for me.
The person just for Chi.
Chi has found.
The One Just For Me.
Chi's special person.
The person just for Chi.
What is that voice?!
Somehow it's echoing
directly into my CPU!
We're all hearing
the same thing.
Because that girl is
linked to all Persocoms.
You and I were
supposedly designed
so we'd be immune to it.
But we do come from the
same system after all.
Whoever the enemy is...
I don't care.
I'm going to do it
before it's too late.
I'm going in!
Don't get in my way.
Surprising...
to be able to bounce Dita's
attack program like that...
If I can't hack my way in,
I'll connect directly!
Sorry about this,
but I'm gonna stop you!
Chi!
What are you doing?!
Get away from her!!
Hope you'll forgive me.
Let me go! Who are
you guys, anyway?!
And what are you doing to Chi?
We're Persocoms.
We were specifically
created to stop this girl.
What's that?!
She is a dangerous Persocom.
Dangerous? Chi?!
What are you doing?!
He's an outsider;
you're not supposed
to say things like that!
He's not an outsider.
He is "The One Just for Me."
This girl is
programmed to connect
to every Persocom in
the world, and then,
when she decides who
"The One Just for Me" is,
she's designed to
run a certain program.
What are you talking about?!
What is Chi supposed to do?
I can't answer that;
because I have no data
concerning what will happen.
We were created to
keep it from occurring;
not to predict what
the outcome might be.
We're designed
to stop the program
and make sure it
never runs again.
That means...
That we're gonna destroy
the OS and stop all functions.
We're going to annihilate her.
Stop it! Don't do it! Chi!
Lemme go!
Why in the world are you getting
so worked up over a Persocom?
Someone I care about's being
erased right in front of me.
You would, too, if you--
You forget: Persocoms don't
have those kind of emotions.
Nothing good ever comes out
of a romance with a Persocom.
Persocoms are too
different from humans.
Yeah, well whether she's
a Persocom or a human,
that just doesn't matter to me.
'Cause I fell in love with Chi.
Chi and nobody else.
Zima?!
Hey, what're you doing?
Chi!
What're you trying to do, Zima?
I want to see it now.
His... no, their future.
And the future of Persocoms.
I must do it.
Myself and my other self.
Chi!
Chi has found.
The One Just For Me.
Chi's special person.
The person just for Chi.
Hideki.
Darling...
Chi! Chi!
Chi, thank goodness!
Are you all right, Chi?
Chi?
Chi.
It can't be!
Hideki.
I am not Chi.
Chi?
I am...
Freya?!
I am Freya.
What does this mean?
I dunno.
CPU, hard drive, system...
everything's normal.
How 'bout you, Zima?
Yeah...
Lord Minoru...
Yuzuki!
Are you all right?!
Anything wrong?!
No, everything's fine.
Was it the same voice as before?
Yes, but...
It was definitely the same,
but this time the
voice sounded very sad.
Huh?
You had me worried there.
So're you guys
back to normal now?
You okay?
Aye!
That voice... there it is again.
Freya?
Miss Hibiya.
Freya!
Mama.
What is it?
Why did you come back?
Freya, where is Chi?
Where did she go?
Please tell me what's
happened to her?
But wait a minute.
Chi's original name
was Elda, wasn't it?
Freya disappeared
because of her feelings
about your husband, right?
When the pain in
my heart made it
so I could no longer move,
and I thought that
I was almost gone for good...
Come to me.
Before you disappear, Freya,
transfer your heart inside mine.
I will protect you.
I will protect
your heart, Freya.
So please, come in.
And we can be one.
Freya. You were
there the whole time?
But what about Chi?
Tell me what happened to Chi!
Miss Hibiya, can you
explain this to me?
You know I don't know
much about Persocoms,
and I have no idea
what's going on!
Chi has disappeared.
Disappeared?
Chi has found
"The One Just for Me."
She was doing what she had
to do once she found him,
but she stopped in the middle.
Why did she stop?
Because she found out,
that even if Persocoms
fell in love with people,
there were things
they just couldn't do.
Even if "The One Just for Me"
were to fall in love with me.
I couldn't do anything.
I don't know much,
but I know you're wrong.
There's no difference between
humans and Persocoms
when it comes to
things like this.
I know, because
I fell in love with Chi.
Maybe so, but Chi didn't
think so for some reason.
Chi! Can you hear me?!
I know you're in there!
Ya gotta believe me!
Please come out!
Freya, we need to know
what happened to Chi.
I can't answer that;
because I'm unable access her.
Mama, I'm afraid
there's no other way.
The time has finally
come to destroy us.
How can you say
something like that?!
I was in love with Papa.
When the pain in my heart was
so strong that I couldn't move,
I thought about telling
him my true feelings
when you weren't there.
But I couldn't do it.
You must face the facts:
we are a failure.
Darling...
Mr. Motosuwa, please forgive me.
Huh?
"Chobits."
Huh? "Chobits"?
Entered.
Password and voice
recognition are confirmed.
Miss Hibiya, what is it?
What are you going to do?
Well, isn't this an
interesting turn of events?
I guess it means that program
won't be running after all.
Standing by, master.
Please give me
your instructions.
No! Don't do it!
Deletion of all data, and
termination of your system.
Chi, don't!
Confirmed.
Proceeding with deletion of all
data and termination of system.
No! You can't do this! Chi!
Initiate.
Chi!
Procedure completed.
"Chobits"!
"Chobits"! "Chobits"!
I'm afraid it won't work.
For it to be recognized,
the password has to be spoken
in either my voice
or my husband's.
Chi really was in love with you.
I'm pretty sure you know that,
but I just wanted
to say it anyway.
And that was why she
decided to pull away
from you like that in the end.
I'm sorry, it looks
like the only thing
I brought to you was
sadness, Mr. Motosuwa.
So it's all over.
We should get going, huh?
It's too bad.
I thought he might have actually
be able to change things.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Chi.
I guess I really
didn't understand
anything about you after all.
And in the end, all I did
was bring you so much pain.
I never even got the
chance to teach you
what true happiness really is.
Hey, if Chi is still
in there somewhere,
do you think it would be
possible for you to teach her?
Teach her about happiness,
and how it's about
being together
with the person you
truly love no matter what.
And also about how there're
going to be lots of hard times
and painful times, too,
you can't avoid them.
But that stuff doesn't
matter at all in the end,
because just so much
better to be together
than it is to be apart.
All I want to do
is make Chi happy.
What is it?
A long time ago, something
very bad happened to me.
It still makes my heart ache.
It made me very, very, very sad.
It was very painful.
It hurt a lot when
I lost something so dear.
But, I am searching.
For the person just for me,
someone who will love me
because I am myself.
And, I found him.
But that was the beginning of
something even more painful.
It is painful to be next to him,
though I could not do anything.
It is painful to see
him go through pain.
That is why I decided
to stop being
in front of him and disappear.
I disappeared
because I loved him.
And yet, it's even more painful
being unable to see him.
And even more painful
not being able to meet him.
I parted ways with him
because I loved him.
You parted ways
though you loved him?
Because that meant
happiness for him.
What is happiness?
Happiness is...
Hideki.
Is this your happiness?
My happiness is right here.
My happiness exists
only inside him.
Even if it's painful?
Even if it makes
your heart ache?
Even if it makes my heart ache,
I want to be with him.
Yes.
I found it.
Chi's happiness.
Chi.
Chi!
Yuzuki!
I hear a voice again.
But it seems to be
different from the last one.
The voice seems very pleasant;
and somehow kinder and warm.
Oh, not this again!
Come on, you guys!
Hey, wait a minute.
Zima!
Do you think she might have...?
Yeah.
Uh-oh! Let me check it out!
It's all right.
Oh, Zima...
Why are blushing like that?
After all, you're a Persocom.
Hideki.
Hm?
Chi is a Persocom.
That's right.
Chi is not human.
There are things
that Chi cannot do.
I know.
But Chi wants to be
together with Hideki.
I know, Chi.
I want to be together
with you, too.
Darling...
This town is full of people.
This town is full of them.
Everyone falls in
love with someone,
and is in turn loved by someone.
All sorts of people,
and all sorts of them,
live in all sorts of places.
Oh, sorry about that.
Among lots of people...
and lots of them,
he had found me.
Good morning.
Good morning to you.
He had fallen in love with me.
Lord Minoru,
I brought you some tea,
would you like to take a break?
I am here right now.
Thank you, Yuzuki.
I am here together with him.
One, two, three, four!
We are happy.
I'm home!
Hideki!
Welcome home!
I am happy.