[KUROKO sighs]
Here we go again.
You're not coming home
tonight, are you, Sissy?
But earlier today you said all
of this would be over for good.
[KUROKO] The look on her face.
There was something there.
I cannot just
continue to ignore this.
There may well be something I
can do to help the situation.
Regardless of what
Sissy might say.
No... I made up my mind.
I told myself I would wait.
[KUROKO] Sissy.
What is going on with you?
[gasps] No!
I must stop this right now!
If I breathe in her scent
for too long, I'll pass out.
I really hate this!
I wish there was some way
to know what I should do!
[bell rings]
[KUROKO] Just-Just a minute!
A visitor to the dorms?
That's unusual.
Yes?
[KAMIJO] Um, yeah, hi.
Is Misaka there?
This is Kamijo.
[KUROKO] Hm...
[KAMIJO] Hello? Are you there?
Is this stupid
thing even working?
[KUROKO] I know that face.
He's the troglodyte I saw with
Sissy by the vending machine!
He must have been
captivated by Sissy's beauty
and followed her back here!
She's in goodness knows how
much trouble, and he thinks
he can just casually make
an appearance like this!
I let him slide before
because I thought he would be
a good example for Sissy of
how useless boys truly are,
but this situation is swiftly
becoming unacceptable!
On the other hand!
There is the possibility
that he might know
something about Sissy!
This is room
two-oh-eight, or is it?
[KITTY meows]
Ow! Hey! Cut it out!
[KUROKO] Even if he
does know something,
I told myself I
was going to wait.
[KAMIJO] Calm down!
It's all right.
Put the claws away!
So, your name's Kamijo?
Oh, whoops.
I guess I have the
wrong room, I'm sorry!
[KUROKO] No, no,
you are not mistaken.
You came here looking
for Sissy, correct?
I live here with her.
I'm Sissy's roommate.
Oh, okay. Hello then.
I take it Misaka's not home.
[KUROKO] She's not.
However, I am expecting
her at any moment now.
If you have something
pressing to discuss with her,
I recommend you
come in and wait.
Oh. are you sure?
[KUROKO] That would
be the best idea
if you do not wish to miss her.
Besides, when curfew hits, the
dorm security will be activated,
and you will no longer be
able to wait in the lobby.
[knocking]
[KUROKO] Come in.
Really, go ahead.
The door is not locked.
You can open it from out there.
Um, maybe I should--
[KUROKO] Don't just stand there.
Come into the room, and
close the door please.
[KAMIJO] Uh, oh, right.
[KUROKO] I apologize.
This room is primarily
intended for sleeping in.
I'm afraid it does not
offer much in the way of
entertainment for guests.
There is no telling how long
you'll be waiting for her.
You might as well have
a seat over on the bed.
[KAMIJO] Uh, no thank you.
I don't think I could do that.
Not without her permission.
[KUROKO] Then you have
no reason to worry.
That one there's
actually my bed.
Huh? What are you doing
on somebody else's bed?
Are you some kind of pervert?
That's really creepy.
You're here at an all-girls
dorm and you call me a pervert?
Everyone has their own
secret, special habits.
They may seem strange
to other people,
but that doesn't make them
wrong or perverted at all.
Like you never secretly
pressed your lips
to your
crush's picture.
or stole the seat from
her bicycle to caress.
No, I haven't!
Shh!
It would be best if you avoided
raising your voice so loudly.
Things will turn ugly if
anybody outside hears you.
Yeah, okay.
[KAMIJO] Hey, you know,
if you guys share a room,
doesn't that make the
two of you classmates?
"Sissy" sounds more like a
nickname for an upperclassman.
Well sure. She is
older than I am.
In fact, I'm actually
a full year behind her.
I saw to it that her previous
roommate was reassigned
and then I took her place.
And it was all totally
legal of course.
Uhh...
Anyway, what business
do you have with Sissy
that brings you here so late?
[KUROKO]
Just a moment!
On second thought,
you need not tell me.
I have already resolved not
to act on any information
I may acquire.
[KAMIJO] Uh-huh.
[KUROKO gasps]
Hey! Did you hear that?
It sounds like a patrol!
If the head resident finds
you here in this room,
it's going to mean big
trouble for both of us!
[KAMIJO] Who's that?
A dangerous, intrusive
person who likes to do
room inspections
without prior warning.
There's no choice.
I have to send you
outside until she's gone.
Huh? I don't get it.
Why isn't my power working?
Well, here's the thing.
[KUROKO] We have no time!
Get down there!
You just have to hide
underneath the bed!
[KAMIJO] There's no room!
[KAMIJO grunts]
[KUROKO] That's too bad.
Do it anyway!
[knocking]
[HEAD RESIDENT] I heard
some unusual noises.
[KUROKO] I know.
I heard them, too.
From next door, maybe?
[HEAD RESIDENT]
Misaka's asleep already?
Yes, she is.
You see, lately she hasn't
been sleeping well at night.
She's catching up
on her rest now.
I would hate for
these mysterious noises
to disturb her.
Perhaps I can help you
find what's causing them?
[footsteps]
[door closes]
[KAMIJO gasps]
[KAMIJO] The pathological
analysis lab.
The 7th Pharmaceutical
Research Center.
"Project Radio Noise."
"How to shift experiment subject
Accelerator to Level 6."
Wait, what's Level 6?
I've never heard of it.
Nothing in
there, either.
[KUROKO] That is odd, isn't it?
Perhaps the next floor up?
[KUROKO] I do not have time
for this stupid charade!
[KAMIJO] "Out of Academy City's
seven Level 5 espers,
it has been determined that only
Accelerator can reach Level 6.
The optimal plan would
involve creating
one hundred and twenty-eight
different battlefields
upon which Railgun
would be killed.
After that number of victories,
it is believed that Accelerator
would advance to Level 6."
Hold on, Railgun?
That's Zapper, isn't it?
[KAMIJO] "Since that number of
Railguns cannot be produced,
a different plan
has been developed.
This plan involves the mass
production of 'Sisters.'"
After killing 20,000 Sisters
in various scenarios,
Accelerator will
achieve... Level 6.
"We are her sisters,"
says Misaka in conclusion.
At 02:23 on August
the 20th. Test 10030.
On August the 21st. Test 10031.
[gasps]
[MISAKA 10032] However
the Misaka who died today
was serial number 10031.
10032. Date: August the 21st.
Time: twenty-thirty hours.
[KAMIJO gasps]
Honestly.
Huh?
Stupid monkey!
What, did he climb out?
This isn't a jungle!
After all that.
I didn't get to
ask him anything.
[KAMIJO] She knew.
She knew about this.
[MIKOTO] Of all places.
[KAMIJO] She knows about the
existence of the clones.
[MIKOTO] Stupid things.
I really can't
stand those blimps.
[KAMIJO] Huh?
What's wrong with them?
[MIKOTO] They're nothing
but big computers.
Programmed to control us.
[KAMIJO] The experiments.
This whole project!
[KAMIJO] There isn't any wind.
It's her!
How could they?
How could they do it?
Why did it turn out like this?
Now here I am.
There's only one more thing
I can think of to try.
And, if this plan
fails them, too...
Then...
[MIKOTO sobs]
Please, help.
Somebody, help.
[KITTY meows]
It's a cat.
[footsteps]
[MIKOTO breathes heavily]
What do you think
you're doing?
Answer me.
[MIKOTO] What's it to you?
I can do whatever I want,
whenever I want.
You're out here, too.
So why don't you just mind your
own business and leave me--
[KAMIJO] Cut the crap.
What's the deal with
you tonight? I'm just--
I read all about
the project.
About all of
your Sisters.
The experiments
and everything.
So like I said,
let's cut the crap.
[MIKOTO] That paper.
How did you?
[MIKOTO] Impossible! He knows!
Heh.
Well, well, well.
Just who are
you, anyway?
You only met my
clone yesterday,
and you already got your hands
on this top-secret information.
You could
be a detective.
[MIKOTO] A guy like this
I can already tell.
He is not going to
approve of my plan.
The very fact that you're
holding that file means
you've been in my room
without my permission.
[MIKOTO] As far as he knows,
I'm a participant
in the experiment
who volunteered
her DNA.
He's probably come
here to condemn me.
Not only that, but you looked
inside of my stuffed bear.
Normally I'd kill
someone for that.
[MIKOTO] Oh, well.
He may not have all the facts,
but the outcome's
the same, anyway.
I blame myself.
Why shouldn't there be
somebody else blaming me, too?
So, why are you here?
Did you come to tell me how
disgusted you are with me?
[KAMIJO sighs]
[KAMIJO] That's what you think?
I'm here 'cause
I'm concerned.
[MIKOTO] You know, it's kinda
nice to hear someone say that.
Even if it isn't the truth.
[KAMIJO] It is the truth.
[KAMIJO] I mean
what I say!
[MIKOTO sobs]
[siren blares]
[MIKOTO] You know
what the Sisters say?
They compare themselves
to laboratory animals
without so much as
batting an eye.
Like rats or guinea pigs.
Their bodies are messed around
with for the sake of research.
and when they're
used up, that's that.
They aren't stupid.
They know exactly what it means
to be some scientist's lab rat.
They know, and still...
That's what they refer
to themselves as.
They're in this situation
because of me.
It's my fault.
And that makes it my duty
to make sure the ones
who are left survive.
Where are
you going now?
There's another experiment
being held tonight.
Before it begins, I'm going
to track down Accelerator
and fight him with every
ounce of strength in my body.
Can you defeat him?
I have the file.
Do you know what
Tree Diagram predicts?
That you'll be dead
in 185 moves.
You can fight, but do you
really think you'll win?
[MIKOTO] You're right.
It doesn't really matter
what I try against him,
There's no way that I can
win in a fair fight.
However, what if I'm even worse
than they expect me to be?
If, for example, I lost the
fight after the first move.
The prediction that
I'd lose after 185 moves
would be proved wrong.
Maybe the researchers
would see that
and begin to doubt
the whole project.
Maybe they'd be forced to
reconsider the simulations.
So, by losing to him.
I could actually
make myself useful.
So that's it.
You plan to die.
And you're convinced
that, if you die
the entire project will
come crashing to a halt?
[MIKOTO] Yeah.
As far as the researchers
are concerned.
Tree Diagram's
projections are absolute.
But, if I was to be
unceremoniously beaten
on the very first move, lying
there, helpless and pathetic.
Surely there's only one
thing they could think.
That something must've
been wrong with
Tree Diagram's original
programming. They'll stop.
[KAMIJO] Wouldn't they just
do some recalculations
and start back up again?
[MIKOTO]
They wouldn't be able to.
The Tree Diagram satellite
was actually attacked
from the ground and brought
down a few weeks back.
There won't be
any recalculations.
Well then.
you've got it all
planned out, huh?
And now you
know everything.
So, will you
step aside?
No way.
I know you've convinced
yourself you're doing
the right thing here.
But I'm not gonna let you
just march off to your death.
[MIKOTO] Oh, really?
Are you saying you have some
other solution to offer?
Yeah, I didn't
think so.
Now take your
idealism and stuff it.
I don't have
time for this.
Say what you want.
I'm not moving.
This isn't getting
us anywhere.
[MIKOTO] What, are you
so heartless you think
since they're just
a bunch of clones,
it's no big deal if they die?
If you're not going to move,
I'll happily shoot
right through you.
Unless you want that,
step aside!
So, you want to settle
this by force, do you?
How many times have
I tried to fry you now?
I'm still not sure what kind
of power you used against me.
But I do know I can't
afford to lose to you today!
So you better be ready
to fight for your life
because if you don't,
you will die!
What do you think
you're doing?
[KAMIJO] Just standing.
I'm not going to fight you.
What?
I won't fight you!
Huh?
You can stop playing
the noble idiot now!
Do you think I'm
going to stand aside
just because you
put your hands up?
I can't take any other
route than this.
I'm not bluffing.
I'll fry the life out
of you if I have to!
Well go ahead, then.
I won't fight.
[MIKOTO] Damn it!
If you want to stop me,
then fight like a man!
If you don't want to fight, then
get the hell out of my way!
But don't just
stand there calmly
while you ruin all my plans!
This is the last time
I'm gonna say it.
Fight me!
[MIKOTO] No way.
I've never been able to land an
attack on him like that before.
It didn't feel like it was
negated like the other times.
It felt like it
went through him.
[KAMIJO groans]
[MIKOTO] Do you understand now?
I'll do it. I will hurt you.
[MIKOTO]
What're you?
[KAMIJO]
I already said.
I refuse to fight you.
I don't get it!
You know these experiments
are wrong, don't you?
I'm trying to put
a stop to them!
Why are you
doing this?
Yeah. I know they're wrong.
What they're doing is crazy.
Evil and disgusting.
[MIKOTO]
Then why are--
[KAMIJO] But, the way
you've got it planned.
You are going to die tonight.
So I...
...won't move.
[MIKOTO] Shut up, you fool.
You're an idiot.
Saying nice things,
trying to reassure me.
Well, I promise
I don't deserve it.
You know what?
Maybe you live in a
world that's full of
happy endings for everybody!
Well, sorry, in a world like
that, there's no place for me!
Say you die and your
Sisters all survive.
Do you really think
they'll be grateful to you?
You must have
realized it.
Do things your way, and
you won't save anybody.
[KAMIJO winces]
[MIKOTO] You don't know
what you're talking about.
If I die tonight.
That means ten thousand
Sisters get to live.
Really it's not even a
difficult decision to make.
If my one life can save
ten thousand of theirs,
that's a good thing isn't it?
It's not much, but
maybe it's enough?
So please, just go.
I'm not moving.
[MIKOTO sobs]
[KITTY meows]
You're really a complete
idiot, aren't you?
This doesn't have
anything to do with you.
You could easily have
turned a blind eye
and pretended that
you knew nothing.
You could have just continued
living your normal life.
[KAMIJO groans]
[MIKOTO] Why would you put
yourself through this?
You look like hell.
I think your heart may even have
stopped for a second there.
[KAMIJO chuckles]
How can you smile like that
after everything
that's happened?
I was just thinking,
"I'm glad I'm on her side."
Now, come on.
Stop crying.
[KAMIJO] I've got an idea.
A way to force them to stop.
Think about it.
The experiment's based
on the supposition
that Accelerator's
the strongest esper.
Well, what if he's proven
to be incredibly weak?
For instance.
Let's say he was
handily defeated
in a fight with a Level 0.
The experiment's basic
premise would be flawed.
What are you saying?
You don't mean--
[KAMIJO] That's right.
I'll fight him.
[MIKOTO] That's impossible!
We're talking about a guy
so strong and arrogant
he wouldn't even break a sweat
if he had to defend himself
from an entire army!
He'd kill you for sure!
[MIKOTO] Mama isn't
here now to make
every little problem go away.
[MIKOTO] Don't do this!
I can't drag anybody else
into this mess with me!
The cost has already
been too great!
[MIKOTO] Santa stopped making
house calls a long time ago.
[MIKOTO] Don't you see?
This is something I
have to do on my own!
Please let me!
[KAMIJO] How about this.
Work with me.
I know you have
your own goals.
Mine is seeing everybody
get through this alive.
So, let's work together.
Maybe we'll both win.
[MIKOTO] All that
is wishful thinking.
It's not like some hero is going
to come dashing to the rescue.
Just let me go.
I'll stop the experiment
and bring your sister back.
That's a promise, okay?
[MIKOTO sobs]
[KAMIJO] It's starting soon.
I have to hurry.
[MIKOTO] Here, kitty.
[KITTY purrs]
Good boy.
[KITTY meows]
[KAMIJO] I don't know if I
have any chance of beating him,
but I have to try.
For their sake.
For her sake.
I'm going to do whatever
I have to, to stop this!