[ACCELERATOR] Amazing!
It's like a part of my body!
Like moving my own arms or legs!
All of this air is completely
under my control!
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
So fighting someone
stronger really was
a shortcut to leveling up!
Guess they were right all along!
Thanks, third-string!
You served your purpose well,
and now I'm going
to destroy you! Huh?
How could this be
happening now?
It looks like the
plasma is diffusing.
Why is the wind
suddenly acting like this?
It's not wind manipulation?
So, what?
The windmills are
turning the wrong way.
Hold on.
I've heard about this before.
It's something about
dynamo motors.
When they're hit by particular
electromagnetic waves, they--
Is it them?
Damn it. What do they
think they're doing?
Those windmills aren't just
spinning around haphazardly.
They're being directed
to disrupt my formulas!
She's doing it!
The images she sees are
going across the network!
I'm gonna' kill you!
I won't let you!
I don't understand
you people.
First we have a gallant
appearance from third-string.
And then you show up.
Just to defend
this wind-up doll.
That's an overproduced,
factory reject of yourself.
I would think, out of
everyone in the world,
you would be the most
disgusted by it.
Or maybe it freaks you
out to see something
that looks like you
getting all beat up.
But then, that's not
a very good reason
to put your life on the line.
[ACCELERATOR laughs]
So maybe you just can't
stand to have somebody else
become a Level 6 before you.
Or, maybe, it's some kind
of atonement for being
the reason they started these
experiments in the first place.
[MIKOTO] I don't desire power
for power's sake the way you do.
Nor do I think of this as
atonement for any of the things
that I've done
wrong in the past.
She's my sister.
All of these girls.
They are my little sisters.
That's why I'm here.
I'm sorry.
After all this time, I have
no right to ask you this,
but still...
Just this one time, may I
fulfill my role as big sister?
[MISAKA 10032] Yes.
[MIKOTO] Heh.
I will not let another
one of them die!
[ACCELERATOR] Huh?
[ACCELERATOR laughs]
Man, that's rich!
I have to admit that I
didn't see that one coming.
Playing at sisters?
That's a good one!
You're way out of
your league here.
If there's something I
wanna do, you can't stop me.
Two little girls like you
can't even slow me down.
It's kind of like
how a person's vision
can only be measured
up to 20/20.
Level 5 is the highest
rank an esper can attain
in Academy City.
So that's where I'm stuck,
even though I'm better
than the rest of you.
I'm sick of looking at the
same damn face day after day,
so I'm gonna kill all--
[thud]
[MIKOTO gasps]
[ACCELERATOR] Impossible.
Doesn't he get it?
I'm the most experienced killer
this city's ever seen.
I know so much about what it
takes to destroy a person,
I'm almost sick of it.
He's standing.
He shouldn't even... be alive.
[ACCELERATOR] What am I doing?
[ACCELERATOR] This idiot just
doesn't know when to quit.
Sure, I lost control
of the wind.
But I can still finish him off.
All I need is one touch.
This really has
been fascinating.
But I've had enough.
It ends now!
[ACCELERATOR yells]
[ACCELERATOR screams]
[KAMIJO] You're the strongest
guy in Academy City.
That's not gonna
help you now.
The weakest guy
is taking you down.
[ACCELERATOR] I don't get it.
Why can't I break this guy?
He's protecting them.
The wind-up dolls.
I was one step away from it.
From absolute power.
And now. And now.
[ACCELERATOR] What if
having too much power,
turns the world
itself against me?
Ultimately resulting
in destruction,
rather than protection.
[SUNGLASSES MAN 11-A]
Just think.
If you were to gain even
greater power than you have.
Then what would
your life be like?
[LEVEL 6 PROJECT GUY]
Just do the experiments,
you have nothing to lose.
It's not like any
people will get hurt.
[ACCELERATOR] Guinea pigs.
Wind-up dolls. Clones.
It's not like I'm
seeking immortality.
I just want to
gather enough power
that nobody will ever
want to fight me again.
If that happens.
[CHILDREN laugh and yell]
[ACCELERATOR]
Then someday, maybe.
If that happens, then.
[ACCELERATOR] Then, no one will.
[KAMIJO] So many Sisters,
living the best that they can.
[MIKOTO] All of these girls.
They're my sisters.
[ACCELERATOR] Really.
[ACCELERATOR] What am
I even doing anymore?
[creaking]
[KITTY meows]
Hi. Are, are you?
[smack]
[door opens]
Just thought I
would drop by.
Oh, guess he's asleep.
[footsteps]
To think he actually defeated
the first-ranked esper
in Academy City.
You must be crazy
or something.
You know that?
Uh... Sorry. Did I wake you?
Uh. Here! Get well soon!
I picked the most expensive
cookies the store had.
For the price, I'm guessing
they're pretty good.
I just thought...
I really ought to try
and do something to,
you know, say thank--
When it comes to cookies...
Don't people say
homemade are the best?
Huh?
Heh, heh. Is that so?
Can you seriously picture
me baking cookies?
[KAMIJO] No, never.
I'm pretty sure if you tried
to the cookies would come out
all misshapen and disgusting.
It would be ugly for sure.
[MIKOTO] I meant that
baking's not my style,
not that I can't do it!
[KAMIJO] Hey, calm down!
I'm injured, here!
You're gonna fry all the
hospital's fancy equipment
if you're not careful!
[KAMIJO pants]
[MIKOTO] Okay, fine.
[KAMIJO chuckles]
[KAMIJO] So, uh.
Your sister stopped by.
She said the
experiments are over.
[MIKOTO] Mmm.
They're over, but
because of me so many...
[KAMIJO] Well, you know,
if you hadn't offered them
your DNA map, none of the
sisters would ever have existed.
That experiment was
messed up in a lot of ways,
but at least there was something
good that came from it.
Your sisters.
You can take pride in that.
Think about it this way.
If it weren't for you,
they wouldn't have had a
chance at life whatsoever.
What's the point in moping?
I don't think they'd like
to see you like this.
Beating yourself up.
[KITTY meows]
[GIRL 16-A]
What should we play on?
[MIKOTO] How are
your injuries doing?
[MISAKA 10032] These are
really nothing serious
compared to what
happened to that boy.
Good. I'm glad.
Here we go. Whee!
[GIRL 16-B] Ha, ha, ha! Yay!
[MIKOTO] Lives created
by a machine.
They're born without
knowledge of the world.
Blank slates.
So it's not surprising
that when they are told
they're nothing but lab rats.
they swiftly come to accept
it as the simple truth.
However, if they're
given the chance to look
at the world around them.
Like she did.
Then surely, they can--
So, listen, um.
You probably can't
forgive what I did.
I doubt you even
want to see my face.
But, uh. I do think you
might have some trouble,
you know, adjusting to
a normal life. So, if, um...
If there's anything at
all I can do to, uh, help?
[MISAKA 10032] "This is called
'stand and swing'," Says Misaka,
putting into practice knowledge
she gained from Testament
and showing off her skills.
Wow!
That's amazing!
[KITTY meows]
"Done. Any more
of that and I risk
aggravating my injuries,
so that's all for me.
Whew!" says Misaka,
growing tired.
"What? Is something
the matter?"
[MIKOTO] Sorry,
just give me a moment.
[GIRL 16-B]
Come on, Sis!
Let's do it again!
No. I think
that's enough.
[MISAKA 10032] "No, it isn't."
"As the big sister,
it is your obligation
to indulge your younger sister."
[GIRL 16-A] Huh?
Says Misaka to the
impressionable youngster,
hoping to brainwash her.
[MIKOTO]
Hey, you!
[KITTY meows]
[MISAKA 10032] Cute, yes?
It is what people call a kitten.
[GIRL 16-B] I know that!
Hey, are you and this
other lady sisters?
You look the same!
[MIKOTO] Uh...
[GIRL 16-A] You've got
to be twins, right?
So who's the older sister
and who's the younger sister?
Uh...
[MISAKA 10032]
Well, the thing is--
Ah! Hold on, hold on!
I wanna guess!
Okay, let's see. I think...
Hm...
[MIKOTO] You were the one
who wanted to guess.
[GIRL 16-B] It's you!
You're the younger sister!
You've gotta be!
I mean, you've got a Gekota.
Uh...
[GIRL 16-B] I like
stuffed animals, too!
Huh?
[MISAKA 10032]
"Mmph!" says Misaka,
indicating
stifled laughter.
It cannot be denied.
Her tastes are
inappropriate for her age.
She is rude, hot-tempered,
and belligerent.
She is sensitive,
easily embarrassed,
and even more easily offended.
However, this problematic
older sister of mine
risked her life for me.
[GIRLS] Huh?
[bells ring]
It is strange.
After last night's experiment,
Misaka was supposed to be dead.
It was supposed to play
out as it always had,
more than ten thousand
times before.
The same course of events.
And yet, here I am.
Misaka is still alive.
Still walking and talking.
The Misakas
were disposable.
We were created in
order to be killed.
That was the sole purpose
for our existence.
The reason for
which we were born.
And now, thanks to
you and that boy,
we have lost our purpose.
We are unemployed.
[MIKOTO] Huh?
[MISAKA 10032] We are lost.
Adrift in a world that
makes little sense.
So, please.
"Help Misaka.
Stay with her while
she goes on her search.
While she tries to
discover a new meaning
for this life of hers."
Says Misaka,
asking her big sister
for a world of indulgence.
[MIKOTO] Yes. I'd love to.
[GIRL 16-B] Do it again, Sis!
[GIRL 16-A] Okay, okay. Ready?
[GIRL 16-B] Uh-huh!
[UIHARU] That's all she said?
So she didn't give
you any details then?
No. None.
Misaka baking. Huh.
[SATEN] She said she
wanted to get away from
all the prying eyes
in the dorm kitchen,
so she asked to borrow
my oven instead.
It seemed like a
really big deal.
I almost don't believe it.
Pigs must be flying now.
Yeah, right?
Still. I'm glad.
She seems more cheerful
than she's been in a while.
I agree.
I wish we knew who she was
making the present for, though.
I asked a million times, but
she wouldn't give up a name.
Yeah?
Yeah.
[laughing]
[MIKOTO] Jeez. Saten got
a little too much enjoyment
out of the whole thing.
After all, it's not like this
is supposed to mean something.
It's a thank-you. That's it.
Of course, this is him
we're talking about.
"I was only fighting
for my own sake.
I've done nothing that
deserves any thanks."
I'll bet that's what he says.
Maybe I'm just being childish.
[MIKOTO] No, no, no! Anyway,
whether he wants thanks or not,
I still need to show
him proper gratitude.
U-Uh--
I went to all the trouble
of making these things,
and if he doesn't accept them,
then he's going to pay for--
[KAMIJO]
What's he gonna pay for?
Huh?
What are you doing
all the way out here?
Huh?
[MIKOTO] You're still supposed
to be in the hospital!
[KAMIJO]
Well, uh...
hospitals aren't
exactly cheap.
And I have a hungry roommate
who gets even more violent
every day that
I'm away from home.
[MIKOTO] Huh?
[KAMIJO] Hey.
For that matter, what are
you doing way out here?
[MIKOTO] Uh.
Well, I...
Oh, I know.
You must've been coming
to visit me again.
Hah! Yeah, right.
I-I was not!
Wow, uh. you don't have
to deny it so forcefully.
[MIKOTO] Idiot!
Uh, no, I wasn't coming
out here to check on you.
It's just that, lately, you've
helped me out an awful lot.
I-I, uh,
didn't... mean to.
I just, wanted to.
Look, ants!
[KAMIJO] Ants?
Oh. You have a research
project or something?
Some summer vacation homework?
[MIKOTO] "Look, ants!"
What am I, five years old?
[KAMIJO] Sorry to interrupt you.
See ya around, zapper.
Mikoto Misaka!
What?
[MIKOTO] I have an actual name!
It's Mikoto Misaka.
It isn't Zapper.
You always call me that.
Try using my real name sometime!
Then again, maybe that's
just too much to ask of you.
[KAMIJO chuckles]
[KAMIJO] See you later, Misaka.
[KUROKO] I've got bad news!
Listen, Sis-
What happened? What's
the matter with you?
Ah! Are you feeling okay?
Are you hurt somewhere?
Did you eat something that
didn't agree with you?
[MIKOTO] What? What
are you talking about?
And what's this bad
news you mentioned?
Oh, about that.
The head resident seems to
have learned about the nights
you've been away from the
dorms without permission.
She says you'd better have
a very good explanation
for your absence.
[MIKOTO] That's bad, huh?
I'm gonna need an excuse.
Wait--you came all the way
out here just to tell me that?
Thank you.
But how did you
know where I was?
Huh? As they say,
"like calls to like."
Wherever Sissy is,
there too will be Kuroko.
But more importantly, are
you sure everything is okay?
Because if anything were
to happen to you, Sissy,
I wouldn't rest until I
had done everything tha--
[MIKOTO] Honestly.
Keep talking crazy and
I'll leave you here.
Can you really
blame me, Sissy?
There was a look on your face
that I've never
seen there before.
[UIHARU] I'm so glad
Misaka's feeling better now!
[SATEN] I still want to know
who those cookies were for!
[KUROKO] Exposed!
[UIHARU] Uh, Shirai?
[KUROKO] It's time to come
out of your shell, Sissy.
Body and soul!