Around here...
This is where it came from.
Who... are you?
[MIKOTO] What are you?
Mya.
Huh?
[MIKOTO] "Mya"?
So... what does that mean?
Is it her name?
The organization she's with?
Or did I mishear what she said?
Maybe it was a
different language?
"Mya," says the furry,
four-legged creature
caught up in a tree.
[meows]
[MIKOTO] A cat?
A little earlier today,
I was passing
through this area...
As I did, I noticed a
baby who was left alone
inside a car that was
parked on the street.
The baby could have
suffered a heat stroke.
So Misaka used her
electrical power to unlock
the door and open
the window, but...
[MISAKA 9982] The poor
creature was startled
and fled up the tree.
He was then unable
to climb back down...
"You see?" asks Misaka, having
fully explained the situation.
Ah... Wait, that's not
what I was asking about!
I want to know what the deal
is with you, not the cat!
Look at him.
His situation becomes
more precarious.
"Shouldn't we see
if we can help him
get down?" asks--
He's a cat!
Being up in a tree isn't
a big deal to him, okay?
So, why don't you just
tell me what you're...
Oh, I see...
So, Big Sister, you do not
care if this creature slips
from the branch,
falls out of the tree,
and is violently
smashed on the ground?
If, as a result,
his internal organs
are seriously injured,
and he is unable
to survive on his own,
that does not concern you?
Okay, you win...
What do you want me to do?
"You could get on
your hands and knees
in front of the tree...
Then I should be
able to reach it...
Right?" Misaka
seeks confirmation.
Well...
I'm not really seeing
anything else around here
that could give us
enough of a boost.
[MIKOTO] Wait...
why am I on the bottom?
Could you move a little further
to the left, Big Sister?
[MIKOTO] You've gotta
be kidding me!
Yeah, I'm fine,
thank you!
[MISAKA 9982]
I have managed
to safely secure the
creature... See?
Hey, come on!
You can't just go around
holding up your skirt like that!
You're supposed
to be a young lady!
You need to behave if you're
gonna go around lookin' like me!
[meows]
[MIKOTO] Aw, just
look at this sweet guy!
He's a cute little
kitty-kiddy, huh?
Kitty-kiddy?
Yeah, he's a cat's
kid: a kitty-kiddy.
It's too bad cats are
always spooked by me.
They aren't crazy about
the slight electrical field
my body constantly produces.
The same is true
for Misaka, it seems.
Hey!
You keep distracting me
and dodging my question!
You've been referring
to yourself as Misaka.
So, are you...
are you my... my...
Are you my clone?
Yes.
[MIKOTO] Oh... kay.
But I thought that project
was supposed to have
been frozen for good.
In which case... why does
someone like you even exist?
"ZXC741. ASD852.
QWE963-Dash. Well?"
Misaka seeks
password confirmation.
What?
[MISAKA 9982] Your inability
to respond means that
you are not involved
in the experiment...
and so I cannot answer
your question, Big Sister.
Well, then you can
at least tell me
who is in charge
of this project.
That is confidential.
What is the purpose
of your creation?
That is confidential, too.
You want to get
hurt, is that it?
If I have to force
it out of you...
[MIKOTO] Okay, fine...
Get going.
All I have to do is
follow where you lead...
You must be heading back
to whatever laboratory
is responsible for creating you.
When I get there,
I'll start by collecting
your manufacturers.
They can give me
the answers I want.
[MIKOTO] Sisters...
[MIKOTO] If she
wasn't right here...
I don't know if
I would believe it.
[MIKOTO] No...
I guess that's not true...
For a while now,
I've been frightened
that exactly this sort of
thing was going to happen.
That someone who looked
just like me would show up.
[MIKOTO] Although...
I didn't expect...
something like this.
[MIKOTO] I thought it would be
more sinister and sophisticated.
[MIKOTO] Like some sort
of black op where they plot
to put someone to death
and then replace them
with an identical twin who has
been subverted by the enemy.
[MIKOTO] But this has
me completely thrown off.
[MIKOTO] Wait, "Sister...s"!
[MIKOTO] Hey! Hold on!
[MIKOTO] I... just need
to know one thing!
Okay, this might sound crazy...
but am I gonna find
another five or ten others
like you somewhere out there?
"Kitty-kiddy."
If you say it backwards,
it still sounds almost
exactly the same.
Stop trying
to avoid the subject!
[MISAKA 9982] "Kitty-kiddy."
[MIKOTO] Quit saying that!
I asked you a question!
[MISAKA 9982] "Kitty-kiddy."
[MIKOTO] Oh, come oooonnnn!
[ICE CREAM MAN 5-A]
Hey! What's going on?
It's a shame
to see sisters
fighting like that.
[MIKOTO] She is not my sister!
Hey... That's the kinda thing
you should never say, especially
if you're angry. Wait one sec.
[ICE CREAM MAN 5-A]
Here you go.
[MIKOTO] Um...
[ICE CREAM MAN 5-A]
These are my best cones.
You two eat them
and stop fighting.
Uh...
That's nice of you,
but I don't think ice cream
is exactly what we need, here.
A rich and
refreshing sweetness
without an
overbearing aftertaste...
Clearly, quality
milk was used...
and this kind of texture
cannot be achieved
without well-ground sugar...
Furthermore, the cone
is flavorful enough
to be a cookie in its own right.
[MISAKA 9982]
"Excellent job!" reports Misaka,
offering her sincerest praise.
Well, thank you.
Now... when a couple breaks up,
they can just go back
to being strangers,
But sisters share
their blood for life.
If I don't start charging
for the ice cream,
my old lady might
become a stranger again.
Uh... that
sounds personal.
[ICE CREAM MAN 5-A]
Anyway, you sisters be good!
[MIKOTO] I told you,
we are not sisters!
Though... looking at us, what
else is he going to think?
"No, sir, our genes
are totally identical,
but we're not sisters,
I promise!"
[MIKOTO] Huh?
Hey, you!
"Is something the matter?"
asks Misaka, playing
innocent while enjoying
the mint chocolate chip
aftertaste... secretly.
My clone, huh?
If that's really the case,
how can you be such
a gluttonous pig--
"Eating ice cream
has made me a bit chilly.
I think I would like
some hot tea now,"
says Misaka, ignoring
Big Sister's bad attitude.
[MIKOTO] Huh?
"I may not look it,
but I am pretty
particular about my tea,"
reports Misaka, considerately
offering up a disclaimer.
[MISAKA 9982] "If it helps, I
will be ordering milk tea,"
says Misaka, in an effort
to streamline the process.
[MIKOTO] Stop screwing with me!
[MISAKA 9982] "That milk tea
was more than satisfactory...
as was the strawberry
shortcake on the side,"
remarks Misaka,
offering her candid opinion.
[MIKOTO] So, When are you going
back to wherever you belong?
[MISAKA 9982]
I forgot to mention this...
but Misaka is now headed
for her experiment...
so she will not be returning.
[MIKOTO] Huh?
You're free to
follow me, Big Sister,
if that is what
you wish to do,
but you will not
see Misaka's creator.
But... why didn't
you tell me...?
I didn't say because
you didn't ask.
[MIKOTO] So what now?
Would it be quicker to
decode her password
and search for more
information that way?
I do have my PDA with me.
[MISAKA 9982]
What is that object?
This? It's a prize
I got from a vending
machine, that's all.
[MISAKA 9982]
What are you doing?
[MIKOTO] Just hold
still a sec, will you?
There. This should give
me a much clearer picture
than looking in
a mirror would...
Seeing it like this,
it's not so bad, really.
"No, it's worse than bad,"
Misaka says,
shocked and appalled
by her model's absolute
lack of fashion sense.
Uh... excuse me?
Well, obviously,
I was just kidding around.
Come on...
[MIKOTO] You know it's bad if
your own clone shoots you down.
did you actually
think I was serious?
Geez, what is with you?
"The moment you
put it on Misaka,
ownership of this
button transferred to her,"
Misaka calmly asserts.
If Big Sister attempts
to take it back,
she is guilty of robbery.
Please, that's ridiculous.
[MISAKA 9982] "No, it is a
true statement... Besides,"
adds Misaka,
"This holds special importance
as the first present
given to me by Big Sister."
"Though one would think
she could have found
something better to
give me than this...
Would that really have
been so much trouble?"
asks Misaka, with a sigh.
Alright, you give that
back to me right now!
[MIKOTO] Calm down...
You're letting her
distract you again...
At this rate, I'm not
going to get anywhere...
I should just check the net.
[MIKOTO] Okay, fine...
It's getting late.
I'm gonna call
it quits for today.
Uh... Unless there
was something else?
No.
That's all there is...
Farewell, Big Sister.
Yeah, okay...
I'll be seein' ya.
[MIKOTO] Geez...
she sure was strange.
I'm not even sure what to
make of the day I just had.
Helping a stranded cat...
Eating ice cream cones...
Fighting over a button...
It's almost
like we were...
First things first:
I need to find her creator!
[UIHARU] Thanks so much!
I really appreciate this!
[HARU'UE] I don't know how many
times you've helped me out!
Really, I'm more
than happy to give you
a hand with your homework.
It's no problem at all!
[UIHARU] The Judgment
recruiting drive took up
more time than
I thought it would.
I'd be totally lost
without your help!
[HARU'UE] There we go...
Is this all of it?
Is that you, Misaka?
Hey, Uiharu.
I'm really sorry for
calling you so late.
I'm just gonna get
straight to the point, okay?
Write this down:
ZXC741-ASD852-QWE963-Dash.
Do you know what that means?
Let me think .
Where have I seen this?
Oh, yeah, I've got it!
This code looks like
a password attached
to information that's
security Rank A or higher.
I've actually tried
to crack something
like this before, myself.
[MIKOTO] Great, thanks!
You're a huge help!
[UIHARU] Huh? Hold on! Misaka!
What's wrong?
Is something the matter?
Well, Uh...
I'm not sure.
[MISAKA 9982] "The current time
is 20:58," Misaka reports.
[MISAKA 9982] Experiment
number nine-nine-eight-two
will begin shortly.
Countdown... Two minutes.
[MIKOTO] What the hell?
[MIKOTO] This is...
[MISAKA 9982 "It is now
21:00 hours," states Misaka...
"It is time. Experiment
number nine-nine-eight-two
will commence immediately."
[MIKOTO] "How to
shift an absolute esper
to Level 6 through
the use of Sisters."
[MIKOTO] "In Academy City,
there are seven people
who are ranked as Level 5s.
However, based upon the
predictive calculations
made by Tree Diagram,
it has been established
that only one person
has the ability
to reach status Level 6."
[MIKOTO] "If the subject
in question were to be put
through normal
Academy City curriculum..."
[MIKOTO] "...he would not
reach Level 6 for a long time...
an estimated two
hundred and fifty years...
Thus, we have set
aside this plan for now...
and are instead pursuing what
some would consider a more
radical course of action."
[MIKOTO] "We will prepare a
number of specific battlefields
and will manipulate the
direction of his development
by proceeding him through
a course of combat scenarios."
[MIKOTO] "The optimal plan
would involve creating
one hundred and twenty-eight
different battlefields...
The subject would
then kill Railgun
one hundred and
twenty-eight times...
After that number
of victories...
he would advance to Level 6."
[MIKOTO] "However...
since it is impossible
to secure multiple Railguns,
a different plan
has been developed."
[MIKOTO]
"The Sisters created during
the now-frozen Project Radio
Noise will be repurposed...
They will serve as
Railgun substitutes."
[ACCELERATOR] What's the matter?
Turning tail already?
[MIKOTO] "A large number of
armed Sisters will be required,
as their quantity
must substitute
for the Original's quality."
[MIKOTO] This is crazy...
One hell of a practical joke.
[MIKOTO] It talks
about killing me...
and using these Sister
clones as proxies...
[MIKOTO] There's no
way a project like this
could actually go through.
That's all there is...
Farewell, Big Sister.
[MIKOTO] No!
[ACCELERATOR]
Run away, run away!
The longer you run,
the more time you
have before you die...
After all, this is a life or
death game of tag
we're playing, here.
[ACCELERATOR] Because
once I catch up to you...
It's the end. Game over.
Too slow!
You should really
be more careful.
You don't have time to
waste with falling down.
What's wrong?
You're not broken already,
are you? That's no fun.
I don't see how
I'm gonna make it
to Level 6 if this is
all I have to work with.
[ACCELERATOR]
Oh...? Very nice.
You're a tough
one, aren't you?
That's the attitude
we're looking for!
I was right...
No way did a project
so insane actually ex--
Lying down on the
job like that...
Finally running out
of steam, are you?
Need a rest?
Or are you ready to give
in and declare defeat?
Misaka... does not...
have an accurate grasp...
of the target's ability...
however... judging from
experimental results...
up to now...
[MISAKA 9982] Misaka has
come to the conclusion that...
the target projects
some kind of barrier...
around himself...
Furthermore... seeing as how...
he steps on the ground...
when he walks...
[MISAKA 9982] Misaka believes...
That his ability...
does not extend downward...
or at least, not beyond
the soles of his feet.
[MISAKA 9982]
Therefore, Misaka determined,
a surprise attack
from that direction...
would prove to be
the most effective.
[ACCELERATOR] Hey, what are
you mumbling about over there?
If you won't run,
I'll finish you off.
[MISAKA 9982] I am not
running... anymore.
[MISAKA 9982]
As per my plan...
I have succeeded
in leading you
to the desired location...
Now... there is only one
more thing left to do.
Mission complete...
The target has been neutrali--
Oh. Hi.
It was a nice idea...
But so incredibly
far off the mark!
Aww, now we can't
play tag anymore, huh?
You'll croak on your own
if I just leave you there
but standing around waiting
really isn't my thing.
[ACCELERATOR] Well... still
trying to run away, huh?
That way is a dead-end, though.
Do you have some
other pathetic,
useless trick hidden
up your sleeve, maybe?
[ACCELERATOR] We've
played for long enough now.
[ACCELERATOR] I think
it's time to say good bye.
Oh, no!
No! It can't be...!
No!!
[ACCELERATOR] That concludes
today's experiment.
[yawns]
[ACCELERATOR] I made
quite a mess this time.
I wonder how long it'll
take them to clean it up.
Eh... who cares?
I should stop by the
store on my way home.
♪
[ACCELERATOR] Whoa, hey!
What's going on?
There's only supposed to
be one experiment tonight!
Oh, right... I understand...
I know who you are.