[YOUNG MIKOTO]
I don't understand.
What is that boy doing?
[DOCTOR 2-A] This young man
has a serious disease
called muscular dystrophy.
Dys... what?
[DOCTOR 2-A] It's a disease
that makes his muscles
grow gradually weaker...
He's had it all his life...
It's the type of disease people
are born with, you see.
As you can tell,
he's fighting against it...
Trying to beat it.
To overcome it.
[DOCTOR 2-A] However...
no matter how hard he fights...
it's a battle he
is sure to lose.
Our current
medical science offers
no cure for this disease.
His muscles will
continue to weaken...
In time, he won't even
be able to stand up...
And then... finally...
his lungs and his heart
will stop working.
However, as I said,
that's only currently.
Things can always change.
You have an amazing
opportunity here.
Your ability can
help him and other people
like him who are suffering.
It's the simplest
thing in the world,
and all you have to do is
give us your DNA map, okay?
[DOCTOR 2-A] Thank you.
[MIKOTO] A dream...
Why would I dream about that?
Oh, right...
I went to see Edasaki yesterday,
and that must have...
[MIKOTO] Ahhhh!!
[KUROKO] Heeey! Sissy,
you're going too fast!
Wait for meeee!
[MIKOTO] Shut up, you perv!
But... But it was nothing...
I wanted to feel the warmth of
someone else's body, that's all!
[MIKOTO] I don't care
what you wanted.
You can't come crawling
into my bed like that!
So... that's all water
under the bridge now.
Where are you off to?
Well, you know how there's
that regional
field trip happening
at the beginning
of September, right?
[KUROKO] Oh... yeah.
I want to be
prepared for it,
so I thought I'd go buy
all the sundries
I'll need for traveling.
[KUROKO] Ughh...
What you mean
is that you're going
shopping for more
of the childish stuff
that you're so addicted to...
Despite the fact that our tiny
room is already overflowing
with fancy-looking knockoffs
of famous characters.
Did you say something?
[KUROKO] No, nothing at all.
So we get to have a
shopping date today, huh?
[MIKOTO] Ugh... Well,
it really isn't necessary
for you to tag along.
I don't mind, though...
Now, let me think a moment...
What else would be
useful for you to have
before going on the fieldtrip?
[MIKOTO] Maybe something
to stop creepy intruders
from sneaking into my bed?
You're still angry about
that little incident, then?
[MIKOTO] Not at all.
Right...
Well, I promise I can be helpful
in all sorts of ways today.
Here's an example!
If you are on
your way to the mall,
allow me to helpfully
point out this route
as a potential shortcut for you.
Now, then...
after you, Sissy.
Okay, fine...
But if you try to use this
as an excuse for groping me,
you won't enjoy
the consequences.
Oh, no, such a thought
never crossed my mind.
Wow.
It's so cramped
and narrow in here.
How do you even know
about this back alley?
It comes with the job...
I have every map of
the city memorized,
down to the last
nook and cranny.
[BLUE SHIRT GUY 2-A] Excuse me.
[KUROKO] No, go right ahead.
[MIKOTO] Passing people
is a little awkward
in such tight quarters, huh?
True, but fortunately that
doesn't happen very often.
[YELLOW CAP GUY 2-A] Excuse me.
[KUROKO and MIKOTO]
No, go right ahead.
So... is this, like, a
popular shortcut or something?
It's normally not this busy.
I don't know what
everyone's doing here.
[KUROKO] Honestly!
Why today of all days?
This is--
Whoa! Are you okay?
Except for this
huge pain in my head.
What? Is something wrong?
[KUROKO] No. I just thought I
saw something stuck under here.
[MIKOTO] An envelope?
[KUROKO] I think so...
but there's no name
or address on it.
[MIKOTO] What fell out?
It's a Money Card.
That's strange.
[UIHARU] Huh? So you found a
Money Card on the ground, too?
Too?
We've been receiving
a lot of reports over
the last few days from
people who have randomly
found Money Cards all
across School District 7.
There are now
forty-eight incidents.
[UIHARU] Oh... It just
jumped up to fifty-six.
That many?
[UIHARU] And that's
on the low end...
I'm sure not
everybody reports them.
Maybe this is the work
of some counterfeiting
operation.
[KONORI] We thought of that.
But all the cards that have been
turned into us
so far are genuine.
[MIKOTO] Really, Konori?
All of them?
[KONORI] Uh huh.
Something odd is going on...
I don't understand.
Why is this the first time
I'm hearing anything
about this case?
Here's the thing.
Intentionally destroying
or abandoning money
is prohibited by law... but
Money Cards are different.
They're exempt...
So there haven't been any
official notices put out.
[KUROKO] Yes, I see...
The amount on the
cards varies significantly.
Sometimes it's a thousand...
Other times it's fifty thousand.
Each of them
was left in a place
where there's generally
little human traffic.
And they were all
found inside envelopes.
In other words,
somebody is obviously
spreading these
around on purpose.
It's all seems
too involved
and organized to
be a simple prank...
There weren't even
any fingerprints
on the envelopes or
the cards themselves.
[UIHARU] As you would expect,
rumor of the mysterious
cards has spread.
So there are a ton
of people prowling
the alleyways,
looking for treasure.
I know what you mean...
We saw it in action.
It's not just
that, either...
Students are stealing
from each other.
And some are even
getting caught up
in nasty fights after stumbling
into Skill Out territory.
[KUROKO] We cannot allow
this situation to continue.
Sorry, Sissy... Duty calls.
It looks like we'll have to put
off our date until another time.
Sure... I can go by myself.
Don't you worry about it.
Bye!
Doomed to suffer through
another lonely day.
Thanks for your help.
If you don't mind, you can start
by searching in this area.
[MIKOTO] Now I can take my time
and actually enjoy shopping.
[GIRL STUDENT 2-A] I'm sorry!
It's okay. No worries.
[GIRL STUDENT 2-B] Aww.
It doesn't look like there
are any of them here.
[GIRL STUDENT 2-A]
Oh. That's too bad.
[GIRL STUDENT 2-B]
I'm starting to think
that story was
really just a rumor.
[GIRL STUDENT 2-A]
But someone told me Rit
in Class B actually found one.
[GIRL STUDENT 2-B] Yeah?
I didn't know that...
Rumors, huh?
I suppose it's no surprise
that Kuroko and I
hadn't heard about it, then.
Maybe this area
has already been picked clean.
[Oh, uh... hello, Saten.
Huh? Oh! Hey, Misaka!
So, what was up
with you earlier?
You didn't even say hello.
Huh? Earlier?
Don't act like you
don't remember...
It was just a little while ago.
You were walking in
front of Seventh Mist...
I called out to you,
but you kept walking
like I wasn't even there.
Sorry...
I'm pretty sure that wasn't
me you were talking to.
What?
But I could've sworn I saw the
Tokiwadai school
uniform and everything.
I've been with Kuroko
and the others until now.
Okay, then.
Maybe it wasn't you.
So, anyway, what
exactly were you doing?
Chasing down a rumor
of abandoned Money Cards,
by any chance?
You know about that?
Taaaa... Da!
That's... amazing.
[SATEN] I know, pretty
impressive, huh?
I seem to have a really keen
nose when it comes to rumors.
Yeah... so I can see.
[SATEN] Right!
We need to go
check over here next.
[MIKOTO] Eh But I need
to do some shopping...
[SATEN] Just come on already!
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER 2-A] Full
school curfew is approaching...
All students, please
return home immediately.
Full school curfew
is approaching.
Awww...
It's already evening.
Time flies, huh?
Here...
You should have your
share of the day's take!
Great, thank you...
Oh! No, I can't!
Those should really
be turned in.
[SATEN] Yeah,
you're probably right...
I'll hand them over
to Uiharu later on.
[MIKOTO] I wanted to ask you...
Have you by
chance heard any rumors
about who's responsible for
distributing those cards?
Huh...
Now that you mention it,
I haven't heard anything.
Hmmm...
Well, I'll see you later.
We can bring Uiharu
next time, too.
Yeah, sure.
[SATEN] All right! Bye!
Have a good one! Bye!
Aw, man...
I ended up wasting
the entire day on that...
I didn't get any
shopping done at all.
Tellin' ya, it's true.
[SKILL OUT 2-A] I was going
into an alley in Block E
to take a leak.
I saw some chick carefully
set down an envelope there.
So I followed her.
[SKILL OUT 2-B] Yeah, and?
Well...
I saw her go into a multi-tenant
building in Block C...
That must be her base.
That's it?
Just the one girl?
She's gotta have
somebody with her.
Naw, I made sure of it...
The sweet girlie
is all by herself.
Let's check it out, then.
[SKILL OUT 2-B] So you're
sure that she's alone?
[SKILL OUT 2-A]
I staked the place out.
[SKILL OUT 2-C]
That is some work ethic, man.
[SKILL OUT 2-B] Haven't
heard anything this good
in a while, huh?
Hey, Kuroko?
Yeah... It's me...
[MIKOTO] Listen...
I need a little favor.
[UIHARU] Oh! Good, you're back!
Are you all
done with the count?
[UIHARU] Yep.
Today's total is...
Seventy-three incidents.
It gets higher
and higher each day, huh?
So, why isn't Shirai here?
Apparently something
important came up
and she had to take off.
Oh, yeah?
[ringing]
Well...
If you need me, I'll be
eating... Eating... Eating...
Yes, hello?
Oh... hey, Saten... Huh?
Oh... Really?
You found one of the
Money Cards, too?
Yes, sure, that's fine.
Tomorrow or whenever...
Oh, one other thing...
No problem...
You just need me to hang out
with Haru'ue until
you get back, right?
Thanks.
I appreciate it.
[SATEN] Oh, hold on a second.
There was something
I wanted to ask you about.
What? Did I see Misaka today?
Yes... She was actually
here with Shirai
earlier this afternoon dropping
off one of the Money Cards.
She was, really?
All right, then, I guess
I must've been wrong.
I probably just mistook
someone else for her...
No... It's nothing, really...
I'll see you later.
This makes no sense.
It looked just like her.
What? Misaka
has a look-alike?
Yes... Saten said she
saw her earlier today.
Now that you
mention it...
there were stories about
Level 5 clones a long time ago.
Seriously?
[KONORI] There was some
research facility somewhere
that used cloning technology
to try mass-producing Level 5s.
Or so the story goes.
That does sort of sound
like Academy City
and like a rumor Saten
would sink her teeth into.
Absolutely.
[KUROKO] Coming!
Oh, Head Resident...
Nice of you to drop by...
I see you're as
diligent as ever.
[HEAD RESIDENT]
Hey... where is Misaka?
[MIKOTO]
Can you hear me, Kuroko?
Where did you put the shampoo?
Shampoo? I should
get that for her...
If you'll please excuse me,
Head Resident...
Just a second,
Sissy, I'm getting it!
[MIKOTO] Geez, can't
you move any faster?!
[KUROKO] Okay, okay.
[MIKOTO] Kuroko,
my towel is all w--
Why are you coming in--
Aren't I a good
roommate, Sissy?
Fooling the head resident
because you didn't make it
back home before curfew...
Imagine what would have happened
if I hadn't had my
"Secret Sissy Voice Collection."
You would've been
in big trouble.
It's been a while since you've
been late like this...
It used to happen a
lot more frequently.
Where are you?
[SKILL OUT 2-A] Hey! Hope you
don't mind some company.
[SKILL OUT 2-A]
Take it nice and easy
and nothing has to get violent.
Was there something
that you needed?
[SKILL OUT 2-D] It's like this.
You know those cards you've
been spreading around town?
We thought we'd stop by and take
all the rest of 'em from ya.
[SKILL OUT 2-A] Easy, now!
It would be a real pain for us
if you hit some kind
of panic button,
so I think we'll just take a
look in there ourselves... Hey!
[SKILL OUT 2-C] On it.
[SKILL OUT 2-C] What the--
Looks like she's only
got two of 'em here.
What?
There's none
over here, either...
We came all the way out
here for two freakin' cards?
Are you kidding?
Yeah.
I'd rather not raise
my hand against a woman.
It's really not my style...
So why don't you just
tell us where they ar--
[NUNOTABA]
There aren't any more here.
Understand?
They've already
been distributed.
No way, she's lying.
And you seem a
little too relaxed,
considering the situation.
What's with you... huh?
Hey, you're right...
You think she has an ability?
[SKILL OUT 2-D]
So what if she does?
There aren't many of them
that can do anything
against a group this big...
For now, let's search
this place top to bottom...
You. Keep an eye on her, got it?
Yeah... Sure.
What are you
so spooked about?
Spooked? What?
I'm not spooked!
[SKILL OUT 2-D] Hey...
Shut up and do it already.
[rummaging sounds]
[SKILL OUT 2-A]
Any luck over there?
[SKILL OUT 2-B] Nothing...
Damn it, where are they?
[SKILL OUT 2-A]
Shut up and keep looking.
[SKILL OUT 2-C] Damn...
I don't know what it is...
but something about
this chick creeps me out.
[SKILL OUT 2-C]
That school badge...
I've seen it somewhere.
[SKILL OUT 2-C]
Nagatenjoki Academy?
[SKILL OUT 2-C] No way...
That's the most elite school
in the whole entire city!
And that's gotta mean this girl
is a high-level ability user!
[SKILL OUT 2-C]
No, hold on, calm down...
That place is different
than Tokiwadai.
They take students who are good
at other things
besides abilities...
So she may not
have one, after all.
Maybe she's just smart.
[SKILL OUT 2-C]
What're ya' staring at?
[NUNOTABA] Your skin--
it looks a little pale...
Are you sure you feel okay?
[SKILL OUT 2-C] B-back off.
[NUNOTABA] You're
breathing hard, too.
And that's a nasty cold sweat.
It looks like you're
shaking pretty badly.
Hey...!
Almost like...
How did you know that?
I just do.
[SKILL OUT 2-C]
Ahhh!
[SKILL OUT 2-A]
Hey, what's wrong?
What... what the
hell did you do?
Man... she's got one!
She's got an ability!
If she did,
wouldn't she have
attacked us earlier
and been done with it?
But she isn't packing...
How else could she
have taken out our guy?
[NUNOTABA] There's a
condition to activate it.
My ability...
It's called "Critical."
It can only be used
against those I've
come into contact with.
It takes one touch.
After that, no matter
how far you run...
no matter where you hide...
I can end your life.
Yeah, right...
Just another lie.
You expect us to believe you?
There's no ability like that.
Give it up already.
[NUNOTABA] Whether
you believe me or not
is totally up to you...
There are many
variations of the ability
that I possess,
but they are real enough.
I can trace and tamper
with others using their
AIM diffusion fields.
Of course...
to Level Zeroes,
such as yourselves...
that description may
not mean very much.
Please...
That's a buncha crap,
and you know it.
Hey! What's with you?
I... I touched her before...
What's gonna happen to me?
If what she's saying is true,
I could be a gonner!
Don't freak out, you moron...
It's like I already said,
she's full of it.
[SKILL OUT 2-A] M-Maybe, but...
It's not gonna
do us any good
to start fighting each other.
[NUNOTABA] Very true.
Fighting amongst
friends is never the answer.
Come on!
[SKILL OUT 2-B]
Hey! What do I do now?
[SKILL OUT 2-A] Just calm down!
Shut up...
I can take care of this.
[SKILL OUT 2-D] What?
[scream]
[SKILL OUT 2-D]
Wh-What was that?
Hey... you guys...!
[scream]
[SKILL OUT 2-D] Damn...
What the hell is going on here?
[SKILL OUT 2-D]
You're kidding, right?
Oh, good.
Only one more to go.
[SKILL OUT 2-D]
Lights off again?
[SKILL OUT 2-D] I'll get her!
I'll get her good!
[SKILL OUT 2-D] I can hear you!
[pained moans]
[SKILL OUT 2-D] Crap...
My pipe! Where did it go?
[approaching footsteps]
[SKILL OUT 2-D] Damn!
What's she doing to me?
What's happening?
Turn on the liiigghts!
[NUNOTABA]
All it takes is one touch.
Now my ability has you.
Don't worry. It's all right.
It will be over before
you can feel any pain...
Just like it was when
I took care of your friends.
[SKILL OUT 2-D]
Wait, you don't have to!
I'll get out of here...
I'll leave!
I'm sorry! Don't kill me!
[NUNOTABA] It's simple, really.
All I have to do
now is lower my hand.
[NUNOTABA] Three...
Two... One... Zero...
[SKILL OUT 2-D] Noooo!!
[pop]
Well. I got a pretty decent
'pop' out of this thing.
That was an
impressive show you put on.
Special effects and all.
The whole time
I was waiting
to step in if things got ugly...
I never expected
you to neutralize
this many Skill
Outs so easily...
And all with just narrative,
showmanship, and what is that?
Some kind of anesthetic?
[MIKOTO] Is something wrong?
[NUNOTABA] So, it's you...
[NUNOTABA] The Original.
[NUNOTABA]
So, it's you... the Original.
[KUROKO] That's right!
My original "Secret Sissy
Voice Collection" played
a vital role in this episode!
[MIKOTO] No, it did not!