Ha ha ha!
- Ha ha ha!
Mayday! Mayday!
- Pirates!
- Hold them off!
Sheeta, stay out of the way
and you won't get hurt.
Aah!
- Come on!
Hurry up!
Break the door down!
SHEETA: Aah!
Yaah! Oof!
- Where is she?
No!
Hey, I found her!
She's hiding out here!
Don't let her escape!
Quick, get her!
LOUIE: Whoa, Ma!
Don't let me go!
DOLA: Quit your whining!
I got you!
Aah!
She's wearing the crystal!
- Now, go get her!
- Right!
I want that crystal!
Aaah!
DOLA: Oh, no!
There goes my crystal!
Oh, no!
I need some meatballs
for the boss, please.
All right. You're sure
working late tonight, Pazu.
Things are finally busy
for a change.
- Still working?
- Yep. Bye!
Huh?
What is that?
Looks like a body! Whoa!
Whoa!
Aah! Whoa! Whoa!
Yaah!
Huh?
Aah!
BOSS: Pazu!
What are you doing up there?
Did you bring my dinner?
Yeah, I did!
But this girl
came down from the sky!
Ohh...
BOSS:
Blast these old pipes!
Aah! Whoa.
Uh, here you go.
Boss!
BOSS:
Come on! Come on!
Listen, Boss!
A girl came--
What? Not again!
Just when I get
one thing fixed--
Listen to me!
A girl came down--
BOSS: Tighten
the second valve, will you?
There's no time to lose!
Ah, this machinery's too old!
- I think I need a bigger wrench!
- I'll get it!
Go run the hoist
while I fix this!
Huh?
- You think you can do it?
- Yeah! Here!
BOSS: Just stay calm
and use your head!
Right.
- Hit the brake!
- What?
PAZU: Whew.
Well, how'd it go, boys?
No silver,
not even any trace of tin.
We're just not having any luck.
Maybe we would
if we tried digging...
the mines just east of here.
I don't know.
Those mines are worse
than this one.
We just have to start
all over again.
Let's call it a day.
Good night.
- 'Night.
Shut off the boiler, Pazu.
We're not gonna find
anything today.
If things keep going like this.
we'll all be starving soon.
And, Pazu, maybe you can oil
that blasted machine!
- OK!
- Thanks. Good night.
PAZU: 'Night!
SHALULU: Mom, it's no use.
Let's call it off.
There's too much cloud cover.
It's too dark!
- What?!
Mom, don't worry.
I'll find her!
DOLA: We'll all find her!
Ohh!
PAZU: Hello!
It's about time you got up!
How are you feeling?
Hi, there!
My name's Pazu.
I'm really glad to see
you're doing all right.
You had me worried there.
Go ahead. Feed them.
- Don't be shy.
- Aah!
These guys are really happy
we have a visitor.
Well, thank goodness.
You laugh
like a regular person.
The way you fell from the sky...
I thought that maybe you were
an angel or something.
Thank you very much
for saving me.
Oh, I'm sorry.
My name's Sheeta.
Sheeta--
what a beautiful name.
I had to catch you.
You were just floating.
- What? Floating?
- Yeah.
Well, I remember an airship...
but I can't remember
anything else.
That's all you remember?
Mm-hmm. I'm not sure
how I survived.
PAZU: Hmm.
Well, I think I might
have an idea about that.
May I see your necklace
for a second?
This?
My grandmother gave it to me.
It's been in my family
for generations.
Wow, it's beautiful.
Could you hold this?
- Oh.
Thanks. Heh.
Get a load of this! Watch!
Here I go-o-o!
Pazu! Are you all right?
Unh!
Ha! Well, so maybe
I had the wrong idea...
about this necklace. Aah!
Oh!
Aah! Aah!
Whoa!
I'm so sorry, Pazu.
- Ohh.
- Are you OK?
I'm fine.
Oh, you scared me.
Does it hurt much?
Are you kidding?
If my head were any harder...
you could use it
as a cannonball.
Whoa! The kettle!
It must be boiling over!
Come on! Let's go!
Follow me! This way!
I'll get breakfast started.
You can wash up over there.
There's a clean towel, too.
SHEETA: Great. Thank you.
"Laputa."
Sheeta!
It's time for breakfast!
My father took that picture
from an airship.
He loved to fly.
It's Laputa--
the floating island.
An island
that floats in the sky?
Yep. Most people think
it's just a legend...
but my dad actually saw it.
That's a picture
of his airship.
PAZU: It looked like a castle
just floating there in the sky.
He said it was the most amazing
thing he'd ever seen.
And that's the only picture
he was able to take.
But take
a look at this, Sheeta.
Dad kept a journal,
and he made all sorts...
of drawings of Laputa, see?
There it is.
He drew the castle...
and also what he thought
the people'd look like.
He was sure the castle
was filled with treasure...
but nobody believed him.
They called him a liar.
Being called a liar
is what killed him.
But I am gonna prove that
my dad was no liar, Sheeta.
As soon as I'm done building
this plane...
I'm gonna take off
and find Laputa myself.
Hmm.
Ohh!
It's a real automobile!
You don't see many of those around here!
- Those people are pirates Pazu.
- What?
SHEETA: They're the ones
who attacked the airship.
They're probably after you.
Come on!
PAZU: Good morning!
Good-bye!
LOUIE: Hold it! Wait up!
PAZU: Yes?
How can I help you, mister?
Young man, query--
Have you seen a little girl
around here?
Let me see now.
There are about 100 girls
in this town. Which one?
Thanks for nothing, kid!
Bye!
They are definitely
after you, Sheeta.
Louie, go tell your mother!
She's in disguise!
So, she's in disguise!
Go tell my mother!
Haven't seen her.
That's what you keep saying...
but I want you think
really hard about it.
PAZU: Boss!
Boss!
She'd be about the age
of those two.
Aah! Oh, no!
There she is!
Don't let her get away!
Now!
Yeow!
Hey, boss, they're pirates!
They're after her!
Pirates? I want to see!
You can stop right there,
my friend.
Think you're tough, don't you?
- I'm tough enough.
- We'll see about that.
BOSS: Just go away.
We're honest folks here.
What did you do that for?
Quick, leave from the back.
No, I'm gonna fight 'em!
Pazu, what if you wind up
getting yourself hurt?
So?!
So, somebody's got
to protect your friend.
Hmm? Oh. Mm-hmm.
Why don't you get
out of our way?
Why don't you
just try and make me?
Maybe I will!
HENRI: Oh, yeah!
Make your shirt explode.
MAN: Hey, Boss, show him
what you're made of!
Ha ha ha!
Mm-hmm.
MAN: You showed him, boss!
I'm not mending that,
I hope you know.
Take that, you landlubber!
- He took it.
- He certainly did.
LOUIE: Come on, Shalulu!
Give him
something for nothing!
Ooh!
You go get him, boss!
Unh!
BOTH: He said Mom was ugly,
now go get him!
- Oh!
- Raah!
That's it! Get him!
- That's it!
- Punch him!
Come on, you got it!
- Yeah! Yeah!
- Hey, loudmouth!
No... Unh!
Get in there!
Give him a right, a left!
DOLA: Whoa! Oh...
They're headed for
the railroad tracks.
Let's move it!
Hey! Hey!
We're gonna jump on, Sheeta!
SHEETA: Right! Unh!
PAZU: That's it!
- Come on!
- Unh!
DRIVER: Hey, Pazu,
who's your friend there?
PAZU: Her name is Sheeta!
Pirates are after us!
- It's the Dola gang!
- Pirates?
Can you drop us at the police
station in the next town?
DRIVER: Sure.
Help me stoke up the engine!
PAZU: Will do!
- Huh?
- Hey, it's Mom!
You chowderheads!
Get your brother and hop on!
But Sheeta's hiding
inside that house.
Lame-brain! They made an escape.
Now, step on it!
They escaped?
- I want to come!
- Mommy!
Unh! Hey!
Well...
Hey, Pazu, here they come!
Can't this engine go any faster?
This is the best she'll do!
She's old!
Floor it! Move over!
I'd really prefer
to be in the car, Mother!
DRIVER: Increase the steam!
They're gaining on us!
- We got 'em!
- Yaah!
We need you in here!
- Help with the fire!
- OK!
Aah!
Yaah!
Uh-oh!
Unh! Charge!
- Look out!
- Aah!
DOLA: Come on!
Get 'em! Get 'em!
Hey, come back here!
You'll get yours!
Don't just stand there!
Push this train
over the cliff!
BOTH: What?
DRIVER: Ha ha ha!
We sure showed them!
- I can do it now.
- You were amazing!
- Heave! Heave!
- And heave...
- Wait.
- And stop.
You think maybe it's Muska?
Yeah it's Muska, all right.
We gotta find those kids.
Huh?
Well, What do you know about that?
It's the army to the rescue!
Hey! Could you kindly help
these two young people?
Pirates have been
chasing them all day!
Huh? What's the matter?
Good-bye, Pazu!
Young lady, come back here!
- Unh!
- Oh!
Sheeta, wait!
Halt, or I'll shoot!
- Aah!
- Ow!
LOUIE:
It's an armored train, Mother!
DOLA: And we're
the Dola gang! Attack!
PAZU: No! Hey! Sheeta!
SHEETA: Don't follow me!
You'll get hurt!
Aah!
ALL: Whoa!
- Don't let go!
Come on!
- Where are they, Mother?
DOLA: Be quiet!
Just watch them.
SHALULU: Ohh!
Ahh!
Huh? Oh!
Sheeta, we're floating!
You see?
This was what happened
the first time I saw you.
See that?
It's the power of the crystal.
I knew it!
I knew there was something
special about your necklace!
- Oh!
- Whoo!
The necklace will let us down
nice and easy.
Boys, I want that crystal!
SOLDIER: Fire!
It's fantastic!
Incredible!
I must have that crystal!
It's going out!
Ah, wait. Just a minute.
I guess your necklace
must come to life...
whenever you're in trouble.
PAZU:
Wow, that's a long way up.
I hope they're all right--
your boss and his wife
and that nice train engineer.
My friends are all miners.
They can take
care of themselves.
I wouldn't worry about them
if I were you.
Come on, Sheeta. Let's go.
This has been
a mining town...
as long as
anyone can remember.
Most of these tunnels
aren't even used anymore.
PAZU: Here you go.
Thank you. I'm glad
you brought some food.
I'm starving.
And for dessert, I've got
a green apple and some candy.
Really? You know that bag of yours
must be magic.
It's always
got just what we need.
Ha!
Mmm!
Sheeta, where exactly
do you come from?
I come from Gondoa--
deep in the northern mountains.
I used to live there
with my parents...
and we were very happy.
But when my mother
and father died...
I was all alone.
The only thing
that kept me going...
was the farm and
taking care of my animals.
But one day.
everything changed.
That was the day
the men came and took me away.
Whoa, wait a minute.
They kidnapped you?
Yes.
It was that man
in the dark glasses.
I wonder who that guy is...
and what
he's doing with the army.
I think Dola and that man
are both after your necklace.
I think you're right,
but I had no idea...
my crystal was
so incredibly powerful.
It's been in my family
as long as I can remember.
Mother gave it to me
before she died...
and she told me
never to show it...
or give it away to anyone.
PAZU: Huh.
We orphans should stick
together, don't you think?
SHEETA: I'm really sorry.
It's my fault getting you
mixed up in all this.
PAZU: Are you kidding?
This is the most exciting thing
that's ever happened to me.
I wouldn't miss an adventure
like this for the world!
What?
Are you some sort of goblin
come to torment me?
It's Uncle Pom!
Don't worry. He's a friend.
Uncle Pom,
boy, am I glad to see you!
I can't see you
clearly yet, goblin...
but you sound like Pazu.
And if these old eyes
don't deceive me...
there's a she-goblin with you.
There are pirates
chasing us, Uncle Pom.
- Oh?
- The army's right behind them.
Ha ha ha! That sounds
absolutely splendid!
UNCLE POM: The tea is ready.
Help yourself.
SHEETA: Thank you.
This is great.
Don't you get lonely down here
underground, Uncle Pom?
Never, my dear.
All of these rocks
are my friends.
They often talk to me.
Ever since last night, they've been
especially restless.
- The rocks talk to you?
- Oh, yes, Pazu.
The earth
speaks to all of us...
and if we listen.
we can understand.
The rocks speak
in a very small voice.
Huh? Oh, my!
- Whoa!
Amazing!
Pazu, look above us!
Huh? Wow!
It was just a hunk of rock
a while ago.
SHEETA: Oh, my!
UNCLE POM: The answer
lies inside these rocks.
Let me show you.
SHEETA: Pazu, you see?
All the rocks around here
contain a bit of aetherium.
PAZU: Really?
Mankind once knew
how to mine aetherium...
but no longer.
Wait!
Look, my stone's glowing!
Well, goodness!
Bless my soul!
That's a pure
aetherium crystal!
There hasn't been one...
since before
my great-grandfather's time.
No wonder
the rocks were restless.
This stone possesses
incredible power.
Legend has it
that only the people...
of the floating city of Laputa...
knew how to make
such crystals.
They made this crystal?
They used aetherium to make
Laputa float in the sky.
PAZU: I knew Laputa
wasn't just made up!
You see, Sheeta?
It's just like my dad said!
What's the matter?
I'm sorry, but would you
put that crystal away?
It's too strong for me.
Oh, sorry.
What is it, Uncle Pom?
Great-grandpa used to tell me
the rocks become restless...
when Laputa
appears over the mine.
Wow! So that must mean...
Laputa's over the mine
right now!
Listen! Sheeta, now I can prove
that the legend is true!
Sheeta, I must tell you
something.
SHEETA: Yes?
What is it?
That crystal
is extremely powerful...
but with a power
that rightfully belongs...
to the earth
from which it came.
To forget that,
and then to try to use...
the crystal's power
for selfish reasons...
will bring great unhappiness.
- You understand?
- Yes.
Your crystal should remind us
that we come from the earth...
and to the earth
we must return.
Come on, lighten up!
Two times already,
that crystal's gotten Sheeta...
out of some really big trouble.
And I have a feeling...
that crystal's gonna
help us find Laputa.
LOUIE: It's flying away!
HENRI: Mom, can we go back
to the ship now, please?
DOLA: It's too quiet.
We better just stay put
for the time being.
SHALULU:
Does this mean no lunch?
The coast is clear.
Let's go.
Uncle Pom, thank you.
Be careful, my dear.
Wow, look up there!
Beyond that cloud
is a floating city...
that no one here on earth
believes exists.
But I swear--I am going
to be the one to prove it!
- Pazu?
- Huh?
Listen, there's something
I haven't told you yet.
You see my family has a very old
traditional name...
and when the stone
was passed on to me...
I inherited that name.
And the name I inherited was
Lusheeta Toel Ul Laputa.
Laputa? You mean you're...
They found us, Sheeta!
Let's go!
- Head back to the mine!
- Stop them!
- Unh!
- Aah!
Hands up!
Don't you touch her!
- Let me go!
- Aah!
Oh, no!
Are you all right, Pazu?
You have to wake up, Pazu!
- Sir, we've captured them.
- And about time.
Ohh!
Huh?
Huh? Hey, let me out!
Unh!
Where am I?
SOLDIER: Forward, march!
Aah!
We're wasting time!
You twist an arm or two, and
I guarantee the girl will talk.
I respectfully disagree.
Such military tactics risk
wasting more time, general.
If my military tactics
had been used to begin with...
Dola wouldn't have had a chance
to interfere with us at all!
It was a military transmission
that the pirates decoded.
You've bungled things, sir.
and now I must fix them.
Your job, general...
is to mobilize the troops
when it becomes necessary.
Muska, just don't forget...
that the government put me
in charge of finding Laputa!
Don't forget that as
the government's secret agent...
I am in charge of you, general.
Blast.
I really hate that man.
Huh?
I trust you slept well?
Where is Pazu? Is he
all right? I want to see him!
Now, this is fit for a princess.
Don't worry, Sheeta.
Your friend is being treated as
if he were the guest of royalty.
I want you to see something
before you see him.
Please step inside.
What is it?
An artificial life form.
It's called a robot.
Laputa was just a legend
until this dropped from the sky.
Huh?
- Aah!
- Oh! Ohh!
MUSKA:
Now the government wants me...
to unlock Laputa's secrets.
For example, what's this fellow
made of--metal or ceramics?
With our limited technology,
we have no idea.
But he does tell us one thing.
Come and see.
Don't be afraid, Sheeta. He's
really quite dead, you know.
Look there.
It's the same emblem...
that decorates the fireplace
in your home.
And your crystal.
You see, Sheeta, this crystal
also comes from Laputa.
And I believe the powers
locked inside it...
are capable of leading a person
back to that city's treasures.
Then why?
Why don't you just take it?
Just take it and keep Laputa's
treasures for yourself...
but leave Pazu and me alone,
please!
You think I'm doing this
for money?
You understand nothing.
According to the legend,
the same technology...
that kept Laputa airborne
also made it...
a major power that once
dominated the entire planet.
If such a horrible thing
is still floating up there...
you can understand
what a threat it is...
to the peace of the world.
Sheeta,
the stone only works for you.
You must know of some way
to make the stone...
point out
the location of Laputa.
I really don't know anything.
Please let me see Pazu!
I don't want to see
any harm come to anyone...
but I simply can't control what
the military might do to him.
What?!
In the event
that you cooperate...
I'm sure whosever is in charge
will grant Pazu his freedom...
Lusheeta Toel Ul Laputa.
You know my real name.
"Ul" means "ruler" in Laputian.
"Toel" means "true."
You are the legitimate heir...
to the throne of Laputa,
Princess Lusheeta.
Aah!
Unh!
SOLDIER: Let's go! Out!
Sheeta!
Are you all right, Pazu?
I'm OK, but what about you?
They didn't hurt you, did they?
Pazu, I'm so sorry. There's
been a grave misunderstanding.
We had no idea
how nobly you fought...
to protect our little Sheeta
from those awful pirates.
What's he talking about?
Pazu, do this for me.
Forget about Laputa.
What are you saying?
It's been decided
that the search for Laputa...
will be made secretly
by the army...
with Sheeta's cooperation.
Really, the best thing
you can do...
is forget
you ever heard of the place.
Forget about Laputa?
I'm sorry I caused you
so much trouble.
I hope someday
you can forgive me.
I can't forget! No way!
Laputa means too much
to both of us!
- Good-bye!
- Sheeta!
Aah! Come back!
Now, behave, little boy.
Use your head!
Here, take this--
a little something...
to show our appreciation
of your efforts.
Only you can do it.
Remember the words
that bring the crystal to life.
Keep your promise,
and you too will be free.
Unh! Huh?
Hey, mommy! Mommy, it's Pazu!
Pazu's outside!
Oh, my! Pazu!
Where have you been?
We were all very worried
about you, Pazu.
What happened to your friend?
- It's over now.
- What?
Pazu! Come back!
Unh!
Welcome home, sonny.
PAZU: Get out! Aah!
Get out, or I'll throw you out!
This is my house!
Oh, you don't scare me.
You can't even protect
one small girl!
What do you mean?
Hey, Mom,
can I keep this money?
Up and sold the little girl,
did you? I know your type.
PAZU: You don't know
what you're talking about!
They offered you money,
and you took it, didn't you?
I only left
because Sheeta told me to!
That's why.
So, you believed her,
and you came back here, right?
You're just a scared little boy
who runs away!
Says you!
You don't even have the guts to
stand up to Muska and the army!
He who turns and runs away can
steal the treasure another day!
Don't you think
it's kind of strange...
that the army's gotten into
the kidnapping business?
Do you really think
they'll keep her alive?
Don't you see that
they forced her to make a deal?
Huh?
She saved your life. Get it?
LOUIE: Mommy, you amaze me.
How do you know these things?
DOLA: Well, you can't be
a sensitive woman like me...
without leaning a few things.
Sheeta and I
are exactly alike--
all warm and mushy and sensitive.
Now, so when you boys
get married...
You go find a gal like her.
Huh?
She's gonna end up like mama?
- Aw, Mom, that was--
- The ham! Gimme that!
Hmm.
Well, it won't work
changing the code on me.
They're calling
for air destroyer Goliath.
They're planning
to take off with Sheeta.
We've got to hurry,
or it'll be too late!
Come on, boys! Stop eating!
I'm going!
Wait! Are you going
to rescue Sheeta?
No, you little squirt.
We want her crystal.
Wait a minute!
You've got to have Sheeta...
to make
the aetherium crystal work.
Otherwise, it's useless!
Please let me come with you!
I need to save her!
Sheeta means everything to me.
You know something?
You're acting like
a sniveling little crybaby.
Maybe you're right. I should
have protected Sheeta...
but instead,
I was stupid and angry.
But let me come with you...
and I swear
I'll protect her this time!
Pazu loves Sheeta
- Be quiet!
Hmm.
Guess you'll be useful in
getting Sheeta to cooperate.
You might never
come back here again, Pazu.
I know.
- Ready for what might happen?
- Mm-hmm.
We leave here in one minute!
Now, you guys be good.
- Here, fasten this.
- Right!
Let's rendezvous
at the Tiger Moth.
What a superb ship!
Muska, has the girl
surrendered the information?
It will take a little more time.
More time?
Well, you'll have plenty
of that aboard Goliath.
We set out with her
at first light.
Hurry! We have to get there
before sun up!
Sheeta.
Well, well, now,
what shall we do?
Sheeta, maybe grandma
should teach you a spell--
one that will help you
when you're in trouble.
A spell?
Yes, my dearest.
An ancient secret spell.
Leetay latuparita ulus
arialos balu netoreel.
Leetay a...
The words mean "save me."
"save me
and revive the eternal light."
So, leetay latuparita ulus
arialos balu netoreel.
Leetay latuparita ulus...
Aah! Aah!
Aah!
Ahh. I knew it!
It's the sacred light!
The ancient documents were true!
It's not just a legend!
What are you talking about?
Aaah!
Oh!
Tell me the spell!
What are the secret words?
- Did you hear that?
- Yeah.
- Huh?
I'm telling you,
this thing is alive!
Do you hear me? Alive!
What?
GUARD: Help, it's alive!
And it's after us!
- Run for your lives!
- It's the robot! Go! Run!
It's come back to life!
Hurry! Hurry! Sound the alarm!
Quick! Quick!
SOLDIER: He's moving!
- What's happening?
- Sir, it's the robot.
It's coming toward us!
Shut the fire door! Hurry!
- Pull back!
- Look out!
- Aah!
- The power!
Yes, I understand.
It's your crystal.
The force
of the sacred light...
has brought the robot
back to life!
The way to Laputa
has been opened!
Let me go!
- Ohh!
- Unh!
Aah!
It's going to fly!
Oh!
Oh! Oh!
It's Laputa.
Finally.
I now know the way to Laputa.
Hurry! No time to waste!
What do you mean, robot?
I want to know who's trying
to blow up my fortress!
Are you there?
Somebody answer me now!
- We're ready.
- You're connected now, Colonel.
This is Colonel Muska.
We have an emergency.
You'll take your orders
from me now.
Huh?
Hurry! I need that shell now!
- Fire!
Aah!
Let's get up there now!
- We demolished it!
- We got him!
Go get the girl!
- Over there!
- Yes, sir.
SOLDIER: Make sure
it doesn't move, now.
Is she dead?
Hey, get up.
Nah, she's only fainted.
- Come on.
- Oh, no!
Aah!
Wow
Must be some kind of war
goin' on!
- Take her down, Dola!
- Call me captain!
Whee!
Ha ha ha!
Just keep your big head down,
Shalulu!
Huh?
Stop it!
You're destroying everything!
Please, stop!
Captain Mother, Goliath
is moving! Goliath is moving!
If we stay on this heading,
we'll be in the line of fire.
- Change course!
- Look! There she is!
- It's Sheeta!
- What?
- Where'd you see her?
- Steady as she goes, captain!
PAZU:
She's on top of that tower!
One for all and all for mom!
- Cover me!
- Good luck!
Sheeta!
My hand--take it!
Pazu!
I've gotta get in
a little closer, Dola!
Aah! Uhh!
Pazu!
But they're here to help me!
Please, put me down!
Aah!
Sheeta!
Uhh!
PAZU: Dola!
No! They're falling!
No.
Help!
Come on!
Oh, come on, pull up!
Uhh!
It's now or never, Pazu.
I'll take us in,
and you grab her.
PAZU: Right!
Over here!
- OK, captain!
- Go!
What are you doing? Fools!
Don't let her escape!
Aaah!
An entire army,
and they're getting away!
It's not over.
Muska, Muska! What on earth
happened to the robot?
We destroyed it,
and the girl's gone.
What?! Ohh!
Look at this. It's a disaster.
I think we may have found
what you've been looking for.
Extinguish the fire!
Organize a pursuit team!
It still possesses
its sacred light...
pointing to Laputa.
You may now go tell
the general for me...
we will be departing on time.
Sheeta, you OK?
If I did something wrong...
I'd really like
to apologize for it, Sheeta.
DOLA: We all did
something wrong...
wastin' our time
on these two kids.
Here's your valley up ahead.
I'll drop you off there,
and that'll be that.
It's allright.
Dola, will you let us sail
with you and the boys?
Call me captain, darn it!
I don't see what the heck's
in it for me...
since you've lost
the aetherium crystal!
We can work.
And I have to find out
the real truth...
about Laputa for myself,
captain.
So, you're not interested
in money...
but you want to find out
the truth about Laputa.
Heh heh. Well, I guess
there's worse reasons...
for you wanting
to become a pirate.
LOUIE: Mother,
I say let 'em come along.
DOLA: Tow the line and
work hard, or overboard you go.
PAZU: Yes, captain.
Yes! No more
swabbin' the decks! Hooray!
I won't have
to wash the dishes!
I've peeled my last potato!
Yee-haw!
- Whoopee!
- Whee!
CHARLES:
Sheeta, can you make pudding?
I love pudding!
I get to lick the spatula!
And I like chocolate cake
with that--
Oh, what's that frosting?
It's kind of pink and swirly.
Will you shut up?
Ah, what can I tell you?
They just really like dessert.
SHEETA AND PAZU: Whoa!
And disembark.
Uhh! Wow, what is this ship
made out of, cloth?
And don't you rip it!
- Uhh!
Come on, we'll go topside.
Ohh!
DOLA: You're goin'
the wrong way! Come here!
I don't like slow-pokes!
- Ohh!
- Pazu?
DOLA: Come on, matey.
I haven't got all day.
LOUIE: Work, work, work.
Busy, busy, busy, busy.
Left, right, left, right.
You're not here to have fun.
Whoa. This engine room
is really amazing.
Is that what it's called?
Hey, papa! Where are you?!
Oh!
Hey, pop, I finally found you
an assistant!
Stop yelling at me!
I can hear you!
Believe me,
sometimes I wish I couldn't.
Uh, hurry up. He is
even tougher than my mother.
It's too narrow. I can't reach.
It's OK. I got it.
- What's your name?
- Pazu.
But the beam from the crystal
was pointing directly due east.
Are you sure about this?
Yes, I'm sure I could see
the sun rising from the tower.
You know, it's the end
of grass-cutting season...
so the sun rose
not from due east...
but a little further south.
The light was pointing
to the left of the hill...
from which the sun rose,
you see?
Pretty smart.
Found anything yet?
Haven't found a single thing,
captain.
DOLA: They're
jamming the airwaves...
so we can't find 'em.
the flying devils.
Mom, how can we catch them when
they're faster than we are?
Well, It looks like we're cruising
on the windward side of 'em.
So if we manage
to ride the trade wind...
Let's see. According
to my calculations...
with wind velocity at ten...
looks to me
like we'll catch 'em.
Attention, all hands!
Now hear this!
Goliath is already underway
for Laputa.
We're gonna set sail
and go after them.
If we can catch the wind...
we'll be on their heels
by tomorrow.
The first man to spy Goliath
will receive ten gold coins.
That's good money!
And if the stories we've heard
about Laputa are true...
there'll be enough treasure...
to make an honest pirate
of us all.
Ha ha! All right!
All hands aboard!
Look alive and get to work!
Let her rip!
Course, ninety-eight degrees.
Velocity, fifty.
Now you gotta start
dressing like a real pirate.
Let's see... here.
And this is
where you'll be working.
DOLA: This is the galley.
I want it shipshape...
sparkling clean, and
ready for action in one hour.
- That's an order.
- But I--
The boys get awful hungry,
so you'll serve 5 meals a day.
You blubberheads!
I'm not runnin' a luxury cruise!
Now get to work!
Mmm.
Hmm?
Hmm.
SHEETA: Come in.
I'm afraid I'm still cooking.
Nothing's ready yet.
It took me a long time
to clean everything up.
- Ahem.
- Uh, yes? What is it?
Uh...
Yes?
I finished my work
for the moment...
and I've come to offer you
my help.
Well, that's kind of you.
Would you please hand me
those plates over there?
With pleasure,
my little ang-- ohh!
I thought you said
you had a stomach ache.
I'm in love with you!
- You?
- Hello.
- Move!
- Too crowded.
Hey, what do I look like,
a chair?
Hi. Is there anything I can do?
- Huh?
- Hey!
What's come over you, my dear?
It's not like you to challenge
a ship like Goliath.
You know,
the odds are against you.
I'm after treasure. That's all.
Heh heh heh. I must admit,
those kids are cute.
What do you mean by that,
you old fool?
Nothing.
But that little girl...
does remind me of you
not so long ago.
- Who asked ya?
- Nobody.
- Oh, look. Checkmate.
- Huh?
MAN: Fabulous!
Does anyone want any more?
I do believe I will have
a second helping.
- Yes!
- I want some more!
Come on, young pup.
Huh?
Time to go on duty.
It's cold. Take this.
Huh?
- I'll take over.
- Thank you!
Huh?
Sheeta!
Ohh. Whoa!
Ohh! That was exciting.
Wow! You can see forever.
Ohh.
Sheeta? Here.
PAZU: You OK?
SHEETA: That's better.
This is great.
Now we can keep watch together.
- Pazu?
- Hmm?
SHEETA: I'm really scared.
To tell you the truth,
I don't want to go to Laputa.
What do you mean?
Didn't you tell Dola
the truth?
SHEETA:
I didn't lie to Dola.
What I said about
the light's direction is true.
But what if someone else dies?
PAZU:
You mean, like the robot?
SHEETA:
He died to save my life.
I feel awful.
All this is because of a spell
my grandmother taught me.
She taught me
all sorts of spells.
A spell to use when you're
looking for something...
a spell to cure sickness.
There's even one she told me
I must never use.
- What kind of spell?
- The spell of destruction.
SHEETA: She said that
to give power to good spells...
I had to know evil ones, too.
But she told me
never to use them.
I was so scared
when I leaned that spell...
I couldn't sleep.
I didn't know the spells
were connected to my necklace.
Uncle Pom was right
when he said...
that it was dangerous for us to
misuse the power of the crystal.
And what if Laputa
has the same power...
that can also be used
for great evil?
I wish
I'd thrown the crystal away.
But then we never
would have met.
And anyway, even if you had,
Laputa would still exist.
Airplanes and flying machines
are getting better and better.
You know, eventually,
some explorer or another...
will come across the city
of Laputa one day and claim it.
I can't say
I know what's best...
but if Laputa really has
such great power...
we can't let it
fall into the hands...
of bad people like Muska.
And if we run away now,
Muska is gonna chase us forever.
But Pazu, I don't want you
to become a pirate...
because of me.
I'm not gonna become a pirate.
And don't worry.
Dola will understand.
She's much nicer
than she pretends to be.
And when
we've finally found it...
I promise you
we'll go back to Gondoa.
I want to see it all, Sheeta.
The old house where you were
born, the valley and everything.
SHEETA:
Oh, Pazu.
- Sheeta, what's that?
Right there. Under the ship.
See it?
Captain, it's Goliath--
right under our bow!
Starboard rudder,
full speed ahead!
Why don't you go after them,
Muska? Get them!
It's useless to look for them
in the cloud cover.
I don't need to waste my energy
on a wild-goose chase.
Besides, we're running
right on schedule.
It was farther north
than I figured.
Pazu, listen carefully to me.
Everything will be ruined
if we lose track of Goliath.
You've got good eyes.
so I want you...
to watch her
and keep us on course.
How do I do that, captain?
The crow's nest
can be made into a kite.
See the metal handle
on the bulkhead?
- I got it!
- Turn it clockwise!
DOLA: Hook it up
and then turn the handle.
That'll make the wings open.
Now extend the wire.
You'll have to get the hang
of flying it on your own.
Are you up there,
Sheeta, my dear?
- Yes.
- Best you come down right now.
SHEETA: Why?
Because you're a girl--
a female! That's man's work!
But you're female, captain!
I grew up in the mountains.
I can do this!
Sheeta, no!
Be quiet.
And Pazu agrees with me.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
All right, me hearty,
once you take off...
you'll have to use the phone
to communicate.
SHEETA:
You mean this phone?
She is good.
Right. I think we're set.
Ready for takeoff.
DOLA: Aye-aye. Anchors away!
I don't see them.
They must be hiding
under the cloud cover.
DOLA: Perhaps. But they
could also be above you.
Keep your eyes peeled..
- Roger! Whoa!
- Whoa!
PAZU: Hang on tight!
DOLA: What happened?
PAZU:
Nothing. Just a gust of wind.
Didn't bother us at all.
We're fine.
We'll keep on watching.
- Afraid?
- Uh-uh.
I got the hang
of this thing now.
Storm ahead.
Sheeta, look in my bag.
There should be some rope
in there.
OK.
Let's tie ourselves together.
This storm is gonna be rough.
Good idea.
The mercury is dropping
really fast, mom.
Blast our luck, boys.
What a rotten time for a storm.
- When is sun-up?
- In one hour.
Wait a minute.
Something's not right.
The sun is coming up
in the wrong place.
We're out of position.
You're right. We're supposed
to be heading east, not north.
We're going the wrong way.
Captain!
Huh? What do you mean,
we're headed north?
But the compass needle
is pointing east, mom.
There's something
confusing the compass...
and I want to know what it is!
SHEETA:
There it is! Look!
There what is? Is it Goliath?
PAZU:
No, it's a cloud...
and I've only seen
one other like it.
A cloud?
It's heading right for us!
That's it.
I'm not gonna captain my ship
into the eye of a hurricane!
Pull back! Pull back,
I tell you! All engines reverse!
We're being pulled
into the center of the storm!
DOLA: Sorry, Pazu,
we can't help you!
You have to ride it out.
Good luck, sailor!
I can't get it to turn!
Put more backbone into it,
my boy!
Dola, the engine can't take it!
What do you want me
to do about it?
Just do what you can!
Clouds are breaking up.
- Uhh! It's the ocean!
- Huh?
Pazu, it's a hurricane!
I see it, captain!
We're going in!
Wow.
It's just like dad said--
two winds blowing
in opposite directions.
DOLA: Shiver me timbers!
What a powerful storm!
CHARLES: Mom, it's no use!
We'll be sucked in!
If there's one thing
I can't stand, it's a quitter!
PAZU:
Captain, Laputa's in there!
Laputa's where?
This is just the kind of storm
my father saw...
and Laputa's
in the middle of it!
DOLA: It can't be.
It'd be smashed to pieces!
- Pazu! Look there!
- Huh?
My boys, we have a dilemma.
It's Goliath off the port bow!
We're gonna go
into the hurricane.
My dad made it through alive,
and so will we!
Ready?
Brace yourselves, gentlemen!
Aah!
We did it! Got 'em!
If we don't turn,
we'll hit that storm.
- All ahead full.
- Sir?
MUSKA: The light is pointing
to the center of the whirlwind.
Laputa is in that storm.
I won't retreat.
Now go straight ahead--
and that is an order, captain.
- Ready, Sheeta?
- Yes!
Huh?
Father?
Sheeta!
Hey, are you all right?
Wake up.
Mm.
Look.
Laputa.
- Uhh!
- I'm sorry.
- Here.
- Wait a minute.
It's a very tight knot.
And...my... uhh!
My hands are trembling.
Whoa!
- Hoo-hoo!
- Ohh!
- Aah!
- Whoa!
Pretty birds.
They must live here, Pazu.
Huh?
I think he must be here
to meet you, Sheeta.
But I don't have
the aetherium crystal.
Wait, I've gotta cut us loose.
PAZU: Hey, wait!
- You're gonna break that!
- Wait!
Please, Mr.Robot,
don't do that.
We won't be able to go home
without it.
It's a bird's nest.
That's why he's here.
I'm so happy
the eggs are all right, Pazu.
It must be his job
to take care of them.
- He says to follow him.
- How do you know?
I just know that's what he said!
- Ohh!
- Look!
It's a city.
I can't believe
we're inside a building.
Huh?
- Wow, the walls are invisible.
- Yeah.
I wonder what happened here.
This used to be a city
of advanced technology.
It must be a monument.
I wish I could read
what it says.
Someone left some flowers.
Look.
Did you leave the flowers?
Hey, that's a different robot.
It looks like it's been
frozen there forever.
Hey.
They must've been
protectors of the garden.
And they've kept on
guarding the place...
even long after
all the people have gone.
Oh! You've picked
another flower for the grave.
How kind of you.
Oh, thank you.
You must be the only one left.
It looks like
all the other robots...
stopped working a long time ago.
Ha!
You know what, Sheeta?
I bet he's not lonesome at all.
He's got plenty of friends--
the animals and the birds.
He takes care of them.
This way!
The army has destroyed
this part of the city!
SHEETA: I sure hope Dola
and the boys are all right.
PAZU: Me, too. Where are they?
Do you see them?
Wait! There they are!
They've got 'em prisoner!
SHEETA: They've been captured!
We've got to help them!
If we don't, they'll hang 'em
from the yardarm!
- What'll we do?
- Come on.
Hurry!
Sir! Sir!
We've managed
to break down the wall, general.
Just a sample
of what we found inside.
The city
is full of treasure, sir.
- Mama!
- Whoa.
Wouldn't you like to have this?
Well, I've got a different
kind of necklace for you!
Have you radioed a report
on Laputa's discovery, Muska?
I was about to.
See if you can make it
difficult to decode.
And stop pocketing
those jewels, you scum!
MUSKA: The perfect thing to
throw those fools off the scent.
We're up so high.
I hope you're good
at climbing trees, Sheeta.
I've got a plan.
Ohh!
PAZU:
What a greedy pack of thieves.
We can't let them
destroy the garden, Pazu.
We have to find
the aetherium crystal.
We have to find it.
It's the only way
we can protect the garden.
I was wondering why...
all of the storm clouds
just disappeared.
Then I realized
if they hadn't cleared up...
the army
couldn't have made a landing.
You think it was
because of my necklace?
I don't know for sure,
but I think...
the power of the crystal
disintegrated that storm...
and now the castle
has awakened from its sleep...
for whoever holds the crystal.
We can't let Muska figure out
how to use the crystal.
If he does.
it'll be the end of everything.
But even if we can get
my grandmother's crystal back...
how can we use its power?
The spell, Pazu!
The spell of destruction.
Sheeta, it may be the only way.
- Huh?
FIRST SOLDIER:
We need help over here!
SECOND SOLDIER: You, soldier!
Go find the general!
FIRST SOLDIER:
Somebody give us a hand!
SECOND SOLDIER:
Move now! You heard me!
Quickly!
We need to get down there.
I'll go first.
Right. Be careful.
Unh! Aah!
It's OK-- aah!
Unh!
Aah!
MUSKA:
It's around here somewhere.
MUSKA: Hmm.
MUSKA:
It should be here. Wait!
This is it!
- Huh?
- Unh!
It's the boy!
- Aah!
- Sheeta!
- Stop! Don't shoot!
Well, well, looks like
we caught a little princess.
Don't hurt her!
- Unh!
- It came from over here!
- Colonel, what's happening?
- We've found another pirate.
And there's one more
hiding under your feet.
SOLDIER:
Yes, sir! We'll get him.
Sheeta, I'll find you!
SHEETA: Pazu!
Huh?
Is that Pazu?
Uhh!
- Holy smokes!
- Eww.
That wasn't me!
- I need the commanding officer!
- That way!
The general's waiting
over there.
Guards, on the double! Now!
SOLDIER:
You men, come with me!
- Right away, sir!
- Yes, sir!
- Dola.
- Huh?
Hmm?
Hi there.
Sheeta's been captured.
I'm going to save her.
When I cut your ropes.
make a run for it.
Good luck, now, captain.
Wait a minute, boy.
You'd better take this.
Huh? Uhh-- thank you.
The boy has become a man.
What? What do you mean, Muska's
destroyed all the radios?
Sir! He must've done it while
most of the men were outside.
Several of the guards
have been seriously injured.
We've spotted Muska heading
for the black dome below, sir.
He's not alone. He's got
those other two men with him.
So, Colonel Muska reveals
his true nature at last.
Now find him and arrest him!
All right, first platoon, move!
Second platoon, fall in!
You are to shoot
anyone who resists!
We must find Colonel Muska now!
Uh, excuse me, Colonel Muska.
Where are we?
We are in the center of Laputa.
The castle above us
means nothing!
All of Laputa's
scientific knowledge...
is contained in this chamber.
You may wait here, gentlemen.
- Colonel, please!
This is a sacred place...
where only royalty
is allowed to enter.
Huh? What's happened here? Uhh!
These filthy roots
don't belong in this chamber!
Horrible things.
I'll have them burned.
This way. Come!
There it is! This is it.
See?
MUSKA: Not here, too! Aah!
Roots?
At last!
At last I have found it!
The largest
aetherium crystal ever.
And the source
of all the power in Laputa.
The amazing thing
is this beautiful stone...
has been awaiting the return
of its king for 700 years.
SHEETA:
Seven hundred years?
700 years is a long time
to be without a king, isn't it?
It's the black stone,
just as the legend says.
Get away!
There it is. It's the same.
Who are you, Muska?
Yes, my dear.
I, too, have an old secret name.
My real name is
Romska Polo Ul Laputa.
You and I
have the same royal ancestors.
We are both of noble blood.
But then our ancestors
left Laputa to live on earth.
What a mistake!
- The explosives have no effect!
- This is no ordinary stone!
Then use all of the dynamite
we have!
MUSKA: General.
there is no need to do that.
You may come in.
Where are you, Muska?
- Aah!
Huh?
Unh!
Aaaah!
Huh? Aah!
MUSKA:
Really, I don't understand...
why you hesitate, general.
Please come in.
Blast him!
All right, follow me!
Huh?
After him, men! Hurry!
Wait, wait, hold on!
Wait a second.
Just where are you, Muska?
MUSKA: Please be quiet.
- What?
- Up there!
- Whoa.
- What's going on?
Hold your tongue, commoner!
You are in the presence
of the king of Laputa!
The man has gone crazy!
I thought I would show you
an example of Laputa's power.
We are about to celebrate
the rebirth...
of the Laputian kingdom.
Sheeta?
MUSKA: Prepare yourself
for the thunder of Laputa!
Sheeta, I'm coming.
Aah!
The fire of heaven
that destroyed...
Sodom and Gomorrah
in the Old Testament.
The Rahmaniya referred to it
as Indra's Arrow.
The entire world
will once again kneel...
before the power of Laputa.
I can only say well-done, Muska.
You're a credit to our country.
As such,
you deserve this reward.
Huh?
I have really had enough
of your incredible stupidity.
Aah!
- Run, everyone!
- You little brat!
Good-bye!
Blimey! More robots!
Yeah, and there's a lot of them.
Make a run for it!
- Check the flapters!
- OK, mom!
They're ready to travel!
LOUIE: Time to go, mama!
Hush up!
They don't know we're here!
Tarnation.
Now, where are Pazu and Sheeta?
Can't leave without 'em.
Oh!
You had better be gracious
to the new king, dear.
Ohh!
You and I will be spending
quite a lot of time together.
Look at the fools.
Unbelievably stupid!
Pathetic.
They simply don't understand.
It is useless to fight me.
Aah! Uhh!
Aah! Ah!
Huh?
Robots!
Aah!
Sheeta!
MUSKA: A superior being such as
myself has only one option--
burn them.
Don't you agree,
Princess Lusheeta?
MUSKA: Ha ha ha ha ha!
- You insolent little brat!
Uhh!
Seize her!
Ahh.
Be a good girl
and give the crystal back.
Please open up! Please!
Uhh!
Sheeta, listen to me.
Be reasonable.
There's no way you can escape.
SHEETA: Please open! Help me!
Ah!
Sheeta!
Aah!
PAZU: Sheeta!
Pazu? Where are you?
PAZU:
Sheeta! Over here!
Sheeta!
- You're alive!
- Stand back.
I'm gonna blast through.
- Here we go!
- No, Pazu! Hurry! Take this!
Muska's coming! Hurry!
SHEETA: Here, take it!
Throw it into the ocean!
Uhh!
Aah!
Better protect that crystal if
you want to see the girl alive.
Do you hear me?!
Aah!
Get up, princess.
The game is over.
How appropriate that we've
ended up in the throne room.
Now get over here.
This is no longer a throne room.
This is a tomb
for the both of us.
You see, a king
without compassion...
does not deserve a kingdom.
You will never
possess the crystal.
You and I
will die here together.
Now I understand why
the people of Laputa vanished.
There is a song from my home
in the Valley of Gondoa...
that explains everything.
It says,
"Take root in the ground...
"live in harmony
with the wind...
"plant your seeds
in the winter...
"and rejoice with the birds
in the coming of spring."
No matter how many weapons
you have...
no matter how great
your technology might be...
the world cannot live
without love.
Laputa will live.
I will return it to life.
Laputa's power
is the dream of all mankind.
Your ears are next...
unless you get on your knees
and obey me.
I command you.
Give me that stone!
PAZU:
Stop right there, Muska!
I've hidden the stone!
If you do anything
to harm Sheeta...
you'll never get it back!
No, Pazu! Listen!
Run away before he kills you
as well as me!
Look who's here.
Why don't you give me the stone,
and the girl will live.
Otherwise, I'll kill her.
Are you planning
on fighting me?
Go ahead. Use that cannon
you can hardly lift.
You can have the stone
if you let me talk to Sheeta.
No, Pazu! Get out of here
and throw the crystal away!
I'll give you one minute,
starting now.
Ohh, Pazu!
Sheeta,
listen to me very carefully.
Whisper the spell to me.
I'll say it with you.
Just put your hand in mine
and trust me.
Dola and the boys are free.
Don't worry about them.
Time's up. What is your answer?
Huh?
- Balus.
- Aah!
Aaah!
Aah! My eyes!
I can't see!
No! No!
We can't wait anymore, mom!
All right, then.
Let's shove off!
Hurry Up!
Look at that!
The whole thing's collapsing!
Poor kids, I'll really miss them.
They used the spell of destruction.
They saved Laputa from
the evil hands of Muska.
Mother look!
What is that big blue light up there?
It's a big stone
That tree is getting away with our treasure.
Get it! Get it! Move!
Come on you stupid little weirdos!
Sheeta?
Pazu!
Looks like these roots saved us.
It looks fine, it should work.
Ready?
Ready!
Now!
What's going on here?
It's getting away from us.
Sheeta! Yeah!
Dola!
Thank goodness you're alive.
So are you! This is great.
No it's not!
My poor little ship is gone forever.
Stop it a-cryin' you big baby!
I'll get you another ship.
Oh poor little thing,
Nothing worse than having your pigtail shove off.
What have you got under there?
Oh my fault,
You must have hurt yourself on these.
Now how'd they get inside my blouse?
All good pirates listen to their mom.