It happened again.
Dear God, what are we
to do of this?
We must...
act.
What is it Father Vincent?
I fear we have no other choice
but to send for one of them.
Wait...
You don't mean...
Yes.
But what about
the rules of the city?
The situation is so dire we
cannot be held back by rules...
I'm afraid that if we don't
address this now, we'll be...
...finished.
Rabona...?
I believe that's
the holy city, right?
But doesn't Rabona
have rules against...
That's correct...
Anyone considered to be
of 'dubious character'
is forbidden from setting
foot within the holy city.
Needless to say, that applies
to anyone associated
with our Organization.
Then why should we do
anything to help their city?
Rabona's laws
are not an issue...
This time around we'll
sneak you into the city
without alerting their
guards to your presence.
It will be up to you
to find the Yoma
and slay it as
quickly as possible.
Its different from the norm
but I trust you can handle it.
A covert operation.
Taking one of those pills
decreases your Yoma power.
The most obvious
change will be your eyes,
which will revert
to their natural color.
The downside is you'll lose
your ability to detect Yoma.
With your one major advantage
over the Yoma taken away
you will be forced to
infiltrate the city
as a human and search on
foot until you locate it.
If you say the boy is
your little brother,
it will add another level of
authenticity to your story,
making you less suspicious
to their guards,
who have very watchful eyes...
Good morning.
So will you two be sharing
a room or having your own?
Uhhh.
One please...
My brother and I
are traveling together...
We're going to be staying
in this lovely town for awhile.
Any vacancies?
Wow...
This is a great room, isn't it?
They call this place
the holy city...
It's only natural that their
accommodations would be fitting.
Hey are you feeling okay?
It's just the side effects
of the medicine.
Well maybe you should
try taking a nap.
I'm fine.
Time is of the
essence let's go.
Going out for the day?
Yes...
We're going to do a little
sight-seeing before lunch.
Well it is a
beautiful day for that.
What?
Oh nothing...
It's just weird to see
you change personalities
instantly like that.
Claymores are trained for this.
One second I can act like
a noble lady and the next
like a flirtatious prostitute.
A prostitute?
Would you like me
to demonstrate?
Oh, no that's okay, I'm good.
Beyond here is
the baptismal chamber.
Casual visitors are not
allowed past this point.
Thank you...
My brother and I are actually
here to baptized by the Father.
Do you have any proof?
Of course.
Alright you are
free to proceed.
Gah! Gross!
He must have been important
to be buried down here.
I've been all over this
town and yet I don't sense
the slightest presence of Yoma.
If you're here to receive
baptism, then please,
come this way.
You wouldn't happen to be
Father Vincent, would you?
I am.
Then I am honored
to be in your presence.
I baptize thee...
in the name of our Lord...
and Savior.
Tell me, what is
the name of thy God?
The name of my God is Rimuto.
I have traveled here
from the land of Sutauf.
Oh dear God,
then that means you are a...
Have discretion...
Please Father.
Meet me in the tallest
of the cathedral's belfries
one hour after
the moon has risen.
The city is under a strict
martial law at nighttime...
Will you still
be able to come?
I will be there
as you say, Father Vincent.
Antiques?
Yes.
We've been selling the
pieces our father collected
before his death in
order to stay afloat.
This is the final and
most exquisite piece
of his collection.
It's nice.
How much are you
selling it for?
It's about ten million bellars.
Ten mill...?
You'll never
get that much here.
Right...
To be honest, we had
been expecting that...
But my brother and I agreed
we would sell each piece
as close to the price our father
would have wanted as possible.
Well, good luck to both of you.
It looks as if your
brother has become ill.
I think he had too much to eat.
The food was really fantastic.
Well, I did serve him
two helpings...
Oh, right.
I meant to tell you
about the curfew.
No one is allowed to be
on the streets at night time.
Thanks...
I had heard about that today.
Very good.
Have a wonderful night.
I'm sorry for making you
eat so much food.
You're not in pain, are you?
Nah...
I remember what you said
before about not being able
to eat much in one sitting...
Besides I work
for you as a cook.
Eating food is part
of the job, or at least
that's the way I see it.
I just look at it as
research for future meals...
Clare, hold on!
Be...
careful out there.
Of course...
I'll be back soon.
By direct orders from our
leader Rimuto the Organization
from Sutafu has
sent me to your aid...
By request of a Father Vincent
in the town of Rabona.
I assume that is correct.
The first to pass
was Father Van.
Soon thereafter my priests
were being killed regularly.
Sometimes they were alone
and sometimes in groups
of up to three people.
All of this violence has
occurred within the cathedral.
To think that we as servants
of God would be needlessly
tortured and killed
is beyond reproach...
Tell me, is this
to be permitted?
Yoma do not discriminate.
Huh?
They don't care if the faith
of God lives inside you.
Whether you're a man of
the cloth or an infidel...
We're meat to those creatures.
But...
As long as your guts
are inside your body
you're fair game to them.
Please, you have to help us.
I don't care how much
it'll cost, we'll pay it.
I require no money.
Once the job is complete,
someone from our organization
will come by to
collect the money
and you will give it to them.
If I happen to fail my mission
and die in the process,
you will owe nothing and
this Yoma will continue
its slaughter.
Huh?
Its possible that the odds may
be against me this time around.
I have a request for you Father
as a faithful servant to God.
Request?
If I happen to perish
while hunting the Yoma
within your cathedral will you
promise to take in the boy
I've brought with me
and care for him?
What?
There's no need for worry.
He's a good boy.
His family was killed by
a Yoma and he has no one else
to turn to.
Wherever you could fit him
in would be sufficient.
Perhaps he could assist
the priests or even
work in the kitchen.
We will take care of the boy,
you have my word...
And even though I may
be a servant to the Lord,
it doesn't excuse my behavior.
I should be more concerned
with others than myself.
Like you...
A Claymore who isn't allowed
into our city because she's
deemed to be sub-human appears
to be void of selfishness.
Your benevolent care
for the boy is admirable
and is an inspiration
to us all.
Thank you.
I'm in your debt.
I assume you weren't aware
of the strict curfew
the city is under.
If you choose to ignore it...
The possibilities of being
mistaken for a Yoma are great.
This guy's got some moves...
He avoided your attack
with ease, Galk.
Though from the looks
of it he ain't fast enough
to dodge my knives.
Damn you!
Hey, those are mine!
A girl?
Let's go get her!
No...
She's long gone.
But I hit her with
a couple of my knives.
We should go after now
while we have the advantage
against her!
Look...
This is the knife
she threw back at us...
Notice it doesn't have
a single drop of blood on it.
No blood?
Who the hell is this woman?
What's wrong?
Did you hear that?
What the...
Where the hell did
this thing come from?
We searched this entire
cathedral inside and out!
Please...
please...
don't kill -
Oh no!
Where's Clare?!
I see you're awake.
Clare your...
eyes.
Oh...
The medicine I'm taking is only
effective for half a day...
I have to remember
to keep taking the pills
whenever they wear
off or we'll be caught.
Wait...
I'll get water.
I'm certain there was
another Yoma attack
at the cathedral last night.
Stay where you are.
We're looking for Yoma.
But we're both human!
This morning in the
cathedral we found
the remains of two
of our best sentries.
They'd both been murdered
and eaten by Yoma...
We ask for your cooperation.
Hey Galk, is it me or does this
cloak look familiar to you?
Because a suspicious
woman was running around
on the rooftops last
night in the same thing.
I hear you two arrived
in town just yesterday.
What are you accusing us of?!
Look I'm not saying the
woman we came in contact
with last night was
a Yoma or anything...
but I just doubt any
normal human being
could pull off
the stunts she did.
Unless...
she was a silver-eyed witch!
You're a lot cuter than
I would have expected.
Clare took her
medicine just in time.
See we're looking for
one of those mix-breeds.
Someone who sold their body
and soul to the Yoma...
It couldn't be all that
difficult to change
something simple like
the color of your eyes...
Let's see.
What the hell's your problem?
You've got some nerve
accusing her of being
some witch when you
have zero proof of it!
My sister has more love
and kindness in her heart
than everyone in this
entire city combined...!
And you don't know a
single thing about her
so stop trying
to act like you do!
You...!
Let go of me!
We're done...
Now let's move along.
Jerk...
And don't come back,
you hear me?!
I'm surprised you
were able to come up
with that nonsense on the spot.
Right...
The stuff about you being
my sister is made up but
I do think you're
a kind person at heart.
You don't have to be
a human to be a good person.
Is something wrong?
If that man had attacked you,
I wouldn't have stepped in
to help, no matter
how hard he beat you.
If you're looking to me
for kindness I advise you
not to bother...
I assure you in time you'll
find yourself disappointed...
and hurt.
Okay.
So both of your sentries
appeared to have been eaten?
Yes.
It sounds to me like
your cathedral is infested
with a Voracious Eater.
What is a Voracious Eater?
A Yoma's appetite increases
every day it's alive.
They also become
more cunning and strong.
Yoma that display these specific
types of characteristics
are called Voracious Eaters.
It's very probable the Voracious
Eater chooses to hide here
because Claymores are forbidden
from entering the city.
Our unique ability to detect
Yoma is useless when
we can't get near them.
Do you think we'll be alright
given the circumstances?
I need more information,
such as which people could
have entered or exited the
cathedral yesterday evening.
In addition to those
who are allowed to stay
on the grounds overnight.
Hopefully, the list is small.
After sunset no one
comes and goes...
Inside, only the priests, the
monks and a few chosen guards
are allowed to stay
within the cathedral.
Just as I was expecting,
the most probable place
for it to be is
somewhere inside here...
However I don't understand
why the creature would choose
to stay within such a confined
space like this cathedral.
Something's not adding up...
I feel like I'm
forgetting something.
Did you see that?
It's the girl from earlier.
Well now...
Looks like you're out
of excuses this time...
Your little brother
isn't here to stand up for you.
Her eyes are silver...
Hell even the expression
on her face is different.
Unfortunately I don't
have time to talk...
Your efforts are appreciated,
but they're not needed.
Should you attack me, the
consequences will be dire.
Don't you threaten us!
Take that!
She's too good with
both of those blades.
Work on getting rid of one.
I'll try.
Now!
No doubt...
She's a Claymore!
Just look at those eyes!
The cathedral!
She's on the move!
After her!
Did you hear that scream?!
What was that?
It's here...
The Yoma's Yoki
is overwhelming.
Maybe it's a side effect
of the medicine?
But I still can't pinpoint
the Yoma's location.
Its another guard.
He has been eaten recently...
I knew it.
A Voracious Eater
did this to him.
I never expected this
Yoma to be so powerful.
What is that?
A gigantic Yoma!
Stay back!
How in the hell are we
supposed to fight that thing?!
Just keep your guard up
and don't let it get away...
Look out!
What the...!
Hey witch!
What was that for?!
Just get back!
You two don't stand
a chance against it!
You'll die if you stay!
Sacrificing lives
to save lives...
Will it work against
this grave threat?
Next time, Clare's Awakening.