Here we go...
stay quick and focused.
The same to you.
No...
How could...
how could such
weak creatures...
do...
this?
I got him...
I can't believe I did it.
We won...
But we paid
a great price for it.
They've killed
the Awakened Being!
Are you sure?
Yes.
I thought that's
what you wanted.
Of course...
I was just taken by surprise...
You see, that creature was a
very powerful Awakened Being...
I didn't think they would be
able to kill him so quickly.
That's good isn't it?
They accomplished their mission.
Yes...
did they all survive?
I sense three...
if the forth made it
she's very weak...
too weak for me to read anyway.
They only lost one,
that's impressive...
Well, keep an eye
on them for a bit longer.
They killed him.
Is it really that
important to know
what they looked
like afterwards?
Think of it as an old man
concerned for his children.
Alright then.
How is she?
Not well I'm afraid...
she used so much of her Yoma
power to regenerate her arm
that she can't treat
her other injuries...
the rest of her wounds will
just have to heal on their own.
Damn it...
And what about you,
are you okay...? I mean...
you were taking
the most damage.
She was struck the most but
was quick enough to avoid
being hit in vital areas.
This allowed her to limit
her injuries to places
that heal quickly.
But how--?
How could you control
something like that
in the middle of a fight?
I've been meaning to ask you
something for a while now.
Ask us what?
I know this might
be hard to answer...
But have you ever reached the
point where you almost awakened?
I understand if you're
hesitant to tell anyone...
however I need you to be
as honest as you possibly can.
Okay, yes, I have.
When I found myself losing a
fight I accidentally unleashed
my Yoma powers, and I
guess I misjudged myself.
But awakening
is not only painful...
it can also be
quite pleasurable...
The ecstasy is so great
most can't resist.
Right...
I felt it and I can't
believe I made it back.
Okay, I've done it too.
I went too far and
misjudged my limit...
turns out I was
just like the men...
felt like I couldn't resist,
no matter how hard I tried.
But you did resist it.
Somehow I managed
to snap myself out of it...
Deneve has been
through it as well.
But in her case...
she chose to test
the limits of her powers.
Have you known Deneve
for a long time?
Oh yeah...
We were both
in the same class.
And tell me...
Have either of you had
a reputation for being
trouble makers with civilians or
those who employ your services?
Well, you've seen my temper
in action, haven't you?
I might've been in a couple...
unnecessary fights.
And Deneve?
Miss Perfect?
She's way too professional to
cause that kind of trouble...
although she's had quite a few
run ins with fellow warriors.
That's what I thought...
and I've noticed our lowest
ranking member has somewhat
of a difficult time following
the orders she's given.
Do you see the pattern?
All of us here are trouble
makers who have nearly awakened.
Right...
So what are you getting at?
It just seems a bit
too coincidental to me...
I mean, a bunch of miscreants
get the wrong information
and end up having to fight a
male Awakened Being together?
Wait, what are you saying...?
The organization is out
to get us or something?
I'm only theorizing, Helen.
What about you?
I can't see you giving in...
and I have an even
harder time thinking of you
as a trouble maker.
Very few people know this...
but I did almost awaken.
I nearly lost myself
over that edge.
Are you serious?
It happened on my third hunt
pursuing an Awakened Being...
I killed it but unfortunately
the monster turned out
to be an old friend of mine.
No...!
It can't be!
Hilda!
My god, wasn't she in
your class, Miria...?
Why didn't the organization
tell you she was the one
you were sent to kill?
Hilda...
Why...?
Why didn't you just
call out to me...?!
Damn it...
I never would have
let it come to this...
Why couldn't you just tell me
you were in trouble?
Hilda.
I wouldn't think
too much about it...
She lost her humanity
a long time ago...
all that was left
was a monster
Oh no...!
She's losing control
of her Yoki aura...!
Miria!
Well now...
looks like Phantom Miria
is awakening.
It's you!
I hear that when
she's fighting on a team
she's even better
than number one...
Oh, how I'd love
to get a crack at her.
Come on, dear...
Don't you think you're taking a
little too much time with this?
But you're here now
so you obviously managed
to control yourself.
I knew that I'd gone
beyond my limit but I
fought with all I had
to maintain control...
Mainly I was too proud
to give in to her taunting
and I couldn't let her win.
Wait who?
Never mind...
it doesn't matter...
What is important is that
was the moment I decided
I was going to have my revenge
against the organization.
What?
They turn us
into these creatures,
then dispose of us
as if we were garbage.
Well, that was the last straw.
I couldn't go along
with it any more.
But how could you
possibly expect to get
any kind of vengeance?
I'm constantly searching
for ways to exploit
the cracks in
their foundation...
while maintaining
my loyal image.
And have you found
anything on them yet?
Unfortunately I haven't...
but I figure I must be getting
close to something now.
Makes sense...
and now that you've
become a nuisance
they want to get rid of you.
As I said before
this is only a theory.
I really don't know
anything for certain.
Okay now let me
ask you something...
because we got so close...
because we were almost
awakened could it have
changed something in us?
You wouldn't be asking that
if you didn't already have
some idea about
the truth, would you?
How could you doubt it?
Look at your Yoki aura...
It's obviously changed
since before you came
close to awakening...
For one thing you're limitations
are no longer certain...
And I'm willing to bet
you're sometimes overcome
by intense hunger...
am I correct?
Isn't it obvious by now...?
We are already Awakened Beings.
What?
What are you saying...?
That we've already turned?
Something wrong?
Their auras are disturbed...
I'm not sure but I believe the
one with the strongest aura
said something
to upset the others.
And now she's arguing
with the one whose aura
is in the middle...
the one with the
weakest aura doesn't seem
to be bothered at all.
Wait.
Hmm?
No she's just as disturbed
as the others...
but she's trying her best
not to let them know it.
Oh, I see.
Something happened in
her past that caused her
to shut down emotionally.
Amazing...
I had no idea she could read so
much detail from this distance.
Okay, this has gone too far...!
I know myself,
and I'm not a monster!
I don't know about you but I
am nothing like that creature
and I certainly don't have
a desire to eat human flesh!
I have nothing in common
with that thing, you hear me?
Well, let me put it
another way...
I don't think we're
completely awakened
but somewhere in between...
I think that what we are
is half Awakened Beings.
Is...
that possible?
Most reach the breaking point
and awaken suddenly...
but somehow we got
stuck in the middle...
Or it's possible that
we're still awakening
but doing it very slowly.
But that...
can't be right.
Isn't it true that your
ability to stretch your arms
was much harder before you
nearly awakened, and doesn't it
require far less
effort from you now?
And think about
Deneve's healing powers...
Any other healer would
be pushing their limits
if they attempted
what Deneve does.
We have been going
past our limitations
and immediately
snapping back...
That was impossible before.
It makes sense.
And it matches up with
what I've been going through.
You're awake!
So...
let's assume for the moment
that we are half awakened...
What's that supposed to mean
and do we have a choice
in the matter?
Are we supposed to sit around
waiting to become some hideous
monster and not do
anything about it?
I wish I knew what to tell
you but I don't know
what will happen next...
The fact of the matter
is we have no idea
when or how we'll turn.
And that, as you can imagine,
puts us in a very
dangerous position.
Alright then, fine...
I guess there's...
nothing to lose...
Deneve!
What are you trying to do?!
Deneve! Stop it!
Shut up and listen to me...!
I don't have any choice!
If I try to regenerate
within the normal limits
I'm going to die...!
So I'm going to try and push my
Yoki aura as far as possible
and hopefully I can
heal everything now!
But this is too risky, Deneve!
What if you go
too far and awaken?
If what Miria is saying
is correct then we've gone
past our limit
a long time ago...
And I'm guessing that it
even if we push our power
to the point of awakening we
should be able to revert back!
But remember, if I do
become an Awakened Being...
you have to kill me
as quickly as you can!
No!
Deneve!
Helen!
Clare!
I promise you, my friend...
I'll make sure
you don't suffer.
Don't worry...
we won't let you down, Deneve.
I sense that one has awakened.
What's that?
And for some strange reason
she did it voluntarily...
Why would she do that?
Likely the injuries she
suffered were so great
they caused her
to misjudge her limit...
So sad.
And you're fine with that...?
I thought you said you looked
on them as an old man
to his children.
I certainly don't remember
committing myself
to raise any monsters.
How bout that...?
Looks like it worked, huh?
Thank god!
Happy now...?
That was reckless.
How are your wounds doing...
have they healed?
Yeah...
they're all closed up
and back to normal.
You know that may not
happen next time...
if you want to continue
as a human it would be best
not to take any
unnecessary chances.
I realize that...
Trust me, the last
thing I want to do is
walk that razors edge again.
Clare, what is it?
I have the strangest feeling
we're being watched.
Not likely...
I already probed this area...
And we are the only people
in this entire mountain range.
As for anyone
beyond these mountains...
they'd have a difficult time
detecting us from that distance.
Imagining things, I guess.
Hmmm...
That's interesting.
One of them can detect me
from this far away.
Something very odd
is going on there...
the one that I thought was
awakened has now stabilized.
What is it...?
Something I need to know about?
No...
looks like I made a mistake.
There wasn't an awakening...
It seems
all four of them are fine.
A mistake...?
Rather unusual
for you isn't it?
With this kind of distance
it is difficult even for me
to always get
precise information...
maybe you should
consider that the next time
your parental instincts
overcome you.
Enough...
let's go...
you would do well
to remember their auras...
Mark my words.
It may not be too long
before you'll have
to cross swords with them.
Hm.
I think I'd do just as well
to be on the look out for you,
old man.
I think it best
if we separate now...
Continue on
as if nothing happened.
We finished our assignment.
The Awakened Being was killed...
And that is all
any of us know...
got it?
Yes, I believe so...
Do everything we can
to keep the organization
from discovering our mistrust.
Exactly...
From here on, do only what
you're told and stay away
from suspicious activity.
We need to change this image
of us as troublemakers.
Ah- do we really have to?
I'm afraid that we're going to
need to proceed with caution
from now on...
if we do that we should be able
to avoid detection for a while.
You sure?
Don't worry.
Everything will be fine...
Besides, you're much
more powerful now
that you've all awakened.
If I had to
rank your abilities,
I'd say each of you is easily
within the single digits.
What do you think,
is that true?
I don't feel that strong.
Believe me
you are that strong...
it's unlikely you'll have
to fight one of our ranks
but if so know that the odds
will be in your favor...
That is unless you happen to run
into a number five or greater.
If you're faced
with one of those...
You'd be a fool to even
attempt to fight them.
So in other words you're
saying we should steer clear
of anyone ranked in the single
digits, is that about right?
There's more to it than that...
It's not just any high rank.
Where you're concerned,
there's a huge difference
in your chance of survival
fighting a five versus a six
That bad?
These are the emblems
of the top five.
Don't forget them...
From the right.
Number one, Alicia...
Number two, Beth...
Number three, Galatea...
And number four...
Why did you stop?
What's wrong with number four?
Life is meaningless to her.
So she wouldn't think twice
about killing one of her own...
she also has an unusual
obsession with hunting
Awakened Beings.
Unfortunate...
So you think the best
thing for us to do
is keep our distance from her?
That's right...
avoid her as much as you can
without drawing attention ...
She's ruthless and loves to
fight, but more than anything
she loves the sight of blood.
Her name's Ophelia...
and this is her emblem.
Finally number five...
Rafaela.
So what will you be doing
during all of this?
I'll keep on looking
for information
within the organization...
Don't worry.
I'll let you know as soon as I
can if I come across anything.
And you're gonna be
doing this by yourself?
It's too risky
to stick together.
We might draw
too much attention...
Besides we don't really know
that the organization is
trying to get rid of us at this
point- it's just speculation.
Try not to think that
everyone in the organization
is against you.
Now is not the time
to get paranoid.
But that doesn't mean you
should let your guard down.
Stay on your toes and always
keep your wits about you.
We'll meet again...
So please...
Try to survive.
You said that eventually I'm
going to have to face them...
I wonder which of them
will still be alive to face.
They're walking
a very dangerous path.
Can't you see
this is hopeless...?
Look son, I've never
seen a Claymore
go up the mountains
and come back alive.
She'll be back alright...
Clare always
keeps her promises.
She will be back!
It's Clare.
You're back!
I will make it...
I will survive.
Clare!
A blood-soaked warrior...
on a blood ridden path.
The time foretold.
Next time...
The Endless Gravestones Part 1.