So you've been unsuccessful in
contacting Number Forty-Seven,
is that correct?
How long has
this been going on?
Three months, ever since
the Awakened Being
hunt began in Gonahl.
That was the mission that
included Number Four, right...?
So I assume you've
entertained the possibility
that she is deceased.
I wouldn't dream
of it until a body's found.
The body of
Number Four, Ophelia,
was discovered recently
as an Awakened Being...
Is there any chance it was by
Number Forty-Seven's doing?
Considering the vast
difference in their abilities,
I'd say the chances are slim.
I guess that's one way
of looking at it...
However I believe
Number Forty-Seven
is much more powerful than we
imagined and when you consider
the fact that she
is using Teresa's blood,
it should come as no surprise.
We handed over the
flesh and blood of one of
the most successful
half-breeds to date...
The only reason to do that is to
build a more powerful warrior.
However...
I understood the experiment
was a disappointment.
If you look at their rankings
it was a disaster...
but there are some
unanswered questions
about Number Forty-seven
that we still haven't
taken into account.
Either way, til we
determine her status
we can't let this
issue escape our focus.
If she is alive then it
is only a matter of time
until we find her.
Ermita.
Yes.
Due to the importance and high
priority of this mission,
I would like for you
to take command...
This supercedes
all other business.
Understood.
Ermita's involvement means
it must be her turn...
Your fate is
as good as sealed...
Clare.
Excuse me, sir.
Yes?
I'm looking for my brother...
Have you seen a boy come
through here wearing a sword
on his back in
the last few days?
No.
I'm sorry...
Yeah...
We haven't seen him.
Is that right?
Look uh...
you may want to check out
the city of Hamel...
It's a big market town
just up the road.
You'll probably have
a much better chance
of finding someone there.
Thank you.
I will try there.
No problem.
Good luck.
I hope you find him, sir.
What is wrong with you?
That was so rude!
You just called
that woman sir.
No way.
That wasn't a woman!
What woman do you
know of who carries
a big sword around with her.
He's got to be a man.
I need to deepen my voice more.
That woman didn't
buy me for a second.
Elongate my vocal chords...
Pardon me...
I'm looking for
my little brother.
So you think your brother may
have passed through here, eh?
We got separated
a few weeks ago.
Well I hope everything
works out for you...
This city's bigger
than you think...
Give it time and you'll
find someone who can help.
Thanks.
Raki.
Come in.
Would you like some dinner?
Sure.
You really must care
an awful lot about him.
Oh, I'm talking about
your brother...
You know, nowadays, if a
family member goes missing,
people are content
to assume the worst...
Yet here you are, braving
the country on your own...
It's just not what
you expect anymore.
Yes, I find it
a little strange myself.
It's nothing...
Well...
make yourself at home.
Oh, I almost forgot.
There's a bit of
a situation in town.
A few days ago a group of
Claymore's came into town
and they've been
here ever since.
Claymores?
The rumor going around is
there's a gigantic Yoma
somewhere up in the
Zakol Mountains,
but that's all I've heard...
I think they've sent in
four Claymores so far.
Four of them...?
An Awakened Being.
Anyway, hope I
didn't scare you.
I just thought
you'd want to know.
Well thank you.
I never expected
to run into them here.
The pills that suppress
my Yoki aura are both
helping and hurting.
I can't be detected by other
Warriors, but I can also
unknowingly end up in towns
occupied by my comrades.
I can't allow the
Organization to find me now,
not before I'm finished.
There they are...
If they're hunting
for an Awakened Being,
then at least one of them should
be ranked in the single digits.
But which one?
Jean...
What's the matter?
Nothing...
don't worry...
Just my imagination.
That's her...
She's the one.
You're up early...
Good morning.
And good morning to you...
I'm heading to
the morning market...
I'm hoping someone
there has seen my brother.
Well good luck to you.
Oh, and about the Claymores
I mentioned yesterday...
It seems they left
sometime last night.
If you ask me, it's a relief
they're gone, though...
Sure they may be fighting
on the side of humans,
but it doesn't change
the fact they're half Yoma...
If it is an Awakened Being
hunt, no matter how skilled
the warriors are, it will take
at least a day to kill it.
Not having to deal with them
will save me a lot of trouble.
A boy carrying a sword?
No. I'm afraid I haven't.
Thank you.
No one knows anything...
Raki, where the hell are you?
Brother, look, here it is!
I told you!
It's the statue
of Teresa and Clare...
Isn't it pretty?
The statue of Teresa and Clare?
Clare was one of
the twin goddesses.
She was beautiful,
virtuous, and good...
Your parents probably
wanted you to grow up
with the goddess' traits.
See, that one on
the end is Clare,
and the other one's Teresa.
Stop acting like you
know everything.
I'm the one who told you that.
No you didn't!
I did so!
And then the other day you told
that stranger all about it
like you sculpted it yourself.
That isn't true
and you know it.
He kept on asking me
which one is Clare.
What was I supposed to do,
ignore him?
Show off.
I am not!
Oh shut up.
Excuse me, Miss.
This stranger you spoke to...
Can you tell me
anything more about him?
Huh...?
It was just some guy.
I dunno.
He sure wasn't
from around here.
What did he look like...?
Did he wear a sword
on his back?
Yeah...
I think I remember him
carrying something on his back.
Did he happen
to tell you his name?
No...
But he was all beat up
and injured...
He was creepy looking.
You still talked to him
for like twenty minutes!
Yeah, I know...!
I already explained
that didn't I;
he kept asking me
about this statue...!
When I told him about Clare,
he got a big smile on his face
and actually started
acting kinda normal.
And from that point on,
I wasn't scared of him.
Okay.
Did you see where he went?
Uh uh.
Well, this all happened
about ten days ago,
and we haven't seen
him around since then,
so I'd say he's
probably left town by now.
I see...
Thank you.
So, who is this guy anyway?
Is he a friend of yours
or something?
He is...
more than that.
Look, I know I can't really be
of any use to you...
But that doesn't
change the fact
that I want to be with you...
I don't care when
I die just so long
as we're together until than.
Please, I only wanna
be where you are.
What is he to me...?
Damn it...
I refuse to die...
If I can survive
a while longer...
I'll see Clare again.
Who the hell is that?
Oh my God!
What should we do?
Someone...
Please help.
Please I'm begging you...
My friends are...
Hang in there...
Hey!
Please...
you...
must contact the
Organization for me...
It was too strong and...
Can you tell me
what happened...?
Did an Awakened Being do this?
Are you one of...
are you one of us?
Promise me...
You'll try to save my friends!
They're...
still alive...
They're alive.
There's...
something different
about this one...
The Yoma are plotting something.
Please...
just save them.
Hold on!
Could someone please
take care of her body?
She's gone now,
so you have nothing to fear.
Give her a human burial.
Uh...
Excuse me, Mister.
I hope you don't intend
to go into those mountains
by yourself.
It's suicide!
Raki.
I will find you again someday...
Now...
Time to return to my mission...
killing Yoma.
Alright, Dear...
Almost there...
Let's just try one more.
Number six!
This is unexpected...
I thought for sure she
would have awakened by now.
Why are you so stubborn...?
If you don't awaken soon,
we'll just have to throw
your body with
your friend's over there...
Is that what you want?
Go to hell!
Fight it...!
You can't let them win, Katea!
Oh, this one is
coming along nicely...
Pretty soon the pain
will be all gone.
Don't give in to it!
You don't want to
become a monster, do you?!
You better watch out who
you're calling monsters
you stupid bitch!
Open that mouth again and I'm
gonna make you hurt even worse.
Hey, now don't get ahead
of yourself, you silly...
Don't you add
another til I say so.
She called us bad names.
Ooh yay!
Katea, no!
Okay ready or not, Dauf.
My god...
What's going on?
So, Dauf what do you think?
This one no good...
is not strong enough.
Disappointing...
But I guess that's to be
expected from a Claymore
that's ranked
in the thirties...
Go ahead and dispose of her.
Don't do it!!!
How could you.
Well it looks like
we'll need to find someone
in the single digits
to have any success.
You better hurry up
and awaken, Jean.
At number nine you might be
the best hope we have.
Fuck you!
Hey you.
Hold on a minute.
Are you alone?
If you're thinking about
going up into the mountains
by yourself you might
want to think again...
There's a nasty horde of Yoma
swarming all over the place.
If you want to get
to the other side,
your best bet is to go around.
You're an interesting group.
Normally you prefer to work
alone, not like a pack of dogs.
That dirty son-of-a-bitch
is a Claymore!
It worked!
If we attack the feet
and chest at the same time,
you Claymores always jump
you're all so predictable!
You're extremely knowledgeable
of how we like to operate...
And your attacks are
very well coordinated,
which is not normal...
How did you get this way?
You'll find out more than
you bargained for soon enough.
Somebody's outside.
Oh I think you're right...
But it's too soon for
the one who escaped
to have found help...
I...
am sensing a faint Yoki aura.
Whoever it is she's
a very low rank...
No point in expecting much out
of her, even if she does awaken.
I'll just give her to you...
You can do what
you want with her.
Really?
You mean it?
Born human, die human...
My truth...
Next time,
The Witch's Maw Part Two.