There's something strange
about this Yoki aura.
I sense so many distorted
Yoki inside this castle.
It's pulsating...
So these are
the auras I'm feeling.
Damn...!
I'm surrounded by Yoma...
And to think I didn't even
notice them approaching!
How could I fall for this?
No running...
That's bad.
What is this?
I've never felt
a Yoki aura of this size!
Oh no...
You're not a woman...!
I didn't expect you
to be a man.
More fun to torture woman.
Men die too easy.
Which one are you?
You don't have to tell...
I'll just rip
your clothes off and see...
Uh oh...!
The tunnel is too
little Dauf is stuck!
I can't move!
What do you think
you're doing,...?
That, kinda hurt.
Hey! That really stings!
What did I ever do to you?
Stop it!
Too bad...
You're weak...
my turn.
Damn!
Lost your sword fast.
You're not much of a fighter
It's a trap...
Gotcha.
Same to you.
She's actually not bad.
Maybe it would have been
better to have Dauf bring her
to me instead of letting
him toy with the poor thing.
You little bitch...
What the hell are you after?
Well...
I'll be happy to tell you
when you awaken and join us.
Are you insane...?
I would...
rather die than
join you monsters!
What in the hell
are you laughing about?
Oh it's...
just that most people would
consider you a monster, too.
To normal people, there isn't
much difference between
a Claymore and
an Awakened Being...
Really, it's only
a matter of what side
we let ourselves be aware of.
See, in the eyes of the world,
we are both monsters.
We're not that
different after all.
Maybe you're right...
Maybe I am a monster...
But you're wrong to think
I'm anything like you.
I came into this world
as a human...
And that's how
I plan to die...
With my human side
in control...
Do what you like but
I'll never awaken for you.
I wouldn't be so sure...
You intrigue me...
So much so that I've decided
I'm going to make you
my very own little project.
You know, I'm really
starting to get, angry.
Impossible...!
His skin is so tough that the
Quick Sword barely affects him.
One.
Here comes two!
My leg...
The bone!
Pretty good, huh?
If I cut your leg off,
you'll only reattach it.
But if I shatter the bone,
it's harder to heal.
Now let's get those clothes off
and see what
we're dealing with...
Are you a little boy...?
Or a pretty girl?
This is a dilemma.
I'm glad I found you
so easily...
but I'm not sure
what I should do next.
You must admit...
This situation isn't one that
you encounter every day,
now is it?
I've come this far...
I can't just go back without
anything to show for it.
Who the hell are you...?
And why haven't
you drawn your sword,
do you have some
kind of death wish?
That emblem!
She's Number Three...
Galatea!
What is she doing...?
Why is she here?!
Wait.
It seems that we've been joined
by someone truly powerful.
Don't worry little Claymore,
I'll get to you-- I just have to
finish up with this one first.
Hey!
Wow...
You're much lighter
than you look...
You really should eat more.
My business here
is with this one...
So if you'll excuse me.
Don't underestimate him!
He's--
Now hold on...!
What was that little trick
you just pulled on me?
Don't you ignore me!
Hey, what the hell...?!
Why can't I hit her?
All of his attacks are
veering away from us...
How is that possible?
Who'd have thought...?
It appears that our little
playmate has a brain
in his head after all.
You bitch!
Where you goin'?
I'm not done with
my new friend!
I'm gonna kill you...
But, before I do,
I'm gonna strip you naked,
yank out your limbs, then
pull your steaming guts out
while you're still twitching.
Stay right here...
Do your best to mend that leg.
Oh, ok.
You're lucky...
If I hadn't come along
at the right moment,
you could have easily fallen
prey to that evil creature.
You have to be careful...!
His skin is too tough.
Our swords can't penetrate it.
I wasn't referring
to your giant friend.
I meant the evil creature
who's down below us now...
You have no idea what
trouble you're in, do you?
Her Yoki aura is immense,
but she's tremendously
skilled at hiding it...
If you're able to
match her wavelength,
you should be able
to locate her as well.
I wasn't able to hit you
with all my other attacks,
but this time I won't miss!
I thought you wanted to strip
me down, tear off my limbs,
and pull out my guts
while I watched?
That's right...
But I think
I'll smash you first.
Galatea!
That's what you get for
that cocky little attitude
of yours...
Loser!
You're actually dumber
than you look.
I never would have thought
such a feat was possible.
So it's true.
His outer skin is too
thick to penetrate
with ordinary attacks...
Huh.
Why you-!
It's just as I thought.
Your skin is tough, but there
seem to be some cracks
in your armor.
You bitch!
That hurt!
Mind if I borrow your idea...?
Ripping your arms off
sounds like fun.
So this is what
Number Three is capable of...
It's almost as
if she can control
her opponent's every move!
Damn Bitch...!
You bitch...!
Stupid bitch!
Oh, please.
Don't cry...
It's just as embarrassing
for me as it is for you.
He is an idiot isn't he?
I really must
apologize for that.
Well, look who finally
decided to come out of hiding.
What are you
doing up here, Dauf?
I gave you one simple
task and you can't even
accomplish that...
This is why I'm embarrassed
to tell people you're my man.
I've really been
trying to hit her,
but she's got some
kind of force field...
Promise!
Don't be stupid, Daufy.
She does not have
a magical force field.
But it's true...!
That's why I haven't
been able to-
Listen...
I'll tell you how to make
sure you land your attacks,
but you're not allowed to
miss this time, understand?
Okay.
I want you to hit her
with everything you've got.
Don't hold back.
But I have been attacking her
with everything I've got,
and I haven't been
holding back...
Nothing hits her, I swear!
Quit your whining
and just do it...
Keep in mind if
you miss one more time,
I'm breaking up with you.
No...
Please don't!
Damn you...
All of this is your fault...!
I'll kill you for this!
Huh...?
It didn't veer off
course that time.
Be careful!
That's it.
Good, Dauf.
You're closer...
If you had started with
that kind of intensity,
she would have been
dead a long time ago.
What happened...?
What did you just do?
Me...? I did nothing at all...
Your friend there
has the rare ability
to control her
opponent's aura.
That's not quite true.
At best she's able
to tweak it a bit.
She can't actually
stop them from attacking.
So when Dauf unleashes
all of his rage and power
into his strikes, there
isn't anything she can do
to prevent them from landing.
Look out!
Dodge it!
Hey, I finally got her...!
So what do you want me
to aim for this time?
It looks like
we have a winner.
Oh! Goodness...
Healing yourself so
quickly has caused you
to surpass your limit.
What an unexpected bonus!
I think I'll go
straight for your head!
What the-?
Hey...
You okay?
Come on...
Please hurry...
Revert back.
Damn it.
Stop, Dauf!
Have to...
suppress it...!
Concentrate!
Almost there.
I...
can't do it...
I can't!
What do you know?
You were able to
reverse the process.
Was that...
Did you just do that?
All I did was pull you
back over to our side.
I believe I'm starting to
see why the Organization
wanted you found so badly...
You are very...
unique.
Hey, what was that
all about...?
I was looking forward
to seeing her awaken!
A high ranking warrior...
who can control Yoki aura...
and a mystery fighter...
who can surpass her limit...
I'm impressed.
I think I'll
let you join me...
I'm sure I can find
a use for both of you.
She's so...
...powerful, and her Yoki aura
is dark and menacing.
What is she...?
How can a small child
control a Yoki that size?
In the history of the
Organization there have been
only three like her.
Only three times that a
Number One has awakened
and created such
an incredible power.
One during the era of men...
And two since
they began using women.
The Powerful Three,
were unbelievably strong...
And to avoid conflict
they separated.
One to the North, one to the
South, and one to the West...
And that is where
they have stayed.
Since then, they have remained
out of the public eye...
And they've come to be
known by a new name...
The Creatures of the Abyss.
Creatures of the Abyss?
Am I right?
Or did I leave
something out...
Riful of the West!
Riful...
That's her name?!
She was the first female Number
One warrior in the Organization.
And she reached that status
at a younger age than anyone
thought possible before
succumbing to her Yoma side.
You're very young
to know about all that...
But I'm afraid
it's not quite accurate.
The three of us didn't
go separate ways
to "avoid conflict,"
as you put it...
It was by complete coincidence
that the territories
we chose didn't overlap.
So why have you
suddenly reemerged...?
And you're not
the only one...!
Activity from the other two
has been reported, as well.
Each of you has begun to draw
all of the Awakened Beings
in your respective vicinities
into your lair...
What I can't
understand though is why?
What is it you're
trying to achieve.
You see, the thing is...
The man to the north
is picking fights.
He's been getting really
carried away lately...
If you ask me, this is all
because of that woman
he got his hands on.
What woman?
Some Awakened Being
he discovered
going on a rampage in
the northern territory...
A woman with one horn.
Priscilla!
And it's not like I had
anything better to do,
so I decided to take him on.
Uh-huh.
So that's why I've been
collecting subordinates
to use in our war.
The man in the north...
Where can I find him?
Huh...?
What's that...?
You're speaking so softly
I can barely hear you.
Tell me how to find the Creature
of the Abyss in the north...
I'm going to hunt that
woman down and destroy her.
Well, then...
I suppose that means
you know this girl.
Shut the hell up
and answer me...
I want to know his name.
Tell me exactly
where to find the man
in the northern territory.
That's not a very
polite way to talk...
Let me think.
How about we do this?
If you can land
even one blow on me,
I'll tell you what
you want to know.
Too bad...
and you were so close.
Look up.
Damn you!
Come on, Dauf.
This isn't the best time
to stop and whine, you know.
Hey...
What do you think
you're doing, huh?
I think I'm beginning
to understand.
It seems intentionally
surpassing your limit,
as opposed to doing
so accidentally,
enhances your power and speed.
An interesting side effect,
but it hasn't helped you.
It's over...
Why don't you turn around
and answer my question?
I would...
But you haven't cut me...
We did have a bargain,
didn't we?
If you really
wanna die that badly.
I'll be happy
to grant your request!
I swear, you need more
looking after than a child.
Aw...
And right when you
were getting so close...
Too bad.
What...
What just happened
You came close-
you almost awakened...
You were allowing her all
cheap taunts to get to you...
That's exactly what they want.
We have to destroy
this monster.
If the Creature of the Abyss
doesn't intend to get involved,
then we may still have
a chance of escaping alive...
But in order to do that,
you and I are going to need
the assistance of
the other warrior here.
The other warrior?
Someone with the
ability to drive a sword
into this beast's armor.
And she can.
She's down on
the lower level now...
Jean, the Number Nine
ranked warrior.
The Number Nine...?
Here?
She's here, but she's in an
extremely unstable state...
I believe at any moment,
she could awaken.
There is no doubt in my
mind that Riful has been
having her severely tortured,
both physically
and psychologically...
And given what I know
about Jean, she would choose
to die rather than awaken
and join these creatures...
If she's still alive,
it's because the choice
no longer belongs to her.
Get to the lower level
and find Jean...
I can handle things here.
But if she's gone too far-
if she's beyond your help.
Then it's up to you
to take Jean's life.
Quickly...!
We don't have much time!
Get back here!
I'll get you!
This hurts way worse
than before!
Stop it!
Where is she?
That hurt!
This goes against
my sense of aesthetics,
so I don't do it
all that often.
When I unleash my Yoma power...
my strength increases at a
rate that is unmatched by any
of the other
forty-seven warriors.
I apologize, but I believe
you'll just have to put up
with my new face
until we can settle this.
Oh please...
What do you take me for...?
You think I'm scared of you?
You're gonna die!
I'm gonna kill you!
Smart girl...
Buy yourself some time.
I'm...
too late...
She's gone
Kill me!
Approaching the limit-
and surpassing it.
A foe from far beyond.
Next time...
The Witch's Maw...
Part Three.