I understand...
I will bring her down...
Traitors must be
stopped at all costs!
My apologies, Teresa...
If I had my choice,
I alone would destroy you...
But you have brought this on...
Yourself!
Here we go.
Teresa!
Damn!
Ilena!
Ilena...!
Are you all right...?!
Ilena?!
Don't mind me...
Go!
But I...
I told you...
We were sent here
to do a job...
so do it!
Forget about me...
Just do everything in your
power to take Teresa's head!
Right!
Damn it...
With the four of us...
I thought that maybe
we could somehow...
close in on Teresa, but...
Is that it...?
Was that my error...?
Have I been underestimating
Teresa the whole time?
Extraordinary...
She hasn't even begun
to access her Yoki powers...
What now?
Clare...
Go back to the inn and
gather up our belongings...
We can't allow ourselves to be a
further burden on this town...
We're leaving.
Now then...
No...!
She can sense it...!
Priscilla's true potential...
She sees someone who
could surpass even her!
And she intends to make sure
that it never happens,
right here and now.
Teresa of the Faint Smile
is to be feared...
No matter how many times
she has to fight us,
we pose no threat to her...
So she hurt us just enough
to immobilize us...
But Priscilla, who should
still be on her feet...
is frozen with
terror in the face
of Teresa's
overwhelming strength!
I'm...
I'm scared...!
I'm so scared...
I don't want to die...
I don't want to die!
Please, somebody...
Come save me...!
Daddy...?
Daddy, please...!
Save me!
I swear I must be going soft...
That face will just
keep haunting my conscience.
Teresa!
Got it all...!
Even this 'thing' that
you wear around your waist.
You actually bothered
to bring that too...?
Must've been heavy, huh?
Huh-uh.
You can come attack me
all you want...
I'll defeat you
at each encounter...
Farewell...
Sorry for the mess.
Inconceivable...!
Teresa showing mercy
to an enemy...?
The old Teresa would not have
hesitated to behead her!
However...
at least now,
we still have hope.
Stop crying...!
The fight isn't over yet...!
Now get up!
Unfor--...
Unforgi--...
Unforgivable!
Unforgivable...
Unforgivable.
Unforgivable!
Priscilla...
Teresa's a murderer...!
She's a villain...!
She violated the
Organization's rules!
Stop this...!
It's beyond your control, you
cannot defeat Teresa like this!
Don't go!
Damn brat...!
There's no way
she'll be able to stop her!
Careless...!
I was so mesmerized
by her latent abilities...
that I forgot she
is still just a child!
You all right...?
Noel?
Sophia?
--Yeah.
--Yes!
Good...
Let's move...
She has no idea
what her limits are yet!
Don't do it.
With the state you're in now,
we can fight again and again,
and you will never win.
Priscilla, let it go...
If you unleash too much power
without proper training
you will not turn back.
When we mixed-breeds release ten
percent of our Yoki powers,
the color of our eyes change...
At thirty, it shows
on our faces...
At fifty, our physiques change.
Once you pass eighty
percent, you have no hope
of ever changing
back to normal...
As it stands right now...
You should already
be well over seventy.
Shut up!
You are a murderer...!
A filthy murderer!
The limits to which you
can use your power...
are something you have to learn
gradually from fight to fight.
You however...
lack that level
of experience entirely.
Shut your mouth!
Her Yoki aura is massive...
I can't even read
the energy flow.
Watch out!
You're bleeding!
How dare you
kill my father...?!
how dare you...
Unforgivable...
just die...
you, hear me?! I'll
kill you. I'll kill you!
Her self-awareness
is fading quickly...
Fine then...
I've run out of options...
Just this once...
I'll put a bit
of effort into it.
Damn...
unbelievable...
The Yoki auras
I'm sensing are insane!
I agree.
It's basically just
two monsters over there...
What could we
possibly do against them?
Both auras are greater than
anything I have ever seen...
But...
What?
It's clear one of them
far exceeds the other...
But which one?
What--...?
What the--...?
Is...
Is that Priscilla?!
Ilena...
Is she...?
Not yet...
She hasn't
exceeded her limit...
If we stop her now, she should
be able revert to human form.
If we're able to stop her...
How does one even
begin to battle against
such a fantastic,
unbridled power like that?
Amazing...!
Teresa's able to fend off
her furious rage...
Better yet, she's winning!
And using only enough Yoki
power to change her eye color!
Could this be the true
strength of Teresa's power?
Teresa...
While you can
still heed my words...
You're reaching your limit...
Suppress your Yoma side
and revert to human form.
Now focus, you've got to...
You are fast approaching
the point of no return.
My daddy...
Give me back my daddy.
Daddy was always
so kind to me...
I loved him so much...
And he ate them.
He made me watch it...
He ate their innards...
right in front of me!
No!
That's when I had
to kill my daddy...
While he was
eating my big sister...
I chopped off his head!
He made me do it!
She's past her limit...
That's it.
I can't go back...
Help me please...
You have to...
I don't...
I don't want
to live like this!
Too late...
The Yoma side is
all that's left of her.
Please...
I'm sorry...
It is no longer within
my power to help you.
About the best
I can give you...
is a swift beheading before
you are completely taken over
by your Yoma side.
Then please...
Take my head...
Kill me...
While my heart...
is still human...
So be it...
I will be sure
you do not suffer.
Te-re...
sa...?
What in the hell is that thing?
That "thing"...
transcends Yoma...
It's a species completely
separate from the human race.
Awakened Being!
Is that it...?
All that fuss--there was no
reason for me to hold back.
And I never realized...
it would feel this good.
She's a monster...
Innards...
Time to eat...
I want to tear open
the stomach...
bury my face in the warmth
of wet, bloody entrails...
Savor every piece of viscera...
Down to the last
tiny bits of flesh.
No...
Poor Ilena...
What's the matter...?
It seems your arm
has gone missing.
Oh look...
Here it is...
I suppose you
can have it back...
But do try to hold on to your
belongings in the future.
Noel!
Sophia!
I see...
So all of you here
intend to kill me.
I think you will...
fail.
After all of that activity...
I've worked up
quite an appetite...
Well, then...
Shall we move on?
Time passed...
wounds healed...
The girl took up the sword.
Next time, "Those Who
Rend Asunder Part I."