Oh no.
Not again.
It's a slaughter!
Horrible...
another victim...
It's obvious, isn't it...?
There's a Yoma
hiding in our village!
So what's the plan then...?
Once a Yoma has
disguised itself as human
there's no way
to tell them apart!
Maybe we should
start rounding up people
that look suspicious to us.
Who do you have in mind?
Well...
Don't take this the wrong way...
I watched my wife get eaten
by one of those things
so you better watch your mouth!
I didn't mean it like that!
The kid's got a point...
Look at Kenneth who
was killed this morning.
You two lived
next door to each other.
Damn you!
Enough with the accusations!
We need to stick together here.
I don't wanna die...!
What if a Yoma eats my insides
while I'm still alive?!!
Quiet!
I received a reply
this morning...
They're willing to
send someone to our village.
Well, who's coming then?
A Claymore.
A Claymore?
Is this a joke?!
We don't need
those bastard's help!
We have no other choice.
If I sit on my hands any
longer the entire village
could be wiped out.
But they're Yoma themselves!
I know.
But remember...
They're the only ones who
can spot a Yoma in human form...
They're our only hope.
Zaki!
Hey Raki.
How did the meeting go?
All right...
The Chief has hired
a Claymore to visit us.
A Claymore?
Yeah...
Everyone's a little
shaken up about it...
But Claymores are
the only ones that
are capable of defeating Yoma.
Wait...
So they're like super-human?
Not exactly...
They're far from what
you would consider human.
Claymores are
half human, half Yoma.
Half human, half Yoma?
Wait, Raki...! Hold on!
Hey...
It's a woman?
What, you didn't
know about that...?
You have to be a woman
to be a Claymore.
Wow.
Look...!
Her eyes are silver.
Yeah.
Why do you think they're
called silver-eyed witches...?
Apparently their eyes turn gold
whenever they spot a Yoma.
Creepy.
Let's just hope she
doesn't go after one of us.
Well she does have
some Yoma in her.
I don't understand
why the Chief had to send
for someone like that.
He had to...
It just goes to show
that it takes a monster
to kill a monster.
You idiot!
Watch your mouth!
What if her Yoma side got the
best of her and turned her mad?
She would have
killed you and me!
I'm sorry!
Here's the payment
for your services.
Please check it's all there.
No.
Huh?
Once the job is complete...
a representative will
come by to collect it...
I can't accept payment myself.
Okay...
Whatever you say.
It means if I fail you
and die in the process,
you are not obligated
to pay any money.
Oh...
I understand...
So what do you think...?
Will you be able to find
the Yoma today, maybe tomorrow?
Of course, that will
depend on the Yoma...
If it's taking
extra care to hide its Yoki,
then it could prove difficult.
Eventually...
Either its corpse
or my own will turn up
in the streets
of your village...
That's your only certainty.
Honey!
That...
That's my first Claymore...
I was expecting her to be more
human-like, but she looked...
like a...
Like a monster!
What'd I do...?
I was only
walking behind you...
Wait up a sec...!
You're a Claymore, right?
No.
What?
Claymore is the name
we were given...
given by you people...
our organization
actually has no name.
Well don't look at me...
but I am surprised though...
I mean you look no different
than a normal girl...
I guess I just expected that you
would be a lot scarier looking.
You're very strange.
Do you not fear me, boy?
Well, why should I...?
You're no different
than any one of us.
Uh... Hey, hold on!
Wait for me!
Where are you going?
Y'know, you're about
to exit the village.
So this is the border?
That's right...
The only thing you'll find
past this point is the old mine.
What are you doing?
Sleeping...
I have been walking for
seventy hours straight.
Why don't you tell me why
you've taken an interest in me?
Cause you're a Claymore.
I told you...
That's just a name you
people have given us.
Oh, right, I'm sorry...
Anyway, you're gonna kill
that Yoma for us, aren't ya?
Yeah...
My parents were
the first victims...
the first ones
killed by the Yoma.
When I woke...
only my big brother Zaki
and I were still alive.
I was...
I was right there, but there was
nothing I could do to save them!
But that's why you're here!
To avenge the death
of my parents in my place!
Don't misunderstand.
I came here because
I was assigned to do so.
I have no intention
of exacting revenge for you.
I know that.
You're here to do a job.
I forgot to get dinner ready.
We're staying at
my uncle's house so
I like to help out
since he took me in...
And...
you may be surprised but I'm
pretty good at cooking now...
I could cook you
some food later.
Well, see ya...!
Wait...
What is your name?
There's no point
in telling you.
It's a name...
that will soon be forgotten.
Sorry Uncle...!
I'll get dinner on
the stove right away.
--You're home, Raki.
--Did you see this...?
Uncle's dead!
I should know
since I killed him.
He was quite delicious.
Zaki...
no!
Come on...
What? You never noticed?
I took over your brother's brain
and stole his body as my own.
Ever since then,
I've been able to replicate
his speech patterns,
and have had control
over his thoughts
and memories.
This is why you humans
aren't capable of spotting us.
I had planned to stay much
longer in your little village...
but you just had to send out for
that little silver-eyed witch.
So instead I'll
make you my last meal...
You have no idea how hard
it's been for me to hold back
from devouring that
frail body of yours!
Aw, I'm crying...
There are still remnants
of your brother's memory
fighting for life.
Isn't brotherly love touching?
What's wrong little brother...
is dinner ready?
What a fool...
We've been feeding on
you humans for centuries.
Even though you'd
like to think otherwise,
we are the top
of the food chain.
You're my prey,
so there's no use in resisting.
You god damned witch!
I could smell your
Yoma scent on the boy.
You unwittingly lead me
right to your own death.
Die, you bitch!
Please...
Have mercy on me!
Don't...
Thank God we called in the
silver-eyed witch when we did.
She finished
the job within hours.
Word on the street is she left
the village right after that.
Yes, she probably has
her next job already lined up...
Now, about our other
little problem...
Forgive us, Raki!
It's nothing personal!
It can't be helped.
For all we know he's
infected with Yoma too,
just like his brother.
We can't take that chance.
What...? How did I get here?
Hello...
you're awake...
You were in pretty
bad shape when you got here.
You're lucky to be alive son.
Where exactly am I?
You're in a
little town called Egon.
Did you have any idea
that you've been asleep
for the last twenty-four hours?
How did you end up wandering
around the wastelands like that?
For all we know he's
infected with Yoma too,
just like his brother.
Well okay...
I'd have to imagine
you're starving by now...
Eat up...
go ahead.
But...
I have no money
to pay for this.
Don't worry about that.
Everything's been
paid for in advance.
By who?
One of them
silver-eyed witches.
Huh?
A Claymore brought you here,
which is strange because
they're not known for
their acts of kindness,
if you know what I mean.
Can you tell me where she is?
I think she had
a job to get to.
She left in a hurry.
Do you not fear me boy?
It's a name...
that will soon be forgotten.
Have mercy!
--She's gone.
--Hey kid.
A Claymore was looking around
for you a bit earlier.
Where'd she go?
She wandered into the forest
on the edge of town.
Thank you!
There she is!
You alone?
I am.
It's not her.
The innkeeper told me you were
the one that saved my life.
There's no need to thank me.
But I'm just some stranger.
Why would you pay
for my room and food?
Why are you so suspicious
of my kind gesture
toward your well being?
We Claymore's are
a benevolent organization...
Besides...
I've taken a liking to you.
No...!
I don't believe you're
a Claymore for a second!
I know that your kind
never refers to themselves
as Claymores!
Well...
Thank you.
I'll be sure to remember
that for the next time!
What a perceptive
little brat you are...
Thank you...
you've made my job
a lot easier.
Now show yourself, Claymore!
I know you're out there!
You've been tracking me...
Come out so we can
end this game...
Stop...
Stay where you are...
I know how fast
you are, Claymore.
If you so much as
flinch at me I'll slice
the boy's throat
from ear to ear!
Now toss aside your sword
And no sudden movements.
Do you really think a
hostage will have any effect
on me killing you?
No...
I knew it wouldn't...
Until yesterday.
That's when I saw
you walk into town
carrying this boy
as if he were your own.
Seems you do
have a weakness...
How pathetic...
You 'care' for this meat...
Being half Yoma doesn't
erase your past as a human.
And those precious
memories don't disappear
when you become a Claymore.
Isn't that right, witch?
I'd be willing to bet
that you had a little brother
that looked just like
this boy, didn't you...?
I'm right, aren't I.
I can see it all over
your disgusting face.
Go ahead.
Make a move.
That is if you can actually
find the courage to
kill me and this human.
Are you happy now?
I'll be sure
to end this quickly...
It's time to die!
I've never eaten Claymore
before I look forward to it
I think I'll feast
on you and the boy!
Hey, are you alright...?
Do you need help?
I'm sorry...
It's my fault.
Listen up.
I didn't throw away
my sword just to save you...
Back there...
If I had tried to save you
and kill her, you would have
wound up dead and she would
have easily gotten away.
My only option was to prevent
her escape and put her
in a position where
a swift kill was attainable.
But that doesn't change the
fact that you saved my life.
For the second time
because you killed
the Yoma that ate my family.
When my mom and dad were
killed I was so afraid...
But I tried...
I tried to act tough
the whole time.
Thank you...
I'm so grateful...
I really am.
I'll never forget you
for as long as I live...
I just wanted you
to know that.
Were you banned
from your village?
Of course.
I told them I wasn't a Yoma
but they wouldn't listen.
They just got rid of me.
Did you say you
were a good cook?
Good...
If you agree to be my cook,
you can come along...
Why don't you join me until
we can find a new village
for you to settle in.
Where are you going...?!
I still don't know your name.
Let's tell
each other our names!
My name is Raki.
What's yours?
It's Clare.
I like that name.
The final wish...
The final prayer...
As a testament to
the friendship we shared.
Next time, The Black Card.