I found a few horses for us.
Here.
If you come with us you would
be doing us a huge favor,
you really would...
Oh and by the way
her name is Priscilla...
I've never seen her be so
attached to a stranger before.
The scent of the south
is heavy on you.
It must remind her
of her family.
Family?
Yes...
They were murdered
and eaten by a Yoma.
Just like what
happened to me.
Hello there.
Are you having some sort
of trouble with your horses?
No...
We're okay.
Well good luck to ya...
Hey if you folks are
heading north anytime soon...
I'd steer clear of
a town called Pieta...
From what we've been hearing...
There are a few dozen Claymores
there, and that means trouble.
Where there are Claymore's
there are Yoma hunting us...
I'd avoid it if I were you.
So long.
There are Claymores in Pieta?
I'm really sorry but
I can't go with you after all.
I need to get to Pieta...
Sorry.
Wait a second...
I don't understand why you're in
such a rush all of a sudden...
We're all heading
towards Pieta anyway.
Please stay with us
a little while longer,
for Priscilla's sake.
But...
It'll take up to
a week to get to Pieta...
At this point it wouldn't
make much sense to separate.
I can't believe she
fell asleep on your lap...
She hasn't done that
with me in ages.
I...
noticed your reaction
earlier when I mentioned
the Claymores...
I take it the person you're
searching for is a Claymore?
Yes.
What business could you have
with one of them...?
I don't mean
to sound like a father...
but nothing good ever comes
out of associating yourself
with one of them.
My situation is different...
To me Clare...
is more of a...
So her name is Clare.
Clare.
If it weren't for Clare...
I wouldn't be alive today...
She's always protected me.
That's why I must find her.
She's in danger and now
it's up to me to protect her.
I see...
That's very human
of you, standing brave
in the face of tragedy.
That's easy for you to say...
But are you strong enough
to actually pull it off?
You're...
amazing.
The weak tend to cling to
words as their only defense,
while those of us with
strength end up dying
trying to protect them.
It happens all the time.
Listen kid...
Being helpless is a sin.
Then I am a...
sinner.
I beg of you...
Please teach me
the ways of the sword.
The sword?
The way you handle
that sword is incredible...
You move your body
with efficiency and care...
and your blade
flows beautifully.
Oh...?
I used to practice
a long time ago...
a little.
Then teach me...
I need to become stronger...
before I step foot in Pieta...
Teach me...
There's a look in your eyes...
With time you could be...
strong.
Alright I'll do it, but time is
short so don't expect too much.
Thank you.
I won't let you down.
The tip of your sword
must be steady.
Use your whole body
not just your arms.
Right!
Clare...
I can't wait to see you...
This time, I'll be
the one to protect you!
Please Raki...
be safe.
I thought I was prepared for
this, but I never imagined
fighting Awakened Beings
would be this hard.
The longer I think about it
I'm convinced we're lucky
to be alive...
Though who knows
what will happen next.
I'm not even afraid
of dying at this point...
I just...
don't want to awaken
right in the middle of
a battle that
pushes me to my limit.
Enough with the
whining already.
No one is going to
awaken during the battle...
You're psyching yourself out.
I can't relax being surrounded
by all this doom and gloom.
Just ignore her...
The captain's been
a bit moody lately...
Tabitha, didn't we
receive a shipment
of new supplies recently?
That's right...
Everything is in the
storage shed on the east side
of the inn.
Good.
Looks like we have everything we
need in the way of supplies.
Who's there?!
Is that...?
Captain...?
It's Deneve...
I just came in to replace
some damaged equipment.
I'm changing right now.
Can't I even have
a second of privacy?
That's a strange thing to say
to a fellow warrior.
Just shut up and leave!
Let me ask you something.
Where exactly did you get
this second sword you use...?
Its emblem looks
nothing like yours.
What do you care?
I took it from
someone who was killed.
Is that a problem?
Well normally our swords become
our grave markers
after we die...
You do abide by that custom...
right?
The dead has no
use for a sword.
Besides, it belonged
to someone with such
a low rank no one
even missed her.
You can say that but
I saw you hold it with
your dominant hand...
a hand you could have
used to brace your fall,
but you didn't even
let go after I kicked you.
What the hell
are you trying to say bitch?
Judging solely by the way you
speak, I'd assume you were
some kind of savage that
thinks with her muscles...
but the more I listen
I see you're just putting on
an act for all of us.
Stay out!
That's a direct order
from your Captain!
I said stay out you bitch!
Now I understand.
So this is your true form you've
been trying to hide from us all.
Miss Clare...
I would like you to come
with me for a moment, please.
What is it Captain Flora?
How many times do
I have to say it...?
Leave me alone!
What is wrong...?
Are you panicking
because you nearly awakened
after surpassing
your limit earlier?
You go to hell!
It's nothing
to be ashamed of...
It could happen
to any one of us...
The desire for
more strength...
the intense craving
for Yoma blood.
It's a hideous darkness
found inside all of us...
The first time you feel it,
it is unforgettable.
And how in the hell
would you know anything
about what I'm feeling,
unless you've gone through
the same thing yourself.
It's just something
I've heard said...
Don't read into it...
But...
According to the others...
the transformation can
be especially tough
on those warriors who are
more weak and cowardly.
Are you saying I'm weak?!
You started out as a feeble
warrior, yet found solace
in a friend and survived by
sticking close to her...
But in the end it was
your friend who ended up
dying in the heat of
a battle and not you
She was killed because you
were too weak to protect her.
You were left standing on
your own, so you took your
fallen friend's sword
and vowed to avenge her
by becoming the strongest
warrior ever known.
I think it's obvious you
abuse your Yoma power
to look more muscular...
so the Organization will allow
you the use of two swords.
What...?
Who told you about me?!
No one told me anything,
I just guessed...
You may think your situation
is unique but this is
a common occurrence
for us warriors.
Enough!
Hey, I found it!
It's in here!
It looks like everything
we could possibly need!
Damn it...
Damn it!
Wait, is there
someone back there?
Hello?
Oh it's you Deneve.
I didn't know
you were in here.
Yeah.
Is there anything
good back there?
Not much...
it's mostly just
a bunch of livestock feed.
Livestock feed?
ugh...
too bad.
Well, I guess
I'll get changed.
Though I'm probably
wasting my time
because they'll be torn
to shreds by tomorrow.
Alright, I'm all set.
See you, Deneve.
Sweet dreams, as they say.
You too.
Goodnight.
Dont expect me to be grateful.
Not in the slightest...
Helen's a good person and I like
her but she has a big mouth...
If the rest of the team got
wind of the state you're in,
the fear of the battle ahead
could become overwhelming.
Shut up...!
Stop acting like
you know it all.
There's a story
I want to tell you
that will help you understand.
Once there was a young girl
with an older sister...
When their home
was attacked by Yoma...
the girl's older sister
threw her underneath the bed.
As she lay there helpless,
all the little girl
could do was watch...
and listen to the
cries of her family...
as they were ripped
to pieces by the Yoma.
Years later the little
girl would go on
to become a
half-bred warrior...
Though her original intentions
were to avenge the death
of her sister,
she ended up putting
revenge aside and
became a defender.
And in her heart,
she began to see that
she didn't want to die...
Even while
underneath that bed...
while her sister was sacrificing
her own life to protect her...
she kept on thinking it.
She thought of
herself as pathetic...
and went on to fight the
Yoma with reckless abandon
until one day a fellow
warrior said to her...
Come on...! There's nothing
wrong with wanting to live,
what happened in the
past doesn't matter!
We're all still
humans you know!
She'll never be free from
the demons that haunt her...
but thanks to that talk,
she's still alive to this day.
You are among friends here...
Anything you can't do alone,
we'll be right there
to help you with...
So...
don't try to bite off
more than you can chew...
Captain Undine.
Why would you bring me
all the way out here?
I've been sensing that
something isn't right with you-
or more specifically
with that arm of yours.
Your right one...
It doesn't belong
to you, does it?
I thought not.
I heard a story once.
It was about a fighter
who used the same
technique I've seen you use...
Quick Sword Ilena...
She was formerly Number Two.
She was part of a team
sent to take out Teresa,
who was Number One
at the time...
Since that mission ended her
whereabouts remain unknown
by the Organization,
but if she were skilled enough
to be Number Two, she couldn't
have been killed easily,
considering she
was in a group of four.
So where did you get the arm?
You will answer me,
Forty-Seven.
With your silence
I'll assume you obtained it
through unspeakable means.
I've been waiting a long time
for a chance like this...
to test the limits of my
Wind Cutting technique...
up against the former
Number Two's Quick Sword.
Wait.
Hello Jean...
If you wouldn't
mind standing aside.
This matter is between
Clare and myself, not you.
I've indebted
my life to Clare...
I won't allow you
to cut her down.
Are you implying
there's some reason why
she should be cut down?
Listen...
If anyone draws
their sword against Clare...
It's more than enough reason
for me to draw my own
in her defense.
Wait, Jean, please stop.
Very well then...
For what it's worth, I was only
looking to spar a little-
besides, why fight each
other when we could
come under attack from an
Awakened Being at any minute.
However...
I can't fight alongside
you if I can't even
trust to turn my back on you.
I'll request to have you
removed from the operation.
Enough...
The arm's on loan from Ilena.
She is hiding from
the organization...
I didn't want to speak of it...
if I could help it...
Ilena chose to save me when
I'd lost my dominant arm
in a battle...
And so...
And so because of her sacrifice,
I want to make the most
of the gift I've been
given, in her honor.
Under normal circumstances...
I'd have never accepted...
But I know...
I have to continue fighting...
I have to.
Why?
For the sake...
of the person I lost that day.
I will fight...
And without fail...
I will take the head of the
Awakened Being Priscilla.
The Awakened Being
Priscilla...?
No one has any idea
where she is now...
Do you really think you're
powerful enough to defeat her?
I will find her...
It's the reason
I became a warrior.
Please do it...
Help me!
Put it inside me now!
I guess we each have our
own reasons for fighting.
What do you say Clare...?
Let's stand together
and survive as a team.
Sure.
Captain...
I'm sorry about sounding
so negative earlier...
Trust me, I'm not afraid.
Hah...
I don't recall that.
Make sure all of your wounds
are healed quickly...
I wont allow one member
of our team to become
a casualty in the
upcoming battle.
You got that?
That's an order.
We understand
You know not eating and
actually enjoying eating
are two entirely
separate things.
Eating allows you to free your
mind of everyday worries.
Once this battle is
over and done with,
I think I'll treat the group
to something really nice.
Something decadent.
Eating an apple really makes
you feel alive, doesn't it?
I'm sorry...
I think I'm just letting
my nerves get the best of me.
It's okay...
It's a normal reaction
for a human being.
Human being?
You bet.
Human...
you're right.
Please, if it's possible,
may all the warriors gathered
here survive
the battle ahead.
Miria.
So here you are.
Sorry, I just needed
a few moments to myself...
I'm praying even though
there's no god to pray to.
Soon this town will
become a battlefield again.
Yes.
Sadly...
our battle earlier...
was only the beginning...
You've come face
to face with one
of the
Creatures of the Abyss...
so you should know.
The last few days
have been nothing...
If this Easley of the North...
The ultimate
Creature of the Abyss,
decides to act,
it will get ugly.
Let him sleep, Priscilla...
I think he used up every last
bit of strength he had in him.
Humans are such
bizarre creatures.
No matter how far they
surpass their limits,
the power at their disposal
is pathetically small.
Okay then...
Since you have obviously
taken a liking to him...
I'll teach the
boy swordsmanship...
As he wishes.
Priscilla...
Be on your best behavior...
We have a visitor.
Rigaldo.
It's odd seeing someone
of your stature content
with sleeping in the woods.
I like it...
It is...
a nice change of pace...
So...
How are things going in Pieta?
Well...
I see...
Assemble the army at once.
The Northern Army...
now at twenty-seven strong,
will totally annihilate Pieta,
the first town of Alfons.
And once our army is
finished with that town,
not a single hint
of life will remain.
In the name of
the Silver King...
Eradicate all life...
Not even the rats and insects
will escape our destruction.
They're coming!
A merciless king
with merciless orders...
A night of bloodshed...
Next time, Invasion
of Pieta, Part One.