It's been a long time
since my mind has felt
this free and clear.
I'm awake now.
You will die...
by my...
haaaand...
you bitch...
I swear it!
Your symbol is different...
It's not what you had before.
I'm no longer afraid of you...
Do you hear me?
Die!
I'm going to take your life...
I will have my revenge...
for what you've done...
to my mommy and daddy...
I have to murder...
every last traitorous...
filthy, Yoma.
It looks as though
Priscilla has reverted back
to the physical form
she had when we first met.
But what I find
especially troubling
is the partially-awakened
Claymore...
The way she harnesses
her Yoma power is peculiar.
I see how it is...
The Organization seems to have
a few tricks up their sleeve.
This should make for
an interesting battle...
which I will be
watching carefully.
Priscilla...
you're dead!
Damn...
Clare's power level
has risen again.
So that's Priscilla...?
Why has she decided
to show her face
after all this time?
It was Priscilla who killed
Teresa of the Faint Smile...
I'm not surprised
that she's still alive...
The question is...
why is Clare so obsessed
with fighting her...?
It doesn't make sense.
She was prepared to die
a little while ago,
what could possibly
be so important that
she would change her mind?
Care to shed some light
on this, Miria?
Miria, what do you know?
I did a little snooping
around the Organization...
and I came across something...
Clare's ranking is at
the absolute bottom
at number forty-seven.
Don't you find it odd
that the weakest warrior
we have can display power
that surpasses all of us?
What do you mean?
Now that you mention it,
it is strange.
Turns out there's
a logical reason...
Clare is not a half-human,
half-Yoma like we are.
She's different...
Implanted inside of her is not
the flesh and blood of a Yoma
but the blood of
a fellow Warrior.
What?!
And the name of
that warrior is...
Teresa of the Faint Smile.
Are you serious?
Is that even possible?
I have a feeling it was
probably her own idea.
She must have had some kind of
bond or connection with Teresa.
Of course we all know the
Organization would never
do something out of sympathy.
There was an incentive for
them since it allowed
for a new kind of experiment,
where a Warrior is made
from one of their own,
rather than the enemy.
Sick bastards...
It sounds like something
they would do.
Makes sense...
It explains why Clare is so
determined to kill Priscilla,
because she wants revenge.
You're probably right.
Thing is...
In this heightened state
Clare is in right now...
she'll be fully awakened before
the fight comes to an end.
Even if she were to awaken,
there's no telling if she'd
be able to defeat Priscilla.
Let's move.
I can't believe this shit...
I promised Clare I wouldn't
let her die a monster-
she has to die a human...!
Whatever happens I won't
allow her to awaken...
I just hope she doesn't put up
a fight once I get there!
Look-what is that?
It looks like
some kind of trail...
I guess Miria and the others
must have left it for us.
Do you mind if...
if I ask you something?
What is it that makes you care
about Clare as much as you do?
Well, she saved my life.
I was moments away from
becoming something inhuman...
when Clare swooped
in to rescue me.
That's why I've given
over my life to her...
I am...
now...
in her debt.
I was also...
saved by Clare.
That's why I came here
to find her...
I have to help her
no matter what.
It's the least I can do.
Fighting for the sake
of something or someone
is not a concept
that's ours alone.
It's what Clare's doing now...
What?
The Awakened Being that she's
fighting to withstand...
took the life of someone
very precious to her.
And for those whose
life Clare has saved,
so too have we saved hers.
That's...
true.
She fights for the sake
of the person she lost...
and for...
the sake of the person
she doesn't want to lose...
Those are Clare's
words, not mine.
I think that's just
part of being human.
Clare...
she won't turn into
a Yoma, will she?
No...
she won't.
What's the matter...?
Is there something wrong?
I don't remember...
you being this weak before...
Miss Teresa.
Teresa.
Teresa!
Oh my.
You're not worthy...
of uttering her name!
It's your own fault, really...
My mommy and daddy,
my big brother,
Miss Illena and all
the other Warriors...
Committing those horrible
acts on the innocent.
I blame you for everything,
Miss Teresa.
I told you...
don't say her name!
Alright...
It's time we ended this.
I just don't see how I
could have ever been afraid
of you when I can obviously
kill you so easily.
It's only a matter of time until
you breathe your last breath.
So goodbye now...
Miss Teresa.
You know that really hurt.
Damn it...
She better not have awakened...
If she has I will
never forgive her.
Helen...? Miria...? Deneve?
So this is the Priscilla
we've heard so much about.
I never thought
she'd be so imposing.
Hello...
It's a real pleasure
to meet you all...
Judging by what
I see before me...
the three of you must be
newcomers to the Organization.
I am...
Priscilla,
the Number Two Warrior.
Hold on...
What the hell
is she talking about?
Her memories are limited
to what happened
before she fully awakened.
Either that or she's
just completely confused
Helen, Deneve, move to the
flanks on either side of her...
I'm going to try
to charge her head on.
Sounds like a plan to me.
No...
don't do it...
Well...
what is this about...? Do
you three honestly think
you'll be able to kill me?
Go now!
You are all a disgrace,
fighting on the
side of the Yoma.
Do you really
think you can touch me?
Damn it!
There's no way, I can't
believe she dodged that!
What do you expect
from a monster?
Just don't let your guard down.
I have done nothing wrong- you
are the ones who are monsters.
Committing all
of those atrocities...
against my mommy, my daddy
and my big brother.
All I ever did was eat
a bit of worthless flesh
and nothing more.
I am far from being a Yoma.
Those despicable Yoma...
They must die...
I will kill them...
This is...
unreal!
So much power...
Is that...?
Hang on tight.
But Jean...
You can't- you're wounded!
I'll manage.
It's been gradually regenerating
the entire journey.
You still want to
help Clare, don't you?
All I need to do is get
to Clare's location...
I just hope I can
last that long.
Clare...
Impossible.
What the hell?
You mean she wasn't
completely awakened before?
My my...
Your talents are truly
a thing of beauty...
Priscilla...
Now finish her.
I see no reason to prolong
this any further...
Now prepare to die.
So you're a phantom...
A true Warrior would never
depend on one silly trick.
This sword brings back memories.
Helen!
Get out of here...! Helen!
Bitch!
Damn it, Helen!
So this...
is the power of
a true Awakened Being.
I can see how
you defeated Teresa.
While they may have
been successful
in defeating Rigaldo...
all good things
must come to an end.
What am I doing...
Why am I just sitting here?
I couldn't even
help my friends...
Teresa.
What have I become?
It's Clare.
How does that sound?
Priscilla!
I have to do this...
I have to kill her.
It's why I became a Warrior.
If I can't kill Priscilla...
then this was all for nothing.
Priscilla.
Priscilla...
I will kill you...
I just need...
More...
Power...
Clare...
Is that you?
Clare!
This is the end...
I will kill you!
I promise you!
It's a Yoma.
Priscilla...
Clare!
Distant horizon,
distant dawn.
Emotions entangled.
Next time on Claymore,
To the Successors.