She's approaching her limit.
That's enough for one day.
You should wash up
and get a little rest.
No...
Not yet...
I'm not tired...
I can keep going.
You're finished for today.
Don't strain yourself...
You haven't properly
recovered from your injuries.
You must never
force your training...
In learning this technique,
rest and practice are
equally important.
She's becoming more aware
of her limits.
Her determination is clear.
Still--
A lake surrounded
by mountains...
The perfect place for someone
who doesn't want to be found.
Ah.
A good fit.
It seems we're
very close in size.
This is...
yours from back then isn't it?
Yes that's right.
It's missing a sleeve,
but still...
It's in far better
condition than yours...
Consider it a gift...
Now, sit.
Eat.
I know you're not hungry...
Even so, you need to
replenish your strength.
You haven't changed at all.
You look the same
as you did then.
That shouldn't surprise you...
Because of our
Yoma blood we grow
but never age as humans do...
Unless we die in battle...
or turn into Yoma,
our bodies never change.
If Teresa were alive today she
would look just as she did
on the day that she died.
You feel responsible
for her death, do you not?
And you're not entirely wrong.
In the time that
you traveled together,
Teresa's skills as a warrior
naturally weakened...
She allowed her mind to
stray from her purpose...
Her death was the result.
However...
I think she found
a brief form of happiness.
In the short amount of time
she spent with you...
she was able to see herself,
from a different perspective.
All she had ever known
was the fear and respect
that she commanded
from the rest of us...
But that little girl
adored her...
She began to accept that.
The time she spent with you
must have been peaceful...
I doubt she would have
changed her final days.
The lives we lead
are lonely ones, Clare...
You reminded her of what it
felt like to be human.
Teresa died protecting
the only person who loved her
and the only one
she loved in return.
You gave her a better
death than she expected.
Good...
You're beginning to get a better
sense of your limitations...
Don't ever lose sight
of your boundaries.
How close...?
How close am I to
mastering the Quick Sword?
How long until
I match your skill?
The Quick Sword
requires incredible control...
and great mental fortitude.
You must be able to
maintain composure under
the most grueling
circumstances...
I thought the technique
would suit you well.
I was mistaken...
There's a constant fire
inside of your heart.
A passion you're
not able to control.
You will never learn
the Quick Sword.
You cannot master it...
It is beyond your capability...
You're strong, but your mind is
easily influenced by Yoma power.
Train all you want...
You'll never
last over a minute.
Your speed and force will never
reach one tenth of my own.
In short, it would
be pointless for us
to continue
with your training...
You can try all you like,
but it won't change the fact
that you lack the
necessary will power...
You've accomplished
all that you can.
Stand up.
Why...?
What did you do?
Your wound had
already completely healed.
I merely took the liberty
of creating a new one.
Oh God.
Ilena!
A parting gift.
You stand no chance without it.
What?
What are you saying?
Hurry!
Reattach it before
it's too late!
That arm is your one and
only path to the Quick Sword.
Without it, you have no way
of killing Priscilla.
No.
This is madness!
I'm no longer a warrior so you
have more need for it than I.
May it bring you better luck.
It has been a very long time
since I've needed it.
But--
Accept it...
It's the only way
you can survive.
And the only way
Teresa can be avenged.
Teresa...
When I'm finished,
I will return this to you.
That means we both
have to stay alive.
Well I won't hold
my breath but I'll be here.
Don't worry...
I've survived this long.
Goodbye...
Clare.
I sensed the
presence of another.
Has she gone?
Yes...
She left here
several hours ago.
Ah.
Well, no matter...
It was you I came here
for in the first place.
For many years now,
you have kept your Yoki aura
completely undetectable...
Until now.
Using the Quick Sword
was a mistake...
Such a powerful display
of Yoki left little doubt
about your location...
You were easy to find.
If you've come to kill me, may
I at least ask for your name?
My name's Rafaela...
I'm ranked Number Five
in the Organization.
And how did you earn that scar?
Is it from before you
became a warrior, or after?
It should make no
difference to you now...
You don't have more than
a few moments left to live.
Deserter Ilena...
For your crimes against
the Organization your life
is forfeit.
I was warned to watch out
for your remaining arm...
But I see you have none...
I guess it's not
your lucky day.
True...
Even with both arms,
I'm no match...
Not against the
new Number Five...
But why...?
With the amount
of power you possess,
what's holding you back
from advancement?
Another pointless question
--for one who is about
to lose her head.
What just happened?
My right arm...
Ilena...
What...?
What was that?
Something big...
and it sounds like
it's pretty close.
My, what a coincidence!
Fancy that...
Two old friends
meeting way out here.
Oh...!
I do love your new arm...
Wherever did you get it?
Ophelia!
Now that hurts...
After all we've been through,
aren't you even a little happy
to see me?
Come on...
I thought we were
like sisters...
Didn't you?
My god...
An Awakened Being?!
What? Do you see one...?
Where is it?
I didn't catch its scent.
Oh, I see, you're
just playing games...
like I can't sense
an Awakened Being.
But never mind all that...
You wouldn't happen to have
anything on you I could eat,
would you...?
I'm unbelievably hungry.
Perhaps you can
spare a little meat...?
A taste of viscera
would be nice...
What do you say...?
Not human flesh, of course.
Heavens, no!
I wouldn't want that...
It's not as if
I'm an Awakened Being.
Just in the mood
for something bloody.
No, nothing human...
But something close
does sound divine.
Come to think of it...
The flesh of a half-human such
as yourself would be delicious.
Something is different...
I believe you've
improved since we last met.
Come on...
What's a little bite of innards
between such good friends?
What have you been
doing since I saw you last?
You're not nearly
as slow as I remember.
It's like you're
a different person.
Tell me where you've been!
Fine...
Every woman's entitled
to her secrets.
That's strange...
it doesn't taste
very good at all.
How unusual...
I wonder if her innards
would taste any better.
I'm sorry.
I hate to be
such a picky eater,
but it's quite
a specific craving.
Ever had one of those?
Something tells me I'd prefer
to eat your guts fresh out
of your squirming body...
But I'm sure I'll still
enjoy them once you're dead.
I would imagine it must
be pretty embarrassing
for a warrior like yourself
to drown to death
it's almost comical...
Well, maybe not
so comical to you
What's this...?!
No!
What's going on here...?
Can that be me...?
But how...?
I'm--
Just who the hell is that?
No...!
This can't be happening...!
I don't deserve this...!
I can't...
I can't have awakened!
It's not possible...!
Ahhh!
Why...?
What did I do
to deserve this...?
All I ever wanted to do
was avenge my big brother!
How could I turn
into this monster?
I've always been so careful!
None of this would
have happened if
it weren't for that
one-horned bitch!
It's all her fault.
My arm...
Bitch...
What the hell
did you do that for?
What have I ever
done to you...?
Why did you do that...?
Tell me!
It's all your fault!
You did this...!
You and that bitch
with the invisible sword!
If you hadn't been around,
my brother would be
alive right now...!
And I never would have
ended up like this...!
I'll rip you apart
for what you've done!
Damn you...
Who the hell
do you think you are?
My name is Clare...
Ranked number 47
in the Organization.
Created with Teresa's flesh
and blood and the vare
of Ilena's right arm...
It is my mission to take
the head of Priscilla,
the one-horned Awakened Being.
And if I must...
I'll tear out your heart to make
sure that I accomplish my goal.
Damn you bitch!
Did I misjudge my
boundaries...?
No...
It's because I'm not
used to Ilena's arm.
I see.
Well that explains
your new limb, doesn't it?
I knew I'd seen it somewhere.
Ilena's arm...
Did you kill her for it
or did she just give you
the damn thing?
That's how you were able
to improve so quickly.
Are you completely unleashing
your Yoki aura into your arm?
Then I guess all you have to do
is keep a grip on your sword...
And try not to awaken,
of course...
Does that just about cover it?
So dangerous...
Isn't it...?
Just look at you!
You can't even stop shaking,
how can you ever hope
to control that arm?
There...
Everything that remains of my
humanity, is now right here.
In other words, this is where
I'm the most vulnerable.
Now how about we
play a little game...?
Doesn't that sound like fun?
All you have to do is
chop your way through
my entire body
until you get down here.
If you reach me before the Yoki
aura takes control, you win...
But if you awaken, I do...
And you weren't
strong enough to fight
the one-horned monster, anyway.
Understand...?
Are we clear on the rules?
In the event that I lose...
as per your request, I'll even
allow you to tear my heart out.
How foolish...
She could have come
straight for my weak spot
instead of playing along.
Why is she pushing herself?
She's already
come close to awakening.
Doesn't she have
any consideration
for who she'll leave
behind if she fails...?
Wait.
What made me think that?
Hurry, sis...!
It's your only chance!
I'll distract it,
just get away!
Run!
Please, sis!
We don't have much time.
Oh...
I remember...
Brother...
He tried to protect me from
her by sacrificing himself.
Attacking a powerful
enemy alone...
knowing there's
no hope for victory.
It's so...
pointless.
So, seems you aren't
strong enough...
You barely made it half way.
Damn it...
You bitch...
Why...
Why did ...
My arm...
It won't--
My arm won't...
move!
Are you just giving up now...?!
What if you die?
Have you thought about
what happens to everyone
who depends on you if
I kill you right here?
Oh, what the hell...
If you want it,
come and get it.
Ah...
Maybe that was a mistake.
That was quite impressive...
I was wrong about you.
You played by
the rules and won...
though you still
may not be a match
for the one-horned demon...
It's truly infuriating...
I despise people like you
who put their own lives
in jeopardy for some
glorious, hopeless cause.
Now aren't you going
to tear my heart out...?
That is the honor you were
fighting me for, is it not?
No...
it's not.
You're fighting in my place,
so if you lose...
you won't- be forgiven.
That's why Brother was smiling.
Because he knew...
that by dying he'd
been able to protect me.
all this time
I thought he was weak...
I was wrong.
I'm sorry...
I'm coming to join you...
so we can play again...
Brother...
Wandering thoughts...
A wandering warrior...
The appearance of
a menacing threat.
Next time...
"The Witch's Maw, Part 1"