One
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Five strong warriors...
They must be leading
small squads into battle,
each independent
but working together.
Not a Yoma.
She's an Awakened Being...
At one time she was human.
There's too many of them...
At this rate we'll
never make it...
What the hell?
It feels...
it feels like someone's
coming this way.
There's...
no way!
It can't be...
Rigaldo!
The Silver-Eyed Lion King!
Veronica, no!
Behind you!
Captain!
You're a strong one too...
But not strong enough.
Get out of my way.
I don't waste my time
on weaklings.
Damn you...
you will die tonight.
I hope you can fight
as well as you talk.
This has been
very entertaining...
But now...
Deneve...!
Clare! Wait!
Stay where you are...!
You're the only captain left,
we can't afford to lose you.
He's coming for you next...
Stay back it's not safe!
He killed them all...
All of the captains...
And he'll pay for it.
But he's not going to get you!
Watch out Deneve!
Not bad.
I'm impressed you
even saw that coming...
Not exactly "saw"...
I think it's more likely
you sensed my move
rather than saw it.
Am I right?
You son of a bitch.
I will kill you for this!
Mommy...
Daddy...
Brother...
Sister...
Poor Priscilla.
Why don't you
leave her alone...
You don't want to
make her feel bad, do you?
What she did was
perfectly natural-
you shouldn't be shocked...
She needs to have nourishment
just like you or I do.
Priscilla feeds on
the flesh of humans...
I'm afraid it's
something she cannot help...
And as much as it may repulse
you- it will never change.
But still.
As I said before,
she's an Awakened Being.
Her way of life is
different from yours...
An Awakened Being...
Is that what Priscilla
really wanted for herself?
I'm afraid I don't have
the answer to that...
All I know is that somewhere
along the way she lost control
and went over her limit...
It's a fate that is all but
inevitable for a Claymore.
Wait- what did you just say...?
Priscilla was a Claymore?
Yes...
And awakening is one of
many cruel eventualities
for their kind.
So...
She had a family...
Mother...
Father...
and siblings.
They are only
memories to her now...
Vague recollections
of her life as a human.
A human...
she can become
human again, can't she?
That's impossible.
Besides...
There's nothing
for her to return to.
Why...?
Priscilla...
The closest she will ever come
to regaining her humanity
is in her dreams...
Her fate is absolute-
it cannot be changed.
She is no longer human
and there's nothing
you can do to change that.
We will be moving on soon...
In the meantime, it would be
wise to try and get some rest.
Who the hell are you...?
What else have you
been keeping from me?
Oh, I'm sure you'll
find out soon enough...
Sleep well.
Clare.
Some people just never learn...
Charging in without
a plan hasn't worked
for you so far, has it?
Miria!
She did it!
A clever trick...
But it's not enough
to save you.
A worthy captain...
You move well.
Clare, don't be stupid...!
Leave him to Miria!
Deneve!
Deneve...! Son of a bitch!
Talk to me...! How bad is it?
Bad enough...
I can't do anything right.
Just hold on until
we can get you out of here.
You're not dead yet,
you hear me?
Forget about me...
Miria and Clare
need your help...
You have to keep them safe.
Deneve!
Those two are our only
hope of coming out
of this battle alive...
Without them
we don't stand a chance.
Don't die on me...! Stay here
and let your wounds heal
until I come back for you...
Don't give up!
How could this happen...
I'm so pathetic.
Look at me...
Helpless...
I don't deserve the
rank of Number Fifteen.
"Don't try to bite off more than
you can chew," I said...
"You're among friends here"...
Who was I kidding?
I couldn't save her...
I couldn't even touch the
bastard that killed her...
I let Undine die...
She'd be alive right now
if it wasn't for me...
Undine, no...
Pathetic.
Damn it...! At this rate,
we'll never get close to him!
He's quick...
And he's able to
predict her every move,
even when she uses the phantom!
Miria should be winning...
But instead, she's struggling
just to keep up with him!
There's no way...
I'll never make it...! Damn it,
why is my body so slow?
It's time to make
your decision...
What's it going to be?
Are you joining us?
Very well...
Once we cross that ridge
we'll be near Pieta.
What's wrong?
You're moving slower
than before...
Are you approaching your limit?
I guess you're not
finished after all.
Or perhaps I spoke too soon.
In fact, you can
no longer evade me at all...
Can you?
What a pity...
But I won't
make you suffer long.
This has nothing
to do with you.
Mind your business!
Look out!
It's no use...
He's too strong.
I need more speed...
More.
Hey...! What are you doing?
Turn around and go back!
What's the matter?
There's no time
to be asking questions...!
You and your friends
have to get far away
from here before it's too late!
Why would we do that?
Because of the Yoma, kid...!
There's a whole horde
of them back there!
The only town that way is Pieta-
is that where you came from?
It is...
The Claymores are doing their
best to keep them back, but-
Against that many Yoma,
they don't have a chance...!
No matter how many
fighters they have.
That's right,
and they've got plenty...
Even the lowest
ranked ones are there...
But it's hopeless...
If you don't get going and fast,
you'll be as dead as they are!
What...? The lowest
ranked Claymores...?
Wait- are you sure about that?
I saw it myself...
Now move, if you know
what's good for ya.
Clare is there...
I have to go and find her!
It wasn't safe to use
so much Yoma power.
I've sustained too much injury.
I have reached my Yoki limit.
I will soon become a danger
to everyone here.
There's no choice.
I have to do this while my human
mind is still in control...
I must take my own life
while I still can.
If I hadn't been
there to stop her...
Clare would have...
Mommy...
Daddy...
Brother...
Sister...
Raki.
It's a crime to be so helpless.
Stop, please Raki...
You have to let go of me...
I won't--
No...
I... I have to go...
I'm so sorry.
It's his path to choose.
Now...
It's time for us to go, too.
You thought you
had me, didn't you?
Think again.
No...
Today must be my lucky day.
It wasn't one
of your illusions this time.
Miria!
I grow tired of this game...
Now you die!
Damn it...
I'm too slow...!
Why can't I move faster?
Damn it!
Because I promise...
I'll be trying
my hardest to survive.
And come back to you, you hear.
You will live.
Because I won't fail you...
I will find you, Raki.
We swore we'd live
to see each other again...!
I've kept my end
of the bargain...
This time...
I'm going to protect you.
Clare!
If I just had more speed...
more power...
I could have saved Flora...
and protected Jean...
I need more...
more strength...
more speed...
I need more...
more...
More...
All I need...
is more.
What...? What the hell...?
What happened?!
Clare!
Overflowing grief...
Overflowing rage...
The roar of the lion.
Next Claymore,
"Critical Point, One."