Stand Fast!
I said hold your positions!
Eva!
Kate's gone!
They got her!
Lucia!
What...
What is this?
What in the world is going on?
Just-
Just what in the hell
is happening?
How long do you
intend to follow me?
I won't leave until I've
repaid the debt I owe you...
I would have died...
had it not been for you.
I am in your debt...
My life is yours...
Use it in any way you please.
That won't be necessary...
I have already been repaid.
Very Impressive.
Yesterday, that technique
was impossible for me.
I don't understand.
Before I met you...
I had begun to think the
Quick Sword technique
would always be beyond me...
But then...
I saw what you could endure
in the cave back there...
And I was forced to change
my way of thinking.
Even though your body had
awakened, you were able
to maintain the humanity
of your mind...
I would have
thought it impossible.
You proved that it's not.
I was shocked at the power
of the human will...
And began to wonder if
I could use that strength
to my advantage.
I decided that the idea
warranted an experiment...
So I tried it with
the Quick Sword...
Allowing my human will
to control my Yoki...
made the technique possible.
I taught you...
control?
It was seeing how
mentally strong you were
that gave me
the courage to try.
Oh, don't look at me
like that...
You went missing,
I came to find you...
Are you really surprised?
Rubel!
Impossible...!
I never sensed her coming!
Number Five...
Rafaela!
In case you two haven't noticed,
Rafaela here is unmatched
in her ability
to hide her Yoki aura.
Which makes her ideal
for covert operations.
Oh I wouldn't do that...
Even the two of you together
would be no match for her.
You've never faced
a warrior like her before.
What about Galatea...?
What the hell have
you done with her?
You mean your friend who
ignored her assignment
then contrived a pitifully
transparent lie
to avoid punishment?
Immediately following
her report...
I had her beheaded
for disloyalty.
I'd love to tell you
that's what happened,
but it just isn't the case...
Galatea is useful
in her own little way,
so we spared her life...
However, she will
find herself assigned
to much more difficult
missions for quite some time.
Speaking of...
I've come here...
with an interesting new
assignment for you, Clare.
What are you talking about?
Multiple Awakened Beings
have gathered in the north.
Several warriors,
including Number Seven,
have fallen in our
attempt to destroy them.
Your next assignment...
is to do what
the others could not.
The Organization has begun to
assemble an appropriate number
of warriors for the task...
You will be among them.
If you are able to destroy the
Awakened Beings in the north,
then we may be willing
to grant you a pardon.
Not a bad deal for
a fugitive, wouldn't you say?
Don't worry...
You don't have
to answer right away...
But remember...
You answer to the Organization.
We can locate you
whenever we choose,
and destroy you just as easily.
Oh, one more thing.
Do you remember the young boy
you were traveling with...?
Our resources tell us he's
begun moving north as well.
One might assume he's
still searching for you.
Raki, no!
If it is your wish to be
reunited with the boy
and it's certainly
clear that it is...
I do believe the north serves
a double purpose...
to make that wish a reality
and a chance for you
to earn your redemption.
Bastard!
They're...
all over.
Yeah...
why are there
so many of them?
What's going on here...?
I don't understand.
So this is Pieta...
In the northern land
of Alfons.
Just go away.
I've already told you to quit
following me around everywhere.
Or better yet...
just do what you want.
Well, look who's
alive after all.
It's you again...
Long time no see, Clare.
What's up?
Hello, Helen!
Oh Damn.
She was just greeting an
old friend she hasn't seen
in a long time...
There's no need to get violent.
Deneve!
As greetings go, that was
a bit on the crude side...
Even old friends deserve
some common courtesy,
don't you agree?
What's with your
friend, Clare...?
It looks like you've
partnered up with
a real straight-laced
kind of girl...
So, stranger,
what number are you...?
I'm Helen, Number Twenty
Two, and my associate there
is Number Nineteen...
Well?
Since you asked,
my name is Jean...
But you may call me
Number Nine.
What?
You mean your ranking is
in the single digits...?
Why are you with Clare?
She's only Number Forty-Seven!
If it hadn't been for
Clare's intervention
I wouldn't be standing here...
I didn't ask her number
when she saved my life,
and it matters
even less to me now.
It appears not all the warriors
ranked in the single digits
are completely insufferable.
Who knew.
My name is Deneve...
Please forgive my behavior...
I hope you understand
that Helen meant no harm.
She can be a bit
abrasive at times.
It's fine...
And I didn't mean
to be so critical...
I had no right to speak to a
comrade-in-arms in that manner.
I apologize.
Sure...
Apologies all around?
Everyone...!
Would you please
gather 'round?
It's time for us to
outline our strategy
for the current mission...
For those just arriving,
I'm Flora...
I am ranked number eight
in the Organization
Huh.
Finally, a face to go
with the number.
Hey...
Since you're the
highest ranked warrior here,
that means you're
the leader, right?
Doesn't that make you the
authority in this situation?
It would...
If I were truly the
highest ranked warrior here,
which I'm not...
I believe our leader
is approaching now.
Miria!
Number Six...
I wondered what
she'd look like.
So that's Phantom Miria, then.
Welcome, all.
Thank you for coming so far from
your respective territories...
I hold the Number Six ranking...
You may call me Miria.
For the duration of this
mission, I will be your leader.
Here in the
northern land of Alfons,
multiple Awakened Beings
have joined forces...
Our assignment...
and the reason for the size
of this gathering...
is their total annihilation.
Impossible...!
Multiple Awakened Beings
in one place?
But Awakened Beings have never
banded together before this!
Why would they start now?
All we know is that they have.
That's just great.
What're you, scared?
I guess we're not the
tough crew I thought we were.
I mean I thought that killing
off creatures like these
was basically the entire
reason for our existence...
How can you be afraid when
this mission is exactly
what we were trained to do...?
And you all call
yourselves warriors.
Hey, what's with her?
She sure thinks a lot of
herself, doesn't she...?
And how did she get permission
to carry two swords?
That's Number Eleven.
Her name's Undine.
She claims that she's the
strongest warrior alive,
and she carries two
swords to prove it.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah...
But as far as I'm concerned...
between that and the way
she flaunts her muscles
outside combat, it only
proves she's cocky...
Everything about her
just screams "amateur."
Funny!
Pretty harsh, though.
What did you just say...?
Do you really think I'm just
gonna let that slide...?
Speak up!
I'm sorry...
I thought I was speaking softly
enough you wouldn't hear me,
guess I was wrong...
I'll be more
careful next time.
So you think
you're pretty funny...
Don't you?
Whoa, Deneve.
Take it easy, all right?
Everyone. May I please have
your attention?
There are still things
we must discuss.
But if you insist on fighting,
perhaps I can help...
I would be happy to take on any
one of you in single combat.
Wind Cutting Flora...
The Organization's
Number Eight...
Drawing a sword, cutting, and
returning it to its sheath.
All of them are
simple motions...
But the way she does them...
It's almost unbelievable.
And Miss Jean...
You're also ranked in
the single digits...
Please come forward.
Number Eleven, Undine.
Would you make your way
to the front, too, please.
Also Number Thirteen,
Veronica.
Step to the front.
I count twenty-four warriors
here, so we'll split into five
separate units, each with
four or five members.
The five warriors that you see
before you, including myself,
will be serving as
captains of these units.
Some of you may have fought
Awakened Beings before now...
If so, this particular
strategy may be something
you incorporated.
Yeah, you know,
I think we're all familiar
with the drill by now.
The strategy is simple but
has proven very effective
for us in the past...
Each team will focus its efforts
on a single Awakened Being.
Don't leave your team or
your target for any reason.
We'll mount our
first assault tomorrow.
You will now be
divided into units.
Assignments are
not negotiable.
Number Fourteen.
Cynthia.
Uh...
Here?
Team Veronica.
Number Fifteen.
Deneve.
You're with Team Undine.
Number Seventeen.
Eliza.
Team Jean.
Number Eighteen.
Lily.
Team Flora.
Number Twenty.
Queenie.
You're on Team Miria...
Number Twenty-two,
Helen, Team Veronica.
Number Twenty-Four.
What the hell...?
Why didn't Miria put me
on her team?
Number Twenty-Seven.
Emelia.
Team Jean.
Hey...
You did make sure you weren't
followed, didn't you?
I did...
Besides, everyone
here is far too busy
to pay attention
to anyone else.
Come on in.
The others are already here.
Once again, you're
the last one to arrive.
Miria.
It's been too long,
old friend.
Let's commemorate our reunion.
Well done.
We've all survived.
It's good to see all of you.
Who's out there...!
Show yourself!
Why's she here?
Clare...!
I thought you said that
you hadn't been followed!
No, wait...!
Jean didn't follow
me here, she's...
She's one of us.
I'm sorry to intrude.
I didn't mean
to spoil your reunion.
However, it seems this business
relates to me, as well.
You would need to possess an
extraordinarily strong will.
To revert an Awakened body to
human form is no small feat.
So you'll understand if
I'm a bit skeptical...
Clare, I can't help but
notice your new right arm.
It clearly belonged to someone
with astonishing power.
Someone who knew how
to swing a blade...
Who?
Yeah, whose is it?
I'm afraid that's not
something I can reveal.
Of course not...
You just don't have
the best of luck, do you?
You can say the same thing
about every warrior out here.
There are
twenty-four people...
with no idea how
unlucky they are.
Let me ask you this...
What do you think the odds are
we'll actually accomplish
our goal here?
This operation...
has absolutely
no chance of success.
What?
If it were only multiple
Awakened Beings,
we may have stood a chance...
But there's more
to our assignment.
Our real target is the
mastermind behind
all of these Awakened Beings...
And he is the reason that
we're destined to fail.
What...?
Who the hell are you
talking about?
Isley.
The Silver King,
who governs the north.
The Creature of the Abyss...
Our target.
We're here to destroy Isley?
That's- impossible!
Maybe so.
But it doesn't change things.
The true nature of this
operation is to subdue every
Awakened Being in the northern
territory, and the puppeteer
behind them, even if he is
a Creature of the Abyss.
Wait, what.
What in the hell is the
Organization thinking...?
He's probably the most powerful
Awakened Being of all time!
Calm down.
My best guess is that the
Organization is using us
to buy themselves
time to think...
You see-
They don't expect us
to survive.
So that's Pieta, huh?
Boy, there sure are
a lot of them in there...
Think you can tell how many?
Wait.
There are Twenty-four.
Not that it makes too much
difference how many there are.
What do we do now?
Exactly what we came to do...
Forward reconnaissance.
But there are all those
pretty girls down there...
We can't just ignore them.
It'd be rude not to say hello.
and I hate to be rude!
Damn! Those monsters beat us
to the first attack!
All right boys,
we'll see you there.
Aw.
There he goes again.
I see now what you meant...
He is hopeless.
Evening, everyone...
Anyone want to show
a stranger around?
I'm not feeling
very welcome here.
Hey...
What's the idea
spoiling all my fun,?
Grab your swords
and prepare for battle!
Well!
This certainly is a pleasure.
I don't think I've ever seen
so many ladies in one place.
And I look such a mess!
Everyone break into
your units now!
Team Miria,
we'll take this one...
Team Flora, you take the
roof to the right...
Team Jean, see what you
can do about the one
on that stone pillar
to the left.
Team Undine!
Team Veronica!
Stand by.
Keep a close eye out and assist
any teams that look like
they need help.
They don't seem to be shaken
at all by our sudden attack...
I underestimated them.
So much for the
element of surprise...
I've been here ten seconds and
they've spotted me already.
The Claymore leader is
clearly no stranger to battle.
She's tough, but...
Her greatest weakness is...
her team.
They're terrified.
They simply aren't experienced
enough to keep calm
in a battle situation with
a real Awakened Being.
Forward!
Get off!
Why don't you quit
scurrying around and fight?
She's so quick!
On my team, I doubt I can
count on Numbers Thirty-Nine
and Forty-Seven to
be of much help...
Which means I have
to end this before
he takes his awakened form.
Oh, no!
Something altered the
course of my attack!
Be careful!
He can control your movements
by manipulating your aura!
I...
can't control my body!
I don't think I can...
stop him!
Please...!
Get away!
I can't stop--...!
He has complete control
of my body!
Please hurry...!
Get back!
Illena...
Help me!
What was that...?
I didn't know anyone could
swing a blade that quickly!
That was pretty good...
I'm actually starting
to have fun!
It's times like this...
that remind me why I became
a monster in the first place!
I'm gonna rip you all apart!
Who wants to be first?
You aren't much of
a leader, are you?
A good leader would have
known her weakest fighters
before the battle even started.
And those are the
soldiers you sacrifice.
But you wasted valuable time
trying to protect them!
You brought this
on yourself.
You should really apologize
to your warriors.
You swing that sword
like a rookie, Jean.
Can't you kill one little
Awakened Being without our help?
Helen!
Deneve!
We've got our work
cut out for us...
Looks like a tough one.
Get ready everyone...
We're gonna finish
this right now.
Here he comes!
The white land.
The white night.
A nightmare is unleashed.
Next time: The Carnage
in the North, Part Two.