Speaking of-
I've come here with an
interesting new assignment.
Multiple Awakened Beings
have gathered in the north.
Several warriors,
including Number Seven,
have fallen in our
attempt to destroy them.
You're next assignment is to do
what the others could not...
Oh, one more thing.
Do you remember the young boy
you were traveling with...?
Our resources tell us he's
begun moving north as well.
I count twenty-four warriors
here, so we'll split everyone
into five separate units,
each with four or five
members per unit.
Some of you may have fought
Awakened Beings before now...
The strategy is simple,
but has proven very effective
for us in the past...
Each team will focus its efforts
on a single Awakened Being.
Don't leave your team or
your target for any reason.
There are twenty-four people.
What do you think the odds are
we'll actually accomplish
our goal?
This operation...
has absolutely
no chance of success.
Evening, everyone...
Anyone want to show
a stranger around?
That was pretty good...
I'm actually
starting to have fun!
It's times like this...
that remind me why I became
a monster in the first place!
Here he comes!
Everyone out of the way!
If you can't dodge an attack,
get out of the way!
Move it!
Out of ten fighters
we've only got six left.
What do you think, Miss Flora?
Is that enough
to handle the job?
Not even close Miss Undine,
but it will have to suffice.
Dammit!
Get back here!
Wait!
What do you think
you're doing?
Stop! We attack as a unit!
You brainless things are
such a pain in the ass.
Do me a favor; take your own
head so I don't have to.
Good.
Undine!
Like I thought.
All bark and no bite.
If all you wanted me to
do was nick my own face,
you could have just asked.
I'd have been glad
to save you the trouble. Really.
Impossible!
No one is strong enough
to resist me!
Think again!
Just stay right there
while I decide how
I'm going to kill you.
He's in complete control
of her Yoki aura!
Sorry, but if it's
all the same to you,
I think I'd rather stand.
Not bad.
Everyone get
ready to move in!
No!
Stay where you are...
She hasn't fully
regained her control.
Let go!
Undine, no!
Don't come any closer!
I can handle this little
bastard all by myself.
Injured fighters!
Back!
Worthless son of a bitch!
Tough talk for someone who only
has a few seconds left to live.
We have to do something!
No...!
I said I can handle this...!
You'll only get in the way!
You fools, you're asking for it!
Knock it off!
Sorry, Captain,
it's nothing personal.
The two of them working together
can't even break his hide!
Eight...
Nine.
Hurry, Jean!
We need you!
I'm trying...
Almost there.
You don't really
think you can win?
Enough is enough...!
It's time you
learned your place.
Seventeen...
Three more to go.
Let's see-.
What am I going to do
with the two of you?
Are you sure
you want to do that?
It's one thing to call on
your Yoma power...
But at that rate,
you'll awaken in no time.
And trust me,
there's no turning back.
No!
They've gone too far!
He's right!
I hate to say 'I told you so.'
That's...
Twenty!
We're almost there now.
What a pathetic bunch you are.
Ten of the Organization's
best and you can't even land
a scratch on me.
Or maybe I simply don't
know my own power.
Struggling will
get you nowhere.
Twenty-one.
And just in time.
You're going to have
to do better than that.
How's that...? Good enough?
It's about time.
Hold on...
What are you doing?!
Miss Veronica...
Have you noticed how
thankless this all is...?
We act as bait...
We risk our lives...
Sustain injuries
from head to toe.
You have a good point there...
But as defenders, it's the
job we're best suited for.
It can't be helped...
But it has it's moments.
We get to finish
this bastard off!
Wait!
You can't!
You've awakened...
Surprise, surprise.
I don't understand.
You both have
surpassed your limits!
What is this?
But I saw them...
But how...?
You can't turn back
after awakening!
Either you're mistaken...
Or you've been
imagining things.
Now...
What do you say
we put an end to this?
Dammit!
Knock it off!
Stop...!
Just give it up!
Deneve no!
A noble effort.
But you're badly outmatched.
If you wanted to stop me, you
should have cut off my head
when you had the chance.
One blow isn't enough.
He's too hard.
Have your injuries
sapped your strength,
or were you just too
weak to begin with...?
Go on, tell me.
I promise not to judge you.
Unlike my esteemed
present company,
I'm not enamored
with my own muscles...
I prefer technique.
No...!
You can't do this!
They did it!
That's it...
You asked for it!
Stay back!
All of you...!
He still has the ability
to control our Yoki!
If you're sending me to hell...
then I'm taking you two
weaklings along for the ride.
And since you're both already
in the beheading mood...
Are they going to be okay?
They'll be fine...
But that was a close call.
Damn...
See, this is why I'm always
saying the weak ones
only hold us back...
Well, look who
actually pulled it off.
Our team finished up
a little early.
We thought we might swing by
and lend you guys a hand.
But it looks like
there's no need.
It's good to see I'm not
the only one too slow
to escape injury.
Where is Miria...?
If she was left to fight
with only her own team,
we have to find
her and help out!
What are you worrying about?
Stop.
She's a big girl;
she can take care of herself.
She's...
not bad...
All right!
And not even a scratch!
I know you've gotten stronger
as a result of things
you've experienced
in the field...
But Miria's seen more
than you or I ever will.
It might be difficult for you
to understand, but...
Miria's situation is
far more complicated
than any other
fighter out here.
It seems both units were able
to slay their target.
And with minimal damage.
As for our team, Uma lost
her left arm in combat...
Luckily she's a defender, so
I'm confident she'll be able
to regenerate it
once she's rested.
Unfortunately, until Uma
is able to regenerate,
we're left one fighter short...
Similar injuries should
be reported to me
so the teams can
be restructured.
I don't like this.
So, what?
In this game, we're all the
pawns and you're the queen,
does that about cover it...?
Maybe your majesty
wouldn't mind explaining:
What were you really
hoping to accomplish?
You put experienced fighters
on the same field as those
who've never even seen an
Awakened Being before.
And what do you know,
they couldn't cut it.
In fact, all they did
was get in the way.
Most of this bloodshed
could have been avoided
if the rookies were assigned
to back up the veterans
from the get-go...
Well...?
Wouldn't you agree, my Queen?
Think long and hard
before you respond,
because your answer may lose
you your strongest fighter.
Does anyone know
how many of us fell in battle?
Most of us took a hit or two,
but we all survived...
Just shy of a miracle,
if you think about it.
So what you're saying is-
As a result of today's action,
all of us have now experienced
fighting an Awakened Being.
Miria's true intention in
organizing today's assignments
was to put every last fighter on
equal footing in the field...
which raised the
potential of each unit...
Unless I'm mistaken.
Whatever the case...
Any number of us could have
been killed in that battle...
And I'd prefer not to die
for a training exercise.
Thank you all
for your efforts today...
Try to get
whatever rest you can...
It only gets harder from here.
Are you sure about this?
Someone's bound to
realize sooner or later.
With the forces we have now...
We have no chance of
making it out alive.
Our situation is dire, but we
can't do much to change it...
We're stuck fighting
with our backs to the wall.
Our only option is
to get stronger...
If we want to win this,
it's up to us to improve...
If we don't, every
fighter here will die.
It's the only
chance we have left.
Our only- chance.
Raki...
Be careful.
Thank god...
This isn't Clare's sword...
Oh, thank god.
This is a ghost town.
Is it possible that
everyone who lived here
was wiped out by monsters?
What could have happened here?
Are you okay...?
Are you hurt?
Sorry!
I just- I didn't mean to-!
I'm...
sorry.
What're you doing...?
I'm sorry.
Just hold on a second...
--Hold on.
--Hey!
I was wondering
where you'd run off to...
Is something wrong?
This boy, he smells good.
I haven't seen you get
that attached to someone
in a long time...
You're not...
from around here, are you?
No...
I've traveled a long way
from my home in the south...
There's someone that
I've been trying to find...
I heard a rumor that someone
matching her description
was seen around here,
so I came to look.
Ah, a southerner...?
Well, that explains the smell...
My friend here can
probably still smell
the warmth of
the south on you...
Someday...
I hope I can show her
the south myself.
Well...
I haven't seen
anyone here but you.
Was this town
destroyed by monsters too?
I wouldn't worry
much about it.
You're the closest
thing to a monster
we've seen since we arrived.
You're not used to the cold.
You must be freezing...
We should look for shelter...
Would you care to join us?
It's rare my companion gets
attached to someone like this...
Would you do me a favor and
keep her company for a while?
Uh...
I guess so...
All right.
Come along then.
Priscilla.
The sun that never sinks.
The hope that does.
The distant dawn.
Next time: The Carnage
in the North, Part Three.