Your cathedral is infested
with a Voracious Eater.
What is a Voracious Eater?
You two don't stand
a chance against it!
You'll die if you stay!
Stop right there!
She put up a helluva fight...
she's gotta be dead.
No...
I can still hear
her heart beating.
Galk, what are you doing...?
Put her down...
she's just a monster...
Look, she may be a claymore...
But she saved my life...
I at least owe her this much.
Clare!
Tell me!
Is she going to be alright?
Unfortunately that
remains to be seen ...
we just don't know where
to begin to treat a claymore.
What are you saying...?
You can't mean that
Clare's just going to...
Die?
I don't see what
the fuss is about.
A couple of monsters just
tried to kill each other...
It's not something
to waste your tears over.
--Bastard!
--I'm warning you...
Watch what you say about Clare.
She took me in...
and she's always willing
to sacrifice herself!
You have no clue what
she's done for me...
Clare has made me happier
than I've ever hoped to be...
She's pure of heart and she's
certainly a hell of a lot nicer
than any miserable
human I've ever known.
Ya big baby...
Guess I'll go back to my post.
Are you alright?
Damn...
that...
bastard...
Stop crying.
I believe there is
great power in faith...
At this point, all you
can do is pray for her...
Do you understand?
It's not over yet...
She will live.
You're awake.
Well thank goodness for that.
I'm sorry Father...
I must have been
so much trouble.
Oh no...
no trouble at all.
How long have
I been unconscious?
Since...
the day before yesterday...
Raki stayed by your
side the entire time...
He kept constant
vigil in the hopes that
you would open your eyes.
Forgive me, Father...
but I need a favor.
Huh?
I am sorry to have called all
of you so late in the night...
But I am afraid I'm going
to have to insist that you
trust me for a while.
Father Vincent...
What is this about Vincent?
A Yoma investigation.
What?
A Yoma investigation...?
You mean that thing is hiding
somewhere amongst us?
It's quite possible...
and considering what we've all
been through I don't believe
that we can afford
to take any chances.
Her eyes!
Those are the eyes of a witch!
Outrageous...!
Vincent, are you responsible
for bringing that demon here?
Unfortunately
I didn't have a choice.
Would somebody please tell me
what is going on here?
Vincent...
how dare you...!
You're including the archbishop
in this investigation
of yours...?
You're insane...!
Do you hear me--
Why Vincent?!
Please...
we need your cooperation.
I don't like this...
She's a damned
monster for God's sake.
It's Father Vincent's orders.
I know.
Good...
next...
I can't believe
what she expects of us.
This is crazy.
Are you really
going through with it?
It's simple enough...
She locates the Yoma and traps
it in a vulnerable place...
and we spear it and
her at the same time.
It's so unfortunate...
But, then again, she's able
to heal herself so quickly...
I just don't see any other
options at this point.
This is our fight.
We can't fight
this thing alone...
we need all the help
we can get even with her...
don't let your
pride get to you.
It's not about pride.
Enlighten me.
Humans should defend
humans; that's it...
damn!
You're fine.
Thank you.
I don't understand.
I can't sense
a Yoma anywhere...
If it were here, it would
be missing its right eye,
but everyone checks out.
Good. You're okay.
Perfect...
Why in the world do I
have to wait out here...?
This baptism chamber
is really creepy.
Especially...
with that guy in here.
You're fine.
Only two left.
He's not a Yoma either!
Tell me...
do I pass?
Yes.
Only one left.
Wait...
what are you doing?
I apologize Father...
but I can't afford
to make exceptions.
But I'm not---
This will only take a moment.
What...?
It's not him...
He's human!
This can't be right...
It has to be
in the cathedral...
why can't I find it?
Did I miss something?
What am I not thinking of?
Stop...
think...
think like a Yoma.
It doesn't care who it uses to
hide so long as it stays hidden.
Man.
Woman.
The elders.
Even a child.
Or the body of corpse!
You are disgusting...
They gotta be done with
the investigation by now.
Raki!
Clare should be fine...
I hope...
What the hell was that...?
Clare...?
You're here...
Did it hurt you...?
You alright?
I'm fine.
Don't worry Raki.
I won't let him get you...
Just get out of here...
now.
Watch out---!
Raki!
Stay back!
It's time to run, brat!
Stay back...!
I've got him!
We'll take over from here...
why don't you stop trying
to save everybody yourself?
I think you've done enough
besides I doubt you could even
save this boy
with your injuries.
This is our city, claymore...!
And we have sworn to
protect it with our lives!
Look, you just take care
of the boy and yourself!
We'll take down this monster...!
Sid is right!
This is our city!
And this Yoma has defiled our
sacred grounds for far too long.
Let's go!
Damn!
Hey!
Hey get back here, boy!
There's nothing you can do!
I have to!
Clare needs this!
What is that thing?
Just make sure she gets it!
Here...
catch!
Claymore!
Now Yoma...
your reign of
terror ends tonight.
That's it!
Damn you, bitch...
Amazing.
It's incredible what
she can do with a sword...
I've never seen anyone do what
this claymore is capable of.
We've got to help her...
Clare's pushing it...
she's hurting...
she doesn't have much left.
You're not looking
very good, Claymore.
Now I understand...
You were only pretending
to have the advantage.
Weren't you?
I thought you were toying
with me but you really didn't
want to prolong this.
You were trying to end it
with one blow...
Instead of getting my arm you
wanted to take off my head.
Sorry to disappoint you!
But this fight
is mine now, Claymore!
Be careful!
You can do much
better than this...
I believe you might,
be running out of blood...
I didn't realize that you
Claymores were so light...!
Time to come down... now!
Die!
Galk!
Are you alright...?
Can you stand?
Sorry...
It doesn't look like there's
much more we can do to help...
You were right about us.
We're no match for this thing.
We're not even close.
This is your show now,
but we're behind you
and you can use us
anyway you need...
you just better
bring that thing down...
Take this!
Why would you do such
a stupid thing like that
you foolish human?
Now you die!
What are you waiting for...?
Now!
How do you like that,
monster...?
A little gift from
a couple of fools.
Bastards...
What's he doing?
You can swing your sword from
any direction down there
and you won't
hit anything vital.
Watch out, Clare!
So you don't consider
your head vital...
Yes...!
You killed the Yoma!
Wow...
that Claymore did it...
she really is amazing.
You're right
about that, Sid...
She's truly incredible.
Are you alright?
How can I help you?
What's going on?
It's no use...
I've gone too far.
Just tell me what's wrong!
What in the hell do you
think you're doing?!
It wasn't safe to use
so much Yoma power.
I've sustained too much injury.
I have reached my Yoki limit.
I will soon become
a danger to everyone here.
There's no choice.
I have to do this while my human
mind is still in control...
I must take my own life
while I still can.
No. Don't. You can't...!
Please just stop!
I must do this.
We'll fix it!
--We'll help you!
--Stay away from me...!
Galk now...
do it!
Please, Galk...
hurry!
Stop...
this isn't right...
you can't do this...!
Raki. Listen to me!
I'm beyond saving...
Clare!
The more we use our Yoki...
the closer we get
to becoming full Yoma.
But this transformation
doesn't happen gradually...
it can hit suddenly,
without any warning.
No, No!
My body is already changing.
I can barely hold on as it is.
Please.
What are you doing...?
You'll die!
Stop...
Please Raki...
You have to let go of me...
I won't-
Please don't...
traveling with you was the best
thing that ever happened...
you made me so happy.
After my family was killed
the village pushed me aside...
I lost every single
thing that I had...!
But then you came
and you found me!
You let me travel with you
and for the first time
I allowed myself
to be happy again...
more than anything, I had
someone back in my life.
You said that you weren't kind,
but I know
that's not the truth...
You were nicer to me than anyone
I had known in my entire life...
And that...
that's why...
I need you to live
and just stay with me...
I don't know what I would do
without you by my side...
If you're going to die,
if this is it Clare...
take me with you!
My Yoki's under control...
I didn't transform...
You're still alive!
Wow, can't believe it's over...
What do you know?
She didn't become
a Yoma after all...
So do you think
that's the end of it?
Well, one thing's for sure...
that boy just saved her life.
I owe you so much, Father.
What are you
talking about, Clare...?
We're the ones who
should be indebted to you
for saving our lives.
I was simply doing my duty.
I want you to know...
the bishop has given his
full consent to taking Raki
under our wing here
in the cathedral.
We'll look after him
as one of our own.
Huh...?
Clare?
Or you could stay with me...
your choice.
Yeah.
Hey brat!
Here...
a souvenir.
Huh?
And Claymore...
you take care of yourself.
Time to go, Raki.
Wait a minute, kid!
Just one more thing...
I need you to grow
big and strong got it...?
Strong enough so
you can help out Clare!
Okay I will...
you can count on it, bye!
Despair and screaming.
In a sea of blood a smile
floats to the surface.
Next time, "Teresa
of the Faint Smile."