Impossible!
The Yoma didn't stand
a chance against her.
So that's a Claymore.
Um...
Excuse me.
Thank you for all
that you've done for us...
We have your fee here-
Keep it.
Keep it?
A stranger in black will
arrive soon after I am gone...
Give it to him then.
Our town sees strange
travelers every day
If we were to accidentally give
your fee to the wrong person,
then how would you know?
I wouldn't...
But if my associate does not
receive the fee, then know this.
From then on, no matter how many
Yoma plague your village...
or how desperately
you beg for aid...
we will not respond.
Once there was a small village
that had failed to pay...
They were wiped out by a horde
of Yoma in less than a month.
You hear stories
like that all the time.
W-we'll pay, Claymore...!
We'll pay, I swear it!
Good.
Then your town should
have nothing to fear.
The way you make it sound...
one might think
the Yoma do our bidding.
Do you have my assignment...
Orsay?
The town of Theo
is two days to the west...
They are expecting you.
And anything else?
You want to know?
No...
I don't.
You have all the information
that is necessary
to complete your task.
Find the Yoma...
Kill them...
That is all.
Of course...
sir.
A mixed-breed soldier created
by the Organization...
Teresa.
The 182nd warrior
of the 77th class.
She slays every Yoma
without ever giving way
to the inhuman
half of her mind.
The twisted Yoma features
never touch her face...
With unsettling ease,
she destroys her enemies...
And always with
a faint smile on her lips.
And so she is known as
'Teresa of the Faint Smile.'
The most powerful woman
in the Claymore ranks.
No, not the
most powerful woman...
The most powerful monster.
But the more you purchase,
the cheaper it gets.
A Claymore!
First one down.
Why the hell are
you doing this?!
You're out of your mind!
That's two.
Run!
The silver-eyed witch
has gone mad!
Found the third.
She- she's crazy!
That makes four.
There you are...
Of course, a wiser Yoma would
have shed his human disguise
much sooner and prepared
to face me in combat...
Even so...
Resist all you like, but it will
not save you from your destiny.
The- the bodies!
They're all...
They're Yoma!
You've all been so blind.
Groups of Yoma living
among your village,
feeding whenever it suits them.
Now, then...
I felt the presence
of seven Yoma
as I approached your town...
Let's see how many
I've already met.
One...
Two...
Three...
Four...
Five...
Six.
Ah...
How careless of me.
I've missed one.
I can sense you...
You are here...
Show me where...
Oh, I see...
Did you think a little girl
could hide you from me?
So naïve.
I'll never sleep
lying on this thing.
It's hard to believe that this
is more relaxing than a bed.
Lady Teresa!
We would...
like to offer you your
payment as well as
our gratitude
for all of your help.
A stranger in black
will come for my fee.
You will give the
entire sum to him.
Hey!
That girl...
Who is this child...?
This girl belonged to the
final Yoma I destroyed,
didn't she?
Trying to exact revenge
for your father's death?
No...
She...
She doesn't seem to belong
to any of the townspeople...
And I don't think she belonged
to the Yoma that you killed,
either, although she
was traveling with it.
I don't understand.
Well, she hasn't spoken
to anyone since she arrived.
But I believe that somehow she
knew that the man you killed
was a Yoma, and that
it was keeping her
as some sort of hostage,
traveling with her from
village to village until they
finally arrived here in Theo.
If the girl has
never spoken before,
how can you know all of that?
Well...
Her entire body is covered
in scars and gashes-
mostly likely from her
travels with that Yoma.
Ah, so she has spent time
as a Yoma's plaything.
So you must think I'm some kind
of savior, then, don't you?
Don't misunderstand...
I did not kill your Yoma
to save you or anyone else...
I kill Yoma because it is
my job and my purpose...
It's not to save human life.
Now what are you doing?
I have not have
made myself clear...
The job that I did today does
not make me your savior
or your friend.
What's wrong with her?
Is she not right in the head?
I don't know...
I think we all assumed that
her strange behavior was
a result of being a
Yoma's captive for such
a long period of time.
But I just can't say.
Stop.
Take one more step toward me,
and you will wish you had not.
Surely, you aren't
deaf as well as mute.
She's going to
get herself killed.
Someone should do something.
If you mean interfere with
a Claymore, then you're nuts.
With that Yoma of hers gone,
no one's going to take care
of that kid now.
She might even be
a Yoma herself.
If the witch doesn't kick her
to death, someone else might.
Perhaps next time
you'll listen...
My assignment was to
destroy only six Yoma,
but consider the
seventh a parting gift.
Huh?
Oh...
Be glad...
You've all been
quite fortunate.
I commend you for
keeping up with me
for as long as you have...
But I can't have you
following me any more.
I've already told you once.
I didn't kill those
Yoma to rescue you.
I did it because
it is simply my duty.
I tolerated you in the village,
but you've begun to annoy me.
So if you wish, I can help
you join your precious Yoma.
A Yoma!
Why didn't I sense
their presence earlier?
Humans?!
Don't you dare touch her...
Claymore...
A silver-eyed witch!
Bandits, is it?
You'll find that I have no
possessions worth stealing...
Now you should attend
to this man's injury...
He has very
little time left to live.
His death would create a real
problem for you, am I right?
Imagine my surprise at finding a
Claymore so deep in my forest.
And such an
attractive one, at that.
Boss, this is a silver-eyed
witch that we're dealing with.
You had better
watch your step...
I'm not concerned...
This witch will
do no more harm...
You'll see.
Huh?
All Claymores are forbidden
from killing humans,
accidentally or otherwise.
So don't mistake her
concern for our friend.
She is simply afraid of
being punished for breaking
their most important law.
For such a crime,
she would be beheaded
by one of her fellow witches.
Very little separates these
mixed-breeds from the Yoma.
It benefits them to appear to
have respect for human life.
Without it, who's to say that
they're on our side at all?
Oh, really?
Well...
why should we be afraid of
a such pretty little thing?
If she were to
attack any of us,
she'd be signing
her own death warrant.
And with a body like that...
Sure would be a
shame to waste it...
Is that all you wanted...?
You should have
asked sooner...
we could have avoided
the loss of limbs.
Now will likely be your
only chance to possess
the body of a Claymore.
If it pleases you,
I will travel with your party
until each and every one
of you is satisfied...
Any takers?
I think I'll...
pass.
Damn...
Let's go...
Get Lig back on his feet
and we'll move out.
Come on, now.
You won't get away
with this, Claymore.
I'd run if I were you...
Now go.
For once, you should find a
guardian that isn't a monster.
Don't let me catch you
following me again.
I admire your determination.
But, even so...
Everyone has their limits.
Time to find someone else
to bother, child...
This is goodbye.
I didn't intend to
leave you unconscious
in a strange place...
But you have left me
with very little choice.
What a foolish little human...
If the child dies,
those bandits could easily
trace her back to me.
And I would have
to accept the blame.
Damn...
Even when asleep
the child's a nuisance.
You're lucky to be alive.
The water seems
clean enough for drinking.
Dehydration was as much
the reason for your collapse
as your little
tumble back there.
You're starting
to smell like a corpse...
The scent of Yoma blood
is thick on your body.
It's been making me gag ever
since we left the village.
So scrub your skin
and clothes clean.
I want you smelling like
a flower when you're done.
Look at that...
The villagers were so afraid of
the Yoma that they wouldn't
even wash the poor girl it had
been holding as its captive...
They even feared
the cuts the Yoma left...
And now she will carry the scars
for the rest of her life...
Small reminders of
where trust can lead you.
There's food, as well...
When you're finished,
you can have some of it.
This must be what
owning a pet feels like.
What?
What do you want?
This food is all for you...
I rarely eat that much...
So go ahead.
Don't worry...
I would never allow myself to go
hungry, just for your benefit.
Well...
I suppose I could
do worse for a pet.
Here's the plan...
I can take you with me
as far as the next village.
It's clear that you
would die on your own,
and I cannot be held
responsible for that.
Now get some rest
for the journey tomorrow...
We've got quite
a long hike ahead of us.
You can relax.
I promise not to leave you
while you're sleeping.
I caught a little something
for your breakfast...
Hungry?
I forgot how much of
a pain being human could be.
Having to eat two or three
times every single day
just to function.
What's this...?
Stop that.
Silly girl.
Didn't you hear me say
that I wouldn't leave you
while you were sleeping?
I'm always truthful because I
have no need for deception...
So you can trust me
to speak honestly with you.
Got that?
Why did that laugh
come out of my mouth?
Watch your step.
You'll get yourself killed.
This girl sleeps like the dead.
Not surprising...
The pace we've been keeping is
hardly fit for a small child.
A very unusual girl...
And what remarkable
endurance for one so young.
What is it that
drives her to follow me
with such
stubbornness and resolve?
She could certainly have chosen
a more suitable companion...
Following me will
only bring her grief.
You have chosen poorly, child...
A human would have provided
you with a proper bed, at least.
I can give you
nothing that you need.
But if I am all you have,
then I have to try.
Girl.
It's time to go.
Are you ready?
I can't keep
calling you 'girl...
If you could only speak,
then you could tell me
what your real name is.
Don't strain yourself...
You aren't able speak and
I doubt you know how to write.
So I'll have to come up
with something myself.
Let's see...
I know what your new name is...
-its Clare.
How does that sound?
What?
Are you telling me
that Clare is your name?
It is?
Then it's settled.
From now on, you're Clare.
Clare was one of
the twin goddesses.
She was beautiful,
virtuous, and good.
And her goddess-twin
was named Teresa.
Just like me.
Your parents probably
wanted you to grow up
with the goddess' traits.
I'm sure they
loved you very much.
Don't cry.
Although your parents
are no longer with you,
it doesn't mean their wishes
for you have to die as well.
Now let's move.
Clare.
A woman with a lonely heart...
And a girl with
nowhere to turn...
Two souls become one...
Next time, "Teresa and Clare."