Since the first time we met...
I knew nothing but
suffering from her eyes.
Eyes that could
endure no more...
That screamed for an end
to the anguish and pain.
Good lord!
What's that?
What is she doing?
Teresa always had
that look in her eyes...
The same look
that was in mine.
Please do it!
It's Teresa
flesh and blood...!
Help me- put it
inside me now!
Wait...!
Hey come back...!
There's no reason to
leave in such a hurry...!
Come on!
You're Claymores!
And you must be from Torilo...
So tell me girl
how bad is it in town?
I don't know...
Claire...
these friends of yours?
Interesting.
There were five of them.
It seems that you
fought and killed
four of the
creatures by yourself.
The fifth one escaped and
would have killed a woman
right outside of town
had we not saved her...
So perhaps you'd care to explain
to us what happened here?
I knew you three were
coming from that direction
and could take him...
that is as long as you didn't
take your time getting here.
The organization said
there was a chance that
these were Voracious Eaters
and we were instructed
to wait for them to
gather in the same place.
Then the four of us were
to do the job together...
We were just following orders.
Well, unfortunately
they were just normal Yoma.
I think you mean "fortunately."
If they were Voracious Eaters
then you'd be the one lying
in the street right now
instead of them.
Or was this an attempt
at foolish bravery?
Not really.
I arrived here early and
realized they were regular Yoma.
I then decided to proceed
and confront them head on.
Interesting...
I'm going to inform
the Organization
about your disobedience.
Wait...
you mean you thought
they were Voracious Eaters?
You told me that
they were just normal Yoma.
I did.
Taking them on all
by yourself is crazy!
Clare, you really
shouldn't be so reckless!
Alright Raki...
I'll keep that
in mind for the future.
Well...
I can see that you're
just as careless as ever.
What would you have done if they
really were Voracious Eaters?
Oh, what am I talking about?
You were hoping
that was the case.
Am I correct?
I have to admit
I do admire your courage.
But you have no idea
what you're up against
when it comes to
Voracious Eaters.
That's not true.
I fought one in the cathedral.
Actually that was
just a normal one...
It did need to eat more than
usual to maintain its size,
but it was really
just an underling.
You see we use "Voracious
Eater" as a code word...
Publicly, it's much easier to
explain what those creatures
are by referring
to them as such.
What we're actually
talking about here
are "Awakened Beings."
They are born from the
failures of our own ranks...
Of course as far as the public
is concerned they're just
Yoma who have lived
a very long time.
If you were ever to face
a true voracious eater,
an awakened being,
then remember this...
It is quite certain you'd be
dead in a matter of seconds.
Your lack of faith in my
skills is unfortunate...
Good bye.
It's Priscilla.
You want to take Priscilla's
head, am I right about that?
Well, you'd best
forget that notion.
Because even amongst
awakened beings
she's in the
top of her class...
And her awakening unleashed
all of her latent power.
But of course she
only did so in order
that she could defeat Teresa.
Otherwise there might have
been another outcome.
When it comes to awakened
beings our policy has
always been to treat them
just like any other Yoma...
We are to simply leave
them alone unless ordered
to take them down
as part of a contract.
So what if a job comes in
where we're supposed to
take down Priscilla?
If that were to happen then our
Organization's total strength
would be brought
down upon her...
but only our leader
can decide that.
Don't worry...
our top warriors
are quite capable.
I'm confident
they could bring her down.
Of course every era does
have its heroes you know...
unfortunately,
no matter what you think,
you aren't one of them.
Very well...
I'll add your name to a
team that's been assigned
to an awakened being.
It's a job in the
mountains west of here.
Apparently it's the
result of a warrior who
missed their chance to die...
I believe it will be a
good opportunity for you
to see just how competent
you really are.
Teresa.
So you're supposed to be
meeting in this town?
That's right.
She's really going to fight
a Voracious Eater this time.
You coming, Raki?
Uh...
sorry!
Clare's a great warrior...
she'll be fine.
Follow me.
You're the last one to arrive.
The rest are already here.
I see you brought
the brat with you.
Well, I'm sure
he's not your kid.
What did you do pick up
a stray on your way over...?
Please don't tell me this
little boy is going to be
fighting with us!
No I'm going to
leave him in town...
We'll look for an inn
after this meeting.
I get it now.
He's a little toy
you carry around with you...
Well goodness.
I guess if you're that pissed
off I must have gotten close
to the truth, huh?
You know for such a late comer
you have quite an attitude...
but I guess we're
all a bit on edge
because we had to
wait an entire week.
I'll leave this
argument to you Miria.
That's perfect...
just leave us like this.
Helen and Deneve.
Put them away- right now.
Unbelievable...
First you brazenly
disregarded orders
and now you arrive late
delaying our mission...
You lack much
needed discipline...
However...
we need to get started...
The Voracious Eater we'll be
hunting is on Mount Pablo
just south of here...
We'll be heading out
tomorrow morning...
For now I would like everyone
to introduce themselves
and tells us your rank...
It would also be helpful
to know about any experience
you've had with
Voracious Eaters.
I am known as Miria...
I will be your commanding
officer on this hunt...
I have a ranking of six...
This mission will be my seventh
hunt for a Voracious Eater.
The name is Helen,
my ranking is twenty-two,
and I don't have any experience
hunting these creatures.
My name is Deneve,
my ranking is fifteen,
and I've been on two
other hunting journeys.
So they all have rankings...
I wonder what Clare's is.
My name's Clare...
I have never encountered
a Voracious Eater...
I am 47th...
within the organization.
Huh?
Oh my god!
Did you hear that Deneve?
This one said she was
only a forty-seven!
What were they thinking sending
a rookie on this mission?
Shut up!
What's so damn funny?
Don't you dare laugh at Clare!
She's killed
hundreds of Yoma!
Oh, well I guess she didn't
tell you, did she brat...?
See...
I'd pay attention
if I were you...
The way it works with us is
that we're each assigned
a different territory
within this continent...
Sometimes we get killed and
occasionally will gain new
members but for the most part
our rankings stay the same.
This continent has forty-seven
territories and we are assigned
a number based on
our strengths...
If our number says
how strong we are
and she is forty-seventh
then that means...
That's right.
Out of all of us, your friend
here is the weakest one of all,
hence her ranking
at the bottom.
Oh no.
She's the weakest
of the Claymores.
I'll leave these
with you for now...
You can spend it on whatever
you like while I'm gone.
So how long do you think you'll
be hunting Voracious Eaters?
All things considered
we'll probably be done
in one week's time.
Well in that case I'll just
take these three, k...?
this should be all I
need for a week right?
So you'll be back soon...?
in one week?
That's correct...
You need to
stop worrying so much.
I will be just fine...
and when I tell you
something I need you
to trust me, understood?
What a surprise.
You kept us waiting again.
Let's move.
You've been awfully
quiet today, Clare...
What's the matter?
Are you having trouble
functioning without your boy
to keep you warm?
Let it go.
You would be
wasting your time...
Besides we're all aware that
you're surprisingly weaker
than the rest of us...
save it.
Smart advice...
Helen and Deneve, stop.
I won't tell you again...
Our success on this
mission depends on
how well we work as a team.
Each member is
crucial to our survival.
Oh come on are you kidding me?
She's got the lowest ranking...
the absolute lowest,
it's embarrassing!
Exactly.
It's rare for a warrior even in
the thirties to be assigned
to go after a Voracious Eater.
Luckily, we've got
a 47 with us...
I mean what the hell was
the Organization thinking?
Our superiors decided...
it's not our place to question
them and we won't start now.
Yes ma'am...
I just hope she
doesn't get in the way.
We'll set up our camp
here for tonight...
we should be well within range
of our target by tomorrow.
Okay.
Anyone else dying
for some dinner...?
I guess I'll go try
to find something to eat.
It's amazing.
I don't think I know anybody
that eats as much as you.
When you've got as much Yoki as
I do, you've got to keep eating.
Need anything?
I'm not hungry...
I'm going to rest for awhile.
Well.
Suit yourself then.
I'd like to see you
outside please.
It'll only take a minute.
I challenge you to a
sparring match ...
I just want to get a feel
for everyone's capabilities.
Is my 47th ranking within the
organization not enough proof?
To be honest with you
I'm having a hard time
believing that's your rank...
it doesn't mesh with my initial
impression of your skill level.
When I first saw you
I thought I was looking
at the most powerful
being I'd ever met.
So now we'll see.
Here goes.
Oh!
They're really going at it...
want some?
No thanks.
Wow she's really
quite amazing huh?
You're right.
I can't believe
how amazing she is.
I've never seen anyone
so amazingly bad.
I've seen enough.
Go and get some rest now...
you'll need to recover
your strength for tomorrow.
So what are we going
to do now, Miria?
It really doesn't look
like she's going to
be much help to us tomorrow.
In fact it's gonna take a
miracle for her to survive
just the first encounter.
It's glaringly obvious
that we're going to be
doing all the
fighting tomorrow.
You know that right...?
Do you really want
to take a chance
on such an important mission?
I thought I made myself
clear on this subject.
Our superiors made the call and
we're going to follow orders.
That's it.
Talk about carrying
excess baggage.
What a pain in the ass.
Oh well, I've seen enough...
even if she were to die
of exposure tonight
it wouldn't make
a difference to the job.
Teresa.
Ohhh.
What do you know?
It's still alive.
Look at that.
She was knocked out
the entire night.
How pathetic.
We're leaving, so stand up
and get yourself together.
We're going to go ahead
and take off.
You might want to stay here
if you value living...
See ya around.
Oh great.
I don't know why
she didn't stay behind.
Come on!
You're not really
going to let her fight.
It would be like
sentencing her to death.
I don't appreciate
repeating myself.
Our orders still stand.
Hey!
Over here!
How you doing ladies?
We've been waiting for you
Claymores for quite some time!
Who the hell is that guy?
I've traveled from
the town of Lido...
we're the ones who asked
for you all to come out here.
I tell ya, it's really
great to see that you all
made the journey
out here so quickly.
If you Claymores want
to follow me I'll show you
which direction you need to go.
No!
Miria!
Dammit...
The organization gave us
wrong information...!
We were told that
we would be battling
just a normal
Voracious Eater...
Not something like that!
Do they really expect
the four of us to take on
something of this magnitude?
What is it?
Oh no.
You have got to be kidding me...
A male awakened being?!
Suspicion grows
as the danger rises...
But therein lies the truth...
Next time "Those Who
Rend Asunder Part II"