She focused her
energy completely
on trying to defeat me.
She even allowed
her legs to awaken.
She's amazing.
Well...
I guess that means
you're dead, Rigaldo.
No!
Clare you...
you actually did it!
Amazing.
I knew she could kill him.
She did it...! Deneve!
Miria...! Clare just
defeated Rigaldo!
You're really something...
Always seem to have
a trick up your sleeve.
You guys...
we are gonna be okay!
Come on, this is no time
to be sleeping!
So'd you hear the good news?
Clare just killed that
son-of-a-bitch lion outside!
--Yes!
--She did it!
Yeah Clare, I knew
you had it in you!
So this means it's all over!
Something's wrong.
How in the world did
they manage to defeat
the Silver Eyed Lion
King...? Amazing...
What Priscilla...?
Is everything alright?
Oh children...
such a nuisance.
Clare, stop it...!
That's enough!
I can't...
I can't stop it.
Don't come near me...
I can't control
my own body anymore.
No matter how hard I try,
it just won't let me...
take it back.
Just hang on!
Helen...
I need you to do me...
a favor.
Please, Helen, you have to
behead me, before it's too late.
My body has awakened too far...
There's nothing
I can do about it...
I can't revert...
Please...
Give me an honorable death.
Wait...
Are you sure you've
thought this through?
There's nothing
to think about.
Just do it.
With what little strength I have
left, I will hold my sword
still so you can
finish the job unharmed...
Please Helen.
Clare, listen...
I'm sorry...
that you have to be
the one to end it.
This is bullshit...! You
can't expect me to do this
when we don't even know
if you'll fully awaken!
Do it now...
I'm almost out of time.
God damn it...!
Don't give up yet!
You still have time to revert!
I know my body
better than you...
You have to believe me.
There's no time
for me to revert back!
Fight it.
Brother...
Daddy?!
Don't be so naïve!
If it weren't
for our assistance,
your head would no longer
be attached to your body.
Now Priscilla,
focus all of your power...
and take the life of
this murderous Claymore.
Teresa...? Who is Teresa?
Now then...
Daddy was always
so kind to me...
I loved him so much...
And he ate them.
He made me watch it...
He ate their innards...
right in front of me!
That's when I had
to kill my daddy...
While he was
eating my big sister...
I chopped off his head!
He made me do it!
I can't go back...
Help me please...
You have to...
I don't...
About the best
I can give you...
is a swift beheading...
before you are completely
taken over by your Yoma side.
That can't be...
That can't be me!
Is that it...? All that
fuss--there was no reason
for me to hold back.
And I never realized...
it would feel this good.
I just...
wanted...
to save my sister...
and to...
avenge my daddy!
No!
Now I see...
It's her...
It's all because of her.
God no...
Please, hurry up Helen...
Can't you see I'm
running out of time?
I need you to behead me while
I still have my human mind!
Raki...
I'm sorry I can't
keep my promise...
Of all the people in the world,
I wish I could have seen you
one more time before my death.
Clare...
Fight it...
God dammit Clare...
I can't believe you're making
me do this...! No matter what,
I'm gonna hold this against
you for the rest of my life!
I'm sorry...
Helen.
Helen...
don't listen to her!
Shit!
What is that?!
What...
what's happening?
It can't be!
How is it possible
that you're still alive?
I have a firm memory
of killing you before...
of seeing your head
fly through the air.
Forgiveness is out
of the question...
Not after you defied
the Organization...
And most definitely
not after the hell
you have put me through.
There's no mistaking...
It's her!
That is why I have no choice
but to take your life again...
just as I did before.
You...
you killed Teresa...
I will never forgive you!
Clare, don't go!
Where are you off to?
What the hell
are you doing here?
Due to circumstances...
We are a bit
shorthanded as of now...
The expeditionary force
is in a bind...
Head to the
northern lands at once.
However I want no
intervention on your part.
Reconnaissance only.
If you get involved it will be
seen as an act of betrayal
to the Organization.
It appears as if she
has become awakened...
I assume you know who it is
I am referring to?
Your talents have
never gone unnoticed...
for only you could
know that, Galataea.
Priscilla...
Looks like your
memory has returned...
Today is shaping up
to be monumental...
how fantastic.
You have served me
well my friend...
you may go now.
Save your energy for battle...
I'm having too much fun watching
to join the action just yet.
There's no need for us to put
our lives on the line.
We can enjoy the fireworks
from here a little longer...
I've left the care of our
injured Warriors in the hands
of Cynthia and Tabitha.
What about Clare?
We'll have to try and
follow her Yoki aura...
It may not be
the best approach...
But at this point...
it's all we can do.
Do you really think we have a
chance of catching up to her?
Helen how would you feel if I
told you it was impossible?
I don't care...!
She's our comrade, we can't
just forget about her!
Well it looks like there's
someone else in our group
that agrees
with your sentiment.
I've always been told...
a friend's sword can
act as a grave marker
when the deceased's
is unavailable.
Captain Undine...
Forgive me...
But I have a better use
for your sword.
That's yours, isn't it?
Time to move, Helen.
Right, coming...
Don't try to follow us again.
Are you sure we're
going the right way?
I think...
It feels right.
Damn...
Where are you Clare?
Her Yoki aura almost
feels like its pulsing.
Is it the snowstorm?
Or has Clare awakened...
Look...! Who is that?
It's number three...
Galatea!
I mean no offense, but I think
you three have bitten off
more than you can chew.
So have you come to spy on us?
Perhaps.
Is that a problem?
I'm sorry Galatea but
we're looking for Clare...
we'll fight through you
if we have to.
My...
I can understand one of
you having a death wish,
but all three?
Use your time wisely.
She is at a level where
defeat will not come easily.
Sure she's there?
We don't have time
to be wrong, Galatea.
Getting an accurate
assessment from a Yoki aura...
is something only I can do...
You should know that...
Miria.
And Clare...?
Do you think she can
make it out alive?
Who knows...? I'm only
certain it will be tough
no matter what the outcome.
Well who's she
going up against?
Can you at least tell us that?
Her name is Priscilla...
Teresa of the Faint Smile
was number one...
But she was dethroned from
that ranking when Priscilla
sliced off her head.
What...?! I had no idea.
I would hurry...
if you want to
save your friend.
Understood...
Thanks Galatea.
Let's go!
I know you want
to help your friend,
but crying isn't
going to solve anything.
If we don't hurry, Claire
will most certainly die...
and that's something
neither of us want.
At the end of the day I...
I was all talk and no action.
She saved my life
so many times...
Took care of me
when I couldn't...
but when it came
to helping her, I failed.
Because I was afraid...
I was too scared at the thought
of losing my own life...
I just didn't want to die...
I'm such a terrible,
selfish person.
What's wrong with that?
I'm going...
and I don't care what
the consequences may be.
Why are you doing this?
Because I...
I just want to help her.
Okay...
I'm in.
Wait!
Clare...
Don't go getting yourself killed
before we have a chance to help!
I'm excited to see
what you can do...
Priscilla.
You there...
Standing right
in front of me...
I will never forgive you...
Mark my words...
Priscilla!
Living and dying...
It's all in the past...
with a beautiful faint smile.
Next time on Claymore...
For Whose Sake.