The arts festival's here.
Can you guys believe
it's that time again?
Time for exams too.
The second trimester's
always a pain
'cause there's
too much stuff to do.
This is our last
arts festival in high school
and you're gonna whine
about something like that?
[groaning]
That sign says,
"Opening Ceremony."
Do you guys know
what that's about?
It's a tradition for the
school's Outou Festival.
A group of volunteers has to
come up with the opening act
and perform it.
-[gasps]
-[cowbell rings]
[PATRICIA thinking]
I just had an awesome idea!
All right.
I guess it's unanimous.
We'll have a room where people
can get their fortunes told.
So before next homeroom
everyone needs to decide
what type of fortunes
they want to tell.
-[sighs]
-I'm so touched.
You did your best.
Here's my idea.
We all dress up like
cheerleaders and do a dance.
For what?
For the Opening
Ceremony of the festival.
That's what.
It's the perfect thing to do
if you want to get a lot
of people in the mood
to have some fun.
Yeah, it's over the top,
but it's kinda cool.
I know!
And everyone here's gonna
love the show we put on!
-[GIRLS] Uh...
-When you said we-- wait.
Ah! Don't tell me you've
already signed us up for it.
When I asked the teacher,
I was told
I had to turn in a proposal
along with a list of
all the wonderful people
-who were gonna help.
-[GIRLS moan]
Huh? Ohh.
[gasps] Oh.
So, how about it, Yutaka?
[YUTAKA gasps] Oh, I...
But, Yu-chan, wouldn't it be
a little too physical for you?
-Maybe. Or maybe not.
-[MINAMI gasps]
If it isn't any trouble,
I think I'd like to try it.
-I think.
-It's no trouble.
None of us could imagine
doing it without you,
so welcome to the team!
[HIYORI]
Are you sure about this?
It sounds like it's gonna
be a lot of work and stuff,
and I don't wanna slow
anyone down or anything.
But I think it could be
a really good challenge for me.
Yay! Don't worry
about a thing, Yutaka.
You're gonna be great!
So how about it, guys?
You in?
[BOTH] Uh...
[BOTH chuckle]
Okay then, count me in.
Yeah. I guess
if you're all gonna do it--
You guys are the best!
You're awesome!
[KAGAMI]
Really? Fortune-telling?
Here's a question.
Do you even know
how to tell a fortune?
Hm-mmm. Not at all.
-Ugh!
-For real?
Jeez, wasn't it your idea?
It's an arts festival.
You don't have to be 100%
accurate or anything.
Oh! Hey, Sis,
what's your class
gonna be doing
for the arts festival?
Well, we're sorta doing the
typical haunted house thing.
Cool.
Hmm. How typical.
Well, no one in class came
up with anything better, so.
[grunts] Yeah, what?
Oh, nothing.
Sounds perfect if you ask me.
What's that supposed to mean?
Whoa!
Don't get the monster angry!
I totally knew you'd say that.
Patty-chan told us
she wanted to do
a cheerleading routine.
Yeah?
And then,
I thought it might be fun
if I tried helping out too.
Yeah?
[grunts] Wait, why now?
I guess I've been absent
from school so much
and I never had the chance to
work on any class projects.
But lately,
I've been feeling a lot better.
And I've always wanted to
do something fun like this,
and Patty-chan needs the help.
So, maybe it's a sign
I should do it or something.
Hmm. I don't know.
It sounds like
it could be tough for you.
I know it does.
So Patty-chan was wondering
if you'd help out.
If you were there,
I know I'd feel better.
Please, please, please.
I don't know about this.
But you're really
athletic and everything.
And if you and Minami-chan
are both there,
I know it would help me do the
best I can and keep me going.
You really want me there
and Patty's asking too.
Oh, I gotta think about this.
[groans]
-[phone rings]
-[BOTH] Huh?
Izumi residence.
Good evening, Konata.
Oh, hey, Patty.
I just found out
about that thing,
but I don't know
if I'm the right--
♪ Bum, bum, bum, bum! ♪
Time for a little quiz!
Right now
I'm holding in my hand
a certain ticket to something.
Can you tell me what upcoming
event this ticket's for?
Hmm.
[gasps]
Wait, you're kidding!
Oh, Konata.
I heard you loved
her last concert.
Don't you want to shake
Haruhi's hand?
I know you do.
Yes, I wanna shake her hand!
I do, I do, I do!
I wanna go!
I wanna see Aya!
[PATRICIA] Well,
what were you gonna say
before I interrupted you?
Huh?
-Yu-chan?
-Huh?
[grunts]
Okay, count me in!
Let's go have some fun!
Oh, okay.
So, anyway,
if you aren't a cheerleader,
then you're not cool.
What are you talking about?
Patty was thinking
about putting together
a cheerleading routine
for the opening act
of the arts festival.
Oh yeah, I can totally
see her doing that.
I know.
And it's been decided
you and Tsukasa
are doing it, too.
[BOTH] Huh?
Oh! Can you think
of anyone else in your class
who might be good
at cheerleading?
-Whoa, hang on a sec!
-[whimpers]
Could you at least give us
a minute to think about it?
I don't even think
I can do anything like that.
What?
Come on, you'll never get
another chance to do this.
It's a once-in-a-lifetime thing.
Hmm.
Wouldn't it be fun
to do something like this
with all your friends?
At a festival?
I mean,
the more the merrier, right?
Yeah, I guess.
[groans]
[giggles]
Yeah, count me in.
-[sighs]
-[chuckles]
You're a total pushover,
you know that?
Sorry, but I can't.
I got a ton of stuff
to do for my class.
[crying] It's our last
arts festival together
and I just wanted us to
all be together having fun!
Why do you always
pull out the friend card
when you want something?
I know you're faking,
so stop it!
-[both growl]
-[TSUKASA whimpers]
Yu-chan even volunteered
and she's
really excited about it.
She did?
Is she gonna be okay up there?
I tried to get her
to change her mind,
but I couldn't
talk her out of it.
She's totally excited
about the idea
and said how important it
is for her to do something
special with everyone.
-Oh, really?
-Really.
But they're having a hard time
finding people to help out.
That's why they came to us
to see if we wanted to do it.
I guess I might have been
too pushy a minute ago.
That was totally unfair
and I don't blame you for
not wanting to help us.
[KAGAMI, softly]
I'll do it.
Huh? Wait, you what?
I'll do it!
I said I'll do it, okay?
-[laughs]
-Really, Sis?
Really, you will?
You need the extra help
and my class can always
find someone to replace me.
It's not like I had a choice.
[KONATA giggles, thinks]
Kagami's so cute
when she acts like that.
[MIYUKI]
Ch-- cheerleading?
I honestly don't think
I'd be very good at it.
Well, I'm still not sure
if we've got
everything we need
to pull this off.
[KONATA thinks] Especially
in the volume department.
But I know that if you were
with us jumping around on stage,
we'd be looking fine.
You really think so?
[sighs]
[giggles]
Oh, all right.
If you think I can help,
I'd love to give it a shot.
Oh, awesome!
You're the breas--
uh... thank you.
Seeing how you all
survived your exams,
it's time to get out there
and start preparing
for the arts festival.
And there's
no slacking off, or else.
[KONATA moans]
Great.
It'd be nice if they'd
ease up on the tests
when we've got
all these events happening.
-Hey, what's up?
-Huh?
What's happening
with the cheerleading?
'Cause I haven't heard
anything yet.
Does anyone even know?
Patty was saying...
Hey, they approved our idea!
...before exams started.
But I haven't heard
anything since.
Well, that figures. Does anyone
realize we need to practice
if we're gonna do this thing?
Do we even have time
to practice?
I don't know, ask her.
Sorry.
I haven't had the chance to
figure out the choreography yet.
You gotta be kidding me.
What are we gonna do?
No, wait! It took longer
than I thought it would
to find the right song.
It didn't help that I
was looking for something
-with a "Hare Hare" feel.
-Yeah, whatever.
[sighs]
Look, if you were having
trouble with something
you could have asked
for some help
instead of keeping it
to yourself.
This cheerleader thing
was your idea,
so it's your responsibility
to organize it.
I can't hear you.
♪ La, la, la, la, la, la. ♪
Don't play that game with me!
Suck it up and get to work!
If we're gonna do this thing,
we need
to get organized right now!
Miyuki and I are gonna
find a place to practice
and we'll let everyone know
when and where to meet up later.
You better have some of the
moves figured out by then.
Don't worry
about the rough spots,
we'll fix those in rehearsal.
And next time you need help,
ask somebody! [panting]
-Uh, yeah. So, Kagamin.
-What?
A little while ago
you didn't sound
like you wanted to help out.
So how come you're
all gung-ho about it now?
[grunts] Shut up!
What's your thing
gonna be, Miyuki-san?
I'm going to tell fortunes
with tarot cards.
-[BOTH chuckle]
-And what's yours?
Uh, I haven't decided
what I'm doing yet.
Is there a kind of
fortune-telling that's so simple
even I could do it?
Let me see.
Perhaps you could give
shape readings to people?
[whimpering]
[panicking] The shapes
tell me something about
how your love life
is gonna be awesome
or something like that, I think.
Tsukasa, you don't know
what you're talking about,
-do you?
-What-- what the heck?
[GIRLS singing in Japanese]
You-- you're kidding me.
We're supposed
to learn how to do that?
Don't you think it's cool?
It's not that
we don't like it...
But it looks very difficult.
Well, since we're out of time,
we're just gonna have to
simplify the really hard moves
while we're practicing.
-That's all we can do.
-We're so gonna die.
But if we pull this off,
it'll be the most emotional
moment of our lives!
Put a sock in it!
Uh-oh, we ran out
of masking tape.
[grunts]
I needed a break anyway.
Come on,
we'll go buy some more.
If you're going,
we need some markers.
-And more blades for the cutter.
-And boxes.
-"Playboy."
-Glue.
Okay, somebody threw
something weird in there.
Why's everybody messing around?
If we ran out of supplies,
get off your ass
and go get some!
Do you guys know what
the yakisoba's supposed
to be called?
We're calling that one
Spring's Fragrant Breath.
What's this thing we're calling
the Fallen Drop of Sun's Dew?
Oh, that's okonomiyaki.
This menu's totally insane, man.
How's anyone gonna know
what they're ordering?
Hmm, Japanese culture
is so interesting.
Normally I'd agree with you
but the names of those
dishes are ridiculous.
Yoo-hoo!
So, what are guys gonna
do for the arts festival?
It's called a Zuka cafe.
[stammers]
A what?
It's a cafe where you can
watch a show that's done
in the same style
as the Takarazuka Revue.
You can have a girl
in a glamorous dress,
or if you want, a girl who's
cross-dressing as a nobleman
-serve as your waitress.
-Oh!
-You can have--
-Cross-dressing?
Ah! It's perfect!
Yu-chan and Minami-chan
are gonna be
our most popular servers.
It's a kaleidoscope of beauty.
Who decided we'd be doing this?
Now I'm scared.
I can do the cheerleading,
but this?
Whoa!
Those guys are amazing,
aren't they?
Yeah, I know.
They are totally
in sync with each other.
So tell me something.
Would you say
Miyuki-san is being sadistic
and Minami-chan
is being masochistic?
Yeah, good point.
I wonder if Takara-senpai's
dynamic dance moves are
gonna be too much for
Minami-chan to handle.
-Let's watch.
-Sure, what the heck, right?
Would you guys stop
drooling and go practice?
[GIRLS]
"Lucky Star."
The cheerleading outfits
are here!
[GROUP] Wow!
[chattering]
They turned out wonderfully,
but I don't think I can wear it.
But these outfits are guaranteed
to make the audience happy,
and that's a good thing.
You know it. The outfit
was chosen by a hardcore fan
of all things cheerleadery.
Right, I heard stories
about him.
Your big brother sounds
like a cool guy.
Then the Zuka costumes
are gonna drive you crazy.
I heard you guys are gonna
be doing a cheerleader routine.
[gasps]
[YUTAKA]
Uh-huh.
Can I come down
and take pictures?
[KONATA] As long as you
promise to behave yourself.
[grunts] I'll behave myself.
[KONATA] Well, we haven't
got the moves down yet.
So, I doubt if we're gonna
be able to pull this off.
Don't worry, guys!
I'll give you a dose of Yui
power and you'll be great.
Whoo-oo-oo-oo-oo!
Thanks, but if we did
take some of your power,
it would make us too spazzy
and then we'd wear out quicker.
We're almost out of time
and we still haven't gotten
our routine down yet.
Arts festival, huh?
I can't even remember what
my class did for the one we had.
You know, our class did
something like that too.
I think it's what you guys
call a manga cafe.
Right, I remember.
All the boys in class brought
their manga in that day.
[MATSURI] You guys were
way ahead of your time.
[TADAO] These days you
can bring that stuff to school
and it's no big deal.
But they had strict rules
about it when I was a kid.
Festivals were they only
time we could have them.
Yeah, there are people
who bring manga to school,
but I don't think it's something
the school is aware of.
Oh, are you really
going to tell fortunes?
Make sure you tell all your
classmates that if I show up
they all have
to give me good fortunes.
Well, that really isn't
fortune-telling.
Oh, I've been meaning to ask.
What did you do for your
school's arts festival?
Hmm. I think I remember
every class and club
doing their own
separate projects.
But, you know, in the end,
they were all rather typical
things like haunted houses,
and places that serve
okonomiyaki.
Isn't it odd how the things
you did when you were my age
are the same
as the things I'm doing now?
For example, did you have
an exhibit that focused
on something cultural?
Like the history and craft
of Paulownia wardrobe making?
-[laughs] Seriously?
-[gasps]
Oh, honey, that sounds like
it wouldn't be any fun at all.
You're right, it doesn't.
I know it doesn't.
[KAGAMI] Okay, guys,
let's take a break.
[GIRLS sigh]
We're gonna be so amazing.
I can't wait to see
everyone's faces.
We still have a lot of work
to do before we're ready,
so let's stay focused
and keep working on it,
'til we can do it perfectly.
It's a good thing Hiiragi
is here to crack the whip,
or we'd never be ready in time.
Well, I didn't wanna
graduate without doing
something special with you guys.
[BOTH] Awww!
What are you looking at?
Shut up!
[HINATA]
Oh, no, really?
Sorry about that,
I didn't know.
No worries.
He said today is the rehearsal
day for the students only.
I guess they're still
getting things ready.
And?
And he said that if we're
not actually students here,
we're not allowed
on campus 'til tomorrow.
I told you to make sure
we can come here
before we came
all the way out here!
I know you did,
but I heard that
Akira-chan was going
to be here today.
I'm sorry.
Oh, jeez, what a total
waste of train fare!
We could have bought hamburgers!
I could have had a
hamburger in my stomach now!
[KONATA] Well, for an
unfinished haunted house,
yours is the best
I've ever seen.
Very funny.
What's with that outfit?
You're really gonna
walk around like that?
I'm a walking ad for
our fortune-telling thing.
Well, I think Kona-chan's
costume is really cute.
It's important
to have the right outfit.
I'm gonna tell a bunch
of fortunes today.
You will buy
soft-serve ice-cream
five minutes
and 15 seconds from now.
You will drop it five minutes
and 28 seconds from now.
You're telling fortunes,
not predicting the future.
Cut it out!
Wow, your costumes
look fantastic,
but wait 'til you see
the outfits we put together.
It was cutting it close, but
they got finished just in time.
What do you think?
[giggling]
Wow!
That's so cute.
Those costumes are wonderful.
It's a little
embarrassing walking
around school in this outfit.
-Yeah, I can see why.
-[BOTH gasp]
I mean,
you guys are super cute.
Senpai, it's almost time for
Akira Kogami's show to start.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
This should be good.
My name is Akira Kogami.
It's great to meet you, ma'am.
I'm gonna do the best I can
to entertain everyone today.
Yeah, good.
I'm Sakuraba.
Anyway, today's like some
kind of rehearsal thing,
so take it easy,
and I guess that's it.
Thanks. Oh, and break a leg.
Introduce yourself, Shiraishi.
Oh, sure. I'm Shiraishi,
chairman
of the arts festival committee.
It's a pleasure
to meet you, ma'am.
[SAKURABA]
He's gonna take it from here.
If you need anything,
ask him, okay?
Great, see you.
Thanks!
-[door closes]
-[BOTH humph]
You gonna say something,
or you just gonna stand there?
Huh?
Shouldn't you be
at the monster's meeting?
-What the--
-Is there a problem here?
No, everything's just great.
We just got carried away,
planning stuff
for the show and stuff.
[BOTH laugh nervously]
[door closes]
[BOTH humph]
You're an important guest
for the school, Akira-sama.
And I'm gonna make damn sure
you're treated like one.
Now what?
If you're gonna sing "Misoji
Misaki" in the Lucky Channel
segment tomorrow,
you'll need to do a mike check.
And after the show tomorrow,
you're doing some kind of panel.
Great, that sounds
like a piece of cake.
Then, please head on over
to the stage, thank you.
Yeah, right, you son of a--
-[upbeat music]
-[AKIRA] Nice sign.
Hiya, luckies!
I wanna thank everyone
for coming out today
to see little old me.
Are you guys ready to
have bunches of fun today?
I know you are!
[MINORU]
When will she get to feel
the arms of the man
she loves caressing her?
She wanders the land alone now.
His last words,
her only companion.
Searching for the things
she can never find.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Miss Akira Kogami,
with her version
of "Misoji Misaki."
-[sings in Japanese]
-[MINORU] Okay, cut it!
Let me finish singing, damn it!
It's only a mike check!
Besides we're out of time!
-[AKIRA] Who cares!
-[MINORU] I can't hear you!
[AKIRA] I'm gonna kick
your freaking ass,
you stupid wannabe!
Okay, guys, you ready?
This is our last rehearsal,
so let's get it right.
I never really thought
this cheerleading idea
was gonna turn out
to be anything special.
But I just wanna say I'm
happy I have the chance
to do something cool
with everyone.
Let's not worry about whether
we do it right or not.
Let's just get out there
and have fun.
[static]
[GIRLS sing in Japanese]
[singing continues]
[GIRLS chattering]
[ALL breathing hard]
[ALL gasp]
[GIRLS] All right!
[laughter]
-[GIRLS chatter]
-[GIRL] Oh, it was so much fun!
What's up, you guys?
Why are you all
still hanging around here?
We were practicing
our cheerleading routine.
Oh, is it coming along okay?
[GIRLS giggle]
Guess it's gonna be
awesome then.
How about
you buy us a round, ma'am?
Huh? Okay, sure.
You guys have been
working so hard,
the least I can do is
treat y'all to a drink.
Yes, you're the best.
You really don't mind?
Of course, I don't.
It's my treat, 'cause today
is a special day for you.
But I want you to get that crowd
pumped up for the festival.
Y'all got that?
[GIRLS] Yes!
What's wrong, Tsukasa?
Huh?
[giggles]
Nothing's wrong.
It's just, well,
doesn't everything feel
sort of weird right now?
[MIYUKI]
Yes, it does, doesn't it?
I'm beginning to feel
a little sad myself.
The best part of the
festival is when everyone is
preparing their events
the day before.
I guess tomorrow's gonna
be the real deal, huh, guys?
Yeah, it is.
This is the last time
we'll get to stay here late,
working on projects together.
Kind of makes you feel sad,
if you start thinking about
it that way, doesn't it?
[BOTH sigh]
[YUTAKA] Tamura-san,
you don't look so good.
[HIYORI] It's nothing,
just a little... nauseous.
[KONATA] Tsukasa,
relax, you're all stiff.
[GIRL whimpers]
[KAGAMI]
Speak for yourself.
You don't look like you are
ready to do this either.
They say
the more nervous you are,
the more focused
you're gonna be.
Oh, but I think I'm so
nervous right now, I'm frozen.
-[MINORU] Check, check.
-[GIRLS gasp]
Okay, folks, the Outou
Festival is about to start.
The opening act is something
our exchange student,
Patricia-san, came up with.
-It's a cheerleading routine...
-[GIRLS whimpering]
...by her and her friends.
So put your hands
together and--
[ringtone music]
[MINORU] Could the person
with the cell phone--
whoa! It's mine.
Stop, stop! Bad phone!
[GIRLS and AUDIENCE laughs]
I knew something
was gonna go wrong!
If I keep laughing like this,
I'm gonna pass out!
That was perfect timing!
He needs to get
a better ringtone!
I feel so bad for him.
Well, I guess
I shouldn't be surprised
this happened to us.
I know, that was
totally random, wasn't it?
[MINORU]
And for my next trick--
sorry about that, folks.
What? Yeah, here we go.
Let's try it again.
Here's Patty and her friends
and their performance
of "Motteke Sailor Fuku"!
-[GIRLS giggle]
-[AUDIENCE applauds]
[snoring]
[GIRLS]
Lucky Star.
[MAN singing in Japanese]
♪ So long in my dreams ♪
♪ She's a angel ♪
♪ No, she's a devil ♪
♪ I love you ♪
[MAN singing in Japanese]