[KONATA]
Okay, let's do this!
[MIYUKI]
Sure, let's go!
[TSUKASA]
Grr!
[KAGAMI]
Quit screwin' around and start!
[upbeat music]
Well, starting tomorrow,
you guys get to have
a nice, long break.
Don't forget you're
still students,
and behave like the
good little boys
and girls I know you are.
[STUDENTS]
Okay!
I don't know why,
but you students get antsy
around this time of year.
Then y'all get bored and go out
and cause some trouble.
And as your
long-suffering teacher,
that makes me very worried.
Please behave, and don't
cause any problems.
Got that?
'Cause if you guys get
all delinquent out there,
you're gonna ruin my vacation!
Behave yourselves,
I'm begging you!
[MINORU]
This isn't good.
Yay, we're officially
on vacation now!
And the best thing about it is
the fact that I won't have
to see your face
each and every day.
Come on, sis.
You know, I just
realized that even though
I'm on vacation, I'm still gonna
see our teacher every day.
[KAGAMI]
Why?
You taking an extra
class or something?
No, we're both
in the same party
in this net game.
Yeah, of course you are.
[TSUKASA]
Net game?
Our teacher's a wiz,
and I'm a tanker.
When the two of us
team up, I'm the one
who's gotta pull the monsters.
It's a pretty
sweet deal in terms
of cash and XP.
It's nice, she's got my back,
but I'm always the
one running around.
All she has to do is click
AoE skills the whole time.
Check this out!
The other day,
I pulled a ton of mobs,
but Teach went and fell
asleep at the keyboard.
It took me all day to
get my XP points back.
Ugh, try speaking a
language we understand.
[birds chirping]
Good morning.
I can't believe how
hot it is, can you?
I know, amazing
hair by the way.
How 'bout we turn
the air conditioning on?
Jeez, there you go.
Don't be so quick to
rely on stuff like that.
Use a fan or something
and suck it up.
Here.
Ahh!
You're right, a fan gets
it pretty cool, too.
Yeah, see?
But I'm still hot.
You get so tired fanning,
and you know how when
you stop fanning,
you feel even
hotter than before?
Yeah, well, yeah.
Good try, though.
This is so much fun,
we're all wearing yukatas!
[TSUKASA]
Mm-hmm!
[KAGAMI] Well, I know
it's kinda like cheating,
but our obis are
the pre-tied kind.
They're much easier to put on.
Yeah, putting on
a kimono or yukata's
hard enough, you know?
You have a proper tied-up obi,
don't you, Miyuki?
I'll bet you even
tied it yourself!
Oh, no, actually,
I had the person
at the shop tie it for me.
Tying something
like an obi would
be much too difficult
for me, to say the least.
[laughing] I heard that.
Hey, aren't you wearing
a proper one, too?
I didn't expect that.
Mm-hmm.
[KAGAMI] Did someone at
the store tie it up for you?
Nope, I got my dad
to tie it for me.
Oh, really?
C'mon, let's go!
How come her dad
knows how to tie an obi?
Hey, Konata-chan!
Huh, who's that?
Are you in trouble with the law?
That's Yui nee-san,
she's my cousin.
Nice to meet ya!
[murmured greetings]
I hope you're behaving
yourself today.
Make sure you listen to
what these older girls say
and get home early, okay?
No, no, no, no, no.
Konata isn't an average girl,
we're all in the same grade!
No, all of us are
in the same grade!
Really?
I'm so sorry, I couldn't tell!
I mean, they're so much
taller than, you know.
[laughing] Yeah.
No worries!
[laughing nervously]
I'd tell ya,
kids these days,
you guys sure do
mature awful fast, don't you?
No, like I said, Konata isn't
a normal girl.
We're the normal ones, lady!
Oh, look, it's a
shooting gallery.
Hey, Yui nee-san, I bet
you're good at this stuff.
Well, [laughs] the truth is,
I'm so good, all the
guys back at the station
call me Sharpshooter Yui.
In three seconds, I
can shoot five rounds,
and blast a peace
sign on the face
of a paper target.
[sighs]
Here, show us how
awesome you are.
That's a rifle!
I have to use a rifle?
I didn't know.
I only ever use pistols.
Go, go, shoot, shoot!
Hey!
What's with the
goofy poses, Narumi?
You know you're
still on the clock!
You're on patrol, so patrol!
[YUI whining]
[nervous laughter]
Okay then...
Hey, mister, how does this work?
If we hit a target, can we
pick one of those prizes?
Anything you hit, you get.
It's all good.
Anything?
Yup, anything you hit.
Hmm.
Whoa, lady,
I'm not the prize!
Lower the gun and back away.
At a summer festival, you
can't forget the shaved ice!
It is hot, let's get some!
[KONATA]
Okay, here we are.
I'm lookin' at
all these flavors.
They've got strawberry,
lemon, melon.
Wait, what the
heck's a Blue Hawaii?
What kind of flavor is that?
Well, it's Blue
Hawaii-flavored, I guess.
Of course, I figured
you'd say that.
What do you think, Miyuki-san?
Do you have any idea
what a Blue Hawaii is?
What's a Blue Hawaii?
Uh, lemme see...
Perhaps it's a song,
♪ Blue ♪
No, blue.
I don't really know.
Sorry I didn't know
the answer to that.
I'll look it up when
I get home, okay?
Mm, yeah, sure.
[MIYUKI]
It is possible that--
Yeah, no, the person
who wants to know
should be looking
it up, not Miyuki.
Umm,
I think I might know about
that Blue Hawaii thing.
Hm?
Yeah, I heard
somewhere that the name
and the flavor come from
this blue-colored cocktail.
I also heard that it's
called the Blue Hawaii
'cause it's named after
the movie Blue Hawaii.
So that's where it comes from!
That was a good reference.
Hee-hee.
Man, when Tsukasa's the
one teaching me something,
I end up feeling
like a total loser!
I just noticed I only have
a little bit of money left!
Tsukasa, nothing
is cheap around here.
Think a little before you
spend your money, I swear.
[KONATA]
Come on, Kagami,
it's a festival.
You spend a ton of money here
'cause you get caught
up in the vibe.
Yeah, I guess.
Same thing with Comiket,
you don't think
you're spending a lot
on doujinshi, but that's
the illusion of it!
Then you're like,
"Whoa, I'm broke!"
[KAGAMI]
I'll never understand
the world you live in.
You get up early
to stand in line,
and getting from the west
hall to the east hall
is like a hike and a half.
[KAGAMI] Yeah, I
still don't understand!
Cotton candy's so
fluffy and sweet,
I really love it.
[laughs] You're not
a little kid anymore.
Slow down, or you'll be sick.
I don't know, I never
thought doing that
with another girl
was that much fun.
Don't go there.
Would it be too much to ask
for a little romance
in our lives?
We're at a summer
festival wearing yukatas!
If this was a dating
sim, chances are
one of us would trigger
a flag somewhere.
[TSUKASA]
A flag?
There'd also be
an event scene,
'cause we're outside
wearing yukatas!
Wow, okay horndog, we got it.
[MIYUKI] Is there anything
you wanna play, Kagami-san?
Hmm, now that you mention it,
I'd kinda like to do
some goldfish scooping.
[grunting]
I haven't even tried anything
and they're running away!
Maybe it's because deep
down in their fishy hearts,
they know you're
totally vicious.
The ugly truth has been
revealed at last, mm-hmm.
Ooh, look!
There's one, you see it?
Oh yeah, I see 'em!
Okay.
[yelling in Japanese]
All right!
I got one, I got one, yeah!
Yay, sis!
Don't worry, little guy.
I'm gonna take
good care of you.
Hey, I knew I'd see you guys!
I heard there was
a festival thing
going on around here,
so I thought I'd swing by
and check it out, you know?
I really love festivals!
[KAGAMI]
So, did you come here
with your boyfriend
or something?
[laughs] Of course not,
I don't have a boyfriend!
[KONATA]
There isn't even a tiny bit
of romance for us
anywhere, is there?
[KAGAMI]
Surprise, surprise.
Well, well, we meet again.
Looks like you're having
fun with a new friend.
Howdy!
Huh?
[blinking noises]
Wow, this girl looks like
she hit puberty super early!
Girl?
Nope, wrong,
she's our teacher.
I'm so sorry, I totally
jumped to conclusions
and thought you were
their classmate.
Nah, it's okay.
This is my
cousin, Yui nee-san.
She's a cop, but I guess
you figured that out.
Yeah, and because today's
the summer festival,
they've got me on duty, pounding
the pavement out here.
Can you believe they make
us work in heat like this?
[NANAKO]
Work?
Looks like you're having fun.
Are you working today, too?
You know, like, making
sure your students
don't cause any trouble?
Nah, I was bored, so
I'm just wandering around.
Oh, I'm so jealous!
If I was off duty right now,
I'd be wandering around
and having fun, too!
Looks like you're
already having
enough fun as it is!
So, are you on your own today?
Yeah, just me, myself, and me.
That makes two of us!
Huh?
[laughter]
[ALL]
Lucky Star.
[COOKING TEACHER] I'd
recommend balsamic vinegar,
but if you don't have that,
you can use rice vinegar.
Balsamic vinegar?
Balsamic vinegar.
[laughs] Balsamic vinegar.
You know how during
summer vacation,
you get really,
really bored because
there's nothing to do?
You sorta get used
to being super lazy.
So, if you're
too busy being lazy
and doing nothing,
you won't be asking
to see my homework.
Ah!
I know.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, it's really
cute how it's kinda
pudgy and all rollie-pollie
and everything.
I mean, it totally looks
like a frog, doesn't it?
I know, it does!
Uh huh, oh!
So it's depleted
uranium, that's amazing!
[laughter]
Oh, hey, if I'm on
the phone too long,
I'll get scolded.
Yeah, okay bye!
I was talking to
Kona-chan, and I asked her
why you get bored
during summer vacation.
You know what she said?
Mm-mm.
She said she wasn't
bored 'cause she was busy
playing all the games that
stacked up during school.
I guess some people know how
to have a fulfilling
summer vacation after all.
Maybe I should go
do something, too!
Yeah, well, I
guess that's okay.
But do your homework!
As long as you do that.
Oh man, same old story.
I'm gonna pull one.
De-buff 'em, okay?
Oh, that's cool,
Teach just logged on.
Hello.
You're online a lot, is
it because of vacation?
I have some time, you
wanna go hunt things?
I'm in the cave over
by Chopalan Village.
You got it, I'll be
waiting near the gate.
Huh?
[grunting]
Ma'am, could you not talk about
real world stuff
every single time
we meet inside the gaming world?
Now she's scolding me, just
like Kagami does every day.
Hey there!
It sure is hot out.
Yeah, tell me about it.
Come on in.
Hello.
Hey, you guys got
the fan out today!
Well, like you said, it's hot.
Hang out and enjoy the breeze.
[humming into fan]
Yup, I knew it.
I totally knew you
were going to do that.
Good morning!
Oh, Kona-chan's here.
What up?
Oh, you and your
good mornings.
Do you have any idea
what time it is?
[laughs] Oh well.
Isn't it hot, though?
[humming into fan]
What, you too?
Come on, everybody does it.
Well, I don't do it.
But Kagami, weren't you
doing it this morning, too?
Told ya.
[KAGAMI]
Busted by dad.
It looks like Comp
Fest is really popular.
[TSUKASA]
What is that?
Each time you buy a manga
or one of these magazines,
you get an entry ticket.
Then, if you fill 'em
out and send 'em in,
they'll send you a
limited edition quo card.
Really?
Every time I take my
manga up to the cashier,
it's like I'm
possessed or something.
You were saying
something about
this quo card stuff
the other day.
I swear, the
Japanese are helpless
when it comes to giveaways
and limited editions.
That's why when you
buy something like that,
you always get
one for the vault,
one to look at, and
one to loan out!
Yeah, but you're talking
about how you handle it!
It's not like everybody
thinks the same way as you do.
And sometimes I forget
who I loaned it to,
and then I gotta
buy another one.
So don't forget.
So, do you think
I could take a look
at the you-know-what?
Oh, homework!
Jeez, fine, I'll
teach you all the stuff
you don't understand,
but you're gonna have to do
the rest of it by yourself.
Balsamic vinegar.
Kagami, I don't know this one.
Oh, with a problem
like that, you just...
Kagami, I don't
understand this stuff
from here on down.
[KAGAMI]
Oh, close one.
Kagami--
You're not even thinking
about it, are you?
But I am thinking about it.
Are you really?
Yeah, and I don't
understand any of this stuff
from here on down.
Then you aren't
thinking about it!
She never taught
me how to do these.
It's me!
Came by for a visit.
Yui nee-san, right on time.
Could you show me how
to do this problem?
Huh?
What's that, your math homework?
Sure, I'll help you do it!
Yeah, well, seeing
as how I'm supposed
to be a role model,
you shouldn't rely on
others for answers,
because it won't
do you any good!
Huh?
[beeping]
Homework sucks when you don't
understand the questions.
[laughs] Whether you get
it or not doesn't matter,
just scribble down
whatever seems right.
They just want you to
turn it in on time, see?
Oh, I get it!
Awesome.
But then, this strategy of
yours sorta goes against
the stuff you said before.
If I do it this way, it's
not gonna do me any good.
Yeah, well, that's
how I always did it.
I'm so tired.
I think I'll take a break
and go online for some
hot gaming action.
Half an hour of hunting
should perk me up again.
Half an hour's not
bad, not bad at all.
[clicking]
[incoherent singing]
Oh, a rare drop, no way!
Labatine, I've never seen anyone
with one of those things.
An ultra-rare item!
I got Labatine!
[triumphant music]
Okay, come, come!
I need to try this
sucker out, but where?
Cool, everyone's really excited!
I should go get us some
high-quality potions,
then pass them out
to all the guys.
But I'll need to go
back into town first.
We're gonna get fizzy!
[GROUP]
Lucky Star.
[AKIRA]
Lucky Channel!
Hi, Luckies!
I'm your navigator,
Akira Kogami!
Can you believe it?
Lucky Channel's on
its fifth episode!
And I'm so excited, I
can't hold it in anymore!
Let me introduce my assistant,
who's getting lots of
face time on the show
and getting a big
head because of it!
Nah, I'm just kidding.
The one and only
Minoru Shiraishi!
Clap, clap, clap, clap.
I promise my head's
not gonna get any bigger.
Anyway, folks, it's
an honor to be here,
and I hope I do well.
I'm the assistant,
Minoru Shiraishi.
Now, as you know, we
get a ton of letters
every week from
fans just like you.
Today's hand-picked
letter was sent
by a U.S.S Gatoh in Tokyo!
Is this guy some kind
of [clang] or something,
I mean, he sent in,
like, 50 of those things!
He's probably just some
poor, pathetic loser!
Anyway, here's what
the letter says:
"Big hellos to Akira-san
and Minoru-san.
On Lucky Star, I
always see Konata-chan
go online to play net games,
so I was just
wondering, Akira-san,
do you go online
and play games, too?
By the way, online
I'm what you'd call
a net-gay, but I
don't swing that way
in real life."
Wow!
Someone's got issues!
A net-gay?
What does he mean, net-gay?
Is that short for network game?
I never play those things.
You're better off not
playing 'em, Dorothy.
That was blunt.
Uh, why do you think that?
'Cause there's tons of people
who get so hooked
they totally give up
their lives in the real world.
Betcha didn't know I
used to be that way.
Whenever I had time, I'd log on
and go on these super-long
hunting sessions,
or I'd just PKK some people.
Yeah, but that's
when I was younger.
When you were young-er?
I mean, those terms
you were using,
I didn't understand any of them.
It's better if
you don't know 'em.
Whatever, it's not
like the audience
is gonna understand any
of this stuff either.
Yeah, anyway, you used
to play those things.
Maybe you could, y'know,
share some memories
you might have had as a
gamer with our audience?
Oh, right!
Here I go!
Memories!
When I was just a beginner,
I didn't understand anything
and got into some trouble.
Then these guys who
were experienced gamers
came and helped me out.
Then they pitched
in and gave me lots
of really expensive armor
and super-rare stuff!
I was the happiest
girl in the world!
I'll bet you were.
I had so much fun, I
totally want everyone
to go online and
start playing now!
Oh no, it's time to go!
Bye, nii!
Yeah, well, see ya next time!
So, I guess you're
popular in the world
of online gaming.
Uh, Akira-sama,
something wrong?
[AKIRA]
On page 38, scene 12...
[MINORU]
Uh-huh?
[AKIRA] Who the hell
is Yutaka, dammit?
[MINORU]
You're getting mad about that?
[AKIRA]
My name's Akira, damn you.
[AKIRA] Akira!
[MINORU] Right, I know--
[AKIRA]
Who's in charge?
[MINORU]
Where's the director?
Get the director!
Get the producers!
Akira-sama, you
have to calm down.
--[AKIRA] I am calm.
--[MINORU] I beg you!
--[AKIRA] I got an idea.
--[MINORU] Yes?
[AKIRA] Let's take the
name Minoru Shiraishi,
then we turn it
into something else.
Something like--
[KONATA]
You're so cool, Kagami.
[KAGAMI]
Ah, thanks.
Tsukasa, Miyuki,
who's gonna go next?
[KONATA]
I am!
[KAGAMI]
Again?
Give someone else a chance!
[KONATA]
You can't hesitate,
we're on the clock here.
Time's money.
[MIYUKI]
Sorry, I'm still looking
for a song I know, I'm sorry.
[KAGAMI]
Oh, it's okay.
Let her sing, it's a good way
for us to kill some time.
[pop music]
[MIYUKI]
Oh, I know this song!
[KAGAMI]
I didn't think Konata'd pick
a song from a popular show!
[singing in Japanese]
[MAN] On the next
episode of Lucky Star:
Konata here, when I started
playing Monster Hunter Dos,
the rule was that
you had to defeat
at least five geanos
to use a weapon, right?
So, what did I do?
Yep!
I went back to the village
and had the gathering hall
offer me the quest.
But even after I
defeated the five geanos,
even when I picked all
the snow mountain grass,
even after I got all
that popona tongue,
I couldn't go back
to the village.
That's when I realized I
couldn't access the storage box,
so there I was, getting
boned on reward points,
and it's all because
I didn't read
the user's manual!
I couldn't save any money.
Kinda makes you wonder if that's
how the real world
works, doesn't it?
Next time, fixtures of summer!
[MAN]
Look forward to it!