[KONATA]
Okay, let's do this!
[MIYUKI]
Sure, let's go.
[TSUKASA]
Grrr!
[KAGAMI]
Quit screwin' around and start!
[theme music playing]
'Kay, time to take
your seats, guys.
[classroom chatter]
Happy New Year, everyone.
[KUROI]
Here's hopin' you guys all have
a safe and productive
New Year.
But then again, some of you
will be my responsibility
for only three more months.
I wonder who that could be.
Uh, ma'am, you don't mean me.
I can stay, right?
I believe in that it
feels like a New Year thing.
There's definitely something
in the air.
Yeah, but then
school starts up
and you get
into a weird mood.
It kinda sucks.
There's a weird sorta
something working its power
over the holiday.
You got that right.
'Cause even though I spend my
first three days of the year
working my butt off
for my family,
I gained weight!
[KONATA] That's the magic
of the New Year.
[MIYUKI] You know, it's
harder to burn calories
when it's cold out.
[KAGAMI] It's not like
I was sitting around.
I mean, I was busy doing
all my Shrine Maiden stuff.
Bet you were busy eating, too.
Shrine Maiden New Year's food!
Shrine Maiden zoni soup!
Shrine Maiden snacks,
snacks, snacks!
Shrine Maiden and snacks!
-[KAGAMI] Argh!
-[KONATA] Yeah!
But then, there's the games
you're supposed to play
over New Year's.
You know, stuff like
battledore, Hyakunin Isshu,
and kite flying.
But I never saw anybody play
that stuff over the holiday.
Well nowadays with all
the power lines and traffic,
flying kites can be
pretty dangerous.
I was pretty busy for the first
three days of the New Year,
but after that, I just
read books and watched TV.
Actually, that's what
I did over the break.
I played battledore, Hyakunin
Isshu and Fortune's Smile.
Wow, I didn't think
you'd be into that.
My family tends to be
Western in their ways,
but our country relatives
are much more traditional.
I wore my kimono to
the shrine on New Year's Eve,
and I had a lot of fun
playing games with my cousins.
"Even when the gods
held sway in the..."
[KONATA]
She's way more Japanese than me.
[KAGAMI]
She's more traditional that us!
[KONATA]
What is Fortune's Smile?
Hey, are all of the
100 poems in Hyakunin Isshu
waka poems?
Yes, the first verse is read
and then you have to find the
card with the second verse.
[KONATA]
I bet you're awesome at it.
Oh, no, I'm not as good
as some players.
The really good ones can
grab the correct card
in a blink of an eye.
Yeah, well, with me,
I sorta prefer playing
the kinds of games
that don't make you feel
like you're really studying.
You know, your attitude is the
reason why the future of Japan
is in the toilet.
I know!
We could have battles with
the Hyakunin Isshu cards!
You could summon the power
of the monk Semimaru!
Semimaru's Shining Bright Attack
versus Ono-no-komachi's
Lovely Attack!
Now that sounds like fun.
Going there again, huh?
If you play the game
like that, Kagami,
one that made you move around,
you'd be able to
lose some weight.
Shut up, you!
It's those damn rice cakes.
It's true, rice cakes
are high in calories.
If you have a piece
the size of a matchbox,
it's basically the same calories
as a small bowl of rice.
That means each bite you take
is like a super
huge bowl of rice!
Hold it!
Don't you eat rice cakes?
Yeah, you know,
I grew up without a mom,
so I never really had stuff
like zoni soup to eat.
I don't really eat rice
cakes all that much anyway.
Wow, you don't know
what you're missing!
There a lots of ways
to eat rice cakes.
Zoni soup, shiruko soup,
soy-flavored mochi.
And it sounds like
those rice cakes are gonna
screw up your diet
again next year, Kagami.
Ugh!
I hope you don't mind
me asking, Izumi-san,
but instead of rice cakes,
what does your family
eat for New Year's?
We eat stuff like
pizza and pasta.
Oh.
Our family's New Year always
begins with fresh pasta!
At the end of every year,
my dad goes
and cleans out
the pasta machine.
I bet you guys didn't know
that if you don't use it for
a while, it gets all rusty.
And if you use it without
cleaning it first,
your pasta comes out
all black and stuff.
So me and Dad clean it up and
then we make some fresh pasta
and bake up some
handmade pizza dough.
[MIYUKI]
Ooh, that does sound authentic.
[KONATA]
Unlike Kagami's house,
where the pizza's delivered and
the pasta's the dried stuff.
[KAGAMI]
Ugh!
Yeah, actually, we don't eat
pizza or pasta for New Year's.
No way!
[KAGAMI]
It doesn't work
with a traditional meal.
[KONATA]
It does work.
It goes great
with roasted chicken!
[KAGAMI]
Is that traditional?
[KONATA]
Yeah, it's traditional.
[MIYUKI]
I think that's more Westernized.
[KONATA]
No way, really?
So, Miyuki-san, what food
did you and your family eat
for New Year's?
You wanna know what we ate?
You're a rich girl,
and your family's more
into Western customs.
I can't see you eatin'
rice cakes and traditional
New Year's food.
I bet you ate a full
course of French cuisine
on New Year's Day.
Oh, well that's
not exactly true.
I did eat traditional
Japanese food on New Year's.
In fact, when I took
a bite of rice cake,
I couldn't bite through
and it stretched way out!
[KONATA]
She's a walking Shrine de Moe!
[KAGAMI]
Rice cakes are stretchy.
I can't believe how fast the
New Year's vacation goes by.
[KONATA]
I know, Winter vacation
ends too fast.
Sure, it looks long on paper,
but after doing
the big house cleaning,
writing all those New Year's
cards, and doing homework,
it doesn't leave you with
a whole lot of relaxing time.
Whoa! I didn't get
a New Year's card from you
and you copied
my homework yesterday!
Uguu...
Did you have your first
dream of the year, Kona-chan?
Huh, oh, right.
You're supposed to have
good luck if you dream
of certain things.
[TSUKASA]
Mmm-hmm, yup.
Yeah, usually they say it's
one, Mt. Fuji; two, hawk;
and three, eggplant.
I heard that they've
extended the items on that list
to four, a fan; five, tobacco;
and six, a blind musician.
[TSUKASA]
Wow, the list
goes up to six now!
Yeah, you know,
does anybody really
dream about that stuff?
I mean tobacco, eggplant,
a blind musician?
Tell me about it.
Do you have to see all
those things in the same dream
or something?
I suppose if you saw
them all in one dream
you'd have tremendous
good fortune.
However, you only
need to see one.
Oh, I thought you
needed to see something
like two hawks or three
eggplants in a dream.
Hate to be the one to say this,
but I don't remember
most of my dreams.
I think people who obsess
over stuff like that
are having way too much fun with
the whole New Year's thing.
[KAGAMI]
That's true.
In my first dream of the year,
when I opened my shoe locker,
my shoes were missing!
Imagine, but someone
else's shoes were there,
and since I needed to go
home, I tried to put them on.
Unfortunately, the shoes
were the wrong size.
Hmm.
Later, I looked up
the meaning of my dream
in the dictionary of
dreams and fortune telling.
A dream
is a subliminal message,
and according to the dictionary,
I'm seeking social skills.
And it will be a long time
before I can attain them.
Apparently, whenever
you see shoes in dreams,
it's supposed to mean
social status.
Shoes are social?
Uh-huh.
So you're ambitious,
Miyuki-san.
I kinda get it,
but sorta don't.
Heh-heh.
[yawning]
Did you guys hear what happened
at this year's
Coming of Age Ceremony?
A bunch of people
rushed the stage
and started causing trouble.
Don't they have any shame?
I mean, they're supposed
to be representing Japan.
Why bother going if you're
just gonna get kicked off?
That's what I'm saying.
The Coming of Age Ceremony's
so boring.
I don't wanna go, do you?
[KAGAMI]
She's on her way to becoming
a good-for-nothing adult.
So what are you guys gonna wear
to the Coming of Age Ceremony?
Hmm, since it's a
once-in-a-lifetime thing,
I'd wear a long sleeve kimono.
Now that you brought
it up, what about you?
Yeah, well, knowin' my dad,
he's gonna want me to
wear a long sleeve kimono.
He totally would, wouldn't he?
[cheer]
Although, if you wore one,
you'd look like a kid
celebrating your
seven-five-three!
Guh.
Happy New Year, and
hope it's a good one!
Happy New Year
to you too, Onee-san.
You haven't come by in a while.
Well, with my hubby coming home,
and all the New Year's
stuff that needed doing,
and my little sis caught
a fever too, so...
Yeah, she's frail, isn't she?
I mean, that's not an excuse!
I wasn't trying to
weasel my way out
of giving you all you New
Year's cash or anything, really!
[KONATA]
I didn't even ask,
and she blows her cover.
Rookie move, officer.
[TV ANNOUNCER]
In other sports news today,
there was
a Hyakunin Isshu tournament,
and it was
an awesome turnout.
[KONATA]
Oh, that reminds me!
When you were a little kid,
do you remember
what kind of stuff
you did on New Year's Day?
Hmm? On New Year's?
Let's see, I'm pretty sure
I did something, I think.
Yeah, like, um...
[beeping]
[KONATA]
Dot, dot, dot, dot.
Sorry, brain fart!
I totally forgot.
[KONATA]
Man, she lives in
her own little world.
I don't think I'll ever have a
normal conversation with her.
I blasted all the memories
behind me!
[cat yawning]
[GIRLS]
Lucky Star!
[shivering]
You know,
Tsukasa's been holed up
under the kotatsu lately.
It's been cold though.
[KAGAMI]
I know.
[KONATA]
The kotatsu's awesome,
but when you're under it,
getting up to go to
the bathroom's a drag.
[TSUKASA]
Yeah, right?
But you don't have to say it
out loud like that.
[KONATA]
My dad's got
a killer line he whips out
whenever I've been sittin'
under it for too long.
[TSUKASA]
Really, what does he say?
Hey, Konata,
if you're gonna live
under that kotatsu all day
long, I'm puttin' it away.
Ugh!
[KAGAMI]
So he doesn't mind
not having it out?
[KONATA]
No, he loves it!
He just wants to
teach me a lesson is all.
If we've been sittin'
under it for a while
we both fall asleep.
[TSUKASA]
Oh, I know!
But I heard that if you
fall asleep like that,
you'll catch a cold.
[KONATA]
Yep.
If I catch us sleeping,
I always try to turn it off.
Yeah, those kotatsus are like
a mixture of heaven and hell.
[TSUKASA]
Uh, how?
[KONATA]
Because right before it goes on,
and after you've turned it off,
it feels even colder than ever.
Mm-hmm, you're right,
it does, doesn't it?
Isn't it hard to get out
of bed when it's this cold?
[KONATA]
Yeah, oh,
and when you take a bath
and that time it takes
you to get undressed
and jump in the tub's awful!
Makes you think twice
about runnin' bare naked.
[TSUKASA]
Yeah, 'cause it's slippery.
Oh, and when it's late and you
need to go to the bathroom,
don't you hate that?
[KONATA]
Yeah, brr!
Come on, guys.
We gotta get off.
When you get off the bus
till you get into class
is hell, too.
Yeah.
It's almost Valentine's Day.
It gets more exciting around
this time of year, doesn't it?
It's funny how
everyone walks around
acting like Valentine's
is no big deal,
but secretly, they're
all anxious about it.
Wouldn't it be wonderful
to have someone
special on that day?
Someone to share
your feelings with?
I think that would be
the best thing ever.
Ah, Tsukasa, you're
a hopeless romantic,
and I won't say
it's a conspiracy
invented by the candy industry.
Now that you mention it,
this time of year's special
for someone like me, too.
Why?
'Cause the leftover chocolates
always go on sale afterwards
so I can buy a lot for
cheap to make my own.
You really have no
dreams at all, do you now?
They say,
"Money can't buy you love,"
but when you think about it,
Valentine's Day chocolates
are a way to show your love
and you buy it with money.
That's a cold observation,
considering the only romance
you've had has been in games.
Yeah, well in games,
the whole idea's
to get your
relationship level up.
That's way more important
than the actual day.
[KAGAMI]
Okay.
Yeah, well Valentine's Day's
just another day to me.
It's only an excuse for
the boys to get all weird.
Guess no one triggered the
Kagami flag again this year.
Oh yeah?
You got anything goin' on?
All kinds of people love me.
In your game, yeah, we got it.
You know, I worry about
you with all your talk
of relationship levels
and flags and stuff.
Don't you feel like
you're sort of missing out
if all you do is limit yourself
to the world in your games?
Ugh.
I really hate it when
people talk about stuff
they don't know anything about.
Huh.
You saying I'm wrong?
In game time,
events happen pretty fast,
so when you're playing and you
come across Valentine's Day,
it's usually over
before you know it.
[KAGAMI]
So what?
This year's Valentine's
Day is different.
I wanna give some
chocolate to someone.
You're kidding, really?
Mm-hmm.
It's someone who's playing
the same online game as me.
One of your gaming buddies?
Mm-hmm.
You're gonna hand it
to him in person?
Uh-uh, we're not gonna
be seeing each other
in person-person.
[KAGAMI AND TSUKASA]
Huh?
It's all gonna happen in game.
I mean, we're both human
behind our characters,
so what's the difference?
But does that even count?
In the end, it's just
a character in a game.
Hey, don't insult
my wife like that!
[KAGAMI]
Huh, wife?
Mmm.
In the game,
I play a male character
and I'm married to her.
Uh.
Whoa, in the game the guy's
giving the girl chocolate.
But you're really a girl,
so that means
you'll be giving
another girl chocolate?
'Cause the other person's
a girl, right?
On the contrary, my
wife's a guy in real life.
[KAGAMI AND TSUKASA]
Huh?
[computer processing]
[KAGAMI]
Oh, whatever.
As long as everyone's cool
and having fun, it's all good.
[TSUKASA]
That's right!
I think I wanna go overseas.
Wow, that came
outta nowhere, didn't it?
Well, yesterday,
Miyuki-san told me...
Women giving chocolates
to men on February the 14th
is a tradition that's
exclusive only to Japan.
In Western countries,
people give candies and cards
to friends and loved ones
regardless of their gender.
Really?
That's exactly what she said,
so that means that even
a girl like me could give
a whole bunch of candy!
[KAGAMI]
That's one way of looking at it,
provided you're
as popular as you think
and not just overconfident.
Oh, it's okay,
'cause in other countries,
small girls--
Wow, stop!
Let's keep it G-rated, okay?
[BOY]
Uh, you're rad!
Happy Valentine's Day,
Kona-chan.
This is for you!
Wow, awesome wrapping,
for a uniform,
and the inside's all
heart-shaped and everything!
I put a lot of work into it.
Uh, Tsukasa gets pretty
elaborate with stuff like that.
She was up all night
making those,
and they're only
friendship chocolates.
[KONATA]
Even if these are
friendship chocolates,
don't give them out to boys.
They'll get the wrong idea.
Huh, what?
Huh?
For you, enjoy.
Kagami, you're giving
me chocolate?
I only made 'em 'cause
she was making some, too.
Don't be such as spaz.
Oh.
The fact that you worked
so hard on making this,
even though you suck at cooking,
totally turns me on, Kagami.
Did you know that?
Oh, shut up and put it away!
Huh?
Kagami?
Here, I made this for you.
Don't get the wrong idea.
It's friendship chocolate.
Friendship, got it?
I'm sorry if they look
all weird and everything.
[BOY]
Don't be a fool.
I don't care
if they look funny.
The important thing's that
you made it for me, Kagami.
Whoa, don't be stupid.
It's nothing like that.
Really, it isn't.
Is that what's goin' on?
No, so shut up and put it away.
[BOY]
It's my first time.
[BOY 2]
First time's the best.
Hey, Miyuki-san, did you
give chocolate to anyone?
I gave some to my father
and also to a male relative.
And I gave chocolates
to pretty much everybody
who's friendly to me.
And I gave some to you,
Tsukasa, and Miyuki.
Come on, did everyone have
the boringest
Valentine's Day, or what?
You live in an online game,
so zip it.
[light guitar music]
You said your cousin
was applying to Ryoo.
What happened with that?
She got accepted.
And since she lives far away,
she's gonna stay at my place
starting next month.
She's always been
like a little sister,
and we've been talkin' a lot
about her moving in.
That's awesome!
But compared to you,
isn't it gonna be hard
to tell which of you
is the little sister?
You don't get it.
When I say she's little,
she's little, like way little.
[KAGAMI]
She's that small?
That fact she got
accepted without any hitches
must mean she's super smart.
Well, someone's
sounding confident today.
The school accepted you,
didn't it?
Yeah, but I barely made it.
It still counts though.
I just remembered--
we have to take
our college entrance exams
next year.
Oh brother, we're gonna
be studying forever.
That's gonna be nasty.
Oh no.
Should I take the exams?
I don't have any plans
for the future.
You really need to start
thinking about your future.
Hmm, "academic"
and "labor" are words
that just don't exist
in my vocabulary.
[KAGAMI]
I wonder what someone like her
could do for a living.
She could design games, 'cause
that's her hobby, anyway.
She could make her own manga
and sell it at Comiket.
She's naturally curious,
so she could be a reporter.
No, maybe she becomes a writer
who writes
for a specific genre.
She's good with computers,
maybe a web designer?
Or a screen writer, who
writes about random things
that don't have a plot?
Or she goes to college.
Or, maybe it's all
the same damn thing!
What?
Hmm.
Hmpf!
[gasps]
What's up?
She's here.
Boss, it's really her,
the Legendary Girl!
Ay!
What?
We let her get away
from us last time.
-[MAN] Boss!
-[GIRL 1] Boss!
[GIRL 2] Boss!
But not today!
We'll do everything in
our power to make sure
that the the Legendary Girl A
gets to the cash register!
[KONATA]
Hmm.
Giro, she's having
a hard time deciding.
Hahaha!
Then it's up to us
to make her purchasing
decisions for her!
All right,
people, you ready?
[ALL]
Yeah!
[GIRO] Say what?
[GIRO]
Say what?
[ALL]
Yeah, you know it!
[KONATA]
Hmm.
I have a visual, boss.
I'm gonna try to figure out
what the Legendary Girl A
is looking for.
I'm counting on you.
What's the newest manga?
It's Sergeant Frog,
volume 14, sir!
[GIRO]
Perfect!
Make sure you display them
in the Legendary Girl A's
line of sight!
Deploy the flyers!
Tama!
[GIRLS]
Locked and loaded, sir!
[GIRO]
Good.
Keep an eye on her movements.
Make sure our best sellers are
flanking the Legendary Girl A
as she approaches the register!
[GIRLS]
Roger!
[GIRL]
Sir!
[KONATA]
Eh.
Ugh!
The Legendary Girl A is
not looking for a manga,
repeat,
not looking for manga!
What?
Boss, she's headed
for the DVD section.
Fantastic!
I want blockades up on
both sides of the aisle.
We're gonna funnel
the Legendary Girl A
straight into the new releases.
[GIRLS]
Roger!
[GIRL]
Sir!
Oops, sorry, am I in your way?
Tama, tama?
Oh, I'm so very sorry!
[grunting]
[singing in Japanese]
That a girl.
Ugh!
Boss!
Finally, we got her!
She's gonna buy something!
I did it! I won! I beat her!
We're gonna party like rock
stars tonight, you hear me?
-Woohoo!
-[GIRL] Woohoo, Sir!
[KONATA]
Huh.
She faked us out!
Agh!
[KONATA]
Oh!
Ugh, this calls for
my secret weapon.
Bring me that
ultra rare, out-of-print,
bargain bin DVD, girl.
Boss, she's
headed straight for you.
Yes, that's it.
This is so beautiful,
I never want this scene to end.
The entire U.S. of A
inside me is all cheering
and applauding!
[GIRLS]
Yay for us!
Yay, sir!
[beeping]
1,785 yen, please.
[whimpering]
Huh?
Darn it, I'm short three yen.
[exasperated gasps]
Oh well.
Could you guys
put it back for me?
Thanks.
[gasping]
[screaming]
Foiled again!
[snoring]
[GIRLS]
Lucky Star.
[AKIRA]
Lucky Channel!
Hiya, Luckies!
All righty, let's get this
thing movin' already!
I can't believe Lucky
Channel's on its 13th episode.
Isn't that amazing?
I'm your navigator,
Akira Kogami,
but you guys knew that
already, didn't you?
I bet you did, a-ha!
Nice to see you again!
I'm Minoru Shiraishi,
Akira-sama's faithful assistant.
Isn't this great?
We're on our 13th episode,
and that means
we're in our second season.
In fact, getting
this far is a lot like
reaching the halfway station
on Mt. Fuji,
isn't that right, Akira-sama?
Huh?
You can get to the halfway
station by car, you idiot.
Well, of course you can,
I was just saying.
Oh, that's right.
This one time, I climbed
to the top of Mt. Takao--
What are you, blind?
Aren't you gonna say anything?
-Right. I though of...
-D-d-d-d-d-d-d-drills!
Oh my, Akira-sama, those
twin drills you're sporting
are really cool!
What's so cool
about 'em, slack jaw?
Well, they're all wound up
like a couple of seashells?
Huh?
-Oh, my god.
-D-d-drill.
Oh, that's right!
Today we're
announcing the results
of our very own Lucky Star
Action Figure Project!
Akira-sama, if you'd be so
kind as to announce the winner.
Konata Izumi gets her
very own action figure--
Akira-sama,
read it properly!
Congratulations, woohoo!
Ugh!
Was there any doubt she'd win?
This thing was rigged
from the beginning,
so basically the radio show
and the LC aren't important,
is that it?
Oh, sure, it's all about
the main segment.
You got it all wrong.
We're important, aren't we?
Mmm-hmm.
You see, the producer
says we're important!
There it is!
Yeah, yeah.
Whatever, I'm used to getting
bent over all the time anyways.
I don't really care anymore.
Bent over is not a very
nice way of putting it.
Yeah, bet you're
all torn up about it.
And next, you're gonna
tell me that they made
an action figure out of you,
isn't that right?
No, of course not, God forbid!
Any crap, Konata Izumi gets
her very own action figure,
and as a booby prize,
Minoru Shiraishi gets one, too.
You've gotta be
freaking kidding!
Ugh! Not good.
[game show music]
Oh, it looks like
our time's up for today.
Keep sending us
your comments, questions,
and any good things you might
have to say about the show.
You can use our
homepage if you want
or you can send your letters
the old-fashioned way.
Right, Akira-sama?
I'm going.
Whoa, wait a second!
Bye-ni!
Akira-sama, wait up!
[AKIRA]
Okay people, listen up.
[MINORU]
D-drill!
[singing in Japanese]
[laughing]
[alarm]
[sparkling]
[GIRL]
On the next episode
of Sergeant Frog...
[MAN]
No!
Say, "On the next episode
of Lucky Star!"
[MAN 2]
Giro, Giro.
Sir, I just thought
of something awesome.
Did you know that anime
is a global industry?
We could use it to
brainwash the Pekoponians
and complete our invasion
of Pekopon in no time!
[GIRL]
Oh, Sarge, you're so smart!
[MAN]
Ha, pathetic.
Why don't you
act like a soldier
and crush them
with brute force?
[MAN 2]
Shut up, you red daruma!
[MAN]
Ugh?
[MAN 2]
These days,
the one with the information
wins the war, but seeing
as how you're so old,
you probably don't get it.
[MAN]
Watch your mouth, damn you!
[MAN 2]
Yeah, whatever.
Next time, under one roof!
[GIRL]
Look forward to it!
[MAN 2]
Gi-Giro!