[KONATA]
Senior year, Class B...
[ALL]
Ms. Kuroi!
[KAGAMI]
Yeah, yeah.
[singing in Japanese]
Hey, Kagami. Do you like
those chocolate wafer thingies?
Sure I do. Why?
I knew it. Then these
are for you. Enjoy.
[KAGAMI]
Oh, thank you.
Wow!
I love these things!
I've got more if you want. Here.
[gasping]
[KONATA]
And there's more
where that came from,
so dig in, guys.
Whoa, hang on. What's with you
and all the wafers?
[KONATA]
Yeah, well,
they come with toys, so I have
to buy the wafers by the case
in order to get the toy I want.
Oh, that figures. I should've
known you'd be the type
to ignore a perfectly good
snack for a cheap toy.
Hmmm. A fox.
And you're a squirrel, a dog.
Huh?
Okay, now what are
you talking about?
Oh. I was just thinking
about what kind of animals
we'd be is all.
Since I'm kind of
a prankster, I'd be a fox,
and Tsukasa sort of has
a doggy vibe.
Yu-chan's got the cute
rodent thing happening,
so she'd be a squirrel.
Yeah, I can see that.
I bet next you're gonna say how
I'm like a tiger or wolf, right?
Hmm? Nah, I picture you
as a rabbit 'cause you're
always getting lonely and stuff.
Besides, your pig tails look
like ears.
Okay, that visual is
totally embarrassing.
Could we talk about
something else now?
That's so funny. I wonder
what everyone else would be.
Yui Na-san's always running
around, so she'd be a leopard.
And Iwasaki-san's so cool
and awesome,
I think she'd be a hawk.
Yuki-chan's got that
fluffy feeling about her.
Kind of fumo-fumo, so I
picture her as a sheep.
Hmmm. I hate to disagree
with you,
but Miyuki-san's more of a cow
type. Especially with those.
You're like a pervy
old man.
[birds chirping]
So we were hanging out
at Konata's yesterday
and found some of her old
journals from elementary school.
Oh! That sounds interesting.
Strange is more like it.
I mean no offense, Konata,
but I never figured you'd
hang onto stuff like that.
Dad always told me
to keep that stuff
'cause you never know. You know?
If you think that's surprising,
check out what she wanted
to be when she grew up.
Our girl here wrote about how
she wanted
to be something normal,
like a vet or a lawyer.
They are noble professions.
Yeah, but it's the way she
changed her dreams every year.
That's totally Konata.
It's weird how when I go
back and read my old journals,
I can tell what games
and manga I was into.
[sighs] Okay. Games and
manga. We always end up here.
It could be worse.
You could be one of those people
who say being a bride
is their dream job.
Hello? That's not a job.
[giggling] That sounds
really cute, though.
Yeah. Tsukasa, the truth
is, I was talking about you.
Huh? Really? Are you sure?
[KAGAMI]
Positive.
You're what they call
an airhead.
A lot of airheads don't
realize they're really airheads.
It seems you may
be right about that.
[KONATA]
Oh, Miyuki-san.
You've just proven my point.
What? Do I have something
on my face?
Hey, Miyuki-san,
how bad's your eyesight
without your glasses?
It's way under 20/200.
Oh, is that so?
You know, I heard somewhere
that eating blueberries was
really good for your eyes.
Oh, they are. You can also eat
carrots,
which contain vitamin A.
And green leafy vegetables
like spinach are good.
There's also pork,
which contains vitamin B.
And foods like liver and sesame
seeds, both rich in protein,
are also good things to eat
to help maintain good vision.
Or there's also
the option of Lasik treatments,
which are popular.
[KONATA]
Oh.
The thing is,
I lack the courage
to go through
an ordeal such as that.
Although
the vision training programs
I've seen on TV sound
quite promising.
Wow. You sure know a lot,
don't you?
Well, those are just a few
of the many options out there.
So, if you know about all this
stuff,
how come your eyesight's not
any better?
Oh! I guess I just never got
around to trying any of it.
Oh, yeah? Why not?
I'm sorry. I don't know why.
It's never too late to start,
right?
Why don't you try
the vision training thing?
I suppose I could.
Okay, let's see. First,
you close your eyes.
Then you open them quick.
The trick is
to keep your head still.
Then you look to the left,
and then to the right,
without moving your head.
Miyuki-san! Your head, it
totally moved when you looked!
Really? Oh, oh, dear.
[MIYUKI] How strange.
[KONATA] Whoa. Easy now, girl.
My eyes are tired now
than before.
[sighs] I hope it didn't
make your vision worse.
[bells ringing]
Hey, Kona-chan?
What does "moe" mean?
Hmm. How does one
define something like that?
Uh. How?
I know you definitely
use that word to express
how much you like something,
but I don't have a
solid definition for it.
Hold it. How can you use a word
and not know what it means?
All I can say is that
the only people
who really understand what
"moe" means are
the hardcore-iest
of hardcore otaku.
Not that it matters much,
but I actually think
I sort of know what you mean.
[MAN ON TV]
We're gonna check out doggies
from around the world!
Daffundah!
Puppies are so cute,
aren't they?
Wouldn't it be super neat if we
got a dog?
Hmm?
Whoa. Slow down, Tsukasa.
You better think about
what you're asking for.
Will you be able to
take care of it?
You know, train it, walk it,
feed it.
Are you still going to think
it's cute when it grows up?
And are you even mature
enough to take care
of a living being?
Yeah. You're right, sis.
I guess it's something I need
to think about a little harder.
It's good that you know what
it's like to have a dog.
Oh, well, well, not really.
I mean, what do I know
about having a dog?
I just looked it up is all.
Oh, come on now! You said
you liked this artist, right?
Just give it a shot!
Jeez, okay,
but you're too close.
And you're freaking me out.
[sighs]
[giggling]
[KAGAMI]
Staaaaaaaaaaaaare.
Staaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaaare.
Okay. What is it?
Oh, nothing. I was just
wondering how far you got.
Has a character called Osano
showed up?
No, I haven't reached
that level yet.
Well, go on, hurry up,
keep reading.
There are so many elections
going on right now.
That really blows.
You think so?
What's with the gloomy
look on your face, lady?
You should be studying
for your college entrance exam.
Oh, ma'am, I was just
saying how it sucks
to have all these elections.
The heck are you talking about?
I'm talking about how
the regular shows
get shuffled around 'cause
of all the election coverage.
I mean, the other day,
this one show got
pushed back four whole hours!
And they always interrupt
the regular broadcast
with election updates! And
that L-shape thing they use
makes the screen way smaller!
Hold on there, missy. That
awful election programming
helps you keep up on your
current events.
There's other things besides
anime.
Besides, elections aren't the
only things throwing programs
out of whack. Look at K-1.
They're always kicking shows
to the curb to get on the air.
I mean, come on, I thought
you liked martial arts.
[KONATA]
I've got experience,
but I really don't like
it that much.
[KUROI]
But even anime shows
have special programs,
don't they? My honey!
[KONATA]
But they don't run into overtime
and cause problems for
the show that comes after it!
[KUROI]
But kids facing
college entrance exams
shouldn't worry about that!
They should study!
[KONATA]
It comes down to
a power attack after all!
[rain falling]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Kona-chan's stuck 'cause she
didn't bring an umbrella today.
You could at least watch the
forecast.
Maybe I should just walk
home and not care if I get wet.
You know, like all the guys do.
[giggling] I always wondered
why all the boys never cared
about getting wet in the rain.
'Cause they don't have to worry
about their bras showing
through.
You're so smart.
Okay, you got a point.
But you don't have to
broadcast it
to the whole school.
Ever hear of modesty?
Could either of you hook
a girl up with an umbrella?
Tsukasa and I are both
going straight home now,
so I guess we can get
by sharing an umbrella.
Ah, you guys are the best.
How come you don't keep
an umbrella in your locker?
You know, to keep
your books company.
Well, it's funny you
should mention it,
'cause I did used to keep
an umbrella in there.
But I had to use it one time,
and then I forgot to
bring it back the next day.
It's not like umbrellas
are part of my daily routine.
With an attitude like that,
go figure you'd forget.
Wait up, Suzume! I said wait!
That reminds me. Whenever
I'm wearing rubber boots
and a raincoat,
I always think about
how dorky I must
look to everyone.
Yeah, I know.
You feel sorta immature
wearing stuff like that.
[KONATA]
So how come when you see it
in art and stuff,
it gives off this "moe" vibe?
Like I would know.
[meowing]
[GIRLS]
Lucky star.
Oh, hi-ya, Konata. What's up?
Good morning!
Hey, Tsukasa,
what's with the sad face?
Oh, this month's
cell phone bill was really high,
so I got scolded for it.
You should try my method.
I hardly ever use my cell phone,
so all I pay is the basic rate.
Oh, I see.
It's way more economical.
Okay, how is it economical
when you're paying
the basic monthly rate for
a cellphone you hardly ever use?
That sounds like a waste
of money.
You really need to stop sweating
the small stuff, Kagami.
[phone vibrating]
Oh, a text.
"Could you please pick up some
eggs on your way home today?"
[typing] "Don't worry, I will
"go to
"the store with sis
right after school today."
There! [giggling]
Let me guess.
That was a conversation between
you and your parents?
It's funny how when
you're texting your parents,
you can't help but speak
politely.
Yeah, I sort of get
where you're coming from,
but trust me, that'll change
once you get used to it.
Mm-hmm.
How long have you had
your cellphone anyway?
For about a year now.
And when do you usually
replace it with a new one?
I heard you're supposed
to do that every two years.
They say that's when your
battery starts dying anyway.
Then I'll make mine last twice,
no, I'll make it last three
times as long. I swear it!
Why are you spazzing out again?
I'm just saying I take super
good care of all my stuff.
I make everything last longer.
Especially when you don't
use the stuff you have.
I guess some people
are like that.
They splurge on all their
hobbies,
and they're stingy
with everything else.
Sorry to bother you, sis.
May I borrow your
world history textbook?
Again?
Oh, man, you are so helpless.
Here. And try not to forget
your book next time, okay?
Okay. [giggling]
I'll bring it back later today.
I guess your sister can be
pretty careless sometimes, huh?
Yeah. I guess that's all
the more reason
why I have to be the responsible
one in the family.
Hmmm. Yeah, but is
that good for her though?
I mean, if you're always
there to bail her out,
there's no reason for her
to act any different.
So it's because of you
that your sister's
the way she is, Hiiragi.
[KAGAMI]
Huh. She does have
a point there.
I wonder.
Hey, Hiiragi, what time is it?
I don't know.
The clock's right there.
Oh. There it is.
Ah! The legend of your
morning temper is for reals!
Oh, come on. I dropped it
and a little piece broke off.
Reading manga's nice, Tsukasa,
but try to read
a newspaper once in a while.
You'll learn a whole lot
about the world around you.
Okay.
[KAGAMI] Mm-hmm.
Let's see.
Oh, reading a newspaper
is way too hard!
I mean, it's like,
when I read a line,
I don't know where
the next one starts!
Yeah, I kind of figured you'd
have a little problem with that.
Oh, hey, guy. How's it going?
Yeah? What's up?
For starters, how about you
call Ms. Kobayakawa over here?
I'm a senior. Tell her
Izumi's here to see her.
Yeah, sure. Hey, Kobayakawa!
Izumi-sempai, the senior,
wants to see you!
Hey, Onee-chan! What's up?
Ah, I love how they
get all polite and stuff
when they find out that
I'm older than they are.
They're cute when they do that.
[giggling]
[rain falling]
[YUTAKA]
I wish I was as
tall as you, Iwasaki-san.
Huh?
I wonder why there's
so much of a difference.
Well, I can't be certain.
Maybe it's because I drank
lots of milk or something.
I get it!
It's because you work hard
on it every day, isn't it?
No. If only life were
as simple as that.
I'd love to see a little
bit of growing happening
somewhere else for a change.
Huh?
Hey, guys, it's raining.
So we're gonna be playing
dodge ball
in the gym today for PE.
I always pictured you as
being the last girl standing
on the courts, Iwasaki-san.
I think you look really tough.
If I'm playing infield,
I end up being one
of the last ones left, too.
Maybe it's 'cause I'm small
and I'm hard to hit.
[HIYORI]
Hmm. They both survive the game,
but for very different reasons.
I'd feel awful if I hit
Kobayakawa-san, though.
[whistle blowing]
Darn it. It sucks they put
us on different teams today.
We get to be
on the same team, though.
Iwasaki-san seems like
she's really good at sports.
I bet she's ruthless out there.
It's okay. I asked to be put in
the outfield so it's all good.
I'm glad.
[YUTAKA]
Iwasaki-san's
such a good person.
Ready to pound these
guys, Kobayakawa-san?
Mm-hmm.
And you're okay with
her trying to nail you?
[MINAMI] Mm-hmm.
[HIYORI] Yeah, I bet you are--
I mean, let's have
a good game, okay?
Ah! Oh.
Plowed by the girl who works
in the nurse's office.
Are you okay?
You were pretty amazing
out there, Iwasaki-san.
You pop everybody you aim for,
don't you?
Oh, you think so?
You've got great reflexes
and targeting skills.
Whatever.
What happened?
Is she upset because
I was making a fuss over her?
Oh, no. She's just
embarrassed is all.
Yeah? Well I guess
it's okay then.
I can't really tell with her.
[YUTAKA]
Oh, wow.
She's the type who always
gets misunderstood by others.
I guess if they don't
know her,
they totally get the wrong
impression.
Have you gone on any cool
trips since you came to Japan?
Uh-huh. I went to all
the sacred places.
Sacred places?
Yeah! I paid my respects
at the three most sacred
places in Japan.
Did you go to Kamakura, Kyoto,
and Nara?
Oh, no. I went to Akiba
in Tokyo,
Nipponbashi in Osaka,
and Osu in Nagoya.
[BOTH]
Huh?
And I'm going to go visit
all the important places
around here as well.
You mean like, Tokyo Tower
and Asakusa?
No, not those places.
Like, Nakano and Kichijoji.
Okay.
Ah!
Are you okay?
Yeah. I just got some
dust in my eye is all.
Can I see?
Are you sure you're gonna be
all right?
Yeah. I'm okay.
Look at them! Don't they
look awesome like that?
Ugh, how can I stare
at my friends like that?
God, I'm such a pervert!
[YUTAKA, MINAMI, PATRICIA]
Hello.
[HIYORI]
Hi, come on in.
I'll be right back.
I'm gonna go get some drinks.
Huh?
Hmm.
[YUTAKA]
She's got a lot of books.
I sure hope you guys
are okay with--
Agh!
Wow, Hiyori. I didn't know
you were into stuff like this.
Kill me now.
Just please, kill me now.
Hurry. Do it fast.
I think these are her newest
sketches.
Oh, look at how much
she's improved.
You're right. She's really good.
I can't believe how much
this looks like Iwasaki-san.
Yeah?
Oh! It's Takarazuka!
[YUTAKA]
Is that supposed to be me?
Are you making a fairy tale?
Mm-hmm.
Wow. I'd like to read
it when you're done!
Oh, God! I have to stop
drawing my friends like this.
I'm such a pervert.
Hey, Tamura-san. Would you
like to go to Otome Road?
Yeah, I was thinking about
going.
What's Otome Road?
Is it near here?
You've never heard
of Otome Road?
[YUTAKA] No.
[MINAMI] I haven't either.
Oh, Yadeyade does.
It's called Otome Road, huh?
Otome Road, or "Maiden Road"
is a street
on the west side of
Sunshine 60 in Ikebukuro, Tokyo.
You'll find lots of stores
that specialize
in manga and anime, and shops
that carry figures and stuff.
It's a gathering place for otaku
almost on the same level
as Akiba,
but unlike the scene in Akiba,
there's way more girl otaku
than boys.
That's why they nicknamed
the street Otome Road.
It's known as the street where
the Fujoshi go to hang out.
Fujoshi?
It's written as "rotten girl"
but read as "spoiled lady."
Rotten girl?
Yeah, now that you mention it,
they are kind of rotten.
Oh!
[gulps]
[KAGAMI] Ahh.
Come on,
it's the three second rule.
You know,
the three second rule?
You got like five seconds
before the germs start hopping
on it.
I didn't say anything.
I'm just sitting here.
Mmm!
Ah!
No!
Not my meatball.
[crying]
What happened
to the three second rule?
Okay, that rule only
applies in certain situations
so ease up, will you?
[GIRLS]
Lucky Star.
[snoring]
Lucky Channel!
Hiya, Luckies!
Hi! We're back again
with another edition
of your favorite show.
They said it couldn't be done,
but we've made it to the
18th episode of Lucky Channel!
And all of you should
know who I am by now.
Uh-huh. I'm your navigator,
Akira Kogami! And this is--
Hi, guys!
I'm the one who's trying super
hard to be the best assistant
Akira-sama's ever had.
I'm Minoru Shiraishi.
Anyway, here's the theme
for today.
We're introducing
all the new characters
appearing on the show.
So let's get this thing
started with a big fat bang.
You feel me?
A big fat bang.
[MINORU]
For starters,
we've got Konata-san's cousin,
Miss Yutaka Kobayakawa.
Her classmates are
Miss Minami Iwasaki,
Miss Hiyori Tamura,
and Miss Patricia Martin.
Next up,
we have Kagami-san's classmates.
Miss Misao Kusakabe,
and Miss Ayano Minegishi.
The cast is filled out quite
nicely, don't you think?
I'm sure this stuff's old
news to most of you guys.
These ladies have been a part
of the opening credit
since the very beginning
of the--
How many girls are they gonna
bring out
before I get my friggin' turn?
It's already episode 18!
Actually, you made an appearance
in today's episode, Akira-sama.
You looked ultra cute
in that raincoat
and rubber boots outfit.
[AKIRA] Huh?
Hey, you know, that
reminds me of something.
I had a chance to speak
to Anizawa-san
after last week's show and he
told me something interesting.
He said there's one thing an
actor needs more than anything,
and that's presence.
[AKIRA sighs]
Even though you were only
in the show for a split second,
when you appeared, it was like,
"Whoa. That was Akira Kogami!
Didn't she--"
Whatever.
[phone vibrating]
Ugh.
[AKIRA] Hey.
[MINORU] Yeah, sorry.
[AKIRA] I said, "hey."
[MINORU] No, everything's okay.
No way. Is it time to say
goodbye already? Bummer!
We really wanna know what you
guys think about the show,
so please, please, please, keep
your comments coming, okay?
You can either email us
or call into our radio show.
[MINORU] Well, bye me!
[AKIRA] Turn it off!
[MINORU]
Thanks, guys.
[AKIRA] Texting?
[MINORU] What? I'm sorry?
[AKIRA] You were texting.
[MINORU] No, well, not really.
[AKIRA]
Who were you texting?
[MINORU] My, uh, parents.
[AKIRA] Why?
[MINORU] They want me to visit.
[AKIRA] What'd you tell them?
[MINORU] Well, you know.
[AKIRA] I don't.
[MINORU]
Wait, no, I--
[MAN singing in Japanese]
[speaking Japanese]
On the next episode
of "Lucky Star."
I'm Hiyori.
I'm Patricia.
Patty, you like your job?
[PATRICIA] Yeah, it's awesome!
[HIYORI] I'll bet
the first-time customers
that come in to the cafe have a
lot more fun when you're around.
[PATRICIA]
Well, actually,
I don't deal with first-timers.
[HIYORI]
Oh, really?
[PATRICIA]
I only serve
the regular customers.
You know, the ones
who drop serious cash?
Yeah, that's the cafe's policy.
[HIYORI]
Wow, that's harsh.
Next time,
"There's Substance in 2-D."
[PATRICIA]
Look forward to it.