[KONATA]
Okay, let's do this.
[MIYUKI]
Sure, let's go!
[TSUKASA grunts]
[KAGAMI] Quit screwing
around and start!
[singing in Japanese]
Now that autumn's here, it's
the perfect time for reading.
So, I've been reading
lots of books.
Whoa, that's unusual.
I know it's good for me,
'cause I'm gettin'
all this knowledge, but it's
starting to get expensive.
You don't have to buy them,
just go to the library
and check 'em out.
I'll bet they've got a lot
of stuff you'd like.
No, a library
wouldn't really carry
that big a selection of manga.
[loud sigh]
Reading books, huh?
Reading books.
[sighs] I just
can't concentrate.
[muttering]
Well, everyone needs to take
a breather now and then.
[speaks Japanese]
A little gaming
should help me relax.
[doorbell rings]
Oh, Miss Kuroi's online.
"How's it going? Stop messing
around and start studying
'cause you know I'll yell at
you if your scores suck."
[thinks]
Curses! They got me surrounded.
Please, Teach, have mercy!
Playin' my game's no fun when
reality comes a knockin'.
Sigh.
Quick question, ma'am,
when you were in school
and had to study for a test,
what'd you do
when you got bored?
[doorbell rings]
"When I couldn't concentrate,
I went and goofed off
or I slept. Nothing special."
[laughs]
That's what I do.
[doorbell rings]
"But I'm your teacher,
so I've got to be hard on you."
[thinks]
I get where she's coming from,
but it still blows!
If I want to good at school,
I have to set some goals
and work my way up.
So, could you teach me all
the stuff I don't understand?
Sure, we can study together.
[ticking clock]
So for this one,
the value of "X" is gonna
be equal to--
What?
Nothing, I looked at the clock
and realized my
show just started.
Tonight's episode is
when this magazine
writes an article about
the main character
and then everybody finds
out that she's pregnant.
I see.
Are you gonna watch it, then?
Mmm.
It's okay I'm recording it.
[snoring]
Boink.
[gasps] I know!
[whimpering]
I get sleepy when there's a lot
of stuff I don't understand.
Guess you've been sleepy
the whole time then.
[laughs] Maybe I
shouldn't overdo it
right off the bat like this.
I think I'm gonna call it a day.
Okay, but it looks
like your ambition
needs to do some catching
up with your goals.
[groaning] I still
can't concentrate. All right!
Oh, you say you'd like
some tips for studying?
Yep, I was sort of wondering
if you had any advice for me.
Let me see.
You tend to burn yourself out
if you concentrate
too hard on something.
I find that when studying,
if I stick to my usual habits,
I'll be fine.
I'm feeling confident
about that test today.
It's like I've been
enlightened or something.
But your usual habits consist
of you not doing anything,
so what's the big deal?
Oh, you mean even if
it's really, really cute?
Yep, and you gotta
watch out for their claws
'cause they're poisonous.
My, I didn't realize they
could be so utterly frightening.
--[KAGAMI] Howdy, guys.
--[GIRLS] Huh?
Hey, Kagami, how'd
you do on the test?
Yeah, I didn't do
so hot this time,
but my grade was still
in the top percent.
Even you have rough
patches, don't you?
You know, this time she
helped me study for my test.
And I got a really good
score too, better than usual.
So, how did you do on it?
Even though I was pretty
confident, I didn't do so good.
It's kind of a mystery.
No mystery there.
Inevitable's a more
accurate description.
Anyway, I was thinking
about how we're sort of
like birds of a feather
flocking together.
-Hmm?
-Think about it.
For one thing,
both you and Miyuki-san
are class representatives,
aren't you?
-Yeah.
-And then, you and me
both like to play
video games, right?
Yeah, but we don't
play the same genres.
You like dating sims and RPGs,
and I like to play
shooting games.
I used to think Tsukasa
and me were the same,
but after this test
I can see the difference.
-She's not as dumb.
-[gasps]
Well, I'm not going to worry
too much about blowing
the test this time.
You should definitely worry.
Just 'cause no one did well,
doesn't mean it's okay to slack.
You'll get left behind.
Hmm.
Hmm?
Actually, this time around
me and dad didn't bet
on anything anyway.
So, I've got nothing
to be upset about.
I seriously doubt you're
ever gonna amount to anything.
If you're gonna to look to
Miyuki for studying tips,
try taking more notes
and not just when exams hit.
I think Miyuki-san
is very sensible.
She's definitely
a Type "A" person.
[laughing] You know I hear
that from a lot of people,
but in reality
my blood type is "O."
[KONATA] Really, "O"?
You don't look it.
Well, actually...
...according to this book
on blood types and
personality traits,
I have many of
the characteristics
of a person with type "O" blood.
I'll find an example.
Here, it states that type "O"
people are childish and naive.
That description fits me
perfectly, don't you think?
"Type 'O' people also tend to be
pushy, stingy, and greedy."
Ah, I didn't know you had
a dark side, Miyuki-san.
Aren't you a Type "A" person?
Yeah, although a lot
of people mistake me
--for a Type "B" person.
--Huh?
"The Type 'A' person is sensible
and considerate to others,
and they also create
peaceful relationships."
Are you sure about this?
I'm a caring and sensitive
person, don't you know?
Only about the things
you're interested in.
I'm gentle and kind
and love everyone.
Only when you need
to copy homework.
Hmm.
Okay then, what's
your blood type?
Who me?
I'm a Type "B."
[KONATA] "Blood Type 'B,'
someone who's rude, contrary,
moody, thoughtless,
disjointed, and slacking."
Got a problem with it?
--Then, Tsukasa's a Type "AB."
--Huh?
--Why do you say that?
--Yeah, why?
Just thinkin' out loud.
See, if you go by
your personalities,
Tsukasa looks like a Type "A"
and Kagami looks
like a Type "B."
Nice theory,
although we're both Type "B,"
and we're sort of twins,
so there's that.
Yeah, that's right.
My bad.
And while we're on it, you're
a bigger slacker than I am.
There are several ways
of predicting personality types,
such as using animals
or even sushi.
[KONATA]
Sushi?
Here is what Miyuki-san is.
Ooh, Miyuki's ikura, huh?
Even her sushi's classy.
Goody, I just love ikura!
So, how about me and Tsukasa?
[typing sounds]
[BOTH]
Mmm.
[TSUKASA]
Cucumber roll.
A cucumber roll?
Well, I guess it is
considered to be sushi.
This thing is petty accurate.
What does that
thing say about you?
I wonder.
[typing]
Ginger...
[laughing] You're ginger!
Don't be dissin' the ginger!
She's right, ginger is
an essential component
to any sushi meal.
Besides, her outlook seems
to be a favorable one.
Yeah, Miyuki's right.
Cucumber rolls are more
like sushi than ginger.
[snarling]
Oh.
Hey, Konata, so about
that blood type stuff
we were talking about today.
Well, fraternal twins can
have different blood types.
I didn't want you
to think that you were wrong
when you weren't, but I
just wanted to let you know
you were right about it, so...
Well, thanks for
being so honest.
That's pretty cool of you.
I guess there's Type A
in you after all.
Oh, check it out.
The other day, I saw 'em do one
of those psychic readings on TV.
Yeah, you know
with that kinda stuff,
the guesses hit
the mark sometimes,
but sometimes
they're way off too.
It's all a part the show.
Statistically speaking if
you make enough guesses,
you're bound to get
a few of 'em right.
Kagami, do you realize
that if you keep saying stuff
like that, your life is going
to be the most boring ever?
Can't you act more
like a teenager?
[thinks] Wow, you did pretty
good this time, Tsukasa.
[laughing]
[thinks] Ooh, Kagami,
this time you didn't
--do as good as you usually do.
--[sighs]
[thinks] Even so,
Kagami still got a better score.
Hmm.
Well, girls,
I know you both worked hard.
The two of you studied
and did your best
and I have to say
I'm really proud.
Wow!
You did pretty good, Tsukasa.
[giggling]
But Kagami did better.
No surprise there.
[TADAO]
Come on, Matsuri,
can't you be
a little more considerate?
[BOTH] Good morning,
ma'am, how are you?
Good morning,
girls, how are you?
The two of you are
such fine young ladies.
I really do envy you,
you know that?
Not at all.
You're both Ryouou High, right?
I hear your grades
are so stellar.
If only I could get my child
to be half as smart as you.
[thinks] It feels like
I'm getting compliments
because I'm her sister.
Does that even count?
I don't know.
-[meowing]
-[GIRLS] "Lucky Star."
[groaning]
Since we're done with exams,
how about we go out
and have some fun?
Yeah, good call.
You guys want to go
see a movie or something?
Is there anything
good playing right now?
There is,
and I hear it's awesome.
Oh, really?
Yeah, we're talking
premium entertainment.
It's a hybrid splatter film
slash psycho-suspense thriller.
Whoa, sounds good.
Let's go for it.
We should go home and change
then meet up later.
[KONATA]
Sounds like a plan.
Let's get it on.
[thinks]
I'm not having fun.
I'm really not having fun.
We still have a couple
of minutes.
As usual, she's late again.
We're gonna miss the movie.
Oh, darn it.
For once, I'd like
to see Konata show up
before we do, you know?
Jeez Louise, the thing's
gonna start in a minute.
[gasps]
When'd you get here?
I didn't know it was
you until I saw that.
Glad you could make it.
Now, let's get inside
before it starts.
Ooh, wait a sec.
I need a favor.
Can you guys let me
pose as your sister?
Why, what's the deal?
Well, I'm gonna get
a children's ticket,
but I don't want
to get hassled going in.
[thinks] Lousy brat!
She's always going off
about her height,
but she totally exploits it
whenever she can.
[WOMAN] That was
scary, Tuckabee.
[MAN] Oh, man, you're so cute.
I could use some
food right now.
I heard that.
Aren't you hungry
after all
that screaming, Tsukasa?
[whimpers] Mm-hmm.
What do you want to eat?
Hey, how about we
hit up a cake buffet?
That sounds good.
[laughs] A buffet...
...the sanctuary for all
that a woman desires.
They sure have a lot of
different cakes and drinks here.
Yeah, you're right.
I wonder if we can
try one of everything.
Piece of cake
for you, Kagamin.
First things first,
there's a one-hour
time limit for each table.
You can find our
selection of drinks
over in the drink corner,
and you'll find
our various cakes
in the showcases over there.
So feel free
to take what you want.
-Okay.
-Bow.
Oh, by the way,
if you can't finish
and have an excessive
amount of leftovers,
you'll have to
pay a separate fee
for what you leave behind.
I just wanted to give
you ladies a heads up.
[ALL] Okay.
Very good.
Please enjoy yourselves.
An excessive
amount of leftovers.
Yeah, that's just
for people who take way more
than they're gonna eat.
Let's go, I'm starving.
That's a lot of cake.
You gonna be able to finish it?
Speak for yourself, Kagamin.
When it comes to cake,
this a perfectly normal amount
for me to have, thank you.
[ALL] Let's eat some cake!
Ah!
[BOTH] Mmm!
[KONATA]
And that one, and that one!
[laughing]
[ALL] Mmmm!
[chewing]
[gasping]
Okay, this is
startin' to hurt, now.
We kept filling up our plates,
and now we can't finish.
-Uh, I think I'm ready to pop.
-[WAITRESS] Hmm.
But the lady said we'd be
charged for the leftovers.
Yeah, we have to finish 'em.
[sighs]
I can't!
It's too painful.
Ah, our time's almost up.
[KONATA] Whoa, Kagamin, you're
pounding two pieces at once.
Of course, I don't
want to waste it!
[whimpering]
[sighs]
--[KAGAMI] Don't do it!
--Huh?
If you start
drinking water now,
you're never gonna finish
what's left on your plate.
You gotta focus on shoving
down as much cake as you can.
Pack it in and when you're done,
then you can wash it
down with some water.
--Uhh.
--Don't just sit there!
Pick up your fork
and suck down some more cake.
But I can't eat anymore.
You've got room
for some pudding
or Bavarian cream, go on!
No, it's all you, have fun.
I'm gonna hurl if
I take another bite, come on.
No way,
I've retired from eating.
[KAGAMI] The pudding's gooey.
You can slurp it.
[KONATA groaning]
[KAGAMI]
Come on, hurry up!
[thinks] I'm not having fun.
I'm really not having fun.
Now that our exams are over,
I've been doing some
serious game playing.
No wonder I'm so tired.
If you were only that
hardcore about studying,
your test scores
would be better.
These days, the dating sims
I've been playing
have a ton of save points.
Thing is, I can't find
a good place to stop.
I like to finish those things
in one sitting.
Something's bugging me here.
If high schoolers aren't
allowed to buy games like that,
how the heck do you buy them?
I don't buy that stuff.
Dad buys it.
[KAGAMI thinks]
Whoa! Your family's gotta be
the weirdest family ever.
I can't believe you
make your dad go out
and by that stuff for you.
That's why I'm all sleepy today.
I bet you're not that into
gaming, are you, Miyuki-san?
Oh, well, we don't
have any game consoles,
but there is a computer.
I do play a little on that.
Yeah, that's news to me.
What kinda games do
you like to play?
Things like "Minesweeper"
and "Solitaire."
I think those
games are exciting.
[thinks] Oh, Miyuki-san,
sure they're called games,
but they're not really games.
I know what you mean.
I like when you're playing
simple games like those,
you get totally sucked in.
Yuki-chan, what's your
highest score so far?
On "Solitaire," I usually
score over 10,000.
It's all about luck
with that game.
And then in "Minesweeper,"
I cleared expert mode
in under 100 seconds.
[gasping]
[KONATA thinks]
Ah, she's the type
who plays that stuff
all the time.
There sure was
a lot of stuff happening
in sports this year.
Yes, for starters,
that figure skater won
the gold medal
at the Winter Olympics.
And then, there was that high
school baseball tournament.
Wasn't it amazing how they
had to go into extra innings?
Mm-hmm, and how about
Prince Handkerchief?
If you're talking baseball,
there's also that player
who left for America.
Hey, is this year's
Japan series already over?
Yeah, for a while.
Ahh! No way!
Were there any sales?
Relax, the series was
between the you-know-who's
and that other team.
Neither of 'em owns
department stores
or supermarkets
or anything like that.
There was
a commemorative sale, though.
[gasps]
Hmm, I bet it was
a sale on hammers,
something like that.
Mm-hmm.
I wonder if it was ham.
I just gotta make
sure that next year,
I don't miss the sales.
Well, knowing you,
I bet you're just gonna
load up on candy and stuff.
No way.
I need to pick up stuff
like sugar, salt, soy sauce,
and all your basic
household-y things.
Huh?
Oh, that's right, Kagami,
you wouldn't know about
any of that, would you?
I suck at chores! I got it!
Ha! Ha! Ha!
[quiet whimpering]
Eye drops, huh?
You need any help with that?
Thank you,
I'd really appreciate it.
Okay, lie back and look up.
Oh, okay.
Hi... now just relax.
[whimpering] Yes.
Here it comes.
[whimpering]
Come on, relax, okay?
All right.
Sorry, I'm not doing
this on purpose, really.
It's just that...
your face is scary.
Hmm?
I've always had a problem
with giveaways and stuff,
'cause it takes forever
to get the thing
you sent away for.
True, however,
I found a way to milk
twice the enjoyment out of every
giveaway I participate in.
How?
It's always fun in the
beginning, like a festival,
but then nothing happens
and you start to forget
about it and then it shows
up and you're happy again.
One entry and twice the fun.
[thinks] I guess if you
really like something,
you can find the fun in it.
But I still hate the
waiting-around-for-it part.
[GIRLS]
"Lucky Star."
[AKIRA]
Lucky Show!
Hi, luckies.
Hi, everybody, it's time
for another super happy
episode of "Lucky Channel."
I'm your navigator,
Akira Kogami.
Can you believe we're
already on our ninth episode?
Time sure flies.
And sitting over here,
we have a certain someone
who our producer,
Ito, is gonna say,
"Yo, Shiraishi, can you
come here a second too?"
Why? What'd I do?
Oh, I'm Minoru Shiraishi
giving 100%
of all I got as
Akira-sama's assistant.
It's a pleasure
to see you again.
Well, today we're
gonna introduce another
character from the show,
Tsukasa Hiiragi.
Where is it?
It's under the thing with the--
got it.
[AKIRA thinks]
You sound like a nerdy turtle.
-Finally--
-Hiiragi-- I'm sorry.
Finally, things are
picking up around here.
Yes, we're strapping
on our loincloths
and gettin' down to
business, right, Akira-sama?
Loincloths, huh?
Yeah, since I'm an idol
and everything, stuff
like that is a little,
you know. Just keep
it mind is all, yeah?
Yeah, I'll do that.
Okay...
how about we give
ourselves wedgies
with those loincloths?
So, I'm just gonna
go out on a limb here,
and give you a piece of advice.
You're out on a limb?
If all you got as a comedian
is toilet humor, you're done.
I didn't know
I was a comedian.
And using other people's
material is a no-no.
You do that a lot, cool it.
Okay.
Okay, what are we talking about?
Oh, we were introducing
Tsukasa Hiiragi.
Oh, yeah, that's the one who
looks like the chick from...
-[yelling]
-..."To Heart," Akari Kamigishi.
Doesn't she?
I can't believe
you'd say that.
What'd you mean,
I think she kinda looks
like an idol from way
back when, don't you?
Yeah, I guess you're right.
She does a little bit,
okay, I see it.
She definitely has what it
takes to become an idol.
If I didn't know better--
Are you high or something?
Tsukasa Hiiragi's an idol?
You didn't have to
throw an ashtray at me.
How long you been here, huh?
'Cause it blows my mind that
you still have no concept
as to what a real idol is.
Learn your friggin' job.
-I'm sorry.
-That girl is just
a soothing character type.
I mean, come on,
with those droopy eyes
and that sad look, hello.
Okay, maybe she doesn't
look happy.
Whatever, that hoochie's not
what's important right now.
I'm gonna teach
you once and for all,
right here and now, what
an idol's all about.
We'll start with
the posing basics.
Huh?
You know I'm doing this
to help you out.
So it would be freaking awesome
if you could pay more attention
while I'm flapping here.
-Yes, ma'am!
-Here's how to deal
when you're ambushed
by a bunch of cameras.
Okay, go ahead,
push the button.
[MINORU]
Droopy eyes and a sad look.
[camera shutter clicking]
You see what
I'm talking about?
And then, there's these
props-- very essential.
It's a good thing for an idol
to keep a few of these handy.
-Where?
-There's times you'll
be walking down the street
looking fabulous.
You never know when
someone's gonna whip out
a camera and start shooting,
so you gotta stay frosty.
And make sure your choppers
are sparkly white.
--[speaks Japanese]
--Theater.
Your eyes should be
big and round,
and don't even
think about blinking.
--Confined to this area only.
--Psycho.
When posing, your expressions
must be natural and organic.
For example, if someone lines
up a medium close-up of you,
like this,
"Akira so surprised!"
It's like that.
Right, very natural.
There's also a version
of that pose
for when you and some guy
are caught leaving a ho--
--[trumpets play]
--Oh no!
It's time to say goodbye
already?
Now, don't you guys
forget to keep
sending in those cards
and letters.
We really, really want to know
what you think of the show,
and don't forget to let me
know how much you love me too.
You can also shoot us an e-mail
or call into the radio show.
Yes, we'll be seeing you
all in the next episode.
Bye!
We had a photo shoot, didn't we?
[MINORU] That's right, we did.
I wore
this little pink cardigan.
--[AKIRA] Ooh! You were so cute.
--[MINORU] Thank you.
--What's wrong?
--[AKIRA] Mmm, maybe not.
[MINORU] Well, everyone
said it was cute.
[AKIRA] But you were
so into it, weren't you?
[MINORU]
Yeah, I guess I was.
[AKIRA]
Bet you were having fun.
[MINORU] Well, I mean,
looking up into the camera,
the hands folded
under the chin pose.
Yeah, it was fun, yeah, yeah.
[AKIRA]
Ahh, you're totally hooked.
[MINORU] Totally, even the
cross-dressing. Totally hooked.
[AKIRA]
Did you check the photos?
[MINORU]
No, I haven't.
--[AKIRA] Well, the manager did.
--[MINORU] Yeah?
-[AKIRA] She checked the photos.
--[MINORU] Okay.
[AKIRA] She said something
about a couple of shots being...
problematic.
[MINORU] Well, I wouldn't
worry too much about it.
I'm sure they got a ton of shots
of me where I'm really h--
[KONATA]
Sorry, that was a rookie move.
Let me make it up to you guys.
[KAGAMI] She says as
she enters another song.
Give someone else a chance.
[KONATA]
Okay, here.
You guys decide on something?
[TSUKASA]
I'm still Looking.
[MIYUKI]
I'm looking too, but I'm afraid
I don't know that many songs.
[KONATA] No sweat, I'll
just sing until you're ready.
[KAGAMI] You think you
could sing something else
besides an anime song?
[KONATA]
You're in luck. It's not.
[KAGAMI]
Huh? I heard this before.
What is it?
[KONATA]
It's Kyon Kyon.
Me and my dad used to sing it
all the time when I was a kid.
[KONATA]
So, instead of an anime song,
you picked an oldie.
[AKIRA] What?
You're insulting Kyon Kyon
by calling this an oldie.
[singing in Japanese]
[KONATA] Look, Tsukasa,
just pick an easy song.
Like a children's song.
[TSUKASA] Oh, yeah. I'm looking
in that section. I'm so sorry.
[KONATA] No, it's okay.
Don't worry about it.
We still got lots of time left.
[singing continues]
[ANNOUNCER] On the next episode
of "Lucky Star"...
Konata here,
you know how in World 3-1
in "Super Bleep Bleep Brothers"
when you get to the stairs
near the end of the level?
Well, there's that
turtle over there, right?
All you have to do
is stomp on it
and keep hitting
your "A" button.
If you do that you
can keep hoppin'
and jumpin' and
kickin' that sucker
and get pretty much
infinite lives.
Cool, right?
But if you keep jumpin'
on that turtle
and go over 129 lives, you die.
That's it, game over.
No more lives.
What's up with that?
Hello, anyone else
see a problem here?
Infinite lives means
you live forever!
Anyway, I think it sucks,
but then again,
maybe that's the point.
Maybe the guys in that building
by Tofukuji Station,
are trying to teach us a lesson
about moderation, you think?
Next time, "Desires."
[ANNOUNCER]
Look forward to it!