[KONATA]
Okay, let's do this!
[MIYUKI]
Sure, let's go!
[TSUKASA]
Grr!
[KAGAMI]
Quit screwin' around and start!
[BOTH laughing]
[KAGAMI]
It's so stinky, y'know!
Stinky!
[MR. HIIRAGI] Well girls,
Golden Week's almost over now,
were you two able to get done
with all your
homework and stuff?
Um, I haven't finished yet.
You know how you just wanna
play during these long holidays.
We're in trouble...
aren't we, Sis?
Sorry, but I'm almost
done with my homework.
[TSUKASA] But we've been
playing this whole time...
[alarm chirps]
Thanks for breakfast.
Can you help me
with this problem?
If you can't figure it out,
do you honestly think I could?
You're in college, aren't you?!
[MRS. HIIRAGI] Do me a
favor and wake Tsukasa up.
No... She won't
wake up for me.
[MRS. HIIRAGI]
Honey, wake up already.
Dad sure is
late, isn't he?
Yeah, didn't he have
a groundbreaking
ceremony this morning?
Okay, Mom.
What time is it?
--[MR. HIIRAGI] I'm home.
--[MRS. HIIRAGI] It's past noon!
Hi, Dad!
How was work?
[TSUKASA]
Good morning...
It's afternoon.
How can you sleep for so long?
[TSUKASA laughs]
Did you see the special finale
of Love Apron last night?
No. Missed it.
I fell asleep in the middle...
You didn't see the end?
I can't believe you slept
through the end of it!
This guy shows up outta nowhere
with a red bucket on his head!
[yawns]
--[MRS. HIIRAGI] Kagami...
--[KAGAMI] Mm?
[MRS. HIIRAGI] Miyuki-chan's
on the phone for you!
'Kay!
I was wonder if you'd
like to get together
to go over the answers
on our homework.
Sure. That sounds
like an awesome idea.
[MRS. HIIRAGI] Kagami,
Konata-chan's on the phone!
Yeah, so, do you
wanna get together
to go over all the answers
to our homework?
Wait a minute! You're just gonna
copy all my answers, aren't ya?
'Kay, I'm here. Can I
copy your homework now?
Man, talk about being blunt...
Fine! You can copy
my homework if you want,
but if you don't do it on
your own, you're still gonna
blow that exam we have
coming up after the break.
I guess you're right...
In the long run, it's not
gonna be good for me.
I'm good at pulling
all-nighters before a test,
so I'm down with
the copying action.
Do you even have a conscience?!
[door opens]
Hello, everyone.
--[KAGAMI] Oh, hi, Miyuki.
--[KONATA] Hey, what's up?
Are you going to be studying
with us as well, Izumi-san?
No, she's just gonna copy it.
You're kidding me?!
Haven't either of you
done your homework?
Okay... What'd you guys
do during the break?
--[TSUKASA] Let's see...
--[KONATA] Hmm...
Hmm... I got 23 pages of math,
20 pages of world history,
and 30 pages of English to do...
I got a five-day break...
If I study for five,
no, four hours a day...
Math takes 1.15 pages an hour...
Oh, no, I haven't done
any homework today.
[TSUKASA] Let's see...
I got three days left,
so I guess if I work
six hours a day...?
--[TV muttering]
--[laughing]
[TSUKASA]
Two more days...
If I work all day and night...
[MR. HIIRAGI] Well girls,
Golden Week's almost over now,
were you two able to get done
with all your
homework and stuff?
Yeah, so, do you
wanna get together to
go over all the answers
to our homework?
I wanted to get everything done.
I even had it planned out.
Your plans failed.
Your resistance was futile.
You're worse off than her!
[KAGAMI] At least she tried her
best and did it on her own.
No matter what anyone says,
deep down, she's a hard worker.
[KAGAMI] But her accuracy's
horrible. I can't bear it.
Horrible...
just horrible...
So, were you guys able to have
any fun during the short break?
I know you had quite a
lot of homework to do,
and you also have that
little midterm thing today.
Don't tell me you spent the
whole vacation goofing off,
instead of studying!
Man, that didn't feel
like a vacation at all!
Life's tough.
I just kicked back and
played around the whole time!
Uh, Ma'am...
Yeah?
I kicked back and played
around the whole time, too!
Hey!
I always thought they
designed these things
so that you couldn't
get the prizes.
Eh, kinda depends on the prize.
Some of these are supposed
to be hard to get.
Really?
Whatever, I never felt
like trying it anyway.
[TSUKASA]
Oh, amazing!
Yeah, this little guy's
an easy one to grab.
Really...
[KAGAMI] If it's that easy to
get one, maybe if I tried it...
[KONATA]
"...I could get one, too,"
is that what you were thinking?
No! What are you talking about?
I wasn't thinking anything!
But I guess it couldn't hurt
to just try this one time.
Go for it, Sis. You can do it!
Darn. I thought I had
that one for sure.
Oh, bummer.
[KAGAMI]
No way!
Why?!
A wise man once said that:
"A UFO catcher's someone
else's piggy bank."
[KAGAMI]
True words of wisdom.
What? Oh! Again?
Oh, no....
I totally suck at this game.
You've got really good
rhythm, Kona-chan.
Nah, it doesn't have
anything to do with rhythm.
Rhythm, coordination,
problem-solving,
the skills you get from gaming
are useless in the real world.
Looking at you, I don't
doubt that one bit.
Wow, you're super strong.
Yeah, I know.
[KAGAMI] How much money does
she spend on these things?
Izumi! Hm?
Has anyone seen Izumi today?
Hey, Miss Kuroi? I got a
Miss Izumi on the line for ya.
Kuroi speaking.
Why aren't you in class?
[KONATA] I'm sorry.
I gotta take the day off.
I'm not feeling too good.
That's unusual. Did you
catch a cold or something?
[KONATA] Nah, it's just
the May sickness is all.
I feel sluggish, you know.
Hurry up and get down here!
Hey, we're going home now.
What's up, Konata?
Why are you stuffing all
those books in your bag?
The exam's start tomorrow,
and that means I gotta take
all my books home tonight,
so I can cram till dawn.
You never take your
books to study?
You leave them here every day?
Unbelievable. Look, Konata,
for one thing, there's no way
you're gonna learn all that
stuff the night before an exam.
Eh, I've always made it through
exams doin' it this way.
You're confident.
We'll see how long that
attitude lasts you tomorrow.
Okay, I'm gonna return the
exams you took the other day.
[STUDENTS groan]
[KAGAMI]
Not too shabby.
How'd you do?
Please don't ask, Sis, but I did
the best I could, ya know?
How 'bout you, little
miss all-nighter?
Totally passed it.
You aren't human, are ya?!
[ALL]
Lucky Star!
[KONATA] Blah... I don't
feel like doin' anything.
Come on, we're all going home.
On the way home, you always end
up hanging out with us anyway.
Oh, it's Comp-Fest!
And they're gonna be
givin' out QUO Cards.
I gotta collect 'em all.
Right! Time to get
a part-time job!
You're talking out loud
to yourself again.
That's crazy. I've never
heard of anyone using
a case of May sickness
as an excuse before.
I understand where she's
coming from though.
Well, they call it a sickness,
so the excuse is
totally legit, isn't it?
Do you honestly
think that's true?
--Yeah.
--Ah...
What exactly is the
May sickness anyway?
Miyuki, you wanna explain it?
Well...
By definition, May sickness
happens after you've
accomplished a major goal,
such as a college entrance exam.
Or if you've just
gotten a new job.
It also happens
when a relationship
that started in April
doesn't work out,
or when you can't reconcile
the life you wanted
versus the life you have.
The symptoms include
lethargy, apathy,
and even a mild depression.
You see, if you
just feel lethargic,
I don't think you can call
that the May sickness.
Besides, all of us are
still in the eleventh grade,
so it doesn't even
apply to us yet.
I like the change
of pace in spring.
I always do my best
this time of year.
Oh, yeah.
I guess I can see
your point, though.
I tend to feel a little blah
around this time of year, too.
I dunno, it's like sometimes
I don't even feel like
doing homework and
stuff when I get home.
Yeah, I'm the same way!
[KAGAMI sighs] I'm skipping
the snide remark, I'm pooped.
--[footsteps]
--[sighs]
What's wrong, Yuki-chan?
Why are you sighing and stuff?
I'm a little embarrassed
to talk about it,
It's like my phobia
about contact lenses.
I'm afraid to go to the dentist,
and I've put it off for so long,
that my cavity's gotten worse.
And now it's so bad that it
hurts even I drink water.
But... isn't that...
sorta normal?
I mean, I'm afraid of that, too.
But if you knew it was
gonna get this bad,
then why didn't you take
care of it earlier?
Well, even though I knew it
was going to be tough for me
when my teeth
starting hurting...
For some reason, you still
don't want to go to the dentist.
Even after the pain starts,
you still don't want to go
anywhere near a dentist,
you just put it off and try to
bear it for as long as possible.
Are dentists really that scary?
I've never had to deal
with them, so I don't know.
You've never been to a dentist?
I'm jealous!
There's that distinct medicine
you smell in the office,
and then the tension as
you wait in the lobby.
I know! And the sound
of those drills
drilling away in the back!
[KONATA]
Change Getter!
So scary!
Maybe guys like going to the
dentist more than girls do.
Why's that?
Don't they say that a drill
is kinda like a guy's...
[KONATA]
Dinosaur Empire!
I hear guys go totally nuts
for battles between robots
that use drills for weapons!
Yeah, but I think they'd hate
to have their teeth shaved off.
Know what? When you
go to the dentist,
have you ever noticed how pretty
all the dental assistants
and receptionists are?
Come to think of it, they are.
I wonder why that would be.
Maybe the person hiring them has
certain aesthetic standards.
Beautiful dental
assistants and drills...
The way you put it, I agree,
it does seem more
geared towards men.
Then, what do you think a
dentist geared more for women
would be like?
First thing they'd
have to get rid of
would be that medicine-y smell.
And the chair they
put you in should be
one of those puffy, reclining
chairs with a massager in it.
Aromatherapy would be relaxing.
And you could also have a foot
massage at the same time!
That sounds good!
And, if you were able
to play games while
they were drilling on you, that
would help to ease the pain.
It might be hard
to play games then.
But it is a good idea to have
something to distract us.
Like putting on some headphones,
and listening to your
favorite tunes.
Yeah, good one!
That's a great idea!
Mm-hm!
[MIYUKI] But in the end, I still
don't want to go to the dentist.
[TSUKASA]
Me neither.
What the...?!
Now, what's wrong?
They're turning another
one of my favorite series
into an anime, but the
cast is totally different
from the one on the drama CD.
Really? I don't get
what the big deal is.
Is this like an act
of God or something?
Politics? Money? What?
I never got into drama CDs, so
I don't care who's in the cast.
If the voices match
the characters
in the original
series, I'm okay.
But that's not how
it works, Kagamin!
If you're used to listening to
the drama CDs, it's weird when
you start watching the anime and
all the voices are different.
See, it takes a long time before
that weirdness goes away.
Huh?
But something good definitely
comes outta news like this.
Yeah? Like what?
Drama CDs and anime.
You can enjoy two worlds with
two different sets of voices.
That's two for the price of one!
You're quite the tough
shopper, aren't you?
Well, guys, looks like
Miyuki-san's left a nugget
on her plate, so it's
up to us to figure out
who's gonna get to eat it.
How 'bout we have
a staring contest,
and the winner gets to eat it?
What? That is so childish.
That sounds fun!
Come on, let's do it!
I think Kagamin may
have already won.
You say something?
Then let's begin the staring
contest, right now! Buh-blah!
[muffled laughter]
[BOTH laughing]
[KAGAMI]
T-That's insane!
[TSUKASA]
Amazing!
[laughter continues]
[KAGAMI]
That didn't even look human!
Jeez, you guys, talk
about overreacting...
[MIYUKI] I'm sorry I took so
long, the bathroom was crowded.
Did I miss something?
Come on, show Miyuki that
crazy face you just made.
[KONATA]
No, I don't want to.
It was amazing, Miyuki!
You've never seen
anything like this, ever!
[KONATA]
Fine...
[ALL laughing]
[TSUKASA]
Isn't that totally amazing?
It'll come in handy for
the special talent section
of your college applications!
Yeah, use it! Use it
to apply to colleges.
I'm sure you'll get accepted!
Yeah... that's not
really a compliment.
So I saw this report on TV about
how many books the average
Japanese person reads in a year.
Anyway, they said manga
wasn't good enough,
and that only normal
books counted.
Isn't manga...
[KONATA] I wonder if
light novels would count.
Huh? I don't know...
I guess it's okay if you
counted light novels.
What about picture books?
Uhh... Mm.
They're called books,
so I guess they'd count?
If you said Harry Potter and
books like that are ordinary,
everyone who's into the fantasy
genre would agree, right?
So, is there such a thing
as an "ordinary" book?
Besides, they ended the whole
report by saying something
about how the younger generation
is starting to turn away from
printed media and stuff.
The thing is, we use the net
to look at all kinds of
websites and blogs,
so, I think we actually
read more stuff these days
than ever before.
[TSUKASA] Yeah, I kinda get what
you're saying and kinda not.
Hey, guys. Are ya
ready to go home?
Yeah. Almost.
[KONATA] Oh, I'm sorry, I can't
go home with you guys today.
Huh? What's the deal?
Do you have to run an
errand or something?
Mhm. I started a
part-time job, that's why.
Huh?
[KAGAMI] Wait, she
started a part-time job?!
Is the Comp-Fest that
important to her?!
You know, I'm really surprised
Konata actually went
through with it.
Me too. She really got
herself a part-time job.
I thought that she was just
kidding about getting one.
I wonder about it, though...
I'm more surprised by the fact
that someone actually
went and hired her.
That doesn't sound very nice!
Well, for one thing, I'm having
a hard time picturing her
being a diligent worker.
Good point, Sis.
I wonder where she
ended up working.
Maybe she works at a bookstore.
You know how she likes manga.
I wanna buy this.
Yeah, hang on a sec. I'm in the
middle of somethin' right now.
Uh?
[KONATA]
Got 'em!
I really hope she
doesn't get fired...
How 'bout a convenience store?
I wanna buy this.
That'll be 498 yen, please.
Ah, you got the right amount...
--[CUSTOMER] Wha...?
--[KONATA mumbling]
Nah... Not there.
Maybe a fast food place?
[KONATA]
Got a problem with my smile?
[TSUKASA]
Maybe not.
[KAGAMI] Family restaurants
are also outta the question.
[KONATA]
Welcome...
[TSUKASA] I wonder what
kind of job she got.
[KAGAMI]
Yeah...
[TSUKASA]
Maybe she's a traffic monitor?
[KAGAMI]
Nah.
[TSUKASA]
A video rental place?
[KAGAMI]
I dunno...
[TSUKASA]
An izakaya?
[KAGAMI]
That's not it.
[TSUKASA]
Pizza delivery?
[KAGAMI]
No license!
[TSUKASA]
Supermarket cashier.
[KAGAMI]
Nope.
[TSUKASA]
Cram school teacher.
[KAGAMI]
You're kidding!
[TSUKASA]
A bread factory!
[KAGAMI]
Huh?
[TSUKASA]
Let's see... Hmm...
[KAGAMI]
Let's ask her tomorrow.
[KAGAMI] Hey, Konata, what kind
of place are you working at?
[TSUKASA]
Yeah, tell us.
[KONATA]
Hm?
Oh... it's just your
average cosplay café.
[BOTH]
Ah. That's perfect for her.
[KAGAMI]
Should she be working there?
[ALL]
Lucky Star!
[AKIRA]
Lucky Channel!
Hiya, Luckies!
Second episode! It's me,
Akira Kogami, your host.
I hope you're all excited,
'cause I sure am!
And sitting right next to me is
a wonderful young man who's
going to assist me on the show,
Mister Minoru Shiraishi!
Ta-da-da-da-da-dan!
Uh... f-f-fuh...
I'm Minoru Shiraishi,
Akira-sama's assistant.
I'm still really new at this,
so all I'm hopin' for is that
you guys remember my name, yeah.
Clappity-clap, clap...
Now, I know it's just the second
episode of Lucky Channel,
but we're already got tons
of messages from you guys!
Yup! Tons and tons of messages!
You guys are making me
super happy! Thank you!
It's pretty amazing, isn't it?
All this attention's because
you're so popular, Akira-sama.
[AKIRA]
Ugh.
Uh... What?
Saw the show today.
Yeah?
--You were in it.
--Huh?
The show, man! You had a part.
Oh, yeah. They did
give me a little part.
Yeah... They did, didn't they?
Uh-huh. So, uh, what was the
scene you were in anyway?
Sure! Um... It was
Scene 45, Part A,
the classroom after vacation.
Right, right.
Yeah, now I remember.
You came and went by so
fast, I'd almost forgotten.
Yeah, well, I only had
one line the scene, so I--
Bleh. You complaining or--
No! Nobody's complaining!
You should be thrilled those
guys gave a newbie like you
a line in a scene.
Things were different when
I debuted on the screen...
Oh really? How old were you
when you made your debut?
Three years old.
Back then, I was ecstatic that
they even gave me a crummy line.
But it's not about how many
lines you get, after all.
Well, it was pretty
tense for a while there,
being surrounded by the
biggest names in the industry.
What an amazing experience!
Yeah, you were tense.
I could tell.
Huh?!
You were stiff as a board.
You looked like a total amateur.
Tell you what... I don't usually
do this, but what the hell.
Come on, let's hit that scene
together, you and me.
Uh, you mean like right now?
They might bring you back
for another episode, right?
Yeah... I guess.
You have to practice
your craft, man.
Listen, I'm offering
to help you out here!
Oh, yeah! I got it, I got it!
Thank you, I really
appreciate it.
The script, please.
So, which scene was it?
[MINORU]
Scene 45.
Oh, yeah... This one.
Okay, I'll play Kuroi,
the teacher.
Whenever you're ready.
Ready, and... Action!
"So, were you guys able to have
any fun during the short break?
I know you had a
q-q... quiet..."
That's "quite."
[sigh] "Quite a lot
of homework to do.
You also got that little
midterm thingy today.
Don't tell me you spent the
whole vacation goofing off,
instead of studying."
Man, that didn't feel
like a vacation at all.
What was that?
What?
That totally sucked.
There's no motivation.
The line didn't deliver.
Deliver?
Deliver here! Right here!
I gotta feel it!
Oh... I'm sorry.
Hell, if you're just
gonna say the line,
a monkey could do that.
But monkeys can't talk, man. I--
--[AKIRA] Huh?!
--[MINORU] Ahh!
I guess it's time
to say goodbye now!
I think it's sad when
happy times like this
go by so fast, don't you?
Well, anyway, keep on sending
your questions and comments, and
please don't forget me! I need
to know you love me, too, 'kay?
And we'll see all of you
in the next episode.
See you later!
Bye, bye, everybody!
[AKIRA]
Yeah, so, what are they like?
[MINORU]
By "they," you mean...
[AKIRA] The cast. Somebody's
getting kicked off, yeah?
They hate each other, right?
A buncha divas, right?
[MINORU] No, it's not like that.
Everybody's pretty cool.
[AKIRA] Then, why don't
you help a girl out and--
[TSUKASA]
Amazing, Kona-chan!
[MIYUKI]
What a passionate performance!
[KAGAMI]
Hey, Konata!
Are the next two songs
gonna be like the last one?
[KONATA]
I picked a couple anime songs
with a few from some
live-action shows.
[KAGAMI]
That's not the point!
Pick songs that the rest
of us can recognize!
[KONATA] Hey, I can sing
whatever I want, so chill out!
[KAGAMI]
Fine... Whatever.
Hey, Tsukasa, punch some
songs into that thing,
or we'll be listening to her
warbling anime vocals all night.
[TSUKASA]
I don't mind if she does.
[MIYUKI]
Actually, this is kinda fun.
[KAGAMI]
Miyuki, not you, too!
[KONATA]
Sorry if I block the screen,
but I'm gonna do
this one standing.
[KAGAMI] You really
think that's gonna help?
[KONATA]
It's harder if I'm sitting down,
'cause I can't use my diaphragm.
[KAGAMI] You're gonna sing even
louder than the last song?!
[KONATA]
Hey, footage from the show!
[TSUKASA]
Wow, look at that!
[KAGAMI]
This looks like a TV show
from way before we were born.
[MINORU] Okay, ladies,
here are your drinks.
[KAGAMI]
Oh, thank you.
[MINORU]
Uh... oolong tea?
[KAGAMI]
That's me. Thanks.
[MINORU]
And the iced lemon tea?
[MIYUKI]
Right here, please.
[MINORU]
Who had orange juice?
[TSUKASA]
That's me.
[MINORU]
And the ginger ale goes to...?
[KAGAMI] Oh, yeah...
Just, uh, right there. Thanks.
[NARRATOR] On the next
episode of Lucky Star.
[KAGAMI]
Kagami here.
Okay, so when I put 200 yen
in a vending machine
to buy a can of juice
and get back a 50 and some
10-yen coins as change,
I think to myself, "Score!"
But then, when I wanna buy a
150-yen ticket for the train,
and after I put in
a 100-yen coin,
I think, "Oh, I've got
five 10-yen coins left!"
So I put in four,
but I only ever had four,
so now I'm one short.
So I end up putting in another
100-yen coin to buy the ticket.
And then I get back nine
10-yen coins as change...
and I feel so defeated,
you know? [sighs]
Next time: Various People.
[NARRATOR]
Look forward to it!