[KONATA]
Okay, let's do this.
[MIYUKI]
Sure, let's go!
[TSUKASA grunts]
[KAGAMI] Quit screwing
around and start!
[singing in Japanese]
It feels like forever since
we last wore these uniforms.
Oh, look, it's Kona-chan.
Kona-chan, good morning.
Well well,
Kagami-san, Tsukasa-san.
How do you do? Kiran!
Uhhh!
My, Tsukasa-san,
it seems that your ribbon
has been tied crooked.
Thanks a lot.
Gross.
What's wrong, Kona-chan?
You seem different.
Ah, yes, as of late I've found
myself completely obsessed
with Marimite.
Marimite?
Grow up already!
Ha, ha, ha!
Ah ha ha ha!
So now what?
You're not gonna start
dressing like a character
from that show?
Let's see. Isn't that cosplay?
Don't worry. I'm not
gonna take it that far.
You sure about that?
Yeah, besides, I already
do a ton of cosplay at work.
That's right. She works at
a place like that, doesn't she?
Wonder what she'd be
like as a classy lady.
Hmm.
That's so wrong I
can't even picture it.
The baseball broadcasts are
running longer and longer,
why do the fans
of new anime have
to be the ones getting
hosed all the time?
If watching anime is
that important to you,
why don't you get
cable or something,
don't they have channels
for that kind of stuff?
Ha, you know if I could
get it I totally would,
but the cable guys all
say the same thing,
"We don't provide
that service here."
[sighs]
Hi, Yuki-Chan, good morning.
Hello, Tsukasa-san,
good morning.
Why are you so gloomy?
Did something happen?
I had to have a cavity
taken care of the other day.
Oh, so you went to the
dentist? That's pretty brave.
Why is it that when
you go to the dentist
to get some work done,
you find yourself
returning there again and again?
You're so right!
I totally know how you feel.
It's never just one or
two trips, it's way more!
Miyuki-san, how do you do?
Oh Konata-san, how do you do?
I trust you're
having a good day.
Yes, thank you for asking.
Wow, Miyuki-chan's amazing.
It doesn't sound
weird when she talks
proper like that.
She doesn't even notice that
Konata's talking that way.
This is the first time
I've ever seen anyone greet
someone else with
a "how do you do."
Oh, is that so? At the all-girl
high school that my other
friends attend, it's common
for them to greet each other
with a "how do you do."
Wow. Schools for well-to-do
girls are something else indeed.
So very elegant.
Hey, so teach
told me to collect
your homework
from summer vacation.
Very well then, Sebastian.
Seba-- who?
I would assume all butlers
are named Sebastian, no?
I guess that's one
way of looking at it.
Say something
amusing, Sebastian.
[MINORU]
No way.
Well, your
vacation's over, people,
but now's not the time
to be spacing out.
Y'all should be thinking
about the future while your
divin' head first
into your studies.
The future, huh?
What am I gonna do?
I mean, now that I'm halfway
finished with high school.
Oh, come on, Kagami,
don't tell me you're seriously
thinking about your future?
Huh?! What's that
supposed to mean?!
Well, for one thing, you did
choose the liberal arts route
so you could be
in the same class as us.
Tsukasa, you tattle-tale!
Sorry.
And of all the people you,
you tell her?
Aw, you could
tell us, be honest.
You're a lonesome
little girl, aren't you?
There, there, it's okay.
Shut up you!
High school, high school.
Yoo-hoo! I'm here
to hang out with you!
Onee-san, it's the homework
I did over vacation,
I did what you said and wrote
the answers that seemed right,
even though I didn't
understand the questions,
and now I'm being forced
to do it all over again.
You've gotta help me!
I guess I could, but then,
if I help you, they'll just
make you do it all over again.
I think you know what I mean.
Curses.
You don't get an extension
on summer vacation,
but you get one on the homework.
I better borrow Kagami's notes.
[cicadas buzzing]
[snores]
[gasps]
[yawns]
Listening to the cicadas
always puts me to sleep, oh!
Huh? What the-- huh?
Aha! The baseball game went
late, so the schedule's off.
Huh, guess something good
can come of it after all.
Wait! My recorder's timer's off.
[KONATA]
Huh?
[TSUKASA] Where are
your glasses, Yuki-chan?
Well, you see,
they broke this morning,
I had placed them on my
chair and forgot about them,
it was an accident,
I'm terribly sorry,
may I borrow today's
notes from the two of you?
[laughs] Of course!
You're still as clumsy
as ever, keep it up!
Konata-san, you're
handwriting is so mysterious.
Tsukasa-san, keep trying!
I swear it's like those two
are totally useless, here.
Thank you so much.
It's a good thing we have the
same teacher or you'd be stuck.
And could you please keep
this a secret? It was such
a nice gesture and I'd hate
to pour cold water on it.
[sighs]
[KONATA]
I'm starving!
Are you ready to have
lunch with us, Yuki-chan?
[laughs] Tsukasa-san,
Konata-san, here are your notes.
Thank you so much for them.
Not at all, no need to
thank us, we're happy to help.
I never thought I'd be
lending you my notes, Yuki-chan.
I was so surprised.
Doubt it'll
happen again though.
Ah! Mmm! Stare.
Uh, what is it, do I
have something on my face?
[gulps] In games when characters
with glasses come to school
without glasses,
they suddenly become popular.
But I guess that doesn't
happen in real life.
Ah! No I guess
not, unfortunately.
Anyone else think choco cornets
look like drills?
Huh, drills?
That's right! I just
remembered we were talking about
which end of a choco cornet's
the head,
and how the thin end
kinda looks like a butt.
Hmm, although
if you look again,
the thicker end looks
more like the butt.
A butt?
[popping noise]
Well, that's a big butt,
and a layered belly.
When you gain weight on
the lower half of your body,
trying to find a skirt that
fits you is really difficult.
Yeah, right! When it fits
your waist it doesn't fit
your hips, when the skirt
fits your hips just right,
the waist is all loose.
But you can't help it,
so you buy the one with
the loose waist, and then
when you're out walking,
the skirt starts spinning around
until it's backwards.
[laughs] I know!
A layered belly
on a cornet body.
Flip it to the side
and it's a sleeping body.
If you sleep too much,
you'll get a cornet body.
Let me know when I'm
supposed to laugh, okay?
Hey, sis, didn't you
go on some kind of diet
to get rid
of your summer pudginess?
Yeah, I did, but even
though I lost some weight,
I didn't lose anything
on my waist or hips.
No, Kagami, it did work.
I can totally see
the fruits of your diet.
[gasps] Really?
Yep, the difference
is crystal clear.
They say that when
you go on a diet,
the places where you don't
wanna lose weight
are always the first ones
to go bye-bye.
Cut it out!
Don't even go there!
So when you read literature
the idea is to always
be thinking about
the message that
the author is trying to convey.
[KONATA]
I see, I see, I see.
I heard that
if your eyesight's bad,
you look like you're glaring
and it freaks people out.
But then again,
it depends on the person.
Hold it right there!
You looked at me when you said
it depends on the
person, didn't you?
I heard that when you
make your eyes all narrow,
it makes you look pretty.
You get this wistful faraway
look, or something like that.
[sighing]
Wait, what are we doing?
Konata's late,
she should be here by now.
Where the heck is she?
Oh, there!
I'm here, I'm here!
Sorry I'm late.
Oh you think?
You know, for someone
who's always complaining
about ball games running late,
I'd think
you'd be more punctual.
Yeah, well, you know, lately
all the games have been
going over so I guess
maybe I caught the bug too.
What, like the flu?
Well, what's the story,
why are you late? Slept in?
No, no, it's not that.
I'm not a child.
Then I can't wait to hear
the grownup reason you're late.
Well, okay, when I got ready
to leave the house to come here,
I noticed that
it was still early,
and I had some time to kill.
I figured "yeah." So I started
playing this game,
and then I just couldn't stop.
Even for a child
that's a crappy excuse.
Now that we're in
our second trimester,
we've got the arts festival
and sports festival coming up,
and exams right after.
You'll do great at the
sports festival, Kona-chan,
'cause you're so athletic.
Sports festivals
make me tired.
Yeah, well, it's rare
to find a homebody like you
who's in such good
physical shape.
I wonder what our class is
gonna do for the arts festival?
I don't think there's
anything anyone wants to do.
We can't really
decide on anything to do
unless somebody steps up and
says they wanna do something.
But the person who does
always gets stuck putting
everything together so
nobody says anything.
And then the only time we have
to do anything is after school.
And then we get home late
and miss all the anime.
[KAGAMI]
Where have I heard that before?
[slurps]
[GROUP] Lucky Star!
Since dad's put me in charge
of cooking the dinner tonight,
I gotta go grocery shopping.
Yeah? So what
are you gonna make?
Everyone's favorite,
chicken curry.
Everybody in my family
just loves chicken.
Chicken curry, huh?
That sounds good.
You know, I heard once that if
you let curry sit out overnight,
it gets yummier.
I heard that too. I know what
I'll do, I'll make a little
extra and then I can have it
for lunch tomorrow.
We always have leftovers.
[phone ringing]
[TSUKASA]
Hiiragi residence.
[KONATA]
Uh, Tsukasa.
[TSUKASA]
Kona-chan?
It's so early. Anything wrong?
[KONATA]
Yeah, it's the curry.
[TSUKASA]
Curry?
[KONATA]
The curry I made yesterday,
I left it out overnight,
and it spoiled.
[TSUKASA]
What? No way.
[KONATA]
Way.
[TSUKASA] But why? Curry doesn't
usually go bad overnight.
[KONATA] I
know.
[TSUKASA] Did you put
something weird in it?
[KONATA]
No, but this morning there
was mold all over it.
So cornets for lunch again?
I don't mind.
This thing's tasty.
Well, as long as
you're okay with it.
Wait, hang on a second.
You know, I just
realized something
about the kind of lunches
you guys bring to school.
Some days you bring
proper lunches,
and other days you
bring simple lunches.
Why's there such
a huge difference?
Oh, well, that's because
Tsukasa and I always take
turns making the lunches.
Hmm.
Stuff like lunches always
end up being kinda simple
'cause I'm not that good
at doing housework.
There, I'm simple.
Happy now?
Yes! Kagami, you're the
type of person who makes pots
and pans explode
whenever you cook.
Relax, nobody can do that.
Wow, Yuki-chan, your lunch
looks super tasty today.
[MIYUKI]
Really? Oh, I just packed
some of last night's leftovers.
[GROUP]
Oh!
[KONATA]
Dinner at Mikyuki-san's house.
[TSUKASA]
Is really fancy.
[KAGAMI] And these
are just the leftovers.
Hey, um, everything
looks so good,
what's the filling
inside the fried eggs?
[MIYUKI]
Oh, well, we had eel last night,
so I just put that
into the eggs.
[TSUKASA]
You never see leftover eel.
[KONATA] Moldy curry's
the only leftover at my house.
[KAGAMI] Well, your house
isn't really normal, is it?
--Good Morning.
--Hi.
Hey, you.
Look, look, my parents
bought me a cell phone.
That's pretty cool of them.
Yeah, I did really good
on my exams this time,
so they got it for me.
Well, now that you
finally got one,
give me your number
and I'll give you mine.
Sure, I just gotta
go find my number.
Let's see.
[beeping]
Hmm.
Uh, sorry,
this'll take a second.
Oh, oh!
[beeping]
I didn't know you had
a cell phone, Konata.
Except I keep it at home 'cause
I always forget to bring it.
Besides, my dad's the only
one who ever calls me.
Then it's pointless for you
to even have a cell phone.
Oh, yeah?
--Kerororo.
--Whoa!
Isn't he cute?
Mom and Dad bought him for me
with the cell phone.
That reminds me,
there's this girl in my class
who's got a ton of straps
hanging from her phone.
She decided to weigh it
to see how heavy it was,
and the straps alone
were like 800 grams.
Oh, wow, that's a lot.
That's heavy.
Once she took the straps off,
her shoulders didn't hurt
anymore.
Think about it,
every time she made a call
or answered the phone
she was working out.
It's weird, but cell phones
always make me nervous,
you never really know know
when they're gonna ring.
Really.
Oh, I hope somebody calls me
on my new cell phone.
You're losing it
over a cell phone.
These days they're
not that big a deal.
[giggles]
By the way,
did you ever find your number?
Oh! Oh, not yet.
[NANAKO] And in England,
the House of Lancaster and
the House of York began a series
of civil wars for the throne.
On the battlefield, the armies
of Lancaster wore red roses,
and the armies
of York wore white.
That's why it's called
the War of the Roses.
The fighting started
in 1455 and went all the way
to 1485 and that's when--
[music playing]
[gasps] Uh, what is that?
Is that my cell phone?
Oh, I finally got a call.
[sighs] Huh? Who's this?
Okay, confiscated.
You can pick it up at
my office after school.
Yay! She gave it back to me.
It sucks that your first
call was a spam text.
[phone vibrating]
Hi, oh, hey, Dad,
yeah I'm still at school.
Just hanging out
with Konata and Miyuki
and lost track of time.
Yeah, I'm fine.
I'll be heading home in
a little bit. See ya.
That always happens even
if I'm a little late.
--[laughs]
--[music plays]
Hello? Oh, hiya, Dad,
yeah, I'm still at school
with Kona-chan
and the others, yeah.
You think he'd figure it out
after calling one of us.
Fathers always worry
about their daughters,
it's what they do best.
[phone ringing]
[KAGAMI] Can you believe how
much spam you get these days?
[KONATA] You just need
to change your address
to something that's
not too obvious.
I changed mine,
and it's all good.
Not too obvious, huh?
Gimme an example.
Well, I got my address
written out to say
"meganekko geki love" in romaji.
What I really wanted was
something with maid in it,
but addresses with maid-san
and miko-san are so popular
they've all been snapped up.
Wait, you don't
have to broadcast it
to everyone on the bus.
I got it, I got it already.
The stuff you're talking about
is worse than the spam problem.
[phone rings]
Good morning!
Hey, you.
[TSUKASA crying]
Oh, why are you crying?
What's wrong?
[cries] My poor little cell
phone, it never hurt anyone.
She sort of forgot
to take it out of her pocket.
Aw, then it's gone on
to a much better place.
[wailing]
They'll never buy me
another cell phone again.
Oh, he made it
through unscathed.
Persistent little guy.
Oh, hey, about that text
you sent me last night.
You know the one that said
something about how Kagami
wanted me to return her
homework notes today?
Was that the last
message you sent?
Yeah, that was the
last, did you reply to it?
Huh? Let's see.
How come it's so hard for you
to return a simple
text message?!
I never reply to a text
when it's from someone
I'll be talking to later on.
You're supposed
to reply to those things.
I see you every day. What's the
point in going to that trouble?
You're gonna lose
friends that way.
Ah, it's not like it's
so important it can't wait.
How can you say that?
[cicadas chirping]
Huh, after all
the back and forth,
I still didn't
get my notes back.
[car horns honk]
[KAGAMI]
Tsukasa, can I come in?
--Oh, hey, sis.
--Ha!
--[laughs]
--What's wrong?
Why are you crying?
This manga I borrowed
from Kona-chan made me weepy.
Good morning! Thanks
for letting me borrow the manga.
It was really cool.
Yeah, wasn't that silly,
bet it made ya laugh.
Huh? But it was so touching
that it made me cry.
It's hard to believe you guys
are talking about
the same manga.
Here if you cry,
you're on Tsukasa's side,
but if you laugh,
you're on my side.
No way.
I don't wanna be classified
with either one of you.
I think it'd be kinda neat
to see how you react to it.
Oh, is it really
such a bad thing to
wanna know what your
friends are all about?.
Here's an idea,
attack number...
--[dog barks]
--did you cry or did you laugh?
--I laughed.
--I cried.
Okay, what's your
favorite manga?
[BOTH]
"Keroro Gunso."
[sighs] I can't
really tell if these
guys are the same
or not anymore.
Why don't you join the manga
club or something, Kona-chan?
I mean, you like manga.
Yeah, I guess I wouldn't mind
joining up with those guys,
I'm pretty sure they've
at least got flexible hours.
Draw draw draw draw.
[gasps] What the,
you call this drawing?
Mm-hmm.
I got a question, this thing
here, who's it a picture of?
[KONATA]
That's Tsukasa.
[TSUKASA]
Really? That's me?
[KONATA]
And that's Miyuki-san.
[KAGAMI] I guess you
sorta got the feel for her.
[KONATA] This is Kagami.
[KAGAMI]
Oh, I breathe fire, huh?
My, it's the spitting
image of you isn't it?
What a scary little girl,
how frightening.
Would you cut it out already?!
Oh, the new "Fullmetal"
book just came out.
Yeah, the new issue of
"Compti" came out today too.
I'm gonna swing by Gamers
now, do you guys wanna go?
Oh, sorry, I think I'll just
go by the local bookstore today
I got errands to run.
But you have to come with
me to Gamers today 'cause
it'll nurture
the friendship between us.
Stop it. What's up with you
today? You use a word like
friendship and it doesn't
fit you at all.
Oh, yeah, that, I was
just trying to get you to
give me all your
purchase points
by appealing to your sense
of loyalty.
So that's all
my friendship means to you?
What a crock.
[GROUP]
Lucky Star!
Man, it's quiet,
is she mad I used
the sunflowers
for the pigtail gag? I wonder.
[MINORU gasps]
Huh, what, who me? Huh?
You want me?
Akira-sama? Me?
Oh, okay, got it.
Hey, um. I think we're
on the air right now so uh...
if I don't do somethin' now
they're gonna change--
[music playing]
Hiya, Luckies! Or you know,
however she says that line.
Okay, guys, Lucky Channel's
on the air again this week
and I'm Minoru Shiraishi,
the assistant.
Akira-sama's in a bad mood.
Ha!
How dare you introduce
yourself before introducing me,
Akira Kogami. Do you not
understand what rank is?
No, I was--
--[thuds]
--Huh!
I've noticed you've
been getting quite
popular around here lately,
you and those pigtails.
Me? Popular? No not at all.
You're so full
of yourself, it makes me sick!
I'm terribly sorry!
First off, everybody
was expecting
the Akira fashion project
to showcase me,
yes, me and my pigtails.
What are those?
You're right,
you're absolutely right!
Hmm, I'm gonna
wear twin drills.
You're kidding, twin drills?
Don't underestimate
the speed of the getter.
[scoffs] Number two, huh?
Pigtails are over.
The next big thing is
going to be twin drills.
Didn't Konata say in episode two
that a drill is kinda
like a guy's, you know?
Did she now?
All righty, everyone, we're
gonna straighten this out
on our radio show
and on our website!
So, until the next episode.
Bye, me!
--[AKIRA] So...
--[MINORU] Yes.
[AKIRA]
The pigtails.
[MINORU]
Oh, the ones I had.
[AKIRA]
The ones in the picture.
[MINORU]
Yes.
--[AKIRA] Were those sunflowers?
--[MINORU] They were.
[AKIRA] I think I've
seen those somewhere before.
[MINORU]
What do you mean?
--[AKIRA] Years ago...
--[MINORU] Whoa! Hang on a sec!
--[AKIRA] One of my first--
--[MINORU] Gero gero! Gero gero!
[TSUKASA]
Boy, was I nervous.
[MIYUKI] It was very cute
and very well done.
[TSUKASA] Don't you get nervous
on the first song you sing?
You think "am I gonna sing this
song good enough," you know?
[KAGAMI]
Your turn, Miyuki!
[KONATA] I'd like her
to sing "Omoide Ga Ippai."
[KAGAMI]
Why that one?
[MIYUKI] Would you please
hand me the mic?
[TSUKASA]
Here. Good luck!
[MIYUKI] Umm, I don't
do this very often,
so I'd like
to apologize ahead of time
if my singing hurts your ears.
[KAGAMI]
Don't worry, you'll do great!
Wow, good one!
[KONATA] I totally get the
connection here. Nice, Miyuki.
[MIYUKI sings in Japanese]
[KONATA]
Oh, her voice is awesome!
This is a new kind of moe
and it's workin'.
[TSUKASA]
Yuki-chan, you're so cool!
[MIYUKI sings in Japanese]
[ANNOUNCER] On the next episode
of "Lucky Star"...
Tsukasa here!
Wait, time's up?
Next time "Energetic
Despite Not Being Myself."
[ANNOUNCER]
Look forward to it!