[KONATA]
Senior year, Class B...
[ALL]
Ms. Kuroi!
[KAGAMI]
Yeah, yeah.
[singing in Japanese]
Do any of you know what
the heck this line's for?
Yuki Chan, do you know?
No, I don't.
Well, guys.
[sighing] I should have known.
And before you get your hopes
up, I didn't win either.
[cries]
It seems I've won.
I did too.
[cries] You're the
best friends I ever had.
What about me?
[music playing]
[grunting]
Oh, man, I can't see anything.
[sighs]
Come on.
Ohh.
[singing]
[TSUKASA]
That was amazing!
[MIYUKI]
I was so impressed.
[TSUKASA]
Did you guys see the emcee,
I thought he was super cute.
[KAGAMI]
Uh, you're kidding.
[TSUKASA]
You didn't think so?
[KAGAMI]
Not really my type.
Are you feeling okay, Konata?
You're awfully quiet.
Huh? Uh-huh.
I guess the concert really
took it out of you didn't it?
I mean, it was pretty impressive
and I'm even feeling drained.
Uh-huh, I wonder what
this feeling I'm feeling is.
[birds chirping]
[coughs]
-What are you doing?
-Huh?
Come on, let's go.
You pick the weirdest things
to get all proactive about.
It's the last day to see
the cherry blossoms blooming,
I don't want to miss it.
Besides, when you put
it off for the next day
or the day after,
something always happens.
It'll rain and all the petals
will start falling off.
Hey, what happened
to that goldfish
you caught at the summer
festival last year?
Hmm, actually, I sort
of gave him too much food
and now he's, like, this big.
That's big like a shogun!
I guess I pamper
the little guy too much.
Wait a minute.
Are you sure you're feeding it
the right food?
'Cause that thing is definitely
not a goldfish anymore.
Maybe he's fat
because he's living
a happy peaceful life, you know?
So are you gonna eat him?
What are you saying?
That reminds me of this anime
with pets
who die and return human.
They go back to their owners
and they're all,
"welcome home, master"
Here you go with another
hardcore reference.
Maybe I should put him
on a little diet.
Kagami...
You're not gonna replace him
with a skinnier one, are you?
What?
It's getting pretty cold,
isn't it?
I guess we'll head home.
[KONATA] It kind of sucks
when you're out to see the
cherry blossoms at night, but
you're not dressed for it.
Your butt gets so cold while
you're sitting down too.
[MIYUKI] I heard somewhere the
average temperature in March
is basically the same
as December's.
And April's average temperature
is similar to November's.
[TSUKASA] Wow, if this
was November or December,
I'd be piling on the layers.
[KAGAMI]
Yeah, and in March and April,
you never seem
to have enough layers on.
[KONATA]
Maybe it's 'cause you get tired
of wearing your winter clothes.
[MIYUKI] Perhaps it's
how one subconsciously
expresses their desire
for spring to arrive.
[KONATA] Hey, Kagami,
doesn't look like she's cold.
Huh?
So she must have come prepared
wearing wool undies, huh?
I am not!
Ah, sorry, Keopie,
that's all you get today.
[splashes]
If this thing comes back to
me as an aggressive boyfriend,
I am so gonna be hating my life.
I wonder what's wrong with her.
[blows nose]
Man, my nose hurts.
My skin's so delicate,
it's gotten raw
from all this blowing.
This time of year always does
this to me, it's relentless.
That sucks, Dad.
I guess
I'm always home anyway.
Don't worry, I heard
there's lots of stuff
you can buy now that helps
with hay fever and allergies.
Oh, really?
[grunting]
Transformation.
This rocks!
And it's cutting out
like 99% of the pollen.
Now you're as suspicious
on the outside
as you are on the inside.
Please, Dad, don't let
the police catch you like that.
Well, I'm off to the store now.
Okay, have fun, Dad.
You wanna go?
Nah, no, thanks.
Hold it, Dad, you're not going
out there like that, are you?
Why not? That's why I got my
gear on, I'll be okay.
On to our next story.
Around 11:00 last night,
a woman barged
into a convenience store
and attempted
to walk out
with the day's earnings.
-Hey, Yu-chan.
-Uh-huh?
I was thinking that maybe
all these convenience store
robbers are really just
pretending to have allergies.
Huh, yeah, I guess
you're right.
-Freeze!
-Why me?
-Whoa.
-What, tomorrow?
Yeah, let's go, we haven't
done that in a while.
And I finished all
of my homework by myself.
Huh, did you say by yourself?
No way, you're kidding
right, you really did?
Nope, I lied.
Come on, it's April Fools,
did you forget?
Didn't you tell a lie today?
That's what it's about.
I guess you're not gonna do
your homework by yourself.
You must be so bored,
calling me up at this hour
just to April Fools me.
[sighs] Whatever, Slackenstein,
I'll see you tomorrow.
[phone rings]
Izumi residence.
Oh, hiya, this is Kuroi.
Oh, hi, ma'am.
[KUROI] Oh, hey, it's me, so
that game you let me borrow,
I sort of accidentally
saved over your data.
What?
[KUROI laughing] I got you.
I so got you,
you totally fell for it.
April Fools!
She must be so bored calling
this late.
Uh, ma'am...
[KUROI] Yeah, what's up?
The other day Miyuki-san said...
[laughs] Come now,
being a teacher is such
an easy job, I mean if
Mrs. Kuroi can do it.
That's what she said.
[KUROI] That brat, so that
nice crap's all an act, huh?
Um, ma'am, April Fools.
So basically Konata called
just to April Fools me,
unbelievable.
[giggles]
You have a chance to trick
anyone with a lie today?
Uh, yeah, I did.
No way, you did?
What was the lie you told?
Uh, what I said just now.
I lied when I said I lied.
You what? Wait,
you don't have to force yourself
to tell a lie today, you know?
So, what kind of lie
did Kona-chan tell?
Mmm, she said she finished
her homework all by herself,
and I was pretty dumb
to fall for it too.
Everyone knows that'll never
happen.
If she was lying, it means she
hasn't finished her homework.
Knowing her, I'm positive
she hasn't finished it.
Oh, okay.
You're just glad someone's
in the same boat as you,
aren't you?
Uh, well I-- [giggles]
[knock on door]
Hmm?
Hey, Konata, you got a minute?
Mm-hmm.
[sighs]
So, is it interesting?
Yeah, unique.
Hmm, well that's good.
[sighs]
Konata, I'm thinking about
getting married again,
-and, well, there it is, okay?
-Okay.
No, it's perfectly normal
you'd be against the idea,
Kanata's your real mom
and she always will be,
but that's not what, huh?
Wait a sec, Konata, are you
saying if I get married again,
you're okay with it?
Sure, why not?
[gasps] And you do know
that it means
you'll have a new mom, right?
You're still okay with that?
Oh, yeah, so what's my
new mom gonna be like?
Yeah, well, I mean
it's a pretty serious thing.
You can't take new mothers
lightly, unh-unh.
[ANNOUNCER] Next question,
what is the modest and polite
form of the word... "iku."
That's an easy one,
it's... "ukagau."
Yeah, you're right.
It's definitely... "ukagau."
I'm with you girls
on that one.
-Oh, come on, of course it is.
-Mm-hmm.
[ANNOUNCER]
And the answer is "mairu."
[all gasp]
[KAGAMI] Oh yeah,
yeah that's right.
[TSUKASA] I guess it is,
isn't it?
Great, now it's all weird.
It's always like this when
someone who thinks they're
right finds out they're wrong.
[ANNOUNCER] The first
multiple choice question is,
which of the following
prefectures
do not face towards the ocean?
Is it A, Ibaraki,
or is it B, Tochigi,
or is it C, Kyoto?
It's B!
-B right?
-Definitely B.
This one's way too easy.
[ANNOUNCER] And the answer is B.
Next question.
The most famous problem in
the history of mathematics
was finally proven
by Professor Wiles
of Princeton University in 1994.
Which of the following
three choices
is the name of that theorem?
Is it A,
the Pythagorean theorem,
or is it B,
Taylor's theorem,
or C,
Fermat's last theorem?
Funny how everyone's so quick
to answer when it's obvious,
but when it's not,
they all clam up.
Hey, guys, before our
spring break's over,
what do you say we all go
and hang out at Miyuki-san's?
Awesome idea, I always
wanted to see her place,
but it's so far away.
Miyuki-san's rich, I bet
her house is really amazing.
I wonder what it's like.
Maybe she's got a swimming pool.
Maybe she's got security guards
all around the perimeter.
Oh, come on, that's silly.
Oh, I bet she's got a pet
or something like that.
I always pictured her
having a white ferret,
a really cute one.
Unh-unh, a dog, a big white dog,
and she's got a big backyard
and a white parasol.
Well, the dog's a possibility.
So, that's pretty much
how that conversation went.
You're welcome to come over,
but please don't get
your hopes up.
For one thing,
we don't have any pets at all.
Oh, but one of our neighbors has
all the criteria
you're looking for.
They have a big white dog,
and I believe a parasol.
Ahh, she said her neighbor's
going to be starting
Ryoo high school this year too.
Really?
Hey, you wanna come
along if we invite her?
One of my friends has
a cousin who will be
starting her first year
at Ryoo this spring.
[KONATA AND MIYUKI]
It really is a small world,
don't you think?
[ALL] Lucky Star.
I'm super sleepy today.
'Course you are,
that's 'cause you're
always waking up in the middle
of the day.
Oh, there's Konata.
Hey!
Got in the habit of sleeping
in too, huh?
I've been gaming my brains
out for three days straight.
I'm gonna die.
These guys have one thing
in common, they're totally lazy.
Look, we're in the same
class again.
Yeah, you're right,
isn't that awesome?
Good morning.
Hi, Yuki-chan, good morning.
Morning. Guess what.
You're in the same class as us.
Really?
Oh, there I am, fantastic.
I hope we all have
a great year together.
I second that.
Wow, look we're
in the same class.
Mm-hmm.
I hope the two of us
have a good year together.
So do I.
[giggles]
[sighs]
Hey, Kagami's in a different
class again.
It's not like I don't see
you guys all the time anyway.
I mean, if I wasn't
in a different class,
you guys would wear me out.
I think it's a shame.
Not even, this is the
way it's always been.
Besides, Konata's gonna be
swinging by all the time
to borrow notes
or a book or something anyway.
You read my mind.
So it's cool, okay?
I'll see you guys later.
[TSUKASA]
Okay, sis, see you later.
[sighs]
Hey, Hiiragi,
you think we're in the same
class again?
Yep, we're in the same class
again.
Man, we've been in the same
class together
five years in a row.
Let's have another good one.
Uh...
Yeah, sure.
You see that? Some people
are so focused on their goals,
they end up getting all
cold-hearted and stuff.
Oh, be nice.
What are we the background
scenery or somethin'?
What kind of standards
do you think
they use when they split up
the classes?
Let's see,
I heard they try to sort classes
based on average test scores.
They also separate students
depending on
who's related to whom.
Oh, and they also try to put
the troublemakers
in different classes.
Ultimately, I think it depends
on the school you're attending.
Well, on TV and in the movies,
they always put all
the bad kids in the same class.
It's more compelling.
But high schools are
supposed to make sure
that everyone who goes
there is at the same level,
so there shouldn't be
any troublemakers around.
You do have a point.
Miyuki, this is where
you tell her she happens
to be one of the
troublemakers at this school,
and you don't want to be seen
with a troublemaker do you?
It's nothing like that.
[bell chimes]
That was the bell,
but our teacher's not here yet.
I know, I wonder what's up.
[hurried foot steps]
Sit your butts down right now!
That was close,
but I made it.
Just barely.
Listen up, I'm Kuroi,
your teacher.
Since y'all made it this far,
it's important you guys
snap out of vacation mode,
change your ways, and become the
awesome students I know you are.
[gasps for breath]
You gotta be kidding me.
I'm not gonna yak all day about
how y'all need to study hard.
But you're all seniors now,
so make your time count
while you're here.
Let's get to handing
out the class duties.
Takara, you wanna
be the class rep
-for the first half of the year?
-Oh, yes, ma'am.
I tell ya, once you've been
a class rep, it's really hard
to get people to think of
you as being anything else.
Yes, that's true.
But it's fine, I really
don't mind doing it.
Teachers always
decide that stuff
at the beginning of the year.
And since there are
so many people we don't know,
it's hard to nominate someone.
Yeah, but we're talking
about Ms. Kuroi here,
she picked you 'cause
it's gonna be less work for her.
I heard that.
[bangs]
Our teacher's hair
was such a mess today.
I think we're going to have
another fun year with Ms. Kuroi,
don't you?
Yeah, her classes
are always fun.
You know what they say,
the teacher's the one
who's supposed to set the tone
for the rest of the class.
That totally explains it.
Now I know why
the two of you are so lazy.
It's because your
teacher is too, isn't it?
I heard that, honey.
I'm Iwasaki, hi there.
Oh, wow, that girl's
totally cute.
I was in the same class
as her in junior high.
She doesn't talk, man.
All she does is read books.
She's kinda creepy.
She's not creepy,
she's nice. [giggles]
I'm the only one who knows
what she's really like.
[TEACHER] Next.
Oh, I'm coming.
I have to make a good
impression.
I'll be bright and cheerful.
I'm Yutaka Kobayakawa.
I'm short like a fifth grader,
but I didn't skip any grades
to get here.
Just kidding!
[STUDENT]
She skipped grades?
-[YUTAKA gasping]
-[STUDENTS chatting]
I think Onee-chan's
geekyness is rubbing off on me.
Okay, how about we figure
out the class duties next?
Does anybody wanna
volunteer for class rep?
'Course not, who would?
Iwasaki, you were the rep
in junior high.
Why don't you volunteer?
Is that true, Iwasaki?
You wanna be class rep?
I'm sorry sir, but I'd like
to do something different.
Hmm, I would've liked
someone with experience.
What do you want to do?
Are you gonna work
in the library?
The nurse's office.
[YUTAKA gasps]
I'd like the be
the class rep, sir!
She really is nice.
It's springtime, something new
is about to happen.
I can feel it.
A new friend,
a new life,
a new love.
With a childhood friend,
with an older boy
you have a crush on, or with
a strange transfer student.
The anticipation you feel
the five seconds
before falling in love.
MK5, that's how I always
pictured it to be.
But the reality is you're
starting from scratch
with total strangers,
how depressing.
Whatever,
I'm used to it already.
You're still better off
than I am.
Onee-chan!
Hey, Yu-chan,
haven't see you all day.
Yeah, I know, I know,
not since this morning.
This is the girl who
helped me out that one day,
you know, the one I told you
about.
Oh, right, awesome,
nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
See, see?
It's just like I told you.
I knew she'd get accepted here
and she did.
Yeah, you're right,
there she is.
But she could've picked
a different school
even though she
got accepted here.
But she didn't and now
she's here, so it's okay.
Yeah, anyway, Yu-chan,
where were you guys headed?
We wanted to find
the nurse's office,
'cause I'm sure I'm gonna
be seeing a lot of it.
-I hear that.
-Oh, I know,
you could show us where it is.
Sure, no problem,
I'll show you guys the way.
[chuckles]
Where was
the nurse's office again?
I don't really know, 'cause
I've never had to go there.
You're kidding,
you've been here two years
and you still don't know
where the nurse's office is?
I can't help if I've been
unusually healthy
the last two years.
You went and had your
physical exams there.
Actually, I don't think I've
ever been inside the art room.
Well you are majoring
in music
so you probably don't
have the time.
Take me for example,
I have yet to venture
anywhere near the Judo hall.
And I just found out
a while ago
that we have a tea room
here.
Well I guess if you've gone
to the same school for three
years, maybe what it is,
is that you only go to
the places you need to go,
or something like that.
Hate to say it,
but I don't go
to the study hall that much.
I always go to the study hall.
[chuckles] No way!
It's the only room quiet enough
where a girl can catch
up on her Zs.
[giggling]
I saw Yu-chan hanging out
with that girl
she met during
the entrance exams.
They were looking.
for the nurse's office,
and she said they're both in the
same class. It's like a miracle.
If you ask me, it's a miracle
that I got to meet Kona-chan
and Yuki-chan here and that
we all got to be friends.
Hmm, good point.
It's hard to believe
this will be the last year
the four of us will be
together like this.
[sighing]
And Kagami was in a different
class the whole time.
Thanks for reminding me,
buzzkill.
[KUROI] The answer is
B, the poison carrot.
This will be on the exam,
so make sure to remember it.
Yo, wake up, Izumi.
[gasps] Potemkin!
What the heck are
you dreaming about?
Sorry, teach, I don't know
what happened, I was actually
concentrating really hard
on not falling asleep.
-Oh?
-Yeah, ma'am, but the monster
called sleepiness
just kept coming.
Oh, yeah?
It sneaks up on me, I can't
dodge it, it's my destiny.
I appreciate your
honestly and your attempt
at an explanation,
but maybe this'll wake you up.
You never fall asleep
in class, Miyuki-san,
is there a trick to it
or something?
I can't say there's
any trick to it at all.
I really need my sleep
so I tend to go to bed
around 11 o'clock at the latest.
In fact, until last year,
I'd always be in bed by 10.
No way, that's impossible,
she's like a machine.
[bells ringing]
[sighs]
I knew this stuff was
important and I remember taking
notes in class 'cause I knew
I'd have to study it later,
but I can't tell what any of
this is
'cause I was half asleep
when I was writing it.
I can't tell either.
You know what,
looking at it now,
I'm thinking how awesome is that
'cause it shows I'm trying
really hard to study.
I just wish I could figure out
what the hell I wrote down.
They're equations.
Ms. Kuroi.
That's great, ma'am!
You can understand
my horrible scribbling?
'Course I can, the only
problem is that you
should've been dreaming
about world history
'cause that's when you were
writing 'em.
[embarrassed laugh]
Okay.
[game beeping]
Kona-chan, what are
you doing up so late?
Huh?
[laughs] So it stinks after all.
Uh-oh, I didn't know it
was so late.
Ooo, I wonder if anyone else
is online. Oh!
You never learn, can't wait
to see you in class tomorrow.
[ALL]
Lucky Star.
[AKIRA]
Lucky Channel!
Hi, Luckies! This is Lucky
Channel, the show that strives
for world peace, or so they say,
and I'm your navigator
Akira Kogami!
And I am the assistant,
Minoru Shiraishi.
I cannot believe we are
already on episode 15!
Wait, today's our 15th episode?
That would be correct.
So you're done after
today's episode, huh?
Uh...
Bye, me.
[Minoru screams]
Didn't you hear?
Producers said starting
with episode 16,
I was gonna be flying
solo on Lucky Channel.
Uh-huh, that's what he said,
and he even wished me good luck.
Uh, wait, can't we
talk about this?
Hah, I got you, April Fools!
You totally fell for it,
didn't you?
Oh, yeah, you got me,
oh, yeah, funny.
Sayonara, today's show
looked like a blast.
The performance of
Haruhi Suzumiya could've been
your twin brother hosting it.
He looks so much like you.
I don't think I know
what you're talking about.
So when the hell am I gonna
get my own concert, huh?
Oh, I don't know.
You guys need to tell me
this stuff in advance 'cause my
schedule gets filled up
pretty fast these days, buddy!
Sure, I'll check
on it right now.
Look, the eastern skies,
are burning red.
A circle, it's on,
the producers said
it's okay on the next episode.
Yes, I understand.
Akira Kogami's concert
is happening
on the next Lucky Channel!
What, really?
Are you serious? You guys booked
the arena and stuff?
They twisted a couple arms
and got a place, and then.
Oh, yeah, that's what
I'm talking about!
You're my boy, Itou!
I'm really looking forward
to hearing you sing, Akira-sama.
I can host the show for you.
People seem to think I'm an okay
emcee, so don't you worry.
I'm so happy right now.
This is gonna be so freaking
awesome!
[BOTH] We'll see you guys
next week!
Bye-nee!
[AKIRA] Oh yeah, are you
even gonna be here next time?
[MINORU]
I'm a lieutenant.
[speaking Japanese]
One, two, three, four...
[singing in Japanese]
[singing]
[ANNOUNCER] On the next episode
of "Lucky Star"...
-I'm Inari.
-I'm Matsuri.
-I'm Miki.
-I'm Tadao.
[ANNOUNCER]
Next time, "Ring."
[ALL]
Look forward to it!