[KONATA]
Okay! Let's do this!
[MIYUKI]
Sure! Let's go!
[TSUKASA]
Grr!
[KAGAMI]
Quit screwin' around and start!
[Japanese pop theme playing]
So the other day the three
of us saw a shooting star,
then Kagami said that the
whole wishing on it thing
impossible 'cause you can't wish
fast enough for it to work.
How nice!
Shooting stars.
I rarely get to see them
because the location
of my house isn't
conducive to star gazing.
Oh yeah, that's right.
It's 'cause you live
in the city, isn't it?
I would be
so fascinated watching,
that I wouldn't be able
to make a wish.
You feel so happy
when you look up
and see all those beautiful
brightly shining stars.
When you think about it,
perhaps that explains the legend
that shooting stars
grant wishes.
Your purity shines
so brightly it's blinding me,
blinding me, I say!
Winter vacation's almost here.
But our finals
come right before that.
Hey, Kagami, are you guys going
anywhere over the vacation?
Uh-uh.
Mmm, come to think of it,
we haven't
done any traveling lately.
The other day,
I took a trip to Asakusa.
Yeah?
When did you go out there?
Well, don't you guys get sleepy
riding the train in winter?
[BOTH]
She missed her stop?
Um, wait, isn't that in
the opposite direction?
I slept so long, the train
got to the final stop,
doubled back and went
past my station again.
When I woke up I realized
I was in Asakusa.
Oh, come on, there's
got to be a limit
to how many times you
can skip your station.
Missing your stop 'cause you
overslept isn't a bad thing.
I mean, I got to take
a little vacation to Asakusa.
You shouldn't be taking
little vacations during exams.
For a minute there
I thought I saw a girl
standing on
the platform wearing
a sailor uniform
and carrying a machine gun.
I wonder what the heck
her problem was.
You're not gonna tell us
you saw
someone
get whacked, are you?
Besides, they say that kids
who sleep a lot grow more!
Yeah, right, shorty.
There's someone else
who's worse!
After pulling
an all-nighter on a manuscript,
my dad took the morning
train to go deliver it.
He fell asleep
and missed his stop.
He slept all the way
to the last stop,
then the train turned around,
and before he knew it,
he slept his way back
and forth a bunch of times!
He'd start to wake up whenever
he'd get close to his stop,
but the poor guy always fell
right back to sleep again.
All he wanted to do was
come home and go to bed,
but he couldn't stay awake long
enough to get off the train.
Wow.
And whenever dad got
jostled by the train,
he'd wake up
all startled, but then
he'd get all confused
'cause he couldn't
figure out which direction
he was heading in.
Yeah, right.
Even if I fall asleep
on the train,
I always wake up
before I get to my stop.
That's amazing!
How do you know
when to wake up?
Maybe she's got
an internal alarm clock.
Although the one in her
stomach seems to be broken.
What was that?
It's the one that
gauges your candy intake.
Shut up!
You know how
when you get on the train
and the seats are all warm?
Don't you get sleepy?
I know, that's so true.
It's just like when
you're sitting in class
and you're
by the window and it's
a sunny afternoon in winter.
It's warm, just like that!
It's like birds of a feather
covering for each other.
No, it's
nothing like that, really!
I tried waking her up on
the ride home the other day.
Hey, come on,
wake up, we're here.
Yeah, give me five minutes.
Just five more.
She said out loud in her sleep
and then everyone around us
started laughing.
That's so weird,
I have a friend
who totally said the same
thing in class one day.
Oh brother, you guys are
birds of a feather all right.
Ah, no we're not!
[KONATA] Why do we ask
for five more minutes?
Maybe 'cause you'd get
upset if you tried waking
someone up and they said,
"Hey, give me another hour."
[KONATA] I guess, but asking
for five more minutes
is something that comes
up in other things too,
besides sleeping, like
hang on for five minutes.
Yeah, I guess.
Maybe we use it a lot
because it's not too long
or too short,
but if you wait five minutes
for a train,
it feels like forever.
Yeah, you're right.
Well, maybe.
The thing is though,
whenever someone says
just five more minutes,
it never ends up
being five more minutes,
does it now?
You know how they
tell you that you can't
use your cell phone
or put makeup on
while riding on the train?
Well, I think
it's way worse when you're
sitting there
and a total stranger's
all leaning up against you.
Yeah, sometimes
they're so heavy
that even though
it took you a while
to get a seat
you'd rather stand.
Or when
it's some old person with
a sticky face leaning on you.
Sometimes,
I'm all, "Lean that way,"
but it doesn't work.
No matter how many times
they adjust their posture,
they always end up
leaning against me again.
I know, I know,
isn't that weird?
This one time I was asleep,
there was a middle aged guy
sitting here
and there was an empty seat
sitting here.
I was trying
to lean toward the empty seat,
but I always
ended up leaning on
the middle aged guy instead.
Maybe everyone's
got a particular side
they like leaning on
or something.
Whenever I'm in a spot
where someone's leaning on me,
I'll tuck myself in really
tight just like this,
but then they start jabbing
away at me with their elbows.
You really think they're
asleep when they do that?
What?
You mean they're not?
See ya.
[BOTH]
Bye-ni!
Goodbye.
Oh wait, before you guys go,
you know how some folks
at school take the up train,
and then you got other students
who take the down to get home?
Yeah.
Don't you think
that all the people taking
the up train look
way more sophisticated
than the ones taking the down?
That sounds
just like Yuki-chan.
No, it's not like that.
All right, young ladies,
I better
bust a move
back to shanty town.
[train rattles]
Hm?
[groaning]
[man clears throat]
[brakes screech]
Wha...
Huh?
This isn't my stop,
it's the next one.
[groaning]
Hey guys, what's up?
Yo.
Ah, for some reason,
I couldn't study
at all last night.
Ooh, well, I on the other hand,
studied my brains out
last night so I'm feeling
pretty darn stoked right now.
Good for you.
How long did you study for?
-[KAGAMI] Only four hours.
-[KONATA] A whole four hours!
[BOTH]
What the...?
[KONATA]
Kagami, you do
everything perfect,
you know that?
Not that I'm bragging
or anything,
but just between you and me,
I do a heck
of a lot of studying.
When it comes right down to it,
you're pretty competitive,
aren't you, Kagami?
Well, I guess
it might be my pride
at being the older sister.
I always felt that pressure
and that's why I work hard,
to stay
a step ahead of Tsukasa.
I know I always
tell her that being
older or younger
doesn't really matter,
but I used
to think about it a lot.
But does it even matter
with Tsukasa?
I mean,
where's the challenge?
Um, well, yeah,
I guess there isn't any.
Damn you, Kona-chan!
Christmas is almost here.
I wonder what kind of present
I'm gonna get this year.
You still get presents?
That's so awesome!
How old were you
when you found out
there really wasn't
any Santa Claus?
Huh, you mean there's
no such thing as Santa Claus?
For real?
Did you know Santa never
came by Kona-chan's house?
Her dad tells her Santa gives
him gifts to give to her.
That way she thinks
Santa's really out there.
Her old man
really wants to look good
in front of his daughter,
doesn't he?
How's it going, Hiiragi?
Oh, hey.
Hiiragi-san, I have
yesterday's printout.
Oh, yeah, sure.
It's like that, Hiiragi-chan.
[giggles]
Wait, Hiiragi,
you dropped your pencil.
Oh, thanks a lot.
Hiya, Kagami!
Oh, hey.
Kagami-san,
here's yesterday's printout.
Oh, yeah, sure.
Sebastian's stinky, isn't he?
[giggles]
Hey, Kagami, you dropped
your handkerchief.
For real?
Geez, I guess
I hang out in Tsukasa's
class more than I thought.
You know my cavity's
been hurting a lot lately.
Oh, how can you stand it?
You know how
I totally hate the dentist.
Oh yeah, you went to get
a cavity fixed the other day.
Is it all better?
You know how dentists are.
Once you're
in their clutches,
they take a long time
to fix one tooth,
and then after
they finish working on it,
they find another tooth that
desperately
needs their attention.
So after making
a number of excuses,
I got up and ran away
as fast as I could.
What's a girl to do?
She's all cute when she says
it but that's totally nuts!
Hey, Konata.
How about we all get together
and throw a Christmas party?
Oh, sorry, but I've already
got plans for Christmas.
Really?
Do these plans involve a guy?
Well, you could say that.
Yeah, I'll bet.
Are you and your dad
going out someplace?
Good try, but I did tell him
that I'd be coming home
late that night.
No way, you're going out
on a date with some guy?
When did you get a--
Sorry to burst
your bubble, girls,
but I got
a part-time job, remember?
Phew.
But I wasn't
really lying, 'cause
most of the customers
are guys, right?
I thought you snuck
ahead of us there.
Yeah, so did I.
Every year at Christmas
the cafe puts on this event
where all of us
get dressed up like
Santa Claus for the customers.
You really do like that
kind of stuff, don't ya?
Hm, so do you.
Every New Year's Eve
don't the two of you
go to your family's shrine
and cosplay as shrine maidens?
[KAGAMI]
Do not call it cosplay.
Getting back to Santa,
it's awesome
that he gives out presents,
but that guy's
totally breaking and entering.
I mean when I was a kid,
that really freaked me out.
I wouldn't go around insulting
the legacy of a saint if
I were you, you horrid child.
Whoa, hang on.
Huh?
Santa gives kids
what they wish for
and she's going
to dress up like Santa.
So what kind of men have wishes
that a Santa squirt
like her can grant?
Oh, rolling out the
casual insults, are we?
Come to think of it,
are you guys
even allowed
to celebrate Christmas?
Yeah, we've got
Christmas presents
just like
all the other kids.
Back at our house,
we were brought up
to respect
all kinds of deities.
Our family goes and visits
temples all the time,
and we've even sung
a hymn or two in a church.
Wow, you guys
are so well-rounded.
Yeah, but then our big sister
who's a shrine maiden too,
she told me that
when she got married
it'd be in a wedding dress.
I wonder how Mom and Dad
are gonna feel about that.
Whoa, hang on.
Sounds like it's
gonna get complicated.
[GIRLS]
Lucky Star.
Yoo-hoo!
Boy, it's getting cold
out there.
Hey there, Nee-san.
Come on in.
What you watching, huh?
Just one of
those detective drama shows.
Oh, is it anything good?
No, not really.
There's nothing else on.
[MAN 1 on TV] That's it,
I got it. That guy did it!
[MAN 2 on TV] One moment
please, Detective.
Don't you think there's
something
strange about this case?
[MAN 1]
'Course not, this solves it!
Who are you anyway?
This ain't your business.
Oh brother,
that's a perfect example
of why the cops are such morons.
But aren't you
one of those cops?
[phone ringing]
Perfect timing, Mr. Telephone.
We're almost
at the part of the show
where the bad guy
confesses everything.
How do you know that?
Look.
[MAN 1] So, I guess you're
the one who did it.
[MAN 2]
Yeah, whatever, I give up.
Can somebody
please tell me why the hell
every cop show has to end
at the top of a cliff?
Maybe it's 'cause
people can't get themselves
to go through with anything
unless they've been pushed
to the edge of a cliff.
Yoo-hoo, hey, how's it going?
I'm hanging in there, Nee-san.
So, what
are you watching tonight?
It's the movie version of
a popular detective show.
Dad rented it for us.
[MAN 1] The case isn't here
in the boardroom,
it's out there
at the crime scene.
No, no, no, no,
that's totally wrong.
Like police work ever
gets that passionate.
You sound pretty passionate.
If I remember this thing right,
the thief isn't the guy
who stole the receipt,
it's some other guy who was
hired by the police chief.
Wanna know how you screwed up,
Chief? That's how.
You're talking
about the show, right?
You know, people are
always eating pork bowls
on cop shows, but I heard that
doesn't happen in real life.
Of course not.
Everyone knows most of
that stuff's made up.
You mean the Metro Police chief
doesn't really have that
many granddaughters?
Ugh, the chief's
got granddaughters?
That's the first
I've heard of it.
If anything,
I'd want Mai to be real.
That's all I'd wish for.
And what an empty wish it is.
Hmm, hmm, hmm...
I can't believe all the cases
of adults attacking children.
It's so horrible.
Wanna know
what I think about that?
Martial arts!
If you make every kid
learn martial arts,
stuff like that won't
happen as much, right?
Look at Oyama-sensei.
After years
of intense training--
hi-ya--
he was able to beat down a cow
with one bare-handed slap!
And every day he works out
by giving
20 bears a pounding!
Oh, yeah?
Well, that's all good,
but I don't think
it's very smart in the long run.
I mean,
when those kids grow up,
they're going to turn into
some butt-kicking adults.
Oh, yeah.
But on the other hand,
they say that
when someone
practices martial arts,
they grow up to be a more mature
and level-headed person.
Oh, they do huh?
Really?
'Cause there's someone
right in front of me
who practices martial arts
and she's anything but mature.
That's not very nice.
Okay, you guys,
I got a news flash.
Yui Nee-san has a little sister
who's gonna be starting
high school next year.
She's always been kind of frail,
but she's a really nice girl,
and she's super cute!
Cool.
But there's something
that bothers me about her.
If you buy into that proverb,
a healthy spirit
leads to a healthy body,
I can't help
but think there must be
something
dark and sinister hiding
behind her pretty little eyes.
I doubt that everything happens
the way the proverbs say.
You're living proof of that.
Can you believe
this year's almost up?
Every time
December comes around,
I feel like the year flew by.
This year,
are you guys gonna help
your folks by doing the
shrine maiden thing again?
Of course.
You should come
and pick your fortune.
Oh yeah, those.
If you pick
an unlucky scroll,
you feel lousy about it
and then you get all depressed.
But if you pick a great
blessing scroll, doesn't it
feel like you totally wasted
your good luck for the year?
That's why they say
that middle blessings
are the best to get.
Alrighty, class, 'tis
the season for presents,
and as your teacher,
I got you some report cards!
How'd you do, Kona-chan?
[Kona-chan groans]
Thank you, ma'am, but
I don't want this present.
It's my policy as Santa
to hand out those presents
to show you how hard you
worked in class, so enjoy it!
Hope you like the homework
you get over vacation, too.
I wonder
what kind of Christmas cakes
they're gonna have out
this year?
When you go into
a bakery around this time,
there's so many cakes.
Just looking at all of them
is so much fun, isn't it?
I wonder what happens
to all the leftover cakes
after Christmas ends.
Perhaps the bakery
lets the employees
take them home
to their families.
If nobody wants
to take 'em home,
then they'll throw out
the extra cake.
That reminds me of how
they compare Christmas
and the prime age
for marriage.
Like it's over after 25?
[KONATA] Up until the 25th,
Christmas cakes are the best,
but the day after Christmas,
you're looking at the
same cake differently.
Suddenly all those
decorated cakes don't seem
so yummy and you just don't
feel like eating 'em anymore.
Me and Kona-chan were talking
about Santa the other day.
So when did you stop
believing in Santa, Yuki-chan?
I bet you were like me
and believed in him
for a long time, didn't you?
It's true, I did believe
in Santa when I was younger.
In fact, I wanted to write
Santa a thank you letter for
all the wonderful gifts, so
I decided to do some research.
I tried asking
my parents about him,
but that didn't lead anywhere.
So I did
some more investigating.
And I came across
phrases like stories
that Santa Claus was based on
in the origin of Santa.
Needless to say, my dreams
were shattered early on.
[both gasp]
How'd you do, Miyuki-san?
Let me see!
Whoa.
That's our Yuki-chan.
Wish I could
get grades like that.
Getting blown away like this is
really starting to piss me off.
Oh, come on, Yuki-chan's
always at the top of our class.
We'll never get grades like her.
I'm not talking about grades,
I'm talking about breast size.
I mean,
did you get a load of hers?
[stomach growls]
I'm getting hungry.
I guess I'll have
a cup of ramen.
Not yet?
Oh, it feels like an eternity.
This is the longest
three minutes ever.
I'll pass the time
by reading my manga.
And then your noodles end up all
soggy and everything, you know?
I know, it's
like instant yakisoba
soaking up all the water!
Give me a break.
I knew she was gonna
be late, but this is ridiculous.
I can't let this become a habit.
Here's where I need to be a dad
and stop this
before it gets out of hand.
[KONATA]
I'm home!
Konata, get your butt in here!
Do you even care what time it--
Merry Christmas!
Here's a Christmas present
from me to you, Daddy.
I hope you like it.
I bet you're cold
from being out so late.
You want some tea, honey bunny?
Yeah, you know it!
I'm so happy,
I think I could die now.
[slurring speech]
Hi! What up?
Yui Nee-san's in the house!
[KONATA]
You totally reek.
You didn't drive, did you?
No, I parked the car
and hit the bar, man!
Can you believe this?
It's like Christmas Eve,
but my husband isn't even home.
It was gonna be
our special night.
Couldn't you go visit your folks
once in a while
instead of coming here?
[beeping]
[HUSBAND]
Yui? Oh hey, it's me.
I was gonna
surprise you tonight,
but yeah, the door's locked.
Are you with your parents?
I'm coming home!
I'll be there in
a flash, baby, turbo style!
I won't stop for any
traffic lights either!
Don't go breaking any laws
in your condition there, tiger.
I can take her home.
I'm not ready for bed yet,
so I think I'll log on.
Hey, teacher's online.
Hey, ma'am,
let's have ourselves a riot.
All night long, that okay?
Just a minute, please.
You are not a leftover.
You are
not a leftover.
'Cause I bought you.
Yeah, I came down here
last Sunday too.
I bought some manga.
The train fare down
must really add up.
I know you do it for the points
and all, but that's hardcore.
You really love this.
And do you even use any of the
prizes you get from that stuff?
Seriously.
Mm-mm, I don't use any of 'em.
Well, I guess
it would be kind of hard
to use that stuff after all
the effort it took to get it.
[KONATA] You know it.
It'd be a waste to use it.
Using it makes it less valuable!
Don't you know that?
Okay, if that's
how you feel about it.
[all gasping]
No!
Yes.
Didn't you get shocked
by the static?
Uh-uh.
Well, why didn't you?
She spends so much time
in front of the computer
she probably absorbed all
kinds of weird electric waves.
Static is the worst
thing about winter time.
You can get shocked
just by touching someone,
even if you barely touch 'em.
[KONATA] Maybe these
guys don't like each
other after all, for real.
[humming]
[static crackles]
Ah!
What the heck are you doing?
[DAD] I just wanted
to try it again.
[static crackling]
[Dad groaning]
[GIRLS]
Lucky Star.
[AKIRA]
Lucky Channel!
Hiya, luckies!
I'm your navigator,
Akira Kogami!
It's already
the eleventh episode,
guys, can you believe it?
And since it's the 11th episode,
I can finally tell you the
fantastic gabalicious news that
-you've all been waiting for!
-Yeah, um...
We've gotten lots of
comments from passionate fans--
-She's ignoring me as usual.
-Really want to see Akira-san
in the main segment of the show,
and there were
so many of you out there
wanting me
that it couldn't be ignored!
Hi guys, I'm Minoru Shiraishi,
the assistant to Aki--
Shut the hell up.
I'm going to make an
appearance in the show!
I want to thank
Miss Konata Izumi from Saitama
who sent her postcard
into Newtype,
oh, and everyone else,
thank you, thank you.
Wow, you got cast too,
Akira-sama?
Huh?
Yeah, what's with the attitude?
Like, oh,
you're finally getting a spot
in the show
in like episode 12,
but I was in the show
this whole time, huh?
What's up with that?
No, that's not it!
I swear, I'm totally honored
that I'll be acting
in the show with
you, Akira-sama, believe me!
Hmph, acting
in the show, he says.
All you did today was
pick up a handkerchief.
Oh, how you dream about
making it in the industry,
but you're totally
expendable and you
could disappear like that!
Keep that in mind
and maybe you'll
stick around a bit longer!
Okay.
I'll keep that in mind.
After an announcement like that,
I bet you can't wait
to see the next episode.
You want to see it now,
huh, do ya, do ya?
Everyone's trembling, no, naked
and trembling,
waiting to see it!
I know, let's air it right now!
We can't tease
the fans like this!
Come on, you guys, let's
give 'em what they want!
All we need's
a 30-minute block to do it.
We can steal a 30 from
the next show, right, guys?
Oh well, I guess that's it then.
I want to hear from you guys,
so call into
our radio show or log
on to our website, okay?
Bye-ni!
[MINORU]
[AKIRA]
Oh, what am I gonna do?
It won't be cool if
I upstage the main characters.
[MINORU] I heard that,
I've seen it happen before.
The main character's
friend or the bad guy.
Basically, whoever isn't
the main character,
they end up being more popular.
Uh, Akira-sama, what's wrong?
[AKIRA] So, you're
talking about yourself?
You're talking about you?
You got a big fat head now
'cause you're the popular one?
[MINORU]
No, it's not like that!
[AKIRA] They gonna make
an action figure out of you?
[MINORU]
No, no they're not!
What are you talking about?
I never said--
Hang on a second, please.
Stop it and hear me out!
[clapping]
[KONATA] Yay, looks
like Miyuki-san and
Tsukasa's duet's coming up next.
[TSUKASA] Yuki-chan,
let's go sing up front.
[MIYUKI]
Uh, sure.
[KAGAMI] Huh, I can't
believe you actually
picked a song that Tsukasa
and Miyuki both know.
[KONATA] Oh, I know
a whole lot of songs.
All types, too.
[KAGAMI]
That's an anime song.
[KONATA]
When you need to pick a song
in a hurry, anime song's
are the way to go.
[singing in Japanese]
[MAN] On the next
episode of "Lucky Star."
[TSUKASA]
Tsukasa here.
Okay, so a couple
of nights ago,
I got really,
really hungry, but since
it was so late at night,
I mean, like, really late,
I didn't know if I should eat
something or not, you know?
Anyway, I figured
a little bite wouldn't hurt,
so I went to go get something.
Well, I went to the kitchen
and I opened the fridge,
and I was thinking
about these pastries
I had that I saved and--
Oh, that's it?
Next time:
Let's Go to the Festival!
[MAN]
Look forward to it!