[MS. KUROI]
Senior Year, Class B?
[GIRLS]
Ms. Kuroi!
[KAGAMI]
Yeah, yeah.
[upbeat techno music]
[singing in Japanese]
[GIRLS chattering]
[GIRLS singing]
Hey, Konata, can I borrow
your computer for a second?
I just remembered about
this committee meeting
that's coming up, and I need
to write something for it.
Yeah, sure.
Okay, I have been feeling
a little out of whack lately.
But I think
I'll be ready on time.
I'd like to get
a bigger head start...
but I don't want to rush it,
because I want
to make sure everybody is
feeling comfortable with it.
And I'd like it if we could
work out all the details
of the assignment.
Yeah, so are you gonna
tell me what's going on
with your computer, or what?
Hah hah! Maybe other people's
computers are just too hard
for you to deal with, Kagami.
Whoa!
I didn't check my email
for a couple of days,
and now my inbox is megas full!
You get email?
I never pictured you
as being all that popular.
Okay.
It's called your inner voice
for a reason.
You gotta keep it inside.
A good 90% of my emails
are phisher spam.
I bet it's because of all
the sketchy sites I visit.
[YUI] I'm pretty sure you
shouldn't admit that to a cop.
In fact, I'm positive.
Isn't it amazing how
these guys always come up
with the funniest things
to put in the subject line?
I mean,
some of this stuff's hilarious.
[KONATA]
Yeah, I know.
Wow, it's copying pretty fast.
Looks like it'll be done
before I know it.
Huh.
[gasps]
[thinking] Ugh! How can anyone
rely on what the timer says
when it goes up and down
like that! Jeez!
Late night snacking
calls for a bowl
of instant ramen, baby.
How could you
tease me like that?
Hey there!
Ooh, thanks.
Is it true that Konata and
Yutaka both caught a cold?
Uh-oh. Hey, Yutaka.
How you doing?
I haven't had a cold in awhile.
[giggles]
Hi, Konata! How you feeling?
What's up, Neisan?
How's it going?
Uh-huh.
Funny how you don't have
the energy to go to school,
but you've got enough
to play your games.
Uh, yeah, well you see--
aw, you know
how it is, don't ya?
[GIRLS]
Hello!
Wow, thanks for coming
by to visit, Minami,
and thanks for bringing
your friends along, too.
That darn cold
really nailed her,
but I gotta say
I've never seen her
as healthy
as she's been lately.
Thanks a lot for being
there for her, Minami-chan.
Oh, it's okay, really.
Back in Junior High,
Yutaka had maybe
one or two good friends,
so I guess you must be
really special to her.
She just can't stop talking
about you, Minami-chan.
And I've never seen her
have this much fun
at school before, either.
You know how when you're sick
people say
it's all in your head?
Well, when you're busy
having fun,
you don't have time
to think about being sick.
[GIRLS]
Hello!
Wow, thanks for coming
by to visit, Minami,
and thanks for bringing
your friends along, too.
That darn cold
really nailed her,
but I've gotta say that
I've never seen her
as healthy
as she's been lately.
Thanks a lot for being
there for her, Minami-chan.
Oh, it's okay, really.
[YUI]
Back in Junior High,
Yutaka had maybe
one or two good friends,
so I guess you must be
really special to her.
She just can't stop talking
about you, Minami-chan.
-[BOTH giggle nervously]
-I've never seen her have
this much fun
at school before, either.
Minami-chan, Tamura-san,
Patty-chan, please come in.
How are you feeling?
Promise me
you'll get well soon, okay?
Uh-huh, I just wish
I wasn't all weak and frail,
because I hate being sick.
I feel bad
for making everyone worry.
No way!
Being weak and frail like that
is a great way to get people
to make a fuss over you.
Yeah, well,
it might look like fun
to someone
who isn't weak and frail,
but if you're weak and frail,
it probably sucks.
Hmm, I guess that's like saying
how if you've got
a little sister in real life,
you probably won't think
little sisters are moe.
[BOTH]
Yeah! That's right.
Whoa! Watch out, the normal
people are attacking us
with weird looks!
I'm being blinded
by their aura of confusion!
We can't help
that we're different!
We're outlaws
in an ordinary world!
Speaking of things we wish
were different about ourselves,
Minami-chan wishes
she had bigger boobs.
-[gasps]
-Wow, is that for real?
No, it's not like that.
[YUI]
I heard that if you massaged
your boobs, they get bigger.
[KONATA]
Yeah, I heard that too.
Are you sure it's okay,
Minami-chan?
Yes, I'm positive.
You're the only person
I could ever ask, Yutaka.
Okay, here goes.
[thinking] Oh, easy, girl!
Get a hold of yourself.
Wow, that's cool, Tamura-san.
I didn't know you were
from that circle.
Yeah, and I had stuff
at last summer's Comiket.
I bought
a couple of your books.
They're good.
Oh, thanks a lot.
That's so cool.
I'd love to read some of the
manga you've drawn, Tamura-san.
Will you let me borrow yours?
Sure, I'll go get--
[grunts]
Please, you don't want
to do that.
Come on, Hiyorin,
don't you want everyone
to experience the doujin
you worked so hard on?
You don't understand.
That stuff's not
for the general market.
Have mercy.
Oh, Hiyorin,
just give it up already.
[MAN on TV]
Isn't that amazing?
Now, let's review.
Chewing gum containing xylitol
has been proven to destroy
the germs that cause cavities,
because when the xylitol
is absorbed by the germs
that cause cavities,
it depletes the ATP
in the bacteria and also it
dissolves the cavity itself.
And...
[thinking] If it's really
that good for my teeth,
I should try it.
[humming]
[crunches]
I was chewing the gum because
it was good for my teeth,
but it made me lose a filling,
so I had to go to the dentist.
[KONATA thinking] A pitiful
and unlucky Miyuki-san is moe.
So that's what
poor, sweet Miyuki-san
was crying about today.
-Yeah?
-Oh yeah.
Oh, um, okay.
That's what Onee-chan
said happened to her.
So that's why Miyuki-san
seemed so gloomy.
Um, I'm really sorry about
what happened to Miyuki-san,
but that's great material!
This sucks, it's been forever
since I've had a good idea.
How do you come up with
ideas for manga anyway?
Hmm. I don't have
any surefire method or anything,
but I usually get ideas
-from real life and stuff.
-[gasps]
From real life, huh?
You read them, didn't you?
Well, that depends on--
Admit it, you did!
Well, I--
She showed you,
even after all that begging.
Um, I'm sorry.
Those stories
weren't from real life.
Anyway, I thought
the stories were good
and really fun to read.
Right, thanks a lot.
And there were a few that
felt like they happened to me.
I got a feeling of deja vu
while reading them.
I'd like to read some
of her stories too.
[thinking] I bet those stories
were based on you guys!
I'm sorry! I'm so sorry!
[BOTH] Huh?
[moaning]
Oh, hey, how's it going, ma'am?
Good morning.
Up all night
playing games again?
Or maybe you did some
late-night anime watching?
You know it, and these days
there's tons more anime series
on late at night.
Yeah, that rules.
Okay, you could at least lie
and tell me you were studying.
I've been seriously
thinking about splurging
on a DVD recorder or something.
That might help.
[laughs]
Save your money. Why bother?
You'll record the shows
and never get around to 'em.
Kinda like
how your games pile up.
Huh? What are you talking about?
Whoa, hang on a second.
You've gotta be kidding.
Yeah, right, you wish.
Listen, I don't have anything
to do with any of it.
[phone disconnects, beeping]
Uh... [grumbles]
[phone, rings]
Hey, it's me.
Did you just hang up on me?
I guess we got disconnected.
Yeah, I had three bars.
Anyway, I was acting
immature a minute ago.
Sorry.
No, I didn't hang up on you.
That's not why.
[thinking] I can't believe
I'm back for another visit.
Let's have ourselves
a peek inside, shall we?
Not to worry. We just need
to pop the filling back in,
and you'll be as right as rain.
Now, about that tooth
in the back.
I believe
I've detected some decay.
We should
start treatment immediately.
[GIRLS]
"Lucky Star."
-Oh.
-Hmm?
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing, sis.
I just kind of realized
how much strawberries smell
like shortcakes is all.
[laughs] I get it.
You meant to say that shortcakes
smell like strawberries, right?
You know, because they have
strawberries inside them.
Huh?
[giggles] I guess.
[chuckles] It's okay.
It's not like getting confused
like that's a bad thing.
Good morning, everybody.
I hope you slept well.
-Hey, Yu-chan. Good morning.
-Good morning.
[MAN on TV]
Here's today's pooch!
Wow, look at all the animals.
They're doing some kind
of special about pets.
[WOMAN on TV] First,
I'd like to introduce you
to a Welsh Corgi named Koo!
Wow, it's a corgi!
He's super cute.
I don't know about the dog,
but the owner
is pretty darn cute.
And her thigh-high socks
get extra points.
There's just enough skin showing
between them and her skirt.
She'd look awesome
in a Gothic maid ensemble.
[Man on TV]
Next we have Sylviana,
-a Siberian husky.
-[DOG whines]
Look, a husky.
I like huskies a lot.
I wonder why you don't see
them that much nowadays.
Whoa! Tsundere! Now that's
what I'm talking about.
Moe-tastic.
Anybody who likes
to walk around with their hair
in ponytails is
definitely tsundere.
Wow, I didn't know you were
into playing games and stuff.
Yeah, but I suck
big time at 'em.
You want to play or something?
[video game noises]
[laughs]
You're awesome, Hiiragi.
Yeah!
Whoo-hoo!
I can't believe you did that.
Did you see that?
Isn't Hiiragi amazing?
Yeah, she is.
[KAGAMI thinking]
Watching her have so much fun
makes me feel like a loser,
because all
I care about's winning.
That's a ton of stinky.
Can something stinky be moe?
Oh, hey there, Patricia-san.
How's it going?
We're seeing you a lot
on this side
of the school these days.
Well, Patty's really
enthusiastic about learning.
In fact, you could say
I've taken her under my wing.
I'm teaching her everything
she needs to know
about the essence
of Japanese culture.
Yeah, whatever,
if you're teaching her,
she's only gonna be learning
about a sub-culture,
if anything.
But otaku are the pride
of Japanese culture.
-Mm-hmm.
-I'm on a mission to absorb
everything I can here,
take it all back to America
and distribute it
to the faithful.
You're right about one thing,
she is enthusiastic.
Anyway, what about music,
Patricia-san?
Do you have any favorite bands
that you like?
Hmm, let me see.
-There's Orange Range...
-[whistle tweeting]
...Chemist, Suneohair,
Porno Graffitti,
L'Arc-en-Ciel, DEEN, Nightmare,
and a bunch of others.
I listen to all kinds
of different Japanese bands.
Wow, you sure do.
That's impressive,
but all the bands you just named
sing anime songs.
Wow! Good one, Konita!
You're so sharp.
And you're only listening
to the songs
they did for anime, right?
Ah! You know, I really need
to get myself a maid.
-Huh?
-It'd be nice to get a maid.
Yeah, I guess
that would be nice.
I heard
you don't live in a dorm,
but you have a place
all to yourself.
Yep, and the cooking,
laundry, manga,
and anime keep me busy.
I bet it's hard, especially
if you're not used to it.
No wonder you want to get
yourself a housekeeper.
Oh no, I don't want
to get a housekeeper.
I want to get a maid.
I didn't even know
there was a difference.
What? You're kidding, right?
They're totally different.
Hasn't this country
taught you anything?
Actually, I think you might
be getting
the wrong idea about Japan.
[DOG whines]
No, I'm sorry, girl, I can't.
Fried food's a no-no.
[DOG whines]
She knows
you'll give in, Minami.
that's why she isn't going away.
I'll take care of her, hon.
Come on,
I've got something for you.
[sighs]
[MOM]
Slow down, girl.
[MINAMI thinking]
But, now I feel so lonely.
Everybody in our class
thinks she's too quiet
and really scary,
but the truth is
that she's super-kind,
totally awesome,
and really cool!
You know her,
she's the one staying over
at Izumi-san's house.
She just admires her so much.
Oh, does she now?
Minami-chan,
would you take this?
I have to agree, she is
rather awesome and cool,
isn't she?
Yes, why even Izumi-san
thinks so.
Minami-chan always gives
off this cool-headed,
Little Miss Perfect vibe.
But when she's with Yu-chan,
you can tell
that she is really
a good human being.
And that's
what she said about her.
[CASHIER] Oh, I'm sorry,
because it's on sale,
we have to limit it
to only one per customer.
-[MINAMI gasps]
-[YUKARI thinking] Oh, my.
She's cool-headed
and a Little Miss Perfect.
And here's what Kagami-san
and Tsukasa-san
have to say about her.
Minami-chan seems like
the type who does everything
quickly, efficiently,
and perfectly.
I think Minami-chan is awesome,
because she seems
like she can do anything.
I wish I could be like her.
Kagami-san and Tsukasa-san
speak so highly of Minami-chan.
I think it's wonderful
that everyone admires her.
Yeah, but, Mom, I can't
because it's limited
to one per customer.
Huh? Oh. Mm-hmm.
[register beeping]
Huh?
She does everything quickly,
efficiently, and perfectly.
[giggles]
-Hey, you.
-Hey, girl.
Hey, what's up?
Whatcha watching there?
It's just some mecha
anime series I rented.
This looks really cool.
You sure are into this stuff,
aren't you?
Mmm. Yeah, but I'm not really
that much into mecha
or anything.
What?
What do you mean
you're not into mecha?
Why the heck are you
watching the show then?
In order to attract
a broader audience,
the creators of these
mecha series are tossing in
a lot more cute boy
and girl characters.
Pretty clever, huh?
What's the point
in calling it mecha anymore?
Got that, Hiiragi?
I'm counting on you for real,
so promise me.
I want to hear you say it.
Go on, say it.
Yeah, sure, relax,
I'll take care of it.
Come on, Misa-chan,
you heard her.
She said she'd take care of it.
-Huh?
-I wouldn't bother her
too much if I were you.
[moans]
If there's one thing
I've learned about people,
it's this--
whenever somebody says,
"Sure, I'll take care of it,"
chances are they're not
gonna take care of nothing.
[KAGAMI thinks]
She picks the weirdest things
to be right about.
Kagami-sama!
Do you wanna go with me
to Gamers today?
I got stuff to do today.
And besides, there isn't
anything I want to buy.
Oh, come on, man.
It's not gonna take
that long, I promise.
-No thanks.
-Yes thanks.
Leave 'em alone.
Why do you always go
to Gamers, anyway?
Isn't there a bookstore
by your house you can go to?
[grumbles]
Once you've been inside
a specialty store like Gamers,
ordinary bookstores don't seem
like they got you covered.
I mean good luck finding all
the things you're looking for.
[KAGAMI] It's probably
because all the things
you're looking for
are too weird.
Okay, what are you gonna get?
Just this. I'm good to go.
You're watching that one too?
Oh no, I haven't seen the anime,
but when I saw the cover,
I couldn't help but think
that I needed to get it.
Like we were somehow connected.
I couldn't fight this feeling
no matter how hard I try.
You're talking crazy.
I finally figured out the
philosophy behind the reason
why people buy stuff
based on the cover art.
For example, you picked
the light novels you read
based on the art, right?
Yeah, you're right.
You got me there.
So, when you buy
a book on a whim
and it turns out to be good,
you think you totally scored.
And even if it turns out that
the book you bought sucks,
you don't care 'cause
you bought it on a whim.
Either way, it's a once-
in-a-lifetime opportunity.
That's a good way of putting it,
and I totally see where you're
coming from, but I don't buy it.
-[hums, sings in Japanese]
-Huh?
[thinks] A once-in-a-lifetime
opportunity, huh?
Achoo!
That was a big one.
You might want to cover
your mouth next time.
Well, you know it's not like
you can control your sneezes.
I've never actually
seen anyone go "achoo"
when they sneezed.
That was hilarious.
Achoo!
[KONATA]
Even with a sneeze,
the difference
between us is huge.
It's not fair!
You're so darn cute,
it's totally unfair!
Whoa, down, girl.
So, if you go all the way
around, it doesn't stink so bad.
Is it true
they stopped doing it?
You know,
you guys get along great.
[BOTH] Hmm?
Do you guys ever argue
or anything?
All the time.
She looks all sweet and mellow,
but if you piss her off,
-she'll cut you, man.
-[giggles]
Yeah, I guess there's
some people out there
-who are like that.
-Oh, come on, leave me alone.
That reminds me, even when
you're not mad, you're scary.
Darn it, I should have known
I was getting set up
for something like that.
We just found out that
Minami-chan got the same time
as you
in the hundred-meter dash.
Oh yeah, that's awesome.
Although, if we ever had a race,
I'd totally beat her
because of my boobs.
You want to try it?
Well, yeah,
but she could still win
because of her height, right?
Can't she?
Wow, she totally ignored me,
didn't she?
Hey, don't you
think so too, Hiiragi?
Isn't that the funniest
thing ever, Hiiragi?
[KAGAMI] Mmm.
Know what
I'm talking about, Hiiragi?
[KAGAMI]
Mmm.
[AYANO thinking]
Misa-chan's attitude is
"Answer me
when I'm speaking to you,"
and Hiiragi-chan's is
"Don't bother me, I'm reading."
Things are starting to get
pretty tense around here.
I think it's so awesome
how the characters
in anime and games have all
this moe built into them.
Yeah, I know.
Hey, is that right
or is the image corrupted?
Nah, it's supposed
to look all blurry
and pixelated like that.
Oh, I kinda like how
it's blurry and pixelated.
-[YUI] Ahem!
-[BOTH yelp]
So, what kind of game
are you underage
high school chicks
playing, huh?
-[chuckles nervously]
-What's everybody doing here?
[GROUP yelling]
It's none
of your business, Yu-chan!
[keyboard clicking]
[sighs]
That's all she wrote.
It's been forever
since I updated the blog
with a big old entry.
I just gotta publish it and...
Ah! No!
Back, back, go back!
[sniffles]
[snoring]
[GIRLS]
"Lucky Star."
[theme music plays]
[sighs]
Okay, I ain't your mom,
so I'm not gonna waste my breath
giving you jerks
a scolding today.
[thinks] Gloomy.
[grumbles]
And I don't even care about
how we all ended up here.
You guys still with me?
Fantastic.
Anyway, I heard
you losers built this show up
from nothing, yeah?
So now that you made it
to the last couple
of episodes,
you geniuses think
you're gonna bust
the place down?
[thinks] Unhappy.
[groans]
People say I'm a mean bastard,
and you know I've done things
that'd make
your hair turn white.
But this is the first time
I've been called in
to stop a boring-ass argument!
-You awake? Good boy.
-[groans]
If we don't get this thing
resolved right freaking now,
it's gonna make me look bad.
And we don't want that,
do we, Shiraishi?
-No, we don't, Gottoza-sama.
-Huh? Do we?
I'm very sorry, ma'am.
Hmm.
[humphs]
You're awfully quiet.
-I'm so very sorry.
-[angrily] Huh?
I'm so very sorry, Gottoza-sama.
[sighs]
All right, you guys,
how's about we wrap
this thing up for today?
Okay? Come here, you freak.
You got one more episode
of "Lucky Channel,"
so go out
and make it awesome.
'Kay? We good now?
[BOTH softly]
Yes, ma'am.
I can't hear you!
[BOTH shout]
Yes, ma'am, we're good!
And now
that we got that settled,
ball's in your court now.
Don't screw it up.
Keep your noses clean
and maybe you guys'll get
somewhere in this industry.
Well, I guess
I'm gonna be heading out now.
I'll let the producer know
about our little talk,
and about how good you were.
Gimme a shout
if you guys need anything,
and I'll send
a couple of my boys down
to give y'all a hand.
-[engine starts]
-Vroom. Vroom, vroom.
Vroom, vroom.
[mimics siren]
-[AKIRA mimics siren]
-[MINORU sighs]
[MAN vocalizing music]
[MEN] On the next
episode of "Lucky Star"...
[MEN chattering]
[KAGAMI]
Come on, everybody!
There's only one more episode,
so let's do this right.
Hello? You guys listening?
Fine, whatever.
I'll just do it by myself, then.
Next time, "To Be Decided."
No way!
They haven't decided?