[KONATA]
Okay, let's do this.
[MIYUKI]
Sure, let's go.
[TSUKASA]
Grr!
[KAGAMI]
Quit screwing around and start!
[singing in Japanese]
[insects buzzing]
Summertime! Beach time!
Before we leave, ma'am,
I want to make sure
you and my cousin are okay
with driving and supervising.
[BOTH]
Oh, yeah!
That's interesting.
Hmm?
You guys must have
a lot of time on your hands.
[BOTH]
Grr!
Sorry if we're taking you away
from your day off.
Oh, no, it's totally cool.
Narumi-san, is it true
you're a police officer
in the traffic safety division?
That's right! I'm the expert
when it comes to traffic laws.
-He passed me.
-Huh?
Damn him!
[KAGAMI thinking] Hey, wait,
you're supposed to be a cop!
[KONATA]
She goes nuts when
she's behind the wheel
She's out of control.
And we just sacrificed
Kagami and Tsukasa to her.
Oh, come on now.
She's a police officer, right?
Hmm? Hey, that's weird.
They were there a second ago.
[gasps]
No, Teach, you're going down
the wrong street!
It says one-way, look!
[wailing]
[thinking] I can't believe I got
it wrong both times. Curses!
[car accelerating]
♪ Ah, yeah ♪
♪ Yo, yo, yo! ♪
♪ Gravity! Gravity! ♪
♪ Feel the power ♪
[screeching]
[MAN] The blue car's
amazing! Who's driving it?
That freaking drift
on the turn was awesome!
It's gaining on the FD!
It's got some serious pickup.
He missed the rail
by like that much!
A good point of attack
would be...
on the five hairpin curves
that are comin' up.
[cars accelerating]
♪ Open your eyes,
open your mind ♪
[MAN] It's speeding up!
Did the brakes die?
No way!
What's with her and her
bleeping-D driving?
[KONATA] Nanako-san,
you're a good driver.
A really good driver.
Huh? You think?
It's funny, but I always
get motion sickness
when riding in cars.
Today, I brought along some
medicine that would keep me
from getting sick.
But you see, Nanako-san,
because you're a skilled driver,
I didn't get sick at all!
Huh?
[growls]
What am I doing talking to you?
We gotta get outta here!
[insects buzzing]
[sighing]
[KUROI]
Okay.
Guess we should find a hotel.
Wow!
It's so sunny outside.
It's perfect for swimming.
I swear, yesterday I didn't
think we'd ever get here alive.
[KONATA]
I'm going to put my swimsuit on
and wear it down to the beach.
Sometimes you can be so
childish, Konata-- [screams]
[thinking]
No way, you can't be serious.
Hey, aren't you a little old
to be wearing
your school swimsuit in public?
Not if you're catering
to special interests, Kagami.
[thinking]
Whoa, how old is that thing?
Hey, do you really
need one of those tubes?
I mean, you're so athletic
and I know you can swim.
Just because I know
how to swim doesn't mean
I have to jump in and start
swimming marathons.
There's a thing called leisure,
you know.
Sweet leisure.
Since I'm trying to meet
the needs
of folks with special interests,
I'm using this thing
'cause it completes the outfit.
I don't think anyone
with special interests
would go to the beach.
Hmm.
You always see people
splittin' watermelons in manga
and anime, but it never
happens in real life.
Naw, I've seen
that happen before.
Maybe people think
it's a waste of food.
You got a point.
'Cause when you blow up
watermelons with a shotgun,
you get pieces of watermelon
all over you.
You watch too much anime.
Miyuki-san, you're rich, have
you ever split watermelons?
I can't say I've
ever done that.
Hmm, on second thought,
I guess I can't really picture
rich people doin'
that kind of stuff.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Oh.
[chuckles mischievously]
[gasps]
Hmm. That figures.
Nothing happens in real life
the way it does in manga.
I'm so sorry
I disappointed you.
So it's like, you know,
whatever. Man, it's so sad.
Here we are at the beach
and we have to babysit.
We're a couple
of lonely single ladies.
-You got it all wrong.
-Oh, yeah,
you could compromise
and lug something
like that around,
but that's no fun.
Give me a bunch of girls
and I'm a happy camper.
-You know?
-But I'm not--
I hear more and more folks are
getting married later in life.
Guess you and I've got
all the time in the world.
-Know what I'm sayin'?
-[thinking] You got it wrong.
The only reason that I'm here
is because my husband and me
have a commuter marriage.
I'm married, married!
If the beach is a mecca
for pickin' up girls,
how come no one's pickin' us up?
It's better this way,
'cause no one's bothering us.
Besides, with you and your
outfit, the guys probably think
we're sisters on vacation
with the parents.
-[grunts]
-[laughs]
[TSUKASA]
Yokkoi Shouichi!
[whimpering]
[whimpers]
[KONATA]
What's wrong?
Oh, you know, doesn't it
feel kinda gross to sit down
when you're all sopping wet?
[MIYUKI]
I know how you feel.
Maybe you should get
into an air chair pose.
She doesn't need a workout.
Hmm...
[grunting]
-What's wrong?
-My neck's tired.
I see.
Yes, I totally knew it!
What are you getting
so excited about?
We've just been served food
that's the epitome
of the beach house experience.
Check it out, runny curry.
That's what I'm talkin' about.
You're right.
Isn't it weird how the things
you'd never eat in everyday life
become amazingly delicious
when you eat them
in a place like this?
[gulping]
Woo-ha!
Chugging beers
at the beach is awesome!
Who cares if it's lukewarm?
This stuff's the best.
[YUI]
Yeah, but they're pushing it
when they charge you
300 yen for a lousy hot dog.
Yeah, right?
The thing's almost raw,
but who cares?
You still eat it anyway.
I kinda like how when you
order the fried chicken,
it's always really greasy and
it's got way too many spices.
The plain fried noodles
also seem to be
much more delicious here.
[lively chattering]
Hey. Does the food here
really deserve all the hype?
Uh-huh. But it's not as cool
as running down the beach
in a loincloth.
That supposed to be
another anime reference?
[YUI]
I'm so hammered.
Looks like we're spending
another night here.
Is that okay, Yui-neisan?
[YUI] I've got
another day of vacation.
It's cool, I'm fine.
[shrieking]
[shivering]
The water's really cold.
Oh, come on, ma'am,
it can't be that cold.
You're just exaggerating.
[shouts]
[yawning]
[ALL] Lucky Star.
[TSUKASA humming]
[splashing]
-[hair squeaks]
-Oh.
Why does your hair
always feel so squeaky
after you've been swimming
in the ocean?
Well, maybe it's got something
to do with all the salt
in the water. Right, Miyuki?
That's true.
It's mostly caused by the salt
and also by the ultraviolet rays
from the sun.
But is that really
such a bad thing?
Your hair's always exposed
to UV rays anyway.
That's also true, but do you
really want me to explain it?
Because I'm afraid it's
quite involved and lengthy.
[ALL] Mm-hmm!
All right!
[clears throat]
The reason your hair becomes
damaged at the beach is due
to exposure to UV rays
as well as salt and seawater
and ocean breezes.
When exposed to these elements,
your hair loses moisture.
Furthermore, if you sunbathe
under strong UV rays,
the melanin in your hair
begins to change,
causing your hair to lighten.
If salts or impurities, such as
chlorine from swimming pools
remain in your hair
for any length of time,
it causes your hair
to turn brittle.
UV rays and impurities are
the main cause
of follicular damage
during the summer season.
However, the factors
I've mentioned also cause
significant damage
to the hair's cuticles.
So, when exposed to strong
UV rays, the cystine bonds
that preserve your hair's
strength become--
[knocking]
Hey, guys, lookit.
♪ Timotei! Timotei! Timotei! ♪
What the?
[grumbles]
[moans]
Sometimes I wonder how
the other folks see us,
when they see us.
I don't know.
[BOTH thinking]
Another short conversation.
I guess they probably
think we look like family
or something like that.
Yeah, I guess.
[YUI thinking]
That's all you've got to say?
Yui-neesan, look!
♪ Timotei! Timotei! Timotei! ♪
No way! I used to do that too!
Bitchin'! That's just
the reaction I was looking for.
How old are you, kid?
Mmm! Mandom.
Enough with the bad puns,
Gramps.
What's wrong, Kona-chan?
Looks like I just
triggered a flag.
What are you talking about?
An event scene is gonna happen.
Remember, if you want to see
all your choices at the end,
save often.
I've going in, girls.
[muttering]
Picture's complete.
That's perfect. Bring it.
I had no idea.
You're such a geek.
No wonder today was
so totally boring.
What do you mean?
Did any guys hit on us today?
[gasping]
It's not like I-- You're the one
who brought it up.
I wasn't obsessing about it
or anything, I was just saying.
That's why I brought up.
Oh, now I get it.
You wanted someone
to hit on you.
No, that's not it.
-[MIYUKI shrieks]
-[thudding]
Oh, no, I missed it!
What is it?
Oh, nothing.
I was just wondering what
you did with unwanted hair.
Well, I'm kinda smooth all over,
so I don't really do anything.
Oh.
What do you do?
Ah! Who me?
I guess I'm kinda normal.
Hmm.
Actually today was kind of risky
for me, if you know what I mean.
No, I don't.
It was almost time for my...
-[gasps]
-...you know what to happen.
[giggling] Oh, I get it.
But it didn't, so that's good.
Were you okay
with yours today?
Mm-hmm, it missed me.
Mine ended just last week,
so I guess you could say,
it was perfect timing.
It's such a hassle when
you want to go to the beach.
Yeah, I know.
It sucks when you can't go
in the water because of it.
But you could always use
one of those thingies.
Yeah, right, but you
still worry about it.
I've never used
one of those things.
-Hmm.
-[shrieking]
Someone's having a blunt
conversation.
What if we are?
It's not like you never--
You're kidding!
What are you lookin' at?
Oh, nothing.
[KONATA]
The story I'm about to tell you
really happened.
A man who worked for a video
software wholesaler left work
one night as he usually did.
It was especially dark
that night
as he got on the bus
to go home.
This man lived
on the edge of town
near where the bus route ended.
One by one the passengers were
dropped off, but the man,
he was alone, riding through
the inky blackness
on this especially dark night.
The bus so was empty
and so quiet now,
the driver thought he was alone,
but he wasn't.
And then...
[gulps]
...he sang "Danzen! Futari Wa...
Cure" in a really loud voice!
[screaming]
Anyhow,
that's the way I heard it.
-[sighs of relief]
-[excited chattering]
[snoring]
[whimpering]
[startled gasp]
Huh?
Oh.
[flushes]
Oh, wow,
wasn't that a scary story?
[laughs] Yeah,
actually it was...
I'm Sukekiyo!
[screaming]
Where the hell did
you get that thing?
Good night, sleep well.
Okay, then, good night.
Inugami clan!
[screaming]
I love scaring Tsukasa.
Go to sleep, already.
[KUROI]
Hey, let's bail!
Oh, okay.
[waves crashing]
[thinking]
I don't have anything
funny to say now.
I'm Tsukasa. I'm Tsukasa.
[screaming]
-Kagami!
-Huh?
-What's wrong?
-It was so scary.
I believe the girl has
taken another step on the path
toward womanhood, Kagami.
Huh?
Man, this year's Comp Fest
is gonna be huge.
The Japanese are suckers
for limited edition stuff.
If labeling stuff as
limited edition is enough
to boost sales, they should
slap it on everything.
Well, if they did that, it
wouldn't be limited, would it?
[MAN on TV]
Though we asked around,
and the truth is
that if you drink...
Don't forget, girls, make sure
to clean up your rooms
before your vacation ends.
Wow! Cool! It's my old
junior high textbooks.
Hey, sis, look.
Check out this old photo album.
Look at this weird
picture of Dad.
[KAGAMI]
Yeah, when I saw that,
it made me wonder
about his thing.
You guys look like
you're having fun.
How's the cleaning going?
Let's see.
Hey, do you want
these clothes?
Oh, yeah, sure,
I'll take them.
Okay, I'll leave them here.
Thanks, sis.
Hey, you want this?
Sure, if you don't want it.
How about this? And this?
[thinking]
Wait! Is she using me
as her trash bin
or something?
You always end up
flipping through
old photo albums instead.
Yeah, I know, I know.
When I find an old magazine,
I can't help but read it.
That's just what I mean.
Hey, where's Tsukasa?
Oh, you know my sister.
She has a hard time
throwing anything away.
She's still cleaning.
Yeah, she seems like the type
who totally keeps everything.
Although, you seem to be the
type who throws everything away.
You know, this negative image
you have of me is really
starting to piss me off, girl.
Wow, you kept all of your
junior high textbooks?
What, you mean you
didn't keep yours?
Oh, no, I left all of that stuff
behind along with my memories.
No, take them home.
You're causing trouble
for the school.
At last,
I finished my cleaning.
Even though there's stuff
I know I'll never use again,
I remembered the times I did,
so now I can't throw them out.
Well, that's just
the way some people are.
They want to keep everything.
You're that type
of person, Tsukasa.
You seem to be the type who'd
toss stuff that could be useful.
I mean, you still leave
all your textbooks behind.
Miyuki, you know you really
should go and get
your teeth checked before
school starts up again.
I know that I should.
It's just that I don't
think that I could.
Well, if that's the case,
I'd feel really bad making you
head all the way down there.
If you can't go to the dentist,
we'll just have
the dentist come here.
No, please, wait a minute!
[ALL]
Lucky Star.
Lucky Channel!
Hiya, Luckies!
Time for the sixth episode
of "Lucky Channel."
Can you guys believe it?
I am Akira Kogami and I hope
you guys are getting used
to this segment
'cause I sure am.
[exclaims]
That's lame.
Did you say something?
[choking]
Oh, well, it looks like my
assistant, Minoru Shiraishi,
still isn't used to this.
He must be nervous 'cause
all the people are watching.
I'd really like it if
he'd get used to his job.
Especially when he's
talking to his superiors.
I mean, how many times does
a girl have to remind him
before he gets it, you know?
It's irritating!
Anyway, on today's episode,
we're going to introduce you
to a key character
on "Lucky Star."
It's Konata!
[whimpering]
Shut up, you pussy.
Why me? I didn't ask for this!
Miss Konata Izumi is 17.
She likes games,
anime, and manga.
Yes, and according to our
sources, she's always watching
the new shows and
reading the latest manga.
On weekends, she spends her
time gaming online till dawn.
So, you're saying
she's an "otaku."
Well, yeah, I guess she is.
Huh...
Hurry, do something.
You know those crazy otaku,
they never leave the house.
They're always crying
while watching
the "Dog of Flanders" and stuff.
How dated is your idea
of otaku anyway?
You do your homework or what?
Can you handle your job, guy,
or what?
Well, umm...
Well, it's true that both
the "Dog of Flanders"
and cute "moe" characters both
have a healing effect, you know?
But girls like me are way
better than some mangey dog.
These days, the public
really wants to see
cute, innocent girls, right?
When I look to the right,
they look to the right.
If I look left, they look left.
They wait in line all night
before a concert
and they don't take a bath.
They stink so bad it makes
your eyes water
and yet, they still
want to see me.
That's what drives them.
Standing like cattle
in the heat, burning under
the damn sun waiting for me. Me!
Waiting until the bandanas
around their heads get so sweaty
and it's all for me!
[sighs]
But in the end, I guess they
are the customers, though.
Even if they insist
on telling me their life story
at a handshake session.
And even if they do make
a few off-topic comments,
you sympathize with them,
you know?
'Cause in the end,
the only reason I'm here
is 'cause of folks like that.
I gotta do my best up here,
'cause those people are my fans,
you know?
Is that what it's
really like for you?
Oh, you'll find out real soon.
Being an idol is the hardest
thing you'll ever do.
Oh, yeah, once you've been
through the best and the worst,
you'll see what it's all about.
Some client or fan you hate
comes up and you gotta smile.
Oh, that was fun!
Okay, did everybody get a good
idea about who Konata-san is?
Yeah? Good! Then I'll see you
again in the next episode.
Bye-nee!
[MINORU]
Uh, actually today's show was
more about otakus
than Konata-san.
[AKIRA sighs]
[MINORU]
Uh, are you okay?
[AKIRA]
You do it.
[MINORU]
Huh? Oh sure!
At that moment,
the reporter saw...
[AKIRA] Now that's lame.
[KONATA]
Yeah! That was awesome.
Kage rules!
[KAGAMI]
Okay, calm down.
So, Tsukasa,
did you pick a song?
[TSUKASA]
Yep, I did.
[MIYUKI] I can't wait to hear
you sing, Tsukasa-san.
[TSUKASA laughs]
I hope I can sing it good.
[KAGAMI] Hey, Miyuki,
what are you gonna sing?
[MIYUKI] Oh, I don't
know that many songs.
It's a little embarrassing.
[pop music playing]
[KONATA] Ooh!
That's what she picked, huh?
[MIYUKI]
Go for it, Tsukasa-san!
[TSUKASA singing
Japanese pop song]
[KONATA singing off-key]
L-O-V-E, lovely, Tsukasa!
[KAGAMI]
Oh, jeez.
[KONATA singing off-key]
L-O-V-E, lovely, Sayuri!
[KAGAMI]
Who's Sayuri?
[TSUKASA singing in Japanese]
[KONATA]
Whoo-hoo!
[TSUKASA singing in Japanese]
[TSUKASA]
♪ Oh baby! ♪
[KONATA]
The name isn't Sayuri Kuninama.
[KAGAMI]
Does anyone know who Sayuri is?
[KONATA] What was her
membership number again?
[TSUKASA singing in Japanese]
[KONATA cheering,
singing off-key]
[KAGAMI]
You're ruining the song.
-[TSUKASA singing in Japanese]
-[KONATA singing off-key]
[ANNOUNCER] On the next episode
of "Lucky Star..."
Kagami here.
You know how
when you've got a hangnail
and it's just wiggling around?
You want to pull it out,
but you think it's gonna hurt,
so you don't, but then you do
and it comes out and it's bigger
than you thought and it hurts!
Then there's scabs.
You try to time it so it doesn't
hurt when you peel it off,
but then it starts getting
itchy and you think,
"Sure that sucker's ready
to rip, let's do this."
So you go slow, peeling
from the sides first and then
you just rip through the center
and you end up bleeding anyway.
And then you're like,
"That's gonna leave a scar."
Next time: "Image."
[ANNOUNCER]
Look forward to it!