[KONATA]
Okay, let's do this.
[MIYUKI]
Sure, let's go.
[TSUKASA]
Grrr!
[KAGAMI]
Quit screwin' around and start!
[theme music playing]
[car engine running]
Yutaka! Come on,
we gotta get going.
[panting]
Upsy daisy.
Okay, sis.
Get ready for the first
day of your new life.
Let's rock, man!
[YUTAKA]
Ahh!
Attention, everyone!
I'm here to announce
that Yutaka got accepted!
Woohoo! Bring her in already.
Come on, Yutaka.
Well, I just wanted
to say thank you
for letting me stay with you.
And I promise
I won't be any trouble.
Just go ahead and make
yourself at home here, okay?
Oh, thanks.
By the way, congrats
on getting accepted.
Oh, thank you!
Man, I'm so glad
you got accepted.
You'll get to hang out
with that handkerchief...
[SOJIRO thinking]
I'm a winner.
I'm living the dream.
[sigh]
Are you all right?
Oh!
Do you want me to take
you to the nurse's office?
[YUTAKA]
She actually talked to me.
And then she let me
borrow her handkerchief.
It makes me all happy
'cause I'm gonna have
a best friend now.
That's really cool and all,
but what if she
doesn't get accepted?
Uhh...
No! People like her
always get accepted! Always!
I know how you feel.
It's just that--
And she's probably
really smart, too!
I didn't say she wasn't.
Thanks for clearing that up,
though.
Hang on.
Yu-chan,
what would you have done
if you didn't get accepted?
Oh, I know, I know.
Don't remind me.
[sigh]
Don't sweat it, Yu-chan.
I'm sure you're gonna be okay.
You're right!
I'll see her again on
the day they announce
the names of the people
who got accepted.
Yeah, maybe.
I still have to return
the handkerchief to her.
[groan]
[YUTAKA]
'Scuse me!
Here. I'm really glad
to see you again.
And I've been wanting to
give this back to you.
You wanna give it back?
Yes.
Sorry. I didn't
wanna trouble you.
I gave it to you thinking
that you would keep it.
To be honest,
I really didn't think
I'd ever see you again.
You didn't think I'd be
accepted here, did you?
No.
I see.
Now I get it. You must be
in the same grade as I am.
I'm sorry, I didn't realize.
It's okay. I guess you thought
I was someone's kid sister.
My family's
picking me up today, so--
Oh, okay.
Well, goodbye, then.
Um, I hope that
the next three years
are gonna be awesome for us.
[YUTAKA thinking]
I'm so lucky.
I haven't even
started high school,
and I've already got
a good friend.
Oh, I forgot to ask her name.
[KONATA]
When you see her again,
make sure you ask for her name.
-[YUTAKA] Mmm.
-[KONATA] Mmm.
How are you feeling?
Are you sick or something?
Oh, yeah. It was the ride over.
I got a little carsick.
I did take some
medicine, though.
Don't worry.
I'll be okay in a bit.
Yutaka's such a frail and
delicate little girl, ain't she?
Wait. Sure she is,
but seriously.
Do you have any idea what
your driving's like, Onee-san?
I mean [hic]
even I got a little...
I wonder
if I'm gonna get along
with all my new classmates
at Ryouou High.
I mean, I'm the only one
out of my old school
that made it in,
and if I get sick
real easy like today--
Don't worry, Yutaka. You're
a good girl. You'll be fine.
Grr. Stop treating me
like a little kid!
[KONATA]
Hm...
Thinking...
Converting...
If you and Miyuki-san
teamed up, that would be
the most awesomest thing in
the history of everything.
Huh?
[birds chirping]
[yawning]
That's right. I'm living in
Konata Onee-chan's house now.
Oh. Oh!
Good morning, Onee-chan.
Why you up so early
on a holiday?
Oh. Actually I was
about to jump into bed.
So I guess it's good night.
I was up playing
games all n-- [yawn]
This place is way
different than my house!
You know how we've got
college entrance exams
coming up next year?
We've been getting
all these calls
from cram schools and
telemarketers selling textbooks.
Man, they're so annoying.
However, if you have
caller ID on your phone,
you can tell right away
if someone like that
is calling you.
On the display, the number
shows up as restricted.
[KAGAMI]
I'm home!
Caller ID, huh?
Hello, Mother. I'm home.
Oh, you can't be serious.
I can't imagine how much
trouble that must've been.
Oh no, it's the same way
in our family. Absolutely.
I'm sorry to cut you off, but my
daughter's just come home.
Yes, yes, we'll talk again soon.
All right then,
have a wonderful day.
You are you talking to?
It sounded like
a lively conversation.
Oh, that was just
a telemarketer.
Mother, I'm sorry,
but didn't you see
it was a telemarketer
when they were calling?
Yes, but I was bored.
So I decided to have
a conversation anyway.
And we ended up talking
for more than an hour.
[CASHIER]
Okay, the total comes to--
What was that about winning
the National Championship?
Tsukasa,
the world's a war zone!
You can never show mercy, ever!
The other day,
I saw this thing
I wanted to get
with my reward points.
So I thought,
"Do I go offense and get it
or defense and save my
points?" So I got it!
But now there's a new
thing that just came out
and I wanna get it
before anyone else!
It's that one over there, but
I don't have enough points!
What'll I do? What'll I do?
Someone sure enjoys
their life, don't they?
Um, you gonna pay?
Okay, where would y'all
like to sit?
Smoking or non-smoking?
Uh, yeah, since we're a
little on the underage side,
maybe we'll go
with non-smoking.
Come this way, please.
Um, I gotta go
to the bathroom first.
Okay.
Oh, hey, Tsukasa, we're
over here. Over here!
Took you long enough.
I know. Sorry.
I have to say this, 'cause
I think about it a lot.
But you know when
you go to a restaurant
and need to use the bathroom?
How come it's always
by the smoking section?
Yeah, right?
Especially since we went
out of our way
to get non-smoking.
Seriously, though, I wonder
why they have it like that.
Well, if someone starts a fire,
they got a place close by
where they can get their
hands on some water.
They can fill up buckets
there and hook up a hose.
Oh, I didn't know they
had a hose back there.
Of course they do. You
didn't know they had a hose?
Hah! That's right.
Someone's never worked a single
day out in the real world.
No, she hasn't.
-Nope. Not at all.
-[KAGAMI] Okay, shut up.
Or one covers the stink
of the other, maybe?
We're gonna eat, so stop talking
about toilets and stinks.
It's kinda gross, okay?
And in other news,
a number of incidents
have occurred recently,
where girls on their
way to elementary school
have been approached from behind
and harassed by a stranger.
We're starting to see
a lot of stuff like that
happening to kids lately.
You better be careful
when you go out, Yu-chan.
Yeah, I will.
Unacceptable!
But I can understand how
he's probably feeling.
You understand him?
They talk about this guy
on the news every day,
making a big deal out of him.
It's amazing to think that
there's someone out there
harassing little girls
like that.
And if I had the chance,
I'd tell him,
"Aren't you jealous of me?"
I'm a little worried
about your thinking, Dad.
Just please don't do anything
that Yui-neisan
can arrest you for, okay?
Huh?
[meow]
[GIRLS]
Lucky Star!
[KONATA]
Is anybody home?
[TSUKASA]
Yes!
Yoohoo! Hello!
Come on in.
[birds chirping]
Where's Kagami?
What's she up to?
Oh, she's hanging out
with a couple of her friends
from class.
Oh, yeah?
It's just, I don't know.
It feels like something's
missing, and it's frustrating.
Maybe 'cause you miss her.
[birds chirping]
Man, is it me, or has it
gotten super-warm out lately?
Yeah, it has.
Isn't it peaceful now
that we're on spring break
and don't have
any homework to do?
Yeah, it is.
[KAGAMI]
Yes, it is.
And I think
that line's reserved
for those who actually
do their homework,
as opposed to copying it.
[MAN IN VIDEO GAME 1]
Don't get in any strange places.
[MAN IN VIDEO GAME 2]
That's impossible!
So, when you're playing
robot games like this,
do you really know who all
the characters are and stuff?
Yeah. I guess
you could say I do.
Hmm. Really?
'Cause I remember
you said that your taste
in anime and manga was
all because of your dad.
[KONATA]
Yup.
Oh, yeah?
So when you were younger,
did you have a hard time
keeping up with the girls
when they started talking
girl stuff?
Hmm? I didn't have a hard time
keeping up with anything.
I got to see way more
of that kinda stuff
than they ever did.
Oh. Uh, yeah.
Okay.
Is that your final answer?
[WOMAN ON TV]
That's my final answer!
[deep breaths]
[suspenseful music]
[commercial music]
[sigh]
Man, that big ol' pause he
takes kills me every time.
And his face is so big,
it's scary.
[TSUKASA]
Oh, it looks like
the show's about to end.
I guess she got
the question wrong.
Oh, come on!
You're guessing if they
got the question right
by looking at how much time
the show's got left
before the commercial.
Yeah, but I can't stand
the suspense of not knowing.
They drag it out too long.
But the show's all about
enjoying that part of it.
Yup, that's our Tsukasa.
[birds chirping]
Hey, you!
Hey, you, too.
Well, here she is.
My cousin, Yu-chan.
Go on, say hi.
It's nice to meet you.
I'm Yutaka Kobayakawa.
And these are my best
friends, Kagami and Tsukasa.
Yeah, I know.
You're the ones Onee-chan
always talks about.
Oh? What kinda stuff has
she been saying about us?
Uh...
What in the hell have
you been telling this girl?
The way she looked just now,
I wonder.
[KONATA]
See? You see? What'd I tell ya?
So, did you already have
your graduation ceremony?
Oh, yes. The other day.
Wow. Graduation.
What memories, huh, guys?
I don't really remember
my graduation ceremony.
So did you get a button
from any of the guys in
your class, Yutaka-chan?
Oh no. I didn't.
At my old junior high,
our uniform was a blazer.
That's right.
I guess a lot of schools
are like that these days.
Although, maybe it's because
there's not a whole lot
of that "getting something
from your crush"
stuff going on anymore.
You really think so?
It sounds kinda sad, but I
guess I never did it myself.
Every now and then,
I'll read a blog
where someone's
talking about that stuff,
so it's sorta still going on.
Wait a minute.
It's all about getting something
from someone you like, right?
Isn't that the whole point
of doing it?
But then you totally
out yourself as having
a crush on the guy when
you go get the button.
Why don't you ask the guy out
and get the whole guy
instead of just a button?
Ideally, yeah.
I guess that's what
you'd wanna have happen.
So, Yutaka-chan,
did you have someone
that you had
a crush on or something?
Oh, not me.
I'd have to stay home a lot
'cause I felt sick.
Even when I went to class,
I'd start feeling ill.
I think I kinda made
everyone around me depressed.
And there's the fact that
I'm really short and frail
and I kinda look like
a little kid.
Everyone was always
making fun of me.
Why would anybody fall in
love with me, you know?
You'll be fine, Yu-chan.
There's definitely
a need for girls like you
as long as you aren't picky.
Huh? Picky?
Pocky. Hey, Yu-chan, can I
take a look at your yearbook?
Me, too.
I wanna see your yearbook.
Well, it's a little
embarrassing.
There's not a lot of
pictures of me or anything.
Hmm.
So what class were you in again?
Wait a second!
Were you checking the absentee
list for my name just now?
You were, weren't you?
Oh, was I being that obvious?
Hmm!
You wanna know the difference
between junior high
and high school?
-[YUTAKA] Mm-hmm.
-[TSUKASA] I know.
For one thing,
they don't make you join
an extracurricular club.
I don't know. Doesn't
that depend on the school?
Well, one difference is
that we're a prep school,
so our curriculum's
bigger and faster-paced
than the one you had
in junior high.
And I guess you'll need more
stamina than in junior high
'cause the commute to
school's really long.
One difference I've noticed
is that from elementary
school through high school,
the time you spend
sleeping at your desk
gets longer and longer.
Especially during hard classes.
Yeah, that's totally true!
Like when you start drifting off
'cause the teacher's talking--
No matter what you do, do
not end up like them, okay?
Okay.
[KONATA]
Hey, Yu-chan,
I see you kept your old
junior high uniform.
Yeah, I thought maybe
I could wear it
as my street clothes
without anyone noticing.
It looks plain enough,
don't you think?
Yeah, I guess.
Hey, Kagami. What'd you
guys do with your uniforms?
Oh, we gave ours to a couple
of younger girls
in our neighborhood.
What about you?
What about me?
You probably
couldn't find anyone
tiny enough to give it to.
Two things, Kagami:
you're rude and shut up.
Anyway, I did what Yu-chan did.
I kept mine
for cosplay purposes.
C-cos?
Yeah, when you put it that
way, it sounds really bad.
Like, really bad.
It's just cosplay, man.
Talking about it sure
brings back memories.
Sometimes I think it'd be cool
to go back to my elementary
school and junior high,
see my old teachers
and say hi and stuff.
But there's been all this stuff
about people
trespassing at schools.
If you went back, chances are
you'd get funny looks
from everyone.
Yeah, and if you went back,
you'd fit right in.
It'd be like you never left.
I'm pretty sure
you weren't trying
to compliment me there,
were you?
Our vacation went by
fast this time, didn't it?
I hear that.
It's like before you know it,
school's about to start
all over again.
And now that spring's here,
we've got all those physical
exams and fitness tests.
Oh man, what a pain.
But you're lucky, Kona-chan.
Your motor nerves are so good.
Hey, Tsukasa,
which nerves are supposed to
be the motor nerves anyway?
Hello, everybody!
How's it going?
Sorry I'm late. And congrats
on the graduating, Yutaka.
Hey, neisan. Come on in.
'Cause we're celebrating
a graduation,
how about we all
go out drinking together?
It's my treat.
Uncle Sojiro's going.
[KONATA]
Woah!
[KAGAMI]
Excuse me, Officer?
We're underage.
Onee-chan, I don't think
they'll even let us
through the door.
You should know
better than that.
[laughter] They won't
notice if you walk in
like you're supposed
to be there.
When I was a student,
I did it all the time,
and I never got caught, man.
Not even once.
[KAGAMI]
Uh-uh.
Your two little relatives
would totally blow our cover.
[SOJIRO]
Hm, really? [grunt]
You'll live.
[SOJIRO]
I was thinking it might be nice
if we all went out to the
amusement park or something.
It's still vacation.
Ohh.
Um, that sounds like
fun and everything,
but you don't have to.
I don't wanna be a burden.
I'd feel bad if you go to
all that trouble for me.
Besides, I went there
on a field trip
with my class the other day.
Hey!
I just remembered I went there
on field trip with
my class, too.
How about it, though?
Were you okay there?
Mm-hmm. I didn't get sick
the whole time I was there.
And I got to hang out
with my friends.
No, I mean were you okay
with the height restrictions
on the rides?
What are you talking about?
I was fine.
I'm in high school now, okay?
You know, I was watching
a school drama show
and I got to thinking.
Junior high and high school
are totally different,
aren't they?
Huh? Well, yeah.
And I heard that the lunches
aren't given out
like in junior high.
Yeah, I guess not.
Either you bring your own lunch
or you gotta buy one
in the cafeteria.
Or you could buy lunch
and bring it.
Do you make a lunch
to take to school every day,
Onee-chan?
[chuckles]
Well, yeah, sure.
Wow!
You're cool!
[KONATA]
Uh-oh, this isn't good.
[YUTAKA thinking]
She's really good at games.
She can communicate
all kinds of ways.
And she cooks and does chores!
So yeah,
I think I'm getting an idea
of the pressure you
feel as an older sister.
When she looks at me
with those big eyes,
I feel like I gotta
do my best, you know?
[YUI]
Huh?
[YUI grunts]
[KONATA]
Yui-neisan drives like a maniac.
Aha! What's up? How ya doing?
[KONATA]
Yui-neisan gets drunk
and crashes at our place.
Homework, huh?
Eh, as long as
you keep it vague,
put down whatever you want.
[KONATA]
Yui-neisan says
irresponsible things.
But then again I wonder
if it depends on the person.
[YUI]
I have no idea
what you're talking about.
[snore]
[GIRLS]
Lucky Star.
My final answer is
my ass, buddy.
I am not doing this anymore.
Uh-uh...
[MINORU thinking]
And she's mad again.
...and when I watch the
damn thing, where'd I go?
[MINORU thinking]
Should I do it? I'm gonna do it.
Aw yeah, I'm gonna do it.
Uh, Akira-sama, you forgot to
call out the title. The title.
Huh?
Uh, please call out
the title, please?
-[grunts]
-[MINORU] Tiny eyes.
Hiya, luckies.
Like any of it matters.
What a friggin' crock.
Right now,
I am so disgusted, man.
All I get's a voice cameo?
Me. Just my voice.
Whoopdie-doodle-doo!
Well, they didn't give me
any screen time, either--
Who cares?
I wasn't talking about you!
[MINORU]
Windy.
Well, Sunshine, did anyone
ask about you just now? Huh?
At any time
during the conversation,
was your flippin' name
ever brought up?
Uh, no, I guess nobody said
anything about me.
Then why the hell are
you butting in like that?
You just come sliding out
with your big fat head.
What are you,
stupid or something?
Always cutting me off
with your me-me-me thing.
Looks like someone's
self-centered, eh, Shiraishi?
Ugh, this thing is leaving
a film in my mouth.
Listen up, Peaches,
the problem
is that I, Akira Kogami,
was not shown
on screen in the main segment.
[MINORU]
I know!
Let me ask you something.
I'm an idol, right? I am.
Well, an idol's face is
their number-one asset.
It needs to be on screen,
or am I wrong?
Yes! I mean, no!
I mean, you're absolutely right!
Huh? I did not hear you.
Ah! What the staff did to you
was completely inexcusable
and unprofessional.
May I ask what you're
writing over there?
[AKIRA] Okay, guys!
Akira needs your help!
I need all your support
so that I, Akira Kogami,
can show up in the main
segment of the show.
So make sure you send in
wads of requests for it.
[MINORU]
What?
I don't care how you get
the message out there.
Just push hard for me, okay?
I really want you guys to
see how good an actor I am.
I really, really want it!
-[MINORU] Really, really?
-[AKIRA] And, just between us,
Compared to my charms, the
other cast members got nothing.
It's really too sad. Yup.
It's sort of like
if you compared
an Oscar-winning
Hollywood actress...
[MINORU]
She's getting desperate.
Really desperate.
Hee-hee.
My acting's on a higher level!
It's pretty. It's gorgeous.
You'll wanna see more!
So here's your chance
to do something good.
Write a letter or leave
a comment on the site.
Your voices will
count for something.
All your wishes
will come true...
[MINORU]
Something wrong?
...if you guys can get me
an on-camera role in Lucky Star!
What? Stop her? Really?
Um, hey, Akira-sama--
Shut the hell up!
What's with all the chitchat
when my career's at stake?
How many times
I gotta tell you?
When I'm talking, you
better shut your stupid--
[theme music]
You're kidding!
Aw, I was just
getting to the part
where I tell you
how fabulous I am.
Or maybe I could show you
guys just how awesome I am
in the main segment
of the next episode.
Just kidding! [laughs]
Yeah. We'll see you all
in the next episode.
-Bye!
-[MINORU chuckles]
[AKIRA]
That was so freaking painful.
Go get me the producer.
Chop chop!
[MINORU]
What, who, me?
[AKIRA] You awake?
This is supposed to be
a revised script, yeah?
So what in the hell is
the title of our segment?
[MINORU]
Huh? Well, it's Lucky Channel.
[AKIRA]
Yeah, script says
Lucky Paradise.
-[MINORU] Well, I--
-[AKIRA] Shut up!
And another thing--
they've got some nerve
treating me like that.
"Hi, I'm a producer. I worked
on a show that was a hit
so that means
I can be a total--"
[MINORU]
No, what are you saying, stop!
You can't talk to him like that!
[MAN singing in Japanese]
[YUTAKA]
On the next episode
of Lucky Star...
[MINAMI]
I'm Minami Iwasaki.
[YUTAKA]
And I'm Yutaka Kobayakawa.
I guess they want the two of us
to introduce
the next episode, right?
But, do you know
what it's about?
[MINAMI]
No. I'm sorry, I don't.
[YUTAKA]
What, really?
Oh, that's not good.
I don't know anything
about it, either.
Oh, well.
Guess I'll just wrap it up.
Next time,
"I Can't Suddenly Change."
I hope no one minds we
didn't say anything.
[MINAMI]
Look forward to it.