[KONATA]
Okay! Let's do this!
[TSUKASA]
Sure! Let's go!
[KAGAMI]
Quit screwin' around and start!
[singing in Japanese]
Look! They bought
me a new cell phone!
Make sure you don't put
it in the laundry this time.
You're right.
This time I'll keep it
where I won't forget it.
[MATSURI] Tsukasa! Could you
help me out for a sec?
Okay. I'm coming!
[object thumps]
[KAGAMI groans]
[crying]
--Ba...
--[phone beeping]
l...
[KAGAMI sighs]
...sa...
Irritated,
irritated, irritated...
--...mic.
--...irritated, irritated.
--Vine...
--Super irritated.
--...gar!
--Really, really irritated!
Ah! That's
really irritating!
Just type it in already
or let me do it!
[grunts]
No, thanks. I'm okay.
I can do it myself.
I'm here to hang out!
Hey! Come on in, Onee-san.
Whatcha playin' there?
It's a dating sim
that just came out.
Huh.
I think I'm gonna pick a manga
and read that for a while.
Okay.
[thinks] Uh-oh. This game's
got an age restriction.
Either she doesn't
know or she does,
but she's letting it slide.
Okay. Come on, Officer,
which one is it?
Get this. We're having
traffic safety week, right?
So we're taking in people
like there's no tomorrow.
--Huh.
--They're making us run
a check on every little thing,
and we gotta explain
all the traffic laws.
It's a big-time
pain in the butt if you ask me.
And the people even get mad
at me for doing it!
[KONATA thinks]
Knowing you and how you act,
how's anyone supposed
to take you seriously
about laws and safety?
Can you believe it?
I sure can't!
[MIYUKI thinks] I hear the cold
that's been going around now
is lasting a long time.
I need to get better, fast.
According to the number
I've taken,
it looks as though
I'll be here for a while.
I'll just read a book
until I'm called.
[RECEPTIONIST]
Mr. Ando! Mr. Shigeo Ando!
[MAN grunts]
[RECEPTIONIST]
Ms. Takara! Ms. Miyuki Takara!
Ms. Takara! Is there
a Ms. Takara here?
Okay. Is Ms. Mariko
Nishiyama here?
[sighs]
[gasps, thinks] Huh?
What? Did they call me?
What time is it? Oh no!
I need to pay more attention
to my surroundings.
[BUS ANNOUNCER] Coming up
is Kamata, our last stop.
[thinks]
Huh? Oh, no! It happened again!
Where am I?
But in the end I still
had to show Tsukasa
how to send text messages
with her phone.
Even after messaging
with it so much
she told me she never
figured it out.
--Really?
--Oh, yeah!
And now that she knows
how it's done,
she's been texting me non-stop
with anything and
everything she can think of.
It's gotta suck
to be on the receiving end
of all of those texts, though.
--No, not really.
--[cell phone buzzes]
I mean, I'm not
gonna lose any sleep
worrying about it. You know?
Here's the thing.
At first she gets really
excited about stuff,
but then she'll get
bored and move on.
Yeah. I know what you mean.
Some people can be
so childish sometimes.
Uh! I got another.
If she doesn't get bored soon,
you're gonna be hating life.
Wait. She can't have that
much stuff to text you about.
I know. And we're together
all the time anyway.
Oh! And she just
discovered emoticons.
You see?
"You wanna buy the soy
milk cream buns again
on our way home today?"
Hm? What's all that
supposed to mean?
I don't know if you can tell,
but she's really having fun
with emoticons.
Might as well
be hieroglyphics.
[cell phone rings]
Mmm?
Huh. Looks like she
got used to doing it.
[keypad dialing]
--[cell phone rings]
--Hm?
--[television audience laughter]
--[cell phone rings]
[grunts]
[sighs]
--[cell phone rings]
--Huh?
--[gulping]
--[cell phone rings]
[cell phone rings]
[grumbles]
[keypad dialing]
--Okay.
--Oh, jeez!
I get you're having
fun with it and stuff,
but you think you could text
someone else for a change?
Hey.
You guys got a minute?
Sure.
Well, I can't seem
to figure out
how to send these
text message things
--from my phone.
--[TSUKASA thinks] For real?
Oh, Dad. That's super easy.
Can't believe you don't know.
Okay. I'll totally
teach you how.
Isn't it funny how
people learn something new
then run out and brag about
how much of an expert they are?
Uh, yeah.
[laughs]
There just aren't words
to describe that hard stench.
[KAGAMI]
I know. It stinks so bad.
--[TSUKASA giggles] Yeah.
--[KONATA thinks] Huh?
Wow. You sure got a lot of
people in your address book.
--Don't ya?
-Hey! Don't look without asking!
You got stuff you don't want
anyone to see or somethin'?
Not really.
You just don't do that.
It's a guy, right?
It's totally a guy!
No! It isn't a guy!
[cell phone ringing]
[sighs]
She's not picking up
her cell phone.
Guess I'll try
calling the house.
[beeps]
[cell phone rings]
[KONATA]
Hello, Kagami!
Hey, Konata?
You know. It'd be awesome
if you could answer
your cell once in a while.
Yeah. Sorry 'bout that.
The ringer's turned off,
so I didn't know
you were calling me.
[KAGAMI]
It's pointless to have a cell
if you never know
anyone's calling.
[KONATA] Where the heck
is that thing anyway?
[KAGAMI]
See what I'm saying?
There's no point
in you even having one.
Yeah.
So, anyway, I wanted
to ask you about
this coming weekend.
[KONATA] Wait. Hang on.
Dad's calling me.
[SOJIRO] Come on.
What's the deal? Hurry up!
[KONATA] I'll be there
in a minute! Jeez.
[SOJIRO] You've been
on the phone forever.
--Come on!
--[KONATA] All right! Sorry!
Dad just chewed me up
for being on the phone too long.
Oh, sorry.
I sorta always pictured
your place to be kinda chill
when it came to stuff like that.
I guess
it's pretty strict, huh?
[KONATA] Nah. We're just
in the middle of playing
a cool fighting game, is all.
Ugh! Why didn't you say
anything about that before?
Whether they're old or new,
point cards have
magical powers in here.
And then, before
I know what's happening
I'm buying all this stuff
I never planned on.
But you never plan
on anything anyway.
I get what you're
coming from, though.
She's here!
In this city you've got...
...Ani-- and G--mers
She comes into our store,
buys something,
then goes to the other shop
to buy the same thing again!
She's the one known
as Legendary Girl "A"!
Heh.
[yells]
Legendary Girl "A"
shift assemble!
[grunts]
[yells]
[ALL]
Yeah!
Welcome to the store!
We've got the "Haruhi"
Volume 5 DVD in stock!
Limited Edition!
Standard Edition!
We've got 'em both! Oh, yeah!
So, you want more stuff?
We've got stuff coming
in all the time!
[thinks]
Yes, that's right.
Show her everything we've got.
The whole store.
She's gonna clean the place out.
I can feel it.
Whoops. I was looking for
the Limited Edition bookmark
from Aquarian Age.
I gotta go Gamers.
[shift team crying]
This sucks!
[yawns]
[GIRLS]
"Lucky Star."
Awesome!
We'll have
a sleepover this weekend
--and play games all night.
--Cool.
Whenever we do
this kinda stuff,
it's always gotta
be at our house.
--How come we never go to yours?
--Huh?
I'd just like to
see where you live.
Hmm...
It's not that you can't
come over to my house.
The reason I don't invite you
is 'cause my dad's always home
on account of his job.
Oh. That makes sense.
Mm-hmm. Besides.
I don't wanna be
held responsible
if anything happens, you know?
--No, I don't.
--[whimpers]
I'm kinda looking
forward to seeing
what's Konata's house is like.
Hey!
Hi, guys. Come on in.
[KAGAMI] Thanks
for letting us stay the night.
We won't be any trouble.
Oh! It's my pleasure.
I've heard so much
about you guys.
Like that you live in a shrine
and that you're a couple
of shrine maidens.
[KAGAMI thinks]
What's she been telling him!
Ew! And this is
the first thing he asks?
Here it is!
[TSUKASA]
Wow! Look at Kona-chan's room!
I gotta hand it to ya.
You're room's amazing.
Oh! She's so cute!
[sighs]
Where does this go?
Don't tell me.
You don't want me to open this
'cause it's where you
keep all the crazy junk
you're too embarrassed
to put on display.
Go ahead and open
it if you want. I don't care.
If you're lookin' for
all my weird stuff
I usually keep it down
in my dad's study.
I share it with him.
Uh. You guys share it?
Didn't you say
your dad was writer
or something like that?
--Yep.
--I bet you probably get hooked
on the light novels
and dating sims your Dad writes.
--Don't you?
--Oh, yeah.
Well, actually, my dad doesn't
write that kinda stuff.
--Oh, really?
--Yep.
Huh. I didn't expect that.
Well, I mean. Since he's a fan
of stuff like that,
wouldn't he wanna write
those kinds of stories?
No. My dad's
kinda like a lurker.
He told me he didn't
wanna write that stuff,
because he felt that,
since his real life
was kinda like one
of those nurturing sims,
he didn't wanna write
about it and live it too.
[KAGAMI thinks] Ever since
I got here, it's been weird.
Yep. That's the Izumis.
[video game noises]
So, get this.
The other day, my dad was
being all clingy and stuff.
--Yeah?
--So I'm all,
"You're actin' like an ass,"
just to see what he'd do.
Ugh! How can you talk
to your dad like that?
Yeah, well, after I said it,
Dad suggested I say,
"I hate you, Dad,"
or somethin'.
Yeah. I'm not sure
about that either.
[groans]
That's the point.
I don't think you
appreciate the complexity
of my dad's way of
thinking, Kagami.
Whatever.
You totally lost me.
[TV playing Japanese pop]
[yawns]
How 'bout we take
a little break?
--It's here!
--[TV audience applause]
Have you noticed lately,
how there's been a lot
of 2chan speak on TV?
What's up with that?
Oh. There has?
I wouldn't know
about that stuff.
--[bell dings]
--That's right!
I just realized you're
this hard-core otaku,
but I've never heard
you talk like that.
I don't normally.
But if I'm online
I talk like this.
[surprised gasps]
[KAGAMI] Whoa.
Is that really Japanese?
[KONATA thinks] I think I've
failed if anybody can read it.
[knife chops]
[whimpers]
You want me to
help with anything?
Sure. Do you wanna
serve the salad for me?
Mm-hmm!
[BOTH]
Huh?
[ALL]
Thank you for the food!
Yummy!
Yeah, you're right.
This stuff tastes amazing!
Whippin' up stuff like
this isn't a big deal
if you do your chores.
If you helped out
in the kitchen more, Kagami,
you'd cook like this too.
I don't need your advice.
Konata look! This is perfect!
Huh?
I always dreamed something
like this would happen
and it has!
[SISTERS]
Huh?
--Oh, yeah.
--[crying]
So, this is what's known
as the three high school girls
having dinner with
a guy scenario.
And if you ask me,
even for dating sims,
it's freakishly overused.
That's, well...
Doesn't it feel like
evenings are getting colder?
Maybe I shoulda
brought a jacket with me.
Look! A shooting star!
Huh?
Darn.
Tried, but I couldn't
make my wish three times.
When they come out
of nowhere like that,
it's kinda hard.
But someday I'll do it!
I'll wish fast enough,
and then it'll grant me a wish!
You'll always be
a dreamer, Tsukasa.
Too bad stuff like
that's impossible
when you stop
to think about it.
[BOTH] Huh?
Whoever came up
with it knew no one
could say their wish fast
enough for it to work.
This one has absolutely
no dreams whatsoever.
Are either of you guys thirsty?
Whoa!
Thank you.
You switched hairdos.
Yeah. What do you think?
We did it for fun
after we took our bath.
[KONATA thinks] Hmm. Isn't it
funny how the vibe you get
from something on one person
is different when
it's on someone else?
Oh! A photo album!
Can I look at it?
Sure, go ahead.
Wow! You're so cute, Kona-chan!
You haven't changed at all.
How old are you
supposed be in this?
It's a cool shot.
I guess you and your dad
are pretty close, huh?
[KONATA] Hmm? Oh!
No. That's my mom!
[KAGAMI thinks]
She's a kid! I mean, so young!
Don't we look alike?
[KAGAMI thinks]
Yeah, like jailbait.
Every time I look at Dad
--I just can't help thinkin'.
--What?
What part of my dad did
my mom find so attractive
that she'd wanna marry him?
[KAGAMI]
It's crazy how much you
and your mom look alike, though.
Do you like the same
type of guy as your mom?
What is your type, anyway?
What's my type?
[sighs]
I don't know. I don't
think I have one.
--Oh. Come on! You can tell me.
--Wait!
Mom said that her and Dad
were childhood friends first.
I don't think my mom
was very picky
about the guy she liked.
Maybe that's a little harsh.
I bet she picked him
'cause she felt sorry for him.
Even with your parents,
you're brutal.
You know, lookin'
at this picture of Mom's
--got me thinkin'.
--Mm-hmm?
These days you've got
characters in manga and games,
like junior high kids,
who seem really mature,
but the adults all act immature.
What's up with that?
[KAGAMI thinks]
Yeah, so?
You waiting for me to whip out
a snide remark or something?
It's too bad Yuki-chan
couldn't come over tonight.
Yeah. She had
stuff to do, though.
I know! I'll text Yuki-chan.
That way
she won't feel left out!
Maybe you shouldn't bug her.
Miyuki's probably
busy doing something.
--[cell phone message alert]
--That was quick.
"Glad to hear you're
all having fun.
"Right now, I'm working
hard and doing my best
"to finish my homework
for the weekend.
If you do it again,
I'll make sure to..."
I totally forgot
we had homework to do!
Don't just sit there, Kagami.
Do something!
[KAGAMI]
I didn't have any homework.
Can I go to sleep now?
No! Wait!
-Oh! Remember the shooting star?
--Yeah?
Maybe if I made shorter wishes
I can get them to come true.
I don't know about that.
What you doin' over there?
I'm trying to figure out
if there's a way
to say my wishes faster.
Stop running away
from reality.
Hurry up and finish it.
[TSUKASA]
Hey, Yuki-chan.
I didn't really understand
this part today.
Can you show me how it's done?
[sighs]
Sure, I'd be glad to.
Kona-chan comes from Konata.
Yuki-chan comes from Miyuki.
Hmm...
Hey, Tsukasa,
what kind of nickname
would you give Kagami?
Kaga-chan? Gami-chan?
Uh. Hmm.
Kyou-chan might be good.
Kyou is another
way to say Kagami.
Ah! That's a good call.
It's perfect 'cause it reflects
her tough-as-nails personality.
It could also work
with this Kyou-chan.
But that's not what I meant when
I said it. Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
I think it's best
we don't mention this
to sis, you know?
How about it you gave
yourself a nickname.
What would it be?
Tsuka-chan? Kasa-chan?
Hmm. How 'bout Hii-chan?
It's hard to make a nickname
out of my first name.
That's perfect! 'Cause I can
picture you as the type
who'd run around shrieking,
"Hihi!" all the time.
That's not exactly
what I meant either.
Right!
From this day forward, Tsukasa,
--I'm calling you Hii-chan.
--Huh?
What? What's wrong?
-What do you mean, "huh"?
-[chuckles]
It's just that it's
kinda weird, you know?
Picking your own
nickname, and all.
--Then, how about that?
--That?
Uh. I guess it doesn't matter.
Don't you want
revenge, Sebastian?
--Shiraishi.
--Hey, Kyou-chan! Kyou-chan!
What the heck are you saying?
Are you calling me?
It's totally confusing,
so stop it.
Okay. Then what do you
want me to call you?
Isn't Kagami good enough?
Well, don't you wanna
have a nickname too?
You know, like
Kona-chan and Yuki-chan?
Hmm.
How 'bout Kagami-sama?
Uh.
Hey! Kagami-sama!
Ugh. Oh, no!
She's using it.
Yeah, what?
I was just callin' ya.
Sorry for the wait, Kagami-sama.
What's wrong, Kagami-sama?
[KAGAMI]
I'm sorry. It's my fault.
Just please call me by my name.
[GIRLS]
"Lucky Star."
[cat meows]
[AKIRA]
"Lucky Channel"!
Hi, Luckies!
Wow! Isn't this great?
Can you guys believe
that Lucky Channel's
surging forward
with its tenth episode!
I'm Akira Kogami,
your navigator.
Hello! I'm her assistant,
Minoru Shiraishi.
How 'bout we get
down to business
by introducing
the fourth character.
It's Kagami Hiiragi!
In the show,
she's the one who plays
the rational character
and keeps things on track.
So, basically she's
a tsundere type. Yeah.
Right, I got it. Tsundere.
Talk about a shallow character.
On the contrary.
Huh?
Let's not jump to conclusions
by categorizing Kagami-san
as a mere tsundere.
[snickers]
What is she then?
Before we get into that,
we must ask ourselves,
do we truly grasp
the concept of tsundere?
See, in this day
and age, it's a sad fact
that as the term tsundere
becomes a part
of the main-stream,
its true meaning gets
lost in the process.
First we must trace its origins.
The term tsundere dates
back to the year 2002,
where it was first
used on the Internet.
It meant "a hostile person
who becomes affectionate."
In other words, it was
supposed to describe
how a character's personality
changed over time!
Yeah, whatever.
These days, however,
tsundere is used
to describe
a character's dual nature.
For example, a girl
who's cold on the outside
but loving on the
inside would fit
the current definition
of the term.
I'm gonna go out on a limb here.
I declare that this
is all a huge mistake!
We must give the people back
the true definition of tsundere!
Sound the warning bells!
Rise up and be counted,
you illiterate masses!
Arise!
You were going pretty
good there, Sebastian.
Who's that?
So if Kagami isn't
a tsundere, what is she?
Who's Sebastian?
I don't get why
you're making it harder
than it needs to be, you know?
But since you
brought it up, chief,
you got another word we can use
besides tsundere that gets
the same point across?
What? Oh! Ah. I'm
sure there's somethin'
out there that would work.
Maybe Cool-dere?
No, that's not it.
Deretsun?
You really are an idiot,
did you know that?
Isn't tsundere good enough?
No, it isn't. That's
what I've been saying!
Oh! How 'bout
we have our viewers
think of a new term that
could replace tsundere?
Now, that's what
I call a good idea.
Coward.
[upbeat jazz disco music]
Listen up! This goes out to
everyone watching right now.
I want you to come up
with a new term
that would describe
a character like Kagami.
And together we'll rewrite
the common facts of
modern-day speech.
We'll call it
The Great Tsundere Debate!
For more info, please
check out our radio show
or log on to our site.
We're counting on your ideas!
Uh. So, are we done now?
'Bout freakin' time.
Lots and lots and lots and lots.
Bye-ni.
--Bye-ni!
--[loud trumpets]
Fast forward!
[MINORU]
Wow! I talked up a storm today.
That was the best show ever!
Uh. Akira-sama?
What's wrong?
[AKIRA]
Happy now?
[MINORU]
Oh, yeah! I mean...
I got a lot of lines today.
I think I did a good job!
[Akira sighs]
[AKIRA]
So, I'm gonna have dinner
with one of the producers
and the president
of the production company.
--[MINORU] Huh? Oh!
--[AKIRA] Yeah.
We're gonna be talking
about your future with the show.
[MINORU]
Hold on a second. Wait!
What's that supposed to mean?
[Akira sighs]
[AKIRA] I don't know if
telling you is gonna help.
I mean, if I have to tell you,
you already don't get it.
--[MINORU] Whoa!
--[AKIRA] You still got that
part time gig in
[bleep], don't you?
[MINORU]
Yeah, like during the day, I do.
But it's not like I'm
getting rich working there.
[AKIRA]
And the Korean barbecue?
[MINORU] Well, yeah,
I work there too, but--
Wait! No!
That doesn't matter!
Just stop it! That's
all private stuff!
[KAGAMI]
Well, here I go.
[KONATA] What do you think
about this song, Tsukasa?
[TSUKASA] Maybe. What do
you think, Yuki-chan?
[MIYUKI]
Yes, I know it.
[KONATA] Then, how 'bout
you guys sing it next?
[TSUKASA]
Thanks for finding it.
[MIYUKI]
Yes, thank you.
[KONATA]
At last.
[KAGAMI]
Did you guys decide on a song?
[TSUKASA]
Yeah!
[KAGAMI singing in Japanese]
[TSUKASA]
Hey! Wasn't this song popular
back when we were
in kindergarten?
[KONATA]
No idea.
[TSUKASA] Oh, I'm sorry.
I don't know either.
[MIYUKI]
I totally remember it.
Our sisters used
to sing it a lot.
[TSUKASA]
It's said that songs sung
by our parents or
older siblings,
even though they're from
a generation before us,
are the ones we
remember the most.
[singing continues]
[KONATA]
Oh! She couldn't hit it.
[KAGAMI] I couldn't help it!
It's too high.
[MAN] On the next episode
of "Lucky Star"!
[KAGAMI] Kagami here!
Say you're out with a friend
and you're getting
something to eat.
And everything's going great
until they bring out the soup.
There's always a little bit
that splashes up, right?
Well, doesn't it suck when
a drop gets on your clothes?
And if it's curry sauce
it sucks even worse!
Doesn't it seem like
it always happens
when you're wearing
your favorite outfit?
And then it's like,
you're totally bummed
for the rest of
the day, you know?
It's like when you buy
a bento box
with soup at the store.
You make sure to walk home
all steady and careful,
keeping that bag level so
nothing spills out, right?
Yeah. But then you get
home and you open the bag
and the soup spilled out
and everything's soaked,
and you're like,
"I'm so not hungry anymore."
And you know how nice it is when
they're bagging your stuff
and they bother to separate
the cold things from the hot?
And then they screw it all up by
putting the magazines you bought
in the same damn bag as
all your cold drinks.
And then the paper soaks up
all the condensation!
And now, you've got these
warped and soggy magazines.
And you're thinking,
"Why the hell did
they separate anything
in the first place?"
You know?
[sighs]
Next episode,
"Various Ways
to Spend Christmas Eve."
[MAN]
Look forward to it!