[HIMENO]
I'm looking.
Oh, you got a smartphone, huh?
Yeah, it's so cool.
Now, here, let's see.
[HIMENO]
Is this it?
[JEAN] Ipomoea lobate,
the firecracker vine,
blooms only in
the deepest jungles.
Combined with other
all-natural ingredients,
the vine's healing properties
make Ipomoea Queen
perfectly suited to
support good health
and ease stress brought on
by today's hectic world.
Ads like this are so cheesy.
I've been seeing this
frog guy a lot lately.
I guess he's some
kind of celebrity.
You probably don't want
to call him a "frog guy."
What's the right term, then?
I would say amphibianfolk.
Jeez, that's kind of a mouthful.
I think I would call him
a Frenchman. It's accurate.
Don't you know his background?
He's a French citizen.
[SUU] One day, when
he was a young child,
Jean Rousseau lost
consciousness in the jungle.
He was found by
French missionaries.
They educated him in
a mammalian society.
[TEACHER A]
His abilities far surpass
those of average children.
[TEACHER B] If that's the case,
then perhaps we should test him.
[SUU] He began working
for a small trading firm
in South America.
His academic background
bolstered his success,
and eventually he
purchased the company
and became its president.
And that's his story.
Why would someone like that
wanna star in commercials?
His work has always gotten
him a lot of media exposure.
Especially his involvement
with minority rights.
He sounds like
an incredible guy.
Are all amphibianfolk
that smart?
No, that's an
overgeneralization.
[ALL]
Hm?
[KOMORI, NEKOMI]
59, 60. 61, 62, 63...
[HIMENO yelps]
Ten more seconds.
I'm sure the amphibianfolk
have their share of idiots, too.
Every race has its
morons and geniuses.
[MANAMI]
Sorry to interrupt,
but did I overhear you
discussing Jean Rousseau?
Well, this is perfect timing.
I've got some exciting news.
Mr. Rousseau is going to
come here and speak to us.
You four could form a committee,
get everything ready.
If you think that we're
right for the job...
Hey!
I apologize. Did I say
something wrong?
I'm so glad you're
willing to help out.
Well, this should
be interesting.
There's never a dull moment
around here lately.
Pardon me, sir. It seems
Mr. Rousseau has arrived.
[PRESIDENT]
Oh.
[EXEC]
This way.
[JEAN]
Thank you.
Welcome, Mr. Rousseau.
[PRESDENT] I was always told
that it was poor manners
to shake hands with gloves on.
[JEAN]
I understand, but my hands...
My hand isn't dirty.
There is no need to clean it.
Are you sure?
Obviously, you still have
a great deal left to learn.
The meeting ran longer
than we expected,
so there's no time
to take a break now.
A change of clothes
is waiting for you
on the airplane, however.
Good, thank you.
[SECRETARY A]
I've also prepared the documents
necessary for the settlement.
There are four matters that
will require your attention
before the end of the day.
The weather report is clear.
Our estimated flight
time is three hours.
[JEAN]
Mhm.
I have a helicopter standing
by for you at the airport.
Good, thanks. Is that it?
There are no further plans for
the day after this visit, right?
Yes, that's correct, but
we need to be careful.
It's a very busy week,
and if anything carries over
into the next few days,
we'll have a lot of
things to rearrange.
[JEAN] What's first on the
schedule tomorrow morning?
[SECRETARY A] A meeting with
the UN Secretary-General.
[FROG A, FROG B yelling]
I noticed you're dressed
rather unconventionally.
You find it strange?
Interesting coming from someone
who regularly wears
mammalian clothing.
True, I wear suits for work.
It's a gesture of respect to
the people I do business with.
That, on the other
hand, is battle attire.
[LEADER]
Naturally.
Our tribe is
constantly struggling
to fend off our enemies.
here is something
going on here,
and I would like some answers.
First, who are these enemies
you say the tribe
has been fighting?
And second, where did you
come by this battle gear?
Who in the world
provided it for you?
Who are we fighting?
Only those who deserve it.
People who attack our
brethren without reason.
As for the gear we've received,
our god told me he would
lend me the power I needed.
He is not like their
useless, invisible god
who does nothing for them.
I don't doubt your devotion
to protecting the tribe
from outside attack,
but it's important not
to act recklessly.
Remember, we must do
whatever is necessary
to coexist peacefully with
the mammalian peoples.
If we fail in that, it is we
who will be destroyed, not them.
Also, our god truly exists.
He is as real as you and I are.
But he is not a selfless deity.
He does not act
according to our wishes.
He isn't motivated by care for
us, but by his own interests.
How dare you!
Insolent blasphemer!
That isn't to say I don't
respect our god, because I do.
However, that doesn't change
the truth of who he is.
[LEADER]
Listen to me.
You may not wish
to believe this,
but you have been
deceived by the mammalians
you have been living among.
They're not as strong as
they want us to think they are.
Yes, there are more of them,
and their technology
is more advanced.
But even so, our god
and his angels
are stronger than they
could ever hope to be.
Trust me. I've
seen it firsthand.
Yes!
And even if we don't have
our god's assistance,
we can never allow
ourselves to yield.
Whatever it takes, we must
reclaim our land and water
from their repulsive clutches.
We must fight them,
even if it costs us our lives.
Though, I don't really
expect you to understand.
You're practically a
mammalian yourself now.
[JEAN] Risking people's lives
for an abstract cause?
Seeking to restore past glory
that may never have
existed in the first place?
That way of thinking is
mammalian, not amphibian.
It is poison to our kind.
Why isn't he able to see that?
[HIMENO] Thank you
very much, Mr. Rousseau.
We appreciate you taking
the time to visit our school.
[applause]
The speech is done.
Is it ready?
It should be.
Much better.
Thank you for coming today.
What's this?
We thought you might enjoy
some tea from your homeland.
I hope we prepared it the way
you like. We did our best.
Merci .
[JEAN]
Water, please.
[siren blaring]
[gunshot]
[thud]
[BOY A]
Please, stop.
[gasps]
[OFFICER]
Excuse me, Second Lieutenant,
we've reached our
quota for today.
Have we? Very well.
Where are they taking us?
[MAN A]
Straight to Hell on Earth, kid.
[MAN B]
No! I don't wanna go in there!
[MAN C]
Please, just let us go home!
[SOLDIER]
Shut up and keep moving!
[JAILER]
Did we say you could stop?
[MAN D] Hey! We don't
take breaks around here!
Now, kid, get back to work!
[JAILER] In return for your
labor, you earn survival.
Stop working and you will die.
[siren blaring]
[BOY A]
This is all I get?
[MAN E] Hey! Why does he
always get a bigger portion?
You'd be wise to take
what you're given.
Calm down. No need to
get worked up about it.
[MAN E growls]
Shut up.
[JAILER]
Enough, you filth.
The amount you get is
determined by body type.
Not all needs are equal.
[grunts]
Listening to you people talk
makes me sick to my stomach.
Every word out of your mouths
is full of jealousy
and prejudice.
Man, I sure am hungry.
Just let it go!
I sure could'a used
more food tonight,
but apparently they're saving
it all up to feed the livestock.
You and that corporal must
be pretty good buddies,
seeing as you're both
barnyard animals and all.
What?
[PRISONER A]
Get him! Make him hurt!
[PRISONER B]
Kill the damn traitor horse!
[PRISONERS shouting]
Stop it, please!
We're on the same side.
[I've got nothin' in
common with livestock!
What're you lookin' at, huh?
[PRISONER E]
Are you all right, child?
We're all prisoners, aren't we?
We shouldn't be
fighting each other.
Things may be changing,
but until recently,
discrimination based on
body type was the norm.
Of course, when you think about
it, not much is different.
Only now, it's the
government that's telling us
who's inferior and
who is superior.
It's a common theme in science
fiction books, right?
If only there were
no discrimination
based on body type,
then the whole world
would finally be at peace.
Isn't that probably true?
No, it's not.
Just think. Hair color,
skin color, nationality.
Tall or short, fat or skinny.
We're all different in some way.
And so long as that's true,
people will always cling
to their prejudices.
But that's awful.
Even if we all looked alike,
we'd find something
to fight about,
like whose clothing was better
or whose house was bigger.
That's just the
nature of humanity.
There's no way to fix it.
Maybe you're right,
but if we don't stop
them, they'll kill him.
You're wasting your strength.
[PRISONER D]
Back off!
That's enough!
Quiet down, you filth!
What're you doing?
Keep swinging that pickaxe.
Why should we take
orders from him?
Who gave that jerk the
authority to boss us around?
[PRISONER F]
I guess the livestock
look out for their own.
Hey! I told you, no
breaks allowed, kid.
[MAN D] Come on.
Time for your punishment.
[BOY A]
I accepted my fate.
This was it. I was going to die.
I set aside some of my
rations for you, take 'em.
Eat. And maybe cry out a little
every now and then, okay?
I don't--
Get back up! Weakling!
This war is the end of the line.
I won't get out alive.
If I remain a prisoner, sooner
or later, someone will kill me.
If I'm freed, I'll be
executed as a traitor,
but you have to live.
Little brat! I told
you to get up!
Why me?
[MAN D] Because you're
one of the good guys.
The more people
like you survive,
the better the world will be.
[MAN D] Now, hurry up
and eat. Then get going.
[gunshot]
Move! Get back on
your feet right now!
[siren blaring]
[PRISONER G]
Sirens!
[PRISONER H]
It's an attack!
[PRISONERS shouting]
[PRISONER I]
The liberation army!
[PRISONER J]
We're free!
[PRISONER K]
We'll get to go home!
Look! It's that brat! He's
as bad as the rest of them!
[PRISONER L]
Damn traitor!
[PRISONER M]
Hang him!
[PRISONER N] Let's get another
rope! String the kid up!
[PRISONER O]
Get back here!
[PRISONERS shouting]
Easy.
[MAN E] Give him to us.
We'll take care of him.
What?
[PRISONER P]
He's the enemy!
[PRISONER N]
A spy!
No! You're wrong!
[MAN E]
Shut up! You are a traitor!
I saw it, you know.
I saw you getting food from
that livestock bastard!
No, please!
[LIBERATION SOLDIER]
Hey, he's only a child.
[MAN E]
So?
I don't care how old you
are, you're gonna hang!
[PRISONERS yelling]
[gasps]
[LIBERATION SOLDIER]
It's chocolate. Have some.
Do you like candy?
Eat this and then see if you
can get some rest, okay?
If you have no family,
you can come home with me.
I'll take care of you.
Pardon me, sir. It seems that
Mr. Rousseau has arrived.
[PRESIDENT]
Oh.
When you're my age, you tend
to doze off at all hours.
[applause]