[TEACHER] Please welcome
Quetzalcoatl Sassassul,
all the way from Antarctica.
[TEACHER] You'll be
sitting next to Kimihara.
[gasps]
[TEACHER]
Kimihara, as her neighbor,
it's up to you to show
her the ropes, okay?
[HIMENO]
Umm...
Nice to meet you.
Oh, uh, yeah, same to you.
[TEACHER]
Now then, let's get started.
Stand. Bow.
Oh! Hey!
Whoops. I'm sorry.
Uh, it's no problem.
[TEACHER]
Take your seats.
[whispering]
I've never seen one in person.
Let's focus on
the lesson, everyone.
[sighs]
[HIMENO]
"I wish to drink it,
but a mounted pipa
player urges me on."
A poem and it's Chinese.
Would she know that?
Ah... Ah...
Um... Ah...
[shudders]
[moans]
[CLASS]
Huh?
[BOY]
What's going on?
[GIRL]
What happened?
[TEACHER]
Kimihara?
Sorry!
What's going on in here?
[NOZOMI]
Hime got a little startled.
Mmm... Ah...
[NOZOMI]
Hey, it's about time.
[KYOKO]
Are you okay?
Huh?
[gasps]
[NOZOMI] It's all right.
She's not in here.
Whew!
Don't look so relieved.
You need to stop freaking
out and get it together.
Yeah, you won't be
able to come to school
if you keep fainting
all the time.
Sure, that's a problem, too.
But really, I would be
more worried about
your negative reaction being
interpreted as discrimination.
That's not it, I swear!
I'd never discriminate
against anyone.
It's just... snake people.
They scare you, don't they?
You better not let
anyone hear you say that.
You'd be in real trouble.
[HIMENO]
Yeah.
[NOZOMI] Why do Antarcticans
scare you so much, anyway?
[HIMENO]
Um...
Well, do you remember that old
movie, The Fear of Antarctica ?
Which one?
The original, or the remake?
[HIMENO]
The one that's in color.
We watched it at home
when I was little.
It wasn't the best experience.
[ACTRESS hums]
[gasps]
Hey! Who's there?
[shrieks]
No!
[sobs]
[screams]
[whimpers]
[NOZOMI]
Still traumatized, huh?
[KYOKO] The villain swallows
the centaur heroine whole,
then spits her skin back out
and wears it as a disguise.
[NOZOMI]
They show it on TV sometimes.
I kinda like it.
[KYOKO] I'm surprised how much
people still talk about it.
[NOZOMI] The whole thing
is so far-fetched, though.
Actually, it worked all right
in the novel it was based on.
The discrepancies were
more obvious in the film.
I thought the part where
it spit up her bones
looked pretty realistic.
That doesn't make the premise
any less absurd, though.
I'm not worried
about production value.
Point is, I've been
scared of snake people
ever since I saw that.
What should I do?
You got any ideas, Kyoko?
Your fear of Antarcticans stems
from watching a
movie as a kid, right?
Maybe if you watched it
again now that you're older,
it would help you
overcome the trauma.
No! I couldn't.
Wouldn't that make
her even more scared?
[KYOKO]
No, hear me out.
I get that it was scary when our
princess here was a little kid.
But really,
it's just an old B movie.
And not one of
the better ones, either.
If you watch it now,
you'll see how
embarrassingly fake it is,
and you won't be scared anymore.
Heh! You really
think that'll work?
[KYOKO]
What do you have to lose, right?
[HIMENO]
Hmm... Oh!
I just realized I have
no idea how I got in here.
Did the two of you
carry me or something?
And how would we manage that?
Do you think we've suddenly
taken up bodybuilding?
[NOZOMI]
Mm-hm. Mm-hm.
Aww...
[SHIGETOKI]
Excuse me. May I come in?
[HIMENO]
Uh, sure.
How are you?
Starting to feel back to normal?
[HIMENO]
Yes, much better now, thanks.
It was Shigetoki
who carried you here.
Oh, and Komori
and Nekomi helped.
[HIMENO]
Oh!
Thank you for doing that.
[SHIGETOKI laughs]
No problem.
Huh?
[laughs]
[SUU] I'm sorry.
I frightened you pretty badly.
[HIMENO]
Oh, no, not at all.
I'm afraid I didn't
do a very good job,
but I was trying to smile.
Really? I'd like to see that.
Will you show us?
I suppose so.
Uh...
Yeah, you might wanna work
on that a little more, sorry.
I knew it wasn't going
to be easy to fit in here,
but I'm starting to think
it will be impossible.
Hey, no, don't say that.
Hime's just got issues
because of this old movie.
An old movie?
[NEKOMI] Man,
Kimihara sure is heavy, huh?
[KOMORI]
Yeah, but so soft.
[snickers]
[NOZOMI]
So, anyway, that's the story.
It's a terrible,
cheesy movie, really.
Very gruesome. Where would
someone come up with that idea?
[KYOKO]
Hmm...
See what you did?!
Hey, I was just trying to help.
[SUU] I have to admit,
it sounds interesting.
Huh?
[SHIGETOKI] I'm not allowed
inside the classroom.
So, I'll leave you to it.
Right, thanks a lot.
[NOZOMI]
Hey there!
[ALL 3]
Hmm?
Hey guys, what's
the special occasion?
This isn't exactly
your usual hangout.
We cleaned out the
aquarium once, didn't we?
You remember, Shrimp.
[PRESIDENT]
Shrimp? You're one to talk.
[startled gasps]
I'm sorry. I didn't
mean to startle you.
[PRESIDENT]
No, um, it's okay.
Oh, wow! This is so cool.
An Antarctican!
Hello, nice to meet you.
We don't have time to talk now.
We just came here
to raid your movie library.
[VICE PRESIDENT]
Hmm...
[NOZOMI]
Aha! Yep, here we go!
Well, sit down, let's watch.
Huh?!
[NOZOMI]
What?
I don't think
I'm ready for this.
[sighs]
[NOZOMI]
I'm starting it.
Open your eyes. No cheating.
But Kyoko.
That movie? Really?
I hope she doesn't
find it too offensive.
[whimpers]
[screams]
[ACTOR A]
Alyssa, what's wrong?
Eyes on the screen, Princess.
You aren't Alyssa, you monster!
[ACTOR A] Whose skin
have you taken this time?
It's your turn to bleed!
[shrieks]
Huh? Oh, sorry about that!
Whatcha think?
It was still as
scary as I remember.
So graphic, too.
A monster that
wears people's skins?
You humans have very active
imaginations, don't you?
You seem nice.
You don't eat people, right?
[gasps]
Of course, I don't!
And neither do any Antarcticans.
Please don't ever compare us
to that monster in the movie.
We don't even have
venomous fangs. Here, look.
[shrieks]
[SUU] Mammals have strong
jaws for chewing their food.
Ours are weak in comparison.
Even if one of us
were to bite you,
it would feel like
the bite of a kitten.
Some snakes constrict prey.
We can't do that, either.
Huh?
[SUU] And we don't have
expanding rib cages,
so we can't swallow
large things whole.
I'm a person. You don't
eat other people, do you?
I would never consider doing
that any more than you would.
It hurts to think
that I could be seen
as a monster like this one.
Yeah, it probably doesn't get
much worse than that, huh?
[PRESIDENT]
Are you going to sue the people
who made the movie?
I wouldn't do that.
I came here to put an end to
misunderstandings like this,
not to start trouble.
And on that note, if I could,
I would like to be your friend.
Sure, that sounds great.
Uh-huh! We'd be happy
to have you as a friend.
--[NOZOMI] Hey, you okay?
--[KYOKO] Hime!
[PRESIDENT]
What the--?
[VICE PRESIDENT]
Princess!
[HIMENO chuckles]
[FUJIMOTO]
Quetzalcoatl.
Uh? What is it?
I'm curious about something.
May I ask you a question?
Go ahead.
[AKIRA]
I've got one!
[BOY C]
Me, too!
Right, that's enough.
One at a time, please.
[COUNCIL D] Are you ever
not bossing people around?
[MANAMI]
Hmm...?
[FUJIMOTO clears throat]
I think I should get
to ask my question first.
Snakes are reptiles, cold-
blooded creatures whose bodies
take on the same temperature
as their surroundings.
So how do you live someplace
as cold as Antarctica?
That's a good question.
However, there are
two central assumptions
you are mistaken about.
First, we are warm-blooded
creatures, not cold-blooded.
In fact, we are more like birds
than amphibians and reptiles.
Also, although we are commonly
referred to as "snake people,"
that's just a term used
because of our appearance.
Our actual link to snakes is
believed to be quite tenuous.
I can maintain a
body temperature higher
than that of my environment.
Thus ensuring I have a stable
supply of energy to my brain.
If I couldn't, I wouldn't be
able to talk to you like this.
The brain consumes
a lot of energy.
Also, contrary to
what you may believe,
not all of Antarctica is buried
underneath ice and snow.
And even though
it's very cold there,
we have heating to keep us warm,
just like most of the world.
My turn to ask a question.
Is it true that Antarcticans
have secretly controlled
humanity for centuries?
[SUU]
Let's see, here.
There are legends suggesting
that several millennia ago,
our ancestors, who still crawled
instead of walking upright,
built underground cities
all around the world.
We don't know if
that's true, however.
And the outlandish
things written about
in so-called "occult books"
are essentially groundless.
We had no contact with humans
until relatively recently,
and it has been very limited.
We differ from humans on many
levels, including spiritually.
It is difficult for us
to comprehend you,
much less control you.
We certainly are not omnipotent.
[AKIRA]
Did you really rule the Aztecs?
[SUU]
We did contribute knowledge
and technology
to their civilization,
but we didn't rule them
or interfere with the way
in which their society
was governed.
Humans and my people have
always had minimal involvement.
But humans are seeking
greater involvement now, right?
Yes, that's true.
For a long time,
Antarctica's very existence
was unknown to
the rest of the world.
Now, boats and
planes make travelling there
not only possible, but easy.
So why did you want
to come to this school?
[SUU]
It's in a college town,
and the environment is
similar to the one I'm used to.
I believed I would be
able to find people here
who were intelligent
and understanding
while still being an
accurate reflection
of humanity as a whole.
[MANAMI] In other words, because
we're slightly above average?
Also, I liked that it was
neither extremely hot nor cold.
I don't know, the wind can
get freezing during the winter.
And the summers
here are sweltering.
Now, with the pedantic
questions out of the way.
Tell us about your love life.
Like, do you have
a boyfriend? Spill!
No boyfriend.
Cool! 'Cause I don't, either.
So, then, what's your type?
Do you have one?
[SUU]
That's a difficult question.
The queen is the only one
of us who can lay eggs,
and for the most part,
our common citizens
and warriors are female.
Well, that's different.
So, given the
constraints of our society,
I shouldn't have
romantic feelings.
Wait, you said "shouldn't."
Does that mean you do?
I'm not sure how to describe it.
We do feel specialized emotions
of favor toward individuals.
These things are hard to explain
to those who are not our kind.
I'm not sure whether
it's equivalent
to your concepts of friendship
or romantic interest,
or something else.
[SUU]
While we are a technologically
and scientifically
proficient race,
there are areas in which
our comprehension is lacking.
One of which is
knowledge of ourselves.
We had never noticed that
gap in our understanding.
It was something
we learned from humans.
This is starting to sound
sort of pedantic again.
[COUNCIL D]
Me next!
[KOJIMA]
Hey, it's my turn!
All right, enough
questions for now.
Aw, but I wanted to ask
what kind of stuff she eats.
[MANAMI] I suggest
researching that at lunch.
There's so much more to ask!
That's just the
tip of the iceberg!
Calm down.
You'll learn more eventually.
For now, everyone
back to your seats.
[SOLDIER]
Forward, men!
It is time to claim our victory!
[cheers]
Sensitive skin? This is for you!
[PRETTY HORN]
Magical Girl Pretty Horn!
Kazuko, please!
No. I can't!
Now, a look at events
following the sinking
of an American research
ship in Antarctic waters.
The US government
has demanded answers.
However, the government of
Antarctica still remains silent.
[gasps]
[NEWSCASTER] Other nations
have expressed dismay
in response to this incident
but are resigned to watching
and waiting to see what
both nations will do next.
[knocking on door]
Huh?
[NOZOMI]
What's that about?
[HIMENO]
Hey, Suu! Good morning.
[SUU]
Oh. Yes, good morning.
You've got a new look, huh?
What's up?
[KYOKO]
Antarctican fashion?
[SUU]
Uh, no. It's well.
You've seen the news?
The news about what?
Oh, wait, do you mean the thing
about the American
ship that was sunk?
That's why?
I just felt it would be best
to avoid drawing attention to
myself after what happened.
That's what
you're going for, here?
Lower your head, please.
Your stealth skills
could use some work.
[KYOKO]
Idiot! Don't do that!
No, please, it's all right.
Just a little
overreaction, that's all.
[KYOKO] We have different
definitions of "little."
More importantly,
was that a demonstration
of what's called "sarcasm"?
Uh, that's more important, how?
Come on,
you're not some burglar.
Lose the mask.
Shouldn't I at least try?
You just look more conspicuous.
Besides, no one can
hurt you right now.
Also, it was an American ship.
You should be fine here.
[SUU] But, American or not,
they were still humans.
[HIMENO]
Well, yeah.
So, aside from the head scarf,
that's what you
wear every day, huh?
[SUU]
Uh!
I do put on a fresh
one each morning.
Why, does it smell?
You're fine.
That's not what I meant, really!
Oh, yeah, that's right.
You guys are always
dressed like that on TV.
It was originally based
on human monk garments.
[SUU] Our ambassador,
who is also my language tutor,
advised me to shorten
the hems a bit.
She said it
would help me fit in.
It's definitely
more girly that way!
If you have a language tutor,
does that mean you learn stuff
the way the rest of us do?
And not by using
osmosis or whatever?
Yes, of course I do.
Memory formation works
essentially the same way
for all animal species,
even insects.
[SUU] My tutor taught me
everything I might need to know,
from etiquette and customs to
language and general knowledge.
[NOZOMI]
Man, that sounds rough.
No, not at all.
I've had so much help preparing
for this I almost feel guilty.
Are you required
to wear those robes?
No, I choose what to wear.
Then I think you should come
look at some clothes with us!
[NOZOMI, KYOKO]
Totally!
[SUU]
Huh?
You know, I think that's
a good look for you,
all sophisticated and girly.
Why don't we see how
it looks on you, Nozomi?
[NOZOMI]
Hmm?!
Me? Why?
[KYOKO]
You look like a boy in drag!
Ugh!
[HIMENO]
I've got a great idea!
Let me just comb your hair out.
Look how handsome you two are!
The cut is quite nice.
It's a bit too open
in the seat, though.
[RETAILER] The tail
opening is one-size-fits-all
so anyone can try it on.
If you buy it, we'll alter
it to fit you perfectly.
Hang on!
I've never altered something
for a snake person before.
Refuse and we'll be sent
to a correctional clinic.
If you can't do it, we need
to find somebody who can.
[laughs]
What d'you think?
It's really delicious,
thank you.
I don't understand.
Everyone is being kind to me,
even after the incident.
Huh?
Why shouldn't they be?
It's not like the ship
sinking was your fault.
And they don't even have proof
that the Antarctican government
was behind it, right?
Yes, that's true.
Naturally, we have
precautions in place
for protecting our waters
from potential invaders,
but I doubt--
Oh, I'm sorry.
I really shouldn't say any more.
Yeah, honestly,
I don't think you need to.
[NOZOMI]
So, anyone up for a movie?
Not if it's one you picked out.
[NOZOMI]
I've got great taste!
We'll go see a popular one.
I'm sure we'll like it.
[HIMENO] Huh? I don't want
to see anything violent.
[NOZOMI]
Don't worry so much.
Sit back and enjoy it.
[NOZOMI] See?
That was pretty good, right?
[HIMENO]
Um...
If nothing else, it certainly
was thought-provoking.
Uh? It's
supposed to be entertaining.
You don't have to
think about it too hard.
I hope by analyzing your culture
I might better understand
the way you think.
Huh?
Oh, really?
Why's that important?
Well, for a normal Antarctican
it would be a matter of duty.
But I'm not normal,
and I'm beginning to believe
that is why I'm here.
Wow, that was an awesome line.
Like out of a movie.