[CHIHO]
Okay, there ya go.
I don't mind you
going outside to play,
just make sure that you keep
an eye on your sister.
Don't worry about that.
We know the drill.
Sue's such a precious,
tiny little thing,
people are always trying
to run away with her.
[MANAMI]
Hold on a second.
What exactly do
you mean by that?
Can we just forget
I said anything?
Okay, I'm sorry! Don't hurt me!
You can't go around saying
that kind of stuff, okay?
I've never once hurt you,
and you know it.
[CHIHO]
No lectures, either!
[MANAMI]
That'll depend on you three.
Well, ya see...
You want a tummy rub,
don't you, Yoshi?
[CHIS]
Meow!
[CHIS giggling, chattering]
[CHIS]
You wanna pet him too, Sue?
[SUE]
Mew.
[ALL laughing]
Okay, you wanna go
play inside now?
[SUE]
Mew?
[ALL gasp]
[SUE]
Mew!
[CHIS]
Move!
Naughty Yoshi.
Sue isn't one of your toys.
Now, you give her back.
[SUE]
Mew.
[MANAMI]
Ah, so that's why they came home
smelling like dog that day.
All right, what else is there?
Well, uh, one time...
[SUE] I won't go that far.
Just a little way out.
Nothing bad is
gonna happen here.
[ALL gasp]
[CHIGUSA]
Where did Sue go?
[CHINAMI]
Sue!
Where are you? Answer us!
[KANA'S SISTER] Who is this?
Where did she come from?
[KANA]
I found her!
[CHIGUSA]
That way!
[CHIS]
We're coming, Sue!
Look! There!
[ALL]
Hey! Give her back, you thief!
No! She's mine. I found her.
She's gonna be my baby sister.
Let go!
[SUE cries
She's your little
sister, isn't she?
I'm sorry. Now, you let
her go this instant!
Okay, I see.
That explains why the
eldest Kawamoto sister
always seems so apologetic
when she sees me.
Um. Nice morning, huh?
Yeah, I guess so.
[RIRI]
Chisters!
Well, can we go?
[MANAMI]
Yes, you may.
But be sure you don't let
her out of your sight!
Yeah, we know.
[MANAMI] Doesn't matter how
many times they say that,
they're going to do it anyway.
[SHINO]
I'm so excited!
[RINO]
Be home before dark, you two.
[HIMENO]
'Kay.
Yeah, see ya later!
♪ We're going for a walk
today, yes we are! ♪
♪ We're going for a walk! ♪
I was wondering, uh...
What?
There are all different
kinds of grass, aren't there?
Yep, there sure are.
But they're all still
called "grass," though?
No, that's just a broad term.
Each type of grass
that's in this field
has its own individual name.
[SHINO] What's this
fluffy one called, then?
That one's green foxtail.
It's named for its appearance.
We also call it " enokoro grass"
because it looks like
a puppy's tail.
Wow. Hm...
How 'bout this one?
[HIMENO]
Indian goosegrass.
[SHINO]
And this?
[HIMENO]
That's evening primrose.
It has yellow flowers.
They stay closed all day
and then open up at dusk.
[SHINO] What are these
little white ones called?
[HIMENO]
Daisy fleabane.
[SHINO]
These next!
[HIMENO]
Red clovers. Sow thistle.
Creeping woodsorrel.
[SHINO] I've seen these before.
The boys play swords with them.
[HIMENO]
That's Canada goldenrod.
Cool.
There are so many plants here.
Do they all have
their own names?
[HIMENO]
All of them.
No matter how plain
or how small they are,
every plant has a name.
[SHINO]
Ohh...
[MAKI] This one...
is called red clover!
You remembered. Good job!
[MI]
It has a name?
You don't just call
it a red flower?
[SHINO]
Mh-hm.
It doesn't matter how
plain or small they are,
every plant has a name.
[gasps]
Like how I'm called Mi, and
you're Shino, and Maki.
It's kinda the same
but different, too.
[MI]
Mh?
So there are different
kinds of blocks, right?
Some of them are triangles,
and some are squares.
That's a triangle,
and that's a circle.
Yeah, that's right.
Flowers are like
all these blocks.
They come in a lot
of different shapes
and they all have
special names.
Blocks are like flowers, huh?
But the triangle can
be a square, too.
[BOTH gasp]
[MI] And the same
goes for the circle.
Uh... Okay, let me think.
The triangle block has
two triangle sides,
and the circle block
has two circle sides,
but the square block
only has square sides.
Are there any that
are only circles?
Or are only triangles?
One that's only triangles
would be pointy,
and one that's only
circles would be a ball.
[thud]
It's one big circle.
But you can't stack it
if it's only a circle.
That's why blocks always
have square sides, too.
[MI]
There, got it.
[SHINO]
I don't think it's gonna work.
[MAKI] Yeah, but it
kinda looks like fun.
[SHINO]
See this purple flower here?
It's a type of aster.
This one has prickly leaves,
and its flowers are
all purple and pointy.
They're called thistles.
Why not call 'em purple flowers?
Remember what we talked about?
There are different
kinds of purple flowers.
That's cosmos.
It has eight petals.
Let's see, there's one,
two, three, four, five,
then six, seven, and eight.
Great job! You're really
good at counting, aren't you?
[MAKI]
Hey, uh...
This one is, um,
red morning glory!
[SHINO] Yeah, that's right,
Maki! Very good!
[MAKI chuckles]
[SHINO]
This is buckwheat.
[MI]
Buckwheat?
Uh-huh.
After it flowers,
people pick the fruit
and then turn it into powder.
The soba noodles we
eat are made using flour
that comes from this plant.
They're so tiny and cute.
It doesn't matter
how big they are.
Smaller flowers than these
have their own names.
This is oriental lady's thumb.
See how it has lots of
tiny red flowers on it?
But there's nothing
that looks like a thumb.
It seemed weird to me, too,
but with some plants,
nobody knows why they're
named the way they are.
Really? Why not?
[SHINO] Someone named
it a long time ago,
and more and more people
started calling it that,
until eventually, no one knew
how the name came about anymore.
[MI] The flowers have
lotsa little bumps.
[SHINO]
Uh-huh.
Some kids use it
when they play house,
'cause it kinda looks
like red rice.
And that's where it gets the
second name it's called by:
The red rice flower.
[MI]
You know so much, Shino!
[SHINO laughs]
[SHINO]
I only know all this stuff
because my big cousin
taught it to me.
We all have to help each other.
When you two are old enough,
you should teach what you
learned to younger kids.
That way, everyone wins!
[BOTH]
Mh-hm!
Hello, ma'am. Good morning!
Morning, Maki.
[MAKI gasps]
[MAKI]
Please, ma'am, come quick!
Someone stole
the flowers! See?
Oh, right here?
Those were weeds we
needed to pull up.
Who did it? Who pulled
the flowers up?
[TEACHER]
Maki,
I need you to put your fists
down for me, please.
[MAKI]
Shino, it's awful!
The pretty flowers are gone!
It'll be okay.
Even if the flowers
are all gone,
the seeds are still
there somewhere.
That means they'll bloom
again next fall, I promise.
And before that, there
will be spring flowers,
and when those are gone,
there will be summer flowers.
We'll be here to
watch them bloom
and learn all their
names together, okay?
'Kay.
[TEACHER]
I'm proud of you, Shino.
You'd make a very
good older sister.
You saw us over there looking
at the flowers yesterday,
but you still pulled
them all up anyhow?
Uh, I saw, but, well,
it had to be done.
[I get it. It's
grown-up stuff, right?
I hope I get to be
a grown-up soon, too.
[chuckles]
[HIMENO] All of these pointed
shapes are called pyramids.
When all sides are triangles,
it's a triangular pyramid.
One with a square bottom
is a square pyramid.
One with a round
bottom is a cone.
Long ones with ends of the
same thickness are prisms.
This one here is a cylinder,
and that's a triangular prism.
Little kids always ask
so many questions.
It's really hard
being a big sister.
You must've studied
a long time, Hime.
It seems like you
know everything.
Thank you.
But you know, there's
still plenty of stuff
I have to learn about, too.
[SHINO sighs]
[SHINO]
Huh.
[SUE]
There.
Down. Go down.
How's it goin', Sue?
You all dressed yet?
There we go! Found your tail.
I wanted to get dressed
by myself, but--
What's taking so long?
Poor thing.
She was having trouble
getting her tail
through the hole in her outfit.
[SUE]
Mew.
That settles it. It's time for
some special tail training!
What's tail training?
This'll be easy. All you gotta
do is follow my lead, okay?
[SUE]
Mh-hm!
[RIRI]
Chisters, you wanna play?
Right.
Now, to the left.
Back to the middle.
And down.
Hey, guys. So what's up?
[CHINAMI]
Learning about tails.
Studying hard, Sue?
I'm proud of you.
Meow.
[CHINAMI]
Wanna study with us, Riri?
Uh, sure, what do I do?
Swing your tail from
the right into a circle.
Like this.
Really?
Yeah, looks tough.
[SUE]
Mew.
I'm not sure I would
call that a circle.
I don't know if anyone
could do those kinda tricks
without having tails that are
as long as you Chisters' are.
Don't worry, you're doing fine.
It's okay if you can't
make a fancy circle.
[CHINAMI]
Look, two circles.
Mew?
That's pretty cool.
[BOTH]
Meow!
Riri, you're here?
I came over to play.
Sissy. Why's my tail so short?
Your tail's fine.
You know, Sue, your
sisters' tails were short
when they were little, too.
See? Look how small they were.
They had flat ears, too.
Wait a minute why were we
dressed up all funny looking?
[SUE]
They look cute!
Yes, they do.
I was the one who picked out
their clothes back then.
Yeah, but still, why those?
Wouldn't it have been
easier to dress us
in those special baby
pants that just snap on?
It's a lot more complicated
with pants and skirts.
The tail has to go
through two holes.
I guess you could just not
put it through the hole.
I don't think you would be very
comfortable in pants, though.
It would cause even more
problems with a skirt.
I guess with a kimono,
there's a way to wear them
that keeps the tail
inside, but even then,
it still has to go through a
specially designed tail holder.
Still, what about
those baby pants,
like Chiho said before?
[MANAMI] The snaps on
those come undone easily.
Remember when that happened
to Sue and she fell?
[MANAMI] At any rate,
if you want your tail
outside your clothes,
you need something
called an undertag.
[CHIHO]
Okay, what's that?
[MANAMI] It's a loose piece
of cloth inside a skirt.
[CHIGUSA]
'Kay. So what are they for?
[MANAMI] Without one, if you
moved your tail to the side,
your underwear would
show through the hole.
[MANAMI] An undertag fills
in the extra space
so your underwear stays hidden.
[CHIGUSA] I don't care
if it shows a little.
Well, I do care.
[CHIGUSA]
Why? You don't even have a tail.
I don't want your
underwear to be visible.
Not to the kinds of
people who would look.
Sissy. Um, were you
little like me?
I was little.
Here, look. This is me.
[CHIGUSA]
You're so cute!
[CHINAMI]
Tiny Big Sis!
[CHIHO]
You looked just like Sue.
If you used to be so adorable,
then why didn't you
stay that way?
Can we give you a makeover?
If I had stayed cute.
I wouldn't be able
to make dinner,
or look out for the four of you.
Everyone has to grow
up sometime.
[CHIS]
Poo, poo!
[MANAMI]
Oh? You don't want dinner, then?
[CHIS]
No, we didn't say that!
As you can see, our next
topic of discussion
is the recent "World's
Prettiest Person Contest."
This "festival of beauty"
began as a symbol of peace.
What's this about?
The World's Prettiest
Person Contest.
That's easy.
It's gotta be Sissy, right?
She's the prettiest.
[CHINAMI, CHIGUSA shouting]
[MANAMI]
Hey!
You know there's no horsing
around in the house.
Sissy.
What is it, Sue?
Well? What's up?
You're the prettiest person
in the whole wide world.
Aren't you sweet?
Careful. Don't say that.
Yeah! You'll give
her a big head.
[MANAMI]
Uhh...
[CHIHO] There's always
somebody who's better.
[CHINAMI]
Yeah, Big Sis seems like
the most important person
in the world, right?
[CHIGUSA] But there are even
more important people out there
that you have to listen
to, like teachers.
That's true.
And don't forget Dad.
[ALL]
Hmm...
[MANAMI] I didn't think that
would require so much thought.
[ALL]
You're saying Daddy's important?
He's the most important
person in this house.
Well, anyway, there must be
somebody who's prettier, too.
Then let's hear it. Who do you
think is prettier than me?
Who?
[gapss]
[ALL yelp]
[KIDS gasping]
[GIRL C]
Wow! That was really great!
Hey, there. Are you all right?
You three really need
to be more careful.
[CHINAMI, CHIGUSA]
Meow.
You know, Miss Ryuko, you're
actually really pretty.
What? Trying to distract
me with flattery?
[CHINAMI]
Hm.
But still, our sister's
prettier. Sorry to tell ya that.
That's okay, dear.
[CHIS sigh]
[CHIS]
Close but no cigar.
[TEACHER] Try not to be
too upset with them.
[RYUKO]
I'm not upset!
Of course no one can hold
a candle to the big sister
who's practically
a mother to them.
I guess there aren't many
pretty people around, huh?
[CHINAMI]
Huh?
[CHIGUSA, CHIHO]
[CHIS] Hey, it's Shino and
all her big sisters, too!
Hey. It's Prez's little sisters.
[ALL chuckling]
Be careful. I might drop ya.
[CHIHO chuckles]
Will you pick me up?
You three love attention, huh?
[SHINO]
Hey! Me, too!
Come here then.
You're totally cute,
but I don't think I would call
you pretty, at least not yet.
You will probably be
pretty someday, though.
My Hime's already pretty!
Aww.
Hey, I bet you're really pretty
back home in
Antarctica, aren'tcha?
I'm not sure, but if you
wanna come over here,
I can pick you up.
Y'know, you're kinda
pretty yourself, Shino.
But you're still
just a kid, so...
Hey, you're still a kid, too.
So, what? You three are out
looking for pretty people?
[CHIHO]
Mh-hm. Mh-hm.
Okay. What do you
think of her, then?
[CHIGUSA yelling]
[CHIGUSA]
Again! Again!
So you're actually a girl?
I thought you were a
boy this whole time.
Hey, you saw me
in my bathing suit
at the swimming pool!
[CHIS]
Sis, we're back!
[MANAMI]
Oh, there you are.
It was getting dark, so I was
about to go looking for you.
[ALL] We've been out searching
all day, like, everywhere.
Yeah, for what?
[ALLI] Well, duh. For someone
who's prettier than you.
[MANAMI]
Find one?
[ALL]
Um...
No. Meow.
[CHINAMI]
Still, it's a really big world!
That's right. I'm sure there's
somebody prettier out there.
Can't you just say I'm the
prettiest and leave it at that?
[CHINAMI] No! Then you'll think
you don't have to try anymore!
[CHIGUSA] And you'll become
an old lady before you know it.
I've got a few years
till I'm past my prime,
and by then, you three and
Sue will be the prettiest.
We're gonna be pretty?
Yes, if you're good girls
who always do what you're told.
Why does talking to you
always end with a lecture?