[SHINO giggles]
Hime. I love-love you!
Himeno certainly is
popular with girls, isn't she?
Sure, but what's
wrong with that?
It's probably a lot better
than getting into
trouble with boys, right?
Of course,
since she's so pretty.
[MIDORIKO]
I'd think boys
wouldn't leave her
alone, either.
As for Shino, I imagine
she loves being spoiled
by her big cousin instead
of nagged at by her mom.
Shino's a cute little girl.
She reminds me a lot of
Himeno when she was that age.
Really? Lucky girl!
Hey, Shino, you're going to be
a beauty when you grow up.
If she takes after her
in the brains department,
too, it'll be perfect.
[RINO sighs]
That wouldn't necessarily
be a blessing.
[MIDORIKO] Are you kidding?
Of course, it would.
Do you know how much of
a relief it would be to us
for Shino to get into a national
prep school like Hime did?
If nothing else, it would
do wonders for our budget.
It's not that simple, though.
Being smart comes
with its own problems.
You spend too
much money on books!
We still have loans
to pay off, you know.
[RINO] I wonder if it might be
better not to have the pressure
that comes with going
to a good school.
[MIDORIKO] I would at least like
her to have the option, though.
Why don't we go read
a story in my room?
The knight defeated
the evil magician
and returned to his
homeland with the princess.
They established a democracy
where all people were equal.
Freedom and justice reigned,
and everyone was happy.
Yay!
Does it feel hot in here to you?
No, I'm super comfy.
[HIMENO]
Are you sure?
You're sweating a little bit.
[SHINO]
Huh?
Hey.
Would you like to go and
get some ice cream with me?
Okay!
It isn't that complicated.
Short-selling is when
you borrow shares,
sell them,
and then buy them back.
If you look at the buy
and sell rates, you'll see--
Hey, Auntie--I mean "Sis."
You'll be here
for a while, right?
Oh yeah, at this rate,
I think it'll be hours.
[giggles]
[sighs]
Hey, Tama.
Are you out running
errands with your sisters?
Oh, hi, Kimihara.
This is a surprise.
I don't see you often
outside of school.
[CHIHO] Wow! Her boobies are
a lot bigger than yours, Sis!
Please stop saying "boobies."
[MANAMI]
Girls!
It's nice to see you.
Chiho. Chinami. Chigusa.
[CHINAMI]
Can I give you a hello kiss?
[gasps]
[SHINO]
No, stop!
Stay away from her!
She's my cousin, not yours!
No one gets to kiss her but me!
You can kiss our
big sister if you want.
[SHINO]
No thanks.
Come on!
Don't you know the rules?
You only kiss people
you love-love.
So, if we love-love her, does
that mean we can kiss her, too?
No way!
She loves me the most!
She doesn't need your kisses.
So you keep her all to yourself?
That's not nice.
You're supposed to share.
Yeah!
[CHIHO] Our big sister
kisses all three of us,
and little Sue, too.
Four times a day!
A good morning kiss.
A going to school kiss.
A welcome home from school kiss.
And a good night kiss.
Yeah, and so what if I do?
Sis, how do you know
the little girl's cousin?
Are you friends?
Yeah, sure.
I guess.
[CHINAMI] So, then, does
that mean you love-love her?
Well, I suppose it means
that I don't hate her.
Do you give her "hello" kisses,
like you do with us?
[SHINO gasps]
I don't.
[sighs]
[CHINAMI]
Why not?
[MANAMI]
Because we're not kids.
Girls don't kiss each other
once they've grown up.
[CHIGUSA]
Oh, really?
It's kinda true.
Huh?
Well, this is an interesting
little gathering.
That your kid sister?
She's my cousin.
[INUKAI]
And these are?
[AKECHI] So, that cloning
thing really works, huh?
They're my little sisters.
Nice to meet you!
So, uh, who are you two?
You friends with our sister?
[AKECHI]
We sure are.
And that means
you love-love her,
but you don't kiss her.
What?
Sis told us girls don't kiss
when they're not kids anymore.
[AKECHI]
That's not true at all. Watch!
[CHIS]
Huh?
[gasps]
There, see?
Hey, keep your lips to yourself!
How could you do
that in front of kids?
[AKECHI]
Come on, what's the big deal?
You sound like an
old lady or something.
[MANAMI]
Who are you calling old lady?
[CHIS]
They kissed each other!
Forget you saw that!
[gasps]
Well, uh...
[AKECHI]
See?
It doesn't matter
if you're big or little.
It's always nice to
kiss someone you love.
You mean Big Sis was wrong?
[AKECHI]
Yes, she was.
Except, the mouth.
You don't kiss just
anybody there, okay?
You should save
those kinds of kisses
for only one special person.
[ALL 4]
Hmm?
[CHIGUSA]
Is that one of those things
that'll make more sense
when we're older?
Yeah, it's one of those.
Cool! Is it something dirty?
Well, I guess it could be.
What's up?
I think I explained it well.
Oh, yeah.
You can kiss other
people on the cheek.
That's okay. See?
Like this.
[gasps]
Get back!
Uh, are we really
the type of friends
who kiss each other?
We are.
We're totally besties.
You stop!
Only I kiss Hime,
'cause she love-loves me.
[AKECHI giggles]
Okay, then I'll
give you a smooch.
That's about enough of that.
Yeah, time to go.
Bye, kittens.
It was nice to meetcha!
Okay, bye!
We had fun, pervy lady!
[sighs]
Hey, do you want a kiss?
No! Don't kiss me.
I don't love-love you.
That's yucky!
Please make her stop!
Why? It's just a kiss.
She ran away!
Come back! Hey!
[SHINO]
Stop!
Um, Shino?
[MANAMI]
Don't worry about it.
Playing around like that
is how kids make friends.
[SHINO]
No!
[CHIS]
Don't run away! Come back!
[MANAMI]
What's up?
It's just, watching
you with the girls,
you almost seem like a mom.
Uh-huh. Yeah, I can see that.
Careful.
Act up in class
and I'll ground you.
Uh, right...
[splashing]
We're gonna be
in so much trouble
when Sis catches us,
but I don't care.
Look at you, and these
are your best clothes, too.
Taking care of
these three gives one
a new appreciation for the
struggles of moms everywhere.
Oh, yeah.
I bet it does.
Are you mad?
No, don't worry.
Bye-bye!
[CHIS]
See ya later!
I'll give you a kiss
next time, okay?
[RINO]
Did you fall in a ditch?
Where have you two been anyway?
[HIMENO] We ran into a
girl I know from school.
[MIDORIKO] What happened
to your clothes, Shino?
Sorry. It's my fault.
[MIDORIKO]
I doubt that.
For a quiet girl, she knows
how to get into trouble.
There's no warm
bathwater drawn yet.
You can take a shower, though.
I wanna shower with Hime!
[HIMENO]
Okay, lay your ears down.
Here comes the water.
[sniffs]
Do I stink?
[HIMENO]
No, you smell nice.
[SHINO] I can wash
your back if you want!
[HIMENO]
Mm-hmm.
Scrub. Scrub.
[giggles]
[SHINO]
Okay, rinsing now!
So, am I all clean?
[SHINO]
Uh-huh!
Huh? Uh...
Hime, uh...
Do you make milk?
No, I can't say that I do.
I'm kinda confused.
Huh?
That girl who kissed the
other girl in the park before.
I don't understand
what she was saying.
Um. Oh, I see.
Well, I think it'll make
more to you sense
when you're a little older.
You mean when I'm taller
and I've got boobies
as big as yours are?
Sorry about that.
It's fine.
[HIMENO]
Bye, Auntie...
I mean, "Sis."
Hime just call me Auntie.
Ya know, I'm not exactly
getting any younger, am I?
[HIMENO]
Night, Shino.
See ya next time.
Shino always has such a
good time with you, Hime,
but now she'll talk about
nothing but boobies for days.
[HIMENO]
Uhh... Um, what?
[PRETTY HORN]
Hang tight!
Magical Girl Pretty
Horn is up next!
Dodgeball. Dodgeball. Dodgeball.
[PRETTY HORN]
That's all.
Heh! Looks like we're going
to be playing dodgeball
during every free period.
Majority rules, and all that.
This time, at least, yes.
However, next time,
we'll decide using a method
that reflects the will
of the minority, as well.
[ACTOR]
What?
You can't do
something like that!
Denying the majority is the
same thing as denying democracy!
[roars]
[PRETTY HORN]
Democratic space is distorting!
Awaken, the power of ethics!
Guide us, law and logic!
Help us to grant
the greatest happiness
to the greatest
number of people.
[PRETTY HORN]
Magical Girl Pretty Horn!
Take this! Ostrakismos!
Lift up your right arm.
Now your left arm.
Keep the right arm up.
Don't lower it.
[CHIHO]
Okay, now raise your tail.
[MANAMI sighs]
C'mon, you better put your tail
up, or you'll lose the game.
Enough TV, little Chis.
But you always let us watch
TV on Sunday mornings.
Party pooper.
It's called being responsible.
Anyway, I'm going
to go out for a while.
I need you three
to look after Sue.
Aw!
But it's the weekend.
We wanted to go out and
play with some of our friends.
[MANAMI] You know she's too
young to be home by herself.
Fine!
We'll take her
with us when we play.
[MANAMI]
That won't work.
She's too weak.
What would happen if she got
a fever while you were out?
No fair!
What are we supposed
to do, then?
Just stay here with Sue
and try to make the best of it.
Why us, though?
Where's Daddy?
Can't he do it?
[MANAMI]
No, he can't. He's at work.
[CHIHO]
Hold on.
Daddy's job is to
paint pictures, isn't it?
[CHIGUSA] How's he
supposed to finish any of them
if he's never here?
That's work he does for himself.
He has a different job
that he does for money.
[CHIS] Why not have
one job that does both?
Trust me, I know it doesn't
make a lot of sense.
But that's how it is.
[CHIGUSA]
If he needs money so bad,
can't he just take some
from the offering box?
[MANAMI]
No.
That money belongs to the gods.
[CHIHO] Aren't grown-ups
supposed to stay home
and spend time with
their kids on days off?
I can't play with you today.
I wish I could.
Babysitting sounds
like a big responsibility.
Are you even allowed to leave
kindergartners home alone?
[MANAMI]
You may be young,
but you're resourceful
and trustworthy.
Besides, there are three of you.
Okay, we'll stay here.
Do what you need to do.
[MANAMI]
Good, I'm counting on you.
[CHINAMI] We can at least invite
a couple friends over, right?
You can, but no
roughhousing, okay?
This old house couldn't take it.
Hey, it's Chigusa.
Yeah. That's right.
Thing is, our sister's
making us stay home today.
Yeah, you want to?
Sounds great!
Hey, it's Chiho.
Can you--? Uh-huh.
[MANAMI] How many friends
are they going to call?
[MANAMI]
All right.
I'll be back in a little bit.
Don't open the door to
anyone you don't know.
[CHIGUSA]
Yeah, yeah. We won't.
[CHIS]
See you later, Sis!
[MANAMI]
You here for club stuff?
Yep.
What about you?
For student council.
[HIMENO]
Well, have fun.
[MANAMI]
What club is she in?
Biology?
[KIDS]
Rock, paper, scissors!
I found you!
[laughs]
[GIRL B]
Hey, wait up!
Sue, are you all right?
[GIRL B]
Over here!
Are you feeling sick?
Maybe you need a nap.
No. Wanna play more.
Just rest for a little, okay?
But I was having so much fun.
Don't worry, she'll be fine.
This always happens when
Sue runs around too much.
Let's play inside, though.
[MANAMI]
Okay, it's three o'clock.
I believe we've discussed
all there is to discuss.
The only thing left
to do is take a vote.
[BOY COUNCIL A]
I can't believe she'd stop now.
How can you say that?
We haven't even come
to a consensus yet.
That's right!
We need to keep talking about
this until we can all agree.
[MANAMI]
No, we decided in advance that
if an agreement wasn't reached
by three o'clock, we would vote.
Now, is everyone ready?
You can't just decide
something like that.
I know.
You just want to
go home, don't you?
Yes, I do. So what?
Well, that was honest.
[BOY COUNCIL A]
Are you serious?
Yes, I am.
It's the weekend.
I've already let this
deliberation carve
into my private time.
We've been at this long enough.
I need to be home
by four o'clock,
so I can make dinner for my
father and my little sisters.
Does anyone have a
problem with that?
[MANAMI]
Good. Let's vote.
[GIRL COUNCIL C]
Um, Mitama?
[MANAMI]
Hmm?
Yes? What is it?
[GIRL COUNCIL C] I understand
what you were saying back there,
and it's not that
I don't see your side,
but being in the student
council doesn't just mean
getting stuff done.
It means working together
and learning new things,
kinda like a club.
Debates are important.
They're part of the high-school
experience, ya know?
Your point?
Just that, maybe
your family can put up
with you being late
once in a while.
[MANAMI]
They can't.
Huh?
[MANAMI]
I'll tell you a story.
My grandfather passed away,
but his whole life,
he paid more attention to
martial arts than his family.
His health failed,
and he was on his deathbed.
He called me by
my mother's name and said,
"Let's go home."
[MANAMI] Since then I've made
sure my family comes first.
Goodbye.
With 30 years'
more experience,
we might be able
to out-argue her,
but I'm not sure even
that would be enough.
Jeez, what's her problem?
She'll never succeed out
in the real world that way.
Uh, and since when are you
an expert on the real world?
[GIRL COUNCIL D]
You know it's true!
Parents can't always go
running home to their kids.
[BOY COUNCIL C chuckles]
Well, if anyone can make
it work, it's Mitama.
[playing children sounds]
[GIRL B]
Are you feeling any better?
Huh? Yeah.
[GIRL B]
We could play house together.
Would you like that?
[GIRL B]
Hi, I'm Mister Bear.
Would you like to
be my friend?
[MANAMI] How many friends
did they invite over again?
Six?
[playing children sounds]
[crashing]
[sighs]
Sounds lively.
At least this means they ended
up staying in the house.
[MANAMI]
I'm home.
Hi!
Hey, Sis.
[SUE]
I'm glad you're back!
So am I. Huh?
You've been keeping Sue company?
Thanks for that.
[CHIHO]
Oh, hey.
We didn't know you were back.
I am, now, please explain.
Why's this girl with Sue when
it should've been you three?
[CHIHO] Hey, at least
we stayed home, didn't we?
[CHIGUSA]
Yeah!
Can you get us
something to eat now?
Everyone's hungry.
[MANAMI]
Yeah, sure.
Round up your friends.
Hey.
What's the matter?
[CHIHO]
Nothing. Never mind.
[MANAMI]
Be careful going home.
Bye-bye!
[MANAMI'S DAD]
Hello, girls.
[CHIHO]
Yay, he's back!
[CHIS, SUE]
Hi, Daddy!
Have you been good today?
[CHIHO]
Yeah. Sure.
Sis left us in charge here.
Except something
kinda weird happened.
We invited six
friends over today,
and all six of them
were playing tag with us.
I know 'cause I counted.
But then, there was still
someone playing house with Sue.
I'm not that good at math,
but six plus one can't
equal six, can it?
Someone probably
just showed up late.
No. No one came that
we didn't invite,
and nobody left
early, either.
Well, maybe a Zashiki
Warashi found her way
into the group somehow.
[CHIS]
Zashiki warashi?
[MANAMI'S DAD] A supernatural
being that takes a child's form.
[CHINAMI]
What, like a ghost or something?
[MANAMI'S DAD]
It's a nice ghost.
There's no reason to be scared.
They're supposed
to bring good fortune.
Still a ghost?
[MANAMI]
You had fun playing, didn't you?
Yeah.
[MANAMI]
Then what's the problem?
[laughter]