[HIMENO]
Sorry! Were you waiting long?
[NOZOMI] Ah! Nice.
I'm liking the disguise.
[chuckles]
Although, I've gotta admit,
you still just look like Hime.
Hard to hide the centaur thing.
Eh, don't worry about it.
[KYOKO] All right, it's just
about time. Shall we?
[HIMENO]
But we still have 15 minutes.
Yeah, except Nakafumi always
arrives 15 minutes early.
Hey, you're getting the
whole check? That's awesome.
You'll pay me back later.
Keep your eyes on the street.
[NOZOMI]
Uh.
You weren't kidding about
him being super early.
Right, they're on the move.
I dunno about this.
We have to make sure
that no mistakes happen.
Mistakes? Like what?
Do we have to spell it out?
As her friends, it's up to us
to prevent sexual indiscretions.
[gasps]
No! They wouldn't!
Shush!
Now, let's go.
Are you excited to go to the
contemporary arts museum?
[SPY C]
Target is now on the move.
Unidentified pursuers confirmed.
I should search our
database of known terrorists.
Not necessary.
Those girls are the
target's classmates.
They're playing a childish
prank. Just ignore it.
We've got company.
Public Security, the military,
the Cabinet Research
Office, of course.
The CIA. The FSB. A whole crowd.
So all the usual
players are here.
Take no action unless
absolutely necessary.
[SUU]
I'm a little confused.
Do humans find this sort of
thing pleasant to observe?
Visual enjoyment isn't really
the point of contemporary art.
At least, I think.
Honestly, I don't know
that much about it.
I find it interesting, though.
For most people, art means the
creation of beautiful things
through painting
and other mediums.
A long time ago, only the
wealthy and privileged
could buy or make art.
A person couldn't simply go down
to the local stationary shop
and purchase a tube of paint.
But times changed and
so did technology.
Photography emerged, offering
a way to capture images
more accurately
than any painting.
The industrial age
arrived, and with it,
the ability to mass-produce
highly-detailed
and precise models
inexpensively.
When the beauty that was
previously rare and precious
became commonplace,
demand emerged for a
different kind of beauty.
Accurate reproduction
of items and people
were no longer enough.
Take the Interstellar Wars
movies, for example.
An immense budget
may have resulted
in more realistic
special effects,
but that doesn't
translate into beauty.
So people began to paint
things in subjective ways
that no photograph could convey.
Some Western artists borrowed
aspects from African art,
which had previously
been viewed as primitive.
Artists began to challenge the
very standards of beauty itself,
creating abstract paintings that
seemed to depict nothing at all.
But even those were still
aesthetically pleasing,
however strange.
That too was lost, however,
when people began putting
ordinary items on display
and calling them art.
And now it's all about changing
the meaning of art in context.
Like a game or race.
Who can change the rules first?
That's my take, but like I said,
I'm not an expert or anything.
What, specifically,
is that context?
[NAKAFUMI]
Uhh...
I'm not sure.
Of course no one's going
to give up that secret.
Anybody who knew the answer
could make a
fortune as an artist.
The art world is cutthroat.
Really?
There's a secret out there
that's that important?
Who knows?
But if there was,
it would be invaluable.
We are talking about
putting a price on reality.
Hey, it looks like
they're moving on.
A date at an art museum, huh?
This guy's got some class.
What d'you think? Is Suu
actually enjoying this?
[KYOKO]
Good question.
Who knows if art is even
a part of her culture.
So what kind of art
is there in Antarctica?
[SUU]
Hm.
We do have drawings, but
they're more like schematics.
I suppose the way
humans look at art
is the same way we view
logical expressions
and numerical formulas.
They're said to be beautiful in
their brevity and precision.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Maybe you would've preferred
a traditional museum.
Oh, no. I can make
sense of those on my own.
But art?
To understand that,
it helps if I have somebody
looking at it with me.
I don't know if I'm
really the best person
to explain this stuff to you.
It's fascinating, truly.
I like hearing your
views on the subject.
You don't have to be an expert.
Hey, watch it. Oh!
That you, Princess?
You recognized me, huh?
[MANAMI]
Um.
[HIMENO]
Uh?
You on a date?
Hey, do you know what that is?
[HIMENO]
Huh?
Hmm...
No idea.
[NOZOMI]
Hime, they're moving!
[gasps]
Well, bye.
[HIMENO]
Sorry about that.
Wait, is that the Class
Prez with Omaki?
[HIMENO]
Yeah.
Did they come to the
museum on a date, too?
Think so.
Can we stay focused on
the date we came here for?
Doesn't look like they're
heading for the station.
[KYOKO]
But that way leads to...
[ALL gasp]
The sun is going down.
Why isn't this
date over already?
Don't get caught up
in the nightlife, kids.
[gasps]
They aren't!
They are. I knew it.
[groans]
Just great.
What do we do?
[NOZOMI]
Is there anything we can do?
How do we stop this?
Get one of our guys
to the front desk
with a fake police badge.
Have them cite the Juvenile
Protection Ordinance
and kick the kids out.
Okay, but what's to stop them
from going someplace else?
We'll just have
to play it by ear.
[NOZOMI]
Almost there!
[HIMENO]
I can't look.
[KYOKO]
I can.
[SHIGETOKI]
Don't do it.
Keep walking!
Too bad, huh?
[HIMENO, NOZOMI]
Huh?
I mean, close call!
[sighs]
So a used bookstore.
Seems this guy's quite
the intellectual.
No kidding.
It's a book about
contemporary art.
Maybe it'll help us
understand a little better.
[HIMENO] So how did
your date go yesterday?
It was lovely.
He showed me some very
interesting things.
Wow! Really, like what?
We went to a museum,
one that exhibited contemporary
art, which I didn't understand.
It was nice.
It's still a novelty for me to
not understand something.
What did you think
of it, Himeno?
Oh, me?
Well, I found it pretty
confusing, too.
All that abstract stuff
is tough to get.
--[KYOKO] Huh?
--Hey!
[HIMENO gasps]
[HIMENO, KYOKO, NOZOMI chuckle]
You knew we were there, huh?
[SUU]
I'm sorry...
[MANAMI]
Thanks for yesterday.
Please, I had a great time.
[MANAMI]
Yeah. Me too.
We should do it again. Really,
thank you for everything.
Sure, of course.
[KYOKO]
Oh, never mind.
[SUU]
Did I miss something?
Really? So you're going out?
Yes, I am. Keep
an eye on things.
Of course, with Dad home today,
I'm sure you'll be fine.
Have fun, okay?
No, we're not gonna have fun!
All he ever does is
sit around and paint.
He's a painter.
[door opens]
[OMAKI]
Tama.
Hey.
You her date?
I guess so.
You're good looking
enough. You'll do.
Uh, thanks.
Still, Sis, leaving the
kids at home on the weekend
to go out on a secret
tryst with a boy?
Isn't that some kind
of child abuse?
"Tryst"? Really? And I'm
not a boy. I'm a girl.
I won't be gone very long.
I'll be back in time for dinner.
[BOTH grumble]
[CHINAMI]
Oh, switching?
Meow.
Are you going out?
Yes, we are. Take care
of Sue, all right?
We'll bring you all
back a souvenir.
[BOTH]
Poo! Poo!
[MANAMI] Hey, what did
I say about that face?
[MANAMI]
See you soon, little Chis.
[OMAKI] Getting outta
the house is tough, huh?
[MANAMI]
Seriously.
[OMAKI] You're lucky
you've got little sisters.
Little brothers are a handful.
Yeah, I don't know.
I feel like raising little boys
might be more straightforward.
Uh, I wouldn't be
so sure about that.
Oh, who knows?
[OMAKI]
Want to link arms?
Uh.
Link arms? Why?
C'mon, it's just karaoke.
I'm not interested.
[PROWLER]
Hm?
Tch.
[MANAMI]
Uh.
This is kind of embarrassing.
It's not a big deal
if it's two girls.
[ONLOOKER A]
What an attractive couple.
[ONLOOKER C, ONLOOKER D] Oh,
wow. They're so good-looking.
[ONLOOKER B]
Are they models?
With stuff like this,
you sometimes spend longer
reading the explanation
than actually
looking at the art.
'Cause if you don't,
you won't understand it.
But you do understand it now?
Not really.
Hey, watch it. Oh!
That you, Princess?
Oh, so you recognized me, huh?
[HIMENO gasps]
You on a date?
Hey, do you know what that is?
[HIMENO]
Huh?
No idea.
[NOZOMI]
Hime, they're moving!
Well, bye.
Wait, the Class Prez and Omaki?
[MANAMI]
Huh.
I'm always running into them.
What are they up to?
It doesn't look like
they're on a date.
Stop. We're here to
look at the art.
But there are more
interesting things to watch.
Come on, Dad!
Stay still for just
a bit longer, okay?
[SUE]
Big Sis?
Oh. Looks like Sue's awake.
[SUE]
Where's Sis?
[CHIHO]
Just a sec, Sue. We're coming.
[alarm sounds]
Switch time!
Wait.
[MANAMI'S DAD]
I would absolutely take
a smoke break right now.
If I were a smoker.
Drinking's out of the question.
Gambling has never held
much interest for me.
And there's no way I'd ever take
my frustration out on the kids.
Even when I do paint,
nothing sells.
But I just can't bring
myself to give it up.
There's no way out for me.
[MANAMI]
Not cheap. Still...
[OMAKI]
ou gonna buy that?
[MANAMI]
Uh.
I didn't understand
anything here.
I think I need more
thorough explanations.
[OMAKI] Look at this.
They sell sweets here, too.
There's enough in
here for everyone.
Here. A little something
for the kiddos.
No, I can't.
Please, I'm the one who dragged
you here in the first place.
Hey, don't get all
uptight on me now.
It just doesn't feel
right to accept a gift
from someone who doesn't
have a steady income.
Come on.
I do actually get paid
a bit for helping out
with the family business,
so don't sweat it.
And besides, I promised
I'd get souvenirs
for the Chisters, remember?
I'll be in trouble if
I don't follow through.
Just take them, 'kay?
Fine. I will, thank you.
So if what we saw here today
qualifies as contemporary art,
I'm guessing that means
your Dad's a little
behind the times, huh?
That's a harsh assessment.
Although, it's also
an accurate one.
I'm not an art
expert or anything,
but if he wants to sell,
he should paint stuff that's
more surreal or edgy.
He could even quit painting and
try performance art instead.
Something provocative
and attention-grabbing.
Like throwing a nationalist
up in the air, maybe.
Yeah, I don't know.
I mean, it's not as if he
can do whatever he wants
and be able to call it art.
[OMAKI]
That's not what I'm suggesting.
I'm just saying,
he should try to challenge
some established concept.
"A true artist's work
will question--
and sometimes invalidate--
social ideals,
and those who look
at it are freed
from the shackles
of preconception."
Y'know? Stuff like that.
[MANAMI] But rather than
invalidating social ideals,
isn't that type of
artist just attempting
to replace existing
ones with his own?
There's the appearance
of freedom,
but if you look closely,
you see the shackles
have just been hidden.
This is getting a little
too deep for me.
[MANAMI]
Honestly, I'm a bit lost, too.
It's funny.
For all that my father says
he wants to be an artist,
I don't think he means it.
Wait, he doesn't?
Now you're starting
to confuse me.
What my father really wants
is just to be a painter.
Which means he's an artist.
[MANAMI]
No, it's different.
All he wants is to
paint simple pictures.
Nothing fancy. Nothing
avant-garde or abstract.
Just plain realism.
[OMAKI] Okay, then why not
become an illustrator?
Good question.
Some of his paintings
have actually been used
as book covers before.
But a career illustrator
doesn't decide what to draw.
They have to do what
they're told, you know?
And he wants creative freedom?
[MANAMI]
Yes.
Besides, it's a surprisingly
competitive field.
There are high schoolers
who are pretty good
and willing to work for less.
[OMAKI] So why doesn't he
just leave it as a hobby?
He can't! That's
totally unacceptable!
[sighs]
[OMAKI]
But why?
If I said it was a hobby,
that would be like
telling my father
that his art will only ever
be worth doing for fun.
It would kill any hope he has.
He's been pouring his energy
and passion into painting
for longer than I've
even been alive.
I can't take that from him.
[OMAKI]
Okay, well,
if he is that
passionate about it,
then he has to be
willing to compromise,
accept the bad along
with the good.
Uh.
Yeah, maybe.
Take a sport, like baseball.
It isn't enough to practice
just batting and catching.
You have to do
boring stuff, too.
Like cardio and
strength training.
Artists tend to think
compromising
damages their integrity.
I don't think my father
could handle that.
[OMAKI]
You know, Tama.
I hate to say it, but you're
too soft on your dad.
[gasps]
[MANAMI]
That's ridiculous!
[OMAKI] What was it people used
to call you? Miss Perfect?
[MANAMI] Yeah, that was my
nickname in middle school.
That's right.
Remember our Home Ec. teacher?
She said you were the most ready
one of us to raise a family.
Your point?
[OMAKI]
You're mature for your age,
but you're still a kid,
same as me.
You haven't been in
the real world yet.
What do you truly know about it?
Does it make sense for a
kid still in high school
to be planning out an
adult's life for him?
Well, no. I guess not.
[OMAKI]
Your dad's not a child.
He can think things through
and make up his own mind.
Maybe the best way
to show your support
is by having faith in him.
You're right. Thank you.
Hey, it's no problem.
Talk to me anytime.
Oh, whoops. It's later
than I thought.
[OMAKI]
Ready to get going?
[MANAMI]
Mh-hm.
Hey, girls!
[CHIS]
Big Sis is home!
Ss promised.
Koma got it for all of you.
[CHIS] Yay! A souvenir!
We got a present!
[MANAMI]
I'll have dinner ready soon.
Dinner's ready. You coming?
[MANAMI'S DAD] Thanks,
but I don't know if I can stop.
I'm, uh, kind of
in a groove, here.
Don't knock yourself out.
Okay. Um, yeah, sure.
[MANAMI] You don't know what
will come of your painting.
If you ruin your health, too,
you'll have nothing left.
[MANAMI]
I may not know much about art,
but I think it's
a nice painting.
Well, first we went to a museum,
one that exhibited
contemporary artwork.
I didn't understand it,
but that was nice for once.
What did you think of
the exhibit, Himeno?
[HIMENO] Well, I found
it pretty confusing, too.
All that abstract stuff
is tough to get.
[NOZOMI]
Hey!
[HIMENO]
You knew we were there?
[SUU] I'm sorry, but you do
kind of stand out, Himeno.
[NOZOMI] Jeez, way to blow
it for the rest of us, Hime.
[HIMENO]
Sorry! I didn't mean to.
[OMAKI]
Good morning.
[MANAMI] Good morning.
Thanks for yesterday.
Please, I had a great time.
Yeah. Me too.
We should do it again. Really,
thank you for everything.
[OMAKI]
Sure, of course.