[alarm rings]
[RINO]
Himeno!
Do you hear me?
Turn that alarm off
and get out of bed!
[ringing continues]
[HIMENO groans]
[HIMENO sighs]
--[HIMENO groans]
--[thud]
[RINO] You'll put a hole
through the ceiling!
[HIMENO yawns]
Good morning.
I'm sorry it took me
so long to get out of bed.
[SOUTA]
Well, glad you could make it.
Go on. Get your face washed.
[HIMENO]
Okay.
Aww!
[SOUTA]
Hey! Hurry up.
Aren't you finished in here yet?
No, I'm not!
[RINO]
Wrap it up already!
[HIMENO]
Jeez, Dad, come on!
--You're taking forever!
--Okay, what's the problem now?
I need to go, too!
[SOUTA groaning]
Hold on!
I'm... working on
a big one, here...
Can we skip the commentary?
You're going to be late.
Why not use the one at school?
[HIMENO]
I hate school bathrooms!
[RINO] Aren't they
careful to accommodate
all body types
these days, though?
[HIMENO]
Yeah, but it's still cramped.
[HIMENO] And besides, there's
no steppy-step for me to use.
You don't need
that thing anymore.
[HIMENO] It doesn't feel
right going without it.
[sighs]
[HIMENO]
Bye! See you after school.
[RINO]
Have a good day!
And slow down.
Be careful for once, please!
That girl!
Honestly, it doesn't matter
how big she gets.
At the end of the day,
she's still a child.
[STUDENTS murmuring]
[HIMENO]
Hmm?
It's really starting
to get long, huh?
[HIMENO]
My hair?
Yeah.
I have been thinking
about getting it cut recently,
but it's sort of difficult.
Are you worried
you won't like it?
[HIMENO]
No, the salon is too pricey.
And now's not
exactly the best time
to ask my parents for money.
And, besides that,
stylists never seem too happy
about working on
centaur clients.
Apparently,
we're a bit of a challenge.
Yeah. I guess that makes sense.
I bet it's hard to work on
someone so different from you.
Trying to comb around my
horns is annoying even for me.
Well, I still
don't think it's fair.
You're paying them
to do their job.
[KYOKO]
What do you know about it?
Your mom cuts your hair
for you, doesn't she?
Honestly, you could stand
to put in a bit more effort
on your appearance.
[HIMENO giggles]
Nobody asked you.
You could change
your hair up a bit.
Maybe try growing it out long?
Nah, I don't think so.
Long hair is such
a pain to deal with.
I'm a low-maintenance
kinda girl.
Whatcha up to?
Talking hairstyles?
Um, yeah.
[AKECHI]
Interesting.
You ready? Here we go!
We will now begin the meeting to
decide Hime's new hairstyle!
Huh?
Okay, I'm first.
I think you should
choose a short style.
It'll be easier.
You've got a point there.
Not a chance!
Short hair wouldn't
suit our princess at all.
She should go for
a Rococo style,
something that screams
feminine beauty.
Just look at that face!
Her features are all
so large and rounded.
The right hairstyle would
accentuate those things.
Ringlet curls, really?
Ugh. Jeez, talk about
high-maintenance.
Well, maybe not.
Back then, nobles didn't
wash their hair much.
I think they even wore wigs.
Sounds fun!
You could make it
a full-on cosplaying thing.
Maybe even pose for that
magazine some more.
Can we please
forget the magazine?
You know,
for something simpler,
you could try straightening it.
Yeah! That would so work.
You'd be like an aloof,
unattainable ice princess!
Who the heck is this?
So, what did you
have in mind, Hime?
Well...
I was thinking about getting it
cut to shoulder-length.
I don't know.
It is kind of a hassle
when it's long like this.
But I wore it short before,
and people didn't like it.
[KYOKO]
Huh? Really? You mean boys?
What? No, not boys.
Just, um...
Well, my cousin, Shino.
Definitely wasn't
a fan of it short.
Shino, what do
you think of my haircut?
It's so short.
Why'd you cut it?
Aren't you a pwincess?
[HIMENO]
Hmm?
I'm sad!
You don't wook like
a pwincess anymore, Hime!
Huh?
[GROUP]
Uh, really?
Yes, really!
I'm actually not too surprised.
Oh. Hey, Prez.
[MANAMI]
My sisters were the same way.
Kids don't like change much.
[AKECHI] The class president
with short hair?
I could see that.
Angelfolks' halos are
just hair, right?
Could you cut yours
if you wanted to?
You can't
intentionally cut them.
It's seen as a form
of discrimination.
The implication is that
you're rejecting your own race.
Of course,
it's possible to be born
without one or to have
it accidentally cut.
In which case, the hospital
or salon will give you
a certificate as proof.
But that just
makes things difficult.
Besides, it looks dumb
when it's growing back.
Sounds like a
whole lot of trouble to me.
You've got it the
easiest of everyone here.
Hair stuff is hard
for you, too, huh?
[MANAMI]
Yes, it is.
So, your tail...
Do you ever have
to get that cut?
[HIMENO]
No, I don't.
It sheds on its own when
it gets to a certain length.
Some people do get pretty
fancy with them, though.
That's something
I've never had
to worry about with my tail.
[HIMENO]
Can you stop staring at it now?
[NOZOMI]
Aw, bashful!
It'd look good fluffy.
[school bell rings]
[HIMENO groans]
Why does she always have to
put peppers in my lunch?
What are you, a seven-year-old?
Be nice!
Put on your big girl pants
and eat your vegetables.
It can't be that bad.
If you want to be big and
strong when you grow up,
you need plenty of
nutritious food.
You sound just
like my mom right now.
[NOZOMI]
Y'know, I'm surprised.
Doesn't look like enough food
for somebody your size.
Um, yeah.
I didn't know you
were a light eater.
What about you?
Do you eat the same things
you would in Antarctica?
I've been able to
acclimate my digestive system
to the food humans eat.
So, I can have most of
the same things you would.
[SUU] Although, the way
my mouth is designed,
I am not able to chew.
So, I have to eat things
that I can swallow whole.
Interesting.
[SUU]
What's wrong, Himeno?
Do you not like your lunch?
Oh, no, it looks fine.
Except for the peppers.
You're on a diet
or something, right?
Really? Why?
Um, well...
She's truly dieting?
Eh. I wouldn't be so sure.
Um... Uh...
That's just... You know...
[MANAMI]
Kimihara.
Students aren't allowed
to have snacks outside
of what they bring
for lunch, you know that.
No! That's, um...
That's the dessert that was
packed in my lunch box.
You're not fooling me
with those eyebrows, missy.
Ah!
Seeing as I'm not a teacher,
I won't take it away from you,
but if you're that hungry,
have your mom
pack a bigger lunch.
--I'm really sorry, Tama.
--Whoopsie. Busted.
--Don't let it happen again.
--She's more of a
--mom than a class president.
--I won't, I swear.
[SUU] I'm sorry, but what does
the word "mom" mean?
[school bell rings]
[KYOKO] I'm sure you've
heard this a bunch before,
but it's rare to see
a Japanese centaur
with red hair like yours.
Yeah, I know.
It actually caused
some trouble in middle school.
My teacher suspected
me of dying it,
and he wouldn't believe me when
I told him it was natural.
Wouldn't that be
considered discrimination?
[HIMENO] Yeah, he ended
up getting arrested.
Is it red because
you're half-Japanese?
No.
My mom's family has
actually looked like this
for generations.
[NOZOMI]
Huh.
[HIMENO] There's a story
behind it and everything.
Interesting! A story?
[HIMENO] Well, I don't know
if "story" is the right word.
"Legend" might be better.
If you wouldn't mind,
I'd love to hear it.
Uh... Sure, why not?
One of my ancestors was
a princess who was kidnapped
by a southern barbarian.
Her siblings pursued
them relentlessly,
in hopes of saving her.
Their search took them
from Southern Europe
to Northern Europe
and on to Anatolia.
Eventually,
they found their sister
and returned with her to Japan.
But from then on,
she and all her descendants
had babies who were
born with red hair.
So, it does come
from having a mixed heritage.
The story about
the princess and the raid
on the barbarians is famous.
I had no idea you came from
such a distinguished family.
Not really.
All that was a long time ago.
My mom's dad was
an ordinary businessman.
You don't have
any historical documents?
I'm not sure.
If we did, I would've
seen them in the house
at some point, right?
[KYOKO]
Still, documentation or not,
the legend is really well known.
It's so amazing.
[KYOKO] The raiders
were set on their path.
They were determined to
bring the princess home.
No area of the continent
was safe from them.
[KYOKO]
The story goes...
[KYOKO] ...that they sank
a ship using nothing
but a single arrow.
Come on, that's ridiculous!
Yeah, you'd think so, right?
Apparently, there are some
records of it, though.
It's a remarkable story.
Regardless of whether
it's entirely true.
And there's more to it.
The raiders freed
slaves across the continent,
who then joined them until
they had formed a vast army.
With that army at their backs,
they were finally able
to rescue the princess.
And the culmination of
that fierce military
bloodline is this.
[HIMENO giggles]
Scary!
[EDITORS murmuring]
Ah, yes, good afternoon.
This is Mochida of Hell Monthly.
Hello, it's great
to hear from you.
Naraku speaks
very highly of you.
[keys clacking]
No problem.
Of course.
Okay.
You'll have it in your inbox
no later than this evening,
I assure you.
Thanks, I hope you
have a good afternoon.
[EDITORS murmuring]
That sounded like a young girl.
His secretary?
Hey, you heard.
Have it finished
by 6 PM, Pops.
Honestly.
Not that you ever listen to me,
but you really shouldn't
call your dad "Pops," y'know.
Something like "Father" or "Dad"
would be more respectful.
Well, you've gotta
earn that respect, Pops.
Fulfill your paternal duty and
have the article done by six.
Do you think you
could cut me some slack?
I'm trying to keep two kids
fed on a writer's wages,
and that's not easy.
Especially now,
with the economy the way it is.
[KYOKO]
Yeah, yeah. Just get it done.
[MOCHIDA]
Excuse me, sir,
is Naraku a particularly
successful writer?
[CHIEF EDITOR]
Well, to an extent, I guess.
It was a while ago, but he
got a bunch of attention
for an article he wrote as part
of an undercover investigation.
So now, whenever
that incident pops back up
in the news, he gets
some time in the spotlight.
Oh.
[CHIEF EDITOR]
Why do you ask, anyway?
Well, uh...
I called him a minute ago and
a girl answered the phone.
I didn't think many writers
could afford a secretary.
[CHIEF EDITOR]
Oh, no. That was his daughter.
What? That geezer--
Oh. I mean...
I didn't know he was married.
Surprise, surprise.
He wasn't born a chubby old guy,
and yes, at some point,
he managed to have
a kid with someone.
I can only imagine
what his daughter looks like.
[CHIEF EDITOR] From what I hear,
she's a pretty cute girl,
on the slender side.
I believe she's in middle--
No, it must be
high school by now.
[MOCHIDA]
A pretty cute girl, huh?
Yeah! That's great!
[CHIEF EDITOR]
I'll tell you what's great.
Since she started working
as his secretary,
he's been meeting
all his deadlines.
I don't know how she manages it,
but those are the kinds
of results that I am
not going to argue with.
[KYOKO]
'Kay, Pops.
You can go ahead
and look it over again.
I fixed the typos
and spelling errors.
Yeah, okay.
And I thought I told you
not to call me Pops.
Anyway, why
no comments from that guy
at Library Paradise University?
You know, Professor Bibu.
I wanted some, but I
wasn't able to get an interview.
Hey! What? Who are you--?
Yes, hello.
Is this Professor Bibu's office?
[NARAKU]
Whoa, hold on!
Oh, yes. Absolutely.
I'm very impressed with the
professor's recent writings.
I agree completely!
Uh-huh.
The seminar was excellent.
In fact, I was hoping I could
hear the professor's opinion.
We'll need to
take a right when
we get to the next
corner, please.
Yes, that's perfect.
Okay.
Thank you so much for making
time to speak with me.
[KYOKO]
Here. The professor's comments.
Right. Okay.
[KYOKO] Give me a sec and
I'll go put on some coffee.
You keep on writing.
[NARAKU sighs]
[KYOKO]
Hmm...
Is that the class president?
Weird. Why's she
dressed like that?
Is she cosplaying?
[NARAKU]
Hey, hurry up with the coffee.
[KYOKO]
Yeah, yeah.
What's up?
Something interesting out there?
[KYOKO] Well, I just saw a
friend of mine from school.
She was wearing
a priestess outfit,
and going into the crazy
neighbor lady's house.
You think maybe
this friend of yours is running
one of those curse
removal scams?
[KYOKO]
What?
Gonna tell me not to hang out
with someone like that?
No. I was gonna tell
you to hang out with her more.
Could be a good story.
[KYOKO]
Sorry.
I don't really think she's the
type to do that sort of thing.
This is it, the box
I was telling you about.
[MANAMI]
Mm...
I saw a medium
before I called you.
According to her,
the thing is cursed.
Right. Did the medium tell you
anything more about the curse?
She said it was so powerful,
she didn't think there was
anything that could be
done to remove it.
So, I'm supposed to leave it
in this spot to contain
the vengeful spirit.
I light candles and make
offerings every day, as well.
[WOMAN NEIGHBOR A] But its power
still seems to be leaking out,
infecting my house.
My cat went missing for a while.
I hear noises coming from
rooms I know are empty,
and sometimes, I can sense
a presence behind me.
[MANAMI]
She's got an active imagination.
Still...
I think I can help.
I'll do what I can to quiet the
box and then have it removed.
[MANAMI]
First, I'll purify the room
and exorcise any remaining evil.
Yes, thank you.
Please, go ahead.
May I ask you to step
outside the room while I work?
[WOMAN NEIGHBOR A]
Of course.
[sighs]
[MANAMI]
Be cleansed!
Be purified!
[MANAMI] I wonder what I should
make for dinner tonight.
I'm all finished in here.
[WOMAN NEIGHBOR A]
Thank you so much for your help!
Just doing my duty.
Now, about that
monetary offering.
[WOMAN NEIGHBOR A]
Oh, yes, of course.
Please accept this, and
reimbursement for the taxi.
[MANAMI sighs] I'll return later
to oversee to the box's removal.
[WOMAN NEIGHBOR A]
Thank you.
My home already
feels more peaceful.
[KYOKO]
Yes. Yes.
We're looking forward to working
with you again next month, too.
Sounds like
they're accepting it.
All right!
Well, that's one less
thing to worry about.
I deserve a reward.
Want to go grab some dinner?
We're not going anywhere.
Brother's getting back late,
and we should have
food for him here.
[NARAKU] Aw. You're always
so concerned about him.
What about your doting father?
[KYOKO] Shut up. I'm going
to go make dinner.
Then, you're going to eat it
and be grateful that you have
such a wonderful daughter.
[CHIS snoring]
Hey, how'd it go?
You're taking dinner
duty tonight, Dad?
Sure am.
The kids exhausted themselves
playing and passed out.
And it sounded like
you'd be home late.
And the painting?
What?
Have you made
any progress on it?
Uh...
Actually, I seem to be in
a bit of a slump right now.
[MANAMI sighs]
[CHIS snoring]
[MANAMI]
Hey, Dad.
I don't know any more about
art than what I've read
in textbooks, but can you
really call yourself a painter?
That's a painful
question to hear
from your own daughter.
I know my painting doesn't put
food on the table, but still...
It isn't about whether or not
it puts food on the table.
You're off work now,
and the kids are asleep.
If you're a painter, shouldn't
you be using this time to paint?
Well. A painting isn't something
you can just poke at when
you get a spare moment.
And besides, doesn't this
make your life easier?
Having dinner already done?
Have you read
Akootahgawa's "Hell Screen"?
In it a painter had to depict
his daughter being burned alive.
[MANAMI'S DAD] That's an awful
thing to have to do.
Both as a painter and a father.
How would that make you feel?
If I did that,
you'd hate me for it.
I would be angry, of course.
But still.
If you're going
to be a true artist,
something like that
shouldn't stop you.
Even if it's
in your spare moments,
and even if it makes your
daughter angry with you.
Paint fearlessly or
choose a different path.
You have to make a choice.
Be an artist.
Or be a good father.
Why does it have to be
either one or the other?
I don't think it's impossible
to be both those things.
Maybe it isn't, but
do you have the talent
necessary to be both?
I'm trying.
Right now, you're doing
two things halfway.
You're a part-time painter
and a part-time contractor,
so really, you're neither,
but what you are...
...is a lousy father
hoping to earn compensation
for your youngest daughter.
[CHIHO]
Hey. Sis.
Hey, Chi. Are you awake?
Hug! Hug!
Well. Anybody hungry?
Dad made dinner for us tonight.
[CHIS]
Yeah!
[HIMENO snores]
[NEWSCASTER]
Now for our next story,
The results of America's
presidential election are in...
She must have been tired.
If she were still Shino's age,
I wouldn't hesitate
to call this adorable.
Well, she really
is just a big child, huh?
Why does she
only snuggle up with you
like that and not me?
Because you're
just a big child, too.
[SOUTA groans]
C'mon, trade spots with me.
[RINO] You'll have to
ask Himeno about that.
[SOUTA]
Aw.
[BOY A]
Later!
--[BOY B] Bye!
--[BOY C] See you tomorrow!
[MOTHER A]
Excuse me!
[MOTHER A] I want to thank you
for all you've done for my boy.
No, really, it's nothing.
If you say that,
you don't realize just how
good a teacher you are.
I mean it.
He's never stuck with any
of his other lessons before.
This is the only class where
he's never missed a session.
Thanks.
[MOTHER A] Well, anyway,
we'll see you next time.
[BOY D]
Bye! Have a good night.
Man...
That's what makes deciding
on my future so hard.
Fascinating. There is
still so much to learn.