[JANE] What do we do now?
It's not like we
can go any higher.
Do you at least have a plan?
[ROCK] I'm thinking about it.
[JANE] Just great.
[ROCK] Ow!
[SHEN HUA] This where
real fight begin!
[REVY] She's headed your way!
--You get her?
--I dunno.
--Watch yourself.
--[EDA] Yeah.
[SHEN HUA] Got you good!
Yes, I did!
[EDA grunting]
[SHEN HUA] Oh, I thinking
for sure I take your head off.
But from sound of voice, look
like I catch nun instead, yes.
Okay, Sawyer!
Damn it!
Shit!
Revy, the knife-wielder's
just a diversion.
She's the one to watch.
Go after her.
Good point.
Besides, helping you
isn't gonna earn
me a damn penny.
--See ya.
--[EDA] Shit.
--[REVY] Don't die.
--[EDA] Yeah.
Feint operation a success,
miss hostage nun.
Hey, you listen up, okay, slut?!
You throw away your gun
and you come out now!
I think you going to Hell
if you let nun die here!
Not good thing!
Revy! Don't worry about me!
I'll be fine! Just shoot her!
Hm. You good actor, nun.
But we both know
slut not inside.
--Now...
--Hey, hey, hey! Slow down!
Don't you wanna hear
what I have to say first?
Seriously, it could
make you a lot of money.
[SHEN HUA] So sorry,
I not stupid.
I not letting you buy more time.
You can't kill me.
Like you said, you'll go
to Hell for killing a nun.
[SHEN HUA] Oh, but I atheist.
Your religion have
nothing to do with me.
--Time to say goodbye, nun!
--[EDA] Dumb bitch.
You're going to Hell a little
earlier than expected.
Take a look!
[smashing sounds]
[JANE] She's here! Oh my god,
she's gonna kill us!
Quick, do something!
Wait! Just wait.
This is no time to panic.
"No time to panic"?!
What, are you blind?
Look, if you've got any
better ideas, I'm all ears.
But hoping she'll just
fall through? That's stupid!
[ROCK] It is not stupid!
The roof from where she is
to where we are is rotten.
All it'll take
is one little step.
Now I've... got... you.
[DUTCH] We're almost in port.
Should see them any minute.
Alright. See anything yet?
[DUTCH] All I can see right now
is the Buddha and
the city lights.
Hold on a sec... Is that...?!
Aw, shit! That's
just fuckin' perfect!
What's wrong, Dutch?
They finally drop
an A-bomb on Roanapur?
I wish. That'd be a whole
lot better than this.
If that were it,
at least I wouldn't be
the only one getting
fucked. Look at this shit!
Some goddamn idiot's started
a bonfire on my dock!
Motherfucker!
[groaning]
It hurts, goddamn it!
Eda, you stupid cow! Why the
hell'd you tip her off?!
[EDA] My bad.
[REVY] I'm skewered,
for fuck's sake!
--[EDA] Sorry.
--[REVY] Useless whore.
[EDA] If I hadn't
distracted her,
I wouldn't have been
able to shoot her.
But forget that.
What's happening upstairs?
[REVY] The ladder's no good.
That spooky chick cut it
down with her chainsaw.
Fuck, this hurts!
What in god's name
is goin' on here?!
No one asked you to turn
this place into Burning Man!
I mean, Jesus! Y'all had
one simple job to do!
All you had to do was
catch one little girl!
Those folks are
all up on the roof.
Huh?
But the fire's so darn fierce,
I can't get up there.
[ROCK] That's it.
Come on. Right this way.
Come here and get us.
[JANE] Is it just me, or is
she in a really good mood?
Usually, I just dismember...
and the job's over.
That's why... jobs like this
are nice... once in a while.
I won't...
--...kill you... today.
--[JANE] Do something!
She's started babbling now!
This can't be a good sign!
But if you don't mind, I might
help myself... to a couple...
...of your hands and feet.
I'm just a cleaner.
Always cleaning up
after other people.
But today... is different.
Today, I'm climbing
up the ladder...
...to a whole new position.
I think we better get started.
This is your cue.
To do what?
[SAWYER] You'll be fine.
I had my throat slit,
but I lived through it
and just look at me now.
[explosion]
What was that?!
Damn! The fire must've reached
the high-octane gasoline!
[JANE] Oh, god!
She's still smiling!
It's over! Now she's gonna
start talking all creepy again
and then she's gonna cut me
up into little pieces!
You have to do something!
[ROCK] What do you suggest?
Now what?
I dunno.
[JANE] What's going on?
Explain this!
How should I know?! I don't
know what's going on either!
[JANE] Oh, no!
Rock, are you alright?
Where's spooky chick?
Ah... Well, she's... here.
Someone wanna
explain this to me?
What the hell did you do?
Uh, nothing I can think of.
It was weird. She got
like this all of a sudden...
...after dropping
her voice machine.
[EDA] One of those, huh? She's
probably got emotional issues.
I've run into these types
before. Very unpredictable.
[ROCK] What do we do with her?
[REVY] Hey, Spooky.
This is what happens when you
try to be something you're not.
Revy, you're bleeding.
Oh, this thing? It's not
as deep as it looks.
Hey! Did you guys see that?!
I'm pretty sure this
building's about to collapse.
[REVY] Huh?
The dock's breaking
up in the fire!
Can you see Revy and the others?
I can't see much.
But once we make our move,
Revy's gonna fall right
into sync with us. No worries.
Benny! Keep it full throttle
and pull a 180 at the pier!
[BENNY] Alright! I'm pretty
sure I can handle that.
[rumbling]
Oh, no!
Help me!
[LOTTON] I am here
to take your life!
And who, you ask, is the specter
that stands before you?
My name is Wizard!
Lotton the Wizard!
And while I have no
grudge against you...
Damn. The whole
thing's destroyed.
[coughing]
[REVY] Damn it.
--The boat!
--[EDA] 'Bout fucking time.
[REVY] Good. They're
headed straight for us.
Get to the pier!
There they are!
After 'em! Move it!
Stop!
--Touchdown, Dutch!
--Hit it now, Benny!
--[BENNY] You got it!
--[RUSSELL] Get back here!
Damn it! A few of these pricks
made it on to my boat!
[REVY] Rock!
Get the girl inside!
Over here! Hurry up!
[SHEN HUA] Oh, you alive, too.
[coughing]
You very lucky, yes.
Were you watching?
[SHEN HUA] Yeah. Well, mostly.
How'd I look?
I think you look very
much like king of idiots.
In future, I suggest you stop
making big entrance like that.
[LOTTON] Are you alright?
Do I look like I in shape
to do Lion Dance?
Well, for next time, you should
wear a bulletproof vest.
It's reassuring to have,
just in case.
Only real weapon
is one of offense.
Either way, there won't be next
time. Not with wound I have.
[LOTTON] I'll take you to
a doctor. Give me your hand.
I can't allow you
to die here alone.
Please come with me.
[SHEN HUA] You not... cut out
for killing in city like this.
I-I think maybe you make
perfect host at bordello, yes.
[LOTTON] Thank you, but I think
I'm much too clumsy for that.
If she's alive...
...we should take her, as well.
[SHEN HUA] She lucky, too.
Lobos! Get your ass in here,
you piece of shit!
[LOBOS] Yeah, Boss?
What's taking
Russell so long?!
I tried to tell you, things are
not gonna be that easy for him.
Fuck that!
I'll be eatin' the shit
sandwich when I hafta go home
and explain this
to Don Gerolamo!
I understand how you feel, but--
Shut up! If you're
looking to die
or you're just plain stupid,
keep talking.
Otherwise, call home
and get us some soldiers!
But that... That's just
crazy. You're gonna end up
starting a war with the
Russians and the Chinese.
I don't give a fuckin' shit!
Now get me to a goddamn phone!
I'll make the call!
Of course. Be right back.
There's a hatch here.
I'm going down.
You guys take care of
their gunmen, alright?
You betcha.
Damn. I'm going back
to the controls.
We're shorthanded as it is!
I'll take 'em to the rodeo.
Even Tuff Hedeman would
be scared of this bull.
Well, it sounds like
fun to me, Dutch.
Let me know before
the show starts.
--Ow, my head...
--[ROCK] Are you alright?
Sorry for rushing you like that.
I wish you'd thought of that
before you pushed
me in head first.
[BENNY] So...
Dutch is back behind
the wheel again.
I take it this is our guest.
Welcome aboard the Lagoon.
Everyone here calls me Benny.
I'm Janet Bhai,
but call me Jane.
From what I hear,
we've got some uninvited guests
on board at the moment.
But you can relax in my room
until this all blows over.
We'll be lightening
our load soon.
Here you go. Oh, and please
don't touch any of the hardware
in this room, okay?
I'm serious. Not a thing.
[DUTCH] We're about to
start the rough stock.
--You ready?
--[REVY] Wait.
Eda. Hang on.
What's going on?
Alright, Dutch,
make this bull dance!
Having fun yet, Eda?!
[EDA] You could've warned me!
Die, you bitches!
I have a question--
is this how you guys
normally drive?
No, this isn't typical.
For a second, I thought
maybe you were hired
to kill me like this.
Fuck off! You think
this is exciting?!
Wait till I put one
between your eyes!
Pretty lame, Revy.
You outta bullets? Shit.
If I can take you out,
--I'll be a goddamn hero!
--[DUTCH] Revy. Try this.
[DUTCH] Well, did you
enjoy the bull ride?
[REVY] Loved it, Dutch.
You're kidding, right?
Never wanna do that again.
Revy?
[REVY] I'll take
the doughboy up here.
[DUTCH] Alright. But
we've got one more rat
that snuck into
the engine room.
Eda. That one's yours, alright.
Sure thing, partner.
[RUSSELL] What the hell
is this place?
Hey, Jane! Where are you?!
So, how long before we reach
the port we're headed to?
I'd say roughly eight hours.
Alright, that's good. That
should give me plenty of time.
Hey, Mr. Japanese, I need you to
go get my laptop out of my bag.
Huh? But I don't have your bag.
Don't have it? What do you mean?
Are you stupid or something?!
Why on earth didn't you
bring it with us?!
How is this my fault?!
If it was so important,
why didn't you
bring it yourself?!
You just don't get it, do you?!
What?!
Don't get rough,
okay, you two?
You'll damage the electronics.
I can't do anything
without my things!
If I don't have my laptop,
then I'm unable to access
the web and without...
Unless...
[RUSSELL] Jane!
Where are you?!
Come on out! Now!
Shit! Shit! Shit! There's
no way through the front door.
Well, fuck you!
I'll show you who's boss,
stupid engine!
When this is all over, I'm
gonna drink till I go blind!
Then I'm gonna run
all over Rawhide
and fuck expensive women
till my balls hurt!
[EDA] Wow, that sure does
sound like fun, cowboy.
You must be one of
those real Texan studs.
But before you do all that,
maybe you should give God a call
and ask him what it's like
to fuck expensive women
when your balls have been
blown to high Heaven.
Dutch. He's covering my field
of vision with his fire.
Ain't that a bitch.
I need another bull ride.
Think you can do it?
I've gotta admit, this guy's
pretty quick for a lard-ass.
I'll signal you once
I've lured him to his grave.
Sure. That's easily
done on my end,
but are you gonna survive it?
That all depends on
your timing, Dutch.
Alright!
Don't push me, you damned nun!
I'm sick and tired of
dealing with you people!
Well, tough shit,
you inbred son of a bitch.
If you don't like us, then
get the hell off this boat!
--No can do, Sister!
--[EDA] Shut up!
[BOTH] Those plates are
mine, shithead!
You don't actually have them?
The plates are lost
on the ocean of the web.
The work had already
been completed,
so all that was left to do was
collect the engineering data
from our team members around
the world and create them.
But now that our data admin is
dead, I can't access any of it.
The encryption is automatically
changed every day. I give up.
We've already been paid, so it
doesn't change anything for us,
--but...
--Yeah.
The problem's Eda.
As soon as she finds out
that you don't have the
plates, she'll find a way
to crucify you that would
impress Jesus Christ himself.
You're kidding, right?
Well, unfortunately,
Roanapur is the kind of place
where violent jokes
tend to come true.
Then can I use your
computer just for a while?!
No can do.
Why not?!
You are so selfish!
Sorry, but the answer's no.
The fact is my machines
are very sensitive
and they don't like
anyone using them but me.
Although, if I were
the one using it,
that'd be a completely
different story.
To be honest, I'm curious
to see what kind of tricks
your operator had up his sleeve.
Don't disappoint me. 'Cause if
this turns out to be something
that a junior high student
could've come up with, then...
...I'll hafta charge you
for wasting my time.
Shucks. I sure do
get a kick outta
playing chase with a young
lady like yourself,
but these old legs can't
keep this up much longer.
Why don't you give up?
I promise I'll just
toast you lightly.
I'll make it quick.
My wife didn't even take
five minutes to cook.
I'll be happy as I can be
once I get a whiff of your
skin starting to char.
And would you just look at this
weather we've been getting.
It's the perfect day
for a barbecue.
[REVY] Dutch! Now!
You're a rocket man, baby!
I knew it. You guys really are
trying to kill me, aren't you?
No, this isn't typical.
Yeah, sure. Well, at least
let me see the data
before I die, okay?
Well, it's not an IFSR
or an exchange code.
If I had to guess,
I'd say it's a GOST type.
We could always cause
a buffer overflow
and take control quickly. But
using force isn't very elegant.
I don't give a shit
about elegance!
You can't rush this. You see,
I'm running six keys against
the GOST simultaneously.
If one of these
breaks the cipher,
we'll know in a few
minutes and all that data
will start downloading.
Simple as that.
[EDA] From the sounds of it, my
partner just took care of fatty.
Now you're the only
one left, cowboy.
If you try to resist,
I'll blow your head off
and toss your corpse
in the ocean.
[RUSSELL] Okay, okay.
Well, I'll be damned. How am I
gonna explain this to the boss?
I don't think you'll
hafta worry about that.
Lobos will take care of him.
He understands how things
work here in Roanapur.
[RUSSELL] We talking
about the same guy?
The Lobos I know,
he don't stand a chance.
It'll be a cold day
in Hell when...
[EDA] What?
Hold up. I've seen you
somewhere before...
Florida? No, no...
Oh, yeah, it was in Dirty City.
Washington D.C., I'm sure of it!
Oh, yeah? Well I've never
seen you before in my life.
I was born in Alabama.
I've never even been to D.C.
Fine. Then I saw a woman
who looked exactly like you.
I didn't recognize you before
on account of them
glasses and that outfit.
Now when was that?
It had to be when Don Gerolamo
was in D.C., so...
It was him. That man!
[EDA] Hey. You better
stop there, cowboy.
You got the wrong
person, alright.
That's it! It's all
coming back to me now.
It was that damn senator,
Jack Bonham!
[BENNY] Tally ho!
It was a GOST code!
Your operator was skilled,
but in the end, he couldn't
match my Kung Fu.
I'm as great as Kevin Mitnick
and Kevin Poulsen combined!
What a rush! I feel amazing!
There you go. I got in,
so what's my reward?
I must get...
You're so cute.
And watching you break code
really turns me on.
[EDA] So, that woman... She was
wearing a navy blue suit, right?
She was having a dinner
meeting with the senator
and several other major
players in Washington...
...at a French restaurant
called the Fontainebleau.
[RUSSELL] That's right!
The Fontainebleau!
But wait... What were you
doing with a senator?
[EDA] At the time, she and
her superiors were there
to discuss NAFTA.
In particular,
there were concerns on the hill
over a number of member states
within the OAS who opposed
the signing of the agreement.
She was there to discuss
how best to deal with them.
--[RUSSELL] You wouldn't be...
--I'm afraid you're mistaken.
It's not me.
I'm just a goddamned nun
from the Ripoff Church.
But I'll tell you one thing,
and this is God's own truth--
I wasn't born in Alabama.
My hometown is actually
Langley... Virginia.
You're CIA!
[gunshot]
[REVY] Hey, sure took
you long enough.
[EDA] Yeah.
So, did you send
that cowboy to Hell?
We're almost in port.
Let's just take it easy.
[EDA] Why not?
God's still up in Heaven
and all is well with the world.
[ROCK] Uh, I won't be
gone too long, okay.
[REVY] After that,
I'm leaving... partner.