[YUKIO] Ginji.
I see that I've woken you, Miss.
Please excuse my carelessness.
The future that you
envision for us...
...to leave this
dirty country behind
and raise the flag of
justice on foreign soil.
To rebuild the family there and
take on the city of villains...
I just can't stop
thinking about it.
But we've learned
from experience
what those Russians
are capable of.
We know they won't
make it easy for us.
I'm going to cut a path
through those soldiers
and challenge this
Balalaika one-on-one.
I've faced many who were not,
but she is undoubtedly
worthy of this white sheath.
I do appreciate your loyalty
and I've come
this far with you.
So, I'll... be with
you from now on.
Does that include... Roanapur?
[YUKIO] Yes.
[BALALAIKA] Excellent work.
Thanks to you,
it looks like this job
will end without incident.
As for me, my work
here is done.
Someone from Moscow
will be taking over now.
So, this is it.
If I have any regrets,
it's that I won't get
to see the aftermath.
It really is a shame.
Hey, Ishiguro.
The three that went inside...
Huh? What about them?
Whaddaya mean
"What about them"?!
The two Caucasians and the
Japanese that came here...
Have you investigated
them yet?
Yes, of course.
I've got someone
looking, but...
What about our request for
an international specialist?
Yeah. Some guy named Kouno's
supposed to be on his way here.
I can tell ya right now,
that woman's definitely
involved in this war
between Washimine and Kousa.
She might be
behind the shooting
at the bowling alley in Adachi.
So, whatever you do, don't
let 'em outta your sight.
Mhm.
[ROCK] What is it?
Nothing. It's just judging
by your expression,
it looks like you might
have something to say.
Well, am I wrong?
Miss Balalaika...
And please, tell me this isn't
what we talked about before.
Uh...
[BALALAIKA] Let me remind you,
I've already spared your
life once on this trip.
But all the same,
if you have another
favor to ask, speak now.
There is something...
Well, no promises.
Alright. I'd just
like to say one thing.
If all of this is about
to come to an end,
...before we go...
...I'd like you to destroy
the Washimine Clan.
To the point...
To the point where their
survival is impossible.
Cut them down until
not even a stump remains.
Only that will free her.
And nothing less.
I... see...
your... point.
I see. I see. Indeed.
That would be the only
way to force the princess
back into some
kind of normal life.
Or at least,
the quickest way.
Quite devious, Rock.
Excellent decision.
I'm starting to think there
may still be hope for you.
Please forgive my delay.
[ROCK translating to Japanese]
I'm certain that
by now, you must be
exhausted from all
these long discussions.
[speaking in Japanese]
Look, Mr. Kousa.
At this point, we
have to make plans
regarding who will
succeed us in the future.
[translating to Japanese]
[KOUSA] Hm?
[BALALAIKA] The fact is
if certain contingencies
should occur in our absence,
it will be difficult
for us to respond properly.
Therefore, I wish to know
your state of readiness
in terms of firearms.
[ROCK translating to Japanese]
Is it adequate?
[speaking in Japanese]
Would you oblige me?
[ROCK translating to Japanese]
[speaking in Japanese]
Oh, and I'd like to see
the bullets, as well.
[ROCK translating to Japanese]
Hm...
I see.
That's quite the competent
bodyguard you have.
Do you have a backup means
of protection, by any chance?
[ROCK translating to Japanese]
[speaking in Japanese]
What is this?
This gun is
absolutely atrocious!
Keep up with me here, Rock.
[translating to Japanese]
Huh?
[BALALAIKA chuckling]
Take a look at this, Sergeant.
Atrocious, isn't it?
Even the biggest pansy wouldn't
be caught dead with
a gun like this.
Absolutely atrocious.
What a hideous gun.
[translating to Japanese]
Have you ever
stopped to consider...
...what it would feel like
to be shot with a
pathetic gun like this?
That's it.
I'm afraid I cannot
work with anyone
who'd be willing to carry
a firearm this loathsome.
Frankly, it's embarrassing.
[gunshots]
What the hell?! Gun shots!
Let's go!
Get in there!
[gunshots]
This is the police!
Open the door!
Either you open
it, or we will!
This is your last warning!
Whaddya know...
This gun wasn't
so bad, after all.
How are we for time?
No problem there, Kapitän .
But, umm... how will we
explain this to the boss?
[BALALAIKA] As I recall,
Pyotr told me to make war
and burn it all to
ashes before we left.
I'm simply
following his orders.
Rock.
This is your gun.
Take it as a souvenir.
[ROCK] I don't like guns...
...and I never carry one.
But it was my desire...
...that you pull this trigger.
I'll never forget that.
[sighs]
Sergeant, throw that
gun away, as well.
We're returning to base.
[banging on door]
This is the police!
Stay right where you are!
This is Yasuzawa
of Department Four!
Detective Ishiguro.
I'm with Department One.
We heard gunshots.
I'd like to ask
you a few questions.
Come with us.
Are we okay?
We're right on time.
Rock, give this message
to the princess--
Hotel Moscow will cease all
attacks as of this moment
and I can personally
guarantee that.
The particular family
that you seek to destroy
has already dispersed
underground by her orders.
I think you underestimated her.
She works a lot more
shrewdly than you imagined.
According to information
Bulgaziviri gathered,
she has a little reunion
planned for the family.
The members are
under the impression
that their princess will
eventually invite them
to Roanapur to
raise their flag.
Of all places,
she chooses Roanapur.
[chuckling]
My ride is coming.
Alright now, clear the
way, civilian policemen!
[YASUZAWA] Hey!
I'm not done with you!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
The ambassador
is waiting for you
at the Mamiana, Miss Vlatirena.
Get back here!
Hold on, we can't.
It's an embassy plate.
[REVY] Rock!
Hey!
--[OFFICER 2] Stop there!
--[OFFICER 1] Get him!
[OFFICERS] Get back here!
Don't let him get away!
[BALALAIKA] Calm down!
We're the ones you want
to talk to, not them.
Don't get distracted
by small fry.
I guess this is goodbye,
civilian cop.
Oh, if you do need to
reach me for some reason,
please contact Mr. Walijinov,
First Secretary, Embassy
of the Russian Federation.
Don't be a stranger, okay?
'Scuse me.
Goddamn it!
I didn't make it in time!
Who are you?
Kouno with International
Investigations.
I don't get it. Why
didn't you arrest them?
I mean, you heard
gunshots, right?
It happened inside the
house. We had no proof.
So, who in the hell
was that woman, anyway?
Did you find out?
That one... She's a big fish.
She's part of Hotel Moscow,
the Russian Mafia
with strong footholds as far
as New York and Chechnya.
Balalaika.
That's the name
that woman goes by.
She's one of their
highest ranking officers.
What?!
Damn it!
Ugh.
Attention! Crime scene
to dispatch!
Send a message to all
patrol cars in the area!
Well, did someone
get a picture of her?
A description at least?
No.
Well, get a sketch
made up ASAP.
In the meantime, I'm gonna try
and track down her
Japanese contact!
Revy!
Before we leave, we hafta
tell her that the war's over!
[REVY] You outta your mind?!
In just over thirty minutes,
this whole place is
gonna be quarantined!
You're not gonna see her!
We don't have time.
Contact her from the ship.
Or they're gonna
leave without us!
But...
[crashing sound]
[YUKIO] Mr. Okajima.
Is that Yukio?
Please escort Ginji and
me to the Maria Zeleska.
Miss.
[REVY] Fuckin' unbelievable!
Now he's been kidnapped
by a high school girl!
Are you old enough to drive?
Well, why not, right?
Okay, and what's
this farce about you
moving the family to Roanapur?
You know what?
I may be standing in
the twilight like you say,
but at least I have perspective.
Doesn't it sound fun?
Hotel Moscow has announced
an end to the fighting.
It's over!
I've witnessed first hand
what Balalaika's
promises are worth.
Yukio...
That woman's like a rabid dog.
Trust her... and it's
only a matter of time
before she bites.
She betrayed us once,
so why not again?
[honking]
[gunshots]
Hey, asshole! I'm carjacking
you! Don't you get it?!
[YUKIO] If I could honestly
believe it was possible
to establish
ourselves in Roanapur
and rebuild the family there,
that'd be a wonderful feeling.
But it was just
a fleeting wish.
Anyway, as long as Ginji
and I are still here,
the Washimine Clan
and our emblem
will continue to exist.
We haven't been buried yet.
Why do you keep
coming back to that?
Like it or not, I was
born into the night.
I grew up with the night.
Sure, I enjoyed playing
on the other side
and even pretending
I belonged,
but the night
was always there.
So, now I've decided
to embrace reality.
I'm not a member
of Hotel Moscow,
so I'll be of no value
to you as a hostage.
Then we'll use you as a shield.
At the very least, I want
you to see how this ends.
I think it's appropriate
after all we've been through.
There's nothing but a
massacre waiting for you!
Yes, you may be
right about that.
But where we die, a flower
may bloom in our place.
As yakuza, we accept that.
Damn it!
Comrades, the operation
is complete.
Let us return to Roanapur.
[cheering]
[honking]
She's here...
Where ya goin?!
Well, Miss?
[YUKIO] Whatever happens,
we can't be the ones to
give way in this battle.
What the hell is
wrong with you?!
See, Rock? I was right
about her, wasn't I?
She's already
the walking dead.
Revy!
I understand the Kousa Clan
has been dissolved due
to an internal dispute.
However, the one who betrayed
and then mercilessly
slaughtered Tsugio Bando,
the head of the Washimine Clan,
still lives.
That person is Balalaika,
the leader of Hotel Moscow.
We have always prided ourselves
on living with honor,
seeing justice through,
and rewarding loyalty.
Bullshit! You're
bound by no such duty!
That's a front
and you know it!
[YUKIO] Please allow us
to pass unharmed.
Ginji...
[boat horn]
[REVY chuckling]
[ROCK] I'm afraid...
...that Ginji is
no longer with you.
You know,
I really shouldn't have
brought her here with me.
Why fight it? In the end,
you and I are the same.
No matter what we do,
we'll never be normal.
Where we are right now...
This is a place only
those like us should be.
Wouldn't you agree... lady?
There was a path
you could've chosen
to avoid ending up
like Miss Balalaika.
And I...
I always assumed that's
the one you would choose.
But I guess that's
where I was wrong.
Be honest with yourself.
This isn't about you
saving face as yakuza.
The truth is you wanted
to be part of the night
so you could be with him.
That's all this is.
Because I stand in the twilight,
I see things you can't.
You should've asked Ginji
to throw away his sword
and run away with him.
And become wanderers together,
seeking a far away land,
maybe open some shop...
That sounds like
a romantic comedy.
This is no comedy!
Where is the real you, anyway?!
[YUKIO] Sure,
I've often wondered,
"What if I'd been able
to live like that?"
But what's the point
of torturing myself?
I've already thrown my dice.
You know, secretly,
I always wished
that our life in Takamachi
would somehow go on forever.
With all the musicians
and the shops...
we always had so much
fun together there.
[gunshot]
Too late. Too damn late.
The only place people
like us end up...
...is a muddy hole in
the ground, my friend.
But you tried...
You did try to live.
Yukio...
[grunting]
[ROCK] Revy! Revy!
I'm alright. Damn.
I'm blacking out.
Those words that you
made her say back there...
In the end, that was the
bullet that killed him.
If it weren't for that,
I'd be on the ground.
Don't talk! This is
gonna hurt. Ready?
[REVY screaming]
Lift your leg up, Revy!
I've gotta stop the bleeding!
[YUKIO] Why?
Why did it have to
come to this, Ginji?
Everything became distorted
when you lied to yourself
that you wanted this.
But you were too
smart to believe it.
So, there was
no escape for you.
Eleven...
[ROCK] Huh?
That's the number of people
who've been killed
under my orders
since that night
I threw the dice.
Believe me... our
city's full of people
with blood on their hands!
Now that I've woken up,
I've realized...
...your city doesn't
have a place for me.
I apologize for
having troubled you.
I think it's best if I bring
all of this to an end now.
Don't look at her,
Rock! Look at me!
[slicing sound]
[boat horn]
[DUTCH] That you, Rock?
I feel like I haven't seen
you in a million years.
How'd you like the
fake Chinese-Canadian
passport I got you?
Heh. They love Canadians.
[ROCK] Dutch, I--
[DUTCH] Yeah, I've heard.
[ROCK] "People are like dice...
We can throw ourselves
in any direction."
Do you know the name of
the person who said that?
Wasn't it Jean-Paul Sartre?
The French existentialist
philosopher.
But I've got a
quote for ya, Rock.
It goes like this--
"Quickly put a hole
in a guy who tries
to put five eggs
into three baskets."
Now that speaks to me.
[ROCK] Yeah, I hear you.
[DUTCH] There's work
as soon as you get back.
The client wants us to
deliver a shitload of guns
by the day after tomorrow.
[ROCK] Later.
[REVY] We've got a plane
to catch, partner.
[BENNY] This came for you
from Miss Balalaika.
The good city
of Roanapur, huh...
Where the power of guns
meets the power of liquor.
You gotta
appreciate a place
where any problem can
be solved with brute force.
It's not such a bad place.
That's what I'm
beginning to think.
[ROCK] Yeah, it's not bad.
I plan to watch everything
that goes on here.
I'll watch all of it from
right here in the twilight.
Alright. Let's
get going then.
Back to our
favorite shithole.
[EDA] And? How was Japan? Huh?
Well, we were there
working for Balalaika.
You know, new country,
same old bullshit.
What are you talking about?
I'm asking about Rock, bitch!
You two were away
together for a long time.
So, did you get some or what?
I don't wanna say.
[EDA] Huh?
[laughing]
When it comes to
you and men, huh?
You may as well be dead.
That's the thing...
We fuckers don't die so easy.
Bang.