[ELVIS] Your selfishness is
starting to become a problem,
young lady. We're as interested
in the quality of the product
as you are. However,
don't forget that everything
has a time limit to it.
Soccer, football, the stock
exchange. Hell, even fucking.
[JANE] You people
are so shortsighted.
We're not there.
We're simply not there yet.
I'm sorry, but there's no way I
can release these as they are.
[ELVIS] Look, nobody's
planning to pass these off
to the US Treasury
Department, alright.
In fact, I bet out of all of
us, you and your friend here
are the only ones who even
give a shit about any of that.
You've gone over budget by
two hundred thousand dollars.
But I guess that's the price
of perfection, right?
And this job was supposed to be
finished over two months ago.
Now personally, I have a
hard time believing this,
but some of my
"investors" think, well,
they think you might be
trying to screw us over.
As in, maybe you feel
none of us are smart enough
to figure it all out.
[JANE] Theo. Just keep working.
[ELVIS] I'm sure
you can understand
how upset that would make them.
But I wouldn't
worry, sweetheart.
Lucky for you, I don't believe
a word of what they're saying.
And you better hope I'm right.
'Cause if what they're saying
turns out to be true,
I'm gonna have to
cut you in places
where you do not
want to be cut.
I'm not the kind of man
who likes to raise his hand
against a woman...
Well, most of the time.
So, what am I supposed
to do in this situation?
[gunshot]
Shit. I'm the one who's
gonna hafta clean this up.
[JANE] What did you
do that for?! Now...
--[ELVIS] Shut the fuck up.
--[JANE] Now we can't...
[ELVIS] We don't
have time to indulge
this little hobby
of yours any longer.
And our pockets aren't so deep
that we can keep
wasting money on you.
When I come back
here in two days,
you better have good
news for me, sweetheart.
[seagulls]
Fuck, it's hot!
Oww!
Fuck me! How much did
I drink last night, anyway?
Usually, I'm a cheap
bitch when I'm drunk.
I never waste bullets
or buy the drinks, but...
...Jesus.
Aw, fuck!
Talk about a shitty
start to a shitty day.
[typing sounds]
So, how d'you like me now?
You're makin' this easy!
What?!
Fuck you. I gotta
go take a leak.
[chuckling]
[urine stream hitting water]
There.
No, I would never fix the
game or nothin' like that.
I was just... Huh?
[smashing sound]
[GANGSTER 1] Let me out! Hey!
[JANE] What is it
with this city?
Everyone looks so damn shady.
[bell tolling]
[EDA]
Alright, the Good Shepherd...
What's his weapon of choice?
[REVY] Huh?
[EDA] Psalm 23, verse four.
"Though I walk
through the valley
of the shadow of death..."
But what I wanna know is
what would you take with you?
You know, if you were him?
Oh. I'd say a
Jericho... 941 FBL.
[EDA] That's a pretty
limp-dick gun for Jesus.
You're the nun.
What's your fuckin' answer?
[EDA] Isn't it obvious?
This guy here.
[REVY] You're full of shit.
I mean, he was Jewish, right?
Of course he'd have
an Israeli-made gun.
[EDA] Goddamn heathen.
You're outta your league
when it comes to this shit.
[REVY] It's hot! If I knew
your AC was broken,
I wouldn't have come
here to begin with.
And the boat's way out
at the dock. Not my day.
[EDA] I know, you've
said it, like,
five fucking times already.
I swear, you're like
a broken jukebox.
So, what's up with you
and that handsome sailor
you got on board? It's been
almost a year now, hasn't it?
Believe me,
he's nothing special!
For one, he won't get rid
of that stupid shirt and tie
and every time we come
up against an enemy,
the guy gets kidnapped.
Oh, and did I mention the
guy's a total fuckin' stiff?!
Gimme a break! Save it for
someone who gives a shit!
It's a simple question, Revy.
Have you sampled
the goods or not?
Tch!
You're no fun at all. You better
not be holding out on me.
[REVY] Fuck, it's hot in here!
[knocking]
Hello?! Hello!
I'm being chased!
Please help me!
I think it's for you.
Sorry! We're closed! Go away!
[JANE] I can hear you!
Let me in!
Please! Open up!
C'mon! You have
to open this do--
[EDA] What the hell's
your problem?!
Don't you know what
Jesus said in Luke 11?
"Don't trouble me. The door
is locked." Got that? Bitch.
B-But this is a
church, isn't it?
So what? God's not in today.
He's on vacation
in Vegas, alright.
You have to help me!
I'm not from here and I
didn't know where else to go.
There's no one I can trust!
I was told that the church
might be able to help and...
What's wrong with you?! Aren't
you supposed to be a nun?!
[EDA] Why don't you come
back on Judgment Day?
You do that and God will...
Jane. Don't make
things difficult.
C'mon, time to go home,
sweetheart.
[LOBOS] Mister Elvis,
you must be careful.
How many times do
I have to tell you?
Things are different here.
Sister. I just need to have a
little talk with this girl here.
Eda!
[EDA] Alright!
You fuckin' bastards!
Any idiot who shows up
and starts shooting at us...
...had better damn well
be prepared to go to war!
Shoot them! Now!
--Take 'em out! Kill 'em!
--Stop it! Don't shoot!
Just stay where you are!
Fuck that! I said shoot!
[EDA] Damn it!
[REVY] These guys
are pissing me off!
Sis! I'm here to help you!
That's "Sister" to you, jackass!
Who is this kid?
--New guy?
--Yeah!
I'm Ricardo, the new apprentice!
The sis has told me
so much about you, Revy!
--Call me Rico!
--Rico!
I told you not to call me Sis!
Revy! Hey, can you hear me?!
It's Lobos!
You can put your guns away now.
This is all a misunderstanding!
Look, I'm sure if we were--
Do I look like a fuckin'
idiot to you, Lobos?!
Misunderstanding my ass!
Damn right, you little pissant!
If you think you can just
walk away unharmed after
putting bullets in this church,
you've got another
thing coming!
You hear me?!
Oh, dear god! They'll kill
us all! We're doomed!
[SISTER YOLANDA] My, my.
What do we have here?
What a mess. Eda!
I'm beginning to lose
patience with you.
What have I told you about
doing this in the chapel?
Huh? Oh, I can explain...
[SISTER YOLANDA]
We'll talk later.
However, first thing's first.
We'll deal with
these non-believers
the same way we did with
the people of Beit Shemesh.
Shit! Let's get outta here!
You too, Mister Elvis!
I'll be back, you
goddamned bitches!
I'll make minced meat
outta the both of ya!
[SISTER YOLANDA] Oh my.
And who will pay
for these repairs?
Not to mention the bullets. It's
just like throwing money away.
I won't stand for it.
Now then...
I'd say you've got a lot of
explaining to do, young lady.
[JANE] Those men are from
the Nouveau Laredo Cartel.
They're a branch of the Gerolamo
Familia based out of Florida.
I was hired by the cartel
to fabricate old bills
that are out of circulation.
My counterfeit bill design team
is scattered all over the world,
but thanks to the Internet,
that's never been a problem.
I'm the team's chief organizer.
The leader, if you will.
So, what did you screw up to
end up being chased by them?
[JANE] Nothing!
We didn't screw up!
The problem was that they
were ignorant Neanderthals.
They lacked patience.
To be clear,
the only reason I accepted
this job in the first place
is because I was told
I'd be able to make
perfect counterfeit money.
I'll be the first to admit I was
shocked by the Super Z bills.
The paper it produced
was absolutely perfect.
Especially the
composition percentage.
The ratio of cotton
to linen fiber
is controlled at
exactly 76.8 to 23.2.
And yes, there are
some people who say
that you can produce
product in a laser printer,
but that's unforgivably
amateur in my opinion.
Compared to that, these guys
seemed quite professional.
They had a Swiss-made
printing press
specifically for this job.
Ooh, I'd do anything to get
my hands on one of those,
but they're monitored
so closely,
it's next to impossible
to do it.
Incidentally, we usually print
ours on a Heidelberg MF521,
which isn't too bad,
but it has its limits
and it shows in the work.
Pretty pathetic,
don't you think?
Meanwhile, these guys
decide they want to start
counterfeiting and gather
this huge budget for it
just like that, even though
I would've been able
to do it for way
less, seriously.
But even that machine started
to cause a bottleneck
in the workflow. For example,
the pressure along the outside
of the Faceplate Number.
We were using an adjustment
method of applying rubber
in order to alter the ink
pressure in each section.
But frankly, in
the grand scheme,
this method isn't too clever.
Since it's just as easy to use
UV radiation to set the ink
after allowing it
to print naturally,
thereby eradicating the need
for complex pressure adjustment.
We've had no problems
so far with sections
that are strictly
green and black,
but with the method
I just explained,
you'd really have to perfect the
details of the Treasury Seal.
Otherwise, the mounted
section on the outside
comes out looking uneven.
--And then...
--[EDA] Hey, hey, hey!
--Question.
--Ah, yes?
Sorry to interrupt you
in full flow, but...
--[JANE] What is it?
--Does this story you're telling
have an end?
Do we at least get
a bathroom break
like they had in
Battle of the Bulge ?
[JANE] You're the ones who
asked why I'm in this mess.
What? Are you bored?
Eda. Her attitude
reminds me of someone...
She's just like that bitch from
my childhood welfare center.
Whatever. Anyway, the fact
is that this type of research
requires both money and time.
--And so...
--That's enough.
I think we've all got the idea.
So, you thought you'd
dazzle 'em with your bullshit
and then find a way to
screw them over somehow?
That's exactly what
those idiots said.
Fine then. Proof over theory.
[REVY] Pfft. You want
me to judge your work?
Please. I'm guessing this'll
take me about two seconds.
Look here. On this one, the
print is off by half an inch,
not to mention the Treasury
Seal is way too green.
On the other hand, thread detail
on this one's a lot finer.
--So, how was that?
--Wow.
So, from what you're saying,
you'd take that bill
in your left hand and enjoy
a day of shopping at Sears,
would ya? How
unfortunate for you,
'cause you'd be going
straight to prison.
Look carefully at the
Federal Reserve Seal
on the bill in your left hand.
--Hm?
I figured you wouldn't
pick up on it.
It's not unusual to see bleeding
and other inconsistencies
in print quality on
bills from the seventies.
But I think you'd
be hard-pressed
to find a Federal Reserve
with the letter M in its seal.
[SISTER YOLANDA]
You've managed to prove
that Miss Revy's eyes are about
as useful as a pair of marbles.
So, I'd be willing
to believe you.
But I think now
it's time for you
to get to the heart
of this little story.
We missed our deadline by
quite a significant margin.
But since I had an objective in
mind, I refused to compromise.
Then these thugs showed up
and they shot my operator, Theo,
who I'd brought with
me from Germany!
His job was to
manage all the data
sent to us by the other team
members. With him gone,
all of our efforts to this
point have been wasted.
They just didn't get it!
Anyway, I got fed up
dealing with their crap,
so I said goodbye to those
Neanderthals and now here I am.
That's everything.
So, it's all your fault.
Yeah. They had a deal and
she didn't keep up her end.
What?! Right! Why would
either of you understand?!
You're the kind of people
who spend their entire lives
fiddling around with their
guns or watching NYPD Blue !
So, I guess you'd
probably have a hard time
believing I watch
Oprah instead.
The result of the
extreme make-over,
right after the gunshot.
[SISTER YOLANDA] Young lady,
the Lord has guided you here.
And you're very fortunate. That
girl pointing her gun at you
happens to be an
escape specialist.
And her fee could
easily be covered
with those plates of yours.
[JANE] I'd hate to give you
anything that's incomplete.
But I'm pressed for time,
so I guess I can't really
afford to be picky.
Excluding my escape costs,
I'll sell it for thirty grand.
[SISTER YOLANDA]
Well, you're on your own.
Go make your request
to some other god.
What?! I don't get it!
Aren't you people servants
of God or something?!
[EDA] In Luke 16,
he says, "I tell you,
make friends for yourselves
with worldly wealth."
It's not worth it, Eda.
You can go and die
if that's what you want.
[JANE] Fine,
if that's how it is,
I don't need your
help, anyway.
But I do thank you for saving
me from a difficult situation.
Well, goodbye.
Hey. Before you go--
where're you planning
to stay tonight?
[JANE] I'll manage.
[EDA] Word to the wise--you go
to any of the usual motels
and you can pretty
much guarantee
you'll end up in the
morgue tomorrow morning.
Now if you'd like
to avoid all that,
there's this shithole
called the Ramsap Inn
just on the other side
of Chalquam Market.
Tell them Eda from
the church sent you
and they'll give you a
room, no questions asked.
Why tell me this?
Hey, I didn't say
it was free advice.
Leave a three hundred
dollar donation
in the offering tray
on the way out.
I see. So, this is
a church, after all.
I can agree to that.
What was that?
You let her off too easy.
[EDA] Hm? Whaddya mean?
[SISTER YOLANDA]
Very well done, Eda.
That tree will
bear golden fruit,
so don't lose sight of her.
[EDA] Yes, Sister.
These naïve foreigners
are so easy to manipulate.
[phone ringing]
--Hey!
--Hi, Leroy! Long time no see!
You know that girl that Lobos
and the guys are chasing after?
--Yeah, the East Indian girl.
--[REVY] You bitch!
[EDA] Say I knew
where she was...
What would that info
be worth to you?
[REVY] You're playing dirty!
You actually know where she is?
Yes, Boss.
That bastard Lobos
is a goddamn coward.
I want you to go instead.
Yes, Boss.
Listen, Russell! These people
are no different from the Moro!
Th-They're goddamn savages,
all of 'em! Can you believe it?!
Even the nuns at that damn
church were shooting at us!
[groaning]
--Boss?
--Damn it all to hell.
I gotta get the fuck out of
this God's asshole of a city
and get back to civilized
Florida, you hear?
I've had enough of
this shit already!
[RUSSELL] Yes, Boss.
Russell, you capture that
Indian girl and bring her to me
no matter what it
takes, you got it?
When I see that bitch,
I'm gonna give her a beating
that'll make Dachau
seem like paradise.
[RUSSELL] Yes, Boss.
After all, I came here
all the way from Florida
just in case something
like this happened.
Hell, in three days,
you'll be sippin' margaritas
and watching the Caribbean
sunset with Don Gerolamo, Boss.
You just leave it to me
'cause I'm your trouble buster,
"Groovy Guy" Russell.
--[REVY] Hm!
--[EDA] What's wrong?
You got a splinter or something?
Don't play dumb.
If you're making money
off a trick like that,
you're giving me half.
It's like I said--you
gotta be patient, Revy.
With stuff like this...
...you cook before you eat.
[REVY] "Cook before you eat"?
What's that supposed to mean?
[EDA] It's like the slot
machines at a casino.
It won't pay out right away,
but if you wait till
the right moment,
coins come pouring out.
What are you planning?
Alright. We're here,
just follow me.
[REVY] You've got that
look right now, Eda.
You might as well fess up.
What'd you do?
Come on. Don't forget I work
for the original trickster.
A man who made water into wine
and walked on
the Sea of Galilee.
A trick like this is
nothing compared to that.
Anyway, Rock's bringing
the car around, isn't he?
Let's go.
First, you tell me
where we're going!
--I dunno.
--Hey, Eda!
I'm talking to you, bitch!
--Sister.
--[REVY] Hold it!
--Hey, Eda!
--Damn.
Listen up! Who are the
guys Lobos called here?
[QUENTIN] Everyone you see
sitting at these tables.
Alright then, I'll be giving you
your orders from here on out.
A thousand bucks a person.
She's staying at a motel
called the Ramsap Inn.
Your job is to bring
her back alive.
By alive, I mean
not dead, got it?
If she makes trouble for you,
you're free to rough
her up a little.
Goddamn, it's a job so easy,
even a child could do it.
We not need extra jab
from you, stupid cowboy man.
If I not have free time, I don't
accept cheap job like this!
[RUSSELL] You...
Shen Hua's right
about that, jackass!
Shouldn't you be fuckin'
cows back on the range?
Damn you!
[HUNTER 1] You're
pretty fuckin' bossy
for a guy who just
stepped off the plane!
[HUNTER 2] I don't
like his style!
Shut up and listen to what
I hafta say, you bastards!
[speaking through device]
If you want us to listen,
you could start
by introducing us
to the new faces
sitting over there.
Hold on. Who are you?
[HUNTER 3] Yeah, I've
never seen her before.
[HUNTER 4] Anyone know where
she's been getting her work?
What are you talking
about, Shen Hua?
You hired me for a job just last
Tuesday. Don't you remember?
Huh? I hire you?
Hi! I so late.
You waiting long?
So sorry about that.
Are you ready?
Oh, you want know
how to cut him up?
Boss Chang say he want
to make example outta him.
You understand?
But he never tell me so far
if he want meat chop or minced.
I guess you decide.
[MAN WITH GAG groaning]
Well, I'm finish.
He all yours now.
You can take care
of things from here.
[HUNTERS reacting in background]
You Sawyer the Cleaner?!
[HUNTER 5] Oh, so that's
what you look like.
[HUNTER 6] You're always
wearing them goggles
--and the face mask.
--Okay, people.
Let's hurry up and get to work.
Whaddya say? How 'bout it?
Those are the new
faces over there.
[SHEN HUA] Oh, you're right.
I not seen them before.
[QUENTIN] Hey, you two,
what are your names?
Hi there. I'm Claude
"Torch" Weaver.
Lotton... "The Wizard."
[QUENTIN] Well, I hope you
won't cast a spell on me
for saying this, but is
that milk you're drinking?
[LOTTON] I'm allergic to
alcohol. It makes me vomit.
It's against my
religion to drink.
Well, that's pretty pansy-assed.
So, what kind of weapon you
two use for hunting then?
[LOTTON] This.
[QUENTIN] What about you?
Don't tell me your religion
won't let you carry a gun.
[crowd reacting]
You idiot! Are you trying
to burn down the bar?!
Cut this out already!
That was very big surprise,
but now at least we know
what we using, right?
Everyone is okay
with that, yes?!
[HUNTER 7] Let's get this
over with and grab a drink.
[HUNTER 8] Hey, is Ramsap
Inn far from here?
[HUNTER 9] Can I get
a ride with someone?
Looks like you're
picking up the tab.
[RUSSELL] Damn it!
[SHEN HUA] Cowboy man,
why you stand still?
We leaving now, yes?
[EDA] Okay. Right here
should be good.
Pull over and kill the engine.
Alright, good work, driver.
And what's so special
about this spot?
What the hell are we doing here?
If you just shut up and wait,
then something very convenient
is going to happen for us.
You know, you have a way of
making things sound immoral.
[distant sirens]
[QUENTIN] Alright then, guys!
Let's get going, shall we?
Let's get this useless,
cheap-ass job over with!