Well, are we out of
their missile range?
I think so.
We're safe if we
maintain this distance.
Assholes. We'll have to keep
an eye on them from here.
[explosion]
[REVY] Let's move.
What the hell are you
doing over there?
Hey, you alright?
You didn't warn me
about an explosion.
What if you accidentally
flooded the place?
You shouldn't be so reckless.
Listen, we can't afford to
be screwing around right now.
The more you whine,
the less time we have.
I understand all that,
but you could have said
something ahead of time.
[REVY] And how did you expect
me to talk underwater?
Why don't you try paying closer
attention to what I'm doing?
But still, at least give me a
signal when you do something...
Bones? Bones!
Well, yeah, there
are gonna be bones.
Look around you.
They're all over the place.
Listen, Rock,
this is a gravesite
that all of us living on
the surface have forgotten.
This is where death
came for all of them.
It was their time,
whether they wanted it or not.
No flowers or candles here.
No one comes to visit
and no one remembers.
A rotting catacomb...
minus all the fucking saints.
I've never liked
these kinds of places.
Not at all.
Smells like something's been
rotting down here for ages.
If we stay too long,
it'll mess with our lungs.
Hey, Revy.
How do you think they felt...
...when they realized
they were stuck here?
What went through their minds
as the lights faded
and it got dark
and all they could do
was struggle to breathe?
[REVY] Now that's
just depressing.
Anyway, how the hell
should I know?
Dying 'cause you can't breathe
can only feel like dying cause
you can't breathe and that's it.
How other people die
is just how other people die.
What does it matter?
Thinking about it isn't
gonna do a damn thing, Rock.
Just try to think
happy thoughts.
Hey, look at these guys.
Seems like they staged
their own version
of Gunfight at the O.K. Corral.
[gunshot]
Captain?
Captain!
You bastard!
[CREWMAN 2] How dare you!
Revy. This must be
the captain here.
[REVY] That Ahbe guy, right?
Is his Iron Cross lying
around here somewhere?
It'll be worth something.
Hmm... Come over here.
This guy's uniform is
different. He's that SS.
And the painting?
I don't know where it is.
If it's not here,
it's in a safe.
I don't get it.
Why'd these guys bother
getting into a major shootout?
Desperation made them panic?
[REVY] Now that's
a laughable theory.
Despair is like the
last stages of cancer--
you've got nothing
left to lose.
Well, I don't know the details,
but I'd say this Gestapo
was the one that shot first.
After that, the sailors came in
here to avenge their captain.
And it all ended with
the Last Stand at the Alamo.
A ship's crew is like family.
They wouldn't kill each other if
they knew they were gonna die.
The only one who'd
bother starting shit
would be the outsider.
[ROCK] Is that how it works?
[REVY] Yeah.
What'd ya find?
Got the goods?
This is it. It's an exact match.
Yeah! This has to be it!
You start putting it away
and I'll take care of the rest.
The rest? But we got
what we came for.
[REVY] We're not kids
running some errand, Rock.
If we don't grab everything
that's worth something,
then this trip's been
a waste of time.
I noticed the captain had
an Iron Cross with a sword.
It's a valuable item.
And it's a little too valuable
to leave behind as fish food,
--alright?
--But you--
Hold on!
[REVY] I'll be back when I've
got everything worth taking.
You can keep those guys company.
What are you looking at?
Quit staring. I'm not exactly
thrilled about it, either.
[DUTCH] What's our
distance, Benny-boy?
The last time I checked,
it was about 5,200 yards.
That puts us out
of their range.
Those guys are a dangerous
bunch, alright. Fucking crazy.
[DUTCH] And the fact
that they just launched
three of those things at once
means they're well-equipped.
[BENNY] They're parked
directly above that U-boat.
[DUTCH] And we can't
do a damn thing.
Take your positions!
Stand by for the
commander's instructions!
[RACHMANN] Gentlemen!
My devoted brothers-in-arms.
Beloved braves of the
Aryan Socialist Union.
I stand here before you
filled with pride,
for today, we shall witness the
creation of a brave new world!
In one glorious stroke,
we will reclaim that
which was lost to us
as the result of meddling by the
Zionists and communists alike.
True patriots are counting
on you, brave soldiers!
This is the utmost
act of courage!
In the name of strict
order and patriotism,
you and you alone will be able
to restore the racial hierarchy
for the way it was meant to be!
Suicide corps--stand on guard!
Kruppen Feller!
You have been chosen
to fulfill this objective.
A true hero. You represent the
courage of the great Aryan race.
There has never...
There has never been a more
glorious moment than this
and I for one... I cannot
find words to express this.
I can only shed
these tears of joy.
I too am filled
with emotion, Commander.
I will sacrifice myself
to fulfill this sacred duty!
[STANDFORD] Commence
singing of our anthem!
[music]
♪ We shall raise our
flags to the skies ♪
♪ March the road ahead
filled with pride ♪
♪ For we know in our hearts
that the strike force ♪
♪ Will be victors
strong and true ♪
♪ We must strike down
those who oppose... ♪
[BENNY] Hey, hey, hey.
Get a load of this,
I think they're holding
a little concert.
Some Nazi marching song.
[DUTCH] Yeah, I hear 'em.
You start with some
random, useless guy,
put him on a podium,
give him some power,
and the next thing you know,
you've got a march-loving,
ego-tripping fool on your hands.
Same shit as always.
And you, what do you think
as a white man, Benny-boy?
That kinda machismo
doesn't agree with me.
Besides, don't
forget I'm Jewish.
"Fuck the Nazis"
is a family creed.
[DUTCH] That's right, I forgot.
By the way,
are the beacons on yet?
Nope. It looks like both of them
are still in the submarine.
Unfortunately, there's nothing
we can really do at this point
but sit around and pick at
each other's politics.
I'm not that concerned
about the job,
but I am worried
about the time.
[DUTCH] Yeah, that's always
gonna be a problem.
If we had the time
to retrieve it,
I'd take the whole thing
back to the port.
That way, I could've shown
that fancy dress parade
on that shit-heap boat what
their Führer went through.
Take a little bit of
the romance out of it.
I hear ya.
Hey, this isn't good.
Those guys are up to something.
Huh?
[BENNY] They're lowering
some kind of pod.
At this rate, there's gonna
be a showdown in the sub.
What now?
[DUTCH] There's nothing
we can do, Benny.
They still have TOWs.
Just having to say
this pisses me off,
but we'll have to wait
till they give us a chance.
So, for now, you'll have
to pray while you shit.
I'm afraid that's
about all we can do.
Phew! Not bad.
Aside from all those
Iron Crosses,
I found stuff the collectors
would drool over.
This place is a
grave robber's wet dream.
Revy.
I was thinking that maybe...
[REVY] Hmm?
...we should leave
all that here.
[REVY] Okay, Rock,
you can spare me the rest.
Wait, I know,
"Thou shalt not steal"?
So, should I be calling
you "Father Rock" now?
That's not it.
These medals are proof
of what these people did.
We don't have the right
to take that away from them.
If anyone has the right
to these medals, it's them.
It's these people right here.
Don't you think?
I found it right
next to his body.
The captain had this photo
with him up until the very end.
The man had a family
waiting for him.
To us, these medals
are just antiques.
But to the people
who were left behind,
they're irreplaceable.
[REVY] Hmm.
So, that's how
you look at it, huh?
I see. Well, since we're here...
I've got a story that's perfect
for this sorta atmosphere.
I'm gonna do you a favor
and let you in on a
little secret, Rock.
Okay?
Let me ask you something...
See this? And this?
What would you say
these two things are?
The first one's an old skull
and that's some sorta medal.
That's where you're wrong.
Both of these are just things.
As soon as you strip
away their meanings,
then that's all
they really are.
Just things and nothing more.
And if you're gonna give these
things any kinda meaning again,
they won't get
any of their value
because they're
someone's precious memory.
Their value will be determined
by the one thing
everybody agrees on....
...and that's money.
The rest of it is just a bunch
of sentimental bullshit.
Is money... your god?
It's power. Something a lot
more useful than God.
And Rock, if you think
about it, other than this,
what do we really
value in life?
God? Love? Don't make me laugh.
Back when I was just a brat,
crawling around
that shit-hole city,
it seemed like God and
love were always sold out
when I went looking.
Before I knew better,
I clung to God and prayed
to him every single night.
Yeah, I believed in God
right up until that night
the cops beat the hell
outta me for no reason at all.
All they saw when
they looked at me
was another little ghetto rat
with no power and no god.
What's left for a poor little
Chinese bitch to rely on?
It's money, of course.
And guns. Fuckin' eh.
With these two things,
the world's a great place.
I wish I hadn't
heard that. I'm sorry.
[REVY] Fuck you.
If I was looking for pity,
I would have told you
something a lot more colorful.
The moral of the story is
when you're living on the edge,
that's all that matters to you
'cause that's all
you've really got.
Not everyone can get off
on being normal, Rock.
And one more thing...
All those rich, fat bastards
living under palm trees
and bitches who think
that life's only about
putting on makeup...
I don't wanna hear you
speaking your mind
from the same perspective
as those hypocrites.
Nothing's worse than being
treated like some whore
by your companions.
I'll say this once--
the next time you decide you're
gonna tell me what's proper,
you'll no longer be one of us.
When that happens...
...I'm gonna kill you.
[ROCK] Right. I understand.
[explosion]
Revy, what was that?
Shh.
[ROCK] Revy!
Go somewhere where bullets
won't find you and keep quiet.
The only ones who'd be
knocking on that door
are either ghosts or crooks.
And since the ghosts
are already down here,
well, we must have
some troublemakers here.
But we left our gear
on the other side
and there's only one way there.
[footsteps]
If we can't get through,
there's no escape.
One.
Two.
And there's more.
Enough. You're not helping.
You've got a lot to learn,
you know that?
What you need to listen for
are the guns on their belts.
What now?
[REVY] "What now"?
Well, that's obvious.
We kill 'em all!
Rock, get our tanks!
Looks like we got company.
A couple of grave robbers.
John! To the other side!
Hey, Rock! Get down!
[ROCK] Damn it! The painting!
This is it! Brunhilda!
Alright, we've got it!
Cover me! I'm off!
They got the painting!
Yeah, they won't
get away so easy.
[KRUPPEN FELLER]
Disconnect the pod.
[STREIFFER] But Richert and the
others are still down there!
Forget them.
As far as I'm concerned,
they're dead. Hurry up!
Move your ass, Rock!
We need to get our gear!
The beacons are on.
--Where are they?
--Directly above the sub.
What the hell are they doing?
Can you tell me
where they're headed?
Their position isn't changing.
They're going straight up
towards the Nazi mother ship.
We have the painting,
I'm looking at it right now.
[RACHMANN] You've done well!
[men cheering]
However, we weren't alone.
Tell me she's not gonna do it.
Neither of 'em know
who they're up against.
She's probably planning to...
Damn it! We're talking
about fanatics
who launch anti-tank
missles without any warning.
Revy's current equipment
isn't gonna help her.
If she surfaces
without realizing...
...it's over for her.
[DUTCH] We'll stay put.
It's too soon.
[BENNY] But Dutch...
[DUTCH] You wanna
show some bravado,
charge in and all
go to hell together?
It may paint a great picture,
but it won't be much
of an ending, boy.
For now, you should just pray
that it's not
Revy's time to go yet.
The enemy is coming up.
The grave robber's
are coming up!
Stand by on the machine gun!
Fire!
[DUTCH] They started.
You think they're alright?
[DUTCH] If they're
still shooting,
it means they're not dead yet.
They've stopped.
[BENNY] Looks that way.
Yeah! We got those bastards!
You idiots.
It was your misfortune
to have touched our
glorious inheritance
with your unworthy hands.
Regret it at the
bottom of the sea.
Retrieve the pod.
We're leaving this area.
[BENNY] The beacons
are still active.
They're drifting southeast
away from the ship.
But I've got no way of knowing
if they're dead or alive.
Can you hear me up there, Dutch?
[DUTCH] Yeah. Their ship
is starting to move.
[BENNY] Shall we go
and pick up some bones?
[DUTCH] That's a bit
too much, Benny-boy.
I guess my nerves
aren't as tough as yours.
[DUTCH] Yeah, I know.
[ROCK] Revy, look.
There's our boat.
So, they got away
with the goods.
Who the hell are they, anyway?
Those bald cocksuckers!
They're neo-Nazis.
A sorry bunch of leftovers from
the Dark Ages, if you ask me.
But I don't know
where they're from.
To hell with this bullshit!
You're telling me
fucking skinheads
got one over on us?
[DUTCH] This is far
from over, Revy.
We took a job and
it's not done yet.
Let's do this, Dutch!
Let's turn that Nazi boat
into a floating morgue!
[DUTCH] Agreed.
Putting all politics aside,
it's not good for business
to leave it at this.
The only cure for these
idiots playing heroes
is some bitter medicine.
So, let's give it to 'em.
[REVY] Listen, Dutch,
I just can't.
I can't partner...
with that guy.