[ROCK]
Roanapur.
In this city, gangs from around
the world jostle for territory.
It's a strange and
deadly game they play.
[TV REPORTER] This is
an unmitigated tragedy.
Sources at the scene tell us
that not much remains
of the embassy.
What we know so far is
that 37 embassy employees
have been killed and
another 150 are wounded.
The DRC military is
currently continuing
with its rescue efforts.
Directly following the bombing,
a terrorist organization
calling themselves
the Protectors of
the Islamic Front
have claimed responsibility
for the bombing.
[ROCK]
This room is filthy.
Revy, are you gonna
sleep all day?
We have a job.
Dutch says it's an emergency.
Revy!
[REVY] Is that you, Rock?
Yeah, it's me. I guess
it's a last minute request.
His exact words were,
"Wake her the hell up."
So, I ran down from the office.
Goddamn it.
This job... Who's it from?
Mr. Chang.
Y'know, from the Triad.
[CHANG] I've been waiting
for quite a while now.
What do I have to do to get
a cup of coffee around here?
Honestly, Dutch, is this
what you call service?
[DUTCH] It's my mistake for not
knowing we were running a café.
You do know why I
own that torpedo boat,
don't you, Mr. Chang?
Dutch. Now that's just cold.
Our place just burned down
and we came straight here.
I'd say the very least you could
do is offer us a cup of coffee.
That's some bad luck, Mr. Chang.
I hear you lost
half the building.
[CHANG] Yeah. I gotta say,
they hit us hard.
Was it the Russians?
No, that's impossible.
We've always been very friendly
with Miss Balalaika
and company.
Hey. Glad you could join us.
Someone wanna fill me in?
Did I miss much?
[CHANG] No, we're just
getting started.
This briefcase is the
cause of everything.
But that just proves
how valuable it is.
I took this off an
incredibly stupid Bulgarian
who was trying to make a
quick buck in my territory.
Here's the thing--I don't
recall giving permission
to sell weapons to anyone,
other than good old Yolanda
from the Ripoff Church.
But for some reason,
this guy thought he'd
give it a try anyway.
He was casually selling
guns on the street
like he was running a
hotdog stand or something.
What's worse, he mistook
all of my warnings
for some kind of crazy joke.
Although, eventually he did
understand and made a deal...
...right around the
time we told him
we were gonna crush
his balls like nuts.
Unbelievable. I mean,
the guy was a real idiot,
but it turns out he had
a very interesting job.
Yeah?
[CHANG] He worked for
Bulgarian Intelligence.
This city is a
comfortable place
for folks like that
too, you know.
Normally, a guy like that would
be very useful to us, but...
You can only play
with fire for so long
before it gets out of control.
And what do you
suppose he offered us
in exchange for his balls?
Well, Dutch?
--Documents.
--Really?
[CHANG] The hiking routes of
a friendly little organization
we all know of.
I'm sure you've heard of them.
If I'm not mistaken,
the little job they
did before hitting us
has been on TV all morning.
The US Embassy!
Sounds dangerous to me.
[CHANG] Turns out that
ball boy's real job
was actually with them.
Apparently, the world's
full of people
who want Uncle Sam
to disappear.
They're just the
latest ones to try.
Anyway, I decided to get
in touch with one such group
and I told them that they'd
dropped something important.
But as soon as I quoted these
guys what it would cost them,
they told me to get
the hell out of there
before they burned
my ass alive.
Not very nice...
So, this is how I answered--
"Fine. Have it your way.
I'll go elsewhere then."
Thanks to that...
...my office was blasted
all the way to Jordan today.
And as predicted, my ass
did nearly become a roast
before I got here,
so it wasn't just talk.
These guys really don't
have a sense of humor.
So, Dutch. Here's the deal--
I want you to deliver this.
Five teams will leave
Roanapur at the same time,
but here's the thing--
each of them will have
a different destination.
There are five cases,
but only one jackpot.
So, it's a feint.
Yup. As insurance, of course.
Your destination is the military
base on Basilan Island.
You have two days.
After that, my company contacts
will have left Basilan.
[DUTCH] Chang, my man. Two days
does not give us enough time.
There's never enough time,
is there, Dutch?
Last night's embassy
bombing is just the first
in a series of events.
Two days from now, the next
schedule is set to begin.
Let's put it this way--when
they're done hiking this time,
there's gonna be
a new president.
Uncle Sam came to me
because their embassy
went up like the Challenger.
If they knew how
to deal with this,
we wouldn't be having
this conversation.
We'll provide you with a
getaway driver and a guard
once you get to the island.
I'm counting on you, Dutch.
[DUTCH] Did you bring
our pay here with you?
Expenses are on top
of that, as usual.
[CHANG] That's fine by me.
We'll do our usual...
[REVY] R! P! G!
[CHANG] Well, they don't
waste any time.
They're already here.
Dai-low! You alright?
Your information's leaked,
Mr. Chang.
We're gonna have
to cancel this one.
[CHANG] Are you gonna quit?
I'd hate to see you stuck
with the repair bill for this.
Anyhow, the least I can do
is escort you to your boat.
But first...
I have to admit,
it's been a while since
I've been in the field.
--Emergency exit?
--I'll show ya.
Follow me.
A little guided
tour, huh? Great.
--Shit!
--Don't panic, Two-Hands.
In this situation...
...if you hesitate, you lose.
Chang's cleared the way
for us. Now let's go!
Yeah, I'm on it.
Careful, boss man.
[CHANG] Don't get cocky,
Two-Hands.
No one can say you
don't have the skills,
but you fail to see
the bigger picture.
True. I can admit I'm
not at your level yet.
I just hope I'll
get there someday.
Now that's a good answer.
I'm sending a car.
It'll get you to the harbor.
[DUTCH] Fuckin' great.
One of these days, I'd like a
job where I don't get shot at.
[CHANG] Quit your
bitching, Dutch.
We're doing all the
dirty work here, anyway.
Hurry!
[DUTCH] I'll leave the
rest to you, Mr. Chang!
[BENNY] This is a
major pain in the ass.
When you get there, don't
forget the password, okay?
The password is...
[IBRAHA] Right, I understand.
Our comrades have spotted the
delivery boys on the main road.
We should be able to take care
of them near Ban Kantang.
[TAKENAKA] I wonder about
that. This job should've been
over with after the bombing
of the Triad office.
That would've taken
care of things.
I'm in no mood to judge
the failures of our comrades.
[TAKENAKA] You mocked
these people as being
nothing more than
simple gangsters,
but Chang turned out to
be a much smarter gangster
than you thought.
Isn't that right?
"Strategically, we should
despise all our enemies,
but tactically, we should
take them all seriously."
Those are the words
of Mao Tse-tung.
You could learn
from that, Ibraha.
Moral discourse from
a man with no god?
It's worthless.
He was right, though.
Besides, I don't
believe in God either.
Never have and never will.
You're still my
comrade, Takenaka.
Well, more importantly,
perhaps we should move faster
with the plan in America.
Don't be ridiculous.
The FBI has been watching us.
If we move now before the
feint, the plan will be wasted.
If I had to guess which of
the five routes they'll use,
I think it's safe to say that we
can rule out anything overland
and flying is far too visible.
That just leaves the sea route.
Do you have any proof?
Don't need proof
when you got intuition.
I'll ask one of our comrades in
the Philippines for assistance.
And as for the sea route,
I guess I'll hafta
take care of that.
This is the final step in
changing the world, Takenaka.
[TAKENAKA] Yeah.
♪ What shall we do
with a drunken sailor ♪
with a drunken sailor... ♪
♪ What shall we do
with a drunken sailor ♪
♪ Early... ♪
[REVY] Did you hear
the password he gave us?
"May the force be with you"?
That is so lame.
I mean, the guy
can handle a gun
and he has great style,
but Chang couldn't even
make a fuckin' retard laugh.
Well, if there's one
thing I've learned,
it's that nobody's
perfect at everything.
[TAKENAKA] You found them?
A torpedo boat? Ooh.
Chang's sure got some
interesting friends, doesn't he?
And you've determined
their heading, too?
That's just perfect.
It's exactly what we predicted.
Looks like I won't hafta
change flights, after all.
Yeah, that's correct. Uh-huh,
I'm on the next flight there.
Stick to the plan. Just don't
do anything until I arrive.
We need to confirm a few
things before we move.
See ya soon.
E-Excuse me.
Hm?
Can you please
lend me your lighter?
I'm guessing you're from Japan.
Thanks.
Yes. How did you know that?
It's obvious. It's the way
you held your hand.
I see.
We're going to Cebu Island this
year for the family vacation.
You must be a brave man
to be traveling that far
from Manila with a family.
Right.
Hmm. Do I...?
Could it be possible that
we've met each other before?
I have this strange feeling that
I must know you from somewhere.
[TAKENAKA] Yes, I'm sure you do.
You know, Mr. Ken. For as
long as I can remember,
people've been saying
I look like him.
I guess I should
probably get going.
I've never been
great at small talk.
Nice meeting you.
[TAKENAKA] Well,
aren't you a sly one.
If you think you've seen
me before, my friend,
it was probably at your
local police station.
[REVY] I got a visual, Dutch.
It's a noisy little fly.
[DUTCH] Okay.
Rock, bring me the Remington
and the Hydra API ammo
while you're at it.
Sure.
We've taken out
the enemy's eyes,
but they may not
be the only one.
Rock. Benny and I
will be the bait
and head straight
towards Basilan.
I want you and Revy
to get off at Zamboanga
and use the Zodiac
to rendezvous with us.
I got it.
[TAKENAKA] Ibraha!
I can't hear you!
Hurry and get down here!
[IBRAHA] Takenaka!
Where are you?
You're in Basilan?
Wait a second!
That's where our
diversion team is located!
[TAKENAKA] Don't panic. Yeah,
I'm at their camp right now.
It's always darkest at
the base of the lighthouse.
We're waiting here
for the local guerrillas
to strike the first blow, but
that also makes this the
ideal place for them to come.
It makes perfect sense
if you think about it.
The only place an
American imperialist
can come and go
freely around here
is the anti-guerrilla
special operations camp.
And it's right over the hill.
I can already see Chang's next
move. This is gonna be fun.
Takenaka, this isn't a game!
Our entire plan hinges on this!
All this is nothing more than
one big chess game, brother.
Hell, I challenge you to find
me anything in this world
that isn't. Either way,
we're the ones poised
to make the next move.
That one's as stubborn
as they come.
What's the point if you
can't have a little fun?
[REVY] So, once we
deliver the documents,
we'll meet you at the base.
Yeah. I'll come and get you when
I lose these guys tailing us.
What a pain in the ass.
Tell me about it.
What is it with these guys
who fight for a cause?
They just don't
know when to quit.
Oh, right. One more thing--
I have an additional message
for you from Mr. Chang.
Remember to tell Rock when
he gets back from the can.
[ROCK] Sorry to
keep you waiting.
[COMMANDO] The target
is traveling due north
towards Zamboanga.
[TAKENAKA] So, they've
passed Basilan, have they?
[COMMANDO] Basilan
is already behind us.
Looks like they'll be heading
north towards Negros.
We will continue our pursuit.
Alright. Good work.
It's not what it seems, boys.
My gut tells me they're
already on their way here.
Yup. They're coming to Basilan.
[seagulls]
Here we are in the fuckin'
capital of dullsville.
What time is it?
[ROCK] It's almost six. It was
more trouble than we expected
finding a place to come ashore.
I'm pretty sure the
village is this way.
It sure is quiet here.
[REVY] Yeah, it's a ghost town.
No one in sight.
They've had martial law
here for two years,
but it hasn't made
any difference.
The army and the guerrillas
are shooting at each
other day and night.
It's a real fuckin' circus.
The people here must've gotten
sick of dating their cousins
and moved to real cities.
Keep you waiting? You're
from Lagoon Company, right?
I heard that there were
four of you, or am I wrong?
And why the hell should
I answer that question?
[TAKENAKA] There's
no reason you should.
[REVY] It's just me, him,
and a briefcase. That's it.
By the way, I don't see
your partner anywhere.
Where's your guard?
That jackass.
He's running around right
now looking for a restroom.
Turns out he doesn't
know the difference
between beer and Volvic.
[REVY] Okay. Enough
with the bullshit.
May the force...
Now how did that one go again?
Hey, old man, this isn't
the time for jokes.
Make this quick, or I'll
hafta shoot you in the face.
Now, now. No need
to get so hot.
I was just trying to break
the ice with a little humor,
that's all. So,
"May the force...
...be with you," right?
You gotta admit, his sense
of humor is a little off.
You think so too, huh?
[TAKENAKA] Yeah.
I mean, I suspected,
but I think he's outdone
himself with this one.
Exactly, you stupid asshole.
In fact, I have a message
from the boss for you.
"I am Tai san fu kwan."
Has a nice ring to it, huh?
It means the god of
death and punishment
shall hereby bring down
judgment upon you
and I've gotta say,
it's not lookin' good.
I have no fucking idea
where you got that password,
but Boss Chang isn't
the idiot you think he is.
He prepared a brand
new password,
made special for
shitheads like you.
You hopped into this
parade with your ass
hanging out of your pants
and now you're fucked.
What? Don't think it's funny?
This is the part where you're
supposed to laugh. So, go ahead.
Well, you got me. I guess
I got a little carried away.
What the hell was I thinking?
Plus, to get handled
like this by a little girl,
it's just plain embarrassing.
Rock, get back!
That fuckin' idiot!
Damn you, Rock! You really
screwed up this time!
[SHEN HUA] The gunfire
has starting.
[LEIGHARCH] Huh?
I don't wanna do this.
Leigharch!
[LEIGHARCH] I can feel
me brain melting.
[SHEN HUA] I tell you not
relax too much before working.
I make very clear for you.
[LEIGHARCH] I just had
the greatest idea...
We'll stay here until
they stop shooting.
So sorry. If they die,
we not getting paid.
[LEIGHARCH] I'll
take a rain check.
[SHEN HUA] No,
work very important.
Damn! They just keep coming!
Stupid shit-for-brains Rock!
Damn him!
Sister! You duck now please.
Are you the getaway driver?!
No, I'm a fuckin' lawyer.
What do you think?
That was uncalled for.
Do not pursue! The military
has just left their camp!
Fall back on the double!
Mr. Chang told me that there
were supposed to be four of you.
So, what the hell happened
to the other three?
Plans changed and
it became two of us.
Then he fucked up
and got captured.
Oh! He sound like real idiot!
Well, we're gonna go
straight to the fuckin' base.
I wanna finish this
job and go home!
So, where's their hideout?
Is north of village
for six mile.
You find there in jungle.
We're not going to
the military base.
We're taking care
of these guys first.
I suggest you wipe your
own damn ass, sweetheart.
Wait, I've got a better one!
You can go tell that to
the cavalry, Mary Read.
We take you to base only,
then getting the money.
We not interesting in work more.
My partner has the
fuckin' documents.
Do you follow?
Understand you yes?
You got that, Chinglish?
Not my new interior.
If you must, do it outside.
[SHEN HUA] My English
not very good
because I am pure Taiwanese.
Maybe you like for me
to skin your ass, bitch?
You don't get it, do ya?
The boss sure as hell
didn't hire you
just to transport
my tight little ass.
The documents. Without 'em,
it'll be us three
idiots in this car
explaining to the
boss why we decided
to come back to the
base empty-handed.
We're gonna look really
fuckin' brilliant then.
Hey, you're here.
We've formed an
alliance with them.
As of right now, this camp
is under our command.
I'm glad to hear that.
Now, my friend, welcome
to our demilitarized zone.
We took the liberty of looking
through your briefcase.
It was completely empty.
I know nothing about it.
Even if I did, you know I
couldn't answer your questions.
A straightforward
answer. Too bad.
At a time like this, I think
the least you could do
is crack a joke. But we've
got nothing but time.
I'll just ask you slowly.
Alright, son.
You do want this to
be painless, don't ya?
If you're gonna get
involved in this stuff,
you should really
be a bit more careful.
You're Japanese,
if I'm not mistaken.
So, how long you been
doing this kinda work?
C'mon, just ease up, kid.
Don't wanna talk?
You know, young man,
it probably wouldn't hurt
for us Japanese to be friendly
to each other, now would it?
This is gonna be a problem.
[CIA AGENT 1]
Whatcha got for me?!
Has the launderer's
delivery boy arrived yet?!
[REVY] Well, well.
You're late again, Langley!