[tires squealing]
[WOMAN 1 giggling]
[MAN 1] Didn't I tell you?
We hafta go back.
[WOMAN 1] Fine.
[door being slammed open]
--[GANGSTER 1] Hey.
--[GANGSTER 2] What the hell?!
[sirens]
[whip crack]
[moaning]
[BANDO speaking in Japanese]
That's quite alright.
Although I would prefer
somewhere a bit quieter.
[speaking in Japanese]
[BALALAIKA] Our neutralization
of enemy targets
is proceeding
according to plan.
But the Kousa Clan
is a very large outfit.
To squeeze them out,
we'll need to
intensify our efforts,
so we'll be
shifting gears
and moving to phase
two of the operation.
[speaking in Japanese]
[BALALAIKA] Yes,
we'll shift gears.
First we clamp down on
their sources of revenue--
clubs, narcotics, pachinko
parlors, waste management...
[speaking in Japanese]
Of course, these actions are
just to rattle their cage,
whereas our main target is...
...something else.
[BANDO speaking in Japanese]
[BALALAIKA] I'm referring to a
tactic that works... anywhere.
An abduction, Mr. Bando.
We'll target the family
of the Kousa Clan's head--
Masami Kousa.
[translating to Japanese]
[speaking in Japanese]
What did he just say?
He just said,
"We can't do that."
[speaking in Japanese]
The idea was for
you to stir things up
so that they'd be forced
into negotiations with us.
If you go overboard,
you'll make things
impossible for us later on.
[BALALAIKA laughing]
Hear that, Sergeant?
I don't think
they understand.
Rock, translate this
word for word, okay?
Mr. Bando.
We will employ any means
necessary to secure profits.
May I remind you, we are
bearing most of the risk here.
Therefore, it follows
that the decision-making
lies with us, not you.
[BALALAIKA chuckles]
[gasps]
[speaking in Japanese]
[cellphone ringing]
[CHAKA] Oh, Rumi. It's just you.
I told you not to call
now, you stupid bitch.
You what? Prada?
I don't want any.
I've got enough to sell.
You talk too much,
you know that?
Keep it up and I'll
knock out two more teeth.
Huh? You're already ugly.
Chaka! What the hell's
wrong with you?!
--Show some respect!
--Do you have any idea
what's going on here,
you dumb shit?!
Oh. Sorry about that, guys.
Dumb fuckin' bitch.
Go on! Get outta here!
[CHAKA] Yeah, sure. I get it.
I'm going. I'm going already.
[speaking in Japanese]
[sliding door opening]
[MAKI] What the... Yukio?
You're still here?
Oh, hi, Maki.
Oh, it is getting late.
Hey... that must be a
good book. What is it?
[YUKIO] Oh, this?
It's Martin Heidegger.
He's a German philosopher.
This one's called
Being and Time .
I think I'll pass.
Fantasy and horror
stories are more my thing.
[YUKIO] That's right. You're a
big Anne Rice fan, aren't you?
So... what about light reading?
What authors do you like?
Hmm...
Let's see.
Umm...
[MAKI] Never mind.
Forget I asked, 'kay.
You know what?
I'm pretty sure whatever
you were just thinking of,
probably wasn't
light reading at all,
at least not for me.
You think so?
I guess I like any book
that takes me away
and makes me feel
like I'm lost out at sea.
Soaking in all that wisdom
and emotion and everything.
Endlessly expanding... yet
somewhat different from reality.
An escape.
I think that's what I like.
[MAKI] Ahhh.
I dunno, I just can't
get into the heavy ones.
How about King,
you ever read him?
[YUKIO] No. I really
don't like scary novels.
Weird. I'm surprised
you'd say that.
You seem like someone
who'd like Poe.
No.
It's just I've never
liked the ones
that make you
imagine the night.
So dark and lonely and sad.
I don't like the night.
There's something about it...
I'm afraid of being
swallowed by the darkness.
I don't find it romantic.
Not at all.
[car approaching]
I understand we've
got a little problem.
They're waiting
for you now, Sir.
[EUGENE] Target
0-1-2 confirmed.
0-1-2, confirmed.
[speaking in Japanese]
Of course we can wait,
as long as it doesn't
interfere with the operation.
That way we can
still raise a glass
to each other
when this is done.
Hey, Taka- san.
So, what's the deal
with that chick?
[TAKA] Huh? Fucking idiot.
Haven't you learned
your lesson yet?!
[CHAKA laughing] Easy.
It's not what you think.
[TAKA] Tch! All I know is
she's that scrawny
interpreter's bodyguard.
She came with
him from Roanapur.
Huh?
A chick and a bodyguard?!
Are you serious?!
Hey, Chaka! Cut it out!
What the hell is
wrong with you?!
These people are guests!
[CHAKA] Yeah.
I know they're
our guests and all.
But still...
I wanna see
what she can do.
[REVY] Is this almost over?
[ROCK] I'm afraid it's time
for socializing now.
What a waste of time.
[ROCK] Don't complain, Revy.
It's a way to make sure
things don't get out of hand.
If this is all it takes,
it's well worth it.
[sighing]
Whatever you say.
If it was up to me, I'd just
serve up a round of...
...arsenic cocktails.
[CHAKA] Oh, there she is.
[REVY] Hmph.
[CHAKA] Well, well.
So, is it true?
I hear... you like
playing with guns?
You Japanese have the
lamest pickup lines.
Go fuck yourself.
Alright, let's try again.
I run this place.
Now how could I do that
if I didn't know how
to talk to a lady?
So, honey, you're
from Roanapur, right?
Rumor has it that city has
more bad-ass motherfuckers
than a supermax prison.
Tell me, sweetheart...
ever shot anyone?
I've got about ten
kills under my belt.
[REVY] Romeo,
can you handle the truth?
[CHAKA] Huh?
[coughing]
Your breath stinks like
you've been sucking cock.
The bad cologne
doesn't help either.
I think your insides
must be rotting.
Revy.
Revy! Let's go.
Balalaika's waiting
for us outside.
Come on.
Hey, Mr. Interpreter.
Can't you see we're in
the middle of a conversation?
If I were you,
I wouldn't interrupt.
Go on, Revy.
Go and get Mr. Bando or...
[CHAKA] Hey!
Who do you think you
are, you little faggot!
Don't you fucking ignore me.
'Cause when I snap, there's
no telling what I'm gonna do.
Ya hear me?! Pal?!
[ROCK grunting]
Hey, cutie.
Must be hard for you to watch
me kicking his ass like this.
Maybe you should
try me instead.
A little pussy like
this couldn't possibly
satisfy a woman like you.
Well, faggot?!
[YOSHIDA] Chaka! What the
hell is wrong with you?!
Look at me, you little punk!
You think you can do
whatever the hell you want?!
Hey, lighten up Yoshida- san.
I was just playing
with the guy.
I'm very sorry.
I'll have a talk
with him later.
An incompetent officer and
a soldier who ignores orders.
This is simply
unbearable, Sergeant.
[BORIS] It would be better
if this were a battlefield.
We could just kill them
all and be done with it.
[REVY] Sorry, Rock.
He had his hand on his
gun the entire time.
I was the bait.
He just wanted you to draw.
I think you're finally
starting to get better at this.
I'm impressed.
I may need my Cutlass after all.
[ROCK] Wait, Revy!
[REVY] Don't worry.
I won't start anything.
But I can tell you
right now, at some point,
he's gonna turn
his gun on us.
He's just a poor, dumb fuck
who thinks he's got
something to prove.
We'll give him his fight.
But for now,
we'll just sit tight.
When he draws, he's
a fucking dead man.
[GINJI] Boss.
Would you please
pass me the miso ?
[BANDO] Here.
We don't have enough power
to shut the Kousa Clan up.
The plan was good
despite the Peacekeeping
Council's decision.
I was counting on
the fact that our money
would speak louder
than our actions.
But because of those
damned Russians...
[GINJI] Boss,
the sweet rice vinegar.
[BANDO] Here you go.
Honestly, this isn't good.
[ROCK] Is there anything
else you need, Benny?
[BENNY] That's it. Thanks again.
I prefer not to go
through the black market
in Bangkok if I can avoid it.
[ROCK] Oh, yeah, Revy needs
you to do her a favor.
Yah?
She wants you to send
over her Cutlasses.
A troubling request.
Is there a storm brewing?
I don't know yet.
But I sure hope not.
[BENNY] So do I.
I'll take care of it.
Thanks.
[announcement about
train being canceled]
You're kidding me.
Guess I'll take... Huh?
--I know you...
[ROCK] Yeah, it's been a while
since I felt this cold.
[YUKIO] Right, you live
in a subtropical zone.
So, have you managed
to make it home
yet, Mr. Okajima?
My home? Well, ah...
Well, to be honest,
I've kinda been avoiding it.
You know, you sound an
awful lot like the old me.
Honestly, I used
to hate my home.
But then it occurred
to me it was
the one place where
I could always return.
I guess... that's
something, right?
Well, you're wise beyond
your years, Yukio.
Actually, my friends say
I act like an old lady.
Huh?
Oh, no. I didn't mean...
[chuckles]
I know. I'm just kidding.
For me... I guess
it's different.
Right now I feel
like I'm in limbo.
Don't wanna go
back to where I was,
but I'm not sure
I like where I'm going.
I've heard it said
that people are like dice.
I think Jean-Paul
Sartre said that.
And like dice, we
can throw ourselves
in any direction.
And that's why we're
condemned to be free.
Everyone's starting
point is different,
but no matter how
small the choice,
at the very least you
can still throw yourself.
In the end, you can't
blame fate.
Your life is the result
of the choices you make.
Well, do you agree?
That's kinda hard to take.
[cellphone ringing]
Please excuse me.
This is Yukio.
Oh, it's you, Ginji.
Uh-huh.
I know. But still,
you worry too much.
Yes. In fact I'm having
coffee with Mr. Okajima.
You know, he's the one
we met at the fair.
--[GINJI] Miss...
--What is it, Ginji?
[GINJI] Perhaps you should...
[YUKIO] What?
Mr. Bando's there now?
Then I'd better hurry home.
Yes. I understand. Right.
I'm really sorry.
I have to go. Bye.
Uh, Yukio... one sec.
[YUKIO] Uh-huh?
Well...
I never asked you
what your last name is...
Huh? Oh, it's Washimine.
Pretty solemn, isn't it?
I'm against this.
What does it have
to do with Yukio?
[BANDO] What if the Peacekeeping
Council heard about this?
They'd never let
us rebuild our clan,
and on top of that,
they'd probably
have us thrown out of
the region altogether.
--Oh, Miss!
--You're already home...
I apologize for not noticing.
Mr. Bando.
What were you just saying?
[BANDO] Goodnight, Miss.
When your father died,
they started making noise
because we didn't have
a legitimate successor.
They said they'd accept
any blood relation.
Goddamn it, they knew exactly
what that would mean.
--So then...
--Yes. That's right.
You were the only one
they would accept,
those damn bastards.
And they're using
that to destroy us.
[cellphone ringing]
Yoshida?
[YOSHIDA] Boss! Are
you okay, Boss?!
[BANDO] I'm fine, but it looks
like someone put a tail on me.
They're not the local police.
[YOSHIDA] Boss!
Could be someone
from higher up.
I'll lose them when
I get the chance.
After that, I've gotta
lay low for a while.
[YOSHIDA] Boss! The Russians are
going completely crazy on us!
They blew up a car in front
of the police station today
when this guy from Kousa
went there to turn himself in!
A fucking car bomb!
[BANDO] Yeah?
[YOSHIDA] I thought they were
gonna wait! That fucking bitch!
[BANDO] I hear you.
I'll be in touch.
--[YOSHIDA] Boss!
--Prepare for trouble
and get cleaned up.
[BALALAIKA] Anything
from Washimine?
Nothing yet, Ma'am.
Waste of time.
Earlier at 0600 hours,
we know that a detective
approached the Washimine
office for information.
It's only a matter of time.
Tell the main unit to
relocate to the Maria Zeleska.
[BORIS] Yes, Ma'am.
What should we tell Laptev?
Don't tell him anything.
[ROCK] Um, Miss Balalaika.
Hmm? What do you want?
Well, um...
What...
What happens if they don't
keep up their end of things?
[BALALAIKA] Rock.
Is that any concern of yours?
[ROCK] No...
That's right.
You'd be wise not to forget
your place in all of this.
Hey, Sis.
Why not cut him some slack.
It's not exactly a big
secret or anything...
...so why not tell him?
There's no reason to make
this personal, Two-Hands.
Silence is golden.
Won't argue with you there,
but Rock's on our side, right?
Trusting each other's
important, too.
I see you're getting
better at this.
Alright, fine.
Let's suppose for a
moment they were to
do something stupid like that.
Well, we'd just add one
more name to our hit list.
Our job here won't change
and life would go on as usual.
It's as simple as that.
[YOSHIBO] Yuki!
I'm sorry.
We'll stay to help
you next time, I swear.
Yeah. Sorry. Bye.
Don't worry. Have
fun at work, alright.
[MAKI] Here's the thing, Yukio.
My last finals went so bad.
When my mom saw the results,
she freaked out
saying she totally
wants me to quit my job.
But I need that job
or I can't afford my...
[YUKIO] Ginji.
I am involved in this.
I was raised in this house.
I hold the Washimine name.
[MAKI] She just kept
nagging and nagging,
like I don't want
a good future?
About that guy, Okajima...
You should know
he's involved in this.
He's on the Russians' side.
Yukio! Yukio!
Huh?
Ohhh...
You probably didn't
hear a word I said.
Oh, sorry.
This is seriously a
big deal for me, okay.
I need your help.
It's just... I'm not...
Huh? What's wrong?
Actually, never mind.
On second thought,
talking about it isn't
really going to help.
What?! Come on!
It's no fair to leave
me hanging like that!
[YOSHIDA] Boss!
[BANDO] Yeah, what is it?
I'm just out for a walk.
No reason to be concerned.
Bro! You're going to meet
the Russians, aren't you?!
It's been a long time
since you called me Bro.
Wait up! I'm coming, too!
Yoshida. Take this.
I want you to find Ginji.
You ask him what to do next.
I know you don't like him,
but he's a good man.
[crying]
Don't do it!
[BANDO] Guess this's goodbye.
It's been quite the ride.
[YOSHIDA sniveling]
[GINJI] When did this happen?
[YOSHIDA] Just this morning.
There was a suitcase sitting
out in front of our office.
Those goddamned
fucking Russians!
Yoshida, regardless
of who did it,
it still would've
ended this way.
Something had to
be done about Kousa.
They were trying
to destroy our clan.
The boss was too
smart for his own good.
That's all it is.
[YOSHIDA] So, what the
hell do we do now?
It's so dark and lonely.
The snowy night sky.
Stop right there!
You Russian bitch!
[stabbing sound]
[BALALAIKA] Rock!
Translate and make sure
he understands every word.
[ROCK] But...
[BALALAIKA] I'm gonna tell
you the truth tonight.
What I seek is
destruction and domination.
I don't care
about anything else.
I'm only interested
in how much I can dance
in the pit of Hell
when it's all over.
See you there one day.
[loud cracking sound]
[REVY] Hey!
Wake up, Rock!
Are you alright?!
Was...
[REVY] You're
sweating like crazy.
Was I asleep?
[REVY] You could call it that.
You sounded like
an old Buick engine.
You shouldn't drink so much.
Yeah.
Anyway, the shit's
about to hit the fan.
We're moving.
--We are?
--They're splitting up.
Between a cargo ship
and the Russian Embassy.
So, this really
is gonna be war.
Damn right it is.
Hotel Moscow is serious.
A storm is coming, Rock.
A storm of steel and blood.
[YUKIO] You're planning
to go, aren't you?
So, if I choose to
walk a path in the sun,
the rest of you will be forced
to wander in the darkness.
Please, Miss.
You mustn't do this.
No, Ginji.
I know how you feel,
but I can't run from this.
You know. I can actually
feel the night
inside of you right now.
It's sorrowful,
but at the same time,
it's not cold like
I thought it'd be.
I feel warmth.
[GINJI] Miss. I...
I wanted you to
have a normal life.
And I always hoped you'd
find true happiness.
I've lived only to see that.
Now Kousa's rats,
those Russian bastards...
They're trying to
take it all away!
Our name, our legacy,
and everything we stand for!
As small in number as we are,
we will not go easily.
If the Council accepts me
in place of my father, so be it.
You know what?
The snowy night is so beautiful.
This is the first time
I ever thought that.
Ginji.
Will you protect me
as you did my father?
I will. Though unworthy,
I am Chief Lieutenant
of the Washimine Family.
I, Ginji Matsuzaki,
will protect you
with all seven
of my incarnations!
[ROCK] People are
just like dice.
We throw ourselves in the
direction of our choosing.
Wait, Ginji. Before you go,
promise me you'll
be careful tonight.
[BALALAIKA] Let's take care
of this quickly, shall we?