[ROCK] At the entrance to
the gulf, a Buddha statue,
once meant to brighten the
world with a light of virtue,
now sits decaying.
Beyond its faded
glory lies Roanapur,
the city of immorality.
From the overland
entrance to the city,
there's always a
noose left hanging,
intended for some
unknown person.
And what awaits
past the scenery
is the city of pleasure,
Roanapur.
Until recently, I was
a businessman in Tokyo.
Now I'm a crew member
on a pirate ship.
I'll kill you! I'll kill
you! Hey, you. Bastard!
I'll kill you! I'll kill you!
You're not getting away! Die,
bastard! Kill you! Kill you!
[DUTCH] Revy, I'm stepping
out for a while.
[REVY] Gotcha. Watch your back.
--You going out?
--Yeah, for a bit.
[spitting]
What the hell is this?
[bell]
--[ROCK] Revy?
--Hm?
Just saw Dutch.
Where's he going?
Who knows?
Besides, it's none
of our business
what Dutch does
in his spare time.
You're right. I only asked
because I was curious.
Nosy types aren't too popular.
What the hell is this? Tastes
like it came out of your ass.
Whatever you paid for those,
you got ripped off.
Guess so. It looks like
things don't get any better
when you go downtown,
either. Not in this city.
You gotta realize international
criminals come here
to lock horns with each other.
They're all trying to scam
one another from top to bottom.
You don't really stand a
chance of surviving here
if you always believe
everything you see.
Then again,
you're lucky if that's
the biggest problem you got.
I'll take it to heart.
She's right. I may
still be too soft.
After all, I don't know the
histories of my crew members.
They keep their
pasts to themselves,
their privacy protected by a
fierce sense of independence.
But I don't care.
That's how I feel.
Hello there. It's me.
So, how you doing?
Yeah, go ahead.
International number
10013. Right.
Send me 120,000 to the
name "Flyer's Company."
Yeah.
[car horn]
[CHIN] Hey, Dutch.
We'll talk later.
Fuck me.
Great weather, huh?
So, how's business going
for you guys? Good, I hope.
Can't complain, Mr. Chin.
We're getting by.
Well, that's great to hear.
Tell me something--
how long do you plan
to work with that
Fry Face bitch, anyway?
Maybe you're just not
thinking straight, eh?
Don't know, Mr. Chin. No clue
what you're talking about.
I'm talking about
that crazy Russian.
Ever since those damn
Russkies got here,
we've been losing
money left and right.
That Ivan's taken
all of our girls,
the rights to our hotels,
and the heroin routes.
They've got no sense of honor.
And if we end up losing
the sea routes to them too,
those greedy bastards are going
to wipe us out completely.
Allow me to spell
it out for you--
what I'm trying to say is you
should pull out--and quickly.
Hey, listen. Let me
give you some advice.
Hm?
[DUTCH] Even bad guys have
common sense, you hear me?
When you went and sold that
junk to the New People's Army,
we were the ones
hired to deliver it.
It wasn't even close to
a "no problem" situation,
but why don't you remind
me who pulled out then?
Why don't you let
that go, huh, Dutch?
It's behind us, so don't
bring up the past
like some old bitch.
I'll say what I want.
And I'll tell you this much--
Balalaika has a hell of a lot
more honor than you ever did.
If you want to do
business with us,
we'll ship your
goods at our rate.
We're done talking now.
I'm telling you, you won't
get any second chances, Dutch.
And neither will
you, my friend.
Try using your head
if you want to survive.
Later.
Hey, Dutch,
why don't you ever come
sample the goods here, baby?
I already know what's
inside your bottles, ladies.
After all, I did
ship them here.
Huh?
[DUTCH] That bastard.
[VERROCCHIO] Is it true that
torpedo boat bastard is working
for some country bumpkin,
Russkie bitch these days?
[BODYGUARD] Yes, sir.
But I've been hearing that
these guys will take on jobs
from just about anyone, so long
as they got money to spend.
I'll be damned if
he can find me a city
as rotten to the core as this.
[car horn]
Huh?
Dutch, look. The new
board's finally arrived.
This is the pure,
unadulterated real deal.
[DUTCH] You're probably the
first guy to ever use the word
"pure" in this city.
Now hurry your ass up and get
that stuff on the boat, Benny.
Yeah, sure thing!
Man, oh, man. Our crew can be
so damn simpleminded sometimes.
Hey, Dutch.
[seagulls]
[snoring]
Wake up, sailor! We have a job.
Oh, okay. A job?
[engine revving]
Where the hell's Rock?
I told him to wash up, but he's
sure taking his sweet time.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
[tires peeling out]
[car horn]
What is it today?
Just came in. Passed on
from Donnie Yen.
Who's Donnie Yen?
[DUTCH] He gives us jobs
from time to time.
Today, we're receiving a package
from the Vietnamese military
at Phu Quoc Island.
I figured since our
schedule was open...
Anyway, nothing's better
than a hard day's work, right?
What are we supposed to do with
all these lame jobs, Dutch?
No wonder we can't
make office boy here
trade these shitty white-collar
shirts for some real clothes.
I wish you'd stop with that.
I told you,
this is just my style.
Which reminds me, Rock,
what happened to that Hawaiian
shirt I got you at the market?
--You know the one.
--The hideously ugly shirt?
Wearing that thing should
be some form of punishment.
[REVY] Something you
want to say, Rock?
You think I don't
have any taste?
[ROCK] Hey, stop that.
[CHIN] Yeah, I got it.
[phone ringing]
That's right. It looks like
they fell for the trap.
Whether you want to
see this thing through
is up to you at this point.
I know for a fact you've
been down on your luck lately.
I hear you messed
up the last time
and got chased around
by a battleship.
Huh? You take care of
this job and I guarantee
you'll get all the tolls
between here and Kalimantan.
Yeah. Yeah, that's right.
That's the deal. Give that one
some thought, why don't you?
I told you, Dutch,
you're not gonna get any
second chances with us.
Take this through
here and back
and it should end up like
this. Hey, that's funny.
Come on.
You have got to be the clumsiest
person I've ever seen.
Or is it that you're
just not trying hard?
Sorry.
[REVY]
You're not cut out for this.
Watch my hands.
A retarded monkey could do it.
I guess... but don't
be so hard on me.
I never did stuff
like this at work.
Well, Rock, what kind of
stuff did you do at work?
I was in the Materials
Procurement department.
I took trips, I wrote reports...
...made calls.
But I think bowing my head to
my superiors was my real job.
At night, I'd accompany my boss
when he'd go out for drinks.
I even got my ass kicked once
when he was really drunk.
That's really great, Rock.
What a disgusting story.
How could you put up
with all that shit?
What are you, some kind of
masochist or something?
Putting up with it
is part of the job.
I mean, no one wants to
end up on the streets.
Plus, that's just
how people survive.
Pathetic.
Revy, what did you do
before you ended up here?
What I do now is pretty much
what I've always done.
Really? Then let me guess--
as a kid, you spent your
days on the river near home
swinging a Cutlass around?
That's the truth.
I stole, I killed.
I did everything that
you'd consider bad.
[gun shots]
It ain't no sick joke.
[seagulls]
Dutch, I've got several
boats approaching.
Start praying, 'cause
you're gonna need directions
for how to get
to heaven, Dutch.
[computer beeping]
It doesn't make sense for there
to be any merchants around.
This is known as Pirate's Bay.
Can you find out who they are?
They're small and fast.
Could be cops looking
to arrest pirates.
Dutch, a red alert!
[DUTCH] What the hell is this?
They blew right by yellow
and gave us the
red lamp already.
[BENNY] Their speed's 28 knots.
--Hey, Dutch.
--Hold on.
Benny will explain
the situation to you.
Wait a second... I just
saw three more boats.
There's a total
of six boats now.
The first three
started accelerating
from the other side of
the island we just passed.
And these last three on our
portside came from behind
a completely different island.
Changing course
portside is dangerous.
The ships on that
side will catch us,
but it's the same
problem to starboard.
[DUTCH] The basic
hunting pattern.
[BENNY] These guys
are hauling ass, too.
--[REVY] Hey, Dutch.
--Yeah.
[REVY] I smell it.
[DUTCH] So, who are they?
I know that stench,
even from this distance.
These guys definitely aren't
marine cops, that's for sure.
There's no doubt in my mind.
They stink too much of
blood and smoke for that.
Pirates? We're actually
being targeted by pirates?
Dutch, what's the
background on our client?
Rock, that observation
really hurts.
I've been conducting
background checks
on Donnie Yen's economic
situation from the beginning.
[LUAK] Hello? Hello,
can you hear me, Lagoon?
That's right, it's me.
Dutch, it's been a while.
Now I see. It's Luak.
Sorry, but there's
no prey here.
You should go home
before you get lost.
There's prey right here, Dutch.
A ratty old torpedo boat.
Six vessels in pursuit.
If it is Luak,
he's brought
everything he's got.
Damn all these stupid bastards.
Chin got you involved
in this, didn't he, Luak?
God must pity you
for your stupidity.
[LUAK] Ha! Once we get
a pint of lead in you,
maybe it'll put an end to
all that pillow talk of yours.
The enemy's got us
on both sides,
but in these positions,
I think they're...
I see that, Rock.
I suggest you get inside.
Nice job.
If you're gonna flank the
enemy, it's common sense
to stagger your positions
to avoid friendly fire.
Amateurs.
[LUAK] Bastard!
Don't get too confident.
I'll send you straight to hell.
Still four vessels remaining.
Dutch, they're coming.
Revy, it's your turn.
Give 'em a taste of Two-Hands.
[REVY] Leave it to me.
[DUTCH] It's showtime.
Can you make them dance?
[REVY] You know I can.
[ROCK] Revy, what are
you planning to do?
Listen, why don't
you take a break
from all the casual
conversation about your world?
'Cause right now, I need
to focus on this world.
Benny-boy, we've got
two closing portside
and another two starboard
astern. Is that about right?
[BENNY] And one more.
Directly behind us.
[DUTCH] Do that one last, Revy.
[REVY] Alright. I'll start
with the shit on the left.
Let's dance the Jitterbug, baby!
How'd she...?
She's on the next boat!
Do something about that bitch.
[PIRATE 3] Damn, I can't
see with all the smoke.
[PIRATE 4] Make sure you
don't hit one of ours.
Damn it.
[PIRATE 2] Kill that bitch.
Finish her off!
Shit!
So, Rock, which boat is she on?
[ROCK] She's working
on her fifth now.
Hold on, looks like
the third is still alive.
[LUAK] There she is right
there! Shoot her! Kill her!
Damn it. My fleet.
She took out all my boats!
[DUTCH] You just hit a dead end.
It seems like you were
the one destined
to dance the Cha-Cha
with some hot lead, Luak.
Damn it. How dare you!
That bitch isn't even human.
Chin can kiss my ass.
I'm not dealing with
these demons anymore.
She defeated them all
single-handedly. Incredible.
Even as I was saying the words,
a completely different
thought had crossed my mind.
I can't even imagine how
her life was shattered
to make her who she is today.
But I must be pretty broken
myself to sit here in awe,
praising her for her
powers of destruction.
[CHIN] Damn it! Luak, you
useless bastard. You screwed me.
That idiot. What kind
of mother raises
such a useless piece of shit?
He puts my balls
in a vice, and then,
oh, how convenient,
he goes and dies.
This is a fucking disaster.
I'd like the chance to kill
him myself all over again.
Eh? Oh. Uh...
[BALALAIKA] Well, well, well...
Moving out so suddenly?
That's such hard work.
Perhaps we could
help you, Mr. Chin.
Uh... N-N-Never mind.
There must be some kind
of misunderstanding here.
I don't know what kind
of pathetic rumor
is floating around town.
If we just sit down over lunch,
you'll see there's a
perfectly good explanation.
It's plain to see...
[grunting]
[BALALAIKA] Listen carefully,
you piece of horseshit--
we didn't come here so
you could tell us a story.
We already know
everything we need to.
Pray. That's about the
only thing you can still do
while you're alive.
Ah, this sucks. We busted our
asses for nothing. What a waste.
It's not so bad.
Kind of like being
bitten by a dog.
[phone ringing]
You dumbass, I'm serious.
Bullets aren't free, you know.
Hello. Lagoon Company.
[BALALAIKA] Oh, Japonski.
It's been a while.
Is Dutch around, by any chance?
Who is it?
[ROCK] Ms. Balalaika.
Hi there, Dutch. I heard you
went on a wild goose chase.
And you got stuck playing
games with Mr. Chin.
[DUTCH] Who told you about that?
He told me himself.
Let's just say he's a bit
too loud to organize
any kind of conspiracy.
He was blabbing away to
just about everyone in town.
Even the dead would have
known what was happening.
Anyway, we'll make sure nothing
like this happens again.
It was a real pain
for you, wasn't it?
No. Wouldn't say that.
It wasn't even enough
to give me a headache.
[BALALAIKA] Thanks, Dutch.
I realize it's hardly enough
after what you went through,
but I'll let you hear
something amusing.
They call this
"pleasure and pain."
[DUTCH] Oh, is it
cooler than JB?
Of course.
Yeah, that sounded cool.
[BALALAIKA] We'll have
a job for you soon.
I'll call you then.
Was that a call about a job?
[DUTCH] Something like that.
She filled me in on some
gossip to cheer me up.
Revy. Rock. You guys
have any plans?
[REVY] Not really.
[DUTCH] You, Benny?
Bit of maintenance work
on the electronics,
but nothing that
can't wait a day.
Alright then.
Considering the mental
anguish you incurred
due to external interference,
as your employer, I should
provide entertainment
as compensation. And after
careful consideration...
--Huh?
--...I'd like to propose
a trip to the Yellow Flag
tonight to drink away our pain.
This one's on me, of course.
So, who's coming?
[REVY] You serious?
Can we stay there 'til dawn?
[BENNY] I'm in.
--[ROCK] Uh, me too.
--[REVY] Then it's decided.
Benny, get the car.
Rock, you're not
on the job anymore.
You should wear that
Hawaiian shirt I got you.
[ROCK] I don't want to.
[CAPTAIN AHBE] Despite that,
there are still some fights
that you must
take on. Let's go!
Prepare the torpedoes
for surface attack.