It's so different.
This place is crazy
compared to my hometown.
[ROCK] I'm sorry. A kid your
age shouldn't be exposed
to a city like this.
Roanapur at night...
I'll be fine.
You have a lot of faith.
You believe in your
family, don't you?
Of course.
I believe in Roberta.
I know that she's
gonna come here
to take me home to my father.
Well, you're fortunate.
To be able to know in your heart
that things will work out.
You're confident that
this maid of yours
is gonna risk her
life to save you.
And I really don't know if
that's gonna happen or not.
But one thing I'm
pretty sure of--
you must have one solid family
to have such faith in them.
It's just...
...sometimes I wonder how my
family actually feels about me.
[GARCIA] You mean they...
Uh, never mind.
It's not important.
Aw, Rocky misses Mommy.
You think so?
If I did, I'm thinking
I probably would've
said goodbye to this
place a long time ago.
Rock. That's
fucking pathetic.
Only some tit-sucking
momma's boy would come up with
that bullshit conversation
you're enjoying.
We're just talking
about ideals.
Y'know, something you hold on
to because you believe in it.
So, if I was ever kidnapped,
would you try to save me?
Would you come charging in with
Cutlass in hand to save me?
I wouldn't forgive you
for being stupid enough
to get kidnapped
in the first place!
If that ever happens,
forget you know us,
and then beg forgiveness
for being such a fuck-up
before you kill yourself.
See? These are the
people I hang out with.
But just the same,
they're worth hanging on to.
Hey, kid. This maid
you've been talking about...
Sure hope she's not just some
bullshit fantasy you made up.
I'd love to meet her.
'Cause my Cutlass
feels too cold.
Who knows? Your maid
could help fix that.
I'm just kidding.
Well, I guess there's no
point in getting my hopes up.
Not when I'm dealing with some
maid-obsessed brat like you.
Ha, ha, Did you hear that?
"Be rude," she says.
What a crazy bitch!
[laughing]
Huh? Is this a fight?
[ROBERTA] I am very sorry, but I
will not be able to hold back.
Please excuse me.
And... I hope you
enjoy yourselves.
Shit, didn't this
place just reopen?
Dutch, I know what
I want for Christmas.
Wha... Why you!
You fucking bitch!
Alright, boys!
We'll finish this now!
I want her dead!
If you think it will help,
then please do what you must.
Fuck you!
Roberta!
[chuckling]
You'll pay, bitch!
I-It's not working, Bro!
Why won't she fall?
Is it made out of Kevlar?!
Goddamn it! You better
pay for all of this!
Somehow, we managed to walk
right into the middle
of a brutal shootout.
But maybe we can take
advantage of the fact
that they're busy
killing each other.
So, anyone else
feel like leaving?
Of course. But where?
We can go fishing
at Phuket Beach
until this cools
down a little bit.
I don't feel like catching
bullets in the back
while I drink.
I'm no Giuliano Gemma.
Hey, will you
hurry up and tell me
if I'm gonna get
to shoot or not?
Good call.
I vote not to shoot.
We'll leave the kid here.
I sure as hell don't wanna go
for a walk carrying a claymore.
[REVY] But he's worth
something, Dutch.
Shit, we were busy talking
and now the front door's
a goddamn war zone.
Anyway, this kid
isn't worth it anymore.
He can't come with us.
You got it?
But if we do that,
we'd just be--
[REVY] We've got no choice.
Oh, fuckin' fuck.
[DUTCH] Alright, then.
Uh, Garcia. Listen to me.
Don't move from this spot
until they stop shooting.
When this thing is all over,
find your maid and
go home to Venezuela.
I... I didn't think
she could just...
That Roberta could be so...
She's not the kind of
person who kills people.
But...
Why?
Garcia...
Rock! What's takin' you?!
Ten fucking grand
to replace my booze,
tack on another fifteen
for the furniture,
plus at least twenty grand
for the building itself.
Now to figure out who
I'm sending the invoice to.
Revy!
You bitch!
Revy! Is this your fault?!
How many times are your
friends gonna tear up my bar?!
They're not my friends!
Don't try to pin this
shit on me, you dumbass!
Fuck.
It's almost like they were
waiting for me to open my mouth.
[ABREGO] Lagoon Company?
What the fuck are you
guys doing here?!
What happened to that package
you were supposed
to deliver to us?!
[DUTCH] Okay, hold on!
Don't jump to
conclusions, Abrego!
Then why the fuck
is the package here?!
You better not have
ignored our contract!
I said don't jump
to conclusions!
We'll talk about payment
later! This ain't the time!
[ROBERTA] Young Master.
[GARCIA] Roberta.
I certainly didn't expect to
see you here, Master Garcia.
Your father has been
extremely worried about you.
Please, come.
It's only natural that
you feel afraid right now.
But if you let me,
I will explain myself.
I promise you will understand.
Who are these people?
Not good. Their eyes met.
No! Roberta, don't!
Stay back, housemaid.
I don't think any
of us wants to die.
Especially not your sweet little
Garcia. Wouldn't you agree?
[ROCK] Are you crazy?
You're gonna make it worse!
[REVY] Shut up!
As long as you're not stupid
enough to start shooting at us,
you'll get the kid
home in one piece.
With his brains
still in his head.
Comprende ?
I need a moment to think.
We're not done with you yet,
you fucking bitch!
I have finished thinking now.
Una bendición
para los vivos .
Un ramo de flores
para los muertos .
That's Spanish. A blessing
for the living.
A branch of flowers
for the dead.
Un castigo de muerte
para los malvados .
[ROCK]
With a sword for justice,
--the punishment of
--Así llegamos al
--death for the villains.
--altar de los santos .
Like this, we arrive at
the altar of the saints.
The Lovelace family creed.
I cannot agree to your request,
though I do intend to have the
young master home in one piece.
However, I must work in
accordance with this creed.
In the name of Santa Maria...
Huh? Those words...
The hammer of righteousness
to all injustice!
That bitch!
[DUTCH] Now! Let's go!
Hey! Fuck off! Get away!
[explosion]
Revy!
Will you just fucking
die already?!
I know you,
Bloodhound of Florencia!
[DUTCH] That is one crazy bitch.
This makes the
Battle of Khe Sanh
look like a walk in the park!
Hey! Is Revy alright?!
[BENNY] Her injuries are minor,
but she does have a concussion.
[DUTCH] Revy! Wake up,
will ya? Hey!
[GARCIA] Please stop...
You have to stop this, Roberta!
Just stop it!
Garcia...
[DUTCH] Rock!
Don't just stand there!
We're leaving!
Run!
Take me with you.
Master Garcia.
I can't... I can't deal with
this. I don't know who she is.
Stay right there! Now...
it all makes sense to me.
Those words you
were saying earlier.
Tu eres el perro des
cassa de Florencia .
That's right, you're the
Bloodhound of Florencia.
I can't fucking believe
that you're still alive.
Not even Jesus Christ
could've guessed that one.
These four years since you left
the Colombian
Revolutionary Army,
everyone from goddamn drug
cartels to fucking Interpol
has been after you, woman.
The cartels put a four hundred
thousand dollar bounty
on your head, dead or alive.
[chuckling]
Looks like luck is
finally on my side!
If I bring your head
back on a platter,
I'll be made a lieutenant
in the cartel! [laughing]
I no longer have a reason
to keep you alive.
If you will excuse me now,
I must be on my way.
However, please accept
this parting gift.
To all of you gentlemen,
I bid farewell.
Ahh!
Damn! When it comes to killing,
she doesn't mess around.
Rock, you dumb fuck.
I told you to leave
that kid behind.
I'm sorry, I couldn't help it.
I couldn't leave
him there to die.
Do you think... that
might've killed her?
[DUTCH] Get in the car!
[ROCK] I shouldn't be
able to hear anything,
but I can feel it.
Her footsteps getting
closer and closer.
And I could swear
that any minute now,
her black maid's outfit will
appear from that fiery exit.
[DUTCH] So, hurry up
and get in the car!
[tires screeching]
[car alarm]
[BENNY] Where should we go?
[DUTCH] Where can we go?
[BENNY] Aw, we're fucked.
Now I know. That maid is a
killer robot from the future!
The only difference is that we
don't have Schwarzenegger here.
That's really not funny.
I'm not laughing.
We've got her precious
little master with us.
Just head for the port.
We've gotta get to the Lagoon!
Bad news isn't hard to find.
And from my experience,
bad news likes company.
Yes, this one is
quite infamous indeed.
Her code name is Bloodhound.
She got it because once
she's locked on to her prey,
she always makes the kill.
This is going to be a pain.
[cell phone ringing]
They're calling, Sergeant.
It's probably the
worst possible news.
She's coming.
[DUTCH] Rock! Wake Revy up!
This isn't the time for her
to catch up on her sleep!
[ROCK] Revy! Revy!
For fuck's sake!
Shit!
Corporal Menisov,
what's the situation?
Ma'am! Yellow Flag's destroyed
and the Bloodhound
and Lagoon are gone!
However, a Plymouth
was seen heading towards
the city on the main street
about ten minutes ago!
[BALALAIKA] Maintain
your position, Corporal.
Continue gathering information.
[MENISOV] Roger. What should
I tell the bar owner?
[BALALAIKA] Tell him not to
worry about the insurance.
I'm heading to the
city with a squad.
So, Kapitän ...
Going to war after so long?
Playing mafia dulls the
instincts and makes one soft.
We'll see.
But it never hurts to be
prepared, now does it?
We owe Lagoon. Or rather,
we owe Dutch for all he's done.
We simply cannot leave
things the way they are.
Let us go, comrades.
Cock your hammers!
Fuck! Will you just die?!
Let go of me, you bitch!
Damn it!
Now's our chance!
Hang on, Dutch!
Oh, shit!
[BENNY] We'll head to port
using these back alleys.
Once we're out at sea,
I don't care who she is,
there's no way
she'll be able to...
--Damn it.
--[DUTCH] Not good, Benny.
We're losing valuable time
if we go this way.
Yeah, but her radiator's
totally shot.
The car's toast.
I never said I was
worried about the car.
Maybe you should've
paid better attention
to Rock's joke
earlier on, Benny-boy.
You need to start
thinking of her
as an invincible killer robot!
[BENNY] Okay, we'll push it!
[DUTCH] Rock, do what
it takes to wake her up!
If this turns into
some big shootout,
we're gonna need
her gun, alright?
Revy! C'mon! Wake up!
Please wake up!
Take the next left!
Get on that main road
and then floor it.
Alright!
Are you alright,
Benny? Wake up!
[BENNY] Shit.
The engine won't start.
Benny, hurry!
Get down!
Master Garcia.
Roberta.
[BENNY] Those are no doubt
the three most
terrifying women in the world.
[DUTCH] This feels way
too much like Ground Zero.