[YOUNG BALALAIKA]
You mean it? Me, Uncle?
In the Olympics?
[GENERAL] Yes, of course.
Everybody needs to
have goals in life.
And in your case, it's not
a question of talent.
You've got plenty of that.
If I make it,
I could regain
my father's honor.
As your father's only child,
your achievements
would be his, as well.
So, that means we could...
[GENERAL] However,
you need to earn it first.
It is a rare privilege reserved
for only the most loyal Soviets.
[BORIS] Lieutenant? Lieutenant!
Hey, Menshov! The Dragunov!
[MENSHOV] Here!
[BORIS] Excellent.
If this were LA,
you'd have the gold medal!
First Lieutenant's
paved the way!
Everyone, move out!
We're leaving the
chemicals behind!
Let's go!
[ANNOUNCER] Women's fifty
meter three position rifle...
The gold medal goes to
Launi Meili of the USA!
Four years ago in Seoul,
Meili finished in sixth place,
[BALALAIKA] And what do you
want me to do about it?
[SAKHAROV] Kapitän .
All of us have been stripped
of our military ranks.
So, I'm no longer a Kapitän .
It's all over... you aren't
in my company anymore.
The country we gave our
lives for, the Soviet Union,
no longer exists in this world.
[SAKHAROV] Regardless
of where we were,
as long as we were
fighting under you,
the path would surely open.
We all believed that.
Even through this
shameful poverty.
[BALALAIKA] After all
the battles we'd survived,
I never thought
my second-in-command
would end up losing his
life over dirty money.
[song in background]
♪ To the world of midnight ♪
♪ Where the darkness
fill the air... ♪
[BALALAIKA] Comrades!
Raise your fists!
As of now, we return to active
military duty on our own terms!
♪ ...nobody has a name... ♪
We've fought through
many battles...
...since that fateful
day, haven't we?
--Yes.
--This is just one step
in a long climb for us.
So, let's take care
of things quickly.
[BORIS] For the Washimine Clan,
she's next in line after Bando.
Hm. A sacrificial lamb.
[MAKI] I can't believe how early
it's getting dark these days.
Um, Yukio, is everything
okay with you?
It's just kind of weird
that you sorted all those
library cards in one day.
I mean, I'm glad
you're done, but...
It's even starting to snow!
[YUKIO] It's a nice evening.
It is? But Yukio, I thought
you didn't like the night
'cause it's lonely and stuff.
--[YUKIO] Maki.
--Huh?
Try to get along
with your mother.
She just wants the
best for you, okay?
Y-Yukio?
Come on, stop it.
Y-You sound like you're
about to die or something.
Excuse us. It is time, Boss.
Yes, thank you.
Very well, let's
get things started.
I... I, uh...
Take care of yourself, okay?
I-I don't get it...
What's going on
here? Are you...?
Wait!
Yukio!
Yukio...
[YUKIO] Have you been able to
find out where Balalaika is?
[GINJI] No, not yet.
They've done a good job
of covering their tracks.
It's not going
to be an easy task.
We've got our people
looking for them.
I don't care how
careful they are,
we'll spot them sooner or later.
[YUKIO] I'd also like you
to send someone to Azabu,
the Russian Embassy,
and anywhere else
they'd be likely to use.
We have ties to
a political group
that operates in that area.
I'll call in a favor with them.
Shouldn't we be sending soldiers
to Narita and Haneda
Airports as well, Boss?
I'm sure they anticipated
our counterattack.
I don't believe it was ever
their intention to flee.
What she wants... is a war.
[YOSHIDA] Boss. Would you like
me to pull over somewhere?
No. That's fine.
I guess I'll have
to get used to this.
--Mr. Yoshida.
--[YOSHIDA] Y-Yes?
I haven't thanked you
yet for the other day.
What you said at the meeting,
I'll never forget you did that.
But, Boss, that was nothing!
Still, I thank you.
What is this, a wake?!
She's here because she doesn't
want to see this family die.
She doesn't want Kousa
to swallow us up,
then throw us out once
they get what they want!
This young lady's putting her
life on the line for you!
If ever there was a time
for you to show your loyalty,
then it should be
right here and now!
You weren't even
involved to begin with,
but you vowed to avenge our boss
as if you were one of our own.
Any yakuza who would not
risk his life for you
is a true coward.
[GINJI] Boss. It's time
for me to begin.
You should go. I'll meet
you at home later.
Ginji.
Before you go, promise me
you'll be careful tonight.
Of course. You have my word.
[phone beeping]
[MAKARUSKA] No answer,
Boss. I'm sorry.
I can't reach Balalaika
or any of the other members.
Then call again
and don't talk to me
until you've reached someone.
But they've left the hotel
and we don't have any idea
where they've gone.
Perhaps it would be wise to
ask for advice from Moscow--
[screaming]
What makes you think I
need direction from them?!
When I say try again, you do it!
Ahh. Damn it!
That bitch must've
turned them against me.
What other reason would
Slevnin have to betray me?!
I don't get it, Boss.
Why would she frame us?
[LAPTEV] It's not "us," it's me!
She's always hated the KGB.
Not to mention the GRU
and the Nomenklatura.
There's a long line of people
who've been crushed
by that woman!
She's a real Trotskyite!
What did Slevnin say about her?
Get down!
[LAPTEV] It's the yakuza!
[RUSSIAN 1] Is it over?
[GINJI] Where are you hiding,
Baryshnikov?
That's right. Let's see
if I can get you to dance.
All he's got is that sword!
What are you waiting
for?! Kill him!
[GINJI] Mister. Where do
you think you're going?
You see, I need you here
to answer some questions.
First of all, where can I find
that lady boss of yours?
Wait! Please don't kill me!
I don't know anything!
I was framed!
Really? So, you don't
know anything, huh?
In that case, it seems
you're of no use to me.
[SOLDIER 1] Tell those Ivans
to make the envelopes
a bit thicker.
They could have me
locked up for this shit.
That's gotta be worth
something, y'know.
Tell 'em yourself, dip-shit.
Huh?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
She'll be pissed.
Alright, let's get going.
I can finally ditch
that Tokarev.
Can't leave home
without my boys.
What's wrong?
It's started.
[REVY] Yeah, the slaughter.
I'm sure she's
laughing her ass off.
A real war, just
like she wanted.
--[ROCK] That girl...
--Huh?
Revy, I have to do something.
Please, we have to
at least warn her.
[REVY] Don't be stupid, Rock.
We're here working
for the Russians,
so what do you think
that makes us?
As far as that girl's concerned,
you and I are enemies.
[ROCK] Please, Revy!
If she's connected to the
Washimine Clan in any way,
she's gonna end up being
dragged into this!
We've both seen how
Balalaika handles things,
so don't tell me I'm wrong!
Yukio's not like us!
--Hey, Rock.
--She's just a kid!
Enough!
This is not Roanapur!
It's different here!
[REVY] You really think so?
How is it any different?
Like it or not,
she's in our world now.
And Balalaika will
sort things out here
like she does in Roanapur.
It'd be the same anywhere.
But still, I...
[REVY] Come on, Rock.
You're on the edge of a cliff
and once you jump off,
you're traveling
in one direction.
Your AmeriPass is expired
and the Greyhound
will never travel
this road again.
What I'm trying to say is
this is your country.
Your home, Rock.
And... I just wanna make
sure you understand that.
I do... but...
[REVY] You know what? Fuck it.
Forget what I just said.
There's something
I just remembered.
I'm just a hired gun on
this trip. In other words,
the only reason I'm here
is to protect your life,
not to interfere with it and try
and change your mind and stuff.
So, lead the way... Boss.
[wind whistling]
[BELLHOP] Uh, thank you.
So, you don't want any
phone calls coming through
unless they're from
the Russian Embassy.
That's correct... right,
Miss... um... Vlatinera?
That's right.
Thanks for everything.
Um, if there's anything else,
please don't hesitate to ask.
That boy is at the peak
of his adorableness.
Now then, Sergeant.
Yes, Kapitän .
The recon team report.
As of now, "Attack Point Two"
is in stage yellow.
They've set up a security
perimeter around Kousa's office.
The police here
are actually skilled.
Yes. Police who don't accept
bribes are always competent.
It's a matter of
quality, Sergeant.
Have you seen the news?
[BORIS] Yes. It would
appear that comrade Laptev
did a fine job.
Indeed he did. For a
useless KGB agent,
he reconnoitered
the enemy quite well.
His successor in Tokyo will
be Bulgazivry the Priest.
I hear he's very skilled
with the abacus.
Not surprisingly, they've
left the violence up to us.
So, let's get to work, Sergeant.
[YOSHIDA] That was
a job well done, Miss.
They should be contacting the
office with the results shortly.
Right. Thank you very
much, Mr. Yoshida.
Oh, ah, Miss...
I'm sorry about what
happened at your school.
I knew it would
cause you trouble,
but I didn't feel
we had a choice, so I...
I understand. It was
something she was going
to have to find out
about eventually.
The truth is you may
have done me a big favor
by showing up.
Thanks again, Mr. Yoshida.
[YOSHIDA] Please, Miss,
you're being much too kind!
In any case, it's getting
too cold for you out here,
so please, go inside and...
Well, look who it is! You're
here sooner than I expected!
It's too bad really. I was
hoping to surprise you guys!
Chaka! What the hell
are you doing here?!
You were given your station!
--Why aren't you there?!
--[CHAKA] Come on, man. Ease up.
Think of the situation.
Isn't that right, Miss?
[YOSHIDA] You need to learn
your place, goddamn it!
This would never be
allowed and you know it!
You listening, you little...
Chaka? Are these... your guys?
[CHAKA] Mr. Yoshida,
you know what?
You're too... trusting.
[YUKIO gasps]
Did that hurt? Sorry
about that, old timer.
Fuck you!
[CHAKA] How should
I put this...?
My loyalty costs money and
the family can't afford to pay.
It doesn't really matter if
it's Kousa or the Russians.
If we can offer her as a gift,
they'll welcome us with
open arms. Right, Miss?
Miss. Get outta here!
You know something... you're a
real pain in the ass, old-timer!
So, fuck it. I'm done with you.
Here, have some more!
Hey!
That hurt!
--Dumb slut.
--Aw, you're fucked.
Hanada can be pretty
scary when he snaps.
[THUG 1] That bitch
is in for it now.
[HANADA] Don't you know
you can hurt someone
when you run into 'em like that?
You listening to me?!
I said it hurt!
I'm serious, you little
fucking slut!
You sure there's nothing
you wanna say to me?!
How about "I'm sorry"?! Or
"I apologize"?! Let's hear it!
Now get up!
[CHAKA] Hey, hey, Hanada.
--Huh?
--I don't remember telling you
to beat the shit outta her.
If you start acting up...
...I'll fucking kill you.
Looks like I owe you
an apology, Yukio.
The thing is about this bunch,
there's a lot of guys here
who have a hard time
controlling their tempers.
[THUGS laughing]
[OKAZAKI] Now who's
the bitch, Hanada?
Well, at least now you know.
You better learn
to follow orders
or it could get dangerous.
Hey, Rock, d'ya think
this is the only entrance?
Revy, we're uninvited
guests here.
The backdoor would be--
No, Rock. Haven't you noticed?
I don't know about you,
but I'd recognize
that smell anywhere.
Footprints! Oh, no! Yukio!
Don't just rush in, Rock!
Yukio!
Damn it.
[REVY] Was it Balalaika?
If it was, Yukio would be
lying here right next to him.
As far as they're concerned,
that girl has no value
as a hostage.
She uses a Stechkin. The other
guys use military autos
like Variags. Maybe even AKs.
But I'm looking around and
I don't see a single casing.
They used a revolver.
[REVY] Yep. Poor old Yoshida.
Now the breeze blows
right through his body.
Look at that. This hole is huge.
It was high caliber. Any idiot
using a gun like this
has gotta be some
show-off wannabe
who's beyond all salvation.
I can think of one guy who
fits that description exactly.
It's him! But why
betray his own?
That's strange.
Why don't I smell
any gunpowder?
That's right, Jumbo.
My gun had nothing to do
with how Yoshida bought
the farm, alright.
Mr. Ginji. We didn't do this.
And Hotel Moscow's not
responsible for this either.
We came here to try and get
Yukio away from the fighting
and we ended up
walking into this.
You have to trust me.
Revy and I...
...we're not involved
with what Hotel Moscow's...
Wait, Mr. Ginji!
Please just hear me out!
I didn't hear a car pull up
when you got here.
Which means, you came
here on foot... alone.
There are tread marks
everywhere out front.
Judging by that and the number
of footprints in the house,
we know that whoever
did this came in numbers
and from a distance.
Tell me... Do you
plan to go alone?
This doesn't concern you.
We don't have time!
It was one of your
own who did this!
Think about it.
He knows you'll
be coming for her
and he's gonna be
prepared for that.
He's expecting you.
But what if a skilled gunman
happened to be at your side?
He wouldn't have
accounted for that.
So, you want to know
where he is, do you?
[REVY] Every station
is just someone talking.
Isn't there any music?
I don't have a fuckin'
clue what they're saying.
Try FEN.
[REVY] The last couple
songs they played
have been fuckin' lousy.
Yeah! Guitar Wolf!
I love these guys!
This ain't no fuckin' J-Pop.
Take a left at the
next intersection.
Why are you helping us?
It doesn't make any sense.
I'm helping 'cause she
doesn't belong in this world.
She deserves better.
I don't want her to be robbed of
a chance to live a normal life.
[GINJI] If someone had
just given her a chance,
maybe she would've
had a normal life.
If only she'd been
given the chance...
[CHAKA] Strike!
All I need is one more point.
What d'ya say, Okazaki?
The top or the bottom?
[CHAKA] Ahh... I say bottom.
[OKAZAKI] Alright, but once
she's completely naked,
the game's over.
[CHAKA] Yeah. There's plenty
of things we can do with her,
like shaving her bush.
That would be hilarious!
[REVY] It's the Dark Tower.
The knight has arrived
to save the princess.
Rock. Jumbo and
I'll take the front.
You sneak in from the back door.
But what should I do?
[REVY] Simple, Rock. Just cover
our backs when we need you to.
That's it.
Revy! You barely know him!
--Can you really--
--[REVY] No problem.
Once the fighting begins,
our instincts will take
over and that'll be it.
No preparation necessary.
It's just how we're made.
[REVY] You're spending
the night in Hell's Motel.
Better start running
'cause the boogeyman's
coming to eat you up!