[ROCK] Okay,
I've got one for ya.
Let me see if
I can remember it...
Okay, how many Polacks does it
take to change a lightbulb?
I'm guessing one to
hold the lightbulb
and 99 to turn the house.
Isn't that it?
[ROCK] Let's see...
So, the Pope says to
this guy who's dressed
like he's homeless--
"I thought I told ya to
get out of here yesterday."
Yeah, good one.
Do me a favor--just shut
up and drive, will ya?
Ah! This sucks!
This really fucking sucks!
Why am I stuck playing
fuckin' errand boy with you?
That's what I
really wanna know.
That lousy prick, Dutch.
I hope he dies.
What? Why me?
I have to work on
the boat all day.
And Benny's gonna be busy
with the electronics.
Oh, right. Revy's just
laying around in here room.
You can take her with you.
Hmm. Take Revy...?
That a problem?
No...
But I can tell you she's
not gonna wanna do it.
[DUTCH] Sounds like something
that you two need to deal with.
And it's got nothing
to do with me or the job.
Start in this neighborhood.
First, head to Rowan
"Jackpot" Pigeon's place
on Rachiada Street.
Welcome, my sweet Rebecca.
And here I thought
you'd given up on me.
So, you finally decided to
shake that fine ass of yours
in an S&amp;M show. I'd knew
you'd come around, baby.
Fuck off, will ya, Rowan?
The only reason I'm here
is 'cause of my job.
So, don't start with that.
I'm not into being tied up
or tying other people up.
You haven't changed.
You look so good,
you'd be great for either.
I'm telling you, girl.
It's a real shame.
So, what brings you here today?
Right. Regarding the goods
you ordered from--
You ordered booze
for this place, right?
We've got 1,500 bottles for ya.
They're in Warehouse Five
at the harbor.
Now this is what
I'm talkin' about.
What?! Tax sure has
gone up on these!
It's killing me! How's a brother
supposed to make a dime? Shit.
Oh, yeah--what's
up with your friend
who looks like he ain't never
seen a pair of titties before?
[REVY] Oh, him.
He's the rookie at our place.
He's got nowhere else to go,
so we had no choice
but to take care of him.
Hmm. Looks like you're in
for a rough ride, brother.
You ever need anything,
don't be shy.
Later, Rowan. And don't forget
about the money, alright?
So, the shipment's
going to be late, is it?
You could've told me
that over the phone,
but instead, you came
all the way here?
[REVY] Hey, I hear ya.
Tell that to Dutch.
Makes no difference. I've gotta
finish fifteen of these today,
so I won't be getting out
anytime soon. No.
Yep, I should've gotten
a part-timer to do it.
I'm seriously losing my mind.
I have a meeting tonight, too.
Some more idiots selling drugs
without permission again.
What a pain in the balls.
Hold on a sec. Is she
taking it up the ass?!
Sure is.
Oh, if you guys hear
anything about that,
I'd appreciate it
if you let me know.
I'll thank you properly.
Yeah, if we hear anything.
I'm sure we'll be
back pretty soon.
Good luck with the rest.
Somebody shoot me.
Ah! This sucks!
This really fucking sucks!
Why am I stuck playing
fuckin' errand boy with you?
That's what I
really wanna know.
Well, only one more stop
and we'll be done.
Let's see...
Receive firearms on order
from Sister PW Deegan
of the Ripoff Church.
[PARROT] Hello.
[REVY] Hey, you old bitch!
It's Rebecca from
the Lagoon Company!
Open this fucking door,
you old skank! Hello?
[PARROT] Hello. Hello.
Open the door, you old skank.
--Hello. Hello.
--[REVY] Hey!
Open the door, you old skank.
[EDA] You've always
been too damn loud.
Just put those in the
shed for now, you got it?
But these are cleaned items.
Are you sure that's
where you want them?
[EDA] It's okay. It's what
the sister wanted.
Hey, Two Hands,
that's the chapel.
I can't let your kind
walk through there.
Over here. Follow me.
[SISTER YOLANDA] Oh my.
This certainly is a surprise.
I never thought I'd see the day
when Dutchy-boy would
send you on an errand.
That's none of your business.
Now why don't you tell us if
you got the goods we ordered,
Sister?
Right. New items
from Eastern Europe,
arriving by way of Cambodia.
All but one item.
Unfortunately, we're
still waiting to receive
the Arwin 37 grenade
launcher you ordered.
Now don't kid around, Sister.
The reason we ordered
everything through you
is because we need all of
those items for the next job.
[SISTER YOLANDA] Well, quite
frankly, we do have the item.
It's just that a different
customer is saying
they need it immediately.
I'm sure you can see
my dilemma here.
However... Lagoon is a good
customer, so I wouldn't mind
handing it over to you,
despite the inconvenience.
But, I'd like a
better deal for us
or a discount on your services.
[REVY] Don't fuck
with us, Sister.
Why don't you do the smart thing
and play this one by the book,
so everyone will be happy?
You wouldn't wanna count your
money with your feet, would ya?
I wouldn't make idle threats
if I were you, Rebecca.
If you insist, then why don't
you bring Dutchy-boy around?
That's all I have to say.
There's nothing before,
nothing after.
Step off, Eda, you
limp-wristed bitch.
Let's see how much you talk
with a hole in your head.
[ROCK slurping]
This is very good tea, Sister.
Sister... Um...
It's Sister Yolanda, young man.
It's been a very long
time since I've had tea
that wasn't from a teabag.
Is this W&amp;M? Or perhaps
this is Fortnum and Mason?
My. You're very
knowledgeable, aren't you?
You're right. This is W&amp;M.
There's nothing nicer
than a good cup of tea.
Yes. It takes a company
with that kind of history
and dedication to deliver
such flavor without fail.
Rock, will you shut the fuck up?
That's true for any company,
even if their products differ.
Am I right in saying that?
I don't quite see it.
What exactly are you
getting at, young man?
What is your point?
Are you trying to imply
that it's also true
for illegal firearms?
I'm afraid we won't have much of
a negation if you get too hasty.
I'm talking about the drugs.
That's what I'm
getting at, Sister.
Lately, drugs are
being distributed
outside the agreed upon routes.
Did you know that, Sister?
Hotel Moscow and other
mafia in the city
have made every effort
to find the source.
They've looked everywhere
they could think of.
But the culprits still
haven't been found.
And that's because
there's a blind spot.
Somewhere they
shouldn't have to look.
For instance, those who
can freely cross borders
under the auspices
of the church.
Or NGO members
who don't even know
they're being used as mules.
It strikes me that these
people are being overlooked.
Sister Eda,
why did you have those men leave
the clean linens in the shed?
Aren't cleaned items normally
taken to the living quarters?
[SISTER YOLANDA] Young man,
you can't make statements
based on mere conjecture.
You make it sound like
the stuff's coming
out of this place.
It's just a hypothesis.
Also, we could talk
about weapon shipments.
The amount of weapons entering
and leaving this place...
They don't seem to add up,
if you know what I mean.
That's easy to figure out
with a little research.
It was dangerously
easy to see, actually.
One last thing. The Lagoon
Company is, of course,
on friendly terms
with Hotel Moscow.
But I wouldn't say
we necessarily
work together, either.
I see your point. If you
improve your timing a bit,
then you'll really take shape.
--Eda.
--Yes, Sister?
[SISTER YOLANDA] He's a bit
rough, but he passes.
Add the Arwin to the list.
[EDA] Okay.
Dutch-boy has a good eye.
I can't imagine
where he found you.
It's almost time for mass.
I apologize, but you'll
have to be on your way.
Young man, come visit
us again sometime soon.
[REVY] You got lucky this time.
Go to hell, bitch.
My dear. You could
learn a thing or two
from that young man, you know?
In the end, waving your
gun around doesn't work.
You'll never do good
business like that.
Go fuck yourself.
[ROCK] Oh man.
We should've timed this a
little better. It's crowded.
Let's eat before it gets cold.
I don't wanna eat.
Try it. A good meal
will make you feel better.
Why don't you give me the keys?
I'll go home on my own.
If you do that,
I can't get back.
Why don't you walk?
[ROCK] That's not gonna happen.
Know what?
You should go back to Japan.
You're just not
cut out for this.
Well, you're the
one who invited me.
[REVY] Yup. Really
fucked up there.
[ROCK] I wonder... Maybe you
can tell me who kept the church
from becoming
a bloodbath today.
It's just like
the old lady said--
you can't solve
everything with a gun.
I'm warning you.
You better watch
what you say, Rock.
[ROCK] You've been like this
ever since the submarine.
--Was it our talk?
--[REVY] Who cares?!
I told you never to
talk about that again.
Revy...
I'm not gonna apologize anymore.
I must have misheard you.
You better hope I did.
Otherwise, you're
a fucking dead man.
[ROCK] Is that so?
In that case,
I'll say it again--
I didn't make any mistake!
I've nothing to apologize for!
That's what I'm saying.
That's a shame.
You just stepped
on a non-negotiable,
big-ass fucking landmine.
Like I said... a real shame.
There's just one last
thing I need to ask you--
what do you want on your
tombstone, cocksucker?
Why don't you write, "There's
no cure for a fool with a gun."
Well, Rock, goodbye.
See ya.
See that?
There are some problems
you can't solve with a gun.
You bastard!
Who are you calling
"bastard"? My name is Rock!
You got that?!
Fuck! I've had more
than my fill of this shit!
I've had enough!
I thought I was done with
kissing ass for a living,
but here I am at
the ends of the earth,
now I'm supposed to
be kissing your ass?
What kind of sick joke is this?!
You fucking spoiled,
arrogant son of a--
It's Rock! And "arrogant"?
Who the hell are you kidding?!
Why don't you try taking
a good look at yourself?
Aren't you supposed to be some
kind of outlaw? A wild pirate?
But as soon as you
open your mouth,
all I ever hear you talking
about is "money, money, money."
You think you'd be some hard-ass
villain after the big prize,
but you end up scavenging
off corpses instead.
Is there any fucking limit
to how greedy you can be?
Are you really that pathetic?
Don't you have any
pride left in you?!
You really think you can
judge me, mister white-collar?
What do you know
about my life, huh?
What the hell do
you know about me?!
Go on, why don't you tell me?
A guy like you who spent his
life in a safe little bubble
has no idea what
I've been through!
[ROCK] You're right. There's
no way I could know that.
I'm not you, after all.
But still, let me ask you this--
other than the fact
that I'm white-collar,
what do you know about me?
It doesn't matter who
you are or how you live.
We all have to suffer, right?
You have no intention
of understanding that.
Instead of owning up to things,
you'd rather play the part
of the tragic heroine.
That's the most cowardly
thing about you, Revy.
Shut up! It's convenient
for you to see it like that!
Goddamn it! This isn't
one of those cheap,
picaresque Hollywood films
you love to talk about!
There are no heroes
in this life!
And what's all this about
pride? Fuck your pride!
Look around you. It's shit
as far as the eye can see.
I hate to break it to you, but
there is no fuckin' Robin Hood.
[ROCK] If there's
no Robin Hood,
then why don't you
become Robin Hood?
It's gotta be better than
feeling sorry for yourself.
Crying about your hard life.
Shut up! Shut the
fuck up, damn it!
I'm serious... I'll kill you.
Then do it.
Keep chasing your tail like
a dog if that's what you want.
If you kill me here, then you'll
just end up proving me right.
That's all I know how to do!
[ROCK] Did you forget, Revy?
The reason I ended up here...
My bosses calmly
cut my life away.
I was an afterthought.
And all for what?
To protect their dirty money,
their expense accounts,
their place at
the boardroom table.
When you first invited me in,
it was like waking up
from a long sleep.
My life had become
the rush-hour commute,
the fake laughing,
lowering my head,
risking my life
to score points.
And all of that was fine,
as long as I had a place
to drink after work
and a batting cage nearby.
And then, just like that,
none of it mattered anymore.
The one person who
shook me awake...
...the one who invited me in...
It was you, Revy.
What concerns me now is that
the one woman who showed me
all of this is acting just like
the people who betrayed me.
I'm not gonna stand by
and let that happen.
[REVY] I don't know what you're
talking about, goddamn it.
Ah, fuck it. You're a real
pain in the ass, you know that?
An idiot like you
won't live long.
We're both idiots and we've both
suffered. Just leave it at that.
I'm pretty sure you're the
biggest idiot here, dumbass.
--Gettin' mad!
--[REVY] Ooh, sounds scary.
What are you gonna do?
Write a memo or something?
[WATSAP]
Hey, you two!
Why don't you mind your
own fuckin' business?!
[WATSAP] Surprise, surprise.
I hear someone's making
a ruckus at the market
and it turns out
to be you again.
Revy, this town isn't your
private shooting gallery.
Discharging your weapon without
any concern for who's watching
and I'm the poor slob
who's gotta put out the fire.
[REVY] Isn't that why we give
you all those fat envelopes?
Do I complain to you
about my job, Chief?
[WATSAP] I'm not
saying don't do it,
I'm just saying do it
where no one's gonna see ya.
As long as you do that,
I don't care if you kill people
or play hide the apple,
for that matter.
Out of sight,
out of mind means that
I don't have to
cancel my golf dates
and I can work on my
short game in peace.
Anyway, I'm bringing you in.
There's paperwork to be
taken care of on our side.
Fine by me.
Damn engine is
giving me trouble.
Drown your sorrows?
[DUTCH] Thanks.
Hey Chief, don't go
stealing our car.
[WATSAP] I don't want that piece
of shit. Come get it later.
[REVY] Hey, Rock.
Just one thing.
Let me ask you this and there
won't be any more trouble...
So, um, I just wanna know
which side you wanna be on.
[ROCK] Me?
I'm right here where
I'm sitting, Revy.
I'm not anywhere else.
Rock, give me a light.
[ROCK] Light?
The cop's got the lighter.
What are you talking about?
You got one in your mouth.
What a fucked up day that was.
No shit.
[REVY] Damn.
I'm so tired. I wanna
go home and sleep.
[ROCK] Yeah.
[GARCIA] They're planning
to sell me off somewhere,
aren't they?
[REVY] Even if there
is no justice,
the world's gonna
keep on turning.