I don't trust that look on
your face... It's weird.
I don't know what
you're talking about...
There's nothing weird about it.
I always look this
way when I ask for a favor.
You want my help... again?
Yeah. This is my "favor face".
It's true we both came
from similar backgrounds.
You and I are a lot alike.
The difference is
who we encountered in life.
Perhaps... It's not
too late for you...
What a load of crap.
What happens is
just what happens.
Like how my guns will always
beat your lame-ass footwork.
I know that for a fact.
And the last one
standing is always the one
who has the most power. Simple.
You want me to use this gun...?
That's right.
This gun will help us
bring the game to an end.
You should check your reflection
next time you sneer at someone.
You know what you look like?
Like a skeleton... dancing at
the Festival of the Dead.
Yeah, that's perfect! Ya fuckin'
nailed it, sweet cheeks!
I may be from
the Land of the Dead,
but I'm a fuckin'
well-armed skeleton!
That's where we're all from.
Me, your head maid,
those soldiers... everyone...
So, chiquita...
Welcome to my graveside,
leave a bottle of tequila and
some marigolds. In return...
I'll leave a chocolate skull
as an offering for your soul,
seeing as how
you're fixing to die here,
you pathetic little shit.
You ladies ready?!
Cuz, here comes my cock!
Yeah, that's right...
now start sucking!
So I talked for
a while with Mr. Rock.
And I talked to
that loco gunslinger.
I'm sick of letting them
push us around all the time.
Yeah... Um, be careful...
Young Master!
This feels great!
What in the world are
you doing, Young Master?!
Here, take my hand...
You too, Fabiola!
This isn't funny!
Catch!
Water fight...!
Are those dolphins?
Yeah, Benny.
Those are dolphins.
You know... Rock's okay but
how's Revy doing these days?
Well... she was chatting
with the little maid earlier...
But then she went
into the forward cabin
and now she won't come out.
Fuck...!
Everything's fine, Fabiola.
Uh... What is?
Me, I mean.
You thought I was starting
to lose it, didn't you?
No! I'd never think that...!
No more hesitating.
And no more letting other
people tell me what to do.
Fabiola, you saw
Roberta too, didn't you?
Yes, but the truth is...
she's in a lot of torment now.
She may have started out
intending to
avenge your father...
But I doubt if
she even remembers
why she wants to
kill those men anymore.
Roberta's confused... She's
losing her grip on reality...
She thinks this will
atone for what she's done,
for all her past sins.
Our head maid
is very unyielding.
Murder is a sin to her
and she believes it needs to be
punished harshly
no matter what the cost.
Fabiola, listen carefully.
This is important.
Somehow I'm gonna
save Roberta. I swear it.
And no matter what
that salary man says...
I'll do it on my terms,
the way I want it to happen.
And even... If you went back to
Venezuela and left me alone...
I would still go on by myself
to save her and bring her back!
I'll become her strength...
And I'll make sure
that she never falls again!
Young Master...!
I don't want you to think
of me as your maid right now.
So just listen to me.
Roberta might never get better.
In fact, by now she's
probably too far gone to save.
This isn't make-believe.
Even if she does come back with
us, she'll still be tormented!
I don't care. I'm doing it.
I see. Your mind's made up.
To be honest, I thought
you were going to quit.
Especially when you
saw how disturbed she was.
No matter how capable
and kind-hearted you are,
you've grown-up sheltered.
I assumed you'd
have gone home by now.
Instead... you're
actually sticking with this.
Yes, I refuse to let
her die alone in a ditch as
she fights by herself
against those awful men.
Okay, let's save her!
The two of us can do it.
Together, it's possible.
Right. May God protect us.
Yes, may God protect us.
Fuck... Raised in
a loving family...?
I hate hearing
that fuckin' shit...
You little whore...!
Where I grew up, there wasn't
anyone who gave a shit about me.
Fucking hate him!
Fucking, fuck, fuck...
Cocksucker...!
Mouthy bitch!
F... fuck you! Fucker!
You bastard! I'll kill you!
I'll kill you! God damn you!
Fuck! You...
you... fuck...!
Becky! Get me a
drink, you little bi--
Go to hell!
Damn it... I wanted
to forget all that shit.
We're entering the Mekong
Delta right on schedule.
When it gets light, we'll
see how the water has turned
from a lovely blue
to a lovely... brown.
These are my old
"brown water" stomping grounds,
but I thought it'd be better to
pass through
under cover of darkness.
Benny.
Yeah?
From here on, we'll need to rely
on our GPS and echo sounder.
Plus... we now have access to
a mining company's
latest survey data.
Sucks how we gotta crawl.
The river's so shallow here.
You know who's waiting for us
at the end of this
little trip, don't you?
The maid.
Yup.
I swear...
This is giving me a rash.
The Japanese man said that...
you wanted to see me down here.
Major, this is the
gun that you gave me.
You're never going
to forget how I hurt you.
You're never
going to forgive.
I can see it in your eyes.
Are you going to shoot me?
You sound like you
believe in justice, Major.
If you really are
a man of your word...
You'll listen to
what I have to say.
Alright...
You've had your say.
But... as the commanding officer
I alone am responsible for
what happened to you,
your father and your maid.
I want the opportunity to let my
men fight to protect themselves.
Is that acceptable?
Hey. What did you put
in the Young Master's head?
Okay, then... How about I tell
you what's supposed to happen.
Attention!
Gentlemen, we will reach
our area of operation
sometime tonight.
Rest assured that the enemy
who pursued us
in Roanapur will be there.
That is guaranteed.
Let nothing stand in
the way of your mission!
Shane!
That woman... isn't she
connected to this boy?
Yeah, and I'm taking
responsibility for that.
You're fighting
for justice, gentlemen,
give it your
very best. That is all.
You can't ask him to do that!
Then let me ask you this:
Can you win without
taking some kind of risk?
His risk... You've been planning
this from the very start.
I have. I mapped out all the
risks except for the Americans.
They're the only X factor.
When you reach
the end of the game
and you've factored in
everything except for luck,
that's when the
gambling is the sweetest.
That's... That's nothing but...
a load of fucking crap!
Here we are, people.
We're right on
the triple point border.
Welcome to the Golden Triangle.
A contested area where the
governments have no influence.
Thanks, Captain.
You can keep your thanks.
The bill's already been paid.
Get the fuck off my boat.
Sorry I said that.
This place gets to me.
Happy hunting!
Here's hoping it doesn't
come back to bite us in the ass.
Did Garcia head
out with the Major?
Uh, yeah... he did.
Great! That's just perfect!
We're going to hit
the jackpot on this one!
He lost this gamble, Benny.
"Mr. Chang" is
gonna lose this time.
Echo to Alpha. We've
reached the enemy line.
All clear.
Coordinates are fixed.
Roger that. Standby.
This is Delta. Two hundred
yards from the enemy line.
Alpha rogers that.
All teams, surround site
zero two three zero.
Delta rogers that.
Echo rogers that.
Okay. We gotta
get to the site too.
Major! Major! This is Delta!
We've got strange objects
in front of the village.
Strange objects? Describe.
Rods. There are numerous thirty
inch metal rods on the path.
Charlie, Echo, any
anomalies in your vicinity?
About thirty inches long...?
Echo here.
We confirm they're
at this location too.
Dozens of rod-like objects,
spaced roughly three feet apart.
They don't appear
to be wired to explosives.
This is Charlie. Rods around
the village entrance here, too!
That's strange.
Maybe they're a barrier...?
Shane!
What're they for?
Think maybe
they're religious totems
for the Shan or Wazu tribes?
I've never heard of that.
Young Master...
Yeah. She's already here.
She's ready.
Echo to Alpha. Come in, Major.
This is Alpha. We've
reached our lookout post.
But... something
doesn't seem right.
No movement detected.
Is it abandoned?
Looks that way, Major.
Alpha to Charlie.
What's your status to the east?
Charlie here. No activity.
I can see the plant,
but there's nobody here.
Ah, I got a body!
Echo to Alpha!
We got bodies here as well!
There are several
corpses near the gate.
Detecting a single
light source to the east.
Ray, we're too
far away from them.
Let's move!
Right behind you.
It's Package Romeo!
Positive ID on Package Romeo!
Listen up! The opium plants
are already out of action.
The only people here
are us and Package Romeo!
Package Romeo at
ten o'clock, moving fast!
She's headin' for the jungle!
Delta to Alpha! She's
stopped right in front of us.
She appears
to have a hostage!
Jesus! Target is
moving into the trees!
What's going on?
The target has a prisoner.
She just cut off his ear!
He's still alive,
he just screamed!
Who's the prisoner?
Must be Shi Yan.
He's the bait to draw us in.
Delta, is your
team closest to her?
Affirmative.
Okay, then follow her,
but don't get too close.
Track target's
location at all times.
Delta rogers that!
All teams,
move in and cover Delta.
Delta to Alpha.
Target is not visible!
Alpha to Echo.
Can you see her?
Echo here. Give me a minute.
I have target in sight. Shit!
Delta, come in!
Please respond!
I swear by the
Holy Santa Maria...
I will destroy all those...
who are full of sin!
She took out
Murdoch and Garraty!
This is Sniper Unit two!
We lost the target,
but she took a hit!
Goddamn her!
She's avoiding the body
armor and targeting our heads!
Did all teams copy that?
Except for team leaders,
everyone remove night goggles!
Put on your face-masks!
Prepare for close combat!
Get your facemasks on! Fast!
We're moving in to help Delta!
Let's go!
Echo to Alpha.
Echo, status report.
We found Shi Yan in the jungle.
Be careful! There
are gonna be booby traps.
I saw a helluva
lot of dirty tricks
and some vicious
fighting in Vietnam.
Made me pretty much an expert,
and then some,
on jungle warfare.
If this were Guadalcanal,
we'd be humping mortars.
If this were 'Nam we'd
burn down the whole jungle
with a sky full of napalm...
along with the people
we were trying to help...
Echo to Alpha. We've got a
detonator here.
Looks like a numerical code.
You'll be so distracted
disarming the damn thing,
Package Romeo will
just walk up on ya!
No... Hold on, Gardner!
The whole setup is
the trap! Get outta there!
Roger that!
Team Echo, Pull back now!
Lieutenant Gardner,
there's something over there...
This is Echo leader.
She's killed Wright!
The shot penetrated his vest!
Package Romeo is
using flechette rounds!
She's firing
those rods with a musket!
Jesus Christ, she's hunting
us with a goddamn museum piece!
We saw the muzzle flash!
Fuckin' A, we got her scent!
Let's move it!
All those rods
she's been planting
in the jungle
are a message for us.
No one's gettin'
out of here alive.
All teams, slowly
pull out of the area.
Don't let your guard down.
Sanchez, get into position.
Sniper Team here.
We're covering the retreat.
Damn it...
I can't get outta here with all
these fucking wires she's laid!
Okay. Hold and
prepare for an attack.
She's got the teams in
the jungle trapped like rats.
Which direction is
she gonna hit them from?
Sniper Team, be careful!
She's still headed your way.
Aw, shit!
That's a direct hit.
I aimed for her leg because
I didn't wanna kill her...
And she got up and kept running!
Nice try.
Your tactics...
They won't work.
She's become a wounded tiger!
Let's go.
Listen, once Team Alpha gets
here and can provide cover,
we're gonna get the hell out!
We just have to
hang on 'til then!
Aw, shit...
Fuck these!
Come on, you bitch!
God damn you...!
Sanchez, where is she?
Come in! Return
to base immediately!
Your baby foxes
are dropping like flies.
I'm gonna skin all
their little coats!
The hunt isn't
over yet!
It's her.
Yeah.
You... crazy... bitch...!
Roberta... Roberta!
Can you hear me?
I finally caught
up with you, Roberta.
Listen carefully. I'm
going to tell you where I am.
Please, come to me.
I'll be waiting for you.
Fuck it...
Fine, I get it!
I know exactly what I am.
Hey, Revy. It's almost time.
Won't be long
until this is all over.
Who gives a shit?
I've been working myself
up over a lot of fucking crap
that I tried my
hardest to forget...
And it's all your fault!
Yeah... You know something?
I feel like everyone is dancing
on the palm of my hand, Revy.
Like I control the
fate of everyone in that city.
What's going on with you?
Jesus... maybe that mouthy
little twit was right after all,
you've totally changed.
Rock, you've spent
too much time in Roanapur.
That shithole of a city
has messed with your head.
Once this job is done...
get the fuck out.
What are you talking about?
The end is in sight here.
It's almost over.
I don't know who
the hell you are anymore...
Young Master...
Yes, Fabiola, I know.
I'm pretty scared, too.
I don't know what'll happen.
I'm not sure what Senor
Rock told you, Young Master...
But I know you can
do this. I have faith!
It won't be God who saves her.
You're the real savior here.
I believe in you.
Thank you...
It'll be morning before long.
Once the sun's up the opium army
will send out their day patrols
and we'll know
what happened last night.
But by then,
this game will be over.
You keep going on
about this game, Rock.
How can you be so sure
you have this figured out?
Yeah. It'll be
over in seconds.
And then everything
will be settled.
Come on, do you
even hear yourself?
Revy! I see it.
I know what's going
to happen down this path.
Young Master...!
What's that fox doing here?!
Master Garcia, I can't
tell if you're really here or...
not here, anymore.
Time is so hazy now...
I can hear the dead,
they speak to me day and night!
I don't even know
if I'm dead or alive.
It's all the same...
I just can't tell...
But it's okay! I'll be
fine once I've taken revenge!
Then I can go
back to the manor!
Roberta.
Who is this for?
All this time I
never cared about revenge.
Despite my constant defiance,
Chang let me carry out my plan
and actually
leave with Garcia. Why?
And Balalaika went
along with Chang's wishes
and let Roberta easily
escape rather than kill her.
Again, why?
Simple. Chang's goal wasn't
just about hiding Roanapur
from the eyes of the world...
He also wanted to use Roberta
to break Gray Fox's will.
This entire
region produces drugs
and Roanapur is the
transit port that moves them.
Chang wanted Roberta
to attack the soldiers
to teach them a lesson...
To prevent the Americans from
bringing justice to
the Golden Triangle.
That... was his plan.
I changed it.
Rock, what's the point?
What the hell did
you get out of all this?
That's not true,
it does matter!
Those sinners killed your
father! They broke your heart!
They destroyed
everything important to me!
Young Master,
I have to kill him...!
No, Roberta, you're wrong.
No matter how many
people you condemn and punish,
you will never
atone for your sins.
It'll never be enough.
That's why you're not the one
who can bring this to an end.
Impossible!
You wouldn't...!
You would never kill someone!
There. Now it's over.
No! The Young Master would
never say that it's over!
This doesn't make amends!
Now no one will be saved.
You aren't the Young
Master, you're the enemy!
Is this your way of
taking revenge on Roanapur?
That city messes people up so
bad that when I hold out my hand
to try and help them...
I can't save even a single soul.
Are you still goin' on
about that girl in Tokyo...?
But this time, I'm going
to make a real difference
and that damned city's
not going to stop me.
I've thought hard
about this, Roberta.
What would I
say when I found you?
What words
should I tell you...?
But then... I realized that
words wouldn't be enough...
to change your mind.
Young Master!
I'm going to bet
everything on this.
Listen to me, Roberta. If
you trust me, then the bullet
I'm about to fire won't hurt
you. I guarantee you won't die.
Now let's finish this
never-ending dance of death...
Let's bring these
miserable stories of revenge
to an end with
this one gamble.
Roberta... are you ready?
And what'll happen to us...
You got someplace
else you wanna go?
Can't go back to your peaceful
hometown, you won't fit in.
I got a question...
You've been standing in the
twilight this whole time...
so why did you join the
rest of us in the darkness?
I wanted to win the game.
This was the
only way to finish it.
But... I'm fine with it.
You know why...?
Because... I realized this
is how you've always felt,
all the time, isn't it, Revy.
You don't fucking know me!
Oh my God...!
Young Master!
I... I couldn't stop myself!
I didn't mean to pull
the trigger, Master Garcia!
Roberta... look! Even though I
shot you... you're still alive.
You made it...
It's finally over, Roberta.
Master Garcia...
you're bleeding...!
It's all okay...
Young Master! I didn't mean to.
Where did my bullet hit you?!
Ray... Lower your weapon.
Sorry. You put on such a good
act I nearly started shooting.
Packed a worse
punch than I expected.
Get up! Stop
talking to your friend
and help the Young Master!
You live...?! How
are you still breathing?!
I'll send you to hell...!
Leave him...!
I killed him,
he's dead, the sin is mine.
You're a killer...
and so am I.
There are no winners here.
Our sins are all that are left.
But, I promise I will help
you bear that terrible burden.
I will support you as we live
out our lives together in peace.
Yes, Young Master...
Nice face. What
happened last night?
Hey, look, Rock.
Mission's over. They're back.
Well...? How'd it go? Did
the Americans get Shi Yan?
Yeah, looks like it.
There are three stretchers.
Great!
This really was
the best case scenario!
Way to go, Garcia!
Good work,
I knew you could do it!
Thanks to you...
I actually managed to do
some good and save someone!
Mr. Rock...
Hey...!
We were lucky...
We were extremely
lucky out there in the jungle.
And you...
You're lucky, too.
You're a bastard who took
advantage of the Young Master's
gentle nature and made him play
a round of Cambodian Roulette!
Look, it's just a blank!
Your magic trick was nothing but
a handful of fake brass bullets!
We're never
coming back here...
And I hope we never
have to see you again.
Stay and dance with the rest of
the dead in that cursed city
until God himself
turns away in disgust!
No matter what she says...
we managed to win one today...
I know we did.
Cathy, honey! Put enough
milk and sugar in that coffee
to make a stack
of pancakes, ya hear?!
Boss, you wanna get diabetes?
C'mon, sweetheart,
you only get to live once.
So the Director went
to a private luncheon
with the NSA
advisor to the President.
We're going to clear all this up
at the next security meeting...
But I do know
we're getting jurisdiction
and custody of Shi Yan.
That much is official.
Goodness, I bet that
made him a little upset.
He let loose with a whole parade
of four letter words
in that French restaurant!
Marvelous!
I know!
He didn't know
who he was messing with.
Y'goddamn right!
Man, you look like shit.
Courtesy of Chang.
Apparently it's our bonus.
Didn't see that coming.
It's been months,
and it seems like it's
business as usual in Roanapur.
Money and guns
never go out of style.
That's not gonna
change anytime soon.
Somewhere out there.
Someone else won the bet.
I didn't save anyone.
It's gonna hurt if you keep
looking at that city
with life in your eyes.
But hey, that's
the path you've chosen.
Do what you gotta do so
you don't become a real corpse.
Bang!
You came pretty
close back there...
Yeah, I did.
But this
wasn't the time, Revy.
Maybe... someday...