I can't. You know
how I make my living!
If I fuckin' squeal, I'm done!
Right back atcha. You know how
I make my living, right Leroy?
Squeal, piggy, squeal. Squeal.
In nineteen-forty, the Japanese
built a huge bunker complex.
They planned to
fight to the last soldier.
Hide your ass in there
and no one'll find ya.
Now we know where she is.
Hey! Ya maniac!
Leroy's an easy nut to crack.
Information's not free though.
The tab's going
on the kid's bill.
I just "reminded" him that
the maid wasn't paying
him enough to be a hero.
You mean--
You found Roberta?
That's where we're headed.
Caxton! It's Will!
In here!
Something's definitely
wrong. I can feel it.
I sent a couple of men
to check out the perimeter.
They just got back.
Copy that.
For several hours now
our lines have been clicking
indicating someone
is tapping us.
Here's the latest intel on
the target's location
and the new game plan.
It's from Brigadier General
Wilder. The operation is a go.
Finish making your report.
Sir, the approaches at Chalquam
and Manthey Streets have
been closed
due to construction.
However, it did not look like
there was any work being done.
There are no street vendors
or prostitutes in the
immediate vicinity, sir.
From here to the
town perimeter there are
roughly nine guard
posts and four foot patrols.
Good job. Prepare for
Operation: Street-Cleaner.
That's it.
You should get back
before the shit
hits the fan, Will.
We're across from the
hotel Abrego told us about.
Copy that.
Hmm, so let's see,
we've got the Americans, FARC,
and the local dickwads that
the maid hired to stir shit up.
I think we're gonna
have a war in the hood here.
Stop the car!
Revy, where're you going?!
I know we're in a rush,
but we could use some help!
What the hell?! Phone been
ringing forever, you guys!
You two are so sad!
Hi, hi!
Hey, Chinglish! Want a job?
You'll get to kill
a whole lot of dipshits!
I be happy to
skin you for free, slut.
Jesus, nice fuckin' attitude!
You're the one
who attacked me!
It's being bankrolled by a
stinking rich South American.
How much it pay?
Charlie to Alpha.
Current status: D-Four.
Looks like a group of
armed men coming your way.
Keep your heads up.
Roger that, Charlie.
Bravo and Charlie Teams,
prepare to move out.
I have no idea what kind of
giant clusterfuck
we're caught up in,
but the time for
sittin' on our asses is over.
Gentlemen,
time to earn your pay.
D-one here.
Armed civilians are entering
the target building now.
We're here
for Rosarita Cisneros.
Until we spot
the Bloodhound herself,
no one is to
leave their position.
Roger that.
The snitch said
this is where that
guido we're supposed
to whack is hiding.
Are you sure he
said the second floor?
Leroy always gives
us the straight shit.
This is the place alright.
On three: one, two, thr--!
Cease fire!
I'm gonna blow the
Claymores. Everyone, down!
Holy fuck, who's
blowing shit up?!
Everyone who went
upstairs is dead, man!
Don't just stand there,
you prick! Come on!
Fuck me!
What happened up there?
Hallway's empty. No one's here.
They're gone, man!
Shit! Even the walls are gone!
That's so messed!
What's going on?
Shane, heads up!
Enemy sniper!
She's on top of the billboard!
Everyone, take cover!
Major, what do you
think we're up against here?!
Don't know!
Wright and Horner,
lay down suppressive fire!
Everyone else,
move out on the double!
Go, go, go!
Shit, we didn't
make it in time!
Dammit, she's got some
serious fucking toys, too!
I gonna have to
charge you guys more.
This look like
real war zone to me!
If we can
still hear fighting,
then that means
Roberta is alive!
Garcia.
Yes?
Dutch said that if it ever
came to this I was to pull back.
But if you really wanna
to see this through to the end,
I won't abandon you.
I'm going. Roberta needs
my help. I won't let her down.
That quite well said.
Rich boy have heart of warrior.
Target's location spotted. She's
on an office building roof.
I am deploying my team now.
Wait, Garcia. Take this.
No, it's for later. Read it
in case you lose your way
and you don't
know what to do next.
He isn't coming? Why not?
He's not cut out for this.
He's made for sittin'
in the sun with a cool drink.
Let's go, troops.
In that case, the Young Master's
shouldn't be here either.
Back at the bar, that was
your first time, wasn't it?
What?
I could tell that was
the first time you'd ever
shot at people, for real.
You were in an all-out
gunfight with those assholes,
but you didn't
kill a single person
that entire time, did you?
Don't look at
me like that, I know.
Here's a tip for ya.
Try to think of them
as cardboard targets.
They're just a bunch
of crappy old cut-outs.
If you can pull that
trick off and stay alive,
you'll be an
honest to god gunslinger.
Thank you, but I think
I'll pass on being a--
They're right there!
Now! Cross over!
Move, she's reloading!
This is D-one!
We're engaging the enemy!
We've got her cornered!
We're in trouble,
we've got no cover!
Get over there and
help them, D-three.
Bloodhound's on the move!
Madre de Dios.
She's in pursuit of another
group! They're up ahead of us!
Rendezvous with D-three,
keep after the target.
Roger that!
I was wondering
what this was about.
You just can't trust
those cartel assholes.
I'm hearing a lot of
M-Four carbines out there.
Hurry! We're meeting
up with D-three!
Chinglish! Go!
Why am I gettin' the feeling
she's got this all figured out
and we're being played
like a bunch of fucking newbies?
Shit. How can we question
them if they're all dead?!
Should have thought of that
before you kill
last one so quick.
Any of you pussies
still alive or what?
This one's alive.
Fuckin' A.
This the guy?
Good find, Spooky.
Hey, beaner!
Stop it! Don't be rough
on him! His wound is fatal!
No shit, Mini-maid. Translate
this: "Where is Roberta?
Tell us and we'll take you
to a doctor." Tell him that.
Le damos la mala intencion.
De donde Rosarita ir?
Queremos saber donde esta.
Si nos dicen, vamos
a llevarte a un hospital.
Rosarita esta
persiguiendo a alguien mas.
Ella se mueve, hacia la
interseccion occidental.
Voy a vivir?
No te preocupes,
Dios protegera su alma.
Roberta is
chasing the Americans
towards an
intersection to the west.
She's going west. All right.
Does it hurt bad,
beaner? This'll fix it.
All done.
Must be the intersection
at Ramsap and Nankroy.
Let's haul ass.
We're running outta time.
Come on, Mini-maid!
Try and keep up!
Fabiola!
Mini-maid. You got the wrong
end of that puppy pointed at me.
What the fuck are you thinking?
Why did you shoot him?!
The fighting was over!
It's never over
until the last shot.
And it's the same in
the barrios, you know that.
But he was dying and
we'd just promised him
that we would save him!
And you shot
him like a mangy dog!
What you did to
him was carniceria!
Speak English, chiquita.
She said that it was
overkill, Miss Rebecca.
You're inhuman! Part of
you kills for the fun of it,
you're no different than the
serial killer Jeffrey Merdah!
You mean Dahmer.
Listen maid, I hope
morality lecture be over.
It really boring.
If not, we leave now.
Please, let's go!
We have to hurry if we're
gonna catch up to her now.
That was the right thing
to say, "Young Master."
Sawyer, you're on point.
This place.
It's a nightmare where everyone
knows the Dance of Death.
We don't. And that's why we
need experienced mercenaries.
Which is what those women are.
But you're different, Fabiola.
I want you to stay true to
your own beliefs no matter what.
And then, when this
is over, we can go back home.
To the home where we all
belong. You, me, and Roberta.
Yes, Young Master.
We're all going home together.
That's why we came here!
It's hard to say if Garcia
will catch up to Roberta.
As for the Americans,
there's really nowhere
for them to hide in this city.
They'll keep running, but
it'll be impossible for them
to lose the
Bloodhound of Florencia.
If I wanna help
those men escape,
I have to introduce another
factor into the equation.
That requires one
of the other players
to come out of the shadows.
Now I just have
to coax them out.
It looks like you
didn't make it in time, Rock.
I can see the smoke from here.
Damn it! The last thing I need
right now is lecture from Chang.
Time for you to call it a day.
Dutch must be in
one hell of a bad mood.
I'm not gonna
do that, Mr. Chang.
All the actors
are still in play.
Like the boy,
and the maid, too.
I'm not ready to leave the
stage just yet. They need me.
Don't give me that nonsense.
When you're playing chess
and the odds are stacked
this heavily against you,
you would forfeit.
Just give it up, Rock.
Now that the whole
city is about to explode,
why bother worrying about
the boy and his little maid?
Rock, you know what
I hate most in this world?
Hypocrisy. It's even worse
than what people call "evil".
It's like a poison that affects
both the victim and the user.
Enough perfume and you can
make a turd smell like a rose,
but underneath it's
still a piece of shit.
You know the deal here, Rock.
Right now, you and
I both view the Lovelace kid
and his maid as nothing
more than chess pieces,
pawns in a game they
don't even understand.
With all due
respect, Mr. Chang,
you are the
goddamn piece of shit!
I love it. I can't
even remember the last time
somebody talked
to me like that!
That's what I
like about you, Rock.
You're angry for two reasons:
One, you're a sore loser because
you know this game is lost.
And two, because I have the
ability to consistently guess
what you're really
thinking deep down.
See, I understand people.
I've looked into the hearts of
human beings and seen
things you can't even imagine.
What do you know
of the human heart?
You're a gangster
who lives in a world
of cheap lives and violence!
You want an explanation?
Ya know, this "gangster"
used to be on the other side.
You might not believe it,
but a long, long time ago
he was a fearless guard
dog who burned with justice.
A guard dog for
the Hong Kong police.
That's nothing special.
It's not unusual for people here
to lead lives of contradiction.
Remember, Rock, you're nothing
but a pawn in this game, too.
Just step aside. Do it, before
it's too late to save your soul.
Thank you, Mr. Chang,
but I'm not done.
Fine then, do as you like,
but after a declaration
of defiance like that, I expect
you to put up a good fight.
Goddamnit!
This is Recon Team D-two.
Target is in view.
She's a block away.
Move in closer.
Fuck, why are we still
out here?! We're hurtin', man!
Shut your hole, Jose!
No one wastes my friends
and gets away with it!
Shit!
Ai ya. This really sucks ass.
Think they let us
through if say please?
We'll just have to
murder every motherfucker
who gets in our way.
I'm completely okay with that. I
just have one question for you.
Well, holy shit. Ya actually
talk? So what's your question?
That elevated platform!
Wouldn't diving into battle from
there make for a cool entrance?
Did you have to
bring that freak with us?!
Eh, cut him slack.
You know, he kinda "special".
Still a lot of
gunfire out there.
Who the hell is shooting who?
Let the enemy units through
and then send the Recon.
Eventually they'll link with
Bravo and Charlie
in a pincer attack.
Everybody, check
your mags. Don't waste ammo.
So, what's the
plan after we get out?
We'll go to
ground outside the city
and wait for
orders from the NSA.
But first things first.
We need to concentrate on
finding and
killing that sniper.
Let's hope we catch a
break and she follows the bait.
Let's go around!
Take this, you motherfuckers!
Fuck, yeah!
Roberta's on the other
side of this crazy fight!
Yeah!
Let's go!
Surprise!
This is D-four. We're
moving to support D-two.
We're entering the area now.
Nobody move!
Get back, Young Master.
But--
Get Outta the way,
you fuckin' brats!
I can pull through if I'm by
myself. Hurry up! Don't move!
Wait!
What do I find on this night
beneath a moon
so clear and blue?
Vile scum who raise
foul blades against children!
Any foes who face the
fury of my beloved sidearm
will be blown to pieces!
God is with me,
he protects me.
And I am his
executioner here on Earth!
Now prepare to face
the wrath of-- Wait!
Awww.
Fabiola!
Young Master!
I can't get over to you!
Just stay there and hide!
Okay! You hide too, Fabiola!
Another group is
delaying D-four, sir.
All this and we
still haven't found her.
If I were the Americans,
I would prepare a pincer attack.
Rosarita will be expecting it.
We taught her
that strategy in training.
I know her. The Bloodhound
will be in here. Find her!
Fabiola?
It's not her!
It's the enemy!
They're still fighting.
This is terrible.
Hmm?
A central nervous
system stimulant.
This is what Roberta
ordered from Dr. Heartland!
Still nothing from Lopez.
He was on the third floor.
We've found her.
She's somewhere upstairs.
Roberta's here! Finally!
I've caught up with her!
Lopez!
Did you find anything?
Lopez? What's wrong?
It's okay. There's still time!
I know Roberta's still alive!
She's alive, have faith in her!
It seems the Bloodhound
is still as ferocious as ever.
It's no use.
I know all your moves.
We were trained the same way.
I've come from Havana.
You're from the
Cuban Navy's Special Forces.
Precisely. The request
came directly from Marulanda,
the leader of FARC.
"Why doesn't he just shoot me?"
I can see it in your eyes...
I could have shot you
dead several times already.
Your old commander may
want your head, but not me.
You see, when Central would
meet to plan out our operations,
you were always
essential to our strategy.
We thought you might
inherit Carlos' old name.
You could have
been the next Jackal.
We need someone in our
organization with your talent.
Come back with me, Bloodhound.
Pretending to be
a maid in a country manor
isn't who you really are.
You can't resist
the smell of blood.
Yeah, you're right.
That place was boring. There was
no blood, no gunfire, nothing.
Now that the Master
is dead, it's time to move on.
Once I avenge his death, my
debt to him will have been paid.
This isn't what I
expected from you, Rosarita.
It'll all be over soon.
Just let me finish it.
Very well. A few American
heads should make for
some nice souvenirs.
But, I doubt the commander
will simply forgive me.
Leave that to me. I have
powerful friends in Havana.
Those FARC pricks
wouldn't dare object.
Considering what's going
to happen, I think it would be
a good idea for you to let me
get to know you a little better.
What about those
Americans you need to kill?
They're not going to move until
I show up and take the bait.
Besides, it's so hot in here.
I can smell the blood
and death everywhere.
It's like a greenhouse
filled with funeral lilies.
Makes me wanna fuck.
Bloodhound, are you testing me?
'Cause I'm in charge here.
You wanna be my dog? Show me.
Be my bitch and
stick out your tongue.
Wait! Don't tear my clothes.
I don't want to fight
the Americans naked.
Reach down and,
take my pants off. Do it.
Don't make me laugh.
Do it yourself.
You're being cautious.
Alright then.
Nice and slow.
So don't shoot me.
F-Fucking whore!
What a shame.
You were careful,
but you weren't quite
careful enough, you pig!
I would never join
your damned revolution!
Why? Because you and those
foxes serve the same master!
Your so-called principals.
They're just illusions. And I'll
never be fooled by them again!
There is only one
person that I serve.
One person who can leash me.
And that's Garcia
Fernando Lovelace.
He is my only master! For
him I would wade in the shit
and mud of this world
and give my life to save his!
It is for him alone that I
kill and seek revenge on those
who destroyed his family!
For him I have severed
all my old allegiances!
You're no longer a bloodhound.
You're a lone
wolf that's gone mad.
No, Roberta, stop!
No more, that's enough!
Stop it, Roberta!
Please, stop it! Stop it!
Stop it!
Young... Master?
Young Master?
What are you-- What are
you doing here? No, no, no!
No! No!
Oh dear God, don't look
at me! Don't look at me!
Stop. That's enough.
That's enough.
Young Master! No! No! No!
Young Master! Oh my God! What
have I done? What have I done?!
Perhaps your hallucinations
of me were an attempt to
prevent this from happening.
How long? How long
are you going to haunt me?!
Haunt you?
You're wrong about that.
I'm just an old memory
from the time when you attacked
Taisho Electric's
Magnarelli office
and shot two
Japanese technicians.
Remember? An assassination
from seven years ago.
And just before you killed me,
you tore up a
picture of my family.
So many sad little wounds
that eventually turned into one.
Filling your world
with pain and misery.
And maybe in those
days of peace and quiet,
you found that wound
didn't hurt quite so much.
If you had lived
the rest of your life
in the company of that child,
then maybe those wounds
would have healed eventually.
But, you are the one
who threw all that away.
It was your choice.
What would it take
to find true forgiveness?
I tried to find peace in that
manor, but what was the point...
if I am to be haunted
for all eternity?!
You've hounded
me day and night--
You've never
let me forget my sins!
Why won't you let me forget?!
You took my Master from me
and now you've done
this to the Young Master!
Now, I understand.
So that's it. That's
why you showed him to me.
You'll try anything
to kill me, won't you?
Of course! It's impossible
for the Young Master to be here!
He's still back at
the manor waiting for me
to bring him the
heads of the foxes.
When I return,
he'll smile at me
and everything will
go back to how it was.
But you just had
to show me this illusion
of the Young Master
in this hellhole!
You showed me the one
thing I never wanted to see!
Well, you've
gone too far this time!
This isn't really
the Young Master!
He's just like you,
something from my imagination!
One shot will prove
that he's not really here!
This is Burroughs!
We've encountered the target!
We've deployed tear gas
and the First Sergeant
has pulled a boy to safety!
First Sergeant Horner here.
We've canceled the feint.
Returning to Point A!
Who's the boy?
You said to read
this if I lost my way.
Did you know
who was going to
have to do it
when you wrote that?!