[GRETEL] But I'm offering
you 150 thousand dollars.
Doesn't matter!
After we kill these brats,
don't forget to pick up the
cash on the ground, 'kay, Eda?
Okay. Don't you fucking move.
[GRETEL] I guess this means...
...we're done talking.
[GRETEL giggling]
--Bastard!
--[JODOROWSKY] There they are!
Huh?
This is Jodorowsky!
Engaging enemy at Point Pskov!
[BALALAIKA] Roger.
--[EDA] What the fuck?!
--[REVY] Don't do it, Eda!
That's Hotel Moscow!
It's the Russians, sora mea .
They came out.
They have!
I know, sora mea ...
Wouldn't it be fun
to confuse these guys?
If we can eliminate a few,
they'll probably
return to their base!
That sounds like a good idea!
We'll split up so we can hunt
down the Russians separately!
Good luck, sora mea .
Fratele meu .
[HANSEL] I love you.
[GRETEL] Yes. I love you, too.
[crashing sound]
Right. Target was
lost in combat.
That's fine.
What's important is that we've
shown ourselves to the enemy.
Proceed under the assumption
that they have taken the bait.
Roger. All units,
you've got the go ahead.
[radio static]
[EUGENE] Lavochek Unit,
Lobosfski Unit.
Level two preparations
are complete.
Proceeding to final location.
[radio static]
[BARONIN] Target two located.
Appears to be
pursuing Jodorowsky.
Confirm the number
of targets. Quickly!
This is Baronin to Okchabriagin.
I have only sighted target two.
I repeat, target two only.
Private Eugene confirming.
I see the target
following Jodorowsky.
I'm only seeing
one body, as well.
[BARONIN] As far as I can tell,
target two is still right
on Jodorowsky's tail.
[JODOROWSKY] I'll take him
to the drop point as planned.
So, only target two
has taken the bait?
[BARONIN] Yes, ma'am.
Very well. Bring this
one in and no mistakes.
Don't take anything for granted.
Their instincts are extremely
sharp. It's probably better
to let them believe
they have the upper hand.
Keep that in mind and
proceed to the next stage.
Let's stir up a
little confusion.
[JODOROWSKY] I'll make sure
that my men hit it mafia-style.
Not to worry. We'll be
at the park entrance soon
and we'll be sure to strike
first once we get there.
[BALALAIKA] Your priority
should be to confuse
and frustrate them,
do you understand?
Frustration will
dull their senses,
which will make our job easier.
[JODOROWSKY] Roger.
[BALALAIKA] Sergeant, it's time.
Take command of the final squad.
Yes, ma'am.
Best of luck to you, Kapitän .
[BALALAIKA] Thanks. That
goes for you too, Sergeant.
Now then... Guess it's
about time we put an end
to this boisterous
merrymaking.
Damn it!
Well, I'm the one
who has to go back
to the Church empty-handed.
We should've just
taken the offer,
but that would've been
too easy, wouldn't it?!
Instead, you got greedy
and fucked us both!
Whiny bitch! You're lucky
I was around to save you
from having your
fuckin' balls shot off
by those guys from Hotel
Moscow! Remember that?!
Last time I checked,
I didn't have a set,
but maybe you do,
you nasty she-male
You asked for it, bitch!
Draw your gun right now!
When I'm finished with you,
you're gonna hafta
pick which asshole
you wanna shit through,
you got that?!
[REVY] Y'know,
I don't care anymore.
We fucked up. It's over.
Uh-huh. I didn't get
a penny outta this.
[REVY] Well, I'm going
back to the office.
Call me if something comes up.
Huh? Hey, hold on a second!
You can't just leave me!
Uh, what do you mean?
What the hell do
you think I mean?!
I can't walk to my car alone
when there's a
full-scale war going on.
You have to come with me!
I mean, we're
friends, aren't we?!
I'm sure you can handle
all that on your own.
I've got better things
to do than babysit you.
Wha...?
Fuck you, you
heartless bitch!
[gun cocking]
Huh?
Oh. Hi, miss.
[EDA] Uh... How long
have you been there?
[GRETEL] A while. I was waiting
for you to be alone.
I didn't wanna face the two
of you all by myself.
[EDA] Fuck.
[GRETEL] You see,
there's something I want
you to help me with.
As soon as my brother
kills that Russian lady,
we'll hafta get
outta here right away.
Hmm?
But we already killed
Verrocchio and his men
who were supposed to
arrange that for us.
Dumb kid. If you knew
he was your handler,
then why the
hell'd you kill him?
Anyway, you have no reason
to kill Balalaika now.
So, why do you go on?
What's the point?
"Why," you ask?
Why do we continue,
what a question!
You're so funny!
Because we want to.
We don't need any other reason.
We want to, so we do it.
Huh?
[GRETEL] But right now,
that's not important.
I want you to introduce
me to an escape specialist.
It should be someone who
takes their job seriously.
So, can you tell me
who that is, miss?
[birds chirping]
There's no need to hide.
Why don't you come on out?
Hmph. You knew where I was.
That's very impressive, lady.
And your soldiers
are very good, too.
I chased them around
for quite a while,
but I couldn't
kill a single one.
So, what do you wanna do now?
Perhaps we could use
this time together to talk.
Let's see...
Maybe we could talk about
that soldier of yours.
A normal person would've
died a lot sooner,
but that man just
didn't want to let go.
Up until he died,
he kept yelling,
" Kapitän ! Kapitän !"
And when he finally died,
he went... [gagging]
...like that.
[BALALAIKA] Hmm.
You don't say...
You're a cold person, lady.
But know what?
It won't be very long...
...till you end up
like that man.
It's just a shame we don't
have much time left to talk.
In that case, I've got
some bad news for you.
I'm sorry, little boy,
but... this is it.
The end of the line for you.
But before that happens,
you'll have to apologize for
all the mischief you've caused.
Isn't that right?
Now you're gonna kneel
before me and beg forgiveness.
--You're pretty fu--
--I said kneel!
[grunting]
As I said...
the end of the line.
If you were able
to think rationally,
it would've been
obvious to you...
...that as you pursued us, you
were being led to your death.
Take a look at yourself now--
a pathetic little brat
who's beyond all repair.
And like it or not, this is
where you're gonna die.
[HANSEL] You're funny, lady.
But what are you
talking about?
I'm not gonna die.
I can't die, b-beacause
I've killed so many
people in my life.
We've killed many...
[GRETEL'S VOICE]
...many... many...
[HANSEL] ...many people.
It means we get
to live on for...
[GRETEL'S VOICE]
...that much longer.
[HANSEL] We can... We can
add on to our lives.
[GRETEL'S VOICE] So, we're never
going to die. That's right.
We are eternal.
That's quite the
interesting religion.
It's a wonderful
thought I suppose.
However, I'm afraid that
Oingo Boingo said it best...
"No one lives forever."
That's just the way it goes.
Now then,
I suppose I could be cruel and
torture you before I kill you.
Considering what you
did to my comrade,
there's no question that
it would be appropriate.
But unfortunately,
I'm not as vulgar as you.
It would bring me
no satisfaction.
So, I think I'll
sit here and watch
until you've taken your
last miserable breath.
Judging by your wounds,
you have about
ten minutes at best.
I dedicate these
last few minutes
before you leave this world to
Sakharov and Menshov's souls.
May they rest in peace.
Although...
I'm certain you wouldn't
be able to understand.
[labored breathing]
[gasping sobs]
Don't cry, you fool.
[BORIS] Kapitän ?
[BALALAIKA] Sergeant.
I'm finished on my end.
That was hard, Kapitän .
Just watching
gave me the chills.
[BALALAIKA] I'm sorry.
I had to have my revenge
and you humored me.
[BORIS] Kapitän ...
[BALALAIKA] I'm getting
too old for this.
I feel...
I feel exhausted.
[GRETEL] ♪ Someday
I want to run away ♪
♪ To the world of midnight ♪
♪ Where the darkness
fill the air ♪
♪ Where it's icy cold ♪
♪ Where nobody has a name ♪
♪ Where living is not a game ♪
♪ There I'll hide
my broken heart... ♪
Girl sure can sing.
Hard to believe it's the
voice of a homicidal maniac.
Yeah.
[DUTCH] A devil with
the voice of an angel.
Goddamn,
I sure as hell couldn't
have predicted this though.
[BENNY] You can say that again.
The sadistic serial killer
who terrorized all of Roanapur
is now a client of ours.
Fine by me.
End of the day, she's
just another client.
Hey, where's Revy?
[BENNY] I know she was
really bent out of shape
about us taking that girl,
but right now, she's keeping
watch outside the cabin door.
You know, just in case
something happens to Rock.
[ROCK] That was
a beautiful song.
Where did you learn it?
I heard it on TV.
It's one of my favorite
songs of all time.
You know what else?
You're the first person
I've ever sung it to.
Well... not counting my brother.
Ah...
[giggling]
H-Hey!
I've noticed that
you seem different
from everyone else, mister.
Huh?
It's almost like you're in a
different world or something.
Oh, yeah?
Guess I'm not used
to this job yet.
Go figure.
I like talking to you.
You're nice.
You know, I'm really good
at telling who's nice...
...and who's not.
[beeping noises]
[clicking sound]
[DUTCH] Is this Balalaika?
[BALALAIKA] I presume
you know why I'm calling.
[DUTCH] Yeah.
To be honest, I'm surprised
you waited this long.
I have to ask, Dutch--
you do realize what
you're doing, right?
[DUTCH] Of course.
And the compensation
reflects the additional risks.
This isn't your good
deed for the year?
[DUTCH] Do I look like
a philanthropist to you?
Just checking.
Anyway, it helps me to determine
the appropriate response.
[DUTCH] Sounds like we both
gotta do what we gotta do.
Am I wrong, Balalaika?
Hey. We're heading south, Dutch.
[BALALAIKA] You're right, Dutch.
In fact, I've already made
a number of arrangements.
No doubt.
I think I see some of
those "arrangements" now.
No regrets and no
hard feelings, I trust.
Good luck, sailor.
[DUTCH] Roger, Kapitän .
--Sergeant.
--[BORIS] Yes?
Get me the E file
from the trouble list.
E?
Insurance with a good return.
The Vietnamese Navy?
Yeah. That's correct.
And they're out in force.
The long reach
of Hotel Moscow...
So, are we gonna fight?
[DUTCH] Not if we wanna live.
We're a torpedo boat.
These guys are equipped
with missiles.
And this makes life hard
'cause that eliminates
the Hainan Island route.
[BENNY] How 'bout Brunei?
Y'know, where Mary Lee is.
[DUTCH] Not an option.
We can't afford the time.
Then it looks like our
only remaining option
is to visit Elroy
in Pangkal Pinang.
Big Horn Elroy, huh?
Okay, that's where we'll go.
[BENNY] I'll go contact him.
[GRETEL] Oh...
I bet you the water and
the sky are beautiful today,
but I won't get
the chance to see it.
No fair.
I'm sorry.
[GRETEL] It's alright.
I'm used to it.
Have you never seen the sea?
Back when we were in Sicily
and we lived at the orphanage,
the only thing
we ever got to see
were those gray cement walls.
I was born in a small town
in the Carpathian mountains.
It was a dark and lonely place.
[ROCK] A certain
dictator passed a law
which made abortion illegal. His
plan was to ensure a workforce
for the future of the country.
In reality, most were too poor
to provide for their children.
Many families had no choice
but to put their kids
in state-run orphanages.
The secret police found
numerous uses for these orphans.
The dictator was killed,
but the orphans remained,
born of his policies
and abandoned by all.
[GRETEL] Once we were
sold to the mafia,
all we ever saw was
blood and darkness.
They would beat us
and kick us so hard,
that at night, I couldn't
stop peeing blood.
Every night, my brother and
I would talk to each other.
And we always wondered--
why was it that God wanted
us to suffer like that?
But know what?
After a while,
we stopped wondering,
because we both
realized something.
The other children would
be brought before us.
They'd be crying and then they'd
be beaten to death with bats
and you know what then?
The adults would
all be laughing.
My brother and I
started to laugh, too.
And while we laughed,
we realized,
this is how the
world really works.
Yes.
The world would keep turning,
as long as people
were being killed.
And that must be the
reason why we're here...
To keep doing it forever.
People kill, get killed,
and kill again...
This is the thread that
ties everyone together.
But... doesn't it
make you sad
that your brother
died because of that?
Huh? What are you talking about?
I'm not dead. I'm right here.
My sister and I are
always together, mister...
...because both of
us will live forever.
We can't be touched
by the thread.
That's how it will always be.
So you see,
all we have to do
is keep on killing.
That's the only
reason we're alive.
That's why we don't
have to be sad anymore.
The smell of blood,
the sound of screaming,
and the warmth of bowels...
We've learned to love it all.
No!
You're wrong! That's
not why you're here!
The world is a place
for you to find happiness!
Listen! Blood and darkness
are just a small part of it!
That's not all the
world has to offer!
Hey. It's okay,
mister. Don't cry.
This is the first time anyone's
ever been this nice to me, so...
Here. A gift for you.
[slamming door]
[BENNY] Huh?
--Rock?
--[REVY] Benny!
Go check on him, alright!
I'm gonna take care
of this fuckin' kid!
[BENNY] Yeah, alright!
[GRETEL] Ah!
[REVY] Well, well...
I guess even a little demon
like you has red blood.
Fuckin' pissant.
Let me tell you something--
Balalaika's not the only
one who's disappointed
that you're not dead.
[GRETEL giggling] It's funny.
You have the exact same smell.
It's the smell of blood
and rotten sewers.
It's because you and
I are the same thing.
[REVY] Look, I really
don't give a shit.
If you fuck with him again,
I'm gonna kill you.
Not to mention,
if you do anything
at all to piss me off,
I'll kill you for that, too.
[ROCK] Damn it!
Damn it! Why? Why did
this hafta happen?!
Everyone in her
life betrayed her!
They turned her into a monster!
They turned her into
a fuckin' monster!
--Goddamn it!
--[BENNY] Rock.
Sometimes it's best
to look the other way.
You have to do that if
you wanna survive here.
[ROCK] I'll...
You'll what?! Adopt her?!
Forget it.
You can't just undo
what's been done to her.
If only someone had shown
them a little kindness,
they might've gone to
school, made friends,
and lived happily ever after.
Who knows, right?
But... that didn't
happen, did it?
I'm sorry, but
stories like this
don't have happy
endings, Rock.
[ELROY] Dutch.
Long time no see.
Yeah, it has been a while.
I take it that's the cargo?
[DUTCH] Right. I know
it was last minute,
but were you able
to get her a passport?
[ELROY] Everything's
taken care of.
Besides, when isn't
it a rush job?
It was nice to
meet you, mister.
Hopefully we'll
meet again someday!
We could have a picnic!
Just you and me, 'kay mister?
Yeah.
That sounds wonderful.
Really wonderful.
[gunshot]
[startled gasp]
[GRETEL] It's beautiful.
The sky.
[ELROY] It was
Hotel Moscow, Dutch.
But you probably knew that.
You know you're done
as a getaway man.
I know. I'm washed up.
I have a son living
in South Africa.
I just got a letter
from his wife.
Only 34 years old...
...and the doctors just
diagnosed him with cancer.
Either way,
I'm getting too damn old to
keep walking the tightrope.
This was my last job.
For what it's worth,
Hotel Moscow paid me a hell
of a lot of money to do this.
Well, see ya.
Her last words were
"It's beautiful. The sky."
Fuckin' hell!
[DUTCH] Rock.
You better go find us a tarp.
We're gonna hafta
cover up the body.
[ROCK] No, that
won't be necessary.
This is fine. Just like this.
She can look up at the sky,
and hear the ocean
as she sleeps.
Where the darkness fill the air
Where it's icy cold
Where nobody has a name
Where living is not a game
There, I'll hide
my broken heart
Dying to survive
There, no one can see me cry
The tears of my lonely soul
I'll find peace of mind
In the dark and
cold world of midnight
Midnight (Midnight)
Midnight
[JANE] The only reason
I accepted this job
in the first place is because
I was told I'd be able to make
perfect counterfeit money.