[YOMIKAWA] I've gotta say...
security robots
malfunctioning like this
is a real black eye
for Antiskill.
Luckily for us all,
it didn't get too serious.
Whoa... that's
definitely strange.
Have you found the
source of the problem?
It's kinda
hard to tell.
These robots were just
brought to the site
and their main batteries
haven't been installed yet.
That doesn't make any
sense. Are you sure?
Yeah... Forget malfunctioning,
these things shouldn't
be functioning at all...
Maybe there was power left
in the auxiliary batteries?
[SATEN] Okay...
I guess that's that...
Yeah, don't worry.
Bye for now...
Uiharu and Shirai still have
to investigate the site,
so they'll be awhile.
She said to go
ahead without them.
Okay, Febri. What do you think?
How about I give you
this red Gekota,
and you give me
back the pink one?
This one's cute, too, right?
Look, look!
[FEBRI] No.
[MIKOTO] Ugghh...
Well, how about together
with this blue Gekota?
And, hey, I'll even
throw in the yellow one.
Do we have a deal?
[FEBRI] This is my Gekota!
[FEBRI giggles]
[MIKOTO] If I don't find
a way to get it back soon,
it really will be
hers forever...!
Out of all of them...
Why did she have to
fixate on the pink--
the color I only have one of?
So, it has come to this.
You've been at
that awhile...
You sure do like finger puppets.
[KONGO] Misaka, Saten!
Hello once again.
Yes, hello!
Hi, Kongo!
[FEBRI] Mitsuko!
Oh, my, you're in good spirits,
aren't you, sweetie?
You really came
through before...
I mean it, if you
hadn't spotted Febri,
who knows what might
have happened to her?
Yeah, thank you so
much for your help...
Febri, do you want to
tell Mitsuko something?
Thank you, Mitsuko!
[gasps]
N-No thanks necessary,
I'm sure...
I only did what anyone would
have in the same position.
[KONGO laughs]
Well... we were all just
about to go out for some tea.
It should be fun.
Would you like to come along?
Wow...! A tea party...!
Oh... While I appreciate
the kind invitation,
there are still duties here
to which I must attend.
No worries... You go on
and have fun, Kongo.
Yeah...
We can manage the rest
on our own, I'm sure.
[KONGO] How can you
say such a thing...?
I offered to help, and
that's what I intend to do!
Mitsuko Kongo is not someone
who abandons her friends!
Okay! Mitsuko!
Wanna! Atsuki!
Thank you, bye-bye!
Have a nice day!
And be careful!
All right, then...
Shall we continue on with
our business, ladies...?
Wait...
Heh...
That man again...
[typing]
[SEIKIMURA] How lucky that we
already have a chance to test
the data we acquired on the
fourth-ranked the other day.
[SAKURAI] I would have liked to
have had more time to prepare...
but I suppose I
shouldn't complain.
[MADARAME] This should
be interesting...
I wonder what kind of data
we'll get this time around.
Well, I think it will be
at least mildly entertaining.
Let's see what you
can do... Railgun.
[SATEN] They've got posters
for the Reach Assembly
put up all over the place, huh?
[MIKOTO] So, what
do you think...
I mean, now that
we've seen some of it ?
I'm not sure what I expected.
I've never actually been to one
of these assemblies, either.
Well... I imagine
it would be nice,
having a field of study that
you were passionate about...
Maybe I should try to find
something to research...
Urban legends, maybe!
I don't know
about that...
Oh... No?
[WAITRESS 20-A]
Thank you for waiting.
Ooh, here it
comes, Febri!
[WAITRESS 20-A] Your very
special ice cream.
Well, shucks, you can't eat
with your hands full, can you?
I guess I have no choice but
to hold the pink Gekota for you
while you have your
ice cream... Here.
Aaahhh...
Aw... Such a spoiled
little girl.
There ya go.
Yum!
Aaahhh...
Okay!
[KONORI] Whew...!
I thought we would
never be finished!
We still haven't found the cause
of the security robot incident.
Come to think of it, we
don't know what was behind
the traffic light outage
yesterday, either.
A rash of mysterious
mechanical trouble.
[KUROKO] Hmm?
That sounds like the kind of
story Saten would like to hear.
[KUROKO] Yeah.
[KONORI] Hey...
do you two have some time?
[SATEN] Is it good?
[FEBRI] Yeah! Yeah...!
I want more, more, more!
All right, all right.
[MIKOTO] Yes, hello...?
Oh, Kuroko...
What...? Hold on,
where are you?
[MIKOTO] So... this is what
you do in your free time?
[KONORI] Just you wait...
Nothing beats this
when you're tired...
What do you say, Febri?
Have you ever been to
one of these before...?
Inside they've got the
biggest bathtub ever!
[UIHARU] It's so big we
can all go in together!
[KUROKO] Oh, yes...
sharing a bath with Sissy
is something I've
always dreamed about!
Leave it to me, Sissy...!
I'll be the best bath
attendant you have ever had.
When I'm done with you,
every last inch of your body
will be scrubbed
clean! Every inch!
Every nook and cranny!
[heavy breathing]
[thud]
[MIKOTO] Okay,
let's go inside, Febri.
[FEBRI] Yay!
[SATEN]
♪ Bath time! Bath time! ♪
[SATEN and FEBRI]
♪ It's... bath... time! ♪
[KUROKO] I will not allow
anything to stand in the way
of this blissful opportunity!
Showtime!
Oh... Shirai...
So you're here, too, huh?
[KUROKO] Uh-oh...
[water splashes]
[FEBRI] You're tickling me!
Come on...
stop fidgeting.
There...! That's a good girl.
Those two are like
peas in a pod, huh?
They're adorable!
How are you liking
it so far, Misaka?
[MIKOTO] Huh?
[SATEN] You know,
having a younger sister!
[MIKOTO] Uh... I have
no idea what you mean.
[MIKOTO] A younger
sister, huh...?
[FEBRI] There, see?
All clean, all clean!
[MIKOTO] Hey...!
Where did that come from?
Come on, Gekota,
you stop fidgeting!
She's even
imitating Misaka.
She really does make
a cute little sister.
Just plain
adorable!
See, Gekota, that
feels good, huh?
There, there...
You just sit still, okay?
Good girl...! Good girl!
Good girl!
[FEBRI giggles]
So, Febri... you
really like Gekota?
Mm. Yes!
Thought so...
Tell you what, then.
You can keep it.
Take good care
of it, though.
You promise?
Uh-huh!
Thanks alot, Mikoto!
That's really nice, but
Gekota was already my Gekota.
[MIKOTO] Eh?!
[SATEN] Hey, Misaka,
if Febri's all clean,
come over here and
I'll get your back!
[UIHARU] Ooh, Saten, when you're
done, will you get my back, too?
[SATEN] Sure.
[KONORI] See, I told
you it would be fun!
[MIKOTO]
You're getting water everywhere!
[KUROKO] Sissy...
Paradise awaits just
beyond those doors...!
A sweet, blissful haven that
I alone can truly appreciate!
[HEAD RESIDENT]
Did I say you could stop?
Come on. Can't you rub
any harder than that?
Yeah...
[KONORI] Well, I'm
headed this way, so...
...guess I'll see you tomorrow.
Sounds good. See you later!
Have a good
night! See ya'!
Okay, Kuroko,
let's get going.
[KUROKO] A bath with Sissy...
A once in a lifetime
opportunity!
It should have been me
in there with her...!
Oh, cruel, cruel world!
[MIKOTO] Geez, Kuroko...
What's with you?
[KUROKO sobs]
[FEBRI] Ruiko...
Okay.
I guess it's been a pretty big
day for such a little girl.
[MIKOTO] Your back has become
reserved seating, huh?
Non-stop piggy back rides.
Yeah... I don't mind.
I only get to carry her
around for five more days.
I'm really gonna miss
her when she's gone.
[UIHARU] Yeah...
but it's not like we'll
never see her again.
[SATEN chuckles]
[KUROKO] You try to remember
that, too, Sissy...
Don't get all sad.
I... wasn't planning on it.
[FEBRI] Gekota...
Well... maybe just a little.
[UIHARU] Once she gets all
settled at Asunaro Park,
we can go and
visit her together.
Of course!
Uh, but... this time
I think I'll make sure
to leave all of
my Gekotas at home.
[SATEN] Oh, come on now, Misaka!
[KUROKO] I don't know
what the big deal is.
You have so many of them.
[MIKOTO] Yeah, well, they're
not exactly easy to come by!
[SATEN] Huh?
Sidewalk closed?
[UIHARU] It shouldn't
be a big problem...
Let's just go up one
street and cross there.
[MIKOTO] Uh?
[KUROKO] It's closed here, too?
[UIHARU] It's a pretty
long way around,
but if there's construction,
I guess we don't have a choice.
[SATEN] This is annoying, huh?
[UIHARU] Um...
A dead end. We can't
get through here.
[SATEN] We followed the
detour map exactly, right?
[MIKOTO] I thought
we did, but...
Hold on, I can look
it up on my GPS...
That's strange...
I've got several
missed calls from Kongo.
What does Her
Highness want?
Oh... so do I.
Wow... that many?
[UIHARU] She must have called
while we were in the bathhouse,
and we didn't notice.
I wonder if it was
something important.
[loud clang]
[SATEN] What's that?
[KOSAKO chuckles]
Now... let the experiment begin.
Get back!
Be careful!
[MIKOTO] You know,
I'm not sure...
who you are exactly...
but come on...
did you actually think this
was going to work against me?!
[MIKOTO yells]
Are you okay?
[MIKOTO] Kuroko!
Keep out of this!
Are you sure?
[MIKOTO] I can't control it?
It's not using shields...
In fact, it's got no
electrical systems at all.
Just like the
simulations predicted...
Well then, next up...
[MIKOTO] How is it moving?
[MIKOTO] I'm not sure
what's going on,
but it looks like the type of
thing that has someone inside.
[grunts] Come on...!
I've got better
things to do today!
Oh, no! Look out!
You're okay!
Get your phone...!
Contact Antiskill!
I'll get
right on it!
Uh... no good.
What's wrong... hurry!
[UIHARU] I'm not
getting a cell signal!
No signal? That's kinda' weird--
[MIKOTO] Febri!
This isn't a
good place to be!
What are you doing...?
Get away from here!
[alarm sounds]
[typing]
[KOSAKO] What's the matter?!
It's over...?
[KONGO yells]
Uhh...
[KONGO laughs]
That stupid machine should find
a different dance partner!
It's Kongo!
Geez! What the heck
are you doing here?
[KONGO] Wherever Kongo's
friends are, there she will be.
Huh?
[KONGO] So, tell me,
what is going on here?
Not sure...
I don't know who would
do something like this.
[gasps]
Hey, wait... that's...
It's empty?
This makes no sense.
[SATEN] Febri!
What's the matter...?
C'mon wake up!
Oh, no!
We did predict that
this might happen...
It's always nice when your
calculations are proved correct,
isn't it?
[MIKOTO] Febri...!
Are you all right...? Febri!
Does she have an injury?
[UIHARU] I'll call an ambulance!
But our phones
aren't working--
The signal's getting
through now.
Okay, then call
someone, already!
[KUROKO] R-Right, I'm on it.
[YOMIKAWA] Really?
You guys again?
I wish you had been
there to see it!
I was simply amazing...!
The horrible robot
was closing in,
but I plucked it up
and tossed it aside...
[YOMIKAWA] No pilot, no battery,
and no idea what's going on.
That sounds an awful lot like
the security robots, doesn't it?
We're telling you
the truth...!
Please, just take a look
at the surveillance cameras,
and you'll see!
Calm down. It's not that I
doubt what you're saying...
but I've already received the
reports from the cameras...
and they haven't seen
anything out of the ordinary.
Could they be wrong?
Let me think, here...
Could it be connected to our
phones not working, maybe?
Just leave this up to
Antiskill for now.
Yeah, but...
Your young friend was taken
to the hospital, right...?
See how she's doing.
I guess we should...
Let's go.
Uh... right.
[KUROKO] Thank you.
Yeah.
[sighs] Just great...
Could my job get any weirder?
Hmm...
What's this?
[MIKOTO] Right.
Yes, okay... bye.
Kuroko says they'll
be here soon.
It didn't look like she
was injured or anything...
She'll be okay... won't she?
[MIKOTO] It's the waiting...
that's the worst, isn't it?
[SATEN] Hm?
She'll wake up
and it'll be fine.
[MIKOTO chuckles]
[door opens]
Febri!
Doctor, please...
[MALE DOCTOR 20-A]
Her fever hasn't gone down...
and she hasn't
regained consciousness.
I don't know why her
condition is worsening...
I'm stumped.
There is nothing more
we can do for her here.
We're moving her to
another hospital right now.
O-kay...
This is yours now...
Keep it close to you.
[KOSAKO] Excellent!
We now know that our work
can hold its own nicely
against Railgun
and her ability...
Though it would have been
preferable if our machine
made it through the
experiment in better shape.
Well, we all take risks in
the name of greater knowledge.
[SAKURAI]
Today's data has ensured
that the program will
be even more accurate.
[SEIKIMURA]
It's actually a good thing
the third-ranked interfered.
Today's experiment has
demonstrated something vital...
The fact that even those espers
who possess greatest abilities
are vulnerable to attack...
Academy city's inconsistency
will be exposed.
And now, my friends,
it's time to call a vote.
Concerning Febri's...
disposition?
[SATEN] It's taking
awhile, isn't it?
So, uh...
what was that thing we saw...?
If it had never shown up...
maybe she would be okay.
[MIKOTO] I don't know
who these people are.
But that thing...
it came after me.
It's my fault. I did it.
She's in pain because of me.
[KUROKO] Sissy...!
Oh, hey...
I'm glad you're here.
[UIHARU]
So, how is Febri doing?
Sorry, we...
don't know.
[UIHARU] Oh, okay.
Any news?
Well... Antiskill has taken over
the investigation for now...
and, unfortunately, we haven't
gotten any leads so far.
I'd like to know...
What are you doing here,
Your High-and-Mightyness?!
You have to ask?
Like all of you,
I came because I'm concerned
about Febri, of course.
I guess that I should
thank you again...
I do appreciate it...
Oh, yeah, and I saw that
you called us earlier?
[KONGO] Yes... yes, I did!
There is something I felt
that you needed to know...
Our sweet Febri is in danger!
[gasps]
There was an incident
near the Reach Assembly
with a man who spoke
extremely unkindly to me.
And then...
Hey, is that...?
Hold on, what are
you planning to do?
I just think I should
have a word with that guy
about his attitude...
I don't like what he
said before, Kongo.
I really think he's
wrong about you.
Yes, I agree...
And I would like to
tell him so to his face.
[KONGO] Huh...? But...
Target is currently
on the move...
That's right.
It's unfortunate that we
failed to retrieve Febri...
but aren't we better off
as things stand now?
Hmm...? Yes...
Yes, send them
my way... please.
I think there will be
some interesting results.
[MIKOTO] That guy wanted Febri?!
[KONGO] Yes, so we tried...
but we couldn't
reach any of you...
Then we decided it would
be best to split up
and start searching for--
[phone rings]
Whoops. Please excuse me.
Hello, this is Kongo...
Wannai, Awatsuki?
Yes, I'm so sorry...
I completely forgot to call you
and fill you in on everything.
Oh, yes, I was able to
find Misaka and the others.
And Febri, too...
However...
Well, yes. I'm doing
just fine thank you.
Why do you ask?
Please, feel free to go and
reassure your friends you're OK.
There's no real reason
for you to stay here.
I do not intend
to leave!
Oh, no, sorry! I was
talking to somebody else.
You ladies must be exhausted
after searching the city
for so long...! No, really.
You needn't worry about me.
I assure you, I'm quite well!
Thank you...
I'm sorry. I really am.
I just forgot...
[KONGO] Well then, as much
as I hate to leave you all...
I must go...
But if something
important comes up,
you'll tell me, won't you...?
I mean, after what's happened,
we're all Febri's
friends aren't we?
Yes... we are.
[UIHARU] I don't understand.
What does it all mean?
[KUROKO] Febri is a target...
That's what they said.
[SATEN] Wow,
they're really cold.
Acting like she's
just some thing.
[footsteps]
[FROG DOCTOR] Good morning.
Febri!
Ah, Mikoto!
[SATEN] Are you
feeling okay, Febri?
What...? Am I okay?
[UIHARU] Hi, sweetie...
We were worried about you.
You collapsed all of a sudden!
Gekota... are you okay?
[SATEN and UIHARU] Huh?
[KUROKO] I'm guessing that
means she feels all right now.
[FEBRI] Hmm?
[MIKOTO sighs]
A moment, please?
[SATEN] You're sure that
you don't hurt anywhere?
Gekota's fine!
Still as cute
as ever, huh?
[MIKOTO] Doctor.
We'd like to thank you
for all your help.
Please don't. I didn't
actually do anything.
Huh...? But you...
[FROG DOCTOR] I'm sorry,
but helping her
is beyond my capabilities...
I don't understand...
Is it serious?
Please. Surely you
can do something?
[FROG DOCTOR] No...
If it were some human
illness, I'm sure I could.
But the fact is...
She's not human.
Huh?
The girl has been
scientifically engineered.
She's a construction.
[MIKOTO] What?
[KONGO] Oh, wow!
I got the preview?
I was only doing what I, Mitsuko
Kongo, thought was right.
Next time...
I will save the world!
[KUROKO] Oh, just shut up!