[KAMIJO pants]
Ah!
[thud]
[KAMIJO] Ow! Damn it.
I don't have time for this.
I've got to hurry.
Is that zap earlier
making my legs shake?
Is it that?
Or, on the inside,
am I just terrified?
Ah, I may talk a good game,
but I'm pathetic.
No time for self-pity.
I need to get a grip.
It's starting in-
Seriously?
Of all times to freeze up!
The electric shock!
[MISAKA 10032 groans]
[ACCELERATOR] Hey, come on.
Aren't you guys all supposed to
be mentally linked together
or something?
I gave one of your buddies a big
hint during the last experiment.
Shouldn't you have had time
to learn from it by now?
Hey.
We have a visitor.
How do you suppose that
plays into everything?
[MISAKA 10032] It's you, but
what are you doing here?
[MISAKA 10032 grunts]
What, are you inviting members
of the general public
to our testing sites, now?
That's irritating.
See, I didn't budget any time
for silencing outsiders
who discovered
our secret.
[KAMIJO] Step away from her.
What the hell?
Did you say
something?
[KAMIJO] Step away now.
Get away from
Misaka's sister.
I mean it!
Get away from her now,
you damn loser!
[MISAKA 10032] Why? Why are you?
[ACCELERATOR] "Get away from
her." Is that what you said?
You've got a set.
Talking like that.
There are seven
Level 5 espers.
I am undeniably the most
powerful one in the entire city,
and you stand there
calling me a loser?
I'm sick of
repeating myself.
Get the hell away from her!
Oh, yeah?
I have to admit,
you're intriguing.
But instead of
getting away from her.
How about, I get
her away from me.
[KAMIJO groans]
That was a close one!
[MISAKA 10032] "What is this?"
"What in the world
are you doing here?"
Misaka asks in utter shock.
Why would you take such a
risk for somebody like Misaka?
As long as the
necessary chemicals
and equipment are available.
Misakas can be manufactured
with the touch of a button.
The bodies are fabricated,
stocked with borrowed minds.
The process has been
repeated many times.
There are still nine thousand
nine hundred and sixty eight
untouched units ready for use.
Yet for the sake of a
laboratory rat, you would--
[KAMIJO] I don't care.
Manufactured or not,
it doesn't matter to me.
And you're more than just
a bunch of chemicals now.
After all.
You're still the only one of
you in the whole world, right?
That's why I came here.
Sorry, but, you aren't
going to be dying.
Not today.
You've still got
accounts to settle.
[MISAKA 10032]
"He'll kill you."
Says Misaka.
[ACCELERATOR] Nice speech.
Did you just come up with that,
or have you been practicing?
[KAMIJO] So, do they ever
give you a day off?
What?
[KAMIJO] Last night,
in that back alley.
Oh. You saw the
work I did there, huh?
Blood flow
manipulation.
My first time, too.
Hell of a performance
though, don't you think?
I mean, who knew there
was that much blood
swimmin' around in a person?
Ha! But wind-up dolls
aren't people, right?
[KAMIJO] Enough.
I thought that maybe
they had you doing this
against your will, but now,
I see how wrong I was.
I'm gonna make sure you
don't hurt these girls.
Ever again.
[ACCELERATOR chuckles]
[KAMIJO yells]
[ACCELERATOR] Heh.
[KAMIJO groans]
Oh man, you're slow!
[ACCELERATOR] Seriously.
This is pathetic.
If that's the best you can do,
you don't stand
a chance in hell.
[KAMIJO] Damn.
Heh, heh, heh.
[MIKOTO] I couldn't stop him.
I tried. But I failed
at that, too.
Then again. I wouldn't
put it past that guy
to do something
even I couldn't do.
Like it was nothing.
Of course, it's
a lot more likely
that he'll get himself killed.
[KITTY meows]
Hey, kitty. Have we met?
Was that you stuck up that tree?
[KITTY meows]
[MIKOTO] Heh. I'm sorry.
It's kinda difficult to
tell you apart, you know?
[MIKOTO] Like the sisters.
They're the same on the outside,
but each one of them
still has her own life.
They're people.
[KITTY meows]
[MIKOTO] There's a reason
I can't leave this
up to anyone else.
[KITTY meows]
[MIKOTO] I can't.
Saving them is still
my responsibility.
Now, let's go.
[ACCELERATOR] Hold on.
Could he be?
[KAMIJO coughs]
[ACCELERATOR] By any chance,
are you a non-esper?
The way you showed up
and started trash talking,
I thought you must
have... some rank,
but now I'm starting to think
I was wrong about that.
You're the smallest fry
out there, aren't you?
[ACCELERATOR] I don't like this.
[KAMIJO grunts]
[ACCELERATOR] There have been
any number of misguided idiots
who have challenged
me to a fight,
hoping to win
top-dog status.
And there's
always a moment,
frequently after losing
an eye or a limb.
when they realize their mistake.
Their faces contort in an
agony of regret and terror.
Tch.
And then there's
this guy.
[ACCELERATOR] Come on.
You've gotta know by now I'm
exponentially stronger than you.
Of course, if you want
to die that badly,
I'm happy to oblige by
blowing you to pieces.
You see that
container over there?
Seems there was flour in it.
And there's no
wind tonight, either.
It's nice and calm.
That could turn this into a
really dangerous situation.
[KAMIJO gasps]
[ACCELERATOR] Hey third-string,
have you ever heard
of something called
a dust explosion?
[KAMIJO groans]
[ACCELERATOR] Yeah.
Dust explosions are nasty.
Next time I try that,
I should remember not to
put myself in the
middle of it, though.
I always thought I could survive
even a nuclear explosion.
I may need to reconsider that.
Oh?
You're going to keep
trying to fight me?
Really?
[distant explosion]
[MIKOTO] An explosion?
Oh, no! Is he?
[KITTY meows]
[MIKOTO] Sorry.
But I can't drag you
into this mess, too.
[ACCELERATOR] In a way
you're actually lucky
that you don't have
any esper ability.
My "Reflection" skill doesn't
work well on somebody so weak.
You know, strange as it is,
you've done pretty well so far.
You're still alive, and,
considering I'm your opponent,
that's a miracle.
I'm getting bored, though.
So let's put an end
to this, shall we?
Pick a hand,
any hand.
It doesn't matter
which touches you.
With either one I can reverse
the flow of your blood,
resulting in a messy death.
So, which one
will it be?
The right hand?
Or the left hand?
Or both?
[punch]
[ACCELERATOR] The moon?
What am I looking
at the moon for?
I guess because
I'm flat on my back.
But what the hell am I doing
lying on the ground?
Huh? Him?
He was just in front
of me. How did he?
Wait. Never mind where he is.
How is he still standing
there in one piece?
What the? I'm hurt?
I'm even bleeding?
What the hell
happened here?!
He knocked me
on my ass?
Me? Impossible!
If he did that, his
arm should be broken.
How could he even touch me?
[footstep]
[ACCELERATOR laughs]
I must've focused
everything into my hands,
shutting down the "Reflection"
around the rest of me.
Damn, what an
idiotic move!
Impressive. Ha, heh, ha, ha!
No, I mean it. That was good.
A solid hit! I'll give you that.
You really nailed me! But now!
[MIKOTO] No way.
He's fighting Accelerator,
and he's on the offensive?
Against the strongest
guy in Academy City?
He's basically
a stranger.
We're certainly not friends.
He could walk away.
Nobody would blame him.
But instead...
He's keeping his promise.
[ACCELERATOR]
Damn you! Stop moving!
What is the deal with
your right hand, huh?
I wouldn't get too carried away
if I were you, Third string!
[KAMIJO winces]
[ACCELERATOR laughs]
[KAMIJO] You should never have
gotten involved with this.
So many Sisters, living
the best that they can.
They use up all their
strength just to fight you.
They deserve better.
They're living beings.
Not fodder for some
ruthless bastard.
[ACCELERATOR] They're living?
What's he talking about?
They're just
wind-up dolls.
That's what they
said, isn't it?
I need power.
The power to make him
stop saying this stuff.
No, more.
I need the dominion
over reason and rules
that comes from absolute power!
[ACCELERATOR babbles]
[KAMIJO yells]
[MIKOTO] Where did all
this wind come from?
[MIKOTO gasps]
[thud]
Is, is he?
No.
No!
[ACCELERATOR] The air,
the wind, the atmosphere.
I can win this fight.
I've got the means to kill
that piece of crap right here,
all around me.
If I could control
the direction of the air
that's flowing through
the atmosphere.
If I could control the
world's wind currents,
I could destroy
anything I want to.
My reach would be infinite.
My power would be
absolutely unstoppable!
The strongest esper
in Academy City?
The only Level 6?
I wouldn't need that anymore!
There would be nothing
and nobody in the universe
who could stop me!
The world and everything
in it is in my hand!
Compress it.
Compress all the air!
Hey, third string!
You have given me
a fantastic idea!
What happened to all
that spunk you had?
Come on! Get up! Get up!
I need you to stick with me
for a little longer here.
Okay?
It's almost over now!
[MIKOTO] Accelerator!
Stay right
where you are.
[KAMIJO] D-Don't do it.
Misaka...
[MIKOTO] I can't believe it.
He's alive!
I'm sorry. I know you
wanted a happy ending,
but once I die, the experiments
will finally be over.
It might be selfish.
I know that, but still--I don't
want you to die because of me.
So now.
[MIKOTO] What in
the world is that?
He's compressing the wind into
one point to create plasma?
What's his plan?
To blow this whole area away?
Those eyes. They're so blank.
He paid me no more
attention than an insect.
Obviously the only thing he's
interested in at all right now
is testing his new power.
What do I do? What can I?
He's compressing all the wind
in the city into one point.
Maybe, if I use all the
windmills around town.
Sure, But how?
I can't do it by myself!
[MIKOTO] Please!
You have to wake up!
[MIKOTO] She's freezing.
In the shape she's in now,
how can I ask this of her?
I realize that I'm
asking a lot of you,
and with everything
that's happened,
I know I don't have the right.
But please!
Please, there's something
I need you to do!
It's, it's something
that only you can do!
I hate this!
Why do I have to be
so damn powerless?
I can't do this.
I can't protect everyone myself!
The Ace of Tokiwadai?
One of only seven Level 5s.
And I can't do anything!
I can't heal her injuries.
I can't stop Accelerator.
I can't give Kamijo
the ending he wants!
Please get up! I'm begging you!
Get up and do what you can.
Not for me, but for him!
[MISAKA 10032] I am confused.
I'm not sure I understand
everything you are saying.
But for some reason...
I find your words moving.
So I am happy to help you.
[ACCELERATOR] Amazing!
It's like a part of my body!
Like moving my own arms or legs!
All of this air is completely
under my control!
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
So fighting someone stronger
really was a shortcut
to leveling up! Guess
they were right all along!
Thanks, third-string!
You served your purpose well,
and now I'm going
to destroy you! Huh?
How could this be
happening now?
It looks like the
plasma is diffusing.
I know there were no
glitches in my calculations,
and this is too irregular
to be a natural wind.
Thanks, you did great.
You can let me
take it from here.
[MIKOTO] I should be able to
create a big enough opening
for them to escape.
[MISAKA 10032] I can do it.
If Misaka interferes
with the target
he will focus his attention
on her and be distracted.
Then you can take the boy,
and leave this place.
I don't think so.
You've already done
more than enough.
Let your big sister
take it from here.
[ACCELERATOR] Why is the wind
suddenly acting like this?
It's not wind
manipulation. So, what?
The windmills are
turning the wrong way.
Hold on. I've heard
about this before.
It's something about
dynamo motors.
When they're hit by particular
electromagnetic waves, they--
Is it them?
Damn it.
What do they think
they're doing?
Those windmills aren't just
spinning around haphazardly.
They're being directed
to disrupt my formulas!
[ACCELERATOR] She's doing it!
The images she sees are
going across the network!
I'm gonna' kill you!
I won't let you!
[KAMIJO] That voice.
[MIKOTO] You managed
to defeat me,
both in town and
out by the riverbed.
They're nothing
but big computers
programmed to control us.
If my one life can save
ten thousand of theirs,
that's a good thing isn't it?
It's not much, but
maybe it's enough?
Please, help.
Somebody help.
Please help me.
[ACCELERATOR] I'm not gonna
to let any of you weaklings
stand in my way anymore!
No matter what, I will
become invincible!