Oh, thank goodness.
I made it in time.
Now there's only one
thing left to do.
Johann.
I'm doing what
you asked of me.
No matter...
How much I don't want to.
But I will not
move further.
Not without an
impossible miracle.
It is...
All that I can do to
resist someone so dear.
[Music]
Preventing the God of
Creation's revival.
Capturing the
Palace of the Stars.
Destroying Bal
Masqué's leadership.
We indeed accomplished
none of it.
Look, we're almost there!
Hong Kong International!
I can't wait to see
Sophie and the others.
What's wrong
with you guys?
I've seen livelier
groups at a funeral!
Don'tcha wanna celebrate
us makin' our return to...
Would you show some
consideration for others?
Stupid Marco!
That's what I'm doin'!
Everyone's so
damn depressed,
I'm just tryin' to lighten
the mood a little b...
She must be quite
exhausted indeed.
Rest needed.
Yo!
Greetings. I'm glad you all
made it here as planned.
Good timing.
Yes, well.
How do the kids
put it these days?
We had our asses
handed to us.
Okay.
That is not the
rallying speech
I was expecting from
our fearless leader.
But the expression
does kind of fit.
Got that right.
We just lost eighty
percent of our troops,
and among the survivors,
morale is zilch.
Things are as bad as the
look on the old man's face.
But Khamsin's face aside,
most people would say we're more
or less finished as an army.
Given all that,
you don't seem too upset.
Do you have a
counterattack plan?
Not even an inkling.
But we know what
we have to do.
We gave our word
to Centerhill.
We told him we would
continue to fight.
This isn't over yet.
We're not out of the game.
We still have
one card left.
That basically sums it up.
Yeah, I get it.
I wouldn't say that
it's the craziest plan
I've ever heard.
It's only like threadin'
a needle from a mile away.
Tryin' another long shot so
soon just seems desperate.
But not impossible.
We do have the
Scroll of Secrets
the Spiral Organ gave to the
Specialist of Everything.
I shall offer
you two things.
The first of which
being information.
And the second is...
The Snake of the Festival
insists that
with the creation of Xanadu
we will no longer have
any reason to fight.
Unfortunately, I can't say
that I'm quite as optimistic.
Especially not after
hearing the truth
revealed to us by Centerhill.
Damage to the world
does not occur simply
because Crimson Denizens
use Power of Existence.
It occurs because they
consume human souls,
making that Power of
Existence unstable.
Let's suppose it
goes as he claims,
that all the Denizens
follow him to paradise,
and the new world overflows
with Power of Existence.
If they act there the
same way they have here.
It's just delaying
the inevitable.
Sure, this world might be
protected for hundreds,
or even thousands of years.
But in the distant future,
not only this world,
but the new one,
and the Crimson World,
will be threatened
by a great cataclysm
that cannot be averted.
-Which is why I think...
-One moment.
You do understand
our forces
have suffered a crippling
defeat, don't you child?
That is why we are
attempting to explain...
It's not your plan
I'm worried about.
Only what is in
everyone's hearts.
Yes Shana, as you say,
we could go all-out,
fighting to protect
the world's balance.
It is, after all, our
primary task as Flame Hazes.
However, there are many
who view that task
as nothing more
than an excuse.
Which is why the words of
the Snake of the Festival,
Yuji Sakai,
were sufficient to send
the Flame Haze running.
Many Flame Haze
exist solely
to carry out personal
oaths of vengeance.
Forcing them to
fight for a world
that isn't even ours is
cruel, to say the least.
Of course.
I do not doubt the courage
of anyone in this room.
But I believe that,
in order for us to
determine our next course,
we must all look
inwards to find resolve,
rather than to
words of bravado.
Bear in mind, Headquarters has
yet to reach a formal decision,
which means we will most
likely be on our own
for any future battles.
I cannot guarantee we'll
receive any support from Outlaw.
Well, that's fine with me.
I ain't afraid of
handlin' things on my own.
I'm a big girl
so I don't need Outlaw
or anyone else to fight
my battles for me!
Slow down.
As the Supreme Commander said,
this is not a decision
to be taken lightly.
You can't just jump
into battle this time,
you need to think it over.
That being said,
I'm afraid we don't have the
luxury of time on our side.
François has arranged a
charter flight for us
that will depart in
about four hours.
I would like you
to use this time
to think over everything
we've discussed
and consider your options.
Then, each one of you,
will have to make a choice.
You can either come with
us to fight, or stay here.
She's been thinking
this over for some time.
Abrupt announcement.
Indeed.
I now realize she's
been thinking about
our next move ever
since our defeat.
It was rather foolish
of me to assume
she was simply exhausted.
I thought the same.
I've taught her
since she was little.
We must always
fight for our cause.
This is what a
Flame Haze does.
I made sure it
was ingrained
into the very
core of her being.
For the sake of a friend
who sacrificed
herself to the cause.
And now when the cause
itself appears to waver,
indeed her commitment
is still firm.
This isn't over yet.
I wonder what gives
her that strength.
Yuji Sakai.
Margery!
Hey kiddo, you made it.
How's Heaven's Road?
François's there now.
It's moored
outside the city.
There's not a whole lot of
palace parking near the airport.
Smart thinkin' there.
Margery.
Shana just filled me in.
Have you decided
what you're gonna do?
Are you gonna go
fight with her?
You don't know me
at all, do you?
Well, I thought I did.
What little devotion I
might've had to the cause,
I lost a long time ago.
So the midget's
rallying speech
really didn't
do much for me.
So then...
After everything
we've been through,
there's no way in hell I'm
backing out of this fight now.
What would be the point
of comin' all this way
if we weren't gonna
finish the job?
Gimme a break!
And you, Keisaku?
My decision's
never gonna change.
I'm with you to
the end, Margery.
You arrogant boy.
I wonder how the
young lady is faring.
Me, too. I hope she's safe.
Since you geezers
are still here,
I'm guessing it's
safe to assume
you've decided to
go with Nietono?
Of course.
Judging by your demeanor,
it's fairly obvious your
decision hasn't changed.
Thanks to a
certain someone,
my contractor is
all fired up now.
I wouldn't say "fired up".
But I did take a vow,
and I like to think that my word
is worth something at least.
I can respect that
point of view.
Call it instinct
or experience,
but if something sounds
too good to be true,
it usually is.
Especially in this case,
considering the source.
Forget about me, what
do the two of you think?
Ah, well.
If Shana's plan is the
one that is most likely
to achieve the
results we desire,
then I think we
should try it.
Now I can respect
that point of view!
But any way
you look at it,
we still lack the numbers
we will need for success.
Well, perhaps we
should start by praying
we don't lose any more.
Hey, Sale.
I think Shana's plan is
probably gonna be the best
for everyone involved.
We were told to decide
for ourselves, kid.
You don't need my
seal of approval.
Aw, come on.
How can you be so dense?
Can't you see she's worried
about being separated?
She wants to choose
the same path
so you guys don't
get split up.
No, I... I've already...
I've made my decision.
I was thoroughly
impressed with her plan
but that's to be expected
from the God of Atonement's
contractor.
Having the fate of the
world in our hands is scary
but also exhilarating!
Dontcha think?
I'm not motivated by revenge
like all the other Flame Haze,
'cause I was
artificially created.
But my dear old "dad"
is one of the bastards
who's behind this.
If I can keep that nutcase
from going to a world
full of Power of Existence,
then I got all
the reason I need
to get out there
and fight, you know?
Hurry up!
Quit fiddling
with that, Domino!
You can activate
the Crypta later!
Right now, though,
our one and only goal...
Is to get the blasted Palace
of the Stars up and flying!
What? But without the Crypta,
the Palace of the Stars will be
plainly visible, Professor...
Imbecile!
Don't you think I'm
aware of that, Domino?
But our first priority is
doing everything in our power
to keep Outlaw from
having time to plan!
Those were the orders
Bel-Peol gave us!
And they still stand!
Master, I'm told you have
another proclamation
for the Denizens?
I do.
The ceremony to create
the paradise Xanadu
shall take place in Japan.
And that will
be all for now.
That's rather vague
for an official proclamation,
don't you think?
I said that will be all.
Sir.
This is where you'll
perform the ceremony?
Yes it must be held here.
I would like to count
on your help in this,
Spiral Organ.
Will it involve something
beyond the undertaking
I was previously hired for?
That ring.
It belonged to
Friagne the Hunter.
It did.
What of it?
Nothing. I was merely thinking
how strange fate can be.
I want to thank you,
Supreme Commander.
For what, dear?
For reminding me I can't
just focus on my own task.
I have to consider
everyone else, as well.
I apologize for being
careless with my words.
I got caught up
in her enthusiasm.
Please forgive me.
It doesn't matter what
the others decide,
I am incredibly proud of you
for leading the charge
down a new path.
You hold your head high
instead of cowering in fear.
They have 'em in
Hong Kong, too!
My, my.
In all these years,
that smile hasn't changed.
This one tastes a
little different
than the ones
I get in Japan.
But the outside's
all crispy
and the inside's
all fluffy!
Tell me, Sophie Sawallisch.
While I imagine our
advice was rather helpful.
Do you think it
was really needed?
Well let's see,
Takemikazuchi.
If nothing else,
it gave me the courage
to carry out what
we're about to do.
Shana, let me ask
you something.
I've noticed you're
more comfortable
in your own skin now,
did my letter
help encourage you?
And Yuji had a lot
to do with it, too.
Very good.
Now that I know I don't
have to worry about you,
I should get back to Outlaw
headquarters in Zurich.
Why do you have to leave?
They have demanded
her presence there.
An emergency debriefing,
to discuss this
recent defeat.
The debriefing
is just pretext.
If you go, they'll simply
pin all the blame on you.
It's even possible...
That I will be relieved
of my command, yes.
Sophie!
Part of my job as
Supreme Commander
is taking responsibility
for all the failures
of those under me.
Come.
It's almost time to go.
And if I'm right,
none of the
other Flame Haze
will have the
sense to drop out.
They're as
stubborn as we are!
Yeah!
Yep. I'm taking a special
flight back tonight.
I took an extra
long vacation,
so we can finally have some
"together time" for once.
It's been quiet
around here.
I'm not sure if you'll
see Wilhelmina and Shana,
they've been gone
for some time.
Aw. That's too bad.
Guess it just means I'll
have you all to myself.
Well, you and the soon-to-be
newest member of the family.
And I am gonna spoil
my lovely wife rotten,
since I rarely
get the chance.
Ooh! I'm looking
forward to it.
Everyone has
indeed decided.
Even though all of their
reasons may differ.
Steadfast resolve.
With passion in
their hearts.
Every one of them
will move forward
as best they can.
I've lived to the fullest
for as long as I could.
Yes.
That's the answer
right there,
isn't it,
Mathilde Saint-Omer?
The child I...
no, that we raised.
She'll follow whatever
path she's decided on.
Let that be what
we fight for.
They're gonna make that
paradise in Japan, huh?
Get this, I got a request for
help from Bal Masqué yesterday.
Who knows how the heck they
found us all the way out here.
Well,. I'm sure they're trying
to round up as many pawns
as they can get their
scheming hands on.
Got no problem using
others as pawns
but I don't really dig
it the other way around.
Obviously.
Aren't you worried?
They're gonna get pissed if we
keep ignoring them, boss-man.
You think I give a crap
about their gods or Xanadu?
It ain't exactly paradise
if you gotta work
so hard to get it.
Hell, I'm content
to sit in the sun
and enjoy a hot cup o'
joe with some friends.
That's us: cheap,
relaxed, and simple.
What need have we
for gods, right?
Good morning everyone!
Hey, Louie. Thanks.
Here ya go.
I've found you.
Though I wish I hadn't.
Listen everyone,
I want you all to go out
and fight to the best
of your abilities.
Unfortunately, we'll be
getting a lecture in Zurich
and cannot join you.
So please do some
damage for us.
You can count on me.
I just gotta act natural,
and waltz right inside
the Heaven's Road Palace.
Be sure to give us
the exact timing,
once the plan's
schedule is decided.
If you could, please tell
François I said hello.
Well, we've got a long,
hard road ahead of us.
We have to travel
halfway around the world
and then right back again.
Here's hopin' we'll have
three more folks with us
when we make the
journey back.
It is arranged.
A meeting with the three
remaining Gods of the Earth
indeed awaits
you in New York.
Ah, yes.
With their assistance,
everything we will
have to do next
should proceed a
lot more smoothly.
But whether or not they'll
agree to fight at our side
is still a big question.
Difficult battle.
Stressing out about
it won't help.
We'll just have to
talk to them and see.
You make a good point.
Especially in their case.
And it's not that they
aren't good people.
But the fact that Centerhill
is the easiest to deal with
tells you something.
I'm not looking
forward to it,
-but there's no choice.
-Yes.
On to New York.
I'll pass along to the
remaining Gods of the Earth
the words that
Centerhill left behind.
[Music]
Reignition is a success!
We are cookin' with gas!
Congratulations,
Professor!
Master.
Give the Palace her heading.
We'll go northeast!
On to Japan.
To Misaki City.
Yuji.
I will find you.
[Music]
Shana and the others
head to New York
to meet with the three
remaining Gods of the Earth
and ask for their help.
Meanwhile, back
in Misaki City,
Yuji appears before Yoshida
and Tanaka one last time.
Next time, on Shakugan
no Shana Final.
"For Whose Sake?"