Stop right there.
Shana.
Remember what I said?
It is impossible for me
to stand by your side
as long as you're
a Flame Haze.
Because you will never
stop condemning
the Crimson Denizens
for their nature!
They are treated as
if they don't belong.
You reject
their existence!
That is why I have chosen
to create their paradise.
I will take them to
Xanadu where they belong.
After they've departed,
the world of the humans will
be left in everlasting peace!
Why do you fight to
prevent that outcome?
Do you not realize
this is also the only way to
fulfill Yuji Sakai's desires?
I implore you,
do not stop me.
[Music]
That's it?
You're telling me that's the
reason you can't be with me?
Those feelings.
The ones we shared.
Why can't you
believe in them?
Yuji.
Why?
I would've thought that
after living in the
human world for so long
you'd be better with
the ladies, master.
No, I didn't have
much luck with girls.
If you would be willing to offer
me a few pointers, General,
I'm all ears.
Unfortunately, I never had
much luck with 'em, either.
Ready, Wilhelmina?
I am, milady.
Master!
Throw me! Now!
The Psalm of
the Grand Order.
Yes!
And this is the
Treasure Tool, Chorde!
A projectile weapon that
carries an Unrestricted Spell.
I remember it well.
I have no idea how you got
your hands on the Psalm
but a lone projectile is
no threat to my plans.
What makes you think
I only have one?
It's over!
You must have
underestimated
how important this is to me.
Did you honestly believe
that I would leave
it so vulnerable?
Dontcha think you
should be helping her?
She's a big girl.
She can handle
that bonehead.
What the...?
Should I call the 'big girl'
to help you instead?
Shut up.
It's probably one
of my old man's...
Well, hello Sale Habichtsburg!
I must say,
I'm beyond thrilled
that you could
join us for our
"It's time to pay your dues
and get your just
desserts" party!
Hang on to your
hat, Sale boy!
Huh?
Yes! Tremble in fear
and awe while your eyes
drink in the glory of the
ultimate "One-Hit Kill" weapon!
The miracle of science,
Excellent 252580!
The Ultimate Fist Circle!
Wonderful. I need a drink.
Yeah, make that two.
They certainly sound like
they're having a
blast out there.
Remind me why I'm stuck
inside this roach motel, again?
What did ya
expect, darlin'?
They're the decoys!
We're the ones with the real
job here, so no complaining.
Okay.
Don't give me that
mischievous grin.
If we wanna help our pals,
we have to do
our part, got it?
Yeah, yeah, but
it's still a drag.
I'd rather be drinking.
I didn't expect the girl
to be in the tower as well.
This could be a problem.
Ah. If she's useful to them
they'll keep her close
and make sure she's guarded.
Let's go.
Where did he come from?
No! Wait a second.
He's trying to bring
down the tower!
I'll take care of
this, Bel-Peol!
Stand back!
I guess it worked.
What a mess.
What happened?
Am I going to die?
No.
If that happens,
then there wasn't any
point in coming here.
Sydonay didn't want
Hecate to leave his side
but, in the end,
he let her go,
because he loved her.
I know Shana and Sakai
love each other.
But love is never as simple
as sharing the same path.
When you care that
deeply for someone,
sometimes you have to do things
that hurt them or yourself.
That's how it is
with everyone.
I mean, Pheles is doing
what Johann asked her,
even though it
pains her to do so.
And poor Johann is forced
to be separated from her.
Because they're
both in love.
I think Pheles gave
me the Giralda
because she didn't
want me to use it!
But, if things continue
on their present course,
all that will remain
is sorrow!
I have to!
Shana!
Cut this for me!
Thanks a lot, Shana.
It's time to try it!
Kazumi.
They're trapped in a
fight they don't want.
I have the power
to change that.
By doing this, I could be
putting Sakai's life in danger.
It may even ruin whatever
Shana has planned, but...
I think it's for the best.
I feel like this is
the right thing to do.
For them, I'm willing
to throw my life away.
No.
I won't throw it away.
I'll make it
worth something!
I can hear you.
Your feelings are
so very strong.
I'm alive. Why?
The Giralda was created
as a means for humans
to use Unrestricted Spells.
You see,
humans cannot focus
on a single thought.
Concentration is key.
The chaos of your
mind inhibits you.
However, if you truly believe
you're sacrificing yourself,
your resolve can be used to
cast an Unrestricted Spell.
So I'm not gonna die?
Not today.
Did you give it to me
because you knew
this would happen?
No, quite the
opposite, in fact.
I never imagined that
you would try to use it.
But you did,
and your feelings created a
miracle which brought me here.
As we stand at this
crucial juncture,
I will change the path
that this battle follows.
Kazumi Yoshida.
You have done well.
Rest now, as I
grant your wish.
Pheles!
I am here to change the
course of this battle.
Though I dread it,
the time has come for me
to fulfill Johann's wish.
Pheles.
Why didn't you tell me?
Let me help you!
No, I'm sorry.
Pheles!
I didn't think Yoshida
had the courage to
summon her here.
What?
I've got you.
Wake up, my beloved.
Hello.
It's good to see
you again, Yuji.
Or should I call you the
Snake of the Festival?
I'm leaving you now.
And I'll be taking
our Treasure Tool,
the Midnight Lost Child.
Yuji! Stay out of this!
If you were inside me,
as you claim to have been,
then you know what
Yuji Sakai is planning.
Are you opposed to it?
I suppose you
could say that.
I mean, I admire his
passion and his devotion,
but, I can't go
along with it.
Why is that?
I don't mind the means,
I just don't like the ends.
The ends?
Yes.
It seems to me
Yuji's getting the
short end of the stick.
Right?
While I think
it's a noble vow,
your little plan,
it's pretty boring.
In the end, everyone
winds up miserable.
Now tell me, where's
the fun in that?
You think this is
some sort of game?
I think you do.
And you've made it
nearly impossible
for anyone else to play.
The rules are too narrow;
"I did this,
so I have to do that".
You've left no
other options open.
There are none!
I'll do what I can then
accept my punishment.
It's narrow but necessary!
Is it also necessary to make
the girl you love unhappy?
If love is what inspired
your plan to begin with,
I think it's okay for you
to be a little selfish.
Shana would never go
along with my plan.
How can you be so sure?
You haven't even
told her about it.
You're so obsessed with
pursuing your goal,
you haven't paid any
attention to the person
that goal was meant
to benefit most.
If you mention it, I think
Shana might understand.
I cannot afford to
be that optimistic!
Revealing anything
at this point
could endanger
Xanadu's creation!
Are your plans
really that fragile?
Is it because you don't
trust those around you?
Or could it be...
That's it! Hah!
I have you figured out, Yuji!
Makes perfect sense,
you're underestimating love.
What did you say?
You tell yourself you can't
show her your feelings.
You use them as
an excuse, right?
But all that does is
limit your own potential.
Love has the ability to
leave logic in the dust
and accomplish anything.
One just has to be brave
enough to trust in it.
That is nothing more
than your opinion.
But it's based
on experience.
You, on the other hand,
are throwing away everything
that brings you happiness,
all because you feel
you have to shoulder some
great burden on your own.
Do not pretend you understand
anything about me!
It's nothing more than
my opinion, remember?
It's all right, Johann.
And so is doing this.
I'll let you hold onto
it a little while longer.
What are you doing?
Isn't it obvious?
I'm changing your situation.
Pheles! Ready?
Yes!
I did it.
I did everything
you asked!
I didn't think I'd
be able to do it
but I tried my best for you.
Thank you, my beloved.
I'm sorry I put
you through that.
I promise no one will ever
come between us again.
Yes, I know, we'll
be together forever.
I love you, Johann.
Hurry it up!
Bye now!
Put the pedal to the metal!
You got it, Boss!
You'll be much safer
with them, Kazumi.
He didn't notice the bus
that flew into the
sky was an illusion;
the real one's headed
toward the surface.
That means.
Well, I could've used
her but that's okay.
Yuji!
Tell me.
Did you lose your
detection ability?
An effect of
Johann's departure?
Perhaps.
Does it matter?
How much could
it affect me?
What the...?
Do you normally greet
your guests this way?
Ah. Sorry for forcing
myself on you
but would you like an
escort for your escape?
I'd let a pack of
chimps escort us
if they had your
strength, old man!
I didn't expect the
Hyakki Yakou to show up.
So, the Mobilizer carved a
path for them to get inside.
But why would they
waste so much effort
just to recover that girl?
Who can say?
Whatever their motives, the
damage caused was substantial.
However, I doubt
it'll be anything
more than a minor setback.
Professor, how's the
tower's tuning coming along?
Splendidly, General!
We've just completed the
density calculations,
Now if only this
place wasn't so noisy!
Shut up, Domino!
You're going to ruin my
magnificent, climactic scene
with your incessant
babbling, you moron!
What do you have to
say for yourself?
I'm so very
sorry, Professor!
How long until
we can use it?
Well, when do you
want to use it?
Right now?
Fine.
Sounds good!
Let's do this!
This isn't good, Professor!
The machinery's control room
is completely exposed
to the enemy!
I thought you
removed the monster
form control room functions
after the Strategist
scolded you...
Domino! Keeping
those functions
will add to the tower's
structural integrity!
Call it a "Noble
Self-Sacrifice!"
Sir.
If you want me to protect you,
please keep me informed.
-Can you do that?
-Yeah.
Sorry. Uh. Let's see.
Is it possible to
retract the control room?
I can do better than that!
Canopy close!
Give me a break.
This wasn't part
of the plan,
but I think we're
managing pretty well!
Taking out a single area
would be easier than
demolishing the whole tower!
Eventually we'll have to
destroy the entire thing anyway.
How about we just stick to
the plan we already had?
That sound good to you?
Hey, don't try to
put this on me.
I'm just along
for the ride.
Why do they keep fighting,
when they know they
can't advance?
I really couldn't
care less about
what those idiots are up to.
Soon we'll be in Xanadu and
we'll never see them again.
How strange.
What could they
possibly be planning?
How could this happen?
I've been rejected again.
[Music]
The battle over
Xanadu's creation
grows fiercer
with each breath,
as everyone puts their lives on
the line for their beliefs.
Meanwhile, Flieder
captures Rofocale
and presents him
with a bizarre request.
Next time on Shakugan
no Shana Final:
"The Egg of the World."