No, I'm sorry.
Once again, I find myself
helpless and rejected.
I always try to do
everything myself
yet somehow I never
accomplish anything.
Now no one will
even let me try,
they simply leave me behind.
Indeed, I reached out to her.
I wanted to fight for her.
Yet she chose to reject me
just as everyone else does.
You're free.
Relieved of duty.
Indeed.
She's right.
Now that I've lost my
duty as a Flame Haze,
I suppose that means I'm free.
But here I stand,
terrified at the thought.
What's got you all
upset, Specialist?
We wrapped up our business!
So you can turn that
frown upside down!
I see what's
goin' on here.
You thought your friends,
the Engaged Link,
were gonna ask
you for help,
but instead,
they ditched you
and now you're
feelin' blue about it.
So your buddies didn't
need your help, huh?
Whoa, touchy subject.
I'm upset that nothing is
happening as it should.
Yeah, me too.
But standin' around here
isn't gonna fix anything.
Thousand Changes is bound
to show up any minute now.
You know, you're not gonna
be much help to anyone
if ya don't snap outta
this funk you're in.
Just focus on
what's important
and don't let rejection
get the best of you.
Did you notice
the Engaged Link
took off with the
Hyakki Yakou?
They grabbed Kazumi
and the geezers
and they drove
off into the sky.
That means, there's only
one thing for you to do.
You must take action.
I would get a move
on if I were you.
I'd hate for you
to lose them
'cause you were
wallowing in self-pity.
Indeed, Chanter.
I don't want to lose them.
I cannot hesitate
any longer.
I must act!
Advice from a hunter who
lost her purpose a while back,
the only way to get over it
is to get back in action!
Never thought I'd see the day
you'd be givin' others advice!
[Music]
I know not the road ahead,
however, I still walk it.
As the world changes,
humans and Denizens
change with it.
Is this some
sort of illusion?
We've been looking for you,
Invitation of Cheerful Playing,
Rofocale.
And we've found you.
I must say, you're not an
easy Crimson Denizen to catch.
We were forced to
surround you slowly
to lure you into our trap.
Hello, Transposer of
Corpses and Bodies,
and the Arts and Crafts
of Application.
I can't imagine why you
would go to all this trouble.
Is there a song
you'd like to hear?
No thanks, I'm not a fan.
I don't understand.
I am but a humble musician.
There's nothing else
I have to offer.
Don't try to play dumb!
You know exactly
what we want!
Out of all the god's disciples
you're by far the
easiest to find!
Disciples?
Ah.
You're using your
clairvoyance
to monitor the situation
in Misaki City, right?
We have come to
you with a request.
And that is?
We want an oracle from
the God of Guidance.
I had no idea seeing
the flow of power
would be so
difficult on my own.
It's not going to
take her very long
to figure out the
Silver's attack patterns.
I need new tactics.
Comin' through!
Sorry we're late.
Thanks, Sydonay.
You're here just in time.
All of a sudden, the boy's
personality has become dominant.
This could be a bad sign.
I've completed a
thorough assessment
of the battlefield, Master.
And I believe those three
are our biggest threat.
I didn't expect Margery to make
an appearance, that's for sure.
What did Bel-Peol say?
She thinks the Chanter
and the Mobilizer of
Ceremonial Equipment
planted something
in the tower.
She's investigating
it right now.
I see.
Since you're here with us,
I assume you did
what we asked?
Yep, all done.
No need to worry
about a thing.
Unless you think Lamies
and his little pal
might cause us trouble.
The Spiral Organ
has given us a great deal
of information, indeed,
and has provided
the necessary data
to analyze the Psalm
of the Grand Order.
While she does not wish
to aid us further,
I do not think she
wishes us harm.
Trust for now.
She was gettin' all
caught up in her head.
We practically had to drag
her broodin' butt out here.
We did our best,
as her friends,
to shake her out of it.
but I'm afraid the
rest is up to you.
You ready, Wilhelmina?
Indeed, I am.
A major explosion
has been reported in central
block twenty-four!
The Flame's color is pink.
So far, no intruders
have been sighted.
Interesting.
Purple lightning was recently
detected in block four.
This could be the work of the
Scatterer of Sparkling Light
or the Braider of
Trembling Might
but for some reason,
it feels too deliberate.
I suppose I'll have
to divert some men
to find out the truth.
At this point, we shall
assume the first report
was a diversion.
Thus, your primary task
is recon, not combat.
Yes, ma'am!
I'm impressed
with the enemy.
They'll keep us guessing
till the very end.
Excuse me, Strategist.
I would like to
make a suggestion.
Oh? And what is that?
For your safety, we should order
members of our defensive forces
to stand guard in the
central control room.
I appreciate your concern
but that's not necessary.
But Strategist,
are you sure?
I've already completed
all of the preparations
the master ordered.
There's no need to
protect me any longer.
It's far too late now.
There's nothing they
can do to stop us.
Flieder and Brigid
successfully captured Rofocale?
Yes, ma'am.
Apparently, they're trying to
negotiate with him right now.
And if all goes well,
the oracle will
happen in time.
We need it to come before the
Midnight Lost Child regenerates,
which is only an
hour from now.
Indeed.
All we can do now is wait.
I sincerely hope the God
of Guidance's influence
will somehow
persuade the Denizens
to change their ways
once and for all.
We have done everything
we possibly can.
As you said, all we
can do now is wait.
What will constitute
a victory in this war?
I wonder whose approval
we're ultimately seeking.
I see.
So, you want to
use my god's power
to spread the Flaming-Haired
Blazing-Eyed Hunter's plan
across the entire world?
Uh yeah, that's right.
Impossible.
Impossible?
But you're her
disciple, aren't you?
We were told the only way
to receive an oracle
from the God of Guidance
was to contact one
of her followers!
Technically, you are correct.
but I'm afraid
it's not that easy.
Would you stop making
excuses and...
That's enough, Brigid,
thank you.
After we've come
all this way,
the least that you can do is
tell us why it's not possible.
Very well, then.
I will.
Why, you ask?
What you seek is the
reason it cannot be done.
It is simple.
So very simple.
That which will be,
even if left alone.
That which is already
on such a path.
Needs no guidance.
Without reason we cannot
summon our God of Guidance,
the Thunderous Chant
of Awakening, Shaher.
It is more than simple.
It is natural.
I don't understand.
When that which we disciples
see and hear is like a flame,
at risk of fading away
without guidance.
Only then are we
granted the ability
to summon the divine
power of our God, Shaher,
and act as her vessel.
We're gonna make it
through this, Sale!
They certainly aren't gonna make
this easy on us, are they?
Stop!
It hurts.
I wish I didn't
have to be so cruel.
There's no need
to feel guilty.
It is our duty
to kill them.
We're coming for you,
Grim Reaper!
Whenever I face a foe
without the good sense
to fear my beautiful dead,
I find it to be an
exhilarating experience.
Wouldn't you agree,
my god, Tezcatlipoca?
Yes indeed, I do.
This is almost too easy!
Just look how quickly
they multiply!
As long as our comrades
continue to feast
there is no stopping us!
On this day, we are birds.
We take flight in the
face of difficult winds.
We look down from the
heavens and the stars above.
And see, in our hearts,
how small our world truly is.
The plan of the Flaming-Haired
Blazing-Eyed Hunter
is not enough to merit the
summoning of our god.
It doesn't
require guidance.
To invoke her divine
power would be pointless.
Will you please tell us
what conditions must be met
in order to successfully
summon the God of Guidance?
The first is reality.
If something in Misaki City
happens to catch my god's eye,
then perhaps
there is a chance.
Isn't the Flaming-Haired
Blazing-Eyed Hunter's
plan enough?
No, I'm afraid it's not.
A theatre of war is
unfolding on the stage
where the new world
will be created.
No one can know what
the outcome will be.
If you're fortunate.
Something unexpected
may occur.
How is this possible?
Jeez, would ya
cool it, Khamsin?
Try not to stand
out so much!
You're freakin'
me out, man!
Quit your whinin', Gyuuki.
If he hadn't knocked those
fireballs outta the way,
they would've hit us.
Sorry, I got
bent outta shape
but I'm worried
about the girl.
I'm tryin' to
drive safely.
Just do whatcha can
to help me out, okay?
Huh? The master wants me
to attack the Hyakki Yakou?
Does that mean I
gotta go after them?
Yes, that's what
it would entail.
Aw man, that sucks.
And I just set everything
up to take him down, too.
I can handle Eastedge.
You need to follow
the master's orders.
Yeah, why should I?
I don't think that he
should have the right
to order us around anymore.
Watch what you say.
Just because the master
isn't as present at the moment
doesn't mean
he's not with us.
We simply have to deal
with the boy for now.
Yeah, I get it;
I'll see you soon.
Don't go get yourself
killed, Ribesal.
I'll try not to but I
can't make any promises.
They're trying to separate
me from the master!
Hello, Margery.
I'm sorry about what
happened earlier.
I didn't take
it personally.
After all, this is war.
But don't think
you're gonna get off
without one good
punch to the face!
Won't let me land
a punch, huh?
Then how about this?
The time is indeed now.
We cannot fail.
Dickery, dickery, dare!
The pig flew
up in the air!
The man in brown,
soon brought him down!
Dickery, dickery,
dickery, dare!
No!
We shall not let
you interfere.
It's no use.
I can't stop it!
No, it can't be.
Yuji's Unrestricted Spell?
No way.
How is this possible?
It's not the Snake of
the Festival's spell,
it's mine!
I don't have much time!
I've got to finish this
before he's able to
master the spell!
More rings?
She's going to attack the
World Egg with the Psalm again?
Damn it! This time she
might actually do it!
I have to cast my
Unrestricted Spell.
I did it!
[Music]
With the use of her
Unrestricted Spell,
Shana makes her true
intentions clear.
Meanwhile, the others continue
their assault on the enemy.
Everyone gives their all,
filling the battlefield
with flames and chaos.
Next time, on Shakugan
no Shana Final:
"One Reason."