I have come back for you...
Shana.
Yuji.
Is that really...
Sakai?
Who are you?
How sad that you do
not recognize me...
Flame of Heaven.
Should I?
No...
I suppose it makes sense.
After all, you came to
this world after I did.
Therefore, you've never
heard the sound of my voice
nor the words
I've spoken directly.
Again. Who are you?!
I suspect...
This is another ploy by
that three-eyed harpy...
A Trojan horse
for the Silver.
We're gonna
wrangle you up
and force ya to
tell us everything!
Brainwashed, perhaps...?
Or, rather, it would seem...
That he has indeed
been possessed.
He let his guard down.
I'm sorry, but
you're both wrong...
Wilhelmina...
Margery.
Yeah...? Well,
I don't buy it.
Then you truly are...
Yuji Sakai.
Yes... the one and only.
Of course...
that's just the name
I use in this world.
I have a true
name as well.
A true name?
The hell's that mean?
Who else are you?
Perhaps this will
help you understand...
I'll show you my flame.
Cast a Seal.
A black flame...
That's right...
This is my flame's color...
and...
This is the form
I now assume.
Call me thus,...
Yuji Sakai...
the Snake of the Festival.
[Music]
The Snake of the Festival...?!
Impossible!
It can't be...
Yes... dear Alastor...
It is possible,
for I am the counterpart
to the Flame of Heaven...
I'm the God of Creation...
I am Snake of the Festival.
How are you standing
before us?!
You were sealed in the Abyss
by the ancient Flame Haze...
You once grew so
arrogant in your power
that you attempted to alter
the world's very foundations!
So you're a god from
an old fairytale
who was banished
for eternity...?
Then what the hell
are you doin' here?
The Abyss is a rift
between the human
and Crimson worlds
where even the gods
are powerless!
Bal Masque has been
without their master...
that would indeed explain
their lack of focus.
We were not aware.
Shana...
You're not...
Yuji!
I don't care what you say!
Wrong...
I am Yuji Sakai...
Now come.
We can question him
once he's been captured!
Formidable foe.
You're damn straight!
Yuji!
Whether he's telling
the truth or not...
He claims to be
one of the most infamous
monsters in history...
Who knows what he
might have planned.
What's going on...?
Is the Denizen that
they're fighting
pretending to be Sakai?
No... It can't be...
I can hear it in
Shana's voice...
Whoever she's dealing
with right now...
It really is Sakai!
I'm sorry, Shana...
But I'm not leaving
without you.
We've been trapped!
Shana.
Yu... ji...
Lemme go!
Snake of the Festival!
What kind of sick
joke is this?
What do you want from us?!
I assure you it's
not a joke...
The truth is...
we need each other.
Don't you dare speak...
with his voice!
Shana...
Come with me...
That is the only
reason I'm here.
You bastard...
I want us to be together.
Why, Yuji...?
Why now...?
You've never said
that to me before...
I know...
I was scared to say it...
but... I'm not scared anymore.
We don't have long...
Will you agree
to come with me?
Such a shame...
I didn't want to
resort... to force.
Don't run from me, Shana!
Humpty-dumpty
sat on a wall!
had a great fall!
All the king's horses...
And all the king's men...!
Couldn't put Humpty
together again!
I don't have time to deal
with you right now...
Margery Daw.
So, do me a favor and stay
put a little while longer?
Not even if you begged me!
Then, listen closely
to what I have to say.
I learned something
while I was away...
I think it might...
interest you.
Something...
About the Silver.
What...? Silver...?
Tell me! What do...?!
Calm down, Margery...!
It's a trap!
What do you know about
the Silver...? Tell me!
You mustn't
listen to him...!
Indeed, he is
only taunting you
because he knows that is
what you want to hear most.
False information.
I don't care...!
He has something to say...
and I wanna hear it!
I'd be more than
happy to tell you...
Yuji... don't...! Please!
About the Silver.
Yuji!
Would you just spit
it out already?!
First, I want you to
take a look around you.
The suit of armor you
see is not a Denizen.
It's a physical
manifestation
of fragments of
human emotions;
people's hearts given form.
These countless
fragments of humanity...
Are like cogs in a machine
tracing out my identity...
The Silver only
appears before those
who possess
strong emotions...
It has no will of its own.
It carries out the
desires of the one
from which it draws emotion.
Its behavior is a reflection
of what it has taken in...
It has no mind of its own.
You saw a physical
manifestation of your hatred...
Its sneer was your own...
secret desire.
Do you understand...?
You don't need to
seek revenge...
The Silver didn't
kill those men...
You did, Margery.
No way...
it... was me?!
It's over.
Yuji...
Watch your surroundings.
Margery?!
Are you okay...?!
Answer me!
The Chanter of Elegies
has received information
which has greatly
traumatized her...
She is in a precarious
state indeed.
She's breaking down.
You must get a
hold of yourself.
Maintain your will.
Aw, crap!
Our contract's
about to break!
Snap out of it! C'mon!
You gotta pull through.
Is this really how
you wanna go out?
It's no use!
I can't get
through to her!
No, Margery...!
Don't you dare die,
y'hear me?!
We need you!
For as long as I
can remember...
Others have relied on me.
I helped and
was betrayed...
Then I was relied
on once again.
I was sick of it...
And sick of myself for
allowing it to happen.
And that...
that is why I hated them.
They destroyed everything
I wanted to destroy myself.
Little did I know...
I did destroy
it all myself...
I have no reason to go on.
Please don't die!
You've gotta pull
through this, Margery!
Why the hell should I...?
So you can use me some more?
You gotta stick
around for Sato!
You can't leave him
without even sayin' goodbye!
Tanaka's right!
Think about Sato...
and how you feel for him!
I know he feels the
same way about you...!
You've been loved
for a long time...!
Longer than you know!
He feels... the same?
-Margery!
-You have to fight!
Margery has no
fight left in her...
And Wilhelmina is busy
protecting herself...
Finally, we are alone.
That's it...
I've had enough...
I'm taking you down, Yuji!
It's Blutsauger...
That's right...
You don't know how to
give up, do you, Shana?
Will you shut up?
Which is why the
only path for us...
is the one that
leads to battle.
Shut up!
So I'll fight...
to find my way
into your heart!
Shut! Up!
Why is this so hard?
I haven't even been
able to hit him
with a surprise attack!
Of course not!
He knows my powers
better than anyone.
But, does he know
I can do this?!
It's his house...
Shana.
Yuji...
You're gonna leave
Chigusa behind?
Yes...
It's what I must do.
And you're not being
controlled...?
You're doing this of
your own free will?
That's right...
There's no one else
speaking for me.
Do you think that...
you could protect
everybody you love?
What if...
your loved ones...
were attacked by a
Crimson Denizen...
Would there be enough...
Flame Haze to
guard each of them?
I don't...
There are too many
people in this world
to protect them all...
In Misaki City alone...
I've met so many that
I want to protect...
and yet it's impossible...
That's why...
I'm going to change this
world for the better... Shana...
I'm going to remove the
chance of them getting hurt...
To save them...
To save the people I love!
People like you...
You may be a tool
of destruction,
but I care for you.
Flame Haze are
forced to fight
until their luck
eventually runs out
and they simply disappear...
I'm going to keep you
from suffering that fate.
Like it...
Or not.
There is nothing you
can do to stop me.
I am determined to
have you by my side
as the world changes.
But... why?
For you...
I've always dreamed
of being with you...
So I've made myself
stronger... like you wanted...
Much stronger...!
All for you...!
And now I fight...
I fight with you...
so that one day we'll
never have to fight again!
It's heading this way!
Yoshida...! We've
gotta get out of here!
It's just Sakai...
We're fine.
I'm sorry...
I didn't realize
you were here.
Wh... What're
you doing here?
Is that Shana?!
You... saved her, right...?
is she gonna be okay?
Yeah, she'll be fine...
I'm taking her
back with me.
I've come here...
to reclaim The
Crystal Altar.
No! You can't take it!
I don't see the problem...
The Alter has been mine
from the beginning.
No, wait!
You're taking... her...
with you?
Does she mean
that much to you?
Yes.
But my letter...
Why'd you...?
I had to...
It's the only way I
could send a message...
without saying a word.
I wanted to let you
know I was still alive
without writing
a response...
because I knew it
would hurt you.
Why didn't you...
just tell me?
I suggest you go
home, Yoshida.
I haven't changed anything
yet, but I assure you,
it's a much better
place to be than this.
You're safe... Shana.
[Music]
With Shana trapped in the
Palace of the Stars,...
and Margery out
of commission,...
Wilhelmina devises
a daring plan
to rescue Shana
by herself.
Next time on Shakugan
no Shana Final:
"The Captive Flame Haze."