I got a bad feelin'.
I thought we
foiled his plans.
Why's he smirkin'
like that?
We completely
rewrote the spell
so there's no way he could
have changed it back.
Something has gone wrong.
As you can see,
your tactic failed.
What an honor.
I can't believe my luck.
Disciples of the God of Guidance
may wander for millennia
without ever
being called upon!
Having seen a dazzling
new creation,
the glorious task of
summoning the divine
has been bestowed upon me,
Rofocale, the Invitation
of Cheerful Playing!
He's going to summon
the God of Guidance now?
What could he have seen
that would lead to this?
Did we screw up somehow?
No way!
Not even the Psalm's creator
could restore the spell after
the number we did on it.
Soon his power will
be replenished
by the Midnight Lost Child.
Is he going to use it
to start over again?
No.
We've come too far.
The Strategist and I have
come up with a much better way
to make use of the
Midnight Lost Child.
The Seeking Researcher was so
fascinated by the Treasure Tool
he began an
investigation,
and after the battle
with the Engaged Link
he made two very
important discoveries.
The first, was the secret
of its functionality.
He learned the intricacies of
its ability to overcome loss.
A feature that
is symbolized
by an eternally
ticking clock.
The second, was the
nature of the energy
used to compensate the loss.
It is an elastic force,
the combination of the warping
a lost existence creates,
and the world's attempt
to maintain balance.
In other words,
it's the distortion caused
by the Crimson Denizens
in this world.
With this knowledge,
the professor was
able to devise a way
to extract
unlimited power
from the distortion at
the stroke of midnight,
when the Treasure Tool's
energy is replenished.
I have won.
The Flame Haze Army put
forth a valiant effort,
but I'm afraid it wasn't
enough to outsmart me
and my loyal servants.
Once the clock
strikes twelve,
I shall be an
unstoppable force!
Nothing stands in my way!
What do you intend to do
with your massive amount
of newfound power?
Everything.
Although I am the
God of Creation,
I am only capable
of creating that
which is wished and
desired by others,
but now I have the freedom
to create however I see fit.
This is the plan I concocted
with my Strategist,
the Judge of Paradoxes.
It is the original goal
of the Grand Order and...
...the greatest
deception in history.
There's gotta be
a way to stop him!
I'm afraid it's too late.
I will use the Psalm
of the Grand Order
to create the paradise, Xanadu,
for you, my Denizens!
It's almost time.
As your humble servant,
I call upon thee Shaher,
the God of Guidance,
the Thunderous Chant
of Awakening.
Hear my plea!
The Festival of Creation.
What's happening?
The God of Creation is
summoning his divine power.
I shall be your vessel!
Is that?
Talk about bad timing!
Impossible!
An almighty deed
nears completion.
It's the God of Guidance!
The Chant of Thunderous
Awakening, Shaher!
Could the simultaneous
summoning of divine power
disrupt the Grand Order?
It shines with a dazzling
brilliance, unlike any other.
No matter how hard I try,
I can't seem to
block her out.
She's forcing
me to listen.
Is this the oracle of
the God of Guidance?
We didn't prevent the
creation of Xanadu
but at least our backup
plan worked out.
I mean, it could've
been worse, right?
I don't know whether
I should rejoice
or curse my own weakness.
The Denizens may
not be forced
to obey the God of
Guidance's words,
but they'll never
forget them!
Now all we need her to do
is advocate the
"no eating humans" rule!
I'm so sorry we let
you down everybody!
We don't know
what he saw,
so there's no telling
what's going to happen next.
Protect this new light,
the product of the
Engaged Link's love.
-What?
-The Engaged Link?
What happened to
no eating humans?
You have been bequeathed
the greatest gift of all,
Why Pheles and Johann?
Is it possible that
whatever's inside that bottle
caught the attention
of the God of Guidance?
May hope fill your hearts
as you set forth on your
journey to the new land,
for the new light,
the Heir to Both Worlds,
will be amongst you.
The Heir to Both Worlds?
What the hell is
she talking about?
A thing of myth
and legend.
The combining of
Power of Existence
to create a progeny of the
human and Crimson Worlds.
To put it simply,
it's a half-human,
half-Denizen being.
Is that even possible?
A Crimson Lord and
her contractor tried.
But the former Flaming-Haired
Blazing-Eyed Hunter
and I stopped them.
It'd take an incredible
amount of Power of Existence
to even come close
to pulling it off.
Well, then they picked
the perfect time
'cause there's gonna be
plenty floating around
once the Denizens
leave for Xanadu.
No joke, and there'll be tons
of it on the other side, too.
Those two are smart.
I urge you.
Pheles.
Johann.
You used the creation of the
new world to your advantage.
You knew this would be
your one and only chance
to fulfill your desire.
Seek a new way of being.
A new...
...way of being?
Heed my words of guidance!
What a surprise!
My interest is piqued.
Still, I have work to do.
The preparations for the
Grand Order are complete.
I will now begin
my creation.
I ask that you have
faith in me, your god,
and do not allow the words of
other deities to affect you.
Kneel before me,
my beloved Denizens.
And imagine, in your hearts,
the world that you desire.
I will gather your
prayers and use them
to open the portal to
your paradise, Xanadu!
Until we meet again.
My priestess,
born of wishes.
I call to the heavens!
My beloved Crimson Denizens,
your prayers will
now be answered!
It is done.
What? How can this be?
Impossible.
The Psalm of the Grand Order
still contains the alterations
made by the Flame Haze!
But why didn't it change?
Something inexplicable has
happened, my Strategist.
Master!
At the very moment
of creation.
My beloved Crimson Denizens
told me that
this is what they desire.
It's what they
have chosen.
They must have been
persuaded by the Flame Haze.
Why else would they choose
to live in a paradise
without freedom?
But, even if that
were the case,
you're the one who has
final say in the matter.
You have the power to
overrule their choice!
So, why didn't
you, Master?
I couldn't.
Because, I was touched by
the pain in their eyes.
Master, now your
heart gets to you?
Oh, dear.
Was I wrong to
grant their desire?
No, sir.
If that is your will,
then I assure you it
shall not be contested.
Very well, then.
Thank you, Strategist.
Are you ready to venture to the
Crimson Denizen's paradise?
Yes.
I'll wait for you
at the Shrine.
The new world, Xanadu,
has been created.
General, do I have
your permission
to call off our forces
now that the
battle is over?
Yeah, but tell
them to watch out
for the Gods of the Earth.
While I doubt that they're
gonna keep fighting,
I don't wanna'
take any chances.
Call Ribesal, the
Dashing Earthly Fiend!
Master!
I order you to be
the first Denizen
to go to the new world.
Will you obey, Wanderer?
Yes, sir!
Now that our paradise
has been created,
Bal Masque will be disbanded
until further notice.
So feel free to wander the
new world however you wish.
Thank you.
Is something wrong?
The Yaeger.
He doesn't wanna
leave Pirsoyn.
Ah.
You had better hurry.
I would hate for the two
of you to lose the honor
of being the first
to step foot there.
Yes, sir!
Let's go, Pirsoyn!
Did you see that?
They went to Xanadu.
Does that mean
we can, too?
We can go!
To Xanadu!
We have achieved our
goal, Bal Masque!
I am proud of
every one of you.
I know the path
has been difficult
and we have lost many
comrades along the way,
but this is the time
for celebration,
as our dreams have
become reality.
Now, my loyal servants,
I ask that you make your
way to the new world
we have created together!
We will gladly follow you,
our master, the
Snake of the Festival!
We should be going
as well, Master,
they'll be looking to
you for leadership.
True.
I hate to go, but I
shall obey you, Bel-Peol.
Release your
chains, Tartaros!
I will never forget you;
the human who dared
to use the gods
to achieve his own desire.
That sounds like a
compliment.
It is.
It pains me to
leave you behind
as we go on to paradise.
It's okay.
You've done enough for me.
I must say I'm surprised
you haven't asked us to stay
and fight by your side,
considering that the most
critical battle awaits you.
Yuji Sakai.
After all you've
been through,
is this the best
outcome for you?
It's kinda hard for me to
say just yet, but I think so.
I don't think you stand
a chance against them
on your own.
Maybe not, but I'll
never know unless I try.
That key controls
the Tartaros
that's currently
binding Misaki City.
I'm sure you'll be able
to make good use of it.
Thanks a lot.
I'll stay and
fight with you.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I'm positive.
I feel like it's
the least I can do
after everything
he's done for us.
The Grand Order
is complete.
If that is what you wish,
then so be it.
Yes, sir!
That is what I wish.
Yuji Sakai, the only human
to ever walk alongside me,
your bravery and strength
of will are admirable.
Before I leave,
there is one thing
I want you to know.
I forgive you,
for I am he who
affirms all desires.
Though no one else
may forgive you,
know that I do.
My dear Strategist,
I have a request,
may I tell the Flame Haze
what has become
of the new world?
If that is your wish.
Rejoice, Flame Haze!
Rejoice, Flame of Heaven!
The Crimson Denizens
have requested
that the devouring of humans be
prohibited in the new world!
You may not have
won the battle
but know that the
sacrifices you've made
were not in vain!
Rejoice?
Yeah, right.
Look on the bright side,
at least we're still alive.
Though it may not have
happened as we wanted,
the result is
still favorable.
Must be nice to be a god
and make your own world.
Guess we're gonna have
to find a new place
to entertain ourselves.
Now that we know humans
are gonna be safe there,
maybe it's not such a
bad idea for us to go.
Yeah, but if
that's the case,
there won't be
any work for us.
I could go for an
early retirement.
Well, Miss, looks like
we're all done here.
We'd rather
live in a world
where humans aren't
eaten, ya know?
See ya.
-Safe journeys!
Ah.
This means we don't have to
hunt Crimson Denizens anymore.
I guess we won the
battle, in a way.
God of Atonement,
Flame of Heaven.
I'm honored to have
a new way to live.
As are we, old friend.
Ah.
Kazumi Yoshida.
Thank you, Specialist.
I could not have
protected her without you.
You are the reason that
they are alive right now.
-It is all thanks to you.
-No.
Please Khamsin,
don't die on me!
Look, you and Behemoth
protected this for me.
Don't you see?
You protected something
that meant the world
to Pheles and Johann.
Something so special it
got the attention of a god.
Surely that means...
They'll save
you from dying.
Miss Kazumi Yoshida,
promise you'll
never forget us.
I won't.
Ever!
Ah.
Steadfast Sharp
Peak, Behemoth.
You've been a
wonderful partner.
I'm only as good
as my contractor.
Ah.
This could turn out
to be a good thing.
If the prince
goes to a place
where there's no great
task awaiting him,
do you think that maybe he'll
be able to see the beast again?
Yeah.
I'm sure.
[Music]
The Flaming-Haired
Blazing-Eyed Hunter, Shana,
and the Mystes,
Yuji Sakai.
After everything the two of
them have been through together,
what will become of them now?
What will they
leave behind?
Next time, on
Shakugan no Shana Final:
"The End in the Distance."