Hecate!
I'm all right.
It hurts but the
pain is fleeting.
I thought they
meant to destroy it?
What did you do?
I demand to know
what you've done
to my paradise!
We'll get to that,
but first, there's
something you oughta hear.
The God of Atonement
and his contractor.
Have a message for you.
Our goal is not to prevent
the creation of paradise.
But to prevent the
creation of a world
where anarchy
reigns supreme.
So, we are adding a law to
the Psalm of the Grand Order.
One that shall apply to all
Denizens in the new world.
So, they're not attempting
to destroy the spell
but to change it?
You mean to crush the
dreams of my loyal servants
by altering their
paradise, Xanadu?
The law we've added
prohibits the Denizens
from devouring
human souls.
And if you refuse
to uphold it,
there will be no Xanadu!
[Music]
How dare you?
You would oppose us by
attempting to alter
the very laws of nature?
Sydonay!
Are you prepared to fight?
Yes, sir.
Shame for you.
If only you had
played nice,
I might've let you live.
They cleared the
spell's entire memory!
This is a catastrophe!
They didn't just wipe its
memory, they modified it!
I hate to be the bearer of
more bad news, Professor,
but that spell
fragment is altering
the Psalm of the
Grand Order's very core!
I'm not gonna let them
get away with this!
They think
they can prevent
the transformation of
humanity's existence?
Well, guess again!
How dare those imbecilic,
dunderheaded, buffoons
stand in the way
of our paradise?
Nothin' personal,
we just don't agree with
your idea of paradise.
What'd you expect, Dad?
He may be
artificially created,
but he's still a Flame Haze!
Sale!
I dunno if this
is gonna work.
But we might as
well give it a try.
You have the nerve
to call me "Dad"?
You're merely a reminder
of a botched experiment!
A lemon, a turkey, a flop!
And today's the last day
I have to look at
your face, you failure!
Well, if you haven't got
anything nice to say...
He's got 'em programmed
not to shoot each other.
He's gonna make this hard
for us to the bitter end.
How stupid do you
take me for, "son"?
You really thought your
little trick would work?
Okay, here goes.
I won't allow you to
ruin this day for us!
No! We have waited far
too long for our paradise!
When'd you get here?
We don't have time to
deal with him right now.
I ain't lettin' you
get to the new world;
it'll be a better place without
a dangerous psycho like you!
Oh no! Professor!
I've had enough
of you, Sale!
You're mine!
Surely they realize there's
no tactical advantage
to resuming their advance.
So why do they
continue to fight?
Don't know.
At this point,
all I do know,
is the Flame Haze are
dead set against us
ever getting to Xanadu.
We know what we must do.
We've got to protect
the True Ruler's Shrine.
Envelope and protect!
Robes of Nimrod!
Now that we have
their attention,
we can have a
word with them.
Oh, good. I would
much rather be able
to discuss the
matter with them
than have to fight
to the death.
The words spoken by Alastor,
the God of Atonement,
and his contractor,
the Flaming-Haired
Blazing-Eyed Hunter, Shana,
were meant only
for your ears.
Please tell me that you've
not only heard their message
but you've taken it to heart.
We heard what the
girl had to say
but it's not going to
make any difference.
You're not going
to persuade us
to change the laws of
nature solely to appease you!
Oh, I'm not attempting
to persuade you,
because there isn't anything
that would require changing.
If we share
with you the words
we told the Flaming-Haired
Blazing- Eyed Hunter,
perhaps it will all
become clear to you.
They were,
"Dream a splendid dream,
and then let your actions
reveal the dream."
You've already
ruined our paradise
so I don't see any reason to
continue this pointless battle.
But the party's just
getting started!
Our work here isn't
finished yet, Commander.
We will not rest until we
kill, butcher, and slay
every last one
of your allies!
It shouldn't be
too difficult,
just like lambs to slaughter,
no matter how many fall,
the others still
make their way here.
I could slay ten thousand,
a hundred thousand,
or even a million,
but their desire
to go to Xanadu
would still
lead them to me.
I swear to you,
here and now,
that my beautiful dead
will devour each and
every Crimson Denizen
who's dared to taste
the flesh of man!
I will rip one of you
apart for every life
that has been taken;
for every soul lost!
A gift for the new world,
before its birth!
That is your goal?
But why would the
Four Gods of the Earth
sacrifice themselves
for such a cause?
Who said anything about
sacrificing ourselves,
Commander?
I should get back
to business,
but before I do I have
a message for you.
This is senseless!
How many of my comrades
do you intend to kill?
Hundreds? Thousands?
For what reason?
I want you to listen well,
powerful creature that walks
the bountiful Earth.
It is said
"we will be known forever by
the tracks we leave behind."
And he tracks that
you've left...
Are laden with
the blood of man.
Any who come to this
land out of greed
will feel the wrath
of the heavens.
Their punishment...
...is death.
Those who are lucky enough to
survive the wrath of the heavens
will never forget.
That this is how
those greedy beasts,
those who've tasted
the flesh of man,
were wiped from the Earth.
Insolent fool!
Do you honestly believe
your meaningless threats
are going to stop Denizens
from devouring humans?
Perhaps I cannot dissuade
you and your brethren
but I have no doubt our
actions here today
will influence your
future generations.
Your descendants will
know the new world
as their homeland.
And it will live on
long after those
who have gathered
here have perished.
You will be thought
of as nothing more
than the messengers
of the past.
You will be looked down
upon as the creatures
that once devoured
the souls of man.
When you go to
the new world,
you will share the story of
what happened here today
with your fellow Denizens as
you travel, eat, and play.
You will tell them how
those who devoured man
were kept from
their paradise.
They were killed
without mercy.
Your actions will
be considered taboo.
And your own kind
will rise against you.
Then, once we make
it to the new world,
we'll never speak
of it again!
It would be impossible
to keep such a thing
secret for long.
Eventually someone
would speak of it.
Does this mean we're doomed?
The only reason
we are here today
is to ensure this
prophecy becomes truth.
We have come to
bring death to all
who have tasted
the flesh of man.
Then you'll have to
get through me first!
Why are you telling
me this nonsense
and not the others?
I don't see how that could
possibly do you any good!
If we tell those with many
comrades our intentions,
then we know it will only
be a matter of time
before our words have spread.
The future of your
kind has been decided.
From this day forward,
the devouring of humans souls
is strictly forbidden.
You Crimson Denizens,
who share the Earth with us,
you know, as priests,
it is our duty to
watch over creation.
We are responsible for the
future of not only the Earth,
but the Crimson World
and the rift, as well.
Now and forever.
Your god's tale of creation
cannot continue without us.
Is this a dream?
It's so pretty.
I'd like to thank you,
Kazumi Yoshida.
You're thanking me, Johann?
If it weren't for you,
Pheles never would've
fulfilled my wish
because it went against
her own desires.
But if I had stayed inside the
Midnight Lost Child any longer,
I would've vanished.
Thankfully, your call to
her brought us together
before that happened.
I'm so sorry.
After all this time,
I think I finally understand
how Pheles felt
when she gave
me the Giralda.
I forced her to
make a sacrifice
that would change
her life forever,
all because it might help
two people I care about.
That was so selfish of me.
I hope she can forgive me.
I can't believe you're
apologizing to Pheles,
especially after everything
she's put you through.
You're very sweet
but I should be the
one apologizing
for getting you involved.
No, it's okay.
My sole purpose for
bringing you here
was to ask you to deliver
a message to a friend,
but I'm glad we got
the chance to talk.
A message?
I'm afraid I won't
have the opportunity
to relay it myself.
Even though she
had no choice,
Pheles feels terrible
about being cold to her
and doesn't want to
add to her troubles.
But, as far as
I'm concerned,
she's the only
one we can trust.
I'd say she's the
best friend we have.
So what are you
gonna do now?
If it's something Pheles
doesn't want to happen,
then I assume that means.
Yes. I'm going to disappear.
I know I'm quickly
running out of time,
but I plan to leave a
glimmer of hope behind.
Just one, before
I'm gone forever.
But Johann, there's
gotta be a way.
It's okay.
I've accepted my fate.
As long as everything works
out the way I've planned,
I know my memory
will live on
in the hearts of
others eternally.
I'm going to use the
upcoming miracle of creation
to my advantage.
Basically, we were
hoping to get in
on the God of Creation's
Grand Order.
That's why we gave you the
Scroll to change the spell.
It's all a part
of our plan.
Promise me that you'll keep
all of this a secret, okay?
The God of Creation and
the other Flame Haze
would get pretty upset if
they knew what we're up to.
I will.
I promise you.
Beautiful, isn't it?
Pheles and I came here the first
time we ever flew together.
It was so long ago
and I was so young.
I remember that I wanted
to fly by her side forever,
so I tried my best to ignore
how cold the wind felt.
I tried, but I still
lost consciousness,
and the next thing I knew,
I woke up lying
next to this lake.
I thought she was going
to be angry with me
but she just smiled and said,
"You'll do better next time".
It's been hundreds of years
and this is the first time
we've come back to visit.
We've flown all over the
world together since then.
But, in a way, this is
where our journey began.
That must be why she
decided to bring us here.
Ah, yes.
It almost feels as though
nothing's changed since then.
I'm still just as happy.
I can face anything
as long as I've got
Pheles by my side.
I feel the same
way, Johann.
Where am I?
Oh, you're finally awake!
That's the gist of what
happened while you were out.
Basically, we're
on the run.
I know it's a
lot to take in
especially with the
craziness outside.
Hope I was able to make
some sense of it for ya.
Yeah. I guess.
Our original plan was to lay
low until this was all over.
Unfortunately, our
Denizen comrades
aren't gonna
let that happen.
Damn it! We can't
go this way either.
You're gonna have to come
up with another route, Para!
Roger!
You're mine!
Darn it, I almost had him!
Watch your mouth,
young lady!
You knew this wasn't
going to be easy.
You've gotta hurry but
don't do anything risky!
Thanks, kid.
Well, this is
embarrassing.
Have you completely
gone insane?
What the heck
were you thinking?
Language, Chiara!
But she's right, you are
acting out of character.
You know your dad's just
trying to push your buttons!
Don't let yourself get all
wrapped up in his drama!
But you gotta understand,
this is the opportunity
of a lifetime.
You see, we want to be the
ones who take down Dantalion,
the Seeking Researcher,
and this may very well be
our only chance to do it.
Exactly.
I thought I had a good
shot at it back there.
No matter how
bad things get,
he's not gonna leave
his front row seat
for the creation of paradise.
I was tryin' to get inside
his observation deck,
but it didn't quite
work out for me.
I apologize for
Sale's behavior
but you have to think about
what he's going
through emotionally.
Please don't be
angry with him.
I'm not angry.
You should've just asked for my
help in the first place, silly!
Chiara?
You two rarely
listen to what I say.
It's about time for me to
start making my own decisions.
And I think that
working with Sale
to take down the
Seeking Researcher
is the best course of action for
the Archer of Aurora to take.
It appears the lovely Chiara
is going to be our escort.
Well, I suppose our chances
of survival are greater
if there are two of us.
What're they doing?
What was that?
Do you know?
I can't believe he's
pulling out a new weapon
at a time like this.
So, what do you think?
I've taken the Ultimate
Fist Circle one step farther
to create a super bomb!
Behold my latest invention,
the Ultimate Dispersing Circle!
No armor or Unrestricted
Spell in existence
can protect against it!
It's a miracle of science!
A super-weapon that
disintegrates anything
it touches within a
hundred foot radius!
It's more powerful than
any other bomb in history!
Just when I thought things
couldn't get any worse.
Jeez.
Damn it! Every time
I try to lose 'em
I end up headin'
straight for that tower!
Ah, because that's where
the Denizens are gathering.
They're moving in from
the outskirts of the city.
Merely escaping is
proving to be difficult.
But it would be hopeless
to try and fight them.
I hate to say it,
but it appears we've
run out of options.
We're not racin' 'em, Para!
Slow down, would ya?
Well, I would
but it's not me.
It's out of control!
The van's gone
rogue, Boss!
What?
It's the Unrestricted
Spell, Daimon.
Coachman of
Corpse-Bearing Slaves,
protect Kazumi Yoshida!
I'll do my best!
Um, is there
something wrong?
We've been hit
with a gas attack
that is controlling the van.
There is no reason
to be alarmed.
However, for your own safety,
hold onto those two
and prepare for impact!
-Okay.
-Crap!
I'm tryin' to change course
but it won't let me!
Boss!
Damn, that smarts!
Gyuuki!
Khamsin, help!
[Music]
As Sale fights to get his
revenge on Dantalion,
the Seeking Researcher,
Wilhelmina charges
into battle.
Meanwhile, Shana and Yuji
prepare for their final showdown
which will determine
the fate of Xanadu.
Next time, on Shakugan
no Shana Final:
"Dream of the Stranger."