[Music]
You're not hurt, are you?
No.
Oh good, they're okay.
You've become
like a mother hen.
Um. How did we
survive the crash?
The boss's spell
Kuranominokasa.
It concealed the van
and created an optical
illusion behind us
that acted as a decoy.
Thankfully, the
enemy fell for it
and they fired
at the illusion.
Once we were in the clear,
the Mobilizer took over.
Tell her.
It was not an easy task,
to say the least.
Khamsin!
Ah.
We cast a spell on a
rock inside the van,
and another onto the
rubble from the tower,
then Khamsin
connected the two
in order to pull the
vehicle to safety.
It was a precarious
situation,
but he handled
it beautifully.
Once we'd landed safely,
he enveloped us with
Qadesh's Heart Chamber,
and took on the brunt of
the explosion himself.
Ah. I did what had to
be done to protect you.
That is my responsibility,
after all.
And I'm only
getting started.
According to the Puppeteer
of Devilish Skills,
each of these robots is
carrying a powerful bomb.
What?
If detonated, they will
disintegrate everything
within a hundred
foot radius.
So they're a lot more
dangerous than they look.
Ah.
The Crimson Denizens have
completely lost control.
Hyakki Yakou,
can we trust you to take
care of them for us?
You know it!
Promise to hang on tight
to those two, little lady?
I will!
Activate!
Activating
Qadesh's Blood Seal.
You will overcome the pain,
and, in the end,
it will make you stronger.
I have faith in
you, my friend.
Take care of yourself
and remember to always follow
the path you think is best,
Kazumi Yoshida.
Constructing
Qadesh's Blood Pulse.
Deploying!
Behemoth!
Khamsin!
We've gotta
get outta here.
How could I be such a fool?
I allowed Yoshida to escape
because I thought they
would keep her safe.
There's no way I can
convince the Engaged Link
to do what I
want them to do.
Khamsin seems to be holding up,
but for how long?
It looks like the
geezers and Hyakki Yakou
are completely surrounded.
Why isn't the Engaged Link
helping them fight?
Something's not right.
Enemy advancing.
Indeed, but what
should we do?
We cannot leave this
fight right now.
Wilhelmina, will you go?
I don't understand,
don't you need my help?
Please, old friend.
Specialist of Everything,
Wilhelmina Carmel,
do it for the sake of
the child you raised.
If I were you
I'd get going.
Now that we've
finished the prep work.
All we're really doing here
is wasting time until it's
the right moment to strike.
Besides, if you refuse
the God of Atonement,
I'd hate to see what your
punishment would be!
What about you?
I'll be okay.
Don't worry about me.
You have my permission to
fight however you see fit!
Protect Kazumi,
and your friends,
the Engaged Link, too!
I shall do my best.
I can't help but feel
like I'm abandoning her
at a time when she
needs me the most.
And yet, I know she
can handle it alone.
She's become a
powerful warrior,
and it's time
that I let her go.
Indeed.
That is what's best
for both of us.
I wholeheartedly agree.
You were so
consumed with caring
for the Flaming-Haired
Blazing- Eyed Hunter,
that you lost touch
with yourself.
You were once a force
to be reckoned with
but you chose to
put everything aside
to allow her flame
to grow stronger.
As your Crimson Lord,
I have watched you struggle
with this decision
for so very long.
However, anytime I attempted
to discuss it with you,
I felt as though I was
merely tossing pebbles
into your sea of suffering.
I was so worried
about you.
Well, you needn't
worry any longer.
I'm proud of you.
Really?
Thanks, Tiamat.
I would be lost without you.
Are you prepared to
move forward, Shana?
Yeah.
So it's the two of us
against the two of them, huh?
I gotta feelin' this
ain't gonna be easy.
It shouldn't be too bad,
as long as the lil'
miss has our back!
We just gotta be sure to
look out for each other.
He's right.
I know you're not
too fond of me
but we're gonna have
to work together.
Where'd you get the idea
that I don't like you?
I like you a lot!
You do?
Thanks, kid.
I'm assuming she means
just as a friend,
'cause you've already got a
significant other, dontcha?
Ah, this is more like it.
They are fighting
as hard as they can.
It's unfortunate so
many must die simply
because they're unable
to see the truth.
Protecting something
is difficult.
Indeed but it is
a job worth doing.
Fire!
Gyuuki, it's down already!
Can you cast another one?
Damn, that was fast.
We gotta hold out long enough
to justify using the spell.
Yeah, but with the number
of enemies out there,
we can't wait
too long, Boss.
We can't hide in
here forever,
eventually they're
gonna find us.
Here it goes.
We'll move once they pass.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
I'm okay.
Sorry, it just frightened me.
What'll we do?
We've run out of
places to hide, Gyuuki.
Ya better think fast!
Over there!
Inside the tower?
Para!
Roger!
I'm in! Releasing the lock now.
Doors are open, Boss.
Okay, we're comin'!
Aw, man!
Good job!
You got him!
It was just one!
You've gotta keep
your guard up, Chiara!
Right!
I smell a victory.
It shouldn't be long
until the Mobilizer of
Ceremonial Equipment falls.
I'm surprised
the Engaged Link
hasn't come to
their ally's rescue.
What cowards.
I have come to
help you escape.
Your rear guard.
Wilhelmina!
Are you all right?
What is that?
Well, Pheles and Johann
gave this to me.
Is that the
Midnight Lost Child?
No, it's not.
Discuss it later.
We were gonna run
into the tower
but I don't know if
that's a good idea.
Where does this door lead?
To an interior hallway.
I haven't seen any
enemies so far.
I'll keep watch
once we get inside.
If it gets bad,
I'll let you know.
Roger.
I'll keep them from
chasing after you,
and I shall do what I can
to keep you safe, indeed.
Focus on defense.
That was a little too
close for comfort.
The Specialist of Everything's
gonna guard the doorway.
Meanwhile, what're
we gonna do here?
From what I can tell,
this is actually a chute
used to transport something.
What do you mean
by "something"?
I mean, I don't know
what it transports.
Luckily, I figured out
how to deactivate it,
so we should be
safe for now.
Then let's hang here
as long as we can
but remember to keep an
eye out for the enemy.
You got it.
Please be safe out
there, everyone.
Uh-oh.
Mammon's showed up!
I was tryin' to save this trick
until the very last second.
But we're gonna
have to use it
even though we haven't
perfected it yet.
Chiara, take the lead.
It's about time we show
Bal Masque what we can do!
Okay!
Well, here we go!
Launching in three, two...
Now!
Sale, no!
Havin' fun yet?
No!
Say bye bye!
'Cause I've got
you now, Sale!
Shut up!
Professor! All systems are go!
You can detonate
at any time!
Okay, then!
This is it!
Here we go!
Sale!
Not so fast!
Uh-oh! Your luck's run out!
Ha! Goodbye,
Sale Habichtsburg!
Die!
Professor!
Oh, that's a nice trick!
I've got one, too!
Huh?
Now launching the
emergency escape system!
Oh no.
One more time!
What have they
done to you?
They have defeated me.
I'm sorry, Pirsoyn.
You've come to my rescue
but it is too late.
We've lost the
Seeking Researcher,
Dantalion.
The robots are going berserk
now that he's not
here to guide them
and the control
room's been destroyed.
You must hurry and get
far away from here.
But what about you?
What is he planning to do?
When the enemy's near death
they have nothing to lose.
Be careful, Chiara.
Satisfy my ravenous greed.
These robots.
Bring them to me, now!
Mammon sacrificed himself
to save the tower?
Man, that's some
loyalty, huh?
Well, it's good to know
he had one redeeming
quality at least,
but I still can't say
I'm sorry to see him go.
That ain't good!
The old man's caught
in the middle of 'em!
I've lost the Dragon's
Tail and the Silver.
Is this the end?
I must say, your
naivety surprises me.
Did you honestly believe
altering the Psalm
of the Grand Order
would somehow
foil my plans?
I am the God of Creation.
You have underestimated my power
and insulted the intelligence
of my loyal servants,
the Trinity.
The priestess who
sacrificed herself
to act as the Psalm of
the Grand Order's core.
The Supreme Throne, Hecate.
And he who sits at the
right hand of a god,
a man who would slay any
who dare to oppose me.
Thousand Changes, Sydonay.
Behold!
The stratagem of she who
determines divine will
and judges that
which is false.
The Judge of
Paradoxes, Bel-Peol!
Something has gone
terribly wrong.
The spell didn't change.
So, it doesn't work?
Well it certainly
looks that way.
We infiltrated the
True Ruler's Shrine
and located the Conloquiem
which acts as the Psalm of the
Grand Order's backup system.
While you guys were distracted
with all the fighting,
I hit it with the
same altered spell
the midget had attached to
the Chorde Treasure Tool.
Then all we had to do was
wait for 'ol three eyes
to pull the switch on the
Conloquiem and viola!
Your plan was foiled.
[Music]
The Snake of the Festival,
Yuji Sakai,
awaits the summoning of divine
power with bated breath.
When it seems things
can't get worse,
an unexpected
disaster strikes,
and the shape of the
new world is decided.
Next time, on Shakugan
no Shana Final:
"Dream of the God."