Sale. It looks like
everyone's really sad.
I've never seen such a
miserable looking group.
They've completely
lost morale.
I guess this is the end
of the pursuit squad.
This is seriously
messed up!
Well, we can't just
sit here and cry.
We're gonna have to find a
way to get back up on our feet.
But we should wait and see
what the commander has to say.
Chiara!
You don't reek
of booze today.
-Why is that?
-Jeez, kid.
Ya make me sound
like an alchie.
Well, when the
going gets tough
you're usually drinking.
She hit the nail
on the head!
Although, anyone would
be driven to drink after
hearing the Declaration
of the Grand Order.
Every Flame Haze
around the world heard
what that despicable
bastard had to say,
which means they're
probably in the same shape
as everyone here...
utterly depressed.
It's gonna be hard to
go back into battle
knowing that's the case.
I have faith in you.
I know it's rough.
I felt the same way once,
but I'm here today
because I refused
to give up.
Please, don't be sad.
As long as you
stay positive,
you'll inspire the
others to cheer up.
That's our little Chiara!
Always looking on
the bright side!
I wish we could say the
same for her mentors.
Are you going to
keep fighting?
I'm in, but Sale's gonna
need a stiff drink.
Shut up.
Sure. I might as well.
Not like I was destined
to be a Flame Haze;
I was forced into a contract.
So I guess that "Grand Order"
crap shouldn't affect me.
Do you read me? Sale?
Chiara?
Just in the nick of time!
Please don't tell me
these are all the troops
we have left, Francois.
Oh no, ma'am.
Many of our allies are
still in the mountains.
They've completely
splintered off
and refuse to regroup.
I'm afraid we're going
to have to abandon
our original plan.
Seriously?
You mean, we aren't going
to head towards
Heaven's Road Palace?
No.
"We" are not.
In other words, those
of us whose thoughts
are not clouded
by depression
have a greater responsibility
than retreating.
That is correct.
We shall halt our enemy
pursuit and focus our efforts
on getting our less
fortunate allies
to Heaven's Road
Palace safely.
I gotta say, it's gonna
be tough to pull that off.
Supreme Commander, it
would be a grave mistake
to lead them straight
to the Palace.
The enemy would undoubtedly
learn of its location.
They'll never find it.
I've some tricks
up my sleeve.
We all do but it makes no
difference at this point.
The reality of the
situation is we simply
do not have the manpower
necessary to take action.
I know, but we must save
as many lives as we can.
Pardon me.
I hate to interrupt but
may I say something?
And what about the enemy
forces on the plains?
They've been eliminated.
The few survivors managed to
flee into the mountains.
Attention pursuit squads!
Expand your search radius
to include the mountains.
Your primary target is the
enemy's mobile fortress,
Heaven's Road Palace.
They were clearly headed east
before they scattered.
After mulling over their
choice of direction,
I came to a realization.
The only explanation
is there must have been
something there that was
meant to aid in their escape.
And you think it
was the Palace?
I've ordered our
reinforcements in the
north and south to surround
the mountains at a distance.
They're in hiding now but we'll
draw them out eventually.
Is that snow?
No, it's rain.
My Burning Field has
been rendered powerless.
That's Sirotci's
Unrestricted Spell
but the lapis lazuli
colored flame--
could this rain be the
great barrier, Tlalocan?
That means the Four Gods of the
Earth are aiding the enemy!
We don't stand a chance
against those monsters, sir!
Even as a last resort,
why would Sirotci build such
a tower in plain sight?
And then to light a flame
to ensure we see it.
It must be a decoy.
Please stand.
You have to stay strong.
You mustn't give
up the fight.
You see that tower?
I want you to keep running
until you reach it.
There you will find
a means of escape.
I found them!
Over there! Attack, men!
Amazing.
This is the power
of Tlalocan.
The transformation
of energy.
Like a beacon of light
piercing the darkness,
you must persevere
against your foes.
A Flame Haze remembers the
sorrows of the past
but always looks
to the future.
Allied forces are
currently headed towards
the tower, sir.
And the rain has blocked
all long-distance communication.
My Burning Field has
been disabled as well.
We know the
tower's a decoy
yet we've no way
of stopping them.
Perhaps this was
their plan all along.
Send a messenger to
the rear forces
telling them to hold
their position.
Contact the
advancing squads
and order them to withdraw.
If our encirclement
collapses--
Now we've got you!
If you make an
attempt to advance,
we will indeed stop you!
Have they come
to draw me out?
If that's the case.
How could you let the
pursuit squad walk
right into their
trap, Commander?
It's the General!
He has decided
to show himself.
Thousand Changes Sydonay!
He has arrived.
Apparently.
Come on, we're
almost there!
We gotta keep
going, you guys!
We haven't much time!
Hurry, comrades.
Into the tower!
Watch out!
Ah. The Beckoner
of Brightened Dew
and the Guardian
of Steady Passage
have made our job in this
operation quite easy.
You care to tell
me how, exactly?
Ah.
We just have to wait here.
And we'll have an unlimited
supply of things to destroy.
Now I get it!
It's unscathed?
No! Fire now!
We made them believe
the tower's a decoy
but we're actually
gathering our forces here,
in order to carry out
our true objective.
Yes. We are relying on a
tactician's greatest trick,
the manipulation of
perceived reality.
I bet you weren't expecting
me to show up, were you?
To be honest, I've grown
tired of the games, ladies.
I tried to play nice,
but if there's one
thing you're good at,
it's making me angry.
I'll take care of
these two, Commander.
While I do that,
please try to get our
surrounding forces
under control.
Yes, sir.
Now then.
The master's never
given an order
that would prohibit
me from killing you.
What a shame for you.
-Wilhelmina!
-Right behind you, milady!
All forces within the
encirclement are now safe.
Thanks to your plan to
draw the enemy here,
the process went much
faster than anticipated.
That's good news
but it wouldn't have been
possible without your help.
Gentlemen, this is not
the time to rejoice
for there is still
more work to be done.
True.
The worst is yet to come.
I hope we can
make this work.
Me, too.
There are so many
lives on the line.
What's the matter?
Hero of the Great War?
Blazing eyed hunter?
I thought the two of you were
going to present a challenge.
Good, I was hoping
you'd do that.
Emblaze!
Okay, now we're talking.
I was wondering when you'd take
off the kid gloves and fight.
Consider this
your last warning.
Do not attack unless you're
prepared to burn to death
amidst the flames.
You have been warned.
That's quite a threat.
You really think
you can kill me?
We'll see about that.
Interesting.
Their attacks aren't nearly
as vicious as their threat.
And why do they keep returning
to the same positions?
Keep firing and
we'll take it down!
You heard him!
All troops, fire away!
Now, into the fray!
Our forces will not stop
until they've completely
destroyed the tower.
I can't believe we
were foolish enough
to fall for my
rival's gambit.
Well played, Sirotci.
When I was human I was
taught to fight for
what I care about.
Now, here I am,
centuries later,
still fighting for
the same cause.
But this time,
no one is forcing my hand.
I chose to fight
this battle.
The decoy's served
its purpose
which means Heaven's Road Palace
is probably already gone.
Even though I know the
retreating soldiers are injured
and likely won't have any
effect on the battle.
I still don't want
them getting away.
One of the Four
Gods of the Earth?
This should be fun!
I hate to interrupt
but may I say
something?
After much deliberation,
the Beckoner of
Brightened Dew
has finally reached
a decision.
We will join you, our fellow
Flame Haze, in battle.
He who Walks with Rain
speaks not only for himself,
but the other three
Gods of the Earth.
He came to this decision
after hearing the Snake of
the Festival's declaration.
What did he say
that got to ya?
He claimed that
creating a new world
would not have an adverse
effect on this one.
I remember many
centuries ago,
our wise former teacher,
known as the
Heart of the Sky,
shared something with
us that unfortunately
most Flame Haze
do not know.
The cause of the
storm in the rift
which foretells the
great disaster.
Basically, the devouring of
human souls by Crimson Denizens
creates an unstable energy
that is called the
Power of Existence.
Each time this happens,
the world shakes.
Eventually these small
vibrations combine to form waves
which then grow
to become a storm.
If the God of Creation
takes his Crimson Denizens
to the new world
he creates,
the Earth will regain its
lost Power of Existence
and the storm that has
been brewing in the rift
will subside.
Yes, but if they don't
change their ways,
and they act in the new
world as they did here,
it's a matter of time.
Until disaster strikes.
That's true.
However, if that
were to happen,
it wouldn't have any effect
on the people in this world.
Now, I am sure you
are asking yourselves,
why we four gods
chose to join
your fight against
the God of Creation.
It's because...
Just like the Crimson World,
the new one that
is created...
...will affect this world,
which you are charged
with protecting.
That's right.
As the Four Gods
of the Earth,
it is our duty to uphold
the natural order,
and right now it
is being threatened
by the Snake of the Festival.
If you'll agree to
fight alongside us,
we'll do everything
in our power
to ensure that your army makes
it onto the next battlefield.
Well, Shana?
Will you fight?
When I move into that area
they suddenly cease
their assault,
and whenever I attack
in this direction
they dash to block it.
They must be
hiding something!
Could it be
Heaven's Road Palace
that they're
trying to protect?
They lead us to believe
it had already left,
but it was hidden
here all along.
True Crimson!
Below us!
You think you can hide
Heaven's Road Palace?
Not from me!
Pierce through!
Nice try!
The Chanter?
Six little mice
sat down to spin.
Pussy passed by,
and she peeped in.
"What are you at,
my little men?"
"We're making coats
for gentlemen!"
"Shall I come in and
bite your threads?"
"No, no, Miss Pussy,
you'll bite off our heads!"
"Oh no, I'll not,
I'll help you spin."
"That may be so but
you don't come in!"
Man, I need a nap
and a martini.
Looks like somebody's
back to normal.
It's good to
see you, indeed.
Rendezvous complete.
I feel like I haven't
seen you in ages,
lil miss. ou're lookin' good.
You've got this
aura about you.
It's 'cause I'm
stronger now.
Tell me, how long do you think
your spell will hold him?
All we need is ten minutes
and the Beckoner of Brightened
Dew could come with us.
While I appreciate your
concern for my well-being,
you must remember
that greediness
is not a quality
befitting a true god.
If I undo the Tlalocan now,
it would be disastrous.
Without it, the enemy
would surely realize
that Heaven's Road Palace is
right within their reach.
It's necessary to
cover your tracks
so they cannot figure
out where you've gone.
Therefore, I will stay
and keep it flowing.
I am simply following the
plan that we agreed upon.
You mustn't waste precious
time worrying about us,
or the Guardian
of Steady Passage,
who faces the
enemy army alone.
We are aware of the
fate that awaits us.
Time is running out,
even as we speak.
Please, hurry.
Well, ladies.
We'd better get going.
Our ride should be coming
for us any minute now...
Whoa!
He's already
breaking through?
You thought a simple spell
was strong enough to hold me?
Give me a break.
You'll have to do
better than that.
Thousand Changes!
Oh, I get it.
You're staying behind
to help them escape.
You'll distract
me with a fight
and keep the Tlalocan going
as long as you're able.
Is that the game, old man?
Let me guess,
the real Heaven's Road Palace
is long gone.
So one of the Four Gods of
the Earth is willing to die?
Yes.
I will fight until I've
used the last of my power,
because now I know I'm
fighting for the right cause.
Thousand Changes Sydonay,
we would be honored
if you would fight against
us in our last battle.
You're going to attack me
regardless of how I respond,
aren't you?
The mission was successful.
It seems I've found my way
to death's door once again.
It's no different than
when I was human,
except that this is exactly
where I want to die.
Zirnitra, my dear comrade,
thank you for renewing my
existence with your contract
and allowing me
to fight with you.
My pleasure, comrade.
For six centuries I have rued
the day our contract would end,
Samuel Demantius.
Well, old friend.
I'm afraid that
time is upon us.
Does this mean that
you are going to die?
It certainly
looks that way.
But I don't think it means as
much the second time around.
In that case,
I bid you farewell.
I shall return
to the Crimson World
until my next battle begins.
Good luck to you.
My comrade, Zirnitra.
I thank you for
your service,
and your friendship,
Samuel Demantius.
Do not fret.
There is no one who could
have done more than you,
Thousand Changes Sydonay.
Besides, we are
in no position
to mourn an unexpected
defeat right now.
Yes, sir.
Tell me Bel-Peol,
do you know when my body
will be stable enough to move?
Stabilization is now
at fifty percent,
but, please bear in mind,
we have other
tasks to complete
so it may be a while
before we can leave.
Excellent.
I cannot wait to
leave this place,
once and for all.
[Music]
Using Heaven's Road Palace
to transport all of
our defeated troops
through the enemy's
endless sea of soldiers
would have been
impossible.
Instead, we dug a pit large
enough to hold the Palace
and buried it
into the Earth.
Tlaloc then
summoned greenery
to conceal the
freshly turned soil.
The troops were ordered
to enter the tower
Sirotci constructed.
Once everyone was
accounted for,
they were led here via
an underground passage.
The Guardian of Steady
Passage acted as a decoy
and defended the tower,
while the Chanter of Elegies
made the enemy believe a
fake was hidden nearby,
and the Beckoner
of Brightened Dew
functioned as
a rear guard.
We've lost the battle,
though we gave it our all,
we're left with nothing.
But, we're still alive.
Every Flame Haze
here is lucky.
They will live to
see another day.
That is the one bright
spot in this tragedy.
I will fight.
That is good news indeed.
I knew I could count on
you to fight alongside me
because you are the
contractor of a true god.
Do me a favor,
Bright Flame.
Give the other three
Gods of the Earth,
my fellow priests,
a message on my behalf.
"My friends, I have
become a drop of rain.
I sacrificed myself in the
hopes of forcing you to act.
So please believe
me when I say... "
"Joining the Flame Haze in
their fight is, without doubt,
the right choice to make."
After suffering an
agonizing defeat,
Shana and the others are
left shaken and confused.
Should they face
Bal Masque again?
Is the creation of
Xanadu right or wrong?
Next time, on Shakugan
no Shana Final:
"To Battle Once More."