Yo.
Jerk. You're late.
Yeah.
I hope you have a better
apology than that for her...
Let's go.
Okay.
[Music]
The black mirror in the
sky is called the Divine Gate!
Beyond it...
there lies a path...
that will pave the way...
for the Snake of the
Festival's return!
The body he's
currently using
and the Trinity are inside!
I, the Flaming-Haired
Blazing-Eyed Hunter,
along with my comrades,...
will now venture
in to stop him!
To battle!
[Music]
Hi, Sato... Welcome back.
Yoshida?
You coulda waited inside.
Oh, that was my fault...
I knew you'd be running
all the way to your house,
so I told her to
stand out here
and see which one of
us made it first.
And I won, right?
Just like I said I would.
Jeez... Weirdos.
You're not comin' in?
No thanks...
I'm just happy to
know you're home safe.
And safe you are...
I saw to it myself so...
My job's done.
Wha-... Dude...
Are we the people you came
back here to see...?
No, sir.
Uh, no...
You do know, uh...
how to wake a sleepin'
princess, don't ya?
Later.
Make sure to give us a
call when she wakes up.
Uh... sure.
You just gonna
sit there? !
Marcosias...
What are you doing here?
Whadaya think...? I heard
you were coming back,
an' I missed your stupid face.
That's all?
Ah, don't worry...
I'm not a Peeping Tom.
Wait a second,
you think that-?
That is why you
came back, isn't it?
Well...
yeah.
I take it Eita and the girl
told you what happened.
Yeah, some... I guess.
Well go on then, kid...
I gotta shut up now, 'fore
I say somethin' I regret.
Wha-... I, um...
Go.
Right.
An' remember,... when
it's time to act cool,...
there's no such
thing as too cool.
Best o' luck.
Marcosias... Thanks, man.
You can thank me
when she's okay.
Hey, Margery...
I'm back.
Yeah, so uh...
I heard about everything
that happened...
It must've been hard for
you to find out the truth
about the Silver.
I know you feel
like the centuries
you spent hunting him
are now meaningless.
It's rough...
but you can't give up
'cause we're counting on you...
Shana, Tanaka,...
Yoshida, Ogata...
Hell, even Sakai...
and me...
You've gotta keep
goin' for me.
No matter what anyone
thinks about you...
No matter what you
think about yourself...
The fact that you're even
here means more to me
than you could ever
possibly imagine.
My entire existence
has only one purpose...
I am devoted to
keeping you alive.
This is gonna
sound weird...
but when I heard
you needed me...
I couldn't help
feeling happy...
Because that
happiness told me...
That...
I really do
live for you...
and only for your sake.
And that's what I
want to tell you...
First thing...
As soon as you wake up.
Margery...
I heard...
I heard your voice.
But also...
I heard Eita's and
Kazumi's voices...
as my world was
falling apart.
You can't leave him
without even sayin' goodbye!
Tanaka's right...!
Think about Sato, and
how you feel for him!
And I did...
At that moment I did
think about you...
I thought about my
feelings toward you.
I was surprised to
know they were there...
I doubted them...
I denied them...
I shut everything out.
Why?
If my feelings for
you were real,...
then I'd be able
to postpone
my obliteration...
even if it was only
for a little while...
Until I could be sure.
But they were
real, weren't they?
Real enough to keep
me from slipping away.
Then it was more
than enough...
and to me... that's
all that matters.
Thank you, Keisaku...
Or is that a bit trite?
I don't care...
just... Having you
here, alive...
It's not enough...
So as a woman,...
I ask you, as a man...
Tell me...
and I'm not questioning
your devotion...
Do you love me?
I do! Yes!
Do you remember...?
What I told you
about Flame Haze...?
That we're too strong to
hold anyone too close?
Yeah...
For a short time...
I can make you as
strong as I am...
But then...
if I don't create
some distance...
I'll draw even closer...
Right?
That's how it's
been between us...
'til this point.
And now?
Why don't you find out?
What's that?
A bird... that's
not truly a bird.
It appears to be one of
the Ancient Flame Haze...
who helped to banish
the God of Creation
so many centuries ago.
I guess it wants
us to follow, huh?
Seems to be the case.
The enemy's lack of
organization had begun
to turn the tide of
battle in our favor,
Supreme Commander...
But the latest reports from
troops on the front lines
say the fortress guards
have now emerged.
They were not expecting an
attack on their main stronghold,
and left it ill-defended.
François, show us the
current situation please.
Right... Well,
let's take a look.
Within my
detection radius...
I see a force approaching
from the north...
Most likely, the Bal
Masqué defensive forces...
turning their
attentions inward.
Closer to us,
from the south,...
there's another
force approaching.
Neither group is very
great in number...
We'll have no trouble
defeating them...
The problem is the
two larger forces,...
which have withdrawn,
to the east and west...
Even marching at
top speed though,
I don't think they'd make
it here before morning.
Our own forces
continue to harass
and pursue the
retreating troops.
however...
For now,...
the advantage we
enjoy is temporary...
It will last only until
one of their large
armies arrives,...
from either the
east or the west.
How much can we
still accomplish...
before time runs out?
Firstly... Send about half of
our available reserve units
as reinforcements to aid
those who are bravely
fighting near the
Divine Gate...
It need merely be enough of
our troops to occupy them...
Our goal is to split
the enemy forces in two.
Secondly...
Samuel, you'll lead
the remaining part
of our reserves,...
in an assault on the
Palace of the Stars.
Ma'am.
Thirdly...
Neither the God
of Creation,...
nor any of the Trinity are
present in this battle...
Let's use that to our
destructive advantage.
We lack the
necessary troops...
But the Palace of the Stars
guards our greatest secrets...
It must not fall into Outlaw's
hands even for an instant...
Therefore,...
I must buy time at least until
our nearest forces arrive...
The western forces,
and their commander,...
Burning Agitation Haborym,
are on their way...
Had they arrived, this
would not be a problem.
While they should
be here soon,...
we simply do not have
enough troops
to last until that time.
It seems, then...
I have no choice.
What the-?
This is...
Whatever's causing
it is moving!
Impossible!
Decarabia? !
Standing on the front
lines like this,
leading his troops...
It is so
uncharacteristic...
It seems that attacking
Decarabia directly
is not doing any damage!
And attacks that have so
far been effective
against the Denizens...
are no longer working!
Yes... There's an Unrestricted
Spell of teleportation
around his body, to
deflect attacks...
And he's using defensive
spells to bolster
the Denizens on
the battlefield.
But such simple spells
wouldn't blanket
the entire army.
He must have cast them
on each individual...
His madness
knows no bounds.
He must have appeared
personally...
In order to cast so many
Unrestricted Spells
on the battlefield...
But this...
Any intent he had of
dragging out the battle
has been abandoned.
It's not desperation...
He's taking a
calculated risk.
Are his forces so depleted
that he's willing
to sacrifice his
own life...?
Or perhaps... Reinforcements are
close enough at hand...
that he need hold the line
only for a short time?
Whatever his intent,
it seems that I must not hold
my power in reserve, either!
Focus our attacks
on a single point...
We build a bridge,...
a single road above...
Understood, Zirnitra?
We build a bridge,...
a single road above...
Establishing...
Begin the operation,...
Demantius.
Disrupt...! Then
strike down...
And build anew...
Thy name is honor...
O, Hill of Zizka!
All forces...! Form
your ranks on me!
And ... Ready...!
Unto the breach!
The blizzard...
It has stopped!
With my sight restored,
targeting them
will be simple.
I will only have time
for a single strike...
Therefore,...
That strike will
contain my power...
at its fullest.
Found you!
Yeeeaaaahhh!!!
Nicely done...
But don't you think you
used too much of your power?
Perhaps so, but it
was well worth it...
I'm sure Samuel can handle
things from here on...
Su-Supreme Commander!
Massive incoming...!
From outta nowhere!
On our Western flank!
How? ! We were
watching everything!
That flame...
Haborym, the Burning
Agitation...!
That means...
their western forces
have returned...
But how did they
arrive so quickly?
What we dismissed as
a flock of birds
was an Unrestricted Spell
of concealment...?!
We've been fooled.
Enemy reinforcements!
What the hell...?! They're
right on our flank!
The time has come,...
but sooner than
we expected.
Margery? !
What?
What are you gawkin' at?
Um. Sorry.
So anyway, this file
you brought me...?
I'm all caught up...
Y'know, on Sophie's
plans here...
Operations: Calm...
Crossing...s and Ebb.
So...?
So, get up...
and put on some clothes...
We're leaving.
You are with me,...
aren't you?
Up ahead...
I see Unrestricted Spells
placed on the fortress...
They're centered on
the hidden Rinne.
Three layers...
cloaking and
intercommunication...
but the last one
I don't recognize.
That would indeed bring
it to a total of twelve
defenses which
lie in our path...
Their goal is the
same as always...
Delay progress.
Ah... But what worries
me is your inability
to recognize that
third spell.
We should proceed
with all due caution.
Man, that Judgment spell
of yours sure comes in handy...
If you want, I'll trade
ya for Landmine-
but all it does
is break stuff.
Knowledge over
violence, huh...?
Look who's all grown up!
Oh, shut up.
[Music]
Sabrac attacks but Shana
leaves Wilhelmina
and the others to fight,
so she can chase after me.
The question is,
can she make it before
Hecate completes
the ritual to recover
the Snake of the
Festival's body?
Next time, on Shakugan
no Shana Final...
"Words of a Vow."