Your blade, my master...
As always, I am
your servant.
You have done well.
[Music]
Those are...
Yes...
those are the
Ancient Flame Haze
who were entombed with me.
They've paid the
ultimate sacrifice
for thwarting my plans.
Thousands of years
have passed and yet...
they're still determined
to stand in your way.
Their devotion to the
cause is impressive,
to say the least.
I agree...
Though it may
delay our journey,
we must deal with
them in a respectful,
yet forceful, manner...
For I will not be
denied passage.
The catalyst needed
to change the world
lies at the end
of this pathway.
Once it's mine,
I can free Shana from her
fate as a Flame Haze.
I gotta go...
I don't have time to
waste on these idiots.
Aster!
Hecate... you can go ahead
and get to safety...
We will join you as soon
as we're finished here.
As you wish, sir.
-Domino!
-Right! At your service!
It's time for us to
get going, Professor!
You can finish
collecting data later.
Oh! Wow...!
We've just hit the
mother load here, haven't we? !
Yeah, yeah... Now come on,
we've got to go!
the water I drink, even
my very existence!
Shall we finish 'em?
Shouldn't take
but a minute...
Watch this:
Tartaros: Isolate!
I'm not gonna let
you have all the fun!
We have lost all contact with
Fortress Commander, Fecor.
Without him, it will
be next to impossible
to keep the Divine
Gate concealed.
I suspect the
enemy will soon
launch a full-scale attack.
I don't understand...
How did the intruders
so easily infiltrate
the Palace of the Stars?
I have to tell the others
about the Divine Gate!
Where am I?
It looks like...
Heaven's Road...
Is this...
The Palace of the Stars? !
It is, indeed.
Is it to your liking...
Princess?
It's understandable that you
want to do some exploring...
However, I find
it worrisome
you're not accompanied
by your attendants.
Don't tell me you were
finally successful
in breaking the
bonds of Tartaros?
Allow me to
introduce myself...
My name is Uvall,
I am the Chaotic Beat
of Burdening Drums.
I sincerely hope you won't
consider me a braggart
for telling you that I am a
powerful Crimson Lord.
I've been charged with
the duty of protecting
the Palace of the Stars
from intruders.
Therefore, I have a question
to ask you, Princess...
Who, precisely, are you?
Who am I?
The Flaming-Haired
Blazing-Eyed Hunter...
Shana!
You're a Flame Haze?
In that case, there's
absolutely no reason...
for me to hold
back against you!
It's quite a shame...
I foresee us doing a great
damage to this chamber.
Why are you not
attacking me?
Are you scared?
You've only been in
captivity a few days,
surely you haven't
completely forgotten
how to fight in that time.
I don't think so...
But there's
only one way...
to find out!
You don't sound very sure
of yourself, Princess.
Given the urgency of
the situation,
I'm afraid I'm going to have
to make short work of you,
my dear.
We're now deep within the
Palace and we've yet to find
any sort of
room or cell
that would be capable
of holding her.
Continue searching.
I'm sure the Mystes
has her well hidden...
in the hopes of
protecting her
from the battle
raging outside...
But I have no doubt we'll
be able to find her.
It's the Crystal Altar...
I don't understand...
what on Earth is
it doing here?
Inexplicable.
I wouldn't touch that...
Unless you want them
to know you're here,
Specialist of Everything.
We meet again,
Spiral Organ...
It has been far too long.
Synchronization complete.
Is it me...
or are they suddenly
attacking more vigorously?
Now that the Crypta
has been destroyed,
it appears they are
no longer concerned
with protecting the
fortress from damage.
Ah...
With that in mind,
I am torn over
whether or not we
should remain here.
While I think it would be
foolish to disregard
the mysterious object
floating above us...
It would be far worse
to attack without
first identifying it.
Ah... Until the
Specialist of Everything
rescues the Flaming-Haired
Blazing-Eyed Hunter...
We shall keep fighting.
Set's Wheel!
Deploy Qadesh's
Blood Seal.
Activate...
Deploying.
Synchronizing to
Qadesh's Blood Pulse.
Oh wow...! The geezers
are kickin' major butt!
Don't you think your time
would be better spent
rallying your
troops, Purson,
The Majestic Lion's
Bellowing Call?
I disagree.
Your friend's
destructive power
is quite impressive...
However, I know that had
you two been there,
the damage would have
been threefold.
That is why...
I lured you to join me
in this dance called war.
Well, I'm not much
of a dancer, pal...!
So don't get pissed off when I
end up stompin' on your foot!
The old man's too big to
dodge this loser's attacks,
so I lured
him over here.
At least, that's what I
thought I was doin'...
Turns out that mangy cat was
the one who was baitin' me!
I'm always telling you to
respect your elders,
and when you finally do, it
blows up in your face.
I'll forgive ya for it...
as long as you'll let me
blow somethin' up
in his face...!
Hear that, ya
feline freak? !
If you think such a
threat will frighten me...
you're dead wrong.
For you see...
I have an Unrestricted
Spell, so strong,
it'll knock you to your knees!
I'll play you...
my Fanfare!
The last tune
you'll ever hear!
I don't think so!
Fanfare!
You're not bad...!
I can't believe you've
made it through this fight
without bein' hit by
one of our attacks!
Thanks, but flattery
will get you nowhere.
I must say, you've
surprised me, Spiral Organ...
I never would've
expected you
to lead us through
the Palace,
much less, provide
us with information.
Inconceivable.
What is it you
want in return?
Specialist of
Everything...
all I ask is that you
refrain from entering the
central area of the
Palace which lies ahead.
If you refuse I'll
have to fight you...
on the behalf
of Bal Masque...
and I don't think either of
us wants it to come to that.
Indeed, we won't
go further...
Know that we do not
consider your cooperation
with Bal Masque to
be a betrayal...
You are simply attempting
to achieve a goal.
However, should you keep me
from achieving my own goal...
I will exterminate you.
I completely understand...
I don't suppose I
could persuade you
to leave the
Palace altogether?
Persuade me how?
If you'll agree,
I shall offer...
two things to you...
The first of which
being information.
And the second...
Thanks to the
Spiral Organ,
we were able to
verify her safety...
The Flaming-Haired
Blazing-Eyed Hunter escaped...
she was able to do so
without assistance from me.
Astounding.
While I'm certain our
attack helped create
a diversion that allowed
her to break free...
if she had been left
to her own devices,
I think she would've
been fine indeed.
You should be proud.
I am proud of what
she's achieved...
That said, I can't help
but feel a tinge
of sadness deep
within my heart...
Because she no longer has
any reason to depend on me.
I suddenly feel
so useless...
Snap out of it.
Indeed, I shouldn't be
wasting my time sulking
when there are pressing
issues at hand...
It's better spent...
preparing for the
moment we strike.
Though I am
indeed worried...
I have faith in her.
For now I know, she's
capable of fighting
this battle all on her own.
I thought you unworthy
of the God of Atonement's
contract and our
master's attention...
I stand corrected, you
are quite worthy indeed.
That was nothing...
wait and see...
I'm just getting
warmed up.
Talk is cheap,
little girl...
so let's see
what you can do!
I haven't tapped in to
my full potential...
I've gotta find it...
or else, I'll never
be able to defeat him!
The Crypta continues
to collapse.
It's only a matter of
time before the Flame Haze
pinpoint the
precise location
of the Palace of the Stars.
What am I saying?
They're likely communicating
with the intruders
and therefore already
aware of our coordinates.
If that's true, I know
what Sophie Sawallisch's
next move will be...
Attention: this is
an emergency message.
Respond regardless of
present circumstance.
Do you read me commanders
of the Eastern
and Western forces,
Dashing Earthly Fiend, Ribesal
and Burning
Agitation, Haborym?
This is Ribesal.
I read you loud and clear.
Haborym reporting.
What is it,
Supreme Commander?
I order you to
cease combat
and return to the Palace
of the Stars at once.
I have reason to believe
it will be targeted
in a surprise attack by The
Braider of Trembling Might
and the Flame Haze Army.
A surprise attack? !
Do you have evidence to
support this conclusion?
I will fully brief you
on the matter later.
It is imperative that you
issue a withdrawal order
to all troops immediately.
Understood!
Let them try
their damndest...
But the Flame Haze
will never set foot
in the Palace of the Stars.
It is surrounded by a
protective barrier
of Unrestricted Spells.
We should be
getting close.
Yes.
Captain...
I'm sorry to keep
asking you this but...
are we all clear?
Yes, ma'am...
So far, so good...
We've been scanning
signals in the area,
and we haven't
encountered anything
that would require a
reevaluation of the operation.
Now... just sit back...
and allow us
to demonstrate
how helpful your
human allies can be.
Oh, we're aware...
The entirety of our
army is dependent...
on the might of
the human race.
No need to worry, we've
cast Seals over
every radar facility in
the surrounding area.
I've gone to great lengths
to ensure we don't leave
any trace of
this operation.
Guess I should check the map
one last time before we go...
Everything looks clear
along the rendezvous route;
I don't see any signs
of inclement weather.
Good, I'm glad to
hear it, Francois...
I can't thank you enough
for all your help...
We wouldn't have been able
to conduct this operation
without your knowledge
of meteorology.
The same can be said about
the Specialist of Everything
and the detailed coordinates
that she sent to us.
We are incredibly
fortunate to have
such amazing allies.
Commander Sawallisch,
we're approximately
three minutes from
the drop point.
Thanks for
letting me know.
This is it...
The moment we have all
been waiting for...
Our turn to strike back!
We have been
given an opportunity
to avenge our allies
who were struck down.
This operation depends
upon us defeating the enemy
before their
reinforcements arrive.
Our victory will not only
serve as an example
that future Flame Haze
will strive to attain...
but as a warning to
any Crimson Denizens
who might consider
attacking us.
That being said...
this endeavor will never
become a reality...
if we are unable to defeat
them in the first place.
Gentlemen, we shall now
commence Operation Crossing!
He just won't let up, will
he...? This sucks...!
We shouldn't be wastin'
our time with this guy!
I'm sure he feels the
same way about us.
True... We'll have the advantage
if we can figure out
where he's hidin'!
I found ya!
Watch out! He's
to your right!
I should've known
he was bluffing...!
Your reflexes are impressive
but there's no escaping ...
You're mine now.
Damn... we're screwed...
We won't make it!
An enemy attack?
Why are they
flying so low? .
Where did those
planes come from...?
Yeah, you're outta luck, pal.
They transported
their army by air? !
I suspected an
attack on the Palace
but I didn't anticipate it
being the entirety of
their forces simultaneously.
We must counterattack
at once.
I don't like that sound...
What's happening...?!
We can't descend now!
Bye bye!
She's here; The Braider
of Trembling Might,
Sophie Sawallisch...
The Palace of
the Stars descended,
shattering the protective
barrier surrounding it.
We now have an opening.
Indeed, this is our
chance to go help her.
She's some kind
of monster!
The longer we fight
the stronger she gets!
I can't keep this
up much longer...
Is this a joke?
Am I being sacrificed
to the God of Atonement? !
It's still not enough...
I have to think back...
to what I was taught
in the beginning.
Alastor...
A Flames Haze's power
derives not only
from the image of strength
the contractor holds...
but also from its fusion
with their Crimson Lord's power.
Therefore, in an effort to avoid
unnecessary preconceptions,
the Flaming-Haired
Blazing-Eyed Hunter
is not given a specific
fighting style.
After questioning
my relation to the
Flaming-Haired
Blazing-Eyed Hunter...
I've finally realized
that we are...
One and the same!
If I were to choose a
symbol to represent
my power as a Flame Haze...
What would it be? !
I cannot allow
myself to fall victim
to the God of Atonement's
contractor...
I must do something!
What symbolizes...
not only my strength...
but who I really am...?
The Flaming-Haired
Blazing-Eyed Hunter...
Shana!
True Crimson!
Emblaze!
Judgment!
Conviction!
I was hoping we might run
into you here, milady.
What a joyous reunion!
Thanks, Wilhelmina.
Let's go!
Yuji...
After Operation
Crossing's success,
the Flame Haze suddenly find
themselves with the advantage.
In a last ditch
effort to turn the tide,
Decarabia makes
an appearance
on the front lines
of the battlefield.
Next time, on Shakugan
no Shana Final:
"Feelings Heard."