Hey! Let me outta here!
Man, this sucks...
It's been a week already.
What do they want with me?
I guess this is it.
Seems weird they
don't have a sign...
It makes sense.
I'm here on Margery's
recommendation
so I can't screw up.
I think this is
the right place....
Uh... Hello...
I'm here as the representative
of the Chanter of eleg...
You must be Keisaku Sato.
Please... if
you'll follow me.
Sure.
For security reasons...
I'll need to hold on
to your cell phone...
and any other communication
device you may have.
This is different
than I expected.
So, uh...
Hey!
What's goin' on...?!
C'mon, man...! Let me out!
[Music]
I can't believe I walked
right into a trap.
Why did I ever come here?!
I hope everyone
back home's okay.
I can't believe that
I completely froze
in front of Yuji.
That time we had alone
might've been my only chance
to turn things around.
Maybe I could've undone some
of their brainwashing...
No... it wouldn't
have worked,
he's too far gone.
I was so scared when he
reached out to touch me...
like he might take
something from me.
I don't understand why...
You're such an idiot!
There's no need to
get all worked up.
Are you kiddin' me?!
You typed a letter
to Wilhelmina
and forged my
signature on it!
Of course I'm worked up!
This is exactly why
I've always preferred
handwritten letters!
I'm sorry but it
had to be done...
The situation in Misaki City's
gotten out of hand...
We need her help
now more than ever.
What's goin' on?
I was merely trying
to get her to speak
with Commander Sawallisch...
That's all it would
take to convince her...
Shut up!
I don't understand
why you're so angry.
Flieder's just trying to do
what's best for everyone!
I hate to break it
to you, Brigid,
but what your Flame Haze pulled
was totally out of line.
I would've contacted
her myself
but she won't listen to me.
Now that Margery
Daw's down...
she's basically
on her own.
I didn't have a choice.
Tell me what's happened
to Margery Daw...!
I need to know!
Please tell me!
Lemme guess, you're
the boy she sent...?
Okay fine, I'm comin' in.
Stand back! Get
away from the door!
Hurry!
Stop being reckless!
He's no good to us as
a hostage if he's dead!
I was just
testin' his luck.
There's no need to
get all worked up.
Hello...! You're not
missin' any limbs, are ya...?
You're alive and
in one piece,
I'd say you've
got good luck.
Rebecca Reed, the Scatterer
of Sparkling Light.
And this is the Opened Eye
of Incineration, Balar...
Nice to meet ya.
What?! Margery's in a coma?!
She would never
let that happen!
Yeah well, I don't think
she was planning on it.
But I'm afraid that's what it
said in Wilhelmina's report.
How did it happen?
You've had a bad day and
I hate to make it worse...
but something terrible
happened in Misaki City.
You ain't leavin', kid.
Oh yeah, who says so...?!
Listen... I have to get
back there to see her.
Considerin' the state
she's in right now,
there's nothin'
you can do to help.
When you care
for someone...
it's only natural to
be worried about them!
Aw... you care for her?
I guess so...
I was wondering,
are you good friends
with Wilhelmina?
Why do you ask?
I overheard you say
something about a letter
that had been
written to her.
You heard that, huh...?
Well, I haven't talked to
Wilhelmina in a while...
but I would definitely
consider her my friend.
-Seriously?
-Uh-huh.
Hello...?
Yeah, I know.
I'm on my way now.
I've gotta meeting
to get to...
You stay put
while I'm gone.
Wait a minute!
Rebecca!
Good grief...
Kids these days can
be so belligerent.
Funny you should
say that...
Rebecca...
Is somethin' wrong?
No, it's just that
I've watched you
become increasingly
irritable lately...
and I think this boy could
help you get past it.
I knew it, it's a Rinne...
Stand back, Specialist...
I can handle this
one on my own!
That was too easy.
Scatterer of
Sparkling Light...
I would indeed appreciate
some advance warning.
Right back atcha.
Back then, I'd have no
problem helping her out.
She's never been the
kind to ask for help...
She must be in
big trouble.
This is the last
response to my request...
I'm afraid we've run
out of viable options.
So disappointing.
Outlaw is preparing
to head into battle...
Indeed, it's no surprise
they want to hold their
forces in reserve...
If I must, I am prepared
to take care of this
matter by myself.
I thank you for making the
long and treacherous journey
to join us...
Guardian of Steady Passage,
Samuel Demantius...
and the Peaceful Shield
of Scales, Zirnitra.
I apologize for
our late arrival,
normally we would have responded
to your summons immediately.
I assure you, we will
do everything we can
to meet your
expectations of us.
We'll rely heavily on
you in the days to come.
True...
We're delighted to
have you here with us,
and my only regret...
is the circumstances
of your visit.
Together we will be an
unstoppable force...
Supreme Commander,
Mother Courage...
Sophie Sawallisch, the
Braider of Trembling Might...
and the Thunder Blade of
Banishment, Takemikazuchi.
We are honored to fight
alongside the Flame Haze
of Outlaw.
I can't thank you
enough, Sirotci...
I'm sure that your expertise
will prove indispensible.
Now that our Shanghai
post has been annihilated
our final line of defense
in the eastern theater,
the Tokyo post,
has increased
in importance.
As a result...
I suspect that when Bal
Masque makes their move...
they will attack Tokyo
and the surrounding area.
So, basically, we're
going to need to gather
as many powerful
Flame Haze as we can.
Isn't that right, Flieder?
You'll be in command
of this post...
but we're going to
ask Wilhelmina Carmel
to come and assist you.
Oh really...?
And just how are you
going to convince her...?
She wants to rescue
the captured Nietono.
I don't think there's
anything you could say
to change her mind.
And that's why I'm
going to need your help
to persuade her...
You're a smart girl,
surely you'll be
able to see...
that there's no point in
attempting such a thing.
It would be futile.
You can't just storm into
The Palace of the Stars...
Sydonay, Bel-Peol, Hecate
and the rest of
Bal Masque call it home.
I'm telling you,
attempting a rescue mission
there isn't just a long shot...
it's impossible.
Yeah, I can
see your point.
We can't afford to lose a
powerful Flame Haze like her
to such a hopeless cause.
It would be far more
logical for her to come here
and join our cause instead.
The more I have to
listen to his "logic",
the more it's startin'
to get to me...
When you care
for someone...
it's only natural to
be worried about them!
Oh, so that's it...!
I'm worried about her
'cause I care....
Thanks a lot for
saving me back there.
Surely, anyone else would have
indeed done the same thing.
Ya' know, at
times like this,
it's okay to say
that I owe ya one...
Wilhelmina.
Okay... then you owe me one...
Rebecca.
It'd be nice to repay that
favor a few hundred years later.
Are you listening?
Like it or not, I will
find a way to get her here...
You just watch me.
Are you gonna use the kid?
There's no way
she'll refuse
if she thinks her friend's
life is on the line.
Wow, just when I thought
you couldn't be
any more of an ass...
Um, Flieder's just
doing what's necessary
to get the job done.
There's no need
for name calling...
So, uh...
Rebecca?
Damn it...
Guess I'm stuck here.
Rebecca!
That was dangerous!
What do you think
you're doing?!
I'm ditchin' this place...
c'mon you can handle
things without me.
No, you're not
going anywhere...!
This is going to be the
greatest battle in history
and you're an
important part of...
You better get outta
my way, Flieder.
If you don't, I'll blow up this
building so spectacularly
the whole city
will be in awe.
Wait, is that...?
Yo... How you doin', buddy?
Let go- you're choking me!
We're bustin' outta here.
Seriously?
I started feelin' kinda guilty
about the whole thing...
so I decided I'm gonna help
my friend, Wilhelmina.
Wait, you're from Misaki
City, too, aren't ya...?
I can take ya back with me!
I'm really grateful I
bumped into you, Soto.
Um, it's Sato.
I've been so wrapped up in
my position with Outlaw...
I never would've left
to help Wilhelmina out
if it wasn't for you.
Oh...
You ended up bein' a lot
more useful than a hostage
could ever be.
Let me get this straight,
our hotheaded, little
friend left the Tokyo post
to go to Wilhelmina's aid?
Yes, ma'am.
I'm sorry, Commander.
Flieder did his
best to stop her
but she threatened to
blow up the building...
Did any other Flame Haze
leave along with Rebecca Reed?
Not that I know of...
I believe she was
the only one who left
but she took the
hostage with her.
Well, then it
can't be helped...
As long as it doesn't
cause problems with morale...
I suppose we'll just
have to let her go.
Here ya go...
A parting gift.
What is all this?
Reports I've received
from Wilhelmina.
They'll fill you in on
what's been happening
in Misaki City.
We've also included
some of Outlaw's plans
for the upcoming war.
So guard it with your life.
Right, I will!
If you know what's
good for ya,
you'll go check on Margery.
You mean, you're
not comin' with me?
Now listen up, you...
Your lady wouldn't
be too happy
if you showed up with
another chick on your arm.
No, it's not like that...
I'm just messin'
with ya, buddy!
I don't think I'd
have as much fun
watching you make
out with Margery...
as I'm gonna have teasin'
the Flaming-Haired
Blazing-Eyed Hunter
for lettin' herself
get captured.
Well...? Get goin'!
Right...!
Thanks Rebecca... and Balar...
I appreciate it.
Sure...! It was no problem.
I hope our paths cross
again in the future,
Keisaku Sato.
Well then...
Transposer of
Corpses and Bodies...
I shall leave
the Tokyo Post...
in your hands,
Ernest Flieder.
As you wish,
Supreme Commander.
We promise that we'll do
our very best, Sophie!
And any minute now...
Wilhelmina's request for help
will be answered by Rebecca.
Then, of course...
there's the letter
that I sent her.
You have my
eternal gratitude.
I'll see you tomorrow...
at the rendezvous point.
Rebecca Reed has answered
our call for help.
Our luck has changed!
Yes, indeed...
It's about time.
"Dear Wilhelmina Carmel,
a Flame Haze is coming to you
with classified information...
Please make sure that you
cooperate with them."
The Scatterer of
Sparkling Light...
Rebecca Reed is now...
assisting Wilhelmina...
and so will they...
Yes... I hope she appreciates
the sacrifice you've made.
Your bath is ready,
Lady Shana.
That moment keeps playing
over in my mind...
Yuji was trying to grab me.
No...
That's not it...
He was reaching
for my hand.
I remember...
I once held someone else's
hand in the same way.
Please you have to go.
Thank you for
taking care of us.
It wasn't for you!
None of it...
was for you...
I did it out of
love for Mathilde!
I know what it
means to love, too.
Is that so?
Uh-huh.
I see...
Well...
I feel the same
way about you.
Please... take my hand...
'Kay.
After everything
I've been through...
And everything
I've seen...
I want us to be
together, Shana.
I knew the power Yuji held
in the palm of his hand...
The power of his touch...
Because it's a feeling...
I've felt before.
There's an Unrestricted Spell...
that is so powerful...
it is capable of making the
strongest Crimson Lord...
collapse upon his knees.
Someday...
you'll find it.
Guess what?
I did it, Shiro.
I found the Unrestricted
Spell you told me about...
Yes...
It's love.
What happened?
The Supreme Throne!
You're no longer... needed.
[Music]
A captive Shana stands
helpless before Hecate,
who attacks her
without warning.
Meanwhile, in Misaki City,
Yoshida sees a familiar
face from her past.
Next time, on Shakugan
no Shana Final:
"The Divine Gate."