We now have
further details
on the suspected
acts of terrorism
that simultaneously struck
countless airports
throughout Japan
early this morning.
I thought it couldn't
get any worse.
Now innocent people
have been hurt.
The Denizens are
swarming to Japan
'cause that's where Xanadu's
gonna be created.
And the Flame Haze aren't
gonna let 'em go anywhere
without a fight.
It just sucks that humans were
caught in the crossfire.
Just because the Denizens
have been ordered
not to devour human souls,
doesn't mean they're going
to behave themselves.
[Music]
I was led to believe the
Flame Haze are responsible
for maintaining the
Earth's balance.
Obviously, that
is not the case!
At least the Crimson Denizens
know when to put
away their swords.
That's ridiculous!
We were outnumbered but
we did the best we could.
You do realize the only
reason you're alive
is because of us, right?
I don't see you putting
your lives on the line.
Don't act as though we
humans owe you anything.
While we appreciate the
attempt to protect us,
we cannot simply overlook
such a heinous oversight.
You knew you
were outnumbered.
Yes, but we fought anyway,
for your sake!
I knew this meeting
would be tense
but it's worse
than I thought.
This venue was a mistake.
It would help if we were
able to speak face-to-face.
They've been seduced
by a coward's peace
and lost to the
madness of terror.
In all honesty, I expected
as much from the humans.
The God of Creation could
strike at any moment.
We should be preparing
for his next move;
not sitting in a dusty, old
hall arguing about a battle
that's already been lost.
Once they've had the opportunity
to speak their minds,
I'm sure they will
return all power
to our fearless leader.
This loss was our fault
as much as it was hers.
She alone cannot be
held accountable.
What a travesty.
Their bickering
is an insult to
the troops who gave
their lives fighting.
For now, all we can
do is wait patiently
until they eventually
run out of hot air.
Yes, please enlighten us.
We have to come to an
agreement of some sort.
So the humans are
pissed at Outlaw?
They never cared
what we did before.
I guess there's a first
time for everything.
Well, we did just
get our asses kicked
so I can't blame 'em
for being on edge.
Besides, they're good and
drunk on the "Xanadu" wine
the kid's been pouring
down their throats.
And I'm bettin' they're gonna
stay that way for a while.
Yuji Sakai.
In all of history,
I don't think there's ever
been anyone more deserving
of the title of
"evil genius".
They say when a man's
character isn't clear
you should look
to his friends.
Wonder what that
says about you?
Okay, it's open.
Far as I can tell,
there look to be eighty-two
different layers.
This is amazing.
Each spell is constructed
with unimaginable precision.
Thank goodness for the
Scroll of Secrets;
it would take me decades to
analyze this thing without it.
Hey, Shana?
Is this the first time
you've ever visited New York?
Yeah.
I've been to America before
but never to one
of the cities
where the Gods of
the Earth live.
I can't get her to
come out of her shell.
I didn't think she
was the shy type
but it sure seems that way.
That's yummy!
Finally, a sign of life!
My goodness!
All it takes is a
single raspberry
and all of a sudden
she's adorable!
No joke!
She looks like the
contractor of an angel
not the God of Atonement.
Would you like to
try a blueberry?
Or maybe some pineapple?
Thanks, Chiara.
Now she's being friendly.
She was just nervous,
that's all.
I guess it's
understandable.
I mean, it's gotta be
pretty tough knowing
that the fate of the
world is in your hands.
It's about time;
I thought their flight
would never come in.
Let's find 'em.
Are you sure you're going
to be all right, miss?
Try to cheer up, okay?
Thank you for
being so kind.
This journey would've
been unbearable
were it not for you,
my friends.
It was no big
deal, really.
Here, use this to
dry your tears.
All right, all right,
let's break it up.
Show's over, people.
Time for you to
get a move on.
-Goodbye.
-Take care of yourself.
Ladies.
We meet again
Archer of Aurora!
You're just as
lovely as ever.
Thanks. It's nice to see
the two of you again.
I don't believe that
I've had the pleasure
of making your
acquaintance, miss.
You can call me Southvalley.
I'm the Evoker
of Demon Horde,
known as He Who Shows
the Path of the Dead.
And I am the humble
priest of Tezcatlipoca,
the Pipe of
Hesitation and Fear.
My name is...
It's you!
You are the child who has
been entrusted with the future
by the Drum of
Exceptional Love
and He Who Walks with Rain.
I am the priestess
of Chalciuhtlicue,
who is known as the Bell
of Cleansing Flutter.
I am called the Whirler
of Mighty Waves.
She Who Dances Before
the Surging Sea,
but please feel free
to call me Westshore.
Deity of providence,
avatar of judgment
and condemnation.
Great Flame of Heaven.
It is truly an honor
to finally meet you.
No, the honor is mine.
We appreciate you coming
here on such short notice.
However...
It's not been decided I will
be entrusted with the future,
not yet.
Thanks to the Beckoner
of Brightened Dew
and the Drum of
Exceptional Love,
twenty percent of the Flame Haze
Army survived our defeat.
I'd like to show
my gratitude
and fulfill the covenant
I made with them,
by striking at the heart of
the enemy's forces myself.
That said,
while the plan I've devised
is based on strategy,
it also incorporates my
personal feelings as well.
I realize that it may go
against your principles,
however, as the Flaming-Haired
Blazing-Eyed Hunter,
I feel it is our best
course of action.
If after hearing this, you
still want to join our fight,
I'd be more than happy to
share the details with you.
But if you choose not to,
then from this day forward,
we'll never bother you again.
I'm sorry.
I hate to laugh but I
don't think you know
who you're dealing
with, miss.
You see, the Four
Gods of the Earth
aren't nearly as
concerned with "the rules"
as the rest of
you Flame Haze.
So there's no need to talk
about the great task with us.
The regulations of
others do not sway us.
Even amidst this chaos,
we'll choose which
path we follow.
In fact, the feelings you
see as a disadvantage
may be the
deciding factor in
whether we choose
to join your fight.
Since ancient times,
the interaction between
Crimson Denizens and humanity,
has been part of the
natural order of this world.
We fear the God of
Creation's recent exploits
may jeopardize that order.
And now we realize
that it is time for us
to take a stand against him.
We cannot stand by while
he manipulates this world.
He must be stopped.
If the God of Creation
creates Xanadu
and leaves with all of
the Crimson Denizens,
the Power of Existence
they currently hold,
would come rushing
back to the Earth,
making it incredibly unstable
for a long time to come.
It's highly likely
they're just going to
do what they did here
but to an even
greater capacity.
They won't have any reason to
hold back in the new world.
The Crimson Denizens
will have free rein there
because it was created
specifically for them.
We know what
we must do now.
There is only one way we
can protect the Earth
and its innocent people from
the impending disaster,
and that is to prevent the
creation of the Xanadu.
You've got a message for us,
so let's hear it.
Share with us the words
entrusted to you
by the Drum of Exceptional Love
and He Who Walks With Rain.
"I have become
a drop of rain.
I sacrificed myself hoping
it would force you to act."
"Please believe
me when I say."
"Joining the Flame Haze
in their fight is,
without doubt, the
right choice to make."
Very well.
The decision has been made.
And, who made the
choice to fight?
Just say the word,
and we'll be there.
I'll explain our
plan of attack.
Um, excuse me.
Thanks for inviting us.
If there's anything
we can help with,
call us and we'll
be right over.
Thank you, kids.
But you've got
better things to do
than hang out with
old fogies like us.
Please be careful on
your way home, okay?
-We will!
-Thanks again for the meal!
So, I guess we'll see ya.
Take care of yourselves.
Goodbye.
See ya soon!
Jeez. I thought Tanaka
was a gentleman.
Why isn't he
walking you home?
It's not a big deal.
I'm too busy to
hang out anyway.
You're just
gonna let 'em go?
Yeah.
I think that's what's
best for everybody.
You realize they're
gonna get wrapped up
in this mess eventually.
You shouldn't worry.
Sakai.
Um?
What is it?
You wanna go by your
parent's house and say hi?
Your dad's
there right now.
You could just say that
you're a friend of ours.
Even if they don't
remember who you are
at least you'd get
to see them again.
No, thanks.
I'm sorry but I
can't do that.
What is with you?
If you don't wanna
see your folks
then why the hell
are you here?
I thought Sato would've
told you by now.
I'm creating a
paradise for Denizens.
He told us about Xanadu.
Well, I want to do it here,
in Misaki City.
Do you remember what
I told you, Yoshida?
The last time
we met I said,
"I haven't changed
anything yet."
However, since that time,
I've changed many things.
Now that all of the other
preparations are complete,
there is only one
more thing I need.
And that is your help.
No way! As if it weren't bad
enough that you took Shana,
now you wanna
take Yoshida, too?
Miss Yoshida's cooperation
is absolutely imperative
to Yuji Sakai's plan.
But.
Perhaps you're right,
this is rather sudden.
I'll give her time
to think it over.
How about we go for a
walk in the meantime?
I know it's kind of cold.
And you're not gonna snatch
her like you did Shana?
No. This is your opportunity
to ask me anything at all.
I'll tell you whatever
you want to know.
I've got time to spare
and I'd like to hear
what you have to say.
All right, what happened to that
Snake of the Festival jerk?
He's still here, within me.
So how much of
you is Sakai
and how much is
the creepy dude?
I'd prefer you call him
the God of Creation
or Snake of the Festival.
He's a noble being who
deserves your respect.
I guess you could
say we've merged.
The Snake of the Festival
is focused on his
purpose for existence.
He has no interest in
interfering with my plans
or anyone else's
for that matter.
I trust him because he
had the opportunity
to completely take
over my existence,
but he chose not to.
Are you trying to tell me
that the guy's not a creep?
'Cause from what I saw,
he's an arrogant jerk
with a big mouth.
That's not true.
He simply wants
to grant a wish
that he couldn't
thousands of years ago.
Is that so wrong?
You misconstrued his
fervor for arrogance.
He's not a maniacal leader
but a compassionate one.
He's just more vocal than
other gods like Alastor.
Wait a minute.
You're not gonna fight against
him and Shana, are you?
I'm afraid I
have no choice.
-There's gotta be another way!
-No.
It's inevitable.
But why?
Is it for her sake?
Not just for hers,
but for everyone's sake.
You seriously think that
you're doing the right thing?
Yes, that is
what I believe;
whether you agree or not.
C'mon, Sakai, just think about
what you're doing to Shana!
I understand that it's
difficult for you to see things
from my perspective.
'Cause it's messed up!
And now you wanna get
Yoshida involved, too?
You really can't
do this without me?
No.
I need your help Yoshida.
If that's the case,
then I'll go with you.
Don't do it!
It's okay.
I'm gonna be fine.
I just know there's no way
I'll be able to refuse him.
I'll go as long
as you can assure me
that I'll be helping
Sakai with his plan.
Yes.
You will be there
solely to help me.
I don't see Ogata.
Why hasn't she made
it to practice yet?
She said she
was gonna skip
because she had
something important to do
later this afternoon.
That's why she
was able to go
to your dad's
welcome home party.
I see.
Are you gonna turn the school
into a battlefield again?
Like during the
Autumn Festival?
I don't think
you understand.
It's much bigger
than that.
It all started
here at Managawa.
It's where I met Hirai
who's soul was
later devoured.
But this time it won't
be just the school.
All of Misaki City will
become a battlefield.
What the hell's
gotten into you?
What'll happen
to everyone here?
I've taken every
necessary precaution
to protect innocent civilians
from the fighting.
Believe me, if I thought
that their lives
were going to be at risk.
I never would have
let Ike and Ogata
go home this afternoon.
I'm prepared to
protect Misaki City
and all of its residents.
The Denizens
have been ordered
not to devour
human souls in Japan
and it's being
upheld so far.
But... I can't guarantee
the human's safety for long
'cause the order was given
by the God of Creation,
the Snake
of the Festival.
A god who is known to
affirm all desires.
I think it's fair to say
he's underestimated
by the very
Denizens he serves.
He is an optimistic god,
which has lead his
followers to believe
that he will forgive
them for any wrongdoing.
I'll admit I was
skeptical at first.
I couldn't imagine
the Crimson Denizens
would ever agree to adhere
to his injunction.
But so far, so good.
Ever since we first
mentioned paradise to them,
they've been on
their best behavior.
Call it a reward, or bait,
either way, it calmed
them down for now.
Honestly, I have no
idea what'll happen
when Xanadu's born.
Until then,
all I can do
is observe them and
kill any who disobey.
I hate that it has
to come to that
but I have to keep them in
check one way or another.
Yuji Sakai will be the one
who finally grants
the Denizens' wish
but I must be
strict with them.
Not only to protect
what is here now,
but also what is to come.
I have a difficult
job ahead of me.
I have to be a
tightrope walker.
I must balance between
the small gears
of the giant
machine known as
the creation of
paradise, Xanadu.
And I'm limited by
the current state
of the Snake of
the Festival's body.
I get it now.
Just like me, Sakai's
finally figured out
that he's powerless
but he's decided to
keep fighting anyway.
He's just trying to
accomplish a goal.
In a way, he's no
different from Shana
who's trying to accomplish
her own goal right now.
In the end, both of 'em
are just trying to stand up
for what they believe in.
I bet that's why Yoshida
agreed to go with him,
'cause she wants to stand
up for her beliefs as well.
Long ago, the
God of Creation,
the Snake of the Festival,
wanted to create
a walled garden
that would house all the
Denizens in this world.
But he was banished to the
Abyss before it came to be.
Now, thousands
of years later,
the Crimson Denizens have
a new wish for their god.
They want a world
just like this one
that they can
call their own.
To grant their wish,
the God of Creation has decided
to make an identical world
within the Abyss itself.
A place where his followers
will be allowed to roam free
without being hunted.
A parallel world,
if you will.
It'll be identical to
this one in every way?
But how's that
even possible?
I mean, I thought the
rift was a volatile place;
filled with crazy
storms and stuff.
It's possible.
Time and distance are
completely meaningless there.
I could create
a whole universe
and it wouldn't have any
effect on it whatsoever.
The chaos there has
nothing to do with creation.
The Denizens
have requested
that their paradise
be full of life;
they want it to be
a perfect reflection
of the world
they live in now.
They don't want
an empty playground
with no one to interact
with but themselves.
They want a world
where they can continue
to live amongst the humans
as they have been
all this time.
When the Denizens first
came to this world,
they were fascinated by it.
More than anything, they
wanted to peacefully coexist
with the humans.
I'm creating Xanadu to
give them a second chance.
Once we leave this place,
you will never have to
worry about another soul
being devoured again.
It won't be long
before Shana and the
others try to stop me.
But there is no stopping me.
I'm prepared to do
whatever I must
to make Xanadu a reality.
Hey Sakai.
I don't understand why
you haven't told Shana
what you're telling us now!
-I think she should know!
-I can't.
Why can't you?
I know her well.
There's no way
she would ever agree
to take part in a vague,
optimistic plan like mine.
I am willing to
explain my reasoning
to any Flame Haze who
would care to listen
but I know it won't
sway their opinion.
Their unwillingness to
discuss the matter leaves me
with no other choice.
We'll have to go to war.
You're gonna fight Shana?
Has Sato been in
contact with you?
Shana and the others should
be here in just a few hours.
I would suggest that
you don't stick around.
You don't have
to tell me twice!
I'm gonna tell
Sato everything
then I'm gonna
ditch this bookmark,
head home, eat dinner,
and hit the sack!
It's in your
hands now, Sakai.
Promise me you're gonna do
what you can to protect us!
Everybody's counting on you!
I promise.
Yoshida, are you
sure you wanna go?
Yeah.
I guess this is goodbye.
Listen, Sakai.
I know we haven't really
known each other that long
but it's been one
hell of a ride, man!
Yeah.
As a matter of fact,
it almost feels like
it was all a dream.
I gotta be honest.
I wanted to punch you
when I first saw you
but we're cool now.
Thanks, Tanaka.
I'll see ya.
Well, I'm ready
to go if you are.
You're positive?
In the beginning,
I wasn't so sure
'cause I was scared.
But now that I
know the real Sakai
is still in
there somewhere,
I'm happy to do whatever
I can to help you.
I know it's a lot to take
in but I assure you,
I'm doing what's
best for the world.
Upon her arrival at the
Palace of the Stars,
Yoshida is told her role
in the creation of Xanadu.
Under the protection
of Bal Masque,
Denizens swarm Misaki City
as Yuji and Shana
begin their final battle.
Next time, on Shakugan
no Shana Final:
"Spiral of Conflict."