Constructing
Unrestricted Spell:
-Qadesh's Blood Pulse.
-Deploying!
Ya ready, Gramps? !
What's going on?
Is this an attack? !
Trouble, sir!
It's the destroyer...!
The- the Mobilizer of
Ceremonial Equipment
is right outside
the Palace!
Khamsin? Here? !
No...!
That explosion was...
What're they waitin' for?
Where's Sydonay, huh...?
Or the rest of the Trinity,
for that matter?
The Scatterer of
Sparkling Light!
Why them, of all people...?
All forces, attack...!
Purson! Uvall! Report!
I won't fail...
Magnesia!
Aw, man! Didn't
even make a dent?
Ah... Thanks to Magnesia...
the Tempest Hoof's spell.
They were shrewd
in appointing him
to guard the Palace
of the Stars.
I... I did it, I shielded the
Divine Gate in time...
Lord Fecor!
Your orders, sir?
I'll keep maintaining
Magnesia from here...
Purson, I want you leading
from the front lines...
Uvall, find their
entry point...
You need to verify that no
more of their allies
came through with them.
Also, inform the maids:
the princess is to be
evacuated to the lower
levels immediately.
Understood. Leave it to us.
How is this even
possible...?
Decarabia, Officer
of Boundless Seas
and Supreme Commander of the
Forces attacking Outlaw,
come in.
I have been observing,...
Fortress Commander
Fecor, the Tempest Hoof.
Have you been able
to ascertain
how they could penetrated
our defenses...?
How did they get inside
the Palace of the Stars?
Our outer defenses have
not been penetrated...
Therefore, no explanation
can be discerned.
Are any troops
approaching?
-No.
-So then...?
The nearest reinforcements
will have arrived
here by morning...
They will begin by
searching the area
surrounding
the fortress...
For now, however...
Yes, I understand...
In our master's absence,
we must reinforce
the Crypta spell...
to shield both the
Gate and the Palace!
This is it!
The distraction I
need to break free!
[Music]
Mistress Shana,...
the castle is quickly
becoming a dangerous place.
We have been ordered to
take you to the lower levels,
where you will be safe.
Please, come with us.
Please hurry.
Not yet...
I still have only the
strength of a normal human...
If I tried to attack now,
I couldn't even
defeat these Rinne.
So I'll wait...
For a better moment...
For my opening
to strike back!
It's said... that Fecor's
Unrestricted Spell
is impregnable.
So whaddaya wanna do now,
try blastin' away at
the whole castle?
Kill anybody that might be
stupid enough to come out?
Or maybe...
We could smoke Fecor
out of his hidey-hole.
Ah... But it would be unwise
to underestimate
the Tempest Hoof.
Even on his own, he
is quite formidable.
You're correct that we
should strike before
they've gotten
their bearings...
I'd like to destroy the
Crypta Unrestricted Spell
that's shielding
the fortress.
Since we insisted
on coming here,...
we should contribute
something
that will aid
our covert team.
Oh, we're gonna help
'em out, all right...
'Cause I'm pretty sure they
can't do it without us...
But yeah... anyway...
It's not like we've
run into any serious
challenges so far!
So far, so good.
No one will expect this...
No one would even consider
an attack from within.
Indeed,...
were it not for the
Heaven's Road Palace,
we would not have
known either.
Heaven's Road Palace and
the Palace of the Stars
must never come in
close proximity.
Ah... Gavida, the Soaring
Tower of Quintessence...
A name I've not heard
in a long time...
It was he who was
responsible
for the creation
of both palaces.
Why can they not come...
near one another?
The Heaven's Road Palace
is a place of the sun,...
filled with life...
The Palace of the Stars,
a temple of night,
is its opposite.
Originally, the two
places worked in tandem,
as large Treasure Tools...
By their design,...
if they pass within a certain
distance of each other,...
a path connecting them,
which is currently severed,
will indeed
regenerate itself.
In other words, Bal
Masqué's headquarters...
is gonna be right
freakin' next door to us.
That answers the
question of why Gavida
would forbid their reunion.
Right...
But given the situation that
is our only feasible way in...
Guess we'll have to get used
to our new neighbors...
This is the passageway.
As we draw closer to the
Palace of the Stars,
it will begin
repairing itself.
The path opens.
So this leads
to the castle?
Indeed.
But what exactly we'll
face on the other side...
only fate can say.
Uh-huh...
There's every possibility
that we could walk
right into the middle of
an enemy formation.
A high-stakes wager.
It'll be fun...! Come on!
We were most fortunate
indeed that Gavida
did not tell Bal Masqué
about this passageway.
He despised them.
All that is left
to do now...
is for us to locate
mistress Shana...
and to pray that
we have good luck.
Please Lady Shana,
we need to hurry.
If they're taking me somewhere
that's heavily guarded,...
it's over...
I'll lose my chance...
Come on...!
Gimme a sign...!
I need something big...!
Anything!
Supreme Commander...
I have the
latest report...
Operation Calm is
proceeding as scheduled.
And at this rate...
Is something wrong, ma'am?
I'm worried.
We've based this
operation solely upon...
the coordinates
we've received
and the observations we've made
of the mighty distortion
that's blanketed
the world.
There are lives
at stake...
I question whether or
not this is all part
of the enemy's plan.
That is why I fret...
I cannot rid myself
of that fear.
The unease that comes from
putting one's charges
into harm's way...
is one of a leader's
many burdens.
As I well know.
If you have concerns, let
my men alleviate them
by conducting an
investigation...
to confirm or
deny these fears.
Of course,...
the responsibility is
ultimately yours to bear.
That's is an excellent
idea, thank you.
Balar... that thing we saw
up in the sky...
What the heck was it?
Hmm...? Ah, yes.
That black mirror...
I have no idea
what it is...
but I suspect it's connected
to the disruption we felt...
It's another one of
Bal Masqué's secrets
that we'll
eventually unveil.
Hell yeah, we will.
We're already this deep
in their territory,...
and we still haven't
seen that Mystes,
who's supposedly
their new master...
Nor have we seen a single
one of the Trinity...
Seems fishy.
It makes me think that
creepy black mirror
has gotta have somethin'
to do with them
not bein' around.
Regardless,...
we don't know the
consequences of simply
blowing it up...
I'll bet the geezers have
come to the same realization.
Yeah... And either way,
until we're able to
neutralize Magnesia...
This is just fun!
That's quite enough.
I have let your
wanton destruction
go on for far too long.
Sorry about
that, furball...
But it's kinda what
we're here for,
and we're just
so good at it!
Interesting...
It seems there's no
sense in asking nicely...
So I'm telling you:
leave this place at once.
I'm the Majestic Lion's
Bellowing Call, Purson...
A pleasure to meet you.
Fancy name, it'll look
nice on your tombstone!
What the crap? !
There's only one man
who would invent
something so powerful,
yet so stupid.
The Seeker, of course...
Man, I hate that guy!
Me too...
If I don't see Dantalion
for another hundred years,
it'll be too soon.
It may look foolish,
but as you can see,
it's quite functional.
Facing warriors of renown
such as yourselves
will be a daunting task...
I will use everything
at my disposal.
Heads up... big guy!
Old man!
How do you like my
battle cry...?
It is rather appropriately
titled the Lion's Roar.
Well, you managed
beat up an old man...
So hey, you
accomplished something
before your death.
Alright, Balar...
It's time for the kid
gloves to come off.
As long as you stop
when I tell you to.
What am I...
doing here?
Why am I waiting?
I can't waste this...
It's my chance
to break free.
It must be the chain...
It's keeping me weak.
Power... I need power.
I feel it...
I need to...
get up!
I have to...
Move!
Come on...
You can do this!
There we go...!
Inch at a time!
Please-... Please,
miss come with me.
Please, miss,
come with me.
Please come with me...
Please come...
come with me...
Please come with me...
It's here...
But, where is it?
Where is it? !
Nietono no Shana!
Hey, didja hear that?
Sounded like it was
right out there.
Whoa... That's...
My master.
Tenmoku Ikko!
My Master...
I go to you.
All of our investigations
have failed to reveal
signs of their entry...
None of the outer defenses
were penetrated...
And they couldn't
have found a way
to break through Crypta...
Otherwise, Trivia here
would have detected it.
So how did they
get here...?
How did they bypass
our defenses...?
It's like they
just appeared,
inside the palace...
That's it...!
They were able to
breach the castle walls
before we knew
they were here...
Which means they must've
somehow come
from within the Palace?
But how...?!
There has to be
an explanation...
Thinking back, the Mobilizer
of Ceremonial Equipment
visited Misaki
City once before...
And the Specialist of
Everything was there as well.
She inherited Heaven's
Road Palace from Gavida,
the Soaring Tower
of Quintessence
and lived there
for some time...
Heaven's Road Palace...!
The mobile citadel,
created in tandem
with this fortress...
What if it holds some
secret we are unaware of...?
A hidden path connecting
them, for instance...
To make matters worse, if the
Specialist of Everything
has traveled
here with them...
Then they do not merely
plan to destroy the Palace,...
but to recover
the princess!
Lord Fecor!
Come quickl--
What...?! Tenmoku!
Balar...! Look!
What do you know?
Hey, old man!
I see it... Ready?
Oh no!
Lord Fecor's spell...
it's dissipating!
Not so fast!
That's impossible!
Go, go, gooo!
Welcome back.
Thank you for that.
Your blade, my master...
As always, I am
your servant.
You have done well.
[Music]
With the Nietono no Shana
back in her hands,
Shana fights to test
her power...
Meanwhile, Sophie Sawallisch
and her team leave Zurich
to launch an attack on
the Palace of the Stars.
An operation code-named...
"Crossing"...
Next time, on Shakugan
no Shana Final.