[MARI]
Hey, Yuri.
Makka got into
the steamed buns,
and one of 'em got
stuck in his throat.
[YURI] Victor! You need
to get back to Japan.
It will just be for tomorrow.
One day only, will you
be Yuri's coach?
Huh?
--Huh?
--[PLISETSKY] Huh?
[YURI] I can't believe
this is actually happening.
Ask Yakov if you need help
or don't understand something.
If you're in trouble,
just hug him,
and he'll be there for you.
I'm sorry, Yuri.
I know I won't be here,
but I'll be with you in spirit.
[YURI] And then,
Victor went back to Japan.
"Yuri vs. Yuri. The Horror!
Rostelecom Cup, Free Skate."
It didn't look like you
talked to Coach Yakov
too much during this
morning's practice.
How do you feel about that?
I don't think it's a big deal.
I'll skate like I always have
with Victor, and it'll be fine.
[PLISETSKY] Why did Yakov
take on the pork cutlet bowl?
[YAKOV]
Yuri.
Your grandfather's here
if you want to see him.
[PLISETSKY]
Why are you here?
I didn't think you
were feeling well.
[GRANDPA PLISETSKY]
Hush, now. Just eat.
[grunts]
[PLISETSKY]
Pork, scrambled eggs, and rice?
What kind of pirozhki is this?
A pork cutlet bowl pirozhki.
Eat them and do your best
in the free skate, Yurochka.
Da.
[PLISETSKY] With Victor gone,
I'm the only one
who can win for Russia.
Now's my chance to prove myself.
[MOROOKA] Group Two
is about to take the ice
here at the Rostelecom
Cup in Moscow,
the final event of
the Grand Prix Series.
Each skater came
into this competition
with his own hopes and fears,
as it will determine
who advances to the
Grand Prix Final.
First up in Group Two,
currently in sixth place,
is the Czech Republic's
Emil Nekola.
[electronic music plays]
[MOROOKA] He is skating to music
from the movie Anastasis .
His theme for this season:
"Cyberpunk: I've
ceased to be human."
Just as the theme suggests,
he plans four quads,
a superhuman feat.
That was a beautiful
quadruple Salchow.
And well done!
[MOROOKA] Next up is a
quadruple toe loop combination.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
Quadruple toe loop...
Triple toe loop.
I need to say something
before you go out there.
I'm going to make it to
the Grand Prix Final, Mickey,
with or without you.
It's time for you
to learn how to skate
without me there to support you.
[MOROOKA] His next jump
will also be a quad.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A quadruple toe loop.
[MOROOKA]
That was brilliant!
[SARA]
Take a look around, will you?
I'm not the only
woman in the world!
Maybe not, but you're
the only woman I care about!
I've only come this
far because of you--
how can I keep
skating if you go?
Please don't leave me, Sara!
[SARA]
Learn how to be strong,
because, not only am I
going to skate without you,
I'm going to start dating.
[MOROOKA]
If he finishes second or above,
he may still make
the Grand Prix Final.
[MICHELE]
Do you like Czech men
who smile and laugh
all the time?
Is that it?
Or do you prefer moody Japanese
men who look like closet pervs?
What do they have to offer?
How can any of them
be worthy of you?
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A quadruple loop.
[MOROOKA]
That was perfect!
He's given us four flawless
quads in this program so far.
[MICHELE]
He really isn't human.
[EMIL]
Man, I'm getting tired.
[MICHELE gasps]
[grunts]
[ANNOUNCER 8A] Ah... He'd
planned a combination there.
[MOROOKA] He fell and couldn't
complete the second jump.
[EMIL]
Crap, that was bad!
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A triple Salchow.
[MICHELE]
Oops.
[EMIL]
Still going!
[AUDIENCE cheering]
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[panting]
[MOROOKA] The score for
Emil Nekola is 189.15.
His total score is 271.58.
Aren't you usually rinkside
to send him off to the ice?
[MOROOKA] Next up is
Michele Crispino, age 22.
He finished the
short program in fifth.
Will he make a comeback
in the free skate?
["Serenade for Two" plays]
[MOROOKA] He is skating
to "Serenade for Two."
[MICHELE] Sara, you're
out there somewhere,
watching me, aren't you?
Even though we're apart,
I can still feel your eyes.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A quadruple Salchow.
[SARA]
He looks a little sad out there.
I hope he holds up.
["Serenade for Two" continues]
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
Triple flip, single loop...
...and a triple Salchow!
[MOROOKA]
A three-jump combo!
[MICHELE] What should I do
with my feelings?
I guess... I could skate them?
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A triple axel.
[SARA] His skating is more
mellow than in practice.
Less high-strung.
He's like a different
person today.
Where'd that come from?
Love.
Can't you see it? It's so clear.
His skating is filled
with the pain of lost love.
[MICHELE]
What's changed?
We've been inseparable
our whole lives.
My precious Sara. My lady.
[SARA]
I don't understand!
Why are boys so mean to me?
[MICHELE]
It's because you're so cute.
Don't worry,
I beat them all up!
[SARA] Another guy
wants to go out with me.
[MICHELE]
I'll beat them all up!
I can see it now.
I've been an idiot, haven't I?
[gasps]
[MICHELE]
Sara. This is it.
This is the last time
I skate for you.
[MICHELE] It's over.
I have to accept that.
I'll show you
how much I love you
by letting you go.
Goodbye, Sara.
[SARA sobbing]
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A triple Lutz.
Amazing! That was flawless!
[SARA gasps]
[gasps]
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[MOROOKA] Here come the scores
for Michele Crispino of Italy.
One ninty-three point two four!
His total score was 282.89.
A new personal best!
[MOROKA]
He's surpassed his personal best
--by nearly 20 points!
--[SARA] Mickey!
[MICHELE]
Sara!
[SARA]
Congratulations!
I'm so proud!
That was by far the best program
I've ever seen you do.
You were thinking
about me, weren't you?
[MICHELE]
Eh, si ?
[SARA] I'm sorry for saying
such mean things to you earlier.
But I'm glad I did!
We're better off apart,
and now you can see it, too!
Heh?
Oh, Looks like Seung Gil's
starting. See ya!
[somber music playing]
[SEUNG GIL grunts]
[SEUNG GIL growls]
[PLISETSKY]
Hey, Yakov.
What is it?
I'm changing the
jump composition.
Huh?
I'll reduce the number of jumps
in the first half
from four to two.
So you'll have six
in the second half?
That's right.
That's suicide.
[PLISETSKY] It's the only way
I can win against JJ and Yuri.
[MOROOKA] Although Seung Gil
recovered after a fall
on his early quadruple loop,
he suffered a huge loss
in the standings and has no hope
of advancing to
the Grand Prix Final.
Though, we look
forward to seeing him
at the Four Continents
Championship.
[gasps]
[MOROOKA] Here on his home turf,
we have Yuri Plisetzky,
age 15, in third place
after the short program.
--Just listen to those cheers!
--[AUDIENCE] Yuri! Yuri! Yuri!
[PLISETSKY]
I am going to win the first gold
of my senior division
debut season.
["Allegro Appassionato
in B Minor" plays]
[MOROOKA]
He is skating to
"Allegro Appassionato
in B Minor."
The program was choreographed
by Lilia Baranovskaya,
former prima ballerina
of the Bolshoi Ballet.
For his senior debut,
they've chosen a piece
well known for its
difficulty and intensity.
This is the first season
he's been allowed
to attempt quads. Here's the
first of two in this program.
He landed that with
confidence and precision.
["Allegro Appassionato
in B Minor" continues]
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A triple axel from a spiral.
That was high.
Is he pushing himself too hard?
Yes. Dance with beauty.
Most people don't realize beauty
is a force of righteousness.
Without beauty,
strength means nothing.
[YURI] A hellish step sequence
without even time for a breath.
How is he so calm?
[YAKOV] This is about
when he starts to tire.
Hold up in the
second half, Yuri.
[PLISETSKY]
Damn. This is tough.
[gasps]
[MIRA] He's putting six jumps
in the second half?
[PLISETSKY]
All right, here we go.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A triple Lutz.
[PLISETSKY] Pork cutlet bowl has
three quads and JJ has four.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A triple flip.
[PLISETSKY] To beat them,
I can't make any mistakes.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A quadruple toe loop.
And next up, we have
a choreographic sequence.
[PLISETSKY] I don't want
to lose like that again.
[MOROOKA] With all eyes on him,
Yuri Plisetsky of Russia,
age 15, has completed
an excellent free skate.
[PLISETSKY]
Huh?!
Let's meet again on the podium
at the Rostelecom Cup, Yuri.
See you there.
Shithead!
[ANNOUNCER 8A] Quadruple
Salchow, triple toe loop.
[MOROOKA] That was a beautiful
jump with impressive height.
He's showing no signs of
slowing down in the second half.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A triple loop, double toe loop.
[PLISETSKY]
The last jump combination.
He's changed... so much.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A triple axel, single loop,
and a triple Salchow!
[MOROOKA] That's it,
he landed all his jumps!
[MOROOKA]
He refused to give into pressure
here at the Rostelecom Cup,
instead responding
to his local fans
and delivering a sublime
free skate program!
Russia must be proud today!
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[PLISETSKY pants]
[YURI] A performance beyond
his limits. That's what it was.
[MOROOKA] Yuri Plisetsky's
free skate score is 199.87,
a personal best.
His total score is 297.96.
He is currently in first place,
and has earned himself
a ticket to the
Grand Prix Final!
How'd you like my free skate,
pork cutlet bowl?
["Yuri on Ice" plays]
[MOROOKA]
Yuri Katsuki is in second place
after the short program.
He is skating to "Yuri on Ice."
["Yuri on Ice" continues]
[YURI] I don't want people
to think that everything
Victor's taught me so far
has been a waste.
I have to prove
myself by winning.
If I fail here,
everything is over.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A quadruple toe loop.
[YURI]
I popped it!
What is that idiot doing?
[MOROOKA] His second jump
turned into a single.
[YURI]
Damn it!
Calm down. Calm down.
[YURI]
How do I recover from this?
I've noticed you tend
to flub your jumps
when there's something
on your mind.
Care to share?
Starting today, I'm going
to be your new coach.
And you're going to win.
[YURI] Somehow, he seemed
to know how I felt.
Until Victor came into my life,
I never went around saying
I was going to win gold.
But whether I said it or not,
it's what I was skating for.
[MOROOKA]
That jump had enough rotations.
[PLISETSKY growls]
[YURI]
Honestly, I wanted to win gold
at last year's
Grand Prix Final, too.
You aren't a weak person, Yuri.
Nobody who knows you
would ever think that.
It's changed me.
I'm stronger now.
And I'll prove it
at the Grand Prix Final
with a gold medal!
I made it this far because
Victor believed in me.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A triple loop.
[YURI]
What happens if it ends here?
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
He two-footed that landing.
[YURI] If I don't make
it to the Grand Prix Final?
No, stop it.
Don't think right now.
Idiot! Come on--!
[whistles]
Ah...
How nice. All supportive
now that you've clenched
your spot in the final.
Are you going to
cheer for me, too?
[PLISETSKY growls]
Yuri. Let's go.
[YURI] Yurio looked like
that last three-jump combo
was going to kill him.
That idiot. He doesn't have
as much stamina as I do!
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A triple axel.
[YURI] Whether Victor's
here or I'm alone,
it's still just as difficult.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A triple flip.
[YURI]
I just need to keep it simple.
This program is me.
Nobody else can skate it
the way I can.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A triple axel, single loop,
and triple Salchow.
[gasps]
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A triple Lutz, triple toe loop.
[YURI] Victor and I created
this program together
and I love it so much it hurts.
[YURI]
I'm not finished yet.
I won't be done until
I get the gold with Victor.
[MOROOKA] In this step
sequence, you can feel
Yuri Katsuki's love, a love
he can only express on the ice.
[AUDIENCE cheers]
Aw. He had really good
flow up until the end.
Da. You know,
when you think of how it
could've been with Victor here,
you want to see that.
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[YAKOV growls]
[pants]
[YURI] That's the hardest
I've ever pushed myself
to complete a program.
[YAKOV]
Hey.
Vitya designed that
program for you,
yet you failed to
take advantage of it.
You'd've been better
prepared if you practiced
for the possibility you might...
[YURI]
A lecture at the kiss and cry.
This is where Victor learned it.
[MOROOKA] Yuri Katsuki's score
for the free skate is 172.87,
bringing his total
score to 282.84.
He is currently in third place.
He may yet advance to
the Grand Prix Final,
but we won't know until the end.
Interesting, that's a
higher score than I expected.
[YURI sighs]
[YAKOV]
Hm? What's wrong?
[YURI]
Spasibo .
[YURI] Victor will be going
back to Russia before long.
[MOROOKA] The final skater
is Jean-Jacques Leroy, age 19.
[JEAN-JACQUES]
Finally. I was tired of waiting.
I'm sure the audience was, too.
["Partizan Hope" plays]
[MOROOKA] He will be skating
to "Partizan Hope."
[JEAN-JACQUES]
Yuri Katsuki.
Victor may have chosen you,
but you're no king.
I can tell that much
from your free skate.
I'm the only king here.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A quadruple Salchow.
[MOROOKA] He's planned four
quads for this program.
If he follows through
on all of them,
his free skate program will have
the highest technical difficulty
of all the skaters
competing here today.
Next up, we're looking for
a quad-triple combination.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
Quadruple toe loop,
triple toe loop.
At Skate Canada,
he held off Russia's star
Yuri Plisetsky to
claim first place.
He came in third at last
year's Grand Prix Final.
With Victor Nikiforov
absent this season,
it seems a new prince in
the figure skating world
has been born.
[JEAN-JACQUES]
That's where you're wrong.
I'm no prince.
I'm already a king!
[JEAN-JACQUES]
When I designed this program,
I thought to myself, "I'll be
the one who stops Victor
from claiming a
sixth consecutive
world-championship title."
Of course, I didn't
know he'd quit.
I bet he ran because he was
afraid of losing to me.
I almost pity him.
Poor little Victor.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A triple axel.
[JEAN-JACQUES] Mom and Dad,
my precious girlfriend,
the great people
of Canada, my fans,
and everyone in the world
who loves skating.
This is for you!
But it's not enough--
I have more love to give!
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A quadruple Lutz!
[MOROOKA]
Nice landing!
[JEAN-JACQUES]
It's not just that
I land all my jumps with ease.
I also make sure they blend
into the overall performance.
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A triple flip, single loop...
...and triple Salchow!
[MOROOKA] Amazing!
A superb jump combination!
[JEAN-JACQUES]
Hey, judges! This is JJ!
His last jump will be a quad.
Will he stick this one, too?
[JEAN-JACQUES]
Let's go!
[ANNOUNCER 8A]
A quadruple toe loop!
[MOROOKA] That's it!
He landed all his jumps!
That seals the deal.
He'll take first.
Yuri Plisetsky will take second,
and Michele Crispino
will place third.
[REPORTER 9C]
Fourth is Yuri Katsuki.
[REPORTER 9A] When you total
both competition scores,
Crispino and Katsuki are tied.
[YURI]
We're tied in points,
but I'll squeak into
the Grand Prix Final
since I took second
at the Cup of China.
[AUDIENCE cheering]
[sighs]
[YURI]
The Rostelecom Cup is over.
The final six who will advance
to the Grand Prix Final
are the three who had basically
been confirmed already.
JJ, who cemented his win with
another high score, Yurio,
who place second. And...
[sighs] I'm exhausted.
Then you should get some rest.
Don't worry about the
women's free skate tomorrow.
I'll be fine.
What, I can't even
come to cheer you on?
You would rush straight
to the kiss and cry.
[BOTH gasp]
Hey, Yuri!
Congrats on qualifying.
I knew you would
make it to the final.
Sara!
--[SARA gasps]
--[YURI] Thank you.
[gasps] What in the hell
do you think you're doing?
Eh?
[screams]
Was that Mickey screaming?
Are we having a
hugging competition now?
[YURI]
Hm...
[SEUNG GIL whimpers]
Y'see, JJ style is--
Mm...
No! Stay away from me!
[ALL but YURI sigh]
[YURI]
I'm this close to the end
of my competitive
figure skating career.
I really want the gold now.
The Grand Prix Final
will be my last chance.
Even if I don't
take first place,
I'll have Victor step down
as my coach after the final,
and then--
[YURI yelps]
[PLISETSKY]
There you are, pork cutlet bowl.
I've been looking for you.
[YURI]
Uh, hey, Yurio.
[PLISETSKY] What was with
all that hugging earlier?
Stop creeping me out!
And your free skate
was pathetic!
You get to make the excuse
that you didn't do your best
because Victor wasn't there.
But I was in top form
skating out there today
and earned a new personal best
only to lose to JJ again!
You have no right
to be more pissed off
than me, okay?
[YURI]
Uh--
That's for you.
It's almost your
birthday, right?
[YURI]
Huh?
[YURI gasps]
Pirozhki?
Eat.
[YURI]
What, right now?
Yes, now!
Hey, there's rice in here.
Pork and egg, too.
Wait, is this...?
Da!
My grandpa made them himself!
Aren't they great?
Yeah! They're vkusno !
[YURI] There's so much
I wanna tell you, Victor.
What do I say first?
[MAKKACHIN barks]
[YURI gasps]
[panting]
[VICTOR]
Yuri.
I've been thinking
about what I should do
going forward as your coach.
[YURI]
Yeah, so have I.
Victor, will you...
...be my coach...
...until I retire?
[VICTOR sighs]
[VICTOR kisses]
That sounded like
a marriage proposal.
[gasps]
[VICTOR] In that case,
I hope you never retire.
[YURI gasps, whimpers]
[YURI] Let's win gold together
at the Grand Prix Final.
[VICTOR]
Finally! Vacation!
Where's my swimsuit?
[YURI] This may be a resort,
but it's still winter.
[VICTOR] Oh, right.
It's almost Christmas.
What are you going
to give me, Yuri?
[YURI]
Something round and golden.
[VICTOR]
Wow!
[YURI]
Next time, Tenth Skate:.
[VICTOR]
"Gotta Supercharge It!
[YURI, VICTOR]
Pre-Grand Prix Final Special!"