[VICTOR] You be a good
doggy while I'm gone, okay?
And don't steal too many
steamed buns, little glutton.
[YURI]
Come on, Victor!
We'll miss the flight if
we don't get moving!
I'll give you a
call from Beijing.
Do your best, dear.
We'll be rooting for you!
I won't be far behind you!
[VICTOR] It's been a long
time since I've flown coach.
Do you have to ask
for the champagne?
[YURI] Why don't we
just get some sleep?
[VICTOR] How can I sleep
in a tiny seat like this?
[YURI]
Hey there!
Yuri Katsuki here,
one of the top competitors
in Japanese figure skating.
And finally--
"China's On!
The Grand Prix
Series Opening Event!
The Cup of China Short Program!"
[NAOHIKO] Welcome to the Figure
Skating Grand Prix Series,
where the top athletes
in the sport compete
to determine the
world's best figure skaters.
The race to the podium
has officially begun.
At Skate America, Leo de la
Iglesia won his first gold
in his home country, while
Guang-Hong Ji placed third.
Both will now compete
in the Cup of China.
At Skate Canada,
Jean-Jacques Leroy,
the bronze medalist in last
year's Grand Prix Final,
took home the gold.
Fifteen-year-old
Yuri Plisetsky took silver
with an impressive performance.
And now tomorrow, we move on to
the third event in the series,
the Cup of China.
At age 23,
Japan's late bloomer Yuri
Katsuki will be competing
for his second consecutive
finals qualification.
[YURI] I struggled to
find a theme for this...
[NAOHIKO] When asked for
the theme of his program,
he declared it to be "love."
[YURI] And I'll prove it
at the Grand Prix Final.
[NAOHIKO] Will the power
of love keep his hopes alive?
Well, the power of love
is really powerful--
I'm hungry and this is boring.
Can we go get hot pot now?
I'm kinda in the middle
of an interview, here.
Oh! That's Yakov!
Hey, hey!
We're going out for hot pot,
do you wanna come?
You're not ignoring me, are you?
[YAKOV]
Victor!
Go away.
Watching you play pretend coach
makes me sick to my stomach.
I don't want to talk to you,
not until you beg me to
salvage your skating career.
Is that clear enough?
[VICTOR] Hmm...
I guess Yakov's not interested.
Let's go!
Look, look!
Shanghai crab.
Drunken shrimp.
Duck blood!
[slurps]
Vkusno !
Why aren't you
eating the shrimp?
No raw food for me, not
right before a competition.
[VICTOR]
But it's so good!
Man, I really ran my stupid
mouth at that press conference.
What will people say
if I lose after all that?
[PHICHIT]
Hey? Yuri!
Huh?
Phichit!
I wondered when I would see you!
Hi!
[PHICHIT]
Hey. How are you?
It's so cool I ran into you!
I know! I'll invite Ciao Ciao!
You want to see him, don't you?
Well...
Ciao, ciao!
Um. Hi, Coach.
Want some shrimp?
[CELESTINO]
No, thanks.
Not right before a competition.
It's so yummy, though!
[LEO]
Guang-Hong!
I thought I might
run into you here.
What's up, Leo?
I called a million times,
but you didn't answer.
[GUANG-HONG]
My bad, sorry.
[LEO]
Anyway, Phichit gave me a call.
He wants me to meet up
with him at a hot pot place.
I dunno.
I'm not all that
crazy about hot pot.
Victor is going to be there.
Sold!
Thought so.
[GUANG-HONG] Do you think he'll
let me get a selfie with him?
Let's get down
there and find out.
Hmph! Such children.
[YURI]
Sorry about this.
I think Victor's had a
little too much to drink.
I told him not to open the
second bottle, but, you know.
[YURI]
Victor, snap out of it?
I'm not even sure I'm old
enough to be watching this.
Think it's okay to post it?
No, man. I wouldn't.
[RANDOM LADY A]
Did you see that photo
that Phichit posted last night?
[RANDOM LADY B]
I know!
What were those boys up to?
[YURI]
Seriously?
[PHICHIT]
Sorry!
I wasn't going to, but then
I couldn't help myself.
No fair, you big cheater!
We didn't post ours!
[YURI] This makes it look
like I was screwing around
before the competition.
If I mess up, I'll be disgraced!
Oh!!
Yuri. Why didn't you
invite me to the party?
It was just hot pot!
You're in better shape
than last year.
I guess your new
master must be giving you
very thorough training, eh?
Hi, Chris.
How are you doing this year?
I've lost all motivation.
How could you abandon me?
It always takes you a little
while to get warmed up.
[CHRISTOPHE'S COACH]
Victor!
He's right, you know.
Chris can't get serious
without you to skate against.
It's time to come
back to the fold!
Hi, Victor?
You're seriously a coach, then?
Yuri,
you're committing a grave sin,
keeping him to yourself.
The whole skating world
is hoping for his return.
Group 1 in the
Men's Single Short Program
is about to take to the ice.
You can win this, Phichit.
Stay focused out there.
If you skate like you have in
practice, this season could be
what defines your
entire skating career.
Now, go out there and
make me proud, huh?
[MOROOKA] First up is Phichit
Chulanont from Thailand, age 20.
He took fourth at Skate America,
the first Grand
Prix Series event,
That means he'll need
to place second or higher
in order to qualify
for the finals.
[CELESTINO]
This is a first.
No Thai skater has ever
performed this piece before.
It could be the
start of a new era
for skating in Southeast Asia.
["Shall We Skate?" plays]
[MOROOKA] The music for this
program is "Shall We Skate?"
from The King and the Skater.
The audience is already clapping
along to the familiar theme.
The King and the Skater was
the first movie
Chulanont ever saw,
and it has had a significant
impact on his life.
His first planned jump
is a triple axel.
Let's see how he does.
Nailed it!
[YURI]
Phichit's been wanting to skate
to this music for a long time.
Looks like I'm not the only one
who's going all-in this season.
[PHICHIT] A lot of people
have skated to this song,
but when I'm finished
here, that won't matter.
I'm going to make
this music mine!
[MOROOKA]
More jumps on the way
as his program enters
its second half.
The first is a combination.
[MALE ANNOUNCER]
A triple lutz followed by
a triple toe loop.
[MOROOKA] Now we have a jump
that he added to the second half
to boost his score.
[MALE ANNOUNCER]
A quad toe loop.
[MOROOKA]
Ah, he fell!
[MALE ANNOUNCER]
But He got enough rotations in.
[MOROOKA] Back on his feet
continuing the program.
[MALE ANNOUNCER]
Next is a combination spin.
[CELESTINO] The whole
audience is rooting for him.
[YURI]
You did it, Phichit.
You made the music your own.
[AUDIENCE cheers and claps]
Bravo!
[MOROOKA]
An impressive performance
by Phichit Chulanont
of Thailand!
Stay cool.
[MOROOKA] His short
program score is 86.75.
That's a personal best for him
by a considerable margin.
Next up we have a skater
who distinguished himself
at Skate America,
finishing third in the
first event of the series.
Guang-Hong Ji of China, age 17,
competing on his home turf.
He is skating to
"Le Parfum des Fleurs."
[GUANG-HONG]
Phichit was great.
I don't know how I'll--
no, I can do this.
["Le Parfum des Fleurs" plays]
[MOROOKA] His first planned
jump is a quadruple toe loop,
which he added to his
roster this year.
All right! He landed
his quadruple toe loop!
[YURI]
Watching Phichit perform
helped me realize some things.
The people who want
to see Victor skate
aren't going to be
satisfied with my skating.
And the people who have
cheered me on before
won't be satisfied
with the old me.
[CHRISTOPHE]
Hmm?
[YURI] If they're all
going to hate me as the man
who took Victor from
the world of skating, fine.
I'll prove that I deserve him.
Is he all right?
He seems a bit worked up.
Shh!
Yuri seems different today.
What's gotten into him?
[MIRA]
Yuri!
Your pal is up.
Come and watch with us.
[PLISETSKY]
I'm fine.
I can see from here.
[MOROOKA]
The last skater in Group One
is Yuri Katsuki from Japan.
[VICTOR]
The time to seduce me
picturing pork cutlet
bowls is over.
At this point you can do
it just by being yourself.
You've figured that out
by now, haven't you?
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER] The next
skater, representing Japan...
Watch me, Victor.
Don't take your eyes off me.
[VICTOR]
He's different today.
I don't know what,
but something lit a fire in him.
["On Love: Eros" plays]
[MOROOKA]
Right. Yuri Katsuki from Japan
is skating his first program
of the Grand Prix series.
The music is "On Love: Eros."
He has said that the theme
for his programs
this year is "love."
[MALE ANNOUNCER] Well, he's
certainly a different skater
than we've seen in
previous seasons.
Maybe living with his
coach, Victor Nikiforov,
has helped to bolster
his confidence,
something he's
always struggled with.
[MOROOKA]
He sure seems to be delivering
on the "eros" part
of the program.
[YURI]
They can laugh all they want.
They can doubt and
whisper behind their hands.
But I'm going to
show them the new me,
and when I'm done, they
won't be laughing anymore.
Oh! Perfect!
[MOROOKA]
Just look at that step sequence!
That was amazing!
Oh, wow.
[MOROOKA] With his eye
on a place in the final,
Katsuki's planned all his
jumps for the second half
of the program to up the
difficulty and boost the score.
[ANNOUNCER] A good strategy,
but not an easy one.
[MOROOKA]
Here we go.
His first planned jump
is a triple axel.
[MALE ANNOUNCER] Now, from a
spread eagle into a triple axel!
Nice height!
[MOROOKA]
Next up is his trickiest jump,
the quad Salchow.
He's landed it
less than 30 percent
of the time in competition.
[MALE ANNOUNCER]
A quad Sal!
[MOROOKA]
He nailed it!
[YURI]
Nobody else can satisfy Victor.
Only me.
Nobody else knows Victor's love.
I'm the only one.
Today, that's what
I'm skating to prove.
[MALE ANNOUNCER]
Quadruple toe loop followed by
a triple toe loop!
[MOROOKA]
Nicely done.
His jumps have been flawless.
[CHRISTOPHE]
He's different than last season.
What changed?
[MOROOKA] He's about
to complete a short program
with the highest technical
difficulty in history!
[MOROOKA]
We have just witnessed
the birth of a new Yuri Katsuki!
Today, love wins!
No one can deny that was
a perfect performance.
When the scores come in,
I'm sure we'll be looking at
a personal best for Katsuki.
The audience is
still on their feet,
and the applause in
the rink is deafening?
He used last season's
disappointment
as a springboard for an
outstand transformation.
That was perfect!
Yuri!
The kiss and cry is that way.
[MOROOKA]
His coach certainly looks happy
with his performance.
You did well.
How did it feel when
you were out there?
Good. But mostly I was hoping
everyone else felt
good watching me.
[MOROOKA] And we have
the short program score...
...106.84!
A new personal best after
an amazing performance.
He is currently in first place!
Of course everyone
felt good watching you.
How could they not?
You were incredible today.
I couldn't ask for
a better student.
Maybe you don't need Victor
to skate against, after all.
Focus, Leo, focus!
What's different?
He's never skated
like that before.
I wouldn't worry.
The free skate matters more.
Besides, Yuri isn't used
to being the one to beat.
Listen.
I know it was frustrating
to stand in Victor's shadow.
But now's the chance
to make your mark.
Go out there and do it.
Don't disappoint me.
Da.
Hey, Georgi's
starting his program.
Whatever.
[GEORGI] Now that Victor's
gone, it's my turn.
I'm the new top
skater in Russia.
["Carabosse" plays]
[MOROOKA] Georgi Popovich,
age 25, of Russia.
His theme this season
is "heartbreak."
The music is "Carabosse"
from The Sleeping Beauty .
[ANNOUNCER B]
A triple axel.
[laughs]
I swear, that make-up
cracks me up every time!
[GEORGI]
I am the evil witch Carabosse,
and I will cast
a curse upon her.
She will sleep,
and the only thing that will
awaken her is true love's kiss.
Except, there is no
such thing as true love!
[MIRA] Here. You know
about the ice dancer, right?
The one he used to post
all those kissy photos with?
Well, she broke up with him
and started hooking up
with some other guy.
You've heard
the story, haven't you?
Leave me out of this, hag.
[MALE ANNOUNCER]
A quadruple Salchow.
[MOROOKA] This is
an emotional performance.
No way. I think he's
actually crying.
Seriously?
[GEORGI]
You won't get away from me.
I'll hunt you to
the ends of the earth!
"Please forgive me, Georgi!
I was wrong!"
"Not a chance in hell,
you traitor!"
"No? Oh!"
[MALE ANNOUNCER] A triple
Lutz, triple loop combination.
Am I the only one who can
almost hear her
screams of terror?
Da . He's way too into
this performance.
[MOROOKA]
An intense step sequence.
He executed it well, though.
[GEORGI] She will get
the punishment she deserves.
Fool, daring to
cross an evil witch!
I will curse her.
She will sleep for all eternity.
[AUDIENCE cheering]
[YAKOV]
Well done.
Finally, a performance
worthy of you.
[MOROOKA] Georgi Popovich's
short program score is 98.17.
He is currently in second place.
[MIRA]
I forgot.
His ex must be there.
She's competing in
the Cup of China, too.
[PLISETSKY]
Really?
That's got to suck.
[MOROOKA] Leo de la Iglesia,
age 19, from the United States.
[PHICHIT]
This should be good.
He was polished even
at the first event.
["Still Alive" plays]
[MOROOKA] The music is
"Still Alive" and the program
was choreographed
by the skater himself.
[LEO] This is one
of my favorite songs.
I just have to skate
the way the music feels.
It's not complicated.
[ANNOUNCER]
A triple axel.
[LEO] If I do it right,
the audience will fall in love
with the song, too.
Wow. Leo's just
so cool, you know?
It looks like he's
switched things up
a little bit
since Skate America.
[MOROOKA]
After winning Skate America,
he's the closest among
those competing here
to qualifying for
the Grand Prix Final.
There are no quads
in his program,
but he's earned high marks for
the five performance components,
especially interpretation.
[MALE ANNOUNCER] A triple
flip, triple loop combination.
[MOROOKA]
If he keeps this up,
he'll be looking
at a high score.
[sighs]
[LEO] I don't know where
I would be without music.
It's what drives me
and gives me the courage
to keep fighting
when I'm ready to give up.
It's everything to me.
[MALE ANNOUNCER]
A triple Lutz.
[MOROOKA] He nailed that
last jump with a flourish.
He choreographed this perfectly.
It really maximizes
his strengths.
[MOROOKA]
A solid short program
from Leo de la Iglesia
of the United States.
You can tell the
crowd thinks so, too.
[MOROOKA]
This was a good follow-up
to his performance
at Skate America.
The short program score
for Leo de la Iglesia is 87.98.
That means he's currently...
That was great.
Aw. He barely beat
me by a full point.
I was so close!
[MOROOKA] All right,
we're down to our final skater.
Christophe Giacometti,
age 25, of Switzerland.
He took silver at last
year's Grand Prix Finals,
so all eyes are on him.
This guy practically
oozes sex appeal.
[moans]
[CHRISTOPHE]
I thought it was going to be
a boring season without
Victor to compete against.
But Yuri could turn out
to be a worthy opponent.
Too bad for him--eros
is my specialty.
["Intoxicated" playing]
[MOROOKA] The music for
his program is "Intoxicated."
[MOROOKA]
Into his first jump he's planned
a quadruple Lutz
right off the bat.
[MOROOKA]
Oops. Turned into a triple.
[CHRISTOPHE]
It's all right.
I want to take it slow,
so I can peak at
the Grand Prix Final.
[MALE ANNOUNCER]
A combination spin.
He's got beautiful
position and speed.
[VICTOR]
Chris said he was having
a hard time getting motivated.
He's a solid skater, though, and
never goes into a major slump.
He doesn't like to
peak at the first event,
so he starts slowly.
But, I will say, he doesn't seem
to be holding anything back
when it comes to sex appeal.
[CHRISTOPHE] Yuri, your innocent
sexuality is powerful.
But if there's one
person in the world
who can rival that, it's me.
[MALE ANNOUNCER]
A triple axel.
[CHRISTOPHE]
By the time I'm done today,
you'll realize how much
you still have left to learn.
[MALE ANNOUNCER]
A triple flip followed by
a triple toe loop.
[MOROOKA]
The audience is fired up,
cheering and clapping
as he begins his last spin!
[CHRISTOPHE]
I think I'm going to come.
[MOROOKA] Christophe
Giacometti has delivered
a riveting short program.
He had the audience
on the edge of their seats!
Awww... I can't breathe.
He's amazing.
A weapon of mass destruction.
Well, I guess Chris wins
in the eros department today.
Um, is it just me, or does
the ice look soaking wet?
[MOROOKA]
The short program score
for Christophe
Giacometti is 85.60.
That puts him in fifth place.
Huh? So does that mean I'm--
I can do it! I think
I've still got a chance.
I'm confident
in my free program.
Plus, I'm good at
coming from behind.
I'm going to do
my best to pass you
in the free program.
Look out!
This competition
will be my ticket
to the Grand Prix Final.
For the short program,
second is acceptable.
I won't lose to
a third-rate coach.
[MOROOKA] At the end
of the short program here
at the Cup of China,
Yuri Katsuki of Japan
is in first place.
[cheering]
That was lovely.
But our boy isn't used
to being in first place.
I hope he'll be okay.
I-I'll win with my coach Victor.
The power of love
is on our side!
Go, fight, win!
[VICTOR] My Yuri is in first
going into the free skate!
[YURI]
Victor!
[VICTOR] His short
program was flawless, and--
[YURI] Next time,
Seventh Skate: "China's On!
The Grand Prix Series
Opening Event!!
The Cup of China Free Skate!"
[VICTOR]
Pressure?
[YURI]
No!