[photo snap]
[YURI]
Yuri Katsuki here,
JSF certified figure
skater reporting
from the Grand Prix
Series' Cup of China.
I received a personal best
score in the short program,
which landed me in first place.
I'm within reach
of my first victory
in a Grand Prix Series event!
[TOSHIO]
Well done, Yuri!
We were all very impressed.
[YUKO]
That was seriously amazing!
The hottest performance ever!
[AXEL]
Yuri, that was awesome!
[LUTZ]
Good luck!
[YURI] "China's On! The Grand
Prix Series Opening Event!
The Cup of China Free Skate."
You haven't slept, have you?
No, no, no! I totally did!
A little, anyway.
Ahhh...
[VICTOR] Nap until the
event starts this evening.
It will be okay.
I slept until the last minute
before competitions too.
Victor! Did you set an alarm?
[MOROOKA] The men's free
program is about to start
at the third event of the
Series, the Cup of China.
[YURI grunts]
Can't... open.
Huh?!
You didn't take
a nap, did you, Yuri?
Huh? I did, I did, I did!
You're not allowed any
jumps during warm-up.
Huh?
That's an official order
from your coach.
[MOROOKA] We've reached
the second half of the event,
and Group 2 is taking the ice.
[VICTOR] If he flubs
a jump during the warm-up,
it will only shake his
confidence even more
going into the free skate.
He gets nervous too easily.
[MOROOKA] Let's hope skater
Katsuki is all right.
He doesn't look very
happy after his warm-up.
Oh, my poor Yuri.
That look on his face.
I've seen that look
a lot, and it's never good.
[VICTOR] You can
land it in competition
even if you didn't
during practice.
It happens all the time!
[VICTOR laughs]
[YURI]
I'm sorry.
[VICTOR] We'll just keep
warming up, nice and easy.
[GUANG-HONG'S COACH]
Okay, you can do this!
We prepared this program
especially for today.
It's perfect!
Go out there and
become China's hero!
[MOROOKA]
First up is Guang-hong Ji,
China's young ace, age 17.
He's in sixth place
after the short program.
He will be skating to
"The Inferno,"
from the movie Shanghai Blade .
His theme this year is
"bonds and violence."
["The Inferno" playing]
[GUANG-HONG]
I went with this music
because my coach
pushed it so hard,
but I don't see how skating as
an assassin can make me a hero.
[MOROOKA]
Looks like he over-rotated,
but that's another quad toe loop
after the one in
his short program.
[GUANG-HONG]
I've been living
in Shanghai's seamy underbelly,
but after this last job,
I'm starting a new life.
With my sword in hand,
nothing is going to stop me.
[ANNOUNCER B] Triple axel,
single loop, triple Salchow.
[GUANG-HONG]
Yes!
It's going even better
than it did in warm-up.
[MOROOKA]
He landed all the jumps
in the first half
of his program.
[MOROOKA] Will Guang-hong Ji
grab a ticket to the final
in his first Grand Prix Series?
He has more jumps
in the second half.
[ANNOUNCER B]
A triple flip, triple toe loop--
Ah, he fell!
Ahh...
[GUANG-HONG]
There goes my chance to catch up
and take first.
[ANNOUNCER B] Triple
toe loop, double toe loop.
[MOROOKA]
Looks like he's back on track.
[GUANG-HONG]
How does the story go from here?
The protagonist
infiltrates the enemy lair
and fights his way to the top,
where the enemy boss awaits.
[GUANG-HONG]
He's surprised to run
into an old friend.
It's easier to skate,
now that the
pressure to win is off.
[MOROOKA]
Here comes the step sequence!
Look at that speed--it's
like watching a car chase.
He's barreling
toward the finish!
[GUANG-HONG] With his
friend guarding his back,
the protagonist takes on
the enemy organization's boss.
[MOROOKA] His last jump is a
double axel. Nice and clean!
[AUDIENCE claps]
[GUANG-HONG] My Grand Prix
Series will end here,
but the Four Continents and the
Worlds are still waiting for me.
I'll raise the technical
difficulty of my programs
and claw my way to the podium!
This wasn't my last stand.
I'm not the kind of person who
just gives up without a fight.
[MOROOKA]
He finishes his free program
to loud applause here
in his home country.
[MOROOKA] Guang-hong Ji's
combined score is 248.69.
He is currently in first place.
I'm going to quit all social
media and focus on practicing.
All right, Chris.
You know what to do.
Go at your own pace,
and you'll be fine.
Right.
I love you, Chris!
[MOROOKA] Next, in fifth place
after the short program,
Christophe Giacometti, age 25,
representing Switzerland.
He will be skating to
"Rapsodie Espagnole."
His technical score
in the short program
was below Guang-hong Ji's,
but his presentation
score was much higher,
allowing him to place fifth,
above the skater from China.
He has prepared three
quads for the first half
of his free skate.
[""Rapsodie Espagnole" playing]
[MOROOKA] He's coming up
on his first jump now,
the high-difficulty
quadruple Lutz,
which is considered
his signature move.
[MOROOKA]
He did it!
[CHRISTOPHE'S COACH]
He's far from where he was
at the European Championships,
but he seems
even more focused
than in the short program.
That's unusual for him.
[MOROOKA]
Next up is a quad Sal.
[CHRISTOPHE'S COACH]
Moving into the triple axel,
single loop, triple
Salchow combination.
That's right, take
off in front of that ad.
And... there!
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[MOROOKA]
He nailed the jump combination!
[VICTOR] Let's go warm up
someplace else, da?
[VICTOR] Someplace with
fewer people or none at all.
[CHRISTOPHE]
I'm the only one who skates
exactly the way I want.
I thought Victor was like me,
living for life on the ice.
But I was wrong.
[ANNOUNCER B] Quadruple
Salchow, double toe loop.
[MOROOKA]
Well executed!
That was a perfect landing!
[CHRISTOPHE]
Why did you leave the ice?
Because you found someone
you want to look out for?
That's not like you.
I remember when we
met ten years ago.
You'd won the
European Championships,
and I'd just debuted
in the senior division.
Hey, Victor! Congratulations!
And what is your name?
Christophe Giacometti!
Hmm. Thanks, Chris. Here.
See you at the Worlds.
[CHRISTOPHE]
Yuri cannot surpass you.
I'm going to win this season.
And after I do, I'll bring
you back to the ice with me.
[ANNOUNCER B]
A triple axel.
[MOROOKA]
He landed his final jump!
[CHRISTOPHE]
We're going to stand together
in the rink again
someday, I know it.
Only this time, I'll be the
one standing in the middle.
I'm going to come again.
[CHRISTOPHE moans]
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[CHRISTOPHE pants]
Hot, so very hot.
[MOROOKA]
His combined score is 283.81.
He moves into first place,
leading Guang-hong Ji
by a wide margin.
[YURI]
Hold on, what was that?
What are the current standings?
You don't need to know.
Why don't we take
some nice, deep breaths?
[ANNOUNCER A] Representing
Thailand, Phichit Chulanont.
[MOROOKA] Thailand's
Phichit Chulanont, age 20.
He's skating to a
popular song from
The King and the Skater II ,
"Terra Incognita."
["Terra Incognita" playing]
[ANNOUNCER B]
A triple axel.
[PHICHIT]
Yeah!
I'm the future of
figure skating in Thailand!
[CELESTINO] The
audience has been in love
with Phichit since his
short program yesterday.
Unlike Yuri,
he has plenty of charm
and tremendous innate flair.
[MOROOKA]
The loud cheers we're hearing
from the audience tell us
they have high expectations
for skater Chulanont.
Coming up next is a triple Lutz.
[PHICHIT] Chris and
Yuri are always ahead of me,
with their two types of quads
and high scores on
performance components.
My best bet is to
skate my heart out
and put all my quads
in the second half
of the program for more points.
I'll show them.
I'm the one who will take
home the gold medal tonight!
[MOROOKA]
This expressive footwork is
one of his unique qualities
as a Thai skater.
As we enter the second half,
he has his first quad.
Landed it!
[PHICHIT] Until recently,
I doubt anyone thought
a Thai skater would land a
quad at a Grand Prix event,
but I never stopped
believing in myself,
and now I've proven them wrong!
[ANNOUNCER B] Quadruple
toe loop, double toe loop.
[MOROOKA]
He lands his second quad!
[PHICHIT]
I'm not copying anyone else.
This is something only I can do.
[MOROOKA] All that's left
now is his combination.
He's planned a triple flip,
single loop, double flip.
[MOROOKA]
He nailed it!
All of his jumps were flawless!
With this free skate program,
20-year-old Phichit
Chulanont is rewriting
Thai figure skating history
right before our eyes!
What an incredible performance!
[AUDIENCE claps]
[PHICHIT]
Okay.
Don't listen!
[MOROOKA]
Chulanont finished fourth
in his first event,
Skate America.
Today could possibly
be his first victory.
If he wins here,
it will put him on the cusp
of being the first Thai skater
to advance to
the Grand Prix Final.
His combined score is 285.76.
That's his top
score of the season,
and gives him the
lead over Giacometti.
I hope you'll all root for me
at the Grand Prix Final!
Hey, take it easy.
We don't know
if you made it yet.
Oh, yeah. Right.
I took home first place
at Skate America.
Yes, you did!
And I was in third
after the short program.
Yes, you were!
Out of everyone here,
I'm closest to qualifying
for the Grand Prix Final.
Go get 'em, Leo!
[MOROOKA]
Representing the United States,
Leo de la Iglesia, age 19.
[VICTOR] It's normal for
less experienced skaters
to be affected by their
competitors' standings.
But Yuri should be past
that sort of thing by now.
He has to snap out of this.
How can I motivate him?
I don't know what to say.
Victor, it's almost time.
Don't you think we
should be getting back?
I'm up soon.
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[VICTOR] A skater's heart
is as fragile as glass.
[VICTOR]
In that case, maybe...
Yuri.
Huh?
[VICTOR]
I should see what happens
if I shatter his into pieces.
It is at least partially
my fault if you mess up
your program today and
don't make it onto the podium.
I'll take responsibility
and resign as your coach.
[gasps]
Victor, why would you
say something like that,
like you're testing me?
[VICTOR]
It shattered!
Look, Yuri,
I wasn't being serious.
I'm sorry.
I fail a lot,
so I've gotten pretty
used to it over the years.
But it's different now
because I'm worried about
my mistakes reflecting on you.
Part of me has been wondering
if you secretly want to quit.
I was just saying that.
Of course I don't want--
I know!
I'm not very good
with people crying.
I don't know what to
say in this situation.
Should I just
kiss you or something?
[YURI]
No!
Just have more faith that
I'm going to win than I do!
You don't have to say anything!
Just stay close to me, Victor!
[MOROOKA] Leo de la Iglesia
is currently in sixth place
after his free skate.
Win or lose, your performances
always touch people.
And I've still got
the US Nationals.
[MOROOKA] Next up, Georgi
Popovich of Russia, age 27.
["A Tale of the
Sleeping Prince" plays]
[MOROOKA] He will be skating to
"A Tale of the Sleeping Prince."
[GEORGI]
Anya, where are you?
How could you leave me behind?
Don't you know
how much I love you?
[ANNOUNCER B]
A quadruple Salchow,
triple toe loop combination.
[MOROOKA] His theme for
this season is "heartbreak."
He hopes people will
notice the new range
in his artistic performance.
[GEORGI] My princess,
forgive me for the dire curse
I cast upon you.
You've been waiting for your
prince, and now I've come!
[MOROOKA]
A triple toe loop coming up.
We're done here.
What, already?
Huh?
[GEORGI]
Anya!
Don't leave me!
I'm the one who will save you!
No! You can't leave!
Not again!
I refuse to accept it!
[screams]
[MOROOKA]
Next is a quad Salchow.
He fell!
[YAKOV]
What's wrong, Georgi?
Of all my students,
you're the most willing
to let me guide you.
A strength and a weakness.
I designed this program
to realize all the things
Victor lacks as a skater,
but you have to perform
it with confidence!
[MOROOKA]
Next is a triple flip.
Great!
He carries himself
with such dignity!
[GEORGI]
"Please wake me up!"
I can hear your voice, Anya.
No matter what happens,
I will kiss you.
I will be the one to save you.
Then we will be
together forever,
as I have always known
we were meant to be.
Don't worry, Anya, I'm coming.
You'll never be alone again!
Well, Victor, how does it feel,
watching from the sidelines?
It's my turn in
the limelight now!
[PLISETSKY]
Whoops.
Forgot to watch the free skate.
I wonder if Yuri
is holding up alright.
His eyes look red, don't they?
Yeah, totally red!
Did something happen
between him and Victor?
[VICTOR] "You don't
have to say anything."
[YURI] Just have more faith
that I'm going to win than I do.
[VICTOR] I should have
asked Yakov what to do
in situations like this.
[MOROOKA]
With a combined score of 252.44,
Georgi Popovich
is in third place.
There is some
room for improvement.
I must try to take this
program to the next level
before the Russian nationals.
I'd say there is much
room for improvement.
[MOROOKA] The last skater
is Yuri Katsuki, from Japan.
He finished the short
program in first place.
[YAKOV] If your student
is trying to console you,
you still have a long way
to go as a coach, Vitya.
[MOROOKA] He will be
skating to "Yuri on Ice."
["Yuri on Ice" plays]
[YURI] I feel a lot
better after crying.
And the look on Victor's face
when I started to tear up--
that was priceless.
[VICTOR]
Why is he smiling?
[YURI]
I've cried after a competition,
but that's the first time
I've cried before one.
Anyway, the first jump.
a quadruple toe loop,
double toe loop combination.
[ANNOUNCER B]
Quadruple, double.
[shrieks]
[YURI]
Better than I expected.
[MOROOKA]
His first quad was a success.
In this free skate program,
Yuri Katsuki plans to do three
quads of two different types.
He's unusually relaxed today.
I wonder why.
Don't fall, don't fall,
don't fall! Don't fall!
[YURI] Victor's too
inexperienced as a coach.
It's not like it's news that I
get nervous before competitions.
He should have been
prepared for that.
Stupid Victor.
A quadruple Salchow.
[YURI]
Huh. I made it.
That was beautiful!
[MOROOKA] His theme
for this season is "love."
Love changed me.
I'm stronger now.
And I'll prove it
at the Grand Prix Final.
With a gold medal!
[MOROOKA] He made
a memorable declaration
at the press conference.
[ANNOUNCER B]
A triple loop.
[MOROOKA]
Beautiful.
[MOROOKA] One of his
favorites, the triple axel.
Oh, no. Looks like
he touched down.
[YURI] I could have
controlled the speed better.
Not bad, though, considering
I didn't do it during warm-up.
Next is a triple flip.
Hmm.
What if I made the last quad
a flip instead of a toe loop?
I wonder what Victor
would think about that.
[MOROOKA] Up next is
a triple axel, single loop,
triple Salchow combination.
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[MOROOKA]
He over-rotated on that one.
[YURI]
Could be worse,
given how little
sleep I've gotten.
[MOROOKA] Triple Lutz,
triple toe loop combination.
He's not showing any signs
of fatigue even this late
in the program as he moves
on to the step sequence.
[YURI]
I want to become stronger.
I will become stronger.
I can surpass Victor's
wildest imagination!
[MOROOKA]
For his final jump,
he's planned a
quadruple toe loop.
[MOROOKA]
No!
He changed it
to a quadruple flip!
He fell, but it looked like
there were enough rotations.
[MOROOKA] The quadruple
flip was a signature move
of Victor Nikiforov, his coach.
But not even Nikiforov ever
did a jump of that difficulty
at the end of a program,
when his fatigue
would be at its peak.
Here is one skater who
just keeps on surprising us.
Yuri Katsuki!
Huh? Huh?
Was that a quad flip?
[pants]
[YURI]
Is he crying? Is he mad?
I need to know!
[YURI]
Victor!
See that? I did great, right?
[VICTOR] I wanted
to surprise you more
than you've surprised me.
This was the only thing
I could think of.
Well, it worked.
[YURI]
At the Cup of China,
Phichit won his first gold.
And I kept Chris in
check by winning silver.
Yuri's already proven
he's the skater
to beat this year.
Now, with the quad
flip in his roster,
I'm sure he'll win
the Rostelecom Cup
and advance
to the Grand Prix final.
I look forward to returning
to Russia as his coach.
[MIRA]
Hear that, Yuri?
[PLISETSKY] In Moscow,
I'll make you into borscht.
Little piggy bastard.
[VICTOR] Say the name
of the airport we're landing
at ten times, Yuri.
[YURI] Sheremetyevo,
Sheremetyevo, Sheremetyevo...
[VICTOR] Next time, Eighth
Skate: "Yuri vs. Yuri.
The Horror!!
Rostelecom Cup,
Short Program."
[YURI] One step closer
to the Grand Prix Final!
[VICTOR]
From Russia with love.