[VICTOR]
Sometimes you need a vacation.
Time away from your
hectic everyday life
when you can relax
and be yourself.
On the rare occasions
when I take time
away from skating,
two "L-words" come into mind.
"Life" and "love."
I've spent the last 20 years
neglecting both of them.
[YURI]
"Gotta Supercharge It!
Pre-Grand Prix Final Special!"
[VICTOR sneezes]
[VICTOR]
It's not Siberia,
but Barcelona's still
cold in December.
[CHRISTOPHE] I figured that
a Russian would be the only one
besides me stupid enough
to get into the pool
this time of year.
[VICTOR]
Hm?
[CHRISTOPHE]
I guess I was right.
[VICTOR]
Chris!
Hi. How's Coach Victor?
Here I was hoping I would
get to go skinny dipping.
[VICTOR]
Don't let me stop you.
I'll even take
pictures if you want.
[camera shutter clicks]
[VICTOR]
Hi! My name is Victor Nikiforov.
I was kidding about
being on vacation.
I just arrived
in Barcelona, Spain,
for the Grand Prix
Figure Skating Final.
That is Christophe Giacometti
from Switzerland.
[CHRISTOPHE] I'm one of
the oldest skaters left
now that you're gone.
[sighs]
I'm a relic at age 25!
[VICTOR] These days,
Chris practically oozes sex
whether he's on
the ice of off of it.
But when I first met him
at the European Championships,
he was like a pure little boy
running through
the Swiss meadows.
I've shared the podium with him
at many Grand Prix Finals,
European Championships,
and World Championships
over the years.
We've been skating against
each other for so long,
I can't imagine
a season without him,
and he worried he'd
lose all motivation
without me to compete
against this year.
As it turns out,
he was wrong about that.
He made it to the
Grand Prix Final.
Yuri! Check yourself in now.
You check in for me.
I don't feel like
dealing with it.
--[FANGIRLS squeal]
--[PLISETSKY gasps]
--Yurochka!
--Can I get an autograph?
How about a photo?
You Vetm --
Yuri Plisetsky!
We do not use such
unattractive words.
[growls]
[VICTOR] From Russia,
we have Yuri Plisetsky.
Only 15, he qualified
for the Final
in his first year
at the senior level.
He's a feisty tomcat studying
under my former coach, Yakov.
During a visit to Japan,
he earned the nickname "Yurio."
His rabid fans are
known as "Yuri's Angels"
and show up in droves to support
him at every competition.
[PLISETSKY groaning]
[ISABELLA]
Wow, he's a popular one, huh?
Yuri's Angels are famous.
They're quite enthusiastic.
Oh?
[ISABELLA]
JJ Girls are enthusiastic
but we show more restraint.
Not to mention, we're cuter.
[growls]
Who the hell do
you think you are,
talking about my fans
like that? Vedma !
He's a scary little boy.
Protect me, JJ.
[JEAN-JACQUES] Don't pay
attention to him, darling.
He's just jealous because
my fiancée is so beautiful.
[VICTOR] And that one is
Jean-Jacques Leroy, from Canada.
He's a strong contender
for the gold,
but there's something about him
that keeps the other
competitors at arm's length.
Any guy who wears
sunglasses on his head
like that is a douche.
You can do better
than him, bitch.
--Hey now, easy.
--[ISABELLA] Scary!
We're all friends
here, aren't we?
Otabek! Going out?
Just getting some food.
[VICTOR] Otabek Altin
from Kazakhstan, age 18.
He was one of the first
to qualify for the GP Final.
He shared the podium with me
at World's last season,
and he had a certain
presence about him.
People don't know much about
his personal life, though.
[JEAN-JACQUES]
Going out to eat alone?
Still as odd
as ever, aren't you?
You can join us
for dinner if you want.
Thanks, I'll pass.
[VICTOR]
He doesn't seem interested
in socializing with
other skaters.
[OTABEK grunts]
Huh? Hey, why are you
staring at me, asshole?
--Uh...
--[phone chimes]
[PHICHIT] Yuri's not answering.
There's too much to do!
I can't stand around
here all night.
Going to Sagrada Familia!
All right, see you later.
[PHICHIT grunts]
Okay!
[VICTOR]
Phichit Chulanont from Thailand.
He won the Cup of China,
becoming the first skater
from Southeast Asia to qualify
for the Grand Prix Final.
He's a talented skater, but he's
also a gifted taker of selfies.
He was Yuri's rink
mate back in Detroit.
And Yuri says he's
the only foreign skater
that he considers a friend.
The last of the six skaters
to make it to the Final
qualified by a hair's breadth
after placing fourth
at the Rostelecom Cup.
That would be this
jet-lagged sleeping beauty.
Yuri Katsuki of Japan.
He's the reason I'm here.
I've been Yuri's
coach this season.
After the Rostelecom Cup,
Yuri spent the remaining
days until the Final
getting in as much
practice time as he could.
Hard to believe it's
already been eight months
since I came to Hasetsu.
I can't remember when I last
spent this much time
with Makkachin.
Every day, I get to
soak in a bath
bigger than any tub.
And I get to eat as many pork
cutlet bowls as I could want.
This is heaven on earth.
I've learned a lot over
the past eight months.
Yuri's life and love
have opened up
a brand new world for me,
one I never new existed.
Huh? Victor isn't here?
[YURI] Mm? I guess he's
at the pool with Chris.
Looks like Phichit's here.
[YURI]
And JJ.
And Yurio.
He looks happy.
[sighs, groans]
"Love's changed me.
I'm stronger now,
and I'll prove it
at the Grand Prix Final
with a gold medal!"
Yeah.
[YURI gasps]
[YURI] Where are you,
Victor? I need you.
[CHISTOPHE laughing]
Yuri, I'm freezing!
Will you draw me a hot bath?
I can't feel my toes.
[CHRISTOPHE]
Oh, and while you're at it,
how about some coffee?
[VICTOR]
You were still asleep?
[gasps]
[YURI yelps]
[YURI]
Jeez! You're like human icicles!
Get off me, both of you!
I'm not your heating pad!
[VICTOR] Yuri's planned an
aggressive jump composition,
including a quadruple flip,
which he's yet to land,
for his final free skate jump.
Even if he skates
a flawless program,
if he sticks with his old jumps,
JJ has a higher base score.
[JEAN-JACQUES]
Enough practice for today.
I'm off, everybody.
[growls]
Right. Let's go over it
one more time, Yuri.
What should we do
with the rest of the day?
You should probably
take it easy.
Get a good night's sleep before
the short program tomorrow.
Don't you go turning into
a model coach on me now.
This is my first time
in to Barcelona.
Take me sightseeing!
Your wish is my command.
[BOTH]
Yay!
Salud!
Perfecto!
[VICTOR]
Ah! I haven't shopped in ages.
This is fun!
I think I need a break.
I only wish we could've come
when the Euro was weaker.
You're having fun, da?
Oh. Mm-hm!
[VICTOR] Every competitor
has a different way
of winding down.
Yuri doesn't normally
suggest we go sightseeing.
Maybe that's an indicator
of just how nervous
he is this time.
[VICTOR]
All right, then.
Come on!
I'm going to buy you
a suit for your birthday.
And then we can burn
the suit and tie
you wore at that
press conference.
Huh?
Hold on a sec, you don't
have to do that!
And besides, I kind of
like that suit.
Victor!
[PLISETSKY panting]
[PLISETSKY FANGIRL 10D]
Yurochka, where are you?
[PLISETSKY FANGIRL 10A] I wanted
him to come to the fan meeting!
[gasps] I have his scent!
It leads that way!
Ah! A piece of his hair!
He's nearby.
[PLISETSKY]
Crap! How can I escape them?
[motorcycle revs]
Yuri, get on.
What? Why would you...?
Hey, it's Yurochka!
Look!
He's with Otabek Altin!
Huh? Huh?
What'll it be? Coming or not?
[PLISETSKY gasps]
[VICTOR] Athletes aren't
the only ones sensitive
to the unexpected
tailwinds of life.
Catch the right breeze,
and it can take you
to worlds unknown.
News that the hero of
Kazakhstan had kidnapped
the fairy of Russia spread
across the world like wildfire.
[VICTOR]
However, the brooding hero
wasn't acting on a simple whim.
Yurio didn't think that he and
Otabek had any prior connection.
What he didn't remember
was that five years before,
they had trained together
at Yakov's summer camp.
[PLISETSKY]
Really?
Oh, yeah.
[PLISETSKY]
I don't remember that.
It was actually my first year
in the junior division.
But I wasn't skating at the same
level as the Russian juniors.
So I was placed
in the novice class,
which is where I met you.
Yuri Plisetsky.
It was your eyes
that I noticed first.
The strong, piercing
eyes of a soldier.
Me, really? A soldier?
I had moved my home rink
from Moscow to St. Petersburg.
I was desperate to
make a name for myself.
I swore I would do whatever
I had to to make that happen.
After that camp,
I moved around to train,
from Russia to the US
and then to Canada.
I only managed to return to my
home rink in Almaty last year.
Now, more than ever,
I want to win the
championship for Kazakhstan.
[PLISETSKY]
Otabek.
I don't get why you would
talk to me. We're rivals.
Since I met you at that camp,
I've always thought
we were alike.
That's all there is to it.
Not so complicated,
really. So, friends?
[VICTOR]
Nobody had ever asked Yurio
if he wanted to be friends
with them before.
[VICTOR]
Now, back to the main story,
where I'm shopping with Yuri.
Here, things had taken
a turn for the worse.
[YURI]
No luck. It's not here, either.
Okay, just calm down
and try to remember.
It's a bag of nuts.
Brown paper with green print.
Where did we last see it?
[YURI sighs] Sorry. I don't
know where else to look.
This was my best guess.
I'll go back to the shop
and get another bag!
[VICTOR]
Don't worry about it, Yuri.
I'm sure the shop is
probably closed by now.
Let's go. You're tired, right?
[gasps]
Why are you just
assuming that I'm tired?
Fine, then, I'm tired.
[VICTOR] We ended up
walking through the nearby
Christmas market in silence,
looking around at
the stalls and people.
Your birthday's comin' up.
It's on Christmas Day, isn't it?
[VICTOR]
Mm.
I'll get you a gift
while we're here.
[VICTOR] Mm. In Russia, we don't
celebrate before the actual day.
And we don't really
celebrate Christmas,
not like other countries.
Oh, okay.
[VICTOR] Would you like
to try my hot wine?
[YURI]
No.
I don't like to drink
before a competition.
Oh, right. I forgot.
[VICTOR] It's always
like this when Yuri's
searching for an answer.
He gets quiet and
his eyes sparkle.
He's looking for
something right now
and won't rest
until he finds it.
I don't have to say anything,
just watch over him.
[YURI]
Huh?
[gasps]
Ah, this is perfect! Yeah!
This is gonna work, yeah.
This is it! Let's go in here.
Can I take a look at...
[YURI] I've always wanted
to have a lucky charm.
Yeah, that's what it is.
A lucky charm to help me
do well in the Final.
And a gift for Victor,
to thank him for all his help.
This card, please.
I'll pay in installments.
[CHOIR singing]
[VICTOR] Sometimes,
when backed into a corner,
an athlete can act
completely unexpected.
[church bell rings]
Thank you, Victor,
for everything you've done.
I-I wanted to get you something,
and this was the best
thing I could think of.
Anyway. I, uh--
I'll do my best
from tomorrow on.
So, t-tell me something?
[gasps]
[VICTOR]
Okay.
I'll tell you something
that you won't even
have to think about.
[gasps]
[VICTOR] Tomorrow, skate in
a way that's true to yourself.
Show me a program
that makes you proud.
[laughs]
[VICTOR] There's only one way
to a gold medal that I know.
And that's it.
[YURI]
I'm getting hungry.
[VICTOR]
Let's go grab something to eat.
Whatever you decide, Yuri,
I have absolute faith in you.
[screams]
[MINAKO]
What is it? What's wrong?
Yurio's enjoying the
company of another human!
--It's Otabek from Kazakhstan!
--[YURI] Oh.
Looks like Minako and
Mari are already here.
What are you two doing?
[MARI, MINAKO]
Yuri, we need a huge favor!
[MARI, MINAKO sobbing]
[MARI]
Thanks, little brother...
[YURI]
Way to play it cool, guys.
Why do we all
have to eat together?
[CHRISTOPHE laughs]
[YURI]
It is kinda weird, huh?
I mean, all of us hanging
out together like this
before the competition.
It's a lot different
from last year.
I was always on my own then,
at the banquet, too.
I didn't even have the
courage to talk to Victor.
Are you seriously telling
me you don't remember?
Huh?
At the banquet you got
wasted on champagne
and started dancing.
Everyone was watching.
Huh?
It was the most disgusting
thing I've ever seen.
I got dragged into a dance-off.
It was humiliating.
A dance-off? You're kidding.
Say you're kidding.
It's true. I danced with
a pole and got naked.
Well, mostly.
[screams]
[YURI]
Something happens when I drink.
I go off the rails,
just like my dad does,
and things can get crazy.
So I try not to have too much.
[VICTOR] The banquet is
a party held every season
after the competition is over.
It's a time for skaters
to relax and socialize
after a hard-fought match.
Last year,
Yuri suffered a crushing
defeat at the final.
It looked like his coach
had dragged him to the banquet.
At first, anyway.
Since he couldn't
bring himself to mingle,
he just kept drinking,
and drinking...
I still have videos
if you want to see.
[YURI muffled scream]
Me, too, but they're not
for the faint of heart.
Are you serious?
Yuri, that's so dirty!
[MINAKO, MARI] Yeah,
we're gonna have to see that.
Oh, no! Don't look,
I'm begging you!
Please! Leave me my dignity!
Nice moves, huh?
So, what's with the rings
you boys are wearing?
[PHICHIT, MINAKO, MARI]
Huh?
What rings?
Since when do you wear jewelry?
Um. I don't know what
you're talking about...?
And look, they match!
[PHICHIT gasps]
--Congratulations on
--[YURI] What?
--your marriage!
--No! Wait!
Everybody!
My good friend here just
got married! Woo-hoo!
[DINERS cheer]
No! Stop! Really!
It's a good luck charm--
and a thank-you--and, you know,
there are layers--yeah, layers!
[VICTOR]
Yes, you've got it wrong.
This is actually
an engagement ring.
We'll get married when
he wins the gold medal.
Right, Yuri?
Um, what did you just say?
Ah...
Gold...
...medal...
...huh?
Tch!
Right. Guys, well. I, uh--
You're kidding me, right?
I'll be the one winning gold
and getting married.
I hate to break it to you guys.
That's right.
JJ's obviously going to win.
Sorry we can't congratulate you.
Guess the wedding's off.
Well. We should go.
Early day tomorrow.
Huh? What's up?
You're all leaving?
Hey, come on!
It was just a joke!
[YURI snoring]
[PLISETSKY grunts]
[PLISETSKY grunting]
Victor Nikiforov
is as good as dead.
[PLISETSKY] I don't get
what makes you so happy
about babysitting
that stupid pig.
Did you want to
compete against me?
So arrogant.
You may not realize it, Victor,
but not all skaters
look up to you.
Just give it up
already, old man.
The pig will fail,
and you'll see that the ring
you got from him is garbage.
I'm going to win this.
I'll show you just
how incompetent he is.
[VICTOR]
Hm.
Let me go.
[DOG barks]
[VICTOR] If I hadn't left--
if I'd stayed in Russia
as a competitor,
so much would be different.
Yurio wouldn't be this
motivated to fight.
And neither would I.
This place reminds me
of Hasetsu. You know?
I was thinking the same thing.
[VICTOR]
Yuri, you may not realize it,
but many people have
learned something
about the "L words" from you.
I'm not the only one,
not by a long shot.
[MARI]
Wow!
It almost doesn't
feel real, you know?
Oh, it's real! Now,
get a picture, will ya?
[MICHELE]
Sara!
[gasps] What are you
doing here, Mickey?
I told you not to
follow me to the final.
Someone has to be
here to make sure
the hyenas keep
their paws off of you!
Who's up for a club later?
[phone rings]
Her again? Are you kidding me?
No luck on my end.
So are you getting
anything there?
Nothing.
The livestream's
not coming through.
[KENJIRO] Yeah! Welcome to
the viewing party, folks.
I'll be this evening's
head cheerleader.
[AUDIENCE cheers]
[BANQUET GUESTS murmuring]
[YURI slurring]
Victor.
My family runs
a hot spring resort.
When the season's over,
you should come visit.
Hey, I've got an idea.
If I win the dance-off,
come to Hasetsu and be my coach!
You'll do it, won't you, Victor?
Be my coach!
[VICTOR gasps]
[NOBUNARI] Hola! This is
figure skater Oda Nobunari.
[YURI]
Oda!
--[VICTOR] Nobu, over here!
--[NOBUNARI] Victor! Yuri!
[NOBUNARI]
Hey, what's with those rings?
[YURI]
Next time, Eleventh Skate:
"Gotta Super-Supercharge It!!
Grand Prix Final Short Program."
Oda, can I get a picture?
[NOBUNARI]
Okay!