Over the course of 1,000 years,
the spiritual energy of heaven and
earth gave birth to the Chaos Pearl.
Feeding off the sun and moon, its
power grew at an unstoppable rate.
The divine and demonic life
forces it absorbed fused together,
making it unstoppable and no less hungry.
So my master, the supreme lord of heaven,
sent my brother and I to put a stop to the chaos.
I know what you're thinking,
"Who's that dashing rogue on the pig?"
That would be me, Taiyi Zhenren.
And If I weren't so busy being a super
impressive butt-kicking, day-saving monk,
I've been told I could be a model.
Chaos Pearl.
You can't escape.
This is the end of the line.
Don't scare it, you big meanie.
Go on. There's a good pearl.
Come here. Here, boy!
Or girl?
Uh...
It's over!
It absorbs energy!
You bruised my moneymaker.
Someone needs a time out.
Hit me now. I dare ya!
I was just playin' around?
Master!
I have divided the Chaos Pearl into two parts,
The Spirit Pearl and the Demon Pill.
The Demon Pill is dangerous and nearly indestructible.
I'm casting a heaven-made curse,
a lightning bolt that will seek out
and destroy it in three years' time.
Until that day, you must stay vigilant and watch over it.
Li Jing has won my favor in battle.
And so, the Spirit Pearl will be
reincarnated into his third-born son.
I shall entrust this task to you, my disciple.
Huh?
Right now,
Eleven Golden Immortals sit beside me.
If the pearl is successfully reincarnated,
then you shall join me in the Court of Heaven.
You can count on me, master. Thank you so much!
Once the Spirit Pearl is born
call him...
Ne Zha.
I love a party. And parties love me. It's baby time.
Mm! Ha!
How 'bout a swiggy for the piggy?
Please.
Careful.
Dear, you should worship too.
Why didn't I think of that? I've
only been pregnant for three years!
From the Cave of Golden Light,
my name is Taiyi Zhen...
...ren.
Come on.
Wait for me!
Hurry up! Move it, slowpoke! Come on!
Yeah, slowpoke!
Come on!
A third son! Congratulations!
I'll be a matchmaker for the little man.
We wrote him a song. Wanna hear it?
Thank you for your concern and well-wishes, my friends.
But for now, please remain calm and quiet.
Just wait for the good news
and we'll alert you...
...as soon as he's here.
I can't take it!
He approaches.
Or I think.
Master Immortal, I have something for you...
I can't drink now. That'd be so unprofessional.
I'll just leave it here.
I have important things to do. Take it away.
Hey.
Ah, some people just don't listen.
Well, one sip can't hurt!
Don't want it going to waste!
That's nice.
I mean, I'm basically almost done. So...
Enjoy your enchanted three-day nap!
Ah!
I knew it! A spell was cast, so
only Taiyi would be able to move it.
Your highness.
The immortal's spell must be cast soon!
Has the time come?
What's wrong?
He passed out, I think he's drunk.
He's what?
I guess we'll have to do it the hard way.
Now hold on.
We can't just go beating up on the man.
He's an immortal. It's wrong!
Milord! She won't last much longer!
Out of the way!
Oh, you wouldn't believe the crazy dream I just had.
I beg you. Open the lotus!
Oh, yeah! I knew there was something I forgot!
OPEN
Go on! Is something wrong?
I can't remember the password.
That was some crazy strong stuff!
Okay, let's see, uh...
No big deal! I have four more tries.
What the heck?
And if you're wrong a fifth time?
It locks itself and we can try again in ten years.
Come, out!
Milord! The lady has fainted!
Oh, I got it!
Don't!
Is he mad?
I just remembered. If you forget the
password, you can just verify with a handprint.
Look over there, it's happy hour!
Huh?
I knew something felt off with you.
Look! A Slave Rune.
Huh?
He's got control of her!
You want it so badly?
Okay, I'll give one back.
Halt!
Oh, boy.
Milord! I'm not sure what happened but...
What?
Gotcha!
You're not going anywhere, buddy...
Watch out!
Ah, he's getting away.
With the power of sun and moon, of sea
and sand, Qiankun Hoop, obey my command!
Hold!
Take this, you little demon!
That's my son!
No.
That's the reincarnation of
the Demon Pill and he's bad news!
If he didn't have the Qiankun Hoop containing him, he'd
unleash a reign of terror like the world's never seen.
Go back where you belong!
No!
My love!
Please don't hurt him.
Don't hurt my child!
But...
Lord Li!
For generations we have battled against demons.
Do you think it wise to endanger our
people by letting one live among us?
As the leader of Chentang Pass,
I hope you can consider the
greater good and do what's right.
He's over there.
YOU HAVE A SON!
MY CONDOLENCES
You see that?
I'm here. Don't be scared.
Your Grace. Everyone...
My family is unfortunate. This I know.
But my son is also just a victim of this misfortune.
And I'm not of the mind to kill an innocent child.
I will take care of Ne Zha's education,
and I promise he won't set foot in the village.
If he brings you any harm,
then I will receive your punishment.
I'm willing to pay the ultimate price.
Even if we spare him.
He'll only have three years.
The Supreme Lord put a curse on the Pill
so three years from today,
a lightning bolt will strike him and take his life.
Oh.
His curse can't be broken.
I'll convince him to have it removed.
Don't worry. my darling. I will protect our child.
THE DRAGON PALACE
Finally...
This is the Spirit Pearl?
If I infuse it into an egg...
That means my son will be all-powerful.
Unstoppable.
And my child will become a god?
You'll never...
Never what?
Fail, sir!
Oh, very well.
This is my son, Ao Bing.
As agreed, I will entrust him to
you and he shall call you master.
On the condition you help free
him from this underwater purgatory.
And he joins Heaven's Court.
I can't...
You can't?
...can't be defeated.
I'm going to prove to you that you've
put your trust in the most worthy immortal.
Next time...
Could you do me a favor and just nod?
That right there is a void portal.
The Supreme Lord entered a realm beyond the three worlds,
so this door is the only way we can get to him.
Supreme Lord! It is I! Your disciple, Taiyi.
Taiyi, do you understand what you've done?
Yes, I know I messed up but it's not really
my fault because there was a demon and...
Ah! No excuses!
What took you so long to see me?
I get so bored by myself.
Ah! It's just you.
This is Chang ShengYun. He's in charge of the void portal.
But we just call him Clingy Cloud.
Oh, yeah? Well, we call you fatty!
Hello, new friend.
Not in front of company. Treat me with some respect!
And this is Li Jing, Commander of Chengtang Pass.
A pleasure! Really!
It's a party! I have company!
Oh, yes, sit, sit! Here, have some tea.
It's hard sitting here guarding the gate every day.
So what's new with the mortals?
I've been out of the loop for so long.
Please relay to the Supreme Lord.
We seek an audience with him.
Huh? I'm sorry but...
Unfortunately, our master and some of
his god pals went to the void portal.
Probably attending to godly matters.
But why do you want to see him? Do tell, do tell.
Someone's under a heaven-made
curse, and I want him to call it off.
Say it ain't so!
Then it's useless to speak to him.
That curse is unbreakable.
One day here is a year there.
Which means back on earth, a great
deal of time has already passed.
We need to head back as soon as possible.
Maybe there's something we can do for him.
These dumb walls crush my soul.
Even prisoners get parole.
No friends, no fun, it's just the worst.
Hopefully boredom will get me first.
Ne Zha. What're you doing up there?
Can't go outside and nobody will play with me.
So what else can I do but check out the sights?
Then...
Oh! Why don't you describe the scenery to mommy?
Grass, trees, and dumb flowers.
And a guy showing his butt.
Oh, you with your jokes.
Hey. Why don't I play with you?
Don't mess with me.
You don't have more demons to fight or something?
This is the first time I've seen you in forever.
You never have time to play.
I know. I know this is hard.
I would love to play more, baby,
however the fortress needs protecting.
I can't be everywhere at once.
Uh...
But today has been peaceful.
How does playing Jianzi sound to you?
Well since you're so bored I guess I can play with you.
Ready? Go!
Milady. I think you should put your armor on.
You must be joking.
He is my son and we're playing.
Nobody's died from Jianzi.
Catch...
...this!
Ready...
Uh, you okay, ma?
I'm fine! I'm fine!
Good shot!
On second thought...
Did I kick it too hard?
No. Kick as hard as you want!
You two, join in.
Maybe you should rest.
No. I'm alright.
Look at how much fun Ne Zha's having.
It's been a long time since he smiled like that.
That's wonderful for him, milady.
Report!
An eel spirit's destroying the eastern
fishing village. We need reinforcements.
Mom, catch!
Sweetie...
We're going to have to call it a day.
But next time...
We can play as long as you want.
I promise.
That's what you said last time.
It's fine. I'm used to it by now.
I'll cook your favorite when I come home!
Huh?
And you two.
Master Immortal Taiyi brought
you here to protect the barrier,
not so you can be flashy mascots.
Do not allow him to get out anymore.
Don't worry. I guarded the southern boundary.
And it's his fault Ne Zha got out last time.
You are so f-full of it! The north was secured.
He's clearly guilty. Just look at this guy!
Huh? You turn that finger around!
Once Taiyi Zhenren returns, you just wait!
Cause I'm sure he loves to hear you whine!
That's it! Fight me. Come on, you wanna go?
Bring it! I ain't scared!
Oh, yeah, chicken?
Chicken? You are!
Cut it...
I'll show you a chicken.
Who's the chicken? Chicken says "what?"
Huh?
Huh? What? Whatcha lookin' at?
What's the big idea...
Body Slam!
Dragon Whip!
Crabby Sea Monster!
Immortal Picking Grapes!
Come on, Dad!
One!
Two!
He's out again!
Three!
Four!
Five.
Six!
Seven!
Eight.
Nine!
Ten.
Ready or not...
Huh?
I've had enough.
Let's fight.
But boss. There's no way we can beat Ne Zha.
Not true!
Are we, or are we not The Demon hunters Gang?
Until we can figure out a way... no one goes home!
Huh?
I have a way, boss!
Huh? I told you to keep guard.
Go back.
I was thinking we could set some traps.
Like what?
Check this out!
Ne Zha's gonna come down that bridge,
but he won't know I cut the ropes...
And bam!
Ah!
When he hits the ground, it'll trigger the second
trap, an overhead basket filled with sharp pointy objects!
He'll reach for the nearest
shield, which will be an old pan.
But surprise! There's another trap within that trap!
He'll run and run and run... And
"What's that? A safe space to hide?"
But not so fast...
Lift-off!
Boom!
But better watch out... For that venomous snake!
And he'll start climbing the rope ladder near the tree.
Which should make all those hornets in
the hornet's nest I put there really mad.
If he doesn't want to get stung so bad his head swells
like a balloon, he'll have to jump into the mud pit.
And when he finally crawls out, he'll be so
scared and angry smoke will come out of his ears.
Nice! I never noticed how clever you were.
I'd have to be smart to hang out with someone like you.
You know, when you're right, you're right.
But he needs something way worse.
I got it, let's add some sea urchins to the pit!
That'll do the trick. It's
important for him to stay hydrated.
Um, guys? You don't think that's too mean?
Huh? He's mean.
He humiliates us, so we're just returning the favor.
Yeah. That's right!
Yeah. Exactly.
All right. Well you're the boss.
Who am I to disagree?
Hold on. I just had an important thought.
What is it?
If our plan starts with Ne Zha on
the bridge, how do we get him there?
That part's easy.
We can scare him onto it.
Like how?
Like...
You were right about one thing.
It's important to stay hydrated!
You guys! You guys!
He beat me up.
And he took all my clothes!
Well fellas, it's been real.
You guys are a lot of fun.
Yeah? Laugh all you want.
You demon!
What did you just call me?
I said...
You're a demon!
Ne Zha!
That'll be enough of that.
Boundary Beasts!
Sir!
Tighten the boundary.
He's now prohibited from setting foot outside this room.
Sir!
Enough.
We expected this might happen one day.
We tried but...
maybe this is just his fate.
Even after forbidding them from mentioning the word demon,
people will never see him as anything but.
And I've been so busy fighting
monsters to gain goodwill on his behalf.
I've neglected my boy.
He only has two years left.
Let's resign our positions.
Take him to play in the mountains, and just be with him.
Until the end.
Uh, Lady Yin? This is on me.
So I've decided to take him on as an apprentice.
I'll shape the Demon Pill into a
demon-fighting warrior of justice.
Is that our only option?
To put him through all that?
Shouldn't we just let him enjoy the time he's got?
I do not wish to rob him of a meaningful life.
And would you want this?
For him to be remembered as a demon?
Master Ne Zha!
Time for breakfast.
Huh?
The young Master's escaped again.
What? Oh, no!
What?
That's impossible.
Mm-hm.
I agree.
Don't stand there!
Report this to Master Li.
You can count on me!
I'm on it.
There's no guard alive...
who can keep me locked up.
Huh?
Wha--
Eh?
Woah.
Welcome to the world Inside the painting. Scenic isn't it?
What's the big id--
Ah-da-da. Hold onto your socks.
I'm about to show you a little somethin'.
With one stroke, you can change the painting
to reflect whatever your little heart desires!
You've got a brush. Big deal!
Why don't you just sit back
and watch this bad boy in action!
Do your thing, brush!
No, no, no.
Wow!
Young apprentice, we haven't even started!
Wow...
Mighty impressive, huh?
Just think, you can spend every day here
learning the Immortal magic of Kunlun with me.
Go ahead. Call me master, I know you're impressed.
Master?
What could I learn from you?
Huh? Why you-- You're in trouble now.
On my command, one, two, change!
Look out.
Magic'd!
Huh?
That's my handy-dandy disguising spell.
Wanna learn it?
Yeah!
This looks yummy.
So can you make me look all big and scary?
Now what would I go and do all that for?
Also, that's next-level stuff, even I can't pull that off.
Don't get fancy, learn the basics.
Come on little guy.
Your master's gonna teach you...
That's easy. Teach me something cooler.
The disguising spell is the most basic.
If you won't learn that then I won't even bother!
Fine. Watch me knock this out.
On my command! Change!
Change!
The disguising spell isn't even remotely basic.
Took me six whole months to master my first disguise.
Knock yourself out, take your time.
AN IMMORTAL PREPARES
Master? Master.
Lady Yin. What a nice surprise.
I'm checking on Ne Zha.
I'm just teaching him some stuff.
Where is my son?
Oh, right there...
Huh?
Hang on. What is that?
Ah! Hang on, kid.
I'll save you.
Ne Zha. What happened?
What is this?
Huh? I didn't do that! I promise you!
How'd this happen?
Oh, good, he has a pulse.
Oh! Oh, no! It's poisonous.
You should treat me with more respect.
How'd you master that spell so quickly?
I don't know, by being super awesome?
Okay, don't get jealous.
Even though it took him one day what took you six months.
Share your trick with your beloved master?
Teach me more Immortal Magic and I'll tell you.
Yep! You got it, kid!
Since your element is fire, I'll teach you fire control.
Tongue of flame. Sands of time.
Unleash heat from the holy shrine.
Make it so!
Not cool, that got in my eye.
I can't say this spell right with my tongue all swollen.
Aha! Good thing I have an anti-venom pill in my pants.
Oh, I can't reach it.
Can you get it for me, little guy, please?
No problem.
Whoa! You've got like treasure pants!
Huh? What's this weird moppy thingy?
It's for flies.
What? What about this shiny thing?
That's a fire-tipped spear.
A fire-tipped spear, huh?
Hey, don't touch that switch.
You mean this switch?
Huh? Ha?
Ne Zha! Are you causing trouble again?
Your grace! Are you all right?
I'm an immortal, I can't get hurt, but thanks.
Ne Zha. If you show me respect,
the things I'll teach you...
Like banishing demons and defeating monsters.
What? Banish demons? And defeat monsters?
Nice try! Like I'd ever learn anything from you.
How do I get out of here?
Well you'll have to use this little landscape brush,
if you wish to escape from the painting.
Oh, wait a minute.
You want to keep me locked up in here.
No don't be silly.
A place this lovely could never be a prison, dear.
It's a "training retreat.”
So I train and they'd still hate me anyway.
I'd be better off just taking a nap.
Ne Zha. I'm your mother.
I know you. I know you want the others to accept you.
But you feel more and more
alone every time they rejected you.
And you resent them for that.
Young master?
How did he get out again? Young master?
Huh?
Hi, you wanna play?
Mm-hm!
Ne Zha!
I thought he was locked away!
They let him out!
Everyone run!
Go back to where you came from!
Yeah!
Little demon brat!
No one likes you!
You're a Demon!
Yeah, no one wants you here!
Go away!
You've been through a lot, but it will be alright.
After your training you'll be able to banish demons
with us and earn their admiration.
Why would I do anything for them? Never!
They wanna see me as a demon?
I'll show them what a demon really looks like!
Dear, you...
I guess it's time we tell you the truth.
The secret we've kept for so long.
Why they're so afraid.
You are actually...
The Spirit, what?
Oh. right, right. right!
The reincarnation!
And it's that divine strength they find so intimidating.
Are you... lying?
Use your head.
Your father and I are humans.
How could we give birth to a demon?
Then, why don't you just tell them I'm the Spirit Pearl?
The Spirit Pearl was a secret weapon
the Supreme Lord sent down to the mortal realm.
It's not called an "everyone knows about it" weapon.
They couldn't handle the truth.
The truth...
In the meantime, try to win their hearts.
Treat them as if they're family. Keep them safe from harm,
and they'll surely return the favor,
embracing you as one of their own.
TWO YEARS LATER
Total piece of cake.
No, no, no. Way too impulsive.
Show him, go on.
Stop there.
Yummy human!
See here?
And here too.
Look at that. You harmed all those innocent
civilians, just to destroy a couple skeletons.
Yeah, they're not even real though.
What's the big deal.
If you can't do the right thing in training,
how can we trust you in the real world.
Your Grace, take away his Chaotic Silk and spear.
Until he learns self-control, he's
banned from such powerful weapons.
Fine, so take it back. See if I care!
I've learned all your Immortal
Magic, so I can go kick demon butt.
No way.
In fact, from now on your only
focus will be meditation not fighting.
What? You wanted me to learn how
to fight monsters. Well I did that!
Oh, why won't you let me out of here?
You're not leaving here 'til I say so.
Yeah, whatever.
I'd like to see you try and stop me.
Huh, how'd he get that?
Ne Zha!
Don't worry, I got this!
They're gonna love me!
I'm so sick of seafood. But it's good to change things up.
Yo, demon!
Let go of that dog!
Huh?
What, you want me to eat you instead?
Right here!
Why...
Huh?
Oh, no, you don't!
Get out here!
Show your face!
Stop!
Turn around and watch this!
Come out! Stop hiding!
Be like that. Guess I'll have to smoke you out!
How horrible!
Ne Zha's gone mad!
Hey! Where you think you're goin'?
Ready? It's coming!
Huh?
Ne Zha kidnapped Yaya!
Good luck catching me in the sea, puny human!
I've frozen the sea for half a kilometer.
You can't escape.
Demon, let the girl go.
Why should I listen to you?
Stay back, child. I'm here to save her.
I'm not a child!
You should surrender.
Wrong choice.
Back off and get in line, weirdo!
I saw this guy first!
What... what on earth are you doing?
Huh?
Wait your turn! I'll kick your butt next!
Where are you paren...
Town's only big enough for one cool guy.
Hey, demon! Let that girl go!
Huh?
There's something different about you.
Whatever!
Ow, let go! I said let go!
Huh? Woah, you have horns!
Huh.
Huh, bubbles?
What's goin' on?
Take a good look around you.
I should thank you both for giving
me time to unleash my special attack.
Go on, make a move. Not so tough now, huh?
I can finally have my dinner in peace.
Hey, spit her out!
When I get done with you, you'll wish that you...
You don't look so good.
Uh-oh, my spit gotcha!
Seems like you hit "rock bottom".
Maybe in your next life
you'll learn to mind your own business.
Huh?
Bring it on, kid!
Please have mercy!
I'll give you the antidote!
Antidote?
Don't worry. It's enough.
It tastes like garlic!
Huh? Look at that!
How'll they drink? Their mouths can't move!
Uh, you can also apply it to the skin.
Why didn't you say so?
Well, because you didn't ask.
That's right, spread it evenly.
You have to really massage it in.
The skin'll absorb it faster.
Plus, it makes the complexion all dewy!
Wait
Huh? I
Spare me.
I just wanted a snack.
I didn't eat a person.
You gave us the antidote. So I'm grateful.
But if you try to do evil in the future,
I won't spare you again.
Okay, okay.
Hey, you! Boy!
What? Still wanna fight?
That's not fair to you.
Huh? I'm no match for you?
Come on then. Show me what you got.
Thank you for saving me.
Huh?
And for saving this girl as well.
Today you were my ally.
I will find a way to repay the kindness you've shown.
Nah, it was nothin'.
I was simply following the will of Heaven.
Cause I was destined to be a great demon slayer!
You're not afraid of me?
You save Yaya from bad guy.
Hm. Huh?
Hey. What's wrong?
It's nothing. Just got eyes in my sand.
You mean sand in your eyes?
Let me see. I can get it out for you.
Aw man! This is so embarrassing!
Okay, fine!
My mom's the only other person who'll play this with me.
So I got emotional. Big deal!
Huh?
We're friends now.
If you want to play again,
come to the shore and blow this.
When I hear the conch shell, I'll come from wherever I am.
I forgot. I'm Ao Bing.
And you?
My name's Ne Zha!
Your friends?
What?
Huh?
There's Ne Zha. He kidnapped Yaya!
The demon!
My baby! Oh, Yaya!
Yaya! How are you feeling?
Ne Zha hit. Pow, pow, pow!
Demon go, boom, boom!
Why would you kidnap a little girl!?
That's not what happened!
If I hadn't chased that thing down,
she would've been demon-food already.
So where's the demon then? Did you see one?
How about you?
Do you seriously think we're that dumb?
Yeah?
Yeah!
You won't get away with this!
Okay, I see.
Go away, you demon brat!
You wanna say that again?
Stop it!
See? He's a monster!
We'll kill you!
Die, demon!
Your master has arrived.
Stop hurting people.
Ne Zha.
Commander Li!
Ne Zha burned down the village, kidnapped a child,
and attacked the villagers. We demand he be punished.
My crimes? I'm gonna show you a real crime!
Ne Zha, don't.
Lord Li, you must lock this demon-child up.
Never again to see the light of day.
Lock him up! And throw away the key!
Lord Li,
you must get your son under control!
We'd thank you!
Father... Master.
How did today's assignment go?
I made seven lesser revolutions and four greater ones.
I learned to ice over rivers and create frost and snow.
I've reached the seventh heaven of the Ice Jade.
Also... I made a friend.
I met him near the seashore.
Wha-- what do you mean a friend?
You can't reveal your identity.
He was a human, but he didn't care what I was.
Because I'm his friend.
And who was this person?
His name was... Ne Zha.
Huh?
Sma... small world, apprentice.
Sounds like you just met the Demon Pill.
Oh, no.
Ne Zha...
is your sworn rival.
We've waited three whole years.
On the day the reckoning occurs, the
Demon Pill will begin a mama... massacre...
and then you will rescue Chentang Pass
and claim your birthright as the Spirit Pearl.
Master, might he be granted redemption?
In the times of antiquity,
we dragons were all-powerful
beings, revered and worshipped.
On behalf of Heaven, we fought
monsters, subduing them in the ocean,
earning us the title of Dragon Kings.
Do you understand
what this place really is?
Our Palace, right?
Beneath the magma of this volcano are the
countless creatures we defeated those many years ago
at the request of the Supreme Lord.
"Dragon Palace"?
It's as much our prison as it is theirs.
If we were to leave this place, the monsters
would break free of their imprisonment and escape.
Do you see now, son? They tricked us
into doing their dirty work for them.
After all.
What were we to Heaven other than
just monsters to be locked away.
The title "King" they gave us?
It's laughable. I am nothing more
than another prisoner in this pit.
We sealed our fate the moment we took them at their word.
So, my boy, for the past millennium, the
Spirit Pearl has been our only hope for freedom.
In one year's time,
I'll be able to completely remove the horns on
your head and hide your identity as a Dada... dragon.
If you're victorious on the day of reckoning.
Then and only then will you win a place in Heaven,
and be able to break the dragons
free of this underwater purgatory.
Our fate rests entirely on your shoulders.
Don't let yourself be fooled
by the illusion of friendship.
I'm a scary demon.
Better run and hide.
Legend says I'll eat and eat,
'Til everyone has died
And they're right You should steer clear.
Best take their suggestion
Cause when I eat too much,
I get real bad indigestion.
Please eat. You haven't had anything in three days.
Dear. How long are you going to be like this?
Leave me alone.
I just wanna die in peace.
I try to help but no one cares so honestly why bother?
Isn't Jianzi your favorite, huh?
I could play with you right now.
I'm tired Of being a burden to
I've designed a really neat new training
course in your painting called Ride the Clouds.
Wanna give it a try?
I'll close my eyes And disappear.
Hey! Your third birthday's only ten days away.
The people of Chentang Pass want to celebrate with you.
Yeah?
They'd celebrate my funeral. Not my birthday.
The Sea Yaksha can move as water, without being noticed.
It's saliva can petrify people and leaves a residue.
That misunderstanding has been resolved.
They know you drove off the demon.
Oh! Yes, your father's right.
The celebration's the thank
you for defeating that monster.
It would be.
I see my teachings have paid off!
Now those morons get it.
About time.
Promise you'll be there?
All right, fine!
Why did you lie about his birthday?
Believing he's the Spirit Pearl
has given him joy.
If it means he can stay that way,
then yes, I'm going to lie.
Well, except...
the villagers were clear they want to lock him up.
Why would they attend his party?
Let me handle the details.
On the beach that day,
I saw the Yaksha slime on his hands.
He was telling the truth.
And I will see to it that they
all learn that, at the celebration.
But...
When you've been commander as long as I have,
many people owe you favors.
I'll get them all to attend. You can count on that.
Don't worry.
What do you want?
Ah, don't scare me like that.
My birthday party's in ten days. And
everyone in the Pass is gonna be there.
I uh, drew you a map so you wouldn't get lost.
Li Manor's renowned.
I guess. But you're coming, aren't ya?
Well...
Oh, come on!
I don't care if they don't come but you gotta be there!
Why's that?
Maybe 'cause you're my only friend.
You're my only friend, too.
Do you have any other wishes?
You saved my life. So I'll do
everything I can to make them come true.
Wishes? Eh, like I said!
My wish is you'd come to my party!
I'll go.
It's a deal! See you there!
Don't bail!
I won't.
INVITATION
Ao Bing,
It's time to go.
One more thing.
Father!
Wait, what're you--
My son...
Each of the dragons has given you
their hardest scale for protection.
Dragon scale armor is impenetrable.
It's all up to you now.
Huh? Why're you so sad? Show enthusiasm. Smile.
Why does it sound like a funeral?
When does Lord Li want us to come out?
He'll signal.
Oh.
Hmm. Yeah, I'm feelin' this cape.
Fancy!
A good shroud for a corpse maybe.
What?
I am your ma-mast...
Ew, gross, a demon!
Stop! I know your master!
So I'm a friend to you!
Oh. Your name is Shen something, right?
Shen Go-go-go--
What up, Shen Gonggong?
Brat. It's Shen Go-go-gong-bao!
And I'm here to reveal your true identity.
What do you mean "true"?
Oh, my poor child.
You have been kept in the dark for far too long.
And now let's bring out the birthday boy!
Play with me!
Huh?
Today is your birthday, young apprentice.
And let me tell you I'm gonna spoil you rotten!
Your fire-tipped spear and Chaotic
Silk. They're officially yours now.
And here's the big one!
This shall serve as your noble steed.
Go on, touch it.
This guy's my most prized possession. It can transform
into various mounts based on the traits of its owners.
With you, it will take the form of a flaming chariot!
So why does it turn into a pig with you then?
Huh?
You stinker. Where has the time gone?
Just three years ago, you were
a little meatball in my belly.
And now you've become a man with a personality and...
I so want to watch you grow up.
Why are you talking like that on his birthday?
Dad got you a protection charm to keep you safe.
SAFE AND SOUND
I know I've always been hard on
you, and you're angry about that.
But I was doing what I thought best.
Now son, you have a long life ahead.
Do not pay any attention to what the others say.
You are who you say you are.
That's all that matters.
I believed you.
But all you've done was lie to me.
Why are you saying that?
Come on. The Demon Pill?
I know about everything.
You said I was the Spirit Pearl.
Put me through training in the painting.
But really you were just
keeping me locked up until I died.
All to make these idiots happy!
To keep your dumb reputation, you locked me away!
Now you're being silly.
Don't be so dramatic.
I mean, look at all these people!
Eating, drinking, being merry.
Why am I not surprised?
Fine. If you wanna keep lying too.
With the power of sun and moon of sea and sand...
Where did you learn that spell?
Qiankun Hoop, obey my command!
Run away!
Finally...
It's just you and me demon!
Ne Zha! Stop this!
He's been possessed!
The Qiankun Hoop is our only hope!
Find the hoop!
Looking for this?
Don't waste your time.
Only the heavenly calamity can stop the Demon Pill.
Once he's killed Taiyi and his parents, go subdue Ne Zha.
Until the lightning destroys him.
And when the dust clears, the
villagers will see you as a hero.
After all that, the Supreme Lord will turn you into a god.
Your power will be limitless.
Ne Zha's parents and Taiyi.
They are all innocent.
It's not right. If the hoop was still on,
then Ne Zha wouldn't be evil.
What do you care if he's good or evil?
He's about to get struck by lightning!
If Taiyi and his parents survive how
will I sell our lie to the Supreme Lord?
Fortune didn't smile upon me when I was born.
I had to fight an uphill battle to get this far.
Of all the disciples, I trained
the hardest, never slacking.
Yet continually I was passed over for the others.
Do... Do you know why, my child?
No, master.
Because he knows I was born a lowly jaguar spirit.
So he could care less if I lived or died!
To everyone else, you and I are just monsters.
They could construct an entire
mountain with their prejudice.
And no matter how hard you
try, that mountain is immovable.
But you're being handed a rare
chance to change their minds.
To alter your fate.
Master. I owe Ne Zha my life.
Huh?
Maybe I can't save him
but let me save his parents and his master,
to repay my debt.
Huh?
Go.
Go on, then.
But if, if, if this goes south...
don't say I didn't warn you boy.
If they discover what you are...
Then I promise more than four
will meet their fate today...
Uh... Hey. I was talking!
Nope!
Huh?
Stop! That's your father.
Ah, he's so cool.
Hear that? We're missing the whole party.
Are you sure we can't go out?
Lord Li said there's a signal.
Oh. Oh, oh.
Use the Hoop!
Sun and moon, of sea and sand,
Qiankun Hoop, obey my command!
Hold!
Ne Zha! Ne Zha!
Dear? It's your mother.
Wait!
Please, wait.
Thank you for your assistance today.
Tell me, what is your name?
My name isn't worth knowing, Milord.
Nonsense, I must make a toast, to thank you.
I have an urgent task I must attend to.
I'm sorry. Let me get that.
No need.
A dragon!
Weren't they imprisoned in the Eastern Sea
by the Court of Heaven? How did he get out?
I knew I detected a familiar scent on you.
But that mark on your head confirms my suspicions.
That sigil!
So the dragons stole the Spirit Pearl.
I could chase you if I wanted!
What else would you expect from a bunch of
dragons? No wonder your kind were locked away.
Well, you can't cross the dragons.
So, the dragons were the thieves. Figures.
The Court of Heaven shouldn't have left them alive.
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
How unfortunate.
Brother?
For this to work only four people needed to die.
But wouldn't you know?
Now everyone sees what you are.
Now no one gets to su-sur... survive.
Please tell me you weren't involved.
I'm afraid I can't. It would be quite rude to lie.
As for the Pearl, I stole it.
And Ao Bing is my apprentice.
Uh, have you lost your mind?
I'm gonna tell the Supreme Lord!
Good thing I'm one step ahead then.
If you all die, there will be no
one left to tell him will there?
Apprentice,
there's only one thing to be done.
The survival of your people
depends on the next decision.
For the past millennium, the Spirit
Pearl has been our only hope for freedom.
It's all up to you now.
What is he doing?
He's trying to bury Chentang Pass!
A great deal of time has already passed.
We should head back as soon as possible.
Maybe there's something we can do for him.
You can't leave, you just got here!
I'll die of loneliness!
You're being clingy!
You can't break this curse
but there are ways around it.
Like a transplant spell. You thought about that?
Yeah, but what does he know? Are you
gonna trust me or an annoying cloud?
I've studied with the Master for centuries before you.
I know things you don't!
Let me show you what talent looks like.
Yeah, okay, airhead.
These guys are Fate-Swapping Runes.
Find a relative willing to sacrifice their life.
Have them put one rune on themselves,
and the other on the cursed individual.
And then instead of him, the relative will go boom!
Ow.
Woah, hey! What are you doing?
I've decided to swap my life for that of my son's.
This stays between you and me.
I beg of you, don't tell my wife.
Milord...
Ultimately, your sacrifice would just go to waste.
The Demon Pill will bring disaster and
the Supreme Lord will never let him go.
The Demon Pill?
I will use the remaining two years
I have left to make him a warrior.
The people shall see him as a hero.
No, I can't allow it! If you won't allow it,
when the lightning strikes during the Heavenly Calamity,
I will die with Ne Zha.
That's, that's so not fair!
Uh, who is Ne Zha?
He is my son.
Stop!
Ah!
That's strong armor!
Aim for the head!
Ao Bing?
Don't waste your breath.
Shen Gonggong? What are you doing here?
It's Shen Gong-Bao!
Shen Gongbao was the one who stole
the Spirit Pearl and put it in Ao Bing.
He wants to bury Chentang Pass and everyone in it!
Stop!
Your power is limited by that hoop.
You've no chance.
I'll kick your butt! Hoop or no hoop!
Don't do this.
Ha! Too slow!
Fine. Then I'll ice you out!
Stop, my apprentice!
I'm sorry, master!
Ne Zha!
That's crazy! What the heck are you wearing?
Transformation?
Come and get me! You scared?
Demon, there can only be one of us.
Ah!
You better watch yourself!
I was holding back this whole time.
If anyone deserves to be the 12th Golden Immortal,
it's me, not an incompetent fool like you!
Huh?
Hold on. Master entrusted you with the painting,
not me?
Well, maybe he knew you didn't deserve it!
Very mature of you.
But it's you who'll weep!
Take that!
Coward!
Huh?
Huh? Ha?
I've got you now!
Stop! I am your master!
Nice try. Next time, pay more attention to detail.
Apprentice, let me help you!
That'll teach you!
Great! Job well done!
You are too kind, Master.
Thank you, apprentice!
Huh?
Uh hey...
Totally nailed that! Huh?
No!
Who are you?
Why... I'm your master!
Woah it's me, Ne Zha.
Ooh! That's sneaky!
Come on let's get out of here.
That brush is our only way out.
Get him!
Ao Bing, grab it.
Hey, Ne Zha. Grab the brush for me.
Classy. But you can't keep that up forever.
I, on the other hand, will never run out of ammunition.
What was that you were saying?
Good one!
Uh, question, where'd you learn to draw?
You try drawing with your feet.
Huh?
Hm?
Ne Zha!
Son!
Ah!
Power of sun and moon, of sea and sand.
Listen up, Qiankun Hoop, and obey my command!
Can't lose myself. Gotta focus.
Stop struggling.
You were born the Demon Pill. Why not accept your destiny?
'Cause it is not the boss of me.
I'm the master of my destiny.
I'll be the one who decides.
And I will not be a demon!
Huh?
Why spare me?
I told you.
You're the only friend I have.
Well, my time's almost up.
You should leave.
But aren't you worried I'll...
I thought you were the Spirit Pearl!
I'm the Demon Pill and I'm braver than you?
Don't be such a baby!
I'm a monster.
When I was born, my fate was sealed.
You're not listening.
Your fate's what you want it to be.
No one else gets to decide what you are.
My father taught that to me.
If fate comes at you swingin'...
then you hit back.
Ne Zha!
Ne Zha! Release us!
I know you want to help but...
this is my fight.
Ne Zha! No!
Huh, you know looking back on it...
Three years isn't that long.
I had fun while it lasted!
My only regret?
I never kicked the Jianzi with you, Dad.
It's my birthday. No crying allowed.
Aw, man.
Dad. Mom.
Thank you.
Ne Zha! Ne Zha!
Ne Zha!
Ne Zha! Ne Zha! - Ne Zha! Ne Zha!
Huh?
Are you nuts?
Ao Bing, get out of there!
Dragon scale Armor!
He is ruining my entire plan!
I'm not done with you.
You've not seen the last of me!
You're sacrificing yourself for nothing.
You dumb or what?
'Course I am, I'm your friend after all.
Huh?
I never expected it could absorb this amount of power.
The Chaos Pearl has an appetite.
I can't take it.
I'm about to explode!
You shouldn't have to...
Let's give it back.
Right!
I can't hold on!
Ne Zha! No!
How dare they not invite me to join in...
I love a good party.
Stay strong, you two.
Open!
Where are you? Ne Zha!
How are we alive?
Ha! We made it!
Well, not exactly...
The Multi-colored Lotus couldn't save your bodies...
but it kept your souls intact.
Whereas I'm pretty sure I blew my chance
at becoming the 12th Golden Immortal.
It cost me centuries!
Now I guess I gotta start over again from scratch!
Thank goodness.
I thought I'd never see you again!
if you asked me
whether a person can alter their fate?
Well, I don't really know.
But hey, anything's possible.
Because a boy named Ne Zha,
forever changed his.
A JIAOZI FILM
Okay,
but, are you sure we can't go out?
We, we're still waiting on the signal!
So uh what exactly is the signal?
You know...
That's a good question.
DON'T LEAVE! THERE'S STILL POST-CREDITS SCENE!
Ao Bing...
Everything we have worked for was laid to waste.
And for that, I will make all
of Chentang Pass pay in blood.
Louder,
I don't think they can hear you!
Screaming into the void like a child won't change a thing.
We trusted you to secure our freedom, and you failed us!
Would you like to make a deal?
Dear brother?
DON'T YOU DARE LEAVE! THERE
ARE STILL POST-CREDIT SCENE TO SEE
Jiang Ziya...
You know your sin.
JIANG ZIYA
2020 THE WAR TO SEAL THE GODS AWAY