What a beautiful day it is!
And here she comes
skipping merrily into town
to do a little shopping!
How fun!
Okay so I'm gonna
need some toothpaste,
cleaning sponges
and some packing tape.
Easy.
Shut up!
Someone's coming!
It's the ghost!
Hurry!
Go!
Dumb kids!
How rude.
No kidding.
Other people's children
can be total jerks.
Have you heard about
that old run-down shrine
on top of the mountain?
You mean the one
they said is haunted?
Of course I have!
I'm getting chills
just thinking about it!
People have been saying
they've seen the ghost
of a young girl up there lately.
You mean like a new one?
Yes.
It's so sad.
So I've been telling
the kids to stay far away.
I mean, who knows what
happened to that poor girl!
You're wrong.
It's not like some kind
of creepy haunted movie set!
It's just in a weird place so
everyone freaks out about that.
But Tomoe keeps everything
clean and comfortable!
So not run-down at all!
Oh.
I see.
How enlightening.
Tomo-wha?
I'm sure it's fine, dear.
They thought it was
abandoned and haunted?
I don't think it
looks run-down at all.
Well no wonder they
haven't had any visitors!
Who wants to hang out at
a shrine full of ghosts?
Poor precious lambs.
What is the matter, Nanami?
Um, nothing.
What happened to the lovely day
of shopping you had planned?
I got distracted.
What are you doing up there?
Well.
The branches have started
to encroach on the gate.
I was pondering whether or
not I should cut them down.
I have to fix this.
I know!
An autumn festival
at the Mikage Shrine!
We'll invite everyone and when
they get here they'll know
for sure that it isn't some
creepy run-down ghost town!
Yay!
Fun!
Count me in!
Ridiculous.
A sacred ritual is not
an excuse for a party.
I will have nothing
to do with it.
This brings back fond memories!
We used to host many sacred
rituals back in the day.
It's a little messy.
Lord Mikage has requested that
we not touch anything inside!
Look!
It's a sacred palanquin!
Oh no!
What is that?
Lady Nanami!
You should not
allow things to fall!
Sorry!
Yay!
Let's see how it looks!
It's really not that bad!
We can make it work!
This will be easy.
It just needs some paint!
And maybe some soap.
I cannot believe
she pulled that out.
What is wrong with that girl?
Is she insane?
Look at her!
I was wondering the same
thing about you, Tomoe.
You know, if you're concerned,
you could go help her.
Or maybe not?
It's amazing to me how
you refuse to see Nanami
as anything more than a
helpless human girl because
when I look at her, I don't
see anything less than a god.
She is the only one who
sees herself as a human.
It is all she will accept.
Starting to look good!
I hardly recognize it!
You have been
working hard out here.
Hi, Tomoe!
Look!
It's my palanquin!
Sacred palanquins are for gods.
As a human, you cannot ride it.
Sacred rituals are too big
of a burden for you.
Save yourself the trouble
and let this go.
I'm not giving up!
We can set the
palanquin aside for now.
I wonder what else is in here.
Surely there's
something we can use.
It really is quite amazing.
You never know when to stop.
Having a lack of worshippers
is not a recent occurrence.
This shrine has
been in this exact state
long before you came.
Just because you
are the land god
does not mean you
are held responsible.
I know, but you always work
so hard to keep it clean.
I want others to appreciate it.
I've never seen a shrine
so perfectly spotless.
We never even find trash
in the offering boxes.
It's beautiful and I want
everyone to know about it.
I know if I were a better god
I could do something magical
to get them all here.
But I'm not so, I'm just
gonna have to be the human...
You are the only one
who sees it that way.
It is because of your presence
here that the air appears clear.
Uninhabited shrines tend
to attract negative energy
as well as a strong
miasma into the air.
Even I would be incapable
of exorcising it.
Think back to when
you first arrived.
The place has become
considerably more beautiful,
has it not?
I can see that.
But I still don't want
people around town
talking about it like a shack.
It's done!
Yes!
The Mikage Shrine,
we're holding a festival.
Please come, sir!
Here, take one!
No way!
People that go there
are turned into ghosts!
Not true.
It's beautiful.
Come see for yourself!
Gotta go!
Hope you can make it!
Looking forward to seeing you!
Hosted by a human girl?
Well isn't that
just loads of fun?
Okay everyone!
The festival
is only a week away.
We need to figure out what
kind of events we want to have.
I'm open to any suggestions
you'd like to make!
Oh!
I have one!
I'd like to prepare giant urns
of sake to serve to our guests.
Enough so that we never run out!
Where do you hope to
find that much sake?
My idea is being criticized
by the fox who hasn't even
bothered to make
a suggestion, yet?
Good point.
Why not capture a few yokai
and then provide educational
lectures on each one?
There's no way we'll
ever agree on this.
They're from a different world.
I have to think!
If you're thinking about
providing food for guests,
that will require a permit
from the Health Department.
A sacred kagura dance
is always sure to be a hit.
Let's see-- have
someone tell fortunes.
A kagura dance!
Tell fortunes!
Those ideas are
perfect Kurama, thank you!
What is happening
and why are you here?
Nanami sent me an invitation.
She was worried
about planning events
with a useless fox
and his friends.
Here you go.
I brought you a gift.
Yam love.
They're delicious.
A gift, too?
You're amazing!
We had kagura dances
performed here all the time
at past events.
I did not believe Nanami
would be interested,
so I did not bother
to make mention.
Beautiful!
Try it on over your clothes.
If you would like to, that is.
Can I?
It looks lovely.
You make it beautiful.
You really think so?
You've taken such
good care of this shrine.
If you approve of me
doing the dance then
I trust it completely.
Not so fast.
I will only approve perfection
and you have not yet rehearsed.
There is not much time
so prepare to work hard.
Whatever you say.
Right.
Left.
Front.
Your hand is too high.
You need to slow down.
Good.
This is when
you turn to the right.
Other right!
When will you remember?
You only have a week to learn
up to the ninth movement
and you are still having
trouble with the first!
We do not have time for this!
I'm trying but you're going
through it all so fast.
Can you slow down?
No, I cannot.
You are a slow learner
and must focus.
Now get up.
There is no time to rest.
We must continue.
Nine movements?
No one wants to
watch me for that long.
Maybe we should
cut that in half?
No, Lady Nanami!
It is the land god's duty
to exorcise and cleanse
the land of miasma.
This is the official revival of
sacred rituals at our shrine!
You must do the
complete routine!
It would help
if we had music.
Using all the same drum beats
makes it hard to memorize.
You think music would help?
Definitely!
It appears that Mizuki
is on top of your request.
He doesn't even know
how to play that thing!
You will have to wait!
One more time
straight from the top!
Yes, sir!
I don't consider myself
to be a clumsy person.
I'm normally pretty graceful.
But when he's around,
I can't keep my balance.
I can't focus.
Watch that arm.
Ow!
My arm!
It's dead!
Good morning.
We are going to learn all the
way to the fifth movement today.
Help!
Slave Driving Fox Alert!
That arm is still too high.
You are moving too fast!
That is a left turn,
not a right.
Other way!
Why are you making me
repeat myself?
Don't give up, Lady Nanami!
You can do it!
Stop shaking!
That is not part of the dance!
Take a three and
a half minute break.
Nanami.
Wha'd I do?
You told me I could
take a break, remember?
Give me your hand.
You are getting nervous
because you are only thinking
about achieving perfection.
It is this fear that is
causing you to lose focus.
I have something
that will help you.
It is a magic spell.
Many at the Mikage shrine
have embraced it for decades.
Here, swallow that.
What do you think?
Do you feel more relaxed?
It is used to help
swallow fear.
It also serves to
remind you of your divinity.
A god is never intimidated.
I feel better!
Thank you but
I know that trick.
We used to play it on each
other when we were kids.
Your break is over!
Yes, sir!
Nanami Momozono.
Seventeen years old.
A typical high school girl that
you might find in any hallway.
Appearance, 'C'.
Athleticism is a 'D.' Spiritual
and divine power, both 'C'.
Add it all up and she's
just an average human.
This isn't going
to be easy, is it?
Nope.
Ugh.
Boring.
What the hell was
Mikage thinking?
Surely there were
stronger options?
The man makes no sense to me.
I suppose she has managed
to pass some tests.
That hurdle with Lady Narukami
was quite impressive.
And she did pull through in her
own way that day at the beach
but I still feel like
something is missing.
She's just not serving up that
"land god realness" to me, yet.
I just don't buy it.
This is why I always tell Mikage
to keep his spec lenses cleaned.
They're clean, I assure you.
Don't do that!
How long have you
been sitting there?
Long enough.
The girl has won my faith
in her and that's that.
Then I believe it's
time for a final test.
Good luck, my dear.
Turn to the right!
We go right, left, then around.
No!
That's wrong!
My arm's falling off!
I can't even dance the first
movement all the way through.
What am I doing?
If Tomoe believes in me, then I
must be doing something right.
Ow, that hurts!
I'm such a wuss.
Now we know why you scored
a 'D' in athleticism.
Who are you?
Your manners are
absolutely nauseating.
The one with the lesser social
standing should always be
the first to introduce herself.
Miss Nanami Momozono.
I'm sorry, but how
do you know my name?
You are about to hold a sacred
festival at Mikage's shrine.
I'm here to make
sure you are worthy.
There will be a test to see
if you are truly capable
of carrying out the
duties of a land god.
No, don't!
Who the heck was he or she?
Bye.
Be good!
Exorcising this level of
miasma should be no problem
for a true land god.
Let's see what you've got,
Little Miss Nanami.
Miasma but why?
Everything was fine yesterday.
Tomoe just finished
cleaning that pavilion.
I don't get it.
It is because of your presence
here that the air appears clear.
Uninhabited shrines tend
to attract negative energy
as well as a strong
miasma into the air.
Even I would be
incapable of exorcising it.
Think back to when
you first arrived.
The place has become
considerably more beautiful,
has it not?
It's okay, I'm fine.
I just need to relax.
Purify!
Beauty!
Cleansing!
Exorcise!
And a Purge!
Clean.
Clean!
Go away.
Please leave!
I said disappear!
But why?
God Beam!
God--
Morning, Nanami!
Good news!
I've been practicing and I
think I can make a sound now!
What is going on here?
The miasma around the shrine
has grown much thicker!
There you are!
I don't understand.
It was clear until yesterday.
Do you think Nanami's
powers are up to the task?
Where is she?
Nanami!
Tomoe.
I tried my best to exorcise it.
Nanami!
Is she okay?
Yes.
Can you handle this?
There's so much of it!
But I'll give it a try.
The shrine!
Stay in bed.
We will find a way
to take care of this.
But exorcising miasma
from the land is the land
god's responsibility.
I have to do it!
We do not need you.
Do not move from that spot.
Do you have any more than that?
Of course I do!
It's my sacred sake so
I have plenty to use.
However, this is only
a temporary fix.
As soon as it dries,
it loses effect.
Could you be any more useless?
You haven't even made
an attempt to help
so I don't want to hear it!
I've failed.
I haven't even begun to live up
to Tomoe's expectations.
I let him down.
He's always the one
who has to save me.
I'm supposed to be the god.
But the truth is--
We do not need you.
I haven't tried.
Not hard enough.
I haven't accomplished anything.
I'm not important.
I'm not needed.
I'm a failure.
Nanami?
Where is she?
Nanami!
Where are you?
I'm going into town, Tomoe.
Where could you be?
Nanami!
The miasma is out of control
at the Mikage shrine.
Nanami feels helpless
so she runs away!
Tomoe looks for her
but she is well hidden!
Is this how it ends?
Will they be apart forever?
Next time, "Kamisama Kiss!"
It's the final episode!
Aw, it's been fun!