A Java sparrow wearing
a ceremonial hat flies
toward the Mikage Shrine.
But this is no ordinary
Java sparrow!
It is wearing a
ceremonial hat, after all.
What is the reason
for its surprise visit?
Does it bring glad tidings
or a bad omen?
Excuse me, Goddess.
Hmm?
I come to you with a message,
a message very dear
to Princess Himemiko.
Later this evening, Himemiko
of the Swamp will visit
Mikage Shrine to pay
her respects to you,
the new Lady Goddess
of the Land.
Princess Himemiko?
Originally a catfish spirit,
she is the goddess
of Isara Swamp.
A catfish spirit?
Isara Swamp is a region
under Mikage's protection.
Thus it is only natural that
Himemiko would want to meet
a new land god like yourself.
What does a catfish
yokai look like?
I'm a little nervous
about such a formal visit.
What is the meaning
of this nonsense?
What?
I kinda want to look my best
when they get here.
You need not make an appearance.
Your incompetence is the last
thing we need for this occasion.
Do not set foot outside this
room until they have left.
So good of you to visit,
Himemiko of the Swamp.
I am the familiar, Tomoe.
Unfortunately there has
been a change of plans.
The land god is not feeling well
and will be unable to receive
you this evening.
Excuse me?
When Mikage was god of this
shrine, he established
a friendly relationship
with Himemiko.
I refuse to let that crumble
under Nanami's watch.
Please accept this dinner
invitation as our apology.
Lady Nanami, Master Tomoe
said those things--
--because he cares
about your well-being.
Of course he did.
If I went out there, I'd
be absolutely clueless.
Having said that, can Master
Tomoe handle the guests
by himself?
Lady Himemiko is the leader of
all the yokai in the swamp.
This situation could
prove very challenging,
even for Master Tomoe.
My lady did not make this
trip just to sip tea.
For the new land god to
disrespect Lady Himemiko
like this is unacceptable.
I apologize, sir.
When she is no longer under
the weather we will pay
the swamp a visit.
Rumor has it the new land god
is simply a mere human girl.
With that in mind, she must
be trembling in the back,
deathly afraid of Lady Himemiko.
Such is not the case,
as she comes to us by
Mikage's recommendation.
She may be human, but in
no way is she inferior.
Well, I heard quite
a different story.
A yokai attacked
her the other day.
Terrified, she actually fled!
Are you serious, thinking
that such a frightened,
pathetic child has
business being a god?
I should've known, they're
already arguing about me!
How far this shrine has fallen.
Not so.
Lady Nanami may appear fragile,
but she has a strength
of character not easily found.
I have no doubt she will one
day make the flowers bloom.
Oh my!
Of all things, who knew
the stubborn fox, Tomoe,
could be tamed by a little girl?
You surprise me, too.
Who knew that a
fish out of water
could have such
biting charisma?
Such comments do not put your
princess in the best light,
given that she has
come to pay respects
to that pathetic little girl.
You hold your tongue, vermin!
That girl of yours better come
running out here sometime
very soon or your
head is going to fly.
Got me?
I think now is a good time to
call an end to this occasion.
You have quite the
temper my friend.
Work on that.
Excuse my tardiness!
I am Nanami Momozono,
the land god!
Sorry to keep the
two of you waiting.
My dear sir, please
put away your sword.
Why did I even run out here?
Tomoe told me not to.
Seeing him threatened
with that blade,
I simply couldn't stand by.
But now it's--It's
Tomoe I'm afraid of!
You fool!
Why did you have
to come out here?
You do realize what
this means for me.
While you are present,
it is my sworn duty
to insure your safety.
His words may be harsh,
but his tight grip expresses
an incredible kindness.
So this is the land god!
A homely little girl,
just as the rumors said.
Now then, you need not worry
about your insults as the flesh
of you and that idiot
fox shall atone nicely!
Forgive me, but that exchange
is rather unacceptable.
I intend to protect
my lady to the death.
So do not hold it against me
if you die tonight!
Mammal scum, you dare
to steal my lines?
Oh.
What should I do?
Let me think,
how shall I kill this one?
Boys, enough playtime
for one evening!
How about the two of you
put down your weapons and-
Get out of the way.
Die!
I have decided.
You will make a
splendid grilled fish.
What?
Cook five minutes
over medium heat.
It is quite the delectable
breakfast entrée.
If I may ask...
So how does it feel?
Being grilled alive?
I'm curious.
Tomoe.
You let him go right now!
You're so ridiculous!
Threatening our guest.
Go on, apologize this instant!
Good, that's much better.
You're being awfully obedient.
Ah, so this is
"Sacred Word Binding,"
the spell that thou
cast upon thy familiar.
Thy claim to be the land god
appears to be true, Lady Nanami.
She spoke.
"Sacred Word Binding?"
Allow us to explain.
Orders spoken by a god
become sacred words
that bind familiars.
The more firmly you issue the
order, the more the familiar is
compelled to obey, and they will
be bound by those sacred words.
Those blasted fools!
They were supposed to keep
that a secret from her!
This might be a
sweet job after all.
Look what you have done,
she is happy!
Master Familiar.
I apologize for
Aotake's rude behavior.
I have no desire to quarrel.
I came to request the land god's
assistance in making a match.
Um- Making a match?
Like a romantic one?
Please share
with us your story.
We only met but one time;
ten years ago at Isara Swamp.
I fell in love with a human boy,
Kotaro Urashima of
Sarayashiki Town.
I'm scared, so scared!
He was only eight years old
but he looked most adorable
as he cried.
Ten human years have now passed.
He must have grown into
a fine young man by now.
I wish to rekindle my bond
with the boy I met once more.
But I cannot see Kotaro as
I please, for I am a yokai.
I am lost.
Will Lady Nanami please
help to grant my wish?
No way.
Love between a yokai
and human is forbidden.
Surely you are aware of this.
I know.
I understand.
I will do everything
in my power to help you!
You what?
Thank you, miss.
She harbors an impossible love.
That's why she came to a god.
There is no difference
between human and yokai
when it comes to a girl's heart.
Morning!
A good morning to you,
Lady Nanami!
So, where is Tomoe?
He appears to be
in a foul mood.
He has shut himself
in his room.
He has been down there ever
since Princess Himemiko left.
Master Tomoe?
Lady Nanami is here to see you.
It cannot be helped.
We shall start preparing
the morning meal.
We will let you know
when it is ready.
Are you still upset?
About yesterday?
I realize I may have gone
against your wishes when
I came out to meet Himemiko
and made her that promise.
But I--I was really happy
that you came to my defense.
I promise that I'll work hard,
until you think I'm worthy.
Do you enjoy conversing
with yourself?
Sneak attack!
What did you hear--
Save your breath
in regards to Himemiko.
I will go later and
express our regrets.
Just keep yourself
out of the matter.
Humans and yokai are simply
not meant to be together.
Besides, what could
you have done?
I'll never know until
I give it a try!
Do not waste your energy.
Well, they should at least
be able to fall in love!
Love is a human-centric
emotion that brings trouble.
Forget you, I'll go alone!
Where are you going?
I'm going into town
to find Kotaro.
I'm going into town, Tomoe.
Make sure you hold down the
fort until I get back, ok?
Wait!
I will come too.
Oh?
Uh, alright then.
But you could at least change
out of those filthy clothes!
To fear that Nanami may
leave and never return,
just as Mikage did.
Why is such a thought
even crossing my mind?
We're here!
Bustling city life; busy streets
filled with gossiping crowds.
The exhaust fumes!
Isn't civilization cool?
I suppose.
Look mommy!
He's got ears and
a tail like a foxie!
Hush!
How did I completely
forget that Tomoe's a fox?
Of course people are
going to notice that he's got
fluffy ears and a tail!
Is this any less conspicuous?
I've gotta be careful.
So!
Where do you think Kotaro wou--
Crap!
That's my school uniform!
It's a weekday!
What else am I gonna forget?
Is something wrong?
Let's go get some ice cream!
Now now.
I must have it!
I used to come here
all the time on payday.
Ice cream's the perfect
after-school snack!
Well, how do you like it?
Do not forget the
purpose of this trip.
We are only here
to find Kotaro.
I know that.
No way!
Hey Nanami.
What're you doin' here?
Isobe!
Could this day get any worse?
Aren't you supposed to be
sitting in class right now?
And who's this
sketchy dude you're with?
It's not what you think,
so why don't you go away?
Also, what was up
with you the other day?
The whole thing was pretty
fishy, but seriously.
Your broke daddy running away
from home; all your stuff
getting tossed to the curb;
you sleeping in the park?
With so many rumors
floating around,
it's hard to tell
fact from fiction.
You know those are all lies;
my dad moved away
because of his job!
Bull, that guy's
always unemployed!
I bet he took off
in the middle of the night!
I've got you
completely figured out!
We have to leave.
What?
Come on, I'm just mess--
Do not lay a finger on her.
Have I made myself clear?
Stop that right now!
Don't pay any attention to him.
Are you all right, sir?
What were you thinking,
threatening Isobe?
You can't go around picking
on every human you see!
Do not yell straight
into my ear!
For someone barking out
orders left and right,
you have no idea
what you are doing!
I'm here to do my job!
Uh, ma'am, we don't really
allow fighting inside.
I did not come all the way here
to listen to you reminisce
about eating ice cream!
I came to look for
Kotaro Urashima!
That so?
Then quit complaining
and help me find the guy!
Excuse me.
You two are looking for me?
One of you said Kotaro earlier,
and that's my name.
Only her third day as a god
and Nanami has already
tracked down a most
important target.
Truly this must be--
--the gracious god of destiny
guiding me on my journey!
Thanks for waiting!
I know meeting here was
a really random request.
It's ok.
I'm also sorry about that
whole scene at the restaurant.
Don't worry, it's no big deal!
Just forget about it.
Didn't you say there's something
you wanted to talk to me about?
Ten years ago, you met someone
very special at Isara Swamp.
Do you have any memories of her?
Ten years ago.
Sorry, but I don't
remember anything.
And you went through so much
trouble to track me down.
Hey, don't worry about it, I
was just curious, no biggie!
Forget it!
Hey, isn't that a puzzle cube?
Yes.
I've never been good
at anything in life,
except for solving
this thing over and over.
Fidgeting around with
it helps me calm down.
Ah, so kind of like chewing
gum, or a good luck charm!
This conversation
is going nowhere.
There's someone
I'd like you to meet,
a friend of mine named
Numano Himemiko.
She's had a little crush
on you for like ever.
Do you think you could meet up
with her, maybe just one time?
Excellent job, Lady Nanami!
You were able to secure a
promise from master Kotaro!
Wait a minute.
What are the two
of you doing here?
Master Tomoe made us promise
to keep a close eye on you.
Where is Tomoe?
He is busy bringing
over the carriage.
It appears that you have
finished conversing with Kotaro.
So let us return to the shrine.
Wow, what is this thing?
Mikage's favorite form
of transportation,
the Night Fog Carriage.
It travels through
the cover of darkness.
Please excuse us.
Ahem.
Hurry up and get in.
Pathetic.
If you do not wish
to return to the shrine,
then I shall return without you.
Hey wait a minute!
Where are you going?
You can't just!
You wish to remain, do you not?
As a human being?
Hey!
Quit being stupid
and help me get in!
It's too high for me to climb.
Astounding.
You are quite dependent.
By the way, I have a favor to
ask you about Lady Himemiko.
What about her?
My dear Lady Himemiko
has gone missing!
Is that a fact?
I have yet to see milady
since that puny land god
of yours summoned her!
You had better confess
right now, fox, or else!
Thou art making
a racket, Aotake.
Sorry for the delay!
What on earth
did she do to you?
She's just the right
size for my uniform!
What do you think,
isn't she pretty?
Does it truly look good?
Yes.
Dressed like that, you are
a very convincing human.
Does that mean I can
meet with Kotaro?
Yes, but be careful.
Even my transformation spell
requires that you follow this
very important guideline.
You must never use
your powers like this.
Do so and you will revert
back to your yokai form.
And stop doing that as well.
Well, here we go,
Miss Himemiko!
Kotaro can't wait to meet you!
Oh, Nanami.
I am grateful.
Kotaro will be waiting for you
in the park's plaza
near the west gate, at five pm.
She's late.
Maybe this whole
thing's a prank.
What are the chances of a girl
having feelings for someone
like me to begin with?
Is that thee, Kotaro?
It is thee!
Sweet Kotaro!
Do not cry, boy.
Smile.
Smile!
Isn't this wonderful?
It's been ten years since
they first met!
It is nothing more than
a passing infatuation
between human and yokai.
Please don't be so negative.
Not now, at least.
She's been waiting ten years
for this reunion,
and here it's finally happening.
Kotaro.
So close!
How I longed to see thee.
Oh well, um.
Would ya quit leaning
on me like that?
But why?
I've, never even
met you before, kay?
But my heart yearns
to reach out to thee.
Being told that stuff by
a stranger is kind of, well,
it's confusing.
Oh, I see.
Don't get me wrong,
I'm flattered, you know.
I just don't understand
why you like me.
What is that box?
It's a "puzzle cube."
Don't tell me you've never
tried to solve one before?
Nuh-uh.
It's a hexahedral
three-dimensional puzzle.
You keep twisting the sides
until the colors match up
on each face.
What a mysterious contraption.
Nah, it's really easy
once you get it!
Just twist and take note of
which color's on what face.
See?
Green is done.
Such swiftness and grace!
Thou art truly incredible!
Wanna try it out?
May I?
Go right ahead.
I'm gonna grab us a couple
of sodas so just sit tight
till I get back.
What's this feeling?
It's as if my heart's racing
inside of me.
That's our Lady Nanami!
Congratulations, your
first job is complete!
Bravo, milady!
You make this land god
stuff totally worth it!
Pardon my interruption, but
now is not the time for that.
Wassup honey?
What's a sweet thing like you
doin' all alone out here?
Why don't you come with us?
We'll show you
a real good time!
Hey girl, are you
even listenin' to us!
Hey, lemme see your
toy for a second.
Give it back!
Uh oh, I think
she's gettin' angry?
Oh no!
We have to go help her!
Do nothing.
It is not your place
to do their job.
The responsibility to
move forward lies squarely
on the humans.
That being said, should one
desire to move forward,
all they may need is a little
boost in the right direction.
That, however, is your job.
You provide them
a little boost.
No.
What should I do?
I want to.
I need to help her, but--
I'm so scared I can't
even move my feet!
Kotaro.
Start moving, start moving.
Please start moving!
Go forward.
Go now.
I hope that it reached him.
My boost of encouragement.
Do you think it worked?
Perhaps, yes.
I did not think you would
take such a literal approach
but if it works then
I guess it works.
And from the looks of it.
Whatever you did appears
to have worked.
May Kotaro and Lady Himemiko's
bond grow stronger day by day,
and may it never falter.
Nanami saves
a white snake at school,
but the snake ends up
falling in love with her.
To protect Nanami,
Tomoe disguises himself as
her high school classmate!
Mmm, what a dreamboat!
Next time, "The God
Is Kidnapped." Oh no!