High school student,
Nanami Momozono,
otherwise known as the
protagonist in this story.
As you can see, ordinarily,
darling Nanami is possessed of
a lively beauty but,
right now, she appears to be
rather worn out, as they say.
And who could blame her?
Unfortunately, Nanami's
father loves to gamble.
Therefore, their
household is awash in debt.
It's no wonder she's like this.
Oh, what a terribly
unfeminine lunch box.
Oh, I forgot to
tell the worst part.
Orders have been
issued to evict you!
What?
Where is my father?
He what?
Daddy was long gone,
having run away from it all.
His whereabouts are unknown.
Poor Nanami was
driven from her house,
and found herself homeless.
What, oh what,
will become of our Nanami?
Now, don't worry, this isn't one
of those depressing stories.
It's a proper romantic comedy.
Prepare to enjoy the thrills
and the chills to the very end.
How could that stinking
old man do that to me?
Someone help!
Please, you've gotta help me!
Can you please get
that dog out of here!
Shoo, shoo.
You're a lifesaver.
Thank you.
I had just come back to this
town for the first time in
a while, but that dog ran out
of nowhere and barked at me.
So, you must be afraid of dogs?
Kind of, yeah.
I guess the people
who live around here
don't exactly feel
welcoming towards me.
Are you a local person yourself?
Um, yes.
Well, sort of.
At the moment, I don't
have a place to live.
And so, she explained.
Wow.
Your father was
in serious debt.
I'm sure you must
hate him intensely
for running away like that.
Well, I'm embarrassed to admit
it, but I abandoned my home.
It's been decades since then.
There's no telling
how everyone is doing.
Tomoe's bound to jump kick me
as soon as I show my face.
Tomoe?
Is that his wife?
But still.
At least you have
a home to go back to.
Sounds kinda awesome; I don't
even have that anymore.
I can give you my home.
I don't mind.
The house shouldn't
be left unattended forever.
And if you were there,
I wouldn't have to
worry about it anymore.
Most importantly.
You are more worthy of
that house than I am.
Try going to this
place I've mapped out.
If you tell them Mikage
told you to go there,
they will be sure
to welcome you.
You'll be their
new lady and mistress.
Uh.
Their what?
New lady and mistress?
Might as well roll with it.
I don't have
anywhere else to go.
I got played.
I swear, I am never gonna trust
another adult again ever!
Lord Mikage?
Welcome back home, Lord Mikage.
What?
Lord Mikage.
Ghosts!
Indeed, it is you.
Where have you been?
I have waited quite some
time for your return.
Twenty years feels like
an absolute eternity to me;
how about you?
Die, you fiend!
Rats.
Bad news.
This is not Mikage.
What?
Impossible.
Master Tomoe, as you can see,
the mark of the land god
is here on the forehead,
exactly where it should be.
And I sense Lord Mikage's
spiritual energy.
Yet that does not make her him.
Now, then, woman.
Tell me.
Who are you?
Supernatural things
are everywhere!
I'm in a yokai shrine!
Look, Master!
Yes, this moronic handwriting
has to be Mikage.
He said since I had nowhere
else to go that I should
come and live here.
Wait, so, Tomoe is a guy?
He's gorgeous.
So you know, the man you met was
the land god of this region.
And this shrine is
the home of that land god.
The fact he sent you here as
the new lady and mistress
can only mean he left you to
be the land god in his place.
Oh, what a happy day!
The land god has finally
returned to the shrine!
We must prepare a feast
for the occasion at once!
Please enjoy,
Lady Goddess of the Land!
Help yourself!
Wait!
Hold on!
So.
Uh.
You said that I was
a land god, right?
I'm just Nanami Momozono, just
a normal high school student.
I mean, how and why
did I become a god?
'Tis simple.
It all happened the moment
that you received this mark
on your forehead.
I have a mark?
Really?
Moment?
He kissed me.
Oh no.
That was it.
You call this a god?
What could a pathetic looking
thing like her even do?
At the most, she might
be able to weed the yard
or perhaps count
the money offerings.
Unacceptable!
But this lady--
--was referred by
Lord Mikage himself!
I care not.
Throw her out.
'Scuse me!
You're being awfully high
and mighty and rude
to me for no reason!
I bet a rundown shrine
like this doesn't even
get money offerings!
You couldn't pay me to do it!
Now, now!
Lady Nanami,
please do not say that.
We are overjoyed to have you!
If you intend to give
that creature a place here,
I shall leave this shrine.
Master Tomoe!
I am Mikage's familiar.
I do not intend
to serve anyone else.
If you like, ask a stray dog
or something to step in
as my replacement.
Wait!
Don't go!
So um.
I don't suppose you could at
least put me up for the night?
With pleasure!
Talk about a weird dream!
My dad had run away
and the house got seized,
so I didn't have anywhere
to live until this man gave up
his own home for me,
but when I went there,
it was a rundown shrine
with little ghosts in it
who told me I was a land god,
which made me all like,
what the heck,
and then this obnoxious
guy with ears named Tomoe
or whatever wouldn't
stop saying the whole thing
was unacceptable.
How funny.
Good morning,
Lady Goddess of the land!
And now, if you please.
Get right to it!
To what?
Your duties as
a land god, my lady!
We can begin with
a cleaning of the yard!
All filth is to be purged
to keep evil spirits at bay!
Next, neatly clear away
the fallen leaves!
Then, wipe the hall of
worship with a damp cloth!
Hurry!
We still must weed the flowers!
This is what a god has to do?
Hold on.
I don't think I ever actually
agreed to be this land god,
did I?
Oh no!
What are you saying?
Now that Master Tomoe
has left us.
You are the only one
who can protect this place,
Lady Nanami!
With us!
Onikiri!
Kotetsu!
We shall be here
to help support the shrine!
And we shall support you,
Lady Nanami!
So please do not hesitate
to ask whatever you wish!
You know.
Yes?
Who is that Tomoe anyway?
Oh!
Master Tomoe is a familiar
who serves Lord Mikage!
Familyer?
No, Familiar.
He was originally
a wild fox but was brought on
to serve and guard
in place of a lion-dog.
Lord Mikage is not
exactly a fan of dogs.
Woof.
Oh, yeah, I knew that.
I guess this is the price
for having a place to stay.
Ow!
So, you do not even know
how to properly weed.
What a tragically useless girl.
Whaddayou want?
I thought you left already.
You will never fulfill
the duties of a land god.
Why do you not
head back home before
you are forced to admit defeat?
Because I don't have
a home to head back to.
Thanks to all my father's
debts, the house was seized
and I was kicked out.
Not my problem.
What was that about?
I'm so tired.
They may call me a god,
or land god or what not.
But I have a feeling they're
just using that as an excuse
to take advantage of me.
Dear God.
I'm here to pray
for my daughter.
Please allow her to give
birth to a healthy child.
What?
I can hear her.
That woman.
I just heard her thoughts.
Indeed, you did.
What you heard was the
prayer inside the heart
of the worshipper!
A portion of a land god's
duties is to sit in the shrine
and hear the wishes
from those of the land!
Come, come, Lady Nanami!
We must move on
to your next duty!
We need you to look
through all of these!
What are they?
A record of our
worshippers' prayers from
the last twenty years, my lady.
Twenty years?
Master Tomoe has been
writing them down.
The intent was to have
Lord Mikage look at them
upon his return.
With his absence,
we have sadly seen
quite a decline in
visitors to the shrine.
But, thanks to Master
Tomoe somehow managing
to keep the shrine
in decent condition--
--as you saw earlier--
--we still manage
to have occasional visitors,
which is nice.
We realize we have asked you
to do a lot of work today.
Normally, Master Tomoe
takes care of the shrine
all on his own.
No wonder.
He writes neatly.
The accounts are so detailed.
Dear God, please.
Dear God, please, I pray.
Let my wish come true.
I bet a run down shrine
like this doesn't even
get money offerings!
Well, Lady Nanami?
Do you understand now?
Yeah, I got it.
He's right.
There's no way I can be a god.
What?
I'm just a normal girl.
It's not like I have
powers or anything.
However.
However?
I believe I'd like
to go speak with him.
Clearly some of the things I
assumed weren't entirely true.
I'd appreciate it if you
could take me to see him.
Oh.
Unfortunately, I fear
Master Tomoe has gone.
to the world over yonder.
World over yonder?
The world over yonder.
All dark places in our
realm serve as entrances.
Like wells or the
shadows of grassy fields.
Lying between ours
and the netherworld,
is the land of
the supernatural.
Also known as the place
in which humans are lost
when they look too closely
into the darkness.
It coexists alongside us.
This is it?
The world of the yokai kind!
Master Tomoe!
Where are you, Master Tomoe?
Quiet, you two.
You are making a scene.
Master Tomoe?
Are you in here?
You wanted something?
Master Tomoe!
How deplorable!
You are a familiar
in service to a god!
Already drinking in
the middle of the day,
holed up in the
red-light district!
Leave me alone.
Master Tomoe,
you must change immediately!
And you, harlots,
remove yourselves at once!
What?
Such impertinence from
will-o'-the-wisp children!
You two should leave!
Indeed, you should.
But you have to come back
to the shrine with us.
Lady Nanami needs you
to be her familiar.
Do you not care if
the shrine goes to ruin?
No, I do not care
in the slightest.
Good riddance, if you ask me.
I no longer have to be
a familiar at all.
What a tedious job that was.
So, from this day forward,
I shall idle each day away,
living my life as I please.
Master Tomoe!
We are here for Lady Nanami!
She stated she wished
to see you again.
So she has come over with us.
What?
I do regret coming, though.
You're disgusting.
I don't understand how you
could you just abandon
that shrine like
it was nothing.
You're so selfish!
Goodbye.
Oh, Lady Nanami!
Why did you bring her?
She insisted;
we could not deny her!
I do not care
what she insisted!
Why the hell would
you bring a human here?
Lady Nanami is no
ordinary human being, though.
She is a land god.
Remember?
Which makes it even worse!
How can he even say that after
acting so self-righteous to me?
No, I do not care
in the slightest.
Well, good riddance
to him, then!
Hey there, Missy.
We know you.
You're that human girl they
say became the new land god
at the Mikage Shrine.
I heard Mikage quit being
a land god and found
a replacement but I had
no clue that you'd be, so--
Delicious and tasty looking.
I can't resist!
I'm going to gobble you up,
starting with your head!
Lady Nanami!
Where do you think you're going?
Why if it isn't Master Tomoe.
I don't suppose you'd mind if
we ate that scrumptious looking
human girl, would you?
We'd appreciate it if
you didn't get in our way.
Why ask me?
You do not need my consent.
Seriously?
You don't mind?
Wow!
Thank you!
Although, I am
in an unbelievably,
terrible mood right now.
A helpless girl with
the powers of a land god.
Figuratively speaking,
she is like a duck
that brought along
its own pot and leeks.
Not that it is any
of my business.
We should be safe now
that we have come this far.
At least, we certainly hope so.
Lady Nanami, listen to us,
please go back to Master Tomoe!
You must have Master Tomoe
become your familiar
at all costs!
Wrong!
I'll be fine.
I'm going back.
But Lady Nanami!
If you seal the contract to make
Master Tomoe your familiar.
Master Tomoe will have no choice
but to obey your every command!
My every command?
Seriously?
Yes.
That is one of the powers
a land god possesses.
Oh-ho.
That does sound nice.
So what is it I have to do?
To seal the contract, I mean.
It is quite simple, my lady.
You must take him and then
kiss him right on the mouth!
Do so and Master Tomoe
shall become your
loyal servant forever.
After that, there shall be
nothing you cannot make him do.
Lady Nanami?
Lady Nanami!
No way.
Why would those guys try to get
me to do something so horrible?
I am going back just like
I said I was gonna go back
as fast as I can go!
Excuse me.
You there, young miss.
Would you mind
helping out an old lady?
Lady Nanami!
Where have you gone?
I tripped back there and
just could not get back up.
Where do you live, ma'am?
Lady Nanami!
Uh, ma'am?
Is this the right way
to your home?
Oh, yes, it's right!
Lady Nanami!
Are you hurt?
What is that thing?
It is a demon hag!
We should probably
get out of here now!
You'll never get away from me!
Come back here!
If I eat land god flesh, I'll
live for another thousand years!
Kotetsu will taste not so good.
I don't want you!
I need the girl!
Where did she go?
Master Tomoe!
Lady Nanami!
Kotetsu has gone running
to fetch Master Tomoe!
When he finds you,
seal the contract to
make him your familiar!
No way!
There is absolutely no way!
Please use these, Lady Nanami!
What are they?
They are white talismans.
White talismans?
They are like magical paper.
If you write on them
and make sure they attach
to the object you wish to
target, the talisman manifests
power and makes whatever
words you write down come true!
That's so cool!
Turn into a God Soldier!
Um, Lady Nanami?
The power of the talisman
cannot surpass that
of your own abilities.
Why didn't you
tell me that earlier?
Only two more left!
It's time to dine!
Curse you, girl!
I only have one more!
Has that human
been eaten already?
Please, Master Tomoe!
You have to come
help Lady Nanami!
So, not yet, then?
Tomoe, help me!
Oh yes.
I shall go.
Then I can watch her cry.
It's too high!
Hurry, Lady Nanami!
You must keep climbing!
I found you, girlie!
She's fast!
Lady Nanami!
You seem to be having
a tough time there.
I heard you might be
in a tight spot,
so I rushed over immediately.
Tomoe.
I wanted to enjoy the show.
Do you want some help, Nanami?
Oh, I imagine you must.
If you cry and plead, "Please
forgive this foolish girl,
O great Tomoe," I might
be inclined to give you
some assistance.
No.
Like hell I'd ask you.
Lady Nanami!
Just say it!
"Please forgive--"
No way!
"--this foolish girl--"
"--O, great Tomoe!"
No way!
You only have to
say that one line.
Then he will help you!
Correct, Master Tomoe?
Oh yes.
Indeed so.
Say it, and I will help you.
Just say it.
Lady Nanami!
Say the line!
No!
Lady Nanami!
Say the line!
I said no!
Lady Nanami!
I won't!
There is no way!
I'd rather die
than bow to him!
You stupid girl.
All you had to say to
live was one silly line!
Now you are going to die
because of your foolish pride.
Seal the contract.
He will have no choice.
All right, Tomoe.
Help me right now, jerk!
Curse you!
Lady Nanami.
With that
You have become a true,
honest-to-goodness land god!
Congratulations!
What the hell, man?
Let go of my prey!
Get down here.
You putrid hag!
Because of you, I am stuck
being a familiar again!
Right when I had just
started enjoying my freedom
to the fullest!
What do you have to say for
yourself, you dirty old harpy?
You're beating
a feeble old woman!
What do you have to
say for yourself?
Visually speaking.
This looks very bad.
Tomoe.
What?
You came for me.
Thank you for that!
Can we go?
Back to the shrine, I mean?
All of us.
Kurama, the super popular
pretty-boy pop star transfers
to Nanami's high school.
The girls are all abuzz,
shrieking like crazy.
But he has an unusual
aura about him.
"The God Becomes a Target"
So she's going to be targeted?