Looks like summer break is
just around the corner!
And there's our darling heroine,
Nanami, simply beaming with joy!
Today she's gathered
with Ami and Kei
to make exciting vacation plans!
Oh, what fun they're having!
Are you reading
the right script?
That's not what's
happening here at all!
Whoopsie.
You can't just make
things up as you go!
Stay focused!
Sorry.
All this heat is getting to me.
Ah yes, I remember now!
Last time, she discovered
love was blooming in her heart
and soon after, had it
ripped out and stomped upon.
So, no, she's not joyous at all.
Hey I have a good idea!
Why don't we go to
the beach over break?
Doesn't that sound
like fun, Nanami?
Yeah, fun.
The beach.
Love it.
Let's go to the Alps right now.
When are we leaving?
Her brain!
It's like mush!
That's awful!
The dude she stripped down to
her soul in front of pretty much
told her to take a cold shower.
I kinda get it.
Guess you're still not hungry?
You should at least try to
eat a few bites of rice?
No, seriously.
You look like you're
about to pass out.
Please?
Listen to her.
You scarcely had anything
to eat this morning
and now you are refusing lunch?
What is the meaning
behind this?
If you are fasting, the
timing is inappropriate.
I want to stay strong and stay
in control of my feelings.
But it's difficult when he
can show up out of nowhere
and catch me off guard.
It's not a fast.
I'm not hungry.
Too bad.
Please stop, it won't work.
She still hasn't recovered
from being rejected by you
so you getting mad at her
is just making it worse.
I can't get a grip
on my emotions.
Thank you for your help.
Now, if you are refusing to eat,
then you leave me no choice
but to pry your mouth open
and force feed you.
You know I hate mushrooms!
And then I realized I'm the only
one whose feelings changed.
Tomoe is just the same
as he's always been.
There's only one exception.
Now he's doing everything
he can to avoid touching me.
I'm sorry, Nanami.
I know this is hard but I love
you and I'm here for you!
And I'm dying to take you
to the beach!
We'll have so much
fun that you'll forget
all about what happened!
'Kay!
You're on.
When?
How 'bout Saturday?
Yeah, that sounds
like a lot of fun,
but do either of you
have swimsuits?
Uh.
No.
The ocean?
I'm here to see Nanami!
Are you kidding?
What do you mean I can't go?
I mean you cannot
go to the ocean!
But why not?
Ami went out of her way
plan it all and invite me!
This is so unfair!
Please do not be upset,
Lady Nanami.
It is filled with
demonic creatures.
If you were human, it might be
a different story, but you are
a land god and I cannot risk
something terrible happening.
Also--
I cannot go into the
ocean to protect you.
The answer is no.
I'll be fine!
My friends will
be there with me!
Is that so?
You believe your friends
could stand up to demons?
No, they can't.
But I could always use
a day at the beach.
Take me.
You mean it?
We're here!
The beach!
You've got to be kidding.
Seriously?
Someone want to tell me
what they're doing here?
Looks like we made it!
Okay, we can't have guys
hanging around us.
It's gonna look like
we're 'with' you.
No one will come
cruising for us!
Which cruise line?
P.S.
Forgot to tell you Kei broke up
with her boyfriend yesterday.
The plan to escape thoughts
of Tomoe didn't work.
My stomach hurts.
Who's ready to go swimming?
You look like a freaking
toddler with that thing.
Be nice.
I just don't know how to swim.
How do you feel
about that swimsuit?
Is it working out?
It's really cute.
I love it.
Thank you for loaning it to me!
I've honestly never
worn anything like this!
No problem.
Whatever keeps you from swimming
next to me in a t-shirt,
ya know?
Why don't you go show it off
to your buddies over there?
See what they think?
It'll give them
something to do, at least.
They definitely don't look like
they're interested in swimming.
I don't care what they do!
Let's go swim!
You sure?
Positive!
It's their fault
for following me!
I'm gonna throw up.
Why am I feeling so
self-conscious?
Hurry up, Nanami!
Let's ride some waves!
Do I look all right in this?
Or is it awkward?
Is it obvious the
swimsuit isn't mine?
What are you doing here, Tomoe?
Besides lurking.
I could ask you
the same question.
Girls these days are so
shameless, aren't they?
They wander around in
practically nothing without
any concern for who's looking.
At this rate, even human guys
will turn into beastly yokai.
You are having at least
somewhat of a good time here,
are you not?
I must admit, I was quite
surprised you risked
coming at all today.
And, in case you've forgotten,
I do know exactly why you
can't go into the ocean.
Let me to be frank.
I hate you, Tomoe.
But I will play nice
for Nanami's sake.
Nanami, wait for me!
I want to go swimming, too!
C'mon!
You guys!
This beach has so many
beautiful shells!
Pretty, huh?
Yes, it is.
Well.
Let's go.
Tomoe says he hates anything
that has to do with the ocean.
He does?
He doesn't know
how to appreciate...
He knows exactly
how to get to me.
Touching her because I cannot.
Damn bastard snake.
So, our little white serpent
boy is a water baby?
A dip in the sea does
sound delightful.
Wink!
Have a good time.
You could come with me
instead of taking up space.
I'd like to keep
a safe distance.
If I get closer, Tomoe will
definitely recognize me.
Fine.
Then will you at least
explain why you're dressed
like an Eskimo in this heat?
Ew.
It's part of my image.
People expect it.
Ah.
Yes, well, I can respect that.
And I suppose you
are wise to lay low.
I mean, you abandoned the guy
for 20 years and now here
you are lounging on
the beach in your furs
and secretly watching over him.
I imagine he'd
kill you if he knew.
Tomoe would never do that.
At worst, I can expect
a jump-kick to the head.
I don't know.
Behind those depressing eyebrows
and kill-me-now frown, I think,
perhaps Tomoe has a more
compassionate side
he doesn't always show.
That girl.
I wonder if things
are different with her?
Toodles!
Oh how I do love him,
but it's easy to forget
he's a god sometimes.
On second thought.
It is a beautiful day.
I suppose it would be
silly not to go for a swim.
It's so pretty!
For you!
Really?
Thanks, I love it!
So then?
You having fun?
Yeah, the water feels amazing!
That's good!
I'm glad you came.
I was getting worried.
You were so sad.
Let's get this moving.
Ami?
There is something disturbing
about the way sea water feels.
Ever notice that?
Goodness, what has
happened to you, Tomoe?
Your face is even more furry
and frightening than usual.
Tomoe!
It's Ami and Nanami!
What happened?
Nanami!
Ami!
I lost her!
I went down to look
and couldn't find her!
She doesn't know how to swim!
She could be drowning!
We have to get to her
before it's too late!
Please, Tomoe!
I need your help!
Leave it to me.
Really?
Are you sure about this?
Nanami has requested my
help in her time of need.
It cannot be helped.
Ami.
Ami?
Time to go back.
You found her!
Ami!
How are you feeling?
Are you okay?
Uh yeah, I'm fine.
I just swallowed
a lot of water.
What's wrong with you?
Why did you take off
by yourself like that?
Sorry!
Thank goodness!
Thank you.
You saved her life!
Isn't that sweet?
Yes, thank you, Tomoe.
So nice of you to drop
by the ocean for a visit.
Here you are,
right when I'd started giving
up on ever finding you.
I've been waiting a lifetime
for you to join me for a swim,
Tomoe.
Who're you?
Thought you'd never ask.
I am the Dragon King,
ruler of the sea.
Do yourself a favor
and try to remember that.
What's happening?
Kei?
Ami?
Can you hear me?
Sorry, but I'm going to ask the
spectators to stay out of this.
If you'll excuse me
for just a moment,
it's time for me to collect
a debt from an old friend.
A debt?
I only wish I knew
what that meant.
Tomoe!
I am more than happy to
remind you, you ignorant fox!
Exactly five hundred
twenty six years,
two hundred and eight days ago,
at eighteen minutes and
forty-one seconds past two AM.
A certain yokai fox called
Tomoe, attacked and wiped out
seven dragons,
three sharks, five rays,
and one sea slug platoon
at the north gate of my palace.
He then destroyed the north gate
and surrounding buildings.
And finally, he stole
my right eye and fled.
You are that fox, Tomoe.
The time has come
for you to pay it back.
If you refuse, then I have
no problem taking it from you.
Giant White-Lipped Oyster!
You will slowly turn into
sustenance for the oyster now.
And in a day or so, I'll return
to find a king sized pearl.
Excellent choice as always
your majesty, sea slug.
That despicable wild
creature never stood a chance
against your powerful new
and improved form, sea slug.
That's the truth!
I've been rebuilding
my strength every day for
five hundred twenty-six years,
two hundred and eight days.
It's about time it paid off!
Let's head back
for a celebration!
Sea slug!
Hold it!
What do you think
you're doing with Tomoe?
Hey, wait a second,
why aren't you sleeping?
What are you even doing here?
I want you to let him
out of there!
Is that so?
Sorry.
I wish there was
more I could do.
Run along, now, little girl.
I can't let them get away!
Tomoe!
I cannot go into the
ocean to protect you.
He tried to warn me.
I didn't listen!
I made him go!
It's my fault.
It's scary to think that
even with all his power,
I could lose him and
never see him again.
I can't breathe!
Tomoe!
Your persistence is obnoxious.
Does this mean you're done?
Where is he?
I had the sea slugs
relocate him.
He's far, far away.
Yes, I did carry you to safety.
You are welcome.
Now you owe me.
Fine!
Anything you want.
Just give me Tomoe back!
I'm afraid his debt is
much larger than yours.
I will not release him
until it is paid in full.
Let it go.
I'll help him repay you!
What do I have to do to
get you to set him free?
Since you asked.
I want you to return to me
what is rightfully mine.
Find a way to bring me
back my right eye
and I will consider
sparing his miserable life.
You see, my eye is a pill of
eternal youth and immortality.
It's said that whoever swallows
it will gain great powers.
All those years ago, I lost it
to that insignificant yokai.
I, the Dragon King, had
defeat carved into my face!
So then all I have to do
is return the eye and you
promise you'll let him go?
'All you have to do?'
As if it's that simple.
My dear, it's been five
hundred twenty-six years.
I'm certain something's
happened to it by now.
Like I said, just let it go.
No, wait!
Promise me.
If I can find the eye
and return it,
that you will let Tomoe live.
You really think
this is possible.
Alright but I'm only
holding onto the fox
as collateral for two days.
If that's the only way to save
Tomoe, I have to find it.
Why have I never
eaten ice cream before.
So sweet and creamy
and delicious--
Who the hell said you
could be happy today?
Nanami and Tomoe are missing
and you're sitting here
lounging around like
it's some damn vacation!
You even took a bath!
Has anyone even bothered
to call the police?
Of course not.
There's no need to worry.
Nanami will be back tomorrow.
I think we could all use
a good night's rest.
So I will be sleeping
on the middle futon.
I tend to get lonely by myself.
I don't think so.
This room was reserved
for three girls.
You and Tomoe can find
your own place to cuddle.
No way!
Nanami!
Where have you been?
Are you okay?
I'm sorry for making you worry.
I got lost.
See?
I told you she'd be fine,
didn't I?
Mizuki!
I need to borrow the
time-wending incense burner.
I have to go back in time
and find the old Tomoe.
He has the Dragon King's eye,
and I'm going to
take it from him.
I was told that if I returned
the eye to the Dragon King
in two days, then Tomoe's
life would be spared.
So please.
There's a question
I want to ask you.
One of the girls told me
something and I'm fascinated.
Is it true that you
have feelings for Tomoe?
What?
Why would they say that?
Not that it's
anyone's business.
And besides that--
I think he's quite fortunate.
He has a kind lady and mistress
who loves him as much as you do.
I admit; it hurts.
I hate Tomoe.
I don't feel he
deserves all that he has.
If it were up to me,
I would have him stay missing
and consider it
a small miracle.
I know.
What I'm saying
is not very kind.
It's what they describe
as jealousy or envy.
I feel terrible about it
but I don't know what to do.
Have you ever been this way?
Please tell me.
What can I do to make
these thoughts go away?
I'm sorry.
I know.
I know this is hard for you.
But, you're the only one
I know who can help.
I must admit, it's hard to say
no when you put it like that.
Messing with the past
is considered quite taboo.
But, I doubt anyone
will challenge it because
you're a god, so there is
really nothing to worry about.
So you carry that
thing with you?
I do.
Ever since my home got
submerged, I've made it
a rule to carry
everything of value with me.
Last time, I only
sent your soul.
This will be different.
Tonight you will be
travelling over there
as your corporal self.
I will accompany you.
However, I will only be
available as your guide.
You will have to
complete the task.
Tomoe.
In the light.
All I can see is you.
I love you, so deeply,
So hopelessly, and yet--
I will not ever allow myself
to love a human woman.
It's so cold!
It wasn't snowing earlier so I
guess this means I made it into
the past with no problem.
Uh Mizuki?
You there?
Poor thing.
You must be freezing out here.
What?
This kazuki cloak
will keep you warm.
I'll make you a deal.
Give me the Dragon King's
eye inside you and in return,
I will give you my warm cloak.
Nanami?
There you are!
Please don't go wandering off.
It's dangerous out here.
But there was a woman
standing here a second ago.
Yes, I know.
That was a yokai named Isohime.
She can often be found waiting
by the seashore for lost
and vulnerable humans.
There you go.
Now shouldn't you be out
looking for Tomoe?
Yes!
I have to go.
Thank you!
Tomoe!
How dare you raid our palace
and steal the Dragon King's
right eye?
You will return it
to us this instant!
Unfortunately, I do not
have time for that today.
The same face.
The same voice.
Tomoe, is it you?
Yes it is.
You're the one who has my heart.
I won't give up on you.
Miss Nanami.
Promise.
Promise me that you
will look after Tomoe.
Nanami and Mizuki traveled
to the past in search of
the Dragon King's right eye.
Once there, they find Tomoe
and a beautiful woman.
Who is she?
Will Nanami recover?
Next time, "The God Goes To
The Dragon King's Palace."
Her beauty's too great to
do justice in a painting.