That hot guy who's friends with
Nanami showed up again!
Pinch me.
Right Now!
He stands out without
even doing anything.
How am I supposed
to deal with that?
This isn't good.
All of my land god stuff
is keeping me so busy that
I've barely been able to keep up
with any of this material.
Ujigami High School is
nearing the end of a term.
And the end of a term
brings none other than.
Stupid finals.
They're almost as gross
as these mushrooms.
I told you to quit
packing those for lunch;
you know I hate mushrooms!
Why don't you listen for once?
What was that?
You are more than
just a poor goddess.
From the sounds of it,
you are an equally poor student
unable to keep pace.
How heartbreaking.
I would recommend
dropping out at once.
Save yourself the
utter embarrassment.
Tomoe started coming
to school to protect me,
which made sense
at the time, but now.
What is keeping you so busy?
You have barely done anything
as the new land god.
It's a work in progress.
He wants me to act like a god.
But the things I can
do aren't very useful.
What's up, fox?
Tagging along
with Nanami again?
Make sure you study hard.
What about you?
Still shepherding a flock
of naïve sheep?
I'm surprised Nanami does
not absolutely hate you yet.
But she's bound
to come around soon.
Yes, well.
Coming from a person she
already hates, your words
may carry a certain weight.
She doesn't hate me.
How sad it must be,
to not realize what an annoying
bastard you really are!
I guess it takes one
to know one.
Seriously.
You'd think two yokai would
at least be able to get along.
Is something the matter?
Nope.
Hey, Nanami!
I haven't been able to thank
Kurama for his help yet since
he's always surrounded by girls.
And today.
I thought I'd finally
worked up enough courage
to thank him
but here I am again.
I don't think
he remembers me at all.
So maybe I just
won't say anything.
Poor girl.
She is so freaking adorable!
Don't worry,
I'll get Kurama to meet with
you so you guys can chat.
So Ami.
I'm guessing you want
to talk to him alone.
Am I right?
I've been meaning to ask you
this for awhile now.
Do you have weird supernatural
powers or something?
Supernatural?
You did that Ghost busting in
the locker room the other day.
Is that so.
I swear I haven't told anyone!
Not a single person!
Please believe me!
We cannot blame dear Nanami
for being clueless.
It is a stunt Tomoe pulled the
other day when he went to school
masquerading for
a sickly Nanami.
I dunno.
I don't think that
I'm anything special.
But I guess you never know, huh?
I think I've just
found my next task.
Oh my.
As a personal rule, I never
accept gifts from my fans.
Sorry, ladies.
He apologized to us,
I think I'm gonna faint!
Keep buying my albums,
that's gift enough.
Kurama!
Hold still Please!
Hey, is it just me or did
she go kind of overboard
with our math final?
We've got English the same day,
which definitely doesn't help.
The night before each of them,
maybe we should all
get together and study.
How strange.
It's like I just up and
vanished into thin air.
Would you mind leaving that
on your back for a
little bit longer?
Also, Um.
Could you maybe
do me a huge favor?
Go stand outside
the chemistry room.
Someone wants to meet with you,
so wait for her there.
Are you kidding me?!
Not a single person is
fawning over my presence?!
This superstar's presence?!
What a pity.
Kurama!
I'm so sorry I'm late, my
teacher wanted me to help her
after class and
I couldn't get out of it!
Seriously?
Here!
The other day.
Thank you for helping me.
I never got the
chance to thank you.
So yeah.
Thanks for that and for taking
the time to meet me here.
Hmm.
Sorry.
Who are you again?
I'm a much bigger fan of
the romantic comedy genre.
Nobody!
Owwie.
Dude, we totally just
witnessed an epic panty shot!
Wha?
Isobe?!
You wear strawberry panties
just like a little kid would!
How old are you?!
Strawberry panties!
Starting today I'm
gonna be calling you
Strawberry Panties Nekota!
Please stop it!
Cut it out.
So you two morons finally
saw a girl's underwear.
Big deal.
Kurama looks mad.
Oh, hey.
Gotta run!
Miss Nekota, correct?
Yeah.
May I ask for your first name?
It's Ami.
Thank goodness.
Looks like Ami finally got
to tell Kurama thank you.
Wouldn't you say
my divine powers are
working out pretty well?
You know.
I might be getting the
hang of this god business!
You fool.
You thoughtlessly take on
random favors without regard
to the consequences.
Why even bother getting
that naïve girl's hopes up?
Kurama is a yokai.
If that girl finds out
the object of her affection
is not even human.
I doubt she would be ecstatic.
How do you know,
she might be okay with it.
Why is Tomoe always so
negative when it comes
to this kind of stuff?
I wonder.
Maybe he was rejected and hurt
by someone he loved in his past!
Keep studying!
Tomoe may be unhappy about it.
But I made someone's
day a little brighter.
Is that really such
a terrible thing to do?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I just think it would be better
for both humans and yokai
to get along with
each other, that's all.
What purpose does
befriending one another serve?
There could be some
humans out there that
you'd hit it off
with really well.
You should try getting to know
one, you might be surprised!
There is no point.
Being able to protect you
is all that I care about.
Come on.
You shouldn't say things
like that so casually.
Excuse me, are you Nanami?
If you're not too busy could
we ask you some questions?
About what?
My name's Yumi Sakurada.
I'm a freshman.
I have a crush on Tomoe
but I've never talked to him.
Seriously, there's like
no opportunities like ever.
And it's like you guys
are always together.
You're literally always
with him or he's with you
and it drives me crazy!
In other words, are you and
Tomoe in a serious relationship?
Come on, give her
a straight answer.
Well.
I think this might
surprise you,
but we're not together
or anything like that.
Are you for reelz?!
Be honest, don't you lie to me!
For reelz.
It's a miracle!
Is it okay if I ask you
for a teensy favor?
You're always walking home
with Tomoe, right?
Do you mind if I walk home
with him, just for today?
Go ahead.
Thank you so much!
It's not that big a deal.
This won't require any powers.
I just have to make up
an excuse.
Then I'll start heading
home without him.
Excuse me, Tomoe?
Will you be walking home
all by yourself today?
Why don't we walk together?
No.
I have commitments
The Dutch Declaration
of Independence.
1581.
The Edict of Nantes.
1598.
I wonder if Tomoe ended up
walking home with that girl?
You should try getting to know
one, you might be surprised.
I wish.
I wish I'd never said that.
Can I walk home with him today?
I'm so dumb.
I accepted her request on
the spot and now here I am,
regretting it.
This really sucks.
If I knew it was going
to bother me this much.
I wouldn't have said yes.
I can't help it.
I have a crush on Tomoe!
I like him too.
Me, too?
Me, too.
What is the meaning
of this nonsense?!
You wanted me to become friendly
with a human girl, is that it?
So, you heard that?
Of course I heard.
Do you honestly think
matching a human
with a yokai is considerate?
You really are a simpleton.
Do not set things
in motion out
of the so-called
kindness of your heart.
In my eyes, there is
nothing in this world
that takes greater
priority over you.
I mean that.
With those words,
I finally knew.
I knew exactly how
Tomoe made me feel.
I had fallen so hard for him.
That I never even realized it.
Well?
What is so important
that I had to drag
myself to this foul place?
It's simple.
I overheard your rooftop
conversation with Nanami
and got rather
worried about you.
Being wise to the ways
of the human world,
I thought I'd give my foolish
friend a fair warning.
What conversation do you mean?
There's no one in this
great big world that means
more to me than you, Nanami!
You're the only thing
that's important!
I believe it was something
along those lines.
I never said
anything of the sort.
You can't be serious.
You're even more hopeless
than I thought.
Nanami's at that age
where human girls start dating
and looking for a mate.
As her familiar, do you
really want to be the object
of her affection?
The land god of Mikage Shrine?
Be sure to start practicing
a little more discretion
when you handle the girl.
After all, she is your
lady and mistress.
We wouldn't want things
to get too dicey
between the two of you.
Are you implying that
Nanami is being seduced?
Being a familiar
sounds pretty rough.
Babysitting.
That's all the
fearsome fox does now.
It would all be so much easier
if you'd just hurry up
and make me the land god.
What nonsense!
There is only one being in
the entire world who holds
the power to give me orders.
Yet you would dare say she
is like any other schoolgirl
that loses her head
over petty emotions?
Do not take me for a fool.
Whatever you say.
Time to go.
Why won't it open?
Let me try.
Pardon us.
When I become land god,
the first order I'll give
my familiar will be
to kill himself.
Well, you certainly set some
lofty goals for yourself!
What?!
I am so glad finals are over.
Ugh, that was rough.
Hey, where did
Tomoe run off to?
I think he had mentioned
something about picking up
a few things with Kurama today.
Really.
In that case, why don't we
celebrate finishing up finals?
Do either of you wanna grab
a bite to eat somewhere?
I could really go
for some donut holes!
What do you say?
Count me out.
I've got a date with my new BF.
You're replacing us with a boy?!
Uh, yeah, guys come
first in my book.
A boyfriend, huh?
That must be nice.
What are you talking about?
I could've sworn you
were going out with Tomoe.
You're always together,
so it made sense to me.
We do spend time together,
but we can't help that.
Our problem is that we're
too close to begin with.
Yeah, he kinda told me
I mean a lot to him.
But it wasn't like "mean a lot"
like that, you know.
We live together and stuff,
but it's not like we've
ever been out on a date
or anything fun.
She's bragging, right?
No!
Of course I'm not!
If the two of you still aren't
as close as you want to be,
Why not try switching
things up on him now and then?
But, how would I do that?
If you've never been out on a
date, then go out on a date.
Simple as that.
Drag him to a place he's never
been before and act all cute,
like super cute.
Super cute?
Hello; guys adore adorable.
So win him over with cuteness,
and he'll want more.
Oh Em Gee!
Nanami has a crush on Tomoe!
I didn't know, but I love it!
Oh, hey Ami welcome
to the conversation.
A place he's never been before?
Nanami.
Time to go home.
Right.
Tomoe's always in such
a hurry to get home.
I know he's worried
about taking care
of the shrine and
everything, but still.
Hey Tomoe.
Since school
got out early today,
let's not rush
back home so fast.
Right now's the perfect
time for an adventure.
Wooow.
The aquarium!
I haven't been here
since elementary school!
I can't believe they're still
playing my favorite show,
and it's starting in less
than five minutes!
Let's go now!
Okay, what are you
trying to pull?!
Exams are over, so it's
time for us to relax!
We're already here so we
might as well enjoy it.
Cool?!
Wow, that one's gigantic!
It's amazing the ocean's full
of so many different fish!
What do you think, Tomoe?
Hey.
Don't wander off without me!
I was following the route.
Just look at the fish!
Look at the fish!
It's not working.
He's looked miserable
the entire time.
This day has been
a complete disaster!
I've got to do
something to fix it.
Hey, what do you think
that crowd's checking out?
Let's go see!
I bet you've never seen
anything like it before!
Look at all our new friends
who came here just to see you.
Go ahead and introduce
yourself, Lionel!
Why do people have
to be so tall?!
Quit horsing around!
Were you able to see?
Uh, yes.
Good.
Time to go home.
Take my hand.
Hello; guys adore adorable.
So win him over with cuteness,
and he'll want more.
Pinch me.
Someone pinch me.
Okay then, we just saw
the last fish in the aquarium.
No doubt you are satisfied.
What a happy ending
to this grand adventure!
Now, let's go!
Hey, wait a sec!
We've got to make
the most of this trip.
Look at all of the stars!
I wanna get a better
view before we leave.
A little longer.
Just a little while longer?
Please don't let it end yet!
Hurry up, will ya?!
What an incredible view!
Too bad I didn't
bring my camera.
Do you think we can see
the shrine from here?
Well?
Tomoe?
What's wrong?
You have been acting
strangely today.
You seem more excited and
more cheerful than usual.
Surely the fish
and the night view
did not cause this
transformation.
No.
You're overthinking it.
There is one thing
I want to ask you.
Tell me, have you or have
you not been seduced by me?
It was something
that Kurama mentioned.
Human girls your age
start becoming interested
in finding love.
He implied you
were no exception.
He warned me I must not speak
to you in a manner that might
cause you fall in love with me.
Well, Kurama loves his
jokes and we must think
nothing of them.
What if it was true?
What if I did like you?
And what would you say
if Kurama was right?
No.
You are deluding yourself.
No I'm not!
No.
What if what I'm
really feeling is.
Love.
You fool.
I will never allow myself
to love a human woman.
What are you doing?!
We're going to fall!
Let us hope the cool night
breeze can bring you back
to your senses.
Stop struggling;
this is for your own good.
Admit that you were delusional
and I will let you down.
I won't do it!
Because I really do
have feelings for you!
You told me yourself
that I was important to you!
Never mind that!
So you really never felt
the same way about me?
And you never even once
found me attractive,
not even for a single moment?
Nanami!
I've been rejected.
Getting my hopes up like that.
How was I so stupid?
I can't look Tomoe
in the eye anymore.
I just can't!
Nanami!
Give me your hand!
Do it now!
Tomoe.
No!
Don't help me!
What did you say to me?
Don't you touch me!
The Sacred Word.
You idiot.
Do you want to die?!
If you never even liked me,
you can just stay away from me!
Nanami.
Nanami!
Please!
I promise you that I will
never touch you again,
but please at this very moment,
you have to let me save you!
He's so kind,
and strong, and warm.
How could I ever
give up on him?
It isn't fair.
Time to return home.
It's no use.
I know that my love for him
will just keep growing.
Nanami's declaration of
love ends in heartbreak.
What better place to get over
rejection than at the beach?
But a dark shadow
rises up from the sea,
claiming unfinished
business with Tomoe.
Who invited that guy?!
Next time, "The God
Goes To The Beach".
Don't forget your swimsuits!