Let's travel into the past.
Oh, about several
hundred years or so.
I do not know where I am.
Alas, it does not matter.
For I will perish soon enough.
Regardless of the place,
once I am dead,
I shall become a corpse.
That is all.
What happened to you?
You're covered in blood.
It is not my blood.
I see.
You must be terribly exhausted.
Come with me to my shrine.
You should rest
a while before you go.
Will you let me see
what's killing you?
As I thought.
This mark is a spell cast
by one who was once a god.
It has wrapped
itself around you.
How long have you
suffered from this darkness?
Long enough.
Yokai should stay away
from former gods.
They may have been
divested of their godhood,
but their enchantments
remain and cannot be undone.
My assumption is you must
have sealed some sort of
contract with this fallen god.
I swore.
I swore I would spend
my life with a woman.
A human woman who
was very dear to me.
That woman has died.
So, now, I, too, must go.
I failed to
become human, though.
So, even if I die,
I cannot go where Yukiji is.
And thus, you were
wandering until the end came.
So even a yokai like you can
have feelings for another.
You came to care that deeply
for a child of man?
I loved her.
More than anything.
No matter what it cost me.
I wanted to be with her.
If you are a god,
may I ask you at least
to attend upon my deathbed?
Of course you may.
However, there is
no reason for you to die.
I will aid you with my powers.
Each time the sun rises
and sets, your wounded heart
will heal little by little.
And little by little,
you will forget.
It is the power of oblivion.
All you have to do
is forget the contract,
and you will escape
from its curse.
Come, sleep for now.
Mikage!
What's wrong!
I'm not used to seeing
you doze off, Tomoe.
Were you having
a bad dream or something?
You seemed like you were upset.
Never mind that.
What are you doing?
Well, you looked
so nice and vulnerable
while you were sleeping,
I wanted to watch.
You consider yourself
a familiar here.
So get to work!
But you were the one
who was sleeping!
I realize he used to be a fox,
so he can't exactly help it,
but Tomoe is a little
too violent for my taste.
Actually, compared to
how Tomoe used to be,
he has mellowed quite a bit.
He was a true terror when
he first came to the shrine.
I'm impressed Lord Mikage
bothered to tame him.
Tame him?
Well, this is Tomoe
we're talking about.
I remember who he was;
what he used to be like.
I can only tell you
what he was like when
he first came to the shrine.
Tomoe, from now on,
you should live here
at this shrine as a familiar.
I'm certain the spirits of the
shrine will welcome you, too.
I am a yokai.
I cannot live in such
a stifling place.
You'll be fine.
Once the contract to make you
my familiar is sealed,
you'll be able to
live here with ease.
What tasty looking human flesh!
I'll eat you!
Shame, shame.
You must be the yokai
who has been terrorizing
this bridge recently.
My lord and master is
at the end of his tether
with frightened humans
asking him for help, from you.
Luckily, I get to be
the one who destroys you!
Please save me!
Do not touch me, human!
So.
While you were chasing off this
human girl with your foxfire,
the yokai we've been
trying to find got away?
Incredible.
It is as if you
were there with me.
I am angry, Tomoe!
You are unacceptably
unkind to humans.
Now that you are a familiar
of the shrine, you must find
a way to have more love
towards these people.
I forbid you from
any more violent acts.
If you're going to help people,
you should have a better--
Um, what are you doing?
That human touched me earlier.
I am not a hand towel.
Sit down and get comfortable.
Today is the day I show
no mercy until you repent!
Nag, nag, nag, nag, nag, nag,
nag, nag, nag, nag, nag, nag...
Good grief.
It is already morning.
Master Fox's dislike of
humans is quite the headache.
Why did Lord Mikage make
a wild fox his familiar
in the first place?
That creature will only bring
dishonor to the shrine.
That reminds me, Onikiri.
It seems Lord Otohiko,
the wind god,
will be dropping by tomorrow
on his way back through town.
Goodness!
We must work immediately
to shut Master Wild Fox away
where he cannot be seen!
Oh, is that so?
From where did you come?
I thought Lord Mikage
was still scolding you.
It is over.
So a god friend of Mikage's
is coming here?
He is indeed.
Please, do not forget
your duties as a familiar.
Ha.
This coming from
a hideous clown.
Now, let me see your face.
Stupid.
This thing with Tomoe
is so difficult.
Why does he hate
humans so much?
I made him my familiar
hoping for the best,
but it's been a month, and
he hasn't gotten any better.
Lord Mikage.
I do not understand
why you brought
Master Fox home with you.
It was his face.
The shadow of death
was upon him.
I was afraid if I didn't
reach out to him,
this sad white fox would
die like a lonely rabbit.
I suppose I felt
worried about him.
That familiar looks
familiar, doesn't he?
That's funny.
A yokai serving as a familiar.
Are you running errands
for your Master?
I dare you to come into the
river with your foxfire!
Yes.
Yap while you can.
Once Mikage grants
me permission,
I will wrap you all
in rice cake and eat you.
Um, Mister Fox?
I knew that had to be you!
You are the fox that
saved me yesterday, right?
The human.
I'm glad.
I had a feeling I'd get
to see you if I waited here.
I was so scared I forgot
to thank you yesterday.
Really?
You should have kept
your distance, human.
It is not my fault
if I eat you.
I don't think you will.
You're too white and beautiful
to do something so dark.
Do not touch me!
Go home, dear.
I think I hear your precious
baby brother crying out for you.
Oh.
Yes sir!
Tell me.
What is this hatred
towards humans about?
They are too weak.
I do not wish
to deal with that.
You are the truly weak one.
You need to grow stronger.
I will not have one who
would raise a hand against
a child of man serving me.
How have you been, Mikage?
The great Otohiko has
returned from Izumo!
Long time no see!
It's been like a hundred years.
I brought you a souvenir!
Wow, do you look gloomy.
Otohiko.
Welcome back.
I think I may have scolded Tomoe
a little too harshly yesterday.
Now, I'm worried.
Oh.
It is so like me
to walk in on awkwardness.
You are the truly weak one.
You need to grow stronger.
I will not have one who
would raise a hand against
a child of man serving me.
So this is where you
have been, Master Tomoe.
We have been searching for you.
What is it?
Has Mikage's god friend
gone home already?
Yes.
He just left us.
The moon is full this evening.
It is the one day out of
the month that Lord Mikage
partakes of sake.
You must go pour for him.
Why me?
You two are perfectly capable.
Oh, no.
We cannot fill
a god's cup with sake.
That is the duty of
the god's familiar.
Hello, Tomoe.
I'd be honored if
you would join me.
After that, Master Tomoe
fully carried out his duties
as Lord Mikage's familiar
for several hundred years.
Until one day.
I'm going into town, Tomoe.
Make sure you hold down the
fort until I get back, okay?
With those words, Lord Mikage
left and has yet to return.
It has been twenty years
since that day.
And not too long ago,
Lady Nanami came to
live at the shrine.
Oh.
Yes.
Since Lady Nanami's arrival,
Master Tomoe has
cheered up considerably.
It is odd.
He seems to be enjoying himself.
Although, it is in a different
way than with Lord Mikage.
I wonder why.
Slacking off again,
are you, Snake?
Oh.
I didn't know you were there.
Complaining must be hard work.
Would you care
to join me for a cup?
You drink sake night and day.
Get to work!
So, is Nanami still asleep?
Yes she is, for it is Sunday.
I swear, that girl
has no discipline.
Are you intending to spend
the whole day in bed?
Aw, I'll be up in a bit.
It's Sunday.
Gimmie a break.
Dear Master Tomoe.
He has turned into
such a fine familiar.
I don't know if you know this,
but humans
sometimes need time off.
Unacceptable!
You are a land god, so why not
just get used to it already!
Look!
They're both here for the
first time in like forever!
Kurama and Tomoe, oh my gah!
They're still gorgeous.
Not that I thought
they wouldn't be.
Kurama just came home yesterday
from a location shoot overseas!
I heard Tomoe was so sick
he actually spent time
in the hospital!
I bet he's so frail right now.
I am telling you,
I can't get enough of that
sickly aura he's rocking.
I would judge them so hard
if I didn't feel the same way.
Look, it's friends
without boyfriends time!
Hey, there's like this dating
mixer thing that's goin' down
this weekend, and I kind
of added you two ladies
to the group count.
So, try to come
looking fierce, okay?
You, what?
Where did this
random idea come from?
That's a bit much for me.
I didn't have a choice.
We didn't have
enough girls going.
But I don't want
to go to a mixer.
Oh, come on; think about it.
Don't you want boyfriends
before Christmas?
No.
Not really.
Well, I do,
so you guys are going.
Yes, ma'am.
Wonderful!
Come Saturday at two!
This is the worst!
I've never been to anything
fancy like a mixer before!
And that's because I'd never
want to go to anything fancy
like a mixer!
Well!
We have a grand lineup
of two stories this time!
How can I go?
I already like someone.
Is anything wrong?
Your discussion with Kei
seemed to upset you.
I already like someone.
Oh.
No, it's nothing.
Do not lie!
I heard you say you were going
to some sort of mixing thing!
I said it's nothing!
I just made plans
to have fun, okay?
And guys should always keep
their noses out of girl-talk!
We're going home.
I won't tell him
what's going on.
That way there won't be any
weird misunderstandings.
Besides, Tomoe is the only
person I have feelings for.
Oh my, the fox
just got shut down.
I told you handling humans
is difficult, didn't I?
And girls around Nanami's
age are the hardest.
Nanami said it was nothing.
So it is nothing.
You are ever
the complacent one.
Do you honestly believe what's
going on with her is nothing?
The hell was that for?
Tomoe.
I'm going into town, Tomoe.
So cool to meet you!
We're girls from
Ujigama High School!
I'm Yamada.
Sato.
Tanaka.
I'm Kohiruimaki.
Nice to meet you!
You girls are
still in high school?
Adorable!
Bet you're all popular.
That's sweet.
Not true, but sweet.
So do you girls
have boyfriends?
Moron!
You can't just ask that!
That's why they're here!
Who cares if they do?
I do; I have a girlfriend,
but I still came.
Is that bad?
Will you just shut up!
Yeah, idiot!
Maybe we should order drinks
to start off with, kay?
Yeah, I'll have a beer!
Same for me!
All right.
From what I could
hear next door.
Well it's a mixer.
A mixer?
What is that?
Mixing things?
You're adorable, Tomoe.
You sit there
acting like Don Juan,
but you don't know
what a mixer is.
I shall tell you.
A mixer is where fervent men
and women who have never before
met get together,
lusting for a sumptuous feast.
Isn't that right?
No it's not; shut up.
Why would anyone
in their right mind do that?
And who the hell are you?
My name's Mizuki.
I'm Nanami's familiar.
Nice to meet you, Tengu.
Do you have any idea why Nanami
would attend this bizarre event?
Oh.
Probably to get a little wild.
Tre' natural for
someone her age.
Surrounded by
yokai and spirits,
maybe she wanted to fool around
with humans for a change.
Hot, hot, hot, hot, hot, hot!
This is good.
Don't you think?
Yeah.
I've never had
anything here I didn't like.
This is my first time
at one of these places.
You mean, you've never
gone to karaoke before?
No.
My girl is getting
over a broken heart.
She's in the market
for a new boyfriend,
so I thought
I'd bring her along.
That's not entirely true.
There's something in my bag!
A snake!
Mizuki!
What in the world do you
think you're doing here?
I don't know about this world,
and you were off to have fun
in it, I just wanted
to see what was going on.
Did you come here on your own?
Don't tell me.
Sorry about that.
It seems precious Mizuki
got away from me and set out
to become a nuisance.
Where did you come from?
And what the heck
are you even doing here?
You were behaving strangely,
so I came to check
on you out of concern.
Crap!
He was watching me!
Apparently, though.
That concern was unjustified.
Not to worry.
We are leaving, so,
have a good time.
Oh, of course.
I was only flirting with
a group of random guys.
That's not something
Tomoe would care about.
I'm so dumb.
It's not like I'm even
doing anything bad.
But I still feel guilty.
Hey, Nanami.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I'm fine.
It seems so stupid.
It really is nothing.
I was just having
a little flashback to
when my heart got broken.
Yeah, I feel ya.
Been there, done that.
I bet the mixer didn't help.
Wanna stay out here a while?
It's a nice night.
Yeah, that sounds good to me.
Thanks for letting me
borrow your jacket.
It's no big deal.
Well, thanks anyway;
you're a really nice guy.
Although, at first you did
have me a little worried.
What?
That's not good.
Especially since I thought
you were the prettiest girl
in there when I first saw you.
You have very soft hands.
Would you mind
if I held your hand.
Ow!
What the hell?
Oh, sorry.
It seems precious Mizuki
was being a nuisance again.
Okay, wow, well, I'll
just go back inside!
Why does he always
have to show up and catch
me in something awkward?
Weren't you making
yourselves scarce?
What happened?
He probably thinks I was trying
to mess around with that guy
or something.
I may have told you
to enjoy yourself.
But I did not say you could
canoodle with a punk like him.
What?
Uh, we were not canoodling.
It wasn't like that.
Do you honestly believe what's
going on with her is nothing?
We are going home.
Well, wait a minute!
I can't just leave
without saying goodbye.
I let them know you would be
going home without them.
What?
I have our ride set down
at a nearby park.
Today is a weekend, so I imagine
the buses stop running early.
My arm, it hurts.
I can't break free.
Tomoe.
I wonder.
Are you irritated?
You have to be.
And it's because I was
with a boy, isn't it?
You are so irritated!
Shut up!
Please don't say anything.
This feels good, so I'm just
going to believe that it's true.
But really, I can't
leave without saying
anything to everyone.
I have to return
this jacket, too.
I was cold, so.
Well, you go on
ahead without me.
I'll catch up soon.
It is exactly as you said.
I'm irritated.
Like a child.
Clearly, I am not as indifferent
as most would believe me to be.
From where I'm standing it
seems like he might be hesitant
or unsure about something.
Maybe though, maybe that's
just what I want to see.
Unless.
Unless it means.
How long have you been
standing there, you creep?
What are you talking about?
I've been here the whole time.
Unless, it means.
He has feelings for me.
Meanwhile, Kurama was thoroughly
enjoying his time on stage.
In order to learn from Kurama
to blend with human's,
Mizuki goes into town.
He's forced to buy weird
stickers, frightened by
a scary man, hassled
by a producer, and--.
Oh, dear, Mizuki, are you okay?
Next time, "The Familiar
Goes Into Town".
And Nanami goes on
a date with Tomoe!