Nanami Momozono.
High school student.
This girl is hardly
more than a child.
How did she become god
of the Mikage Shrine?
Where has Mikage gone?
His whereabouts have been
unknown for twenty years now.
Unknown?
Will you give me Tomoe, please?
Um, I think no.
He refuses to give me Tomoe,
and then he disappears
for twenty years?
You have to feel sorry
for poor Tomoe.
How awful to serve a human.
This is unforgivable!
Nanami Momozono.
Whether you are a human
worthy of being a god or not.
I, Lady Narukami,
god of thunder--Shall
take your measure, myself!
Oh, my, seven lightening
strikes to the east.
Narukami must be having
another one of her tantrums.
It is growing closer and closer.
By the looks of it,
she is heading this way.
I can't believe I overslept!
Tomoe!
Why didn't you wake me up?
I'm gonna be late now!
Are you ready for breakfast?
We are having rice porridge.
I have added a thick
Yoshino sauce to it...
Sorry!
Don't have time to eat!
Hold it.
You are leaving without your
lunch, and your head gear.
Your point?
Just put it on!
I'm not going there to fight!
I go to school to learn,
you big freak!
There is a visitor
coming to the shrine today.
Therefore, I cannot
step away from here.
To be honest,
I am worried for you.
You must face it.
You are as weak as a wee bug.
I'm going.
Nanami!
Why does he have
to worry so much?
Looks like we might
be in for some rain.
Darling Nanami's training
as a god and life at school
are both going swimmingly!
Or at least we'd all really
like for that to happen.
Instead, a storm's a brewin'.
I heard Kurama
isn't feeling well,
so he's not coming to school.
What?
Lady Nanami!
What the crap?
You guys?
Down.
Why are you in my bag?
We are here on
Master Tomoe's orders.
We will-o-the-wisps shall
guard you and make sure
you are safe as safe can be.
Hey, uh, Nanami?
They're just kids.
It's not what you think!
So is Tomoe not
coming to school today?
What?
I-um-- Oh yeah, he's not.
No sir.
Not today.
There is no need for you
to worry, Lady Nanami!
Normal people do not
have the ability to see us!
How very odd.
I thought Narukami was
surely headed this way but
the rainclouds have
passed completely.
Perhaps I was
worried for nothing.
The clouds have moved in the
direction of Nanami's school.
Surely not.
Thanks!
You guys saved me by bringing
my lunch along with you!
Delicious!
Was Mister Mikage like a
food lover or something?
All the meals Tomoe
makes me are so good!
Oh, no.
Neither we, nor gods, are in the
habit of partaking of meals.
You must because your body
is of flesh and blood.
In spite of how it may seem,
Master Tomoe studies daily
as he devotes himself
to cooking for you.
I had no clue.
Oh, yes.
Master Tomoe thinks of you first
in all things at all times.
To be honest,
I am worried for you.
Whatever.
There is no way that's true.
But it is true.
Master Tomoe's
regard for you is--
Hey!
You're not supposed
to tease a girl like that!
You are Nanami Momozono?
A yokai?
Oh no!
I've erected a barrier.
We shall not be disturbed.
The four of us might as well
be the only ones here.
I am a god who maintains
a shrine in the heavens.
The Lady Narukami,
god of thunder.
I have heard of the events
which led to your
becoming a land god.
Tis a grave responsibility.
And to have it thrust
upon you like it was--
That must have been
so difficult for you.
Never fear, darling.
Your newfound troubles shall
come to an end this very day.
Troubles?
I, Lady Narukami,
shall take over the
Mikage shrine in your stead.
Oh no.
You've got it all wrong.
I'm not troubled by anything.
I mean, I have the
will-o-the-wisps and Tomoe.
They're wonderful to me.
I actually think of the
shrine as my home now.
You're very kind.
I don't wanna leave
the shrine, though.
Oh, but that is unacceptable!
Nanami!
Tomoe!
Are you all right?
As expected, you have come.
Master Tomoe!
Lady Nanami is in trouble!
Very well.
Why are you here, Narukami?
Let her go.
Can you not see she is scared?
Remember, she is my
lady and mistress.
A weak little girl like this
is your lady and mistress?
How sad.
What should I do?
Oh, crap!
I find it irritating to see
you subordinating yourself
to a mere human.
It is none of your business!
I expected this as well.
That is the reason I
borrowed the Lucky Mallet
from Lord Daikokuten.
Here we go!
Time to grow smaller, Tomoe!
What?
Tomoe!
And you are next.
Mikage's mark.
It belongs to me, forthwith.
And with that done, you
are no longer a land god.
Go and live your life, human.
You may now do so as befits
someone in your humble position.
Goodbye, dear.
Tomoe, no!
Tomoe, if that small
size does not suit you,
come to the shrine.
If you will become my familiar,
I shall restore you at once.
You'll be okay.
Hold on!
Now, will-o-the-wisps,
show me the way immediately.
Yes, ma'am.
Lady Nanami,
we are so very sorry.
But we are spirits
of the shrine.
We have no choice but to serve
our new lady and mistress.
I hope you both have
a wonderful day.
Well, this is great.
We're both homeless now.
I'm sorry.
I don't have any money.
And Tomoe's so tiny.
I have no idea what to do.
It is simple; you should
do as you please.
This is the world
of humans, is it not?
As a human, you will find a
place for yourself in no time
at all if you put
your mind to it.
As for me, I do not
have the ability
to look after you anymore.
Tomoe!
Are you all right?
He has a terrible fever!
What do I do?
Tomoe?
Oh, what do I do?
I'm such an idiot.
Tomoe's not human, so even if
I could get him to a doctor,
what's the point?
He's so hot.
At the very least,
I need to find a place
where he can sleep safely.
Nanami?
What are you doing out
in weather like this?
Hey.
Hold on.
What happened to
your land god's mark?
He's turned into an awfully
cute little thing, hasn't he?
I know you had
to stay home
because you
weren't feeling well.
I'm sorry for
barging in on you.
Not feeling well?
Oh, that was just
an excuse to miss class.
Our school is less than
sympathetic to the plight
of this talented pop star
and the work he must do.
Although, in all fairness,
they've probably never had
someone quite as famous
as yours truly enrolled
at their school before.
Hey, you're a tengu yokai,
aren't you?
Look, I spent a lot of time
convincing people I was
a fallen angel,
so why bring that up?
Because--
I wanted to find
a yokai doctor.
I'm afraid that
won't help much.
He's been regressed
in body only.
So, his original yokai
powers can't settle in.
They're out of his control and
that's what's causing his fever.
Then--
He won't get better unless
he's restored to his old body.
If you will become my familiar,
I shall restore you at once.
This'll only be temporary
fix, but it's worth a shot.
It's an old secret remedy that's
been passed down in my family.
Here you go.
Be warned, it's bitter as hell.
Say "Ah".
And maybe try being a little
grateful to me for this pill,
fox.
Tomoe.
What a relief.
He seems to be resting easier.
Please let him get better.
Here, you can have
a bamboo-leaf rice cake.
Yukiji.
Thank you.
Tomoe!
Oh good!
You're finally awake!
I was so worried!
Are you thirsty?
Is there anything
I can get you?
Bamboo-leaf rice cake.
I would like some.
Kurama!
I need your kitchen
and some money!
Money?
So.
You mean you actually know how
to make bamboo-leaf rice cake?
My mother used to make it for
me when I was a little girl.
I'm honored.
He's never asked me
for a single thing.
I couldn't be
happier to make it.
I hope you like it, Tomoe.
After all, I made
them just for you!
Average.
I guess he's normal
Tomoe on the inside.
Nanami.
Yeah?
I am grateful.
No prob.
You're welcome.
Yeah, I think I have a virus.
I won't be at school today.
It is raining!
The roof is leaking everywhere!
What kind of
pathetic shrine is this?
We are so very sorry.
Master Tomoe had been
maintaining it with
his yokai powers and now,
without him, the shrine has
reverted back to
its original state.
Of course.
I do not know why I believed
that fox would ever give up
and come running back here.
Attention, please.
Bring me Tomoe!
As you wish!
What is this?
It's fuzzy, but
tickles at the same time.
Kurama!
What the?
Who's calling?
Why was I sleeping with you?
I'm not gonna not sleep in my
bed, so if you don't like that.
Sleep on the couch.
So, Tomoe can still
sleep in the bed, then?
Yeah, like hell!
Damn fox.
He can sleep on the floor.
You're a different story.
I don't mind you in my bed.
I will kill you fox.
I will kill you!
I think we just fell
asleep after that!
What kind of a girl
does that make me?
Remember, he is a yokai.
Tomoe!
How do you feel?
Try to be on your
guard a little.
What did you say about me, fox?
Oh, is the little boy going
wakey-wakey already?
It looks like your teething
fever hasn't gone down, yet.
Don't be so rough
with him, okay!
Getting a girl to come to
your defense like that.
Not bad, Tomoe.
You are the reason she's in my
house in the first place.
Remember that.
He has the right of it.
What pains me is not the fever.
This is so irritating.
We have to get Tomoe
back to normal.
If he became tiny because
of the Lucky Mallet.
You'll most likely have
to use the same device
to make him bigger.
You need to get your
hands on that mallet.
Do you think you can
get it from Lady Narukami?
Oh my, look at the time.
Where are you going?
Rehearsal for
a live performance.
Oh.
Right.
Well, someone looks
awfully forlorn.
What?
No, I don't.
I look fine.
Here's the spare key to my house
along with my phone number.
And some money.
If anything happens,
give me a call.
Oh.
Wow, thank you.
Tomoe.
I'm gonna go run
a couple of errands.
Is there anything you
need me to pick up?
Did you hear me?
I shall go.
I feel fine now.
The reason I feel irritated
is because of this body.
So what about your school?
Oh.
It's Saturday; no school today.
Getting you back to normal
is more important anyway.
You should think
about yourself.
I shall take care
of my own affairs.
You shall?
I don't know how you can.
You're way too tiny.
You have been restored
to your human self.
You should live as a human.
I can and will
live as I please.
Tomoe.
I wonder if he's planning
to go to Narukami.
Oh, no, Tomoe!
Your fever's gotten worse!
Master Tomoe!
We have been searching for you!
We have come to escort
you back, Master Tomoe.
Lady Narukami is terribly
concerned for your well
being and is awaiting
your return at the shrine.
After what she did to Tomoe,
she has some nerve saying
that she's concerned.
Tomoe and I are like family,
and we've been driven away
from our home together!
It doesn't matter if
I'm human and he's a yokai.
I'm gonna find a way
to take care of him.
There is no way
for that to happen.
You are incapable
of doing anything.
Face it.
Tomoe?
To live life burdening
you----the thought enrages me.
You there, lion-dogs.
Take me to the shrine.
Yes, sir.
You're leaving?
Are you serious?
I believe what pains me more
than anything is being seen
by her while I am in
this pathetic state.
Farewell, then, Nanami.
Tomoe, you're such a jerk!
Oh, dear.
They split right on up.
Tragic.
What now?
Oh, Tomoe, I feel as though
I have been waiting for you
to show up now forever and ever.
I already know, so no
explanation needed.
And in the end, well,
you had nowhere else to go
other than this shrine.
If you have nowhere else to go.
You can stay with
me at my shrine.
Now, offer up your
whole life to me.
Is it not exciting?
You get to become my personal
possession for all time!
Now seal the contract
and be my familiar!
Are you mocking me?
Tomoe, get back
here immediately!
Nanami?
Well, well.
You've got quite the
honor guard here for you.
Honor guard?
Forget about it.
What are you doing sitting out
here like this?
I was waiting for you.
I wanted to say thank you.
Tomoe went back to the shrine.
I guess he decided to be
Narukami's familiar.
I tried but I
couldn't stop him.
You are incapable
of doing anything.
I--I couldn't do anything.
Oh stop.
There's no point crying over
a little thing like that.
Hey!
I am not crying.
And what do you mean
by a little thing?
All right.
Here's a parting gift for you,
since you've gone
back to being human.
By having a physical piece
of a yokai, you can see all
of the things that are
invisible to the human eye
that you might be missing.
Like what?
Lady Nanami!
Onikiri, Kotetsu, you, too?
When'd you get here?
They've both been crying next
to you this whole time.
We are in dreadful trouble!
Master Tomoe has evaded Lady
Narukami and hidden somewhere
in the shrine!
It has greatly
angered the Lady, too.
At this rate, she is
practically ready to destroy us,
shrine and all!
Lady Nanami, please save
Master Tomoe and the shrine!
We need you!
You are incapable
of doing anything.
Face it.
'Kay, let's go!
We have the Night Fog
Carriage waiting.
Come, please get on.
Your feather.
Can I borrow it?
I have plenty of feathers.
You can have it.
Thank you.
We still cannot find him!
The attic!
The basement!
We searched for him everywhere!
Curse you, Tomoe.
Try to make a fool
out of me will you?
If that's what you want,
then fine!
I have no need for
this rundown shrine.
I shall burn it to cinders!
Hey, god lady!
What kind of
twisted god goes out
and tries to destroy
her own shrine?
Oh, great.
What are you doing here?
If you're looking for Tomoe,
he has hidden.
Oh yeah, well.
If you let me,
I could find him easily.
But that is up to you.
You are a mere human; you
could not possibly find him!
Maybe, but let's say that I do.
You would have to swear to me,
that you'd turn him
back to normal.
All right, I swear.
Then sit back,
and I'll find him.
I can't find him.
Poor Tomoe.
If he still has that fever, he
might be passed out somewhere.
Lady Nanami?
Here?
Oh.
That is Lord Mikage's
pocket mirror.
I can feel him from
inside the mirror.
Tomoe's body heat.
It's so hot.
There he is.
Tomoe.
Let's go home.
Hiding within a
silly mirror belonging
to the previous land god.
That is quite the
show of faithfulness.
If you will not be mine,
I do not want you.
Farewell.
Good for you!
The shrine was so dilapidated,
she did not want it.
And so, it is up to us
to deliver the Mallet,
and the Mark!
Cut the bull crap!
Why won't she face us herself?
At any rate,
we shall return the mark.
My body; I'm glowing.
With that, the mark of the land
god is yours again, Lady Nanami.
Swing the Mallet
at Tomoe, please.
Then at the same time say
to him "Grow bigger."
That is your job, Lady Nanami.
Grow bigger, Tomoe!
I am restored.
It appears your hair has
grown at the same time.
What is wrong?
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
Why am I feeling
this way about him?
Wow, it looks like
the rain's let up!
It let up!
It totally let up!
Wow that is just so awesome.
Like so awesome.
It seems I owe you.
That's right.
You do!
You have my thanks.
The contract between
us is resealed.
I think that was his
way of his promising
we would always be together.
Nanami has ended up catching
a cold, so Tomoe disguises
himself as her and goes
to school in her stead.
And that is when
Kurama makes his move.
Meanwhile, Mizuki
comes to see Nanami.
Next time, "The God
Catches a Cold" Achoo!