[bell ringing]
[PERFORMER 8A]
Earth and water might impede us
in our escape from this
wretched labyrinth prison.
But, the sky is free!
You see, even in
the darkest depths,
there remains a glimmer of hope.
Oh, Father.
You've built such
splendid wings.
But will they carry my weight?
Can I soar freely?
Above everything?
My Icarus. You must
listen to me.
Freedom can addle the mind,
bring delusions and fears,
and arrogance can
lead one to death.
Even the birds fly with...
[AYANOKOJI] Now, this is an
egregious waste of tax dollars.
A few days ago, a man, whose
name I won't mention to you,
contacted the school.
"You must expel Kiyotaka
Ayanokoji immediately," he said.
Well now, I wonder what
his angle might have been.
I hope I'm not supposed
to know who it was.
But we both know
you can't expel me
without good reason.
You're right.
As long as you remain
a student at this school,
the rules protect you
from that injustice.
Of course, if you were
to cause any trouble...
That's a different
matter altogether.
[applause]
[PERFORMER 8B]
Watch me, Father!
[AYANOKOJI]
Sorry to inform you.
But, unlike our
arrogant hero, Icarus.
I do not intend to
challenge the sun.
[PERFORMER 8B]
The sun. It's so near!
Your intentions are
irrelevant in this case.
If I decide that you've
become a problem,
then a problem is what you are.
Is that a threat?
Because it sounds like one.
Not a threat; it's a trade.
If you don't wanna get expelled,
then try to ascend to Class A.
And as long as you do your best,
I will cover for
you, unilaterally.
A good deal by
anyone's standards.
[PERFORMER 8A]
Icarus!
Maybe, but I'm not
going to take it.
[CHABASHIRA]
In that case, Ayanokoji.
You're going to lose
all of your freedom.
You're going to be expelled.
[PERFORMER 8A]
Gods of Olympus.
I beg of you,
put a curse upon me!
How dare you.
You call yourself a teacher?
It would be wise to make
your decision with haste.
Will you try to make it to Class
A, or will you get expelled?
[PERFORMER 8A]
Curse me! I beg of you!
[applause]
Trying to manipulate me
is not gonna work.
You're going to
regret your actions.
Don't worry about me.
My life is so
filled with regrets
that one more won't hurt.
[AYANOKOJI]
Throw away my freedom,
to protect my freedom?
[IKE]
The eternal summer ocean!
The wide blue yonder!
On a ship, in the
middle of the Pacific!
Now this is what I call
cruise paradise!
[KARUIZAWA]
Look at that view!
Makes your heart race and
steals your breath, doesn't it?
It truly is an incredible sight!
Aren't you glad you didn't
get expelled after all?
Yeah. This trip
feels like a dream.
I can't believe
we go to a school
that's so generous they
take us on a nice cruise
for no reason at all!
Yeah!
[AYANOKOJI] The luxury
cruise ship Speranza .
[AYANOKOJI] Onboard, you'll
find a four-star restaurant.
A live theatre venue.
Pools and other various
amusement facilities.
There's even a first-class spa.
[AYANOKOJI]
If I were to purchase a ticket
as a private citizen,
it would cost me a
few hundred thousand.
Wow!
We can borrow any of these
cute swimsuits for free?
[MIT]
Hey, Kikyo!
Wouldn't this bikini
look so fierce on you?
Um, it's a little revealing,
don't you think?
[MIT]
Aw, come on, we're on vacation.
Live a little!
[MIT] Heads up, Kikyo!
Coming at ya now!
Got it!
[KIKYO giggles]
[IKE]
I'm doing it.
I'm finally gonna tell
Kushida how I feel!
What?! A-Are you serious?
[IKE] If I don't, I'll regret it
for the rest of my life.
Can't have that.
[KEN]
Ike.
Go do it, then.
Okay! Here goes nothin'!
So, what is it? You okay?
I was wondering.
[KIKYO]
Hm?
May...
May... May... May...
May I please have
the extreme honor
of calling you by
your given name?
[gasps]
Well. Please don't
keep me waiting.
Would you allow me
to call you Kikyo?
Yes, but only if you allow me
to call you Kanji, in return!
[gasps]
[KIKYO]
Uh, Kanji?
[IKE yells]
[IKE]
Kikyo! Kikyo!
Kanji, please!
Whaddaya know. He pulled it off.
[AYANOKOJI] All he did was
call her by her first name.
Ayanokoji!
You've got to tell me
Horikita's given name!
Huh?
Tell me Horikita's first
name right this second,
or I'll go crazy!
I think it's Suzune.
Suzune. It's beautiful. Lovely.
All right!
I'm gonna go find her
and call her Suzune.
Hi, Suzune.
Suzune, can you talk for a sec?
Suzune, you wanna
take a walk with me?
[YAMAUCHI] Airi. Airi. Airi.
Airi. Airi. Airi. Airi.
What is their problem?
This is weird.
Heh. I'm beautiful.
Whoa, is this place
free to everyone, too?
Do ya think they would
send us a bill for it later?
[YAMAUCHI] Well, people from all
the other classes are eating,
so it's probably fine.
[AYANOKOJI] I think we
should go somewhere else.
Okay, where should we go?
[SERVER 8A]
Welcome.
Would you gentlemen
like a table for four?
[GROUP]
Uh. Sure.
Hey, what kind of food
is this, anyway.
Look, they have French:
"Fro-mage de teh-teh?"
With a delicate,
aromatic herb reduction?
Look. No worries.
Let's just order whatever,
'kay? Hey, over here!
[YAMAUCHI]
S'cuse me!
Can we order some food already?
Hey, dudes!
[AYANOKOJI]
Let's get out of here.
[YAHIKO] You're all from
Class D, aren't you?
Yeah. And what about it, buddy?
A bit of advice.
This fine establishment isn't
intended for garbage like you.
What?!
Trashy people should
be eating trashy food.
Get yourselves some
burgers and fries.
What the hell do you
have against burgers,
you little punk!
[KATSURAGI]
Yahiko.
Cease with these
ridiculous provocations now.
But, Katsuragi...
[KATSURAGI] Despite the fact
that we're on vacation,
we could still lose points
for unsavory behavior.
Please conduct
yourself in a manner
befitting a Class A student.
Uh. Yes, sir.
You lot would also do well
to mind your manners,
and stop being a nuisance
to those around you.
Huh? What did we do, exactly?
[STUDENT 8A]
Isn't that Ken Sudo?
Uh--
[STUDENT 8G]
He's the one who assaulted
those poor guys from Class B.
[STUDENT 8H]
He's got crazy eyes!
I hear he's actually
killed people.
Really?
[KEN]
Gimme a break, you guys!
Repeating your mistakes?
Do you intend to get yourself
into trouble again?
Don't get worked up. Let's go.
[AYANOKOJI]
Katsuragi, from Class A.
[HOSHINOMIYA moaning]
[sighs]
[HOSHINOMIYA]
Yeah, there we go.
Um, Ms. Hoshinomiya?
[HOSHINOMIYA]
Sorry, sorry. Go on.
You were saying?
[ICHINOSE] I think Sakayanagi
and Katsuragi from Class A,
and also Ryuen from Class C--
they're the ones we should
be keeping an eye on.
[HOSHINOMIYA]
And what about in Class D?
[ICHINOSE] Well, Horikita
and Hirata, for sure.
[HOSHINOMIYA] I feel like
there's someone else
from Class D, too, though.
[ICHINOSE]
I've heard rumors that Koenji
has really good grades,
and his athletic abilities
are apparently amazing,
but I don't know.
[HOSHINOMIYA]
No, it wasn't Koenji.
I know that much.
Are you thinking of Ayanokoji?
[HOSHINOMIYA] Yeah!
There's something about him.
My gut says to watch out.
He's on my list for sure.
But, Ms. Hoshinomiya,
I can't just go on
your gut instincts alone.
You're such a meanie!
A few days ago,
a man I won't mention,
contacted the school.
"You must expel Kiyotaka
Ayanokoji immediately," he said.
[doorbell rings]
Hirata?
Sorry. Did I wake you up?
No.
Good, I'm glad.
I'm about to go
hang out with Karuizawa
and a couple of her friends,
so do you wanna come with me?
Karuizawa?
I'll pass, thanks.
I don't really know her,
or any of her friends,
now that I actually
think about it.
This might be
a good opportunity.
No better time than the present.
[AYANOKOJI] Does he honestly
care about my social life
that much? Or is it
something else?
[gasps]
Ayanokoji.
The truth of it is,
there's something
I wanted to ask you
to help me with.
You want my help?
[HIRATA] Would you be willing
to act as a liaison
for me and Horikita?
I think if we want
to unite Class D
and make progress,
well, she'll be an integral
player in making that happen.
[AYANOKOJI]
So that's what this is about.
I've heard she's great.
That she's the one who
proved Sudo's innocence,
and that was no small feat.
If we could work togeth--
[phone rings]
[AYANOKOJI]
Shouldn't you answer that?
[HIRATA] Sorry. I guess
I'd better get going.
If you change your
mind and wanna join,
just call me and I'll let
you know where we are.
I'll do that.
Cool, later, then.
Hello?
Sorry. I'm on my way.
[SERVER 9B]
Sir! Please wait!
We'd prefer that you
dry off before
walking on the carpet
if you don't mind!
[laughs] Sorry to
break protocol,
but I've never toweled
off after swimming
in my entire life.
Sir, please listen to me!
So, would you say that I am,
"dripping with beauty"
or "manliness"?
[laughs] Beautiful!
[SERVER 9B]
Sir, I'm begging you!
[KOENJI grunts]
This is exactly what I deserve.
You sure got here quickly.
I did. What did
you summon me for?
To ask you a question.
Do you believe they'd
just give us a holiday?
[AYANOKOJI] I'm sure there's
some kind of catch.
[SUZUNE]
Go on.
I think we're
heading to an island.
The school owns it,
and there's a boarding house
on it big enough for
all the first-years.
When we get there...
We can't let our guard
down for a minute.
They're watching us.
[RYUEN] It would appear that
I have found you at last.
[RYUEN] You set up decoy
cameras in the special annex.
That was a clever little
prank you pulled, missy.
Sorry, I don't know who you are.
There's a special
place in my heart
for women like you, Suzune.
I don't know how you
accessed that information,
but I've never given you
permission to use my given name.
That's a nice expression.
I think it's incredibly sexy.
Like I said, I don't know you,
and I don't want to.
I find your presence
repulsive at best.
I'm just one of
your devoted fans.
How dare you!
Next time, I'll deal
with you personally.
I'm so looking forward to it.
[IBUKI]
Ryuen!
[RYUEN]
Oh, Ibuki, it's you.
I need to have a talk
with you right now.
Heh, heh.
Missed me so much
you had to see me?
Don't be ridiculous!
I'm fed up with
the way you operate,
and I won't stand for it!
I see. That's all right.
We can talk about it
later in my room.
Just you and me.
[gasps]
[IBUKI]
Albert!
You're going along with this?
I see you've officially
become Ryuen's guard dog.
Get back here right now, Ryuen!
I'm not finished talking to you!
Let me go!
[groans]
That's enough.
[AYANOKOJI]
Hey. Are you okay?
It's none of your damn business.
[sighs] Class C seems to be
on the verge of collapse.
[KAMURO]
That's my full report.
I hope it's enough.
Thank you for all of your
thorough and diligent
work, Ms. Masumi.
[KAMURO]
What should I focus on now?
[SAKAYANAGI]
Good question.
I want you to investigate
some students.
[KAMURO]
Which ones?
That's check.
So that's what
I've been thinking.
How do you feel?
Um, would you ever want,
well, um, want to d--
d-date--
Sakura?
[screams]
What's wrong?
Um. Hi. Uh.
How long have you
been standing there?
I literally just got here.
Did you...
Did you hear what I
said before you spoke?
[AYANOKOJI]
No.
[sighs] Thank goodness.
[AYANOKOJI]
Why?
[gasps] Oh, um, I just...
Uh...
Is something going on with you?
No! No.
Nothing bad is going on
with me, exactly.
But I'm having trouble
making conversation
with our other classmates.
So, I'm sorry for asking
for your help with it.
[AYANOKOJI]
Don't be sorry.
[gasps]
If you just need
someone to listen,
that's something
I'm happy to do.
Thank you so much!
Sure.
It's not like it's
that big of a deal.
[KIKYO] Huh? Is that
Ayanokoji and Sakura?
See you later.
I'm going back to my room.
[KIKYO gasps]
Wait, come back!
I'm sorry.
I wanted to say hi, but I
should have left you two alone.
'S cool.
[AYANOKOJI] I guess Sakura
still hasn't overcome
her fear of strangers.
[KIKYO gasps]
What a beautiful, starry sky!
Right? It's pretty.
Don't you think so?
[AYANOKOJI] When Kushida
displays behavior like this,
it's easy to forget.
She was like a different
person that night.
Well, I'd better
get back to my room.
Are you done for
the night already?
Yeah, I'm gettin' very sleepy.
Sounds good.
I guess I'll see
you tomorrow, then.
Have a good night!
Yeah, thanks, same to you.
Hold on.
Kushida?
You're wary of me
now, aren't you?
I knew you were.
I can always sense
that sort of thing.
Sorry.
When people leave me all
by myself, I get kind of lonely.
I thought that maybe you were...
Never mind, it's nothing.
Forget about it!
[PA dings]
[ANN]
Good morning, students!
Time to rise and shine!
Our island destination
will soon be in view!
We hope you'll take
a few minutes to bask
in the sight of this highly
significant scenery.
Don't let the moment
pass you by!
Significant scenery?
Dang! Get a load of it!
Good morning! Isn't
this so exciting?
Yeah. Good morning.
It's simply breathtaking.
Don't you think it's
beautiful, too, Ayanokoji?
[AYANOKOJI]
The usual Kushida.
By the way, have you seen
Horikita this morning?
Why ask?
I thought she would be with you.
I haven't.
She doesn't quite
seem like the type
to revel in a vacation.
So she's probably in her room.
I bet you're right.
As we make preparations
to disembark on the island.
We'll brief you on
what you can expect
once we dock.
Until then, you're
required to wait here.
It's so hot. I wish
they'd speed things up.
Have you been in your room?
Yes. I was reading, what of it?
It was extremely engaging, too.
But, since we're
not allowed to bring
our personal belongings,
I won't get to finish.
Anyway, what is this?
We'll confiscate
your student IDs.
In their place, you will
wear these wristwatches.
Those who take them
off without permission
will be severely penalized.
They're all acting
especially cautious.
Like they're on high alert.
I agree.
I can't imagine
they'd go this far
if we were just here for
a little fun on the beach.
I'm Mashima, the
instructor for Class A.
To begin with, I'd like
to express my gratitude
that we all made it
to the island.
Almost all of us.
One of you won't be able to
join because of an illness,
and that's a real shame.
Without further ado,
I'm glad to announce
the beginning
of this year's
special examination.
Huh?
Special examination?
The duration of the
test is one week.
You'll live as a group
on the picturesque
desert island you
see before you.
You are your own responsibility
from here on out,
so you're expected
to behave accordingly.
Now! The test
of survival begins!
[AYANOKOJI]
Looks like vacation's over.