[bell ringing]
Ah! Hey, stop splashing me!
Couldn't help myself.
It doesn't hurt
to have some fun!
Fine. Bring it on!
[AYANOKOJI]
Ah, free time during swim class.
People have naturally
broken up into groups,
which makes sense, I guess.
It's official.
I have utterly failed
at making friends.
I'm destined to be a loner.
[sighs]
[SUZUNE] What are you
brooding about over here?
Oh, I was just embroiled in
a painful internal struggle.
How can these losers
even enjoy themselves?
You'd think that they
would be more deflated.
Maybe that's how
these guys cope.
They wanna have some fun,
while they still can.
You could be right, I guess.
[KIKYO]
Hey, stop it! [laughs]
[SUZUNE] They sure are
having a good time.
It's early in the spring
for swimming to start,
and they're first years
on a free class period.
It's normal for them to enjoy
themselves, don't you think?
They're like a bunch of
grade school kids.
Although, I suppose I can't
really fault them for it.
But in the S-system,
they're going to suffer
for that attitude.
But aren't you and I
just like them?
Maybe.
[AYANOKOJI]
The S-system...
Indeed, this is called
the S-system.
It evaluates students
in real time,
and assigns numerical value.
Observe. Class D has
thoroughly proven
that you deserve to be
ranked dead last.
You truly are the
worst of the worst.
Zero?
[SUZUNE growls]
[clapping]
However, I am rather
impressed with this class.
Never in the history of this
school has a class blown through
all of their points in the first
month, not even Class D.
Excuse me, will you
at least tell us what
the school's criteria is for
gaining and losing points?
You're preparing for the
real world, so figure it out.
In the workforce, you're
expected to come to the table
knowing what to do.
On the board, I have written
the current scores held
by all first-year classes.
For every point the class
gets, 100 private points
are distributed to each
student individually.
When the school year began,
each first-year class
was allotted 1,000
collective points.
To be frank, you people
lost every point you had.
Teacher. Will we get the
chance to earn any points back?
Of course.
And in doing so, if you earn
more points than Class C
you'll be promoted
up to Class C,
and Class C will be
downgraded to D.
Your earliest opportunity
to do this
is coming up in the midterms.
Depending on your scores,
you can earn as many as
100 points for the class.
A hundred measly points?
Yeah, but it's better
than nothing, right?
[CHABASHIRA]
However...
...these are the grades from
the most recent quiz you took.
And, as you can see,
they are complete garbage.
From this point forward,
anyone who receives
a failing grade
on any midterms or finals will
be expelled immediately.
Considering this most recent
development, everyone in class
is gonna have to completely
change their habits.
And that's only to get us
a few meager points.
So, if everyone doesn't
ace the midterms,
we're all going to
be royally screwed.
That's right.
Even more than that,
if we're going to measure up
and achieve the high college
entry and employment rates
they promised us, we're going
to have to push ourselves
from here on out to
overtake Class C.
Beating Class C has to
be the primary goal now.
'Cause if we can't even do that,
we have no hope of advancing.
Were you just doing an
impression of Chabashira?
No, why?
Sounded like her. A little.
[gasps]
[SUZUNE]
I was wondering.
Do you play sports or something?
No, not at all.
In fact, in middle school,
I did nothing extracurricular.
That makes no sense.
Your forearms are so muscular,
I thought you must.
[KIKYO]
Hey, there, Horikita!
Do you maybe wanna
come swim with us?
Would you please go away?
[KIKYO]
You don't have to be mean.
Are you a bad swimmer
or something?
No, I am an incredibly
average swimmer.
[KIKYO] Back in middle school, I
was probably the worst swimmer
in the whole wide world! But
then I practiced really hard,
and nowadays I don't think
I'm that bad at all!
Wow. That's fascinating.
[AYANOKOJI]
She's totally aloof, isn't she?
I do wish I could find a way
to get along with her better.
[HIRATA]
Hey, guys.
Do you have a minute
to talk about something?
We didn't get any
points again today,
and that has got to change.
I don't want this
problem to haunt us
for the rest of our
time at this school.
We have to do something
to turn this around.
There's no way I want to go
all the way to graduation
without earning any more points.
[KARUIZAWA] I agree,
we can't let that happen!
You're right, and we won't.
We'll turn this around.
Next month, we're going
to get more points
than any other class.
I don't know why you keep
saying, "we," like that.
Seriously. You can
leave me out of it!
[MANABU]
Class D again.
You're both in Class A.
Sakayanagi... and Katsuragi.
[MANABU]
Congratulations are in order.
Your class earned a total
of 940 points this month.
Quite a feat.
I do hope you're both
very proud of yourselves.
[MANABU]
Now, then.
How much do you know
about the S-system?
[YAMAUCHI]
Hey, Doc! You're my best friend.
You gotta help me out!
Buy this console from
me for 20,000 points?
Actually, it's so funny.
I spent all my points
on accessories
so I'm totally broke now.
I was thinking about borrowing
a couple of points from
all the girls in class
to buy the essentials.
You're one of my best
friends, aren't you?
[SUZUNE]
Do you have any plans for lunch?
I was wondering if you would
be able to join me.
[gasps]
[AYANOKOJI]
Well, let's eat, then.
Thank you for the food.
I have to ask...
Are you sure it's okay
that I put this super expensive
lunch on your tab?
I feel awkward.
Yes. I told you to get whatever
you wanted, and I meant it.
Lunch today is my treat.
So don't feel awkward.
[AYANOKOJI]
What now?
Is something wrong
with you, Ayanokoji?
Dig in, already.
Right.
Now, listen, I want you to hear
me out on something important.
I'm aware that
Hirata and the others
worked out a plan of
action earlier today.
They're all forming
a study group.
Their goal is to make sure
they ace the test.
A study group?
[SUZUNE] Yes. But three of our
classmates refused to join,
and it just so happens they're
the ones with the lowest scores.
Sudo, right?
Yes, and Yamauchi
and Ike, as well.
Well, I can't say I'm surprised.
Those three never did strike
me as the studious type.
I don't see how anyone
could fail a test.
Nevertheless, the
fact remains--they did.
There are kids out there who
don't even know what it means
to be a good student.
I guess some people
really are that pathetic.
That's cold. Don't you
have any sympathy?
Would being sympathetic
keep it from being true?
If we don't do something,
they're most likely
going to fail.
And if we want to
overtake Class C,
not only do we have to stop our
class from hemorrhaging points,
but we've also got to do
everything in our power
to start gaining them back.
Are you saying you want
to start a study group, too?
You're willing to
help Sudo, Ike,
and Yamauchi get good
grades on the midterm?
Yes.
Seriously?
Of course. If left to
their own devices,
they'll sink, and bring the
rest of Class D with them.
I may have to be relegated
to the lowest class in school,
but not for long. I will
claw my way up to Class A.
Hey, wait a minute.
What now?
Did you just say you
want to be Class A?
You heard right.
You sure you didn't
mean Class C?
[SUZUNE]
I meant what I said.
I find my assignment to
Class D utterly offensive
and unacceptable.
I intend to change it.
So, step one is to
rehabilitate the failures?
Since you've grasped that,
you can guess what's next.
I'd rather not.
Do you enjoy your lunch?
An extravagant meal like
that doesn't come free.
Even an idiot could see
you're expected to provide
something in return.
And don't think I've forgiven
you for conspiring with
Kushida and taking me to that
café under false pretenses.
That was foul play.
That's not cool.
If you want to make it up to me,
then you'll work with me to
help save the whole class.
Your job will be to round
up those three losers,
and convince them to
join my study group.
Here's my phone
number and email.
All right, contact me if you
need anything along the way,
but don't think you can
reach out whenever you want.
[AYANOKOJI] This is how
I get a girl's number
for the first time in
high school? Pathetic.
I'm not even happy
that she gave it to me,
but I'd better save it, anyway.
[AYANOKOJI]
I guess I have to comply,
even though I technically
never agreed to this.
[AYANOKOJI]
Well. Here goes nothin'.
Leave me alone.
Yeah... no.
The hell'd you say to me, punk?!
I knew it was hopeless.
Maybe I could enlist help from
someone who can get through
to those three. I should have
done that to begin with.
I wonder if she's
home right now.
I can call her room.
[AYANOKOJI] Hi, can you connect
me to Kikyo Kushida's room?
Yes, from Class One-D.
[AYANOKOJI] Yes, it is about
something school-related.
Yes.
[phone rings]
--[blow dryer hums]
--[KIKYO] Um, hello?
Hi, this is... Hold on.
What's that weird noise?
[KIKYO]
Oh, Ayanokoji?
[click]
[KIKYO] Sorry, was it too loud?
I just got out of the bath.
I was blow-drying my
hair, sorry about that.
You caught me a
little off-guard.
I've never used the dorm's
internal land line before,
so I was startled.
[AYANOKOJI]
I'm amazed you answered.
Anyway, rejoice, Kushida.
I've selected you as a
good will ambassador.
It's for the good of the class,
so I know you'll do your best.
[gasps] What do you mean? Uh...
[KIKYO]
Right. Wow.
A second study group for
Sudo, Ike, and Yamauchi?
Run by Horikita, herself?
Well, when a friend needs help,
I always answer the call,
no matter what it might be.
I'll do whatever it takes!
[AYANOKOJI]
You don't have to, you know.
I think it's cruel that
anyone who fails
gets expelled immediately.
The thought of having to say
goodbye so soon, especially
after we just got to know each
other? I mean, that's awful.
Oh! I do have one request.
In exchange for
helping you guys,
I want to join the
study group, too.
Would that be okay?
Uh, are you sure
that's all you want?
[KIKYO] Yeah! I want to help
the cause in any way.
Let's see... Oh!
Why don't I give you
my cell phone number
so you can contact me whenever,
instead of just when
I'm in my room.
[AYANOKOJI]
You're cool with that?
Yeah! I mean, we're
classmates, right?
Sorry I didn't give it
to you until now.
I just didn't think of it.
You can reach out
anytime you want.
I've got Kushida's phone number.
[phone chimes]
Uh? Wow, she works
like lightning.
Good job, Kushida.
[AYANOKOJI]
And... sent.
[AYANOKOJI gasps]
--Hel--?
--[SUZUNE] No.
[beeping]
[ringing]
Can you at least hear
me out for a minute--?
[beeping]
[phone chimes]
[ringing]
[gasps]
[AYANOKOJI sighs]
Are you kidding me?
What do you mean "what"?
I thought I was being
perfectly clear.
You should be glad.
All three of them have agreed
to come to the study group,
including Sudo!
Thanks to Kushida, your
little plan just might work.
[AYANOKOJI]
I hadn't even sent that yet!
[KIKYO] I understand.
Is that her final word?
[AYANOKOJI] Yeah. Even after
you helped make it happen.
I'm really sorry.
[KIKYO grunts]
Right! It's okay!
You just let me handle her
from here on out.
[bang]
[KEN]
Call me incompetent again!
Well, if you don't know
how to solve a simple
simultaneous equation, I
don't know how to proceed.
I shudder to think of what
the future holds for you.
[KEN growls]
Sudo, stop!
Who needs algebra, anyway?
When am I ever gonna
use it, huh?
If I wanted to prepare for
my future, I'm better off
playing basketball to get ready
for a career in the pros,
not sticking my
nose in some book.
Really?
Delusional.
You playing pro basketball?
Do you even have an inkling
of how difficult it is
to get to that level?
It requires commitment and
dedication that you sorely lack.
Face it, you don't
have what it takes.
I didn't skip practice to
come here and get insulted.
I knew this was a
waste of my time.
You know what. I'm out, too.
Horikita might be smart, but I
don't want help from someone
so condescending. I'd rather
fail than be treated like crap.
[YAMAUCHI]
Yeah, same here!
If you want to get
expelled, be my guest.
See how much I care.
[AYANOKOJI] I left it to you,
like you said, Kushida,
and look what happened.
Do something.
Look, Horikita. No one's
going to study with you
if you make them feel stupid
when they make a mistake.
Yes, I can acknowledge that
I was wrong about them.
It's clear to me that this
is all a fruitless
waste of my time.
[KIKYO]
What do you mean?
I mean that if those idiots are
going to drag us down with them,
we're better off without.
I say, "good riddance."
I see.
Okay, then. I'll work it
out with them myself.
I promise.
I don't think we should give
up on our friends so soon,
and it'd be sad if those
three got expelled.
I won't abandon them, and I
think you'd rather not, either.
That's why you started this
group in the first place.
If you're being
sincere right now,
then I appreciate
the sentiment. I do.
Tell me, why did
you really agree
to help us in this endeavor?
[KIKYO gasps]
[SUZUNE] Are you just
trying to sabotage me?
I can't believe you.
Do you really think that?
I'm not an underhanded person.
The fact that you would
even assume that about me
makes me feel so sad for you.
It's awful, and I hope you
don't mean all that.
I need to go get
some fresh air.
[MANABU]
Suzune.
I'm amazed you had the
brains to track me down.
[SUZUNE]
Listen, brother.
I'm not the failure
that I was in the past.
I followed you because I want
to prove that I've changed.
[AYANOKOJI] That's Horikita,
but who's she with?
"Brother"?
Prove you've changed?
Hardly. After all this time,
you clearly have
not come to terms
with your own shortcomings.
You're foolish to think you
could succeed here, leave now.
You're wrong! I'm going
to be in Class A soon.
Then you'll see!
Don't bother.
I promise.
I know I can make it.
You're an irrational
little brat.
[AYANOKOJI]
The student council president?
[SUZUNE gasps]
[MANABU] Do you ever stop
to think of the shame you
bring this family? My own
little sister in Class D.
Pathetic.
Withdraw from school if you
know what's good for you.
Brother, please just listen.
[MANABU] You don't have
the right to better yourself,
nor do you have the ability to
do so. Someday you'll learn.
Ayanokoji, don't!
Seriously?
You really were planning
to hurt her, weren't you?
You better let her go, now.
Go away. This doesn't
concern you.
[gasps]
[AYANOKOJI] She sounds like a
completely different person.
[AYANOKOJI]
Close one.
[gasps]
You fight like an expert.
Which of the arts
do you practice?
Piano and calligraphy.
Ah. Now I get it.
I think I know who you are.
I'd heard there was a student
who got 50s on all
of his entrance exams.
The other day, you got a
50 on one of your quizzes
in class, as well.
[gasps]
[MANABU] Are you trying to
make some kind of statement,
scoring exactly half of what
you should at this school?
Wow, that's a
strange coincidence.
[SUZUNE gasping]
[MANABU] You pride yourself
on being unique, I see.
Suzune.
I'm surprised you've
made a friend,
although I assume you
had to bribe him.
You're wrong.
He isn't my friend,
he's just a classmate. I don't
need any friends, you know that.
As usual, your immaturity
is leading you
to mistake isolation
for independence.
Anyway. If you truly
wish to be in a less
humiliating class, you're going
to have to work a lot harder.
I'm sorry you had to
witness all of that.
It's okay.
It was sort of a relief
to see you acting like
a normal girl and
not some kind of--
I didn't even say anything.
I'm impressed by your skills.
It's just piano
and tea ceremony.
You said it was calligraphy.
Yeah, I do calligraphy, too.
How did you doctor your scores
on all of the entrance exams?
Tell the truth.
I told the truth. Coincidence.
I don't get you at all.
You're such a weirdo.
Huh, sure.
So, were you serious about
disbanding the study group?
Yes. It's a waste of my time.
If those losers wanna fail,
that's their prerogative.
It makes no difference to me.
Even though failing would
get them expelled?
I don't care what happens to
anyone but me, and their exit
would motivate the rest
of us to be better.
I don't see a downside
to any of that.
Without them, it will be easier
for our class to advance.
I don't think I could have
asked for a better solution.
That sounds like
flawed thinking.
Maybe you're just
lying to yourself.
[gasps]
[AYANOKOJI]
It's a shortcoming.
You make the assumption that
other people hold you back,
so you always keep them at
an arm's length as a rule.
Have you ever considered that
your isolationist philosophy
might be the very thing that
landed you in Class D
in the first place?
Ridiculous.
[inaudible]
[AYANOKOJI]
And so it went.
Everything looked hopeless.
[AYANOKOJI]
Nevertheless, the day arrived.
And all of us...
[pencils scraping]
[AYANOKOJI] ...we students
of Class One-D,
every last poor soul...
In grammar, math,
chemistry, civics, English,
and every other
classroom subject...
[AYANOKOJI]
...we dodged the bullet
with higher scores than ever.