[bell ringing]
♪♪♪
[yawns]
[SUZUNE]
The semester was over at last.
We'd finished finals and
started summer vacation.
[phone chimes]
[SUZUNE]
Huh...?
[SUZUNE sighs]
Can't you take a hint?
I don't want to talk to you.
[AYANOKOJI]
Horikita.
What now?
[AYANOKOJI] Listen, do you want
to go swimming with me t--?
[IKE]
This is the worst.
[KEN]
Where the hell is he?
My apologies for being late.
[KEN] I thought I said to make
sure you got here on time, dude!
[IKE]
Whatever.
Did you at least bring
everything we need?
[YAMAUCHI]
Yeah, of course I did.
[IKE] Better make sure
you set it up right.
[HIDEO]
Time to implement Operation:
Peep on the Girl's
Dressing Room.
This ought to help alleviate
our frustration a little bit.
[sighs] I've got a bad feeling.
[HIRATA]
Oh? Hey, look! It's Horikita!
Man, it's been forever.
What's up?
Wow, Suzune, there were rumors
you had died or something.
No one in school had
seen a trace of you
since summer break started.
I had no real reason to
see any of you people.
[SUZUNE]
Kei Karuizawa.
Kushida leads one of the
two cliques in Class D.
Kei leads the other.
Dating Hirata has
increased her influence
over our class exponentially,
and it's easy to see why.
And as far as Yosuke
Hirata goes...
He's a central figure
among the Class D boys.
He's an above-average athlete,
and his grades are
decent enough.
He's gregarious, too.
I haven't yet figured
out how he ended up
in the loser class in
the first place.
Look, Horikita.
Why don't you hang out with
the D Class peeps sometime.
It wouldn't hurt
to give it a shot.
I'll pass, thanks.
I have no need to,
"give it a shot," as you say.
My time would be better
spent studying or reading.
[KARUIZAWA] Well, that's
just fine with us, then.
Let's get going, Hirata.
She doesn't think
we're worth her time,
so why should we
bother with her?
'Kay, let's go. Later, Horikita.
[SUZUNE]
I don't need friends.
I've made it this
far without them,
why should I change my tack now?
So, then...
What the heck am I even doing
here with these idiots?
[KIKYO ] I'm so excited that you
decided to come, too, Horikita!
[SUZUNE]
Kikyo Kushida.
She's the picture
of benevolence.
Liked equally by both
girls and guys alike.
And yet, I suspect
that she hates me.
I have a strange
feeling about her.
Honestly, I hope that this trip
is what finally leads us
to friendship! Yay!
[SUZUNE]
She's an enigma.
Who doggedly pursues friendships
with the people they hate?
I don't get it.
What's the matter?
Are we still waiting on
Ike, Yamauchi, and Sudo?
I thought they were
coming with us.
Yeah, me, too. I don't know.
[IKE]
Hey, you guys. Sorry we're late!
We all just overslept.
Can you believe it?
You overslept?
But you three're coming from
the direction of the pool.
[ALL gasp]
[IKE laughs nervously]
Uh, yeah.
[YAMAUCHI] It's super not
important or anything, okay?
Right, don't worry about that.
Hadn't we better get going now?
Yeah, time's wasting. Let's go!
[clicking]
[clicking continues]
[ICHINOSE]
Oh, my gosh!
Hey, you guys!
Are you all headed
to the pool, too?
[ICHINOSE] Today's the last
day the pool's open,
so we'd better make
the most of it.
[KIKYO] Yeah. Some other
people might be coming, too.
How long has your
chest been that big?
What?! That's awkward.
I guess it started in the third
year of middle school.
Then, they just kept
getting bigger.
Why do you ask?
Oh, no particular reason.
But I see why you
always seem to have
more on your plate
than you can handle.
[KIKYO]
Hey, I just realized!
This is the first time you've
hung out with all of us, Sakura!
Exciting!
Do you like to go swimming?
Um. No.
I'm not really a fan of it.
I'm only here because
Ayanokoji invited me.
[ICHINOSE]
Oh, I see now!
You came along because you
have a crush on him, then!
[SAKURA]
No. I-It's not like that.
[KIKYO]
It's interesting.
I've noticed a lot more people
hanging around Ayanokoji lately.
He and Ichinose seem
to have gotten really close.
Have you noticed?
[SUZUNE]
I have.
Honami Ichinose.
The central female
figure in Class B.
She came through for Class D
during an incident
in the first term.
But I find her hard to read.
What do you think, Horikita?
I bet that makes
you nervous, huh.
[SUZUNE] Ayanokoji's social
habits make no difference to me.
I have no feelings
whatsoever on the matter.
Uh? Oh, really?
Operation Young Lust: Phase Two.
This is HQ, operatives.
Let's get this party started.
Time limit is
the end of the day.
We've got until
the targets go home.
[IKE]
Argos-One here. Roger that.
[KIKYO gasping]
--[GIRL 7B] Ah! You got me!
--[GIRL 7C] Take that!
[ICHINOSE] All right,
it's time to have some fun!
[KEN, IKE cheer]
Sakura, are you wearing a wet
suit so you don't get sunburned?
No, I just don't like
showing too much skin
in front of other people.
[KEN, IKE]
Ow!
[KIKYO] I got a brand new
swimsuit, you like?
[KEN, IKE]
Oh yeah, we like!
Uh? Hey, guys.
Where did Yamauchi go?
[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH chattering]
How did we lose him so soon?
Maybe we should go look for him.
It's okay, there's
no need! Don't worry!
I bet he's in the bathroom.
Let's focus on having fun!
[KEN] Oh! Look, there's a
volleyball court over there!
Let's go play!
We should go play right now!
Fine. But, like, why are you
freaking out about it?
[SAKURA]
Listen.
I'm not very good at sports,
so maybe I shouldn't play.
[KIKYO]
No, you should play!
We have some strong boys
on our team, so don't worry!
[ICHINOSE]
Okay, here we go!
Take that!
I hope it's not too crowded.
I left my sunscreen.
Can I use yours?
[gasps]
[MATSUSHITA]
Hey, what's this about?
Where are we supposed to change?
[YAMAUCHI grunting]
Damn it! The camera won't
cooperate with me at all.
What am I supposed to do now?
[ICHINOSE]
Uh? What's going on over there?
It's the line for the bathroom.
You think something
bad happened?
I guess we should
go check it out.
[IKE]
No! Stay right here!
Who even cares about the stupid
line for the bathrooms
when we've got a game to win?!
[BOTH gasp]
Huh. What's wrong with Ike?
I don't know.
Maybe he's just always
been this weird.
[HIDEO]
HQ here, come in.
Argos-two.
Awaiting your report.
[YAMAUCHI panting]
You there, Argos-two?
What's happening?
[clinking]
I'm having major trouble.
A failure like me just isn't cut
out for this kind of work.
I don't think I can do it.
[HIDEO]
You must keep the faith.
[gasps]
[HIDEO] Faith in yourself,
and in your allies
who have placed
their faith in you.
Don't stop believing
in the cause.
Boo-yah!
[CHIHIRO]
I can't! [sighs]
Hey, Yamauchi's been gone
a really long time.
I think we should go out looking
for him now, don't you agree?
Uh. No way!
Don't worry, Kushida.
I'm sure he just got distracted!
[KIKYO] But something bad
could've happened to him.
Aren't you at least a
little bit concerned?
[IKE]
No, no! I'm sure he's just fine!
But, Ike. He's your
friend, isn't he?
Shouldn't you be
worried about him?
[IKE]
Uh. Wait.
She'll think I'm shallow
if I keep hiding things!
If manga's taught me anything,
it's that chicks love
male friendships.
I can't! If I'm not concerned,
she might hate me!
No, no, no, I can't give up
the cause just for her sake!
[gasps]
[clicking]
[HIDEO growling]
HQ here, checking in.
Argos-two. You're out of time.
You must abandon the mission.
Return to the base at once.
[YAMAUCHI]
Forgive me.
I am incompetent.
I'm sorry.
[KEN] Apologizing is not going
to fix anything now!
[IKE] I'm sorry. But I
didn't want Kushida
to hate me over this!
[KIKYO] Seriously, guys,
let's go look for him!
Let's all play some volleyball!
Yamauchi's back!
[YAMAUCHI] Wow, the line
for the bathroom was insane!
It was?
Still, I'm relieved you're back.
I was so worried.
So, um, now that Yamauchi's
back in the game,
do you think it
would be okay--
Ah! My stomach's killing me!
I've gotta go to the
bathroom right now!
...rotate out.
[gasps]
Huh? Get this out of my way.
[ALBERT]
Sure thing, boss.
Let's go.
[HIDEO]
HQ reporting!
Enemy-R is approaching quickly!
[IKE] Ah... But I'm just
about done with Phase Two.
I can finish it!
You don't have time!
Argos-one, you have to withdraw!
Withdraw, now!
Argos-one! Retreat!
[KEN growls]
[yells]
[gasps]
[KEN] My leg is cramping!
I've gotta go!
[MAI] That must be an
intense muscle cramp.
You're down to five.
Do you want to continue playing,
or should we call
it quits for now?
Uh...
Listen.
I think we should call it and
forfeit this one to you guys.
That way we can go take
care of Ike and Sudo.
[YAMAUCHI] Don't ever
give up on your dreams!
I'll play hard enough for
both of them combined.
So, you better not
even think of quitting!
Or are you saying that our
beach volleyball memories
never meant anything
to you at all?!
Come on, everybody, show me
all the passion and grit
you can muster to
win this thing!
[SAKURA]
Huh...?
[KIKYO] Has Yamauchi always been
this passionate about sports?
I never knew that he had
a distinct personality.
To be honest, I've always
had considerable difficulty
telling him and Ike
apart from each other.
[RYUEN] Huh? There's no one
cleaning these bathrooms.
[IKE]
Setup complete.
Now I've just gotta
get out of here!
[HIDEO] It's too soon to let
your guard down just yet,
Argos-one. There are two
women there with Enemy-R!
Do you read?
I repeat, two women with
the approaching enemy!
[KIKYO]
Ouch, that hurt.
Oops. I couldn't stop it.
It's okay. Don't worry!
It's cool!
[growls] This isn't cool!
You can't just come
barging in here!
The sign clearly says
this place is off-limits!
Then what are you doing here?
You seriously think I care?
I go where I want.
[KEN]
Uh...
[SAKAYANAGI]
What an unsightly scene.
A fight between two
bottom-feeders is just pathetic.
Sakayanagi?
You weren't invited.
Take your mangy dogs
and get out of here.
No thanks.
Perhaps I should
domesticate you, too.
[KEN gasps]
[MANABU]
What's all this fuss about here?
--[RYUEN] Mm?
--[KEN] Huh?
[MANABU]
I am aware that this place
is a recreational facility.
But, that doesn't mean
school rules don't apply.
Don't forget you're all
still on campus.
[laughs] So the Student Council
President decided to show up.
[gasping]
[SUZUNE]
I can tell you're holding back.
No, I'm just not
very good at sports.
[SUZUNE]
You're athletic.
I've seen you show
your skill, remember?
[SUZUNE] Why do you hide
what you're capable of?
Why, does it irritate you?
Or is it that you just don't
want to lose at anything?
[SUZUNE]
Not in the least.
I admire that.
What's the point
in playing a game
if you're not committed to
winning it at all costs?
Being vulnerable and letting
your emotions show
would help you
make friends, too.
I've told you,
I don't need any friends.
Hey, what's happening
in the locker rooms?
[beeping]
[HIDEO]
HQ checking in.
Argos-one. What's your status?
I'm ready to withdraw,
but I can't.
Help me. With all of
the obstacles outside,
I'm stuck in here!
It's all over.
We made it so far.
[HIDEO] You can't give up now,
when we're so close!
Hey, look. I have to ask you.
Do you think that this
whole thing was a mistake?
[HIDEO]
How can you say that?
Listen. If I don't end up making
it out of this place alive...
You must not abandon
hope, soldier!
[IKE]
Sotomura.
You're to refer to me
as HQ, Argos-one.
And that's an order.
Even as you suffer in
there for the cause,
you've got comrades out
here waiting for you,
depending on you.
So, do not abandon hope.
Heh.
[beeping]
[HIDEO]
Argos-one? Argos-one!
I'm sorry, bud.
Almost lost my nerve.
[HIDEO]
Argos-one!
[IKE] HQ, you'd better
contact Argos-four.
Tell him it's a go.
Execute Phase Extra.
[AYANOKOJI grunting]
[AYANOKOJI] "Draw attention
away from the locker rooms?
Student council president,
Ryuen, and others, too?"
[AYANOKOJI groans]
This is getting ridiculous.
[AYANOKOJI]
Horikita.
I need you to help me with
something important.
Look, I have a
terrible leg cramp!
Stay away from me!
It doesn't look that way to me.
[BOY 7B] Something's
going down over there!
[BOY 7C] Isn't that Horikita
from Class One-D?
[RYUEN]
Horikita?
Give me the names of who
did this, and Al will go easy.
[KOMIYA]
The girl's name is Horikita.
[RYUEN chuckles]
[ALL gasping]
[ICHINOSE] What do you think's
come over Horikita?
I'm just as confused as you.
Why do I even have to
get involved in this?
[inhales, exhales]
Allow me to begin by saying
we are Class-D, year one!
We've been labeled the defective
students at this school.
We're the problem children.
We're fools, and we
fall for the schemes
of other classes pretty easily.
So, to the students of Class C,
you made a bold move in trying
to sabotage our class before.
But now...
...I am grateful for
all of your efforts.
Thanks to you,
everything is clearer.
A class full of defectives
will have a rough time
if we aim high.
But now I see that all classes,
A to D, aren't separated by
anything as simple as
pure academic prowess
or athletic ability.
That's good news.
Especially for loser Class D.
It means we could
become Class A.
We can beat you all and
ascend to the top.
I promise you this:
We will make it to Class A!
[STUDENTS gasp, cheer]
[KIKYO, SAKURA]
Uh?
We love you, Horikita!
[KEN]
You're incredible!
[YAMAUCHI]
You rock!
[RYUEN chuckles]
Oh, really, Class D?
[KEN]
You better watch it!
[IKE]
Tidal wave, comin' atcha!
[YAMAUCHI]
Ow, ow, ow.
[SUZUNE]
What a bunch of perverts.
[AYANOKOJI]
Hm?
[SUZUNE]
There really were cameras set up
in the dressing room,
like you said.
[sighs]
[phone ringing]
[AYANOKOJI]
Seriously.
Do you wanna go to
the pool with me?
Absolutely not.
[AYANOKOJI] Look, to be frank,
I need a huge favor from you.
Class D's future is on the line.
How so?
[AYANOKOJI] Ike's the one who
suggested we go to the pool.
He's planning to set up cameras
in the women's dressing room.
So he and the guys can
spy on you all changing.
Uh?
If I had tried to stop them,
they probably would have
gone behind my back.
Found a way to go
forward with it.
It was better to let them
do it and foil them secretly.
[SUZUNE] I hate to admit it,
but you were right.
[AYANOKOJI] Their plan was
to set up the cameras,
then retrieve them later tonight
after everyone had gone home.
But that's not gonna happen now.
We beat them to the chase.
We could have stopped
them earlier.
If we'd removed
the cards in advance.
Then they would have
gotten nothing.
Yeah, that was the
initial plan, actually.
But the interference from
other classes made things
a lot more difficult.
Is that why you made me
give that stupid speech?
To divert people's attention
away from them?
But you got such
thunderous applause.
Sudo and the others were moved
to tears by your words.
More importantly, did you
have fun at the pool today?
You spent your whole
summer alone.
So, was getting out refreshing?
I didn't come to this
school to have fun.
Besides, people bore me.
I have much more fun by myself.
[AYANOKOJI]
Sure you do.
Well, we've got some time
before the pool closes.
[gasps]
[yelps]
[gasps] What is your problem?
Sorry, I had to do it.
[AYANOKOJI]
Uh!
[splash]
That's payback.
[KIKYO]
Hey! I wanna join in the fun!
[SUZUNE]
Kushida, stop!
We're not playing!
Take that! And that!
[KEN]
Hey, Horikita, check it out!
[BOYS]
Wa-hoo!
[SUZUNE] You idiots stop
splashing my face!
Oh. I'm sorry about that.
[door clicks]
[SUZUNE]
Uh? What's this?
It's less of a risk
to be by myself.