[bell ringing]
[SAKURA gasps]
Wait, come back!
[AYANOKOJI] American
Anthropologist Edward Hall
divided the concept of personal
space into four general zones.
He named one of these
the "intimate space" zone.
With the "close phase"
contained therein.
The latter is near enough
for someone to hug them.
Many resist letting
others into this zone.
However, some people
seem to enter
into everyone's
close phase easily.
Kushida's one of those.
Even if she enters
someone's close phase,
she manages not to trigger
an aversive reaction.
[SAKURA panting]
[AYANOKOJI] Even so,
Sakura resisted Kushida.
[AYANOKOJI] For some unknown
reason, she ran away from her.
She couldn't even
look her in the eye.
[AYANOKOJI] Why does she fear
contact with others?
Um. I'm so sorry!
You two are very kind to agree
to come with me for this.
No, this whole thing
is my fault!
I'm the one who
owes you an apology
for breaking your camera!
[SAKURA] Thanks, but I should
have been more careful.
[AYANOKOJI] So, you're going
to the electronics store
where you got your
camera to get it fixed.
I understand that part.
But why did I have to come?
[KIKYO giggles]
I need you, too.
[SERVICE MAN 5A]
Man, what a bummer.
This is no good.
I see what's wrong here.
Looks like a power
issue if you ask me.
Mm. Definitely.
[SERVICE MAN 5A]
Do you have a warranty with you?
Should be covered.
You did remember to
bring it with you, right?
[SAKURA]
Mm-hm.
[gasps] It hasn't expired, yay!
You could have the broken
part, uh--replaced.
Completely free of charge.
[gasps]
[AYANOKOJI] I see.
Sakura's scared of strangers.
Of course, this guy
would freak her out.
I'm here because she wanted
strength in numbers.
Um. Do you know how
long the repairs will take?
[SERVICE MAN 5A]
Two or three days max, I think.
But don't quote me.
I need you to fill out this
form, but not the whole thing.
Fill out your name here,
home address,
and your cell phone number.
[gasps]
Are you all right?
[gasps] Uh, yeah.
[SAKURA whimpering]
[AYANOKOJI]
Let me do it.
When the repairs are complete,
please contact me
instead of Sakura.
[SERVICE MAN 5A]
What?! Hey, wait a minute!
The camera belongs
to her, doesn't it?
I don't think we can do that.
I'm not comfortable with this.
You saw the warranty.
It notes the time and
location of purchase
so you shouldn't need
her information.
I understand that
it's store policy,
but you won't get in trouble.
I can't imagine there
being a legal issue.
You don't have to worry.
Well. Are you sure about that?
[gasping]
[gasps]
[SERVICE MAN 5A] I guess
we can do that this time.
[SAKURA]
By the way,
thank you very much
for coming to my aid.
[KIKYO] No problem. It was the
least I could do to atone!
But, listen, Sakura.
We're the same age.
You don't have to speak
to us so formally.
I'd like to think we're friends!
Yes, you've been acting
like we're your elders.
[gasps] Um. Yeah.
Makes sense.
I will try.
I mean, I'll do my best.
No need to force
anything, either!
[SAKURA]
Um. Right, I won't.
[KIKYO]
Mm-hm!
I'll be back in a bit.
I'm gonna go freshen up.
[AYANOKOJI]
Being alone with her is awkward.
[gasps]
[AYANOKOJI]
Hm?
Is something on your mind?
Do you not feel
comfortable with the--?
Listen. What do you
think I should do?
I can't figure out what
would be best for everyone.
Oh, you mean about Sudo?
The best thing would be
to do what you want.
[gasps] "Do what I want"?
That's right.
[SAKURA]
If I keep quiet,
I know I'm going to regret it.
[AYANOKOJI] Why are you talking
to me about this?
Your eyes. There's
nothing scary in them.
Eyes?
Never mind.
It's... hard to...
If you need some advice,
I think Kushida's more versed
in this kind of stuff.
She showed up for you today.
[AYANOKOJI]
That's interesting.
I can tell that she's grateful,
but she doesn't seem
to fully trust Kushida.
Maybe she's more
perceptive than most.
You said you'd regret it if you
kept silent about the fight.
Yeah.
Well, I think you already
know what to do.
[gasps]
[AYANOKOJI]
Don't do it for Sudo,
or Kushida, or for any
of our classmates.
Push all of those thoughts
out of your mind.
They don't serve you.
[SAKURA] Serve me?
What do you mean by that?
[AYANOKOJI] Thinking that way
will only convolute things
and make the choice
more difficult.
You should trust your instincts,
and testify for your sake alone.
You mean do the right
thing... for me?
That's motivation enough.
[gasps]
[KIKYO] Sorry for taking
so long in there!
Oh. Welcome back.
All right. Do you guys think
that we should call
it a day now?
It is getting pretty late.
You're right. Hey,
would you mind terribly
if I swung by your room
a little later tonight?
Huh?
[KIKYO]
Thanks for having me!
You just had to come to my room?
What's this about?
I found some stuff online
that I thought you might
be interested to see.
Does this girl look
familiar to you?
[AYANOKOJI]
Hold on. Is that Sakura?
It's hard to say if it's her.
I can't tell just from
the pictures alone.
But this one was definitely
taken in one of the dorms here.
[KIKYO]
Do you think it's her, then?
Well, it could be.
I thought it was strange that
she was wearing fake glasses,
but now it makes perfect sense.
[KIKYO]
They're fake?
[AYANOKOJI] There was no
distortion behind the lenses.
So you think she's wearing
them to disguise her face?
Could that be why she
didn't want to testify?
[phone chimes]
[KIKYO]
It's a message from Sakura.
Let's see here...
You're not gonna believe this.
She might be willing
to help us defend Sudo!
[AYANOKOJI] I guess going
with her today was worth it.
I'm glad she decided she could
trust us, but I wonder why.
[KIKYO]
Hey.
Ayanokoji, are you sure
you're not trying
to hide anything
from me? For real.
[AKANEAKENE]
I've sent out the notification.
All in classes C
and D were invited.
The arbitration hearing is
set to take place tomorrow.
Is that so?
[MANABU]
Class D.
Uh?
What's wrong?
Did you spend your entire
day off with Kushida?
Yeah, because of
the thing with Sakura.
Though we couldn't get her
to commit to testifying.
Not definitively.
I see.
[AYANOKOJI]
What's the matter with you?
What do you mean,
"What's the matter?"
[AYANOKOJI]
Well... You are epitomizing
"that-face" at the moment.
Really? And what do
you mean by "that face"?
This is just my face.
Although...
I am amazed at how self-serving
you've been acting recently.
You hesitate when I
ask for a favor,
but when Kushida does,
you gladly jump for her.
I'm analyzing, rationally,
and precisely,
what factors
account for the disparity.
Doesn't matter.
Could've fooled me.
More importantly.
The student council has
decided on the time of
Sudo's arbitration hearing.
[AYANOKOJI]
When is it?
It's today, after school.
[AKANE] We will now begin
the deliberation proceedings
regarding the violent incident
that occurred last Tuesday.
Your presence is appreciated.
Now, first of all,
I will preside today, as
Student Council Secretary.
The student council president,
attending arbitration over a
little brawl such as this one?
I never dreamed I
would see this day.
[MANABU] My extremely busy
schedule often prevents me from
being present at proceedings
I would prefer to join.
As a rule, though,
I try to attend.
Oh, of course. A coincidence.
[MANABU]
Indeed...
[AYANOKOJI]
Horikita wasn't expecting
her brother to be here.
It seems like his presence
might throw off her game.
Let's begin. The object here
is to ascertain the truth.
Which version of
the events is factual.
Is that acceptable, sir?
[MANABU]
Yes, you may proceed.
[AKANE] Komiya et al, you allege
that Sudo summoned you to
the special annex last Tuesday,
where he then attacked you.
Sudo denies your claim.
He insists that Komiya
summoned him to the annex.
Your versions of these
events are contradictory.
We can be certain
of only one thing.
Sudo attacked
and injured you three.
Komiya, Kondo, and Ishizaki
are the victims here,
and we will proceed
under the agreement
that they are the plaintiffs.
Sudo's the defendant
in this case.
[KEN growls]
I'll admit that I beat them up!
But these jerks are
the real attackers!
[AYANOKOJI] Putting the
focus on their injuries
and giving Sudo free reign here
will do nothing but
harm our case.
Horikita.
[KEN]
...you're jealous that I got
bumped up to first string!
You always try to sabotage
me at practice, but it--
[AKANE] Silence, please.
Return to your seat.
Without any new evidence
or testimony,
we will proceed under the
aforementioned assumptions.
Is this acceptable?
[MANABU]
It's quite apparent
there was no need
for adjudication.
Judging by the severity of
the plaintiffs' conditions,
it's clear that the violence
was one-sided.
I believe this is
sufficient evidence
to allow me to make my decision.
Class D's self-defense
claim lacks credibility
due to Sudo's absence of
injuries. And the plaintiffs'...
[gasps]
[gasping] Hey! Stop it!
[KEN]
Uh...
[gasping continues]
[SUZUNE sputtering]
Cut it out.
[AYANOKOJI]
When someone's spacing out,
a strong physical stimulus can
often snap them out of it.
The stakes are too high
for me to do nothing.
[SUZUNE]
...come on!  Uh!
If you don't start fighting now,
we're going to lose this case.
[gasps]
[SUZUNE]
I beg your pardon.
Before we break, I would like
to question the witnesses.
Would that be acceptable?
President?
I will allow it.
[inhales, exhales]
The first question.
What were the circumstances
under which Sudo summoned you?
I need an answer.
Uh, when practice was over,
he just said he wanted
to talk to me.
[SUZUNE]
I see.
And what was your reasoning for
bringing Ishizaki with you
to the special annex?
He's not on the basketball
team, as far as I know.
There was no reason
for him to be present.
I brought him 'cause I
wanted extra protection.
Protection?
Everyone in school knows what
a violent guy Sudo can be.
And he's pretty big, too!
[SUZUNE]
So you're saying you thought
he might attack you, right?
[KOMIYA]
That's right!
[AYANOKOJI] That sounds
like a studied response.
If I understand, you claim
you brought Ishizaki
as a bodyguard, because of
his reputation as a fighter?
Yeah, I did it to
protect myself!
Understood.
I have some knowledge of martial
arts, as a matter of fact.
Sudo faced multiple adversaries
which is exponentially
more difficult to do.
For him to beat you so soundly,
especially with
Ishizaki at your back
defending you,
doesn't quite add up.
Uh! It does!
He only beat us because we
didn't want to get into a fight!
[SUZUNE]
If you didn't want a fight,
why would you go, knowing
Sudo's propensities?
And if you weren't
fighting back,
how would all three of you end
up with such severe injuries?
Common sense tells me
Horikita has a good point.
[KOMIYA] You can't use common
sense with Sudo!
He doesn't operate that way!
He's a violent,
unpredictable psychopath!
Well, you're in luck,
because someone witnessed
the entire fight.
[SAKAGAMI gasps]
[KEN gasps]
Would the witness
please step forward?
[AKANE]
Welcome, Miss.
Would you state your name,
for the record?
Yes. Airi Sakura.
I'm from Class One-D.
[AKANE]
Please take a seat, Miss Sakura.
[SAKURA]
Okay...
Sakura.
[gasps]
I did see it. I witnessed
the whole thing.
Sudo has been telling
the truth this whole time.
The Class C students attacked
him first, like he said.
I'm sure of it. They're lying.
Your name's Sakura, is it not?
If you did see the fight, then
why didn't you come forward
with your knowledge
before this point?
Well, you see... Because...
[sighs] Honestly, Class D
students are all the same.
I promise this is the truth.
I'm not lying, I swear.
Oh, Sakura. Miss Airi Sakura.
Let's be honest now.
Are you sure they
haven't coerced you?
The stakes are high, and they'd
do anything to save Sudo.
[gasps]
[AYANOKOJI]
This could go badly.
Spin it how you wish.
The fact that she's here proves
that she witnessed the fight.
I mean, think about it.
If she hadn't, why would
she show up today,
even if we tried to coerce her?
Oh?
If all we needed was
someone who'd lie,
why would we choose a girl like
Sakura, who hates to speak up?
Perhaps to lend an air of
credibility to your case,
you specifically chose
someone who is well-behaved.
That's all you've got?
You're the ones with
the burden of proof,
and from where I
sit, the facts--
It's immoral of you to
take advantage of this girl.
She's weak-willed,
so you manipulate her.
That is not what's going on!
Just look at how hard
she's trembling over there!
You put such a burden on her.
I have real proof!
I saw the fight. I'll prove it.
You are only digging
yourselves a deeper hole.
[SAKURA]
Here it is.
The proof that I was there.
In the annex last Tuesday.
See for yourself.
[gasps]
Let's see it.
Yes.
[SAKURA]
I was there that afternoon,
looking for a place
to take pictures.
I don't like to take
them around people,
and I knew the annex
would be empty.
The photo is dated, too.
Dates on digital photos are
relatively simple to alter,
Miss Sakura. Your proof
is rather insubstantial.
Just a minute, Mr. Sakagami.
This photo is sufficient
proof after all.
[SAKAGAMI]
Hm? Ah.
Thank you, sir.
I hope this one will
be proof enough.
I told you that I was
telling the truth.
Thank you so much, Sakura.
[gasps]
[SAKAGAMI]
I'll grant you that much.
It seems that you
were indeed present
in the special annex on
the day in question.
But your photo still
does nothing to prove
that Sudo didn't
start the fight.
It also doesn't provide evidence
that you really witnessed
everything that happened.
[SAKURA]
But I did.
So then, I propose a compromise.
A compromise? What kind?
[SAKAGAMI] Despite the
"evidence" you provided,
you still don't have
any definitive proof.
However, it appears that
Class C may indeed
bear some responsibility
in this debacle.
[SAKAGAMI] I recommend a
two-week suspension for Sudo.
And a one-week suspension
for the Class-C students.
Is that acceptable?
The difference in length
is commensurate
to the severity in harm
done to each party.
[growls]
[AYANOKOJI] If Sakura hadn't
come forward with her testimony,
Sudo would have been suspended
for a month, at the very least.
It is a good bargain, actually.
Ms. Chabashira, does that idea
sound satisfactory to you?
It would appear we have reached
an agreement that will suffice.
[AYANOKOJI] Sakura, you did
everything you could.
Then, that's it.
Miss Horikita,
as representative of Class D,
what's your opinion
of the agreement?
[SUZUNE]
This is my final word.
Sudo has a problem.
I think he contributed
to this, ultimately.
Even if he's not the one
who threw the first punch.
He has no sense of how
he affects others.
Actions have consequences,
but he doesn't see that.
Incidents like this
will not stop.
[gasps] What?!
You need to see the
truth of the matter.
Your poor attitude is what
started all of this, really.
He does need to reflect
on his actions.
But not the missteps you claim
he took in fight last Tuesday.
I mean that he should reevaluate
the person he has been
this whole school year.
Horikita?
In regards to the incident
we're discussing right now,
that's different.
I truly believe Sudo is free
of all guilt in the matter.
The truth is, I know that Sudo
didn't stumble into that
fight of his own accord.
This was a premeditated set-up,
instigated by Class C,
and that is truly heinous.
I will not back down.
I assert that he is innocent.
[laughs] Premeditated set-up?
That's hilarious, young lady.
I think the president's
sister is a--
As the witness
testified earlier,
Sudo's not guilty in this.
I implore you to make
the appropriate decision.
We've been victimized
by him! He's guilty!
You shut your mouth! Jerk!
I'm innocent,
and all of you know it!
You're just trying
to sabotage me
and usurp my place
on the team...!
[MANABU]
Just as I predicted.
This hearing was a waste
of everyone's time.
I'm appalled at the pathetic
behavior on display right now.
Nothing can be settled unless
the liars come forward.
[AKANE]
I agree. This is pointless.
[MANABU]
Therefore, I ask you, Class C.
Can you honestly say right
now that the statements
you've made today are
the unadulterated truth?
What? Of course they're true!
[MANABU]
What about Class D?
Certainly.
[MANABU]
Very well, then.
I will announce my decision
tomorrow at four o'clock.
If I receive no
amended statements,
as in admission of guilt,
nor proof of your opponents'
guilt by then,
I will be putting expulsion
on the table as well.
That is all.
[AYANOKOJI]
Do we have a chance?
Well, I don't intend to lose,
and I never give up, either.
I'm sorry.
I should have just spoken up
from the very beginning
about what I saw.
I'm not... I'm not brave.
You did just fine. It's okay.
But it's not!
[MANABU]
Why are you two still here?
When you showed up
with Suzune today,
I assumed you had a strategy.
But, I suppose I grossly
overestimated the both of you.
I never claimed to be
some star detective,
and I'm not a trial
lawyer, either.
So, no, I don't have a strategy.
You mean Suzune went
out on a limb today?
She truly believes
he's innocent?
[AYANOKOJI]
I guess it's a radical idea.
[MANABU]
Interesting.
Your name's Sakura, right?
[gasps] Yes.
If you can't provide evidence
to corroborate your claims,
they're nothing but lies,
and your mask will
become your prison.
But... It's not a lie.
I swear.
I was telling the truth.
[AYANOKOJI]
I believe every word.
[SAKURA gasps]
[MANABU]
I see. Well, in that case...
[AKANE gasping]
[SAKURA gasping]
Do you have what it takes
to prove her right?
I guess you'll
find out tomorrow.