[bell ringing]
[SAKURA] I've always had trouble
interacting with people.
I can't even bring myself
to look them in the eye.
It scares me.
That's why I hide.
I use my mask to cover
up my real self.
That way, it's harder
for people to hurt me.
I'm okay being by myself.
It's safer that way.
I'm okay being lonely.
I can get over that feeling.
--[gasps]
--[phone chimes]
[SAKURA gasping]
--[phone chiming]
--[SAKURA cries]
[SAKURA sobs]
[AYANOKOJI]
It's hot in here.
[SUZUNE]
You're right,
and intense heat usually causes
people to be irrational.
Which makes it the
perfect place for a set-up.
Sudo'd be less likely
to keep a cool head.
So, then. Have ya come up
with a stellar plan yet?
I'm in the brainstorming phase.
Sakura's testimony
bought us time.
But we won't always
be so fortunate.
I just wish we could find some
more substantial evidence
to seal the deal.
Oh, speakin' of which,
this area doesn't have any.
[AYANOKOJI]
Security cameras.
[SUZUNE]
That's true.
If there'd been cameras, well,
then we would have all the
evidence we need, wouldn't we?
Indeed.
On the other hand, if this
area did have them up,
those jerks would never
have summoned Sudo here
in the first place.
[gasps]
What's the matter?
[SUZUNE] I think I've
come up with a plan.
[AYANOKOJI]
Sakura?
[gasps]
Oh, hey.
Good morning.
Oh. Um...
Yes, good morning.
[sighs]
What's wrong?
You don't have to
testify again, you know.
The hearing's private today.
So, there's no need
for you to be so tense.
[sighs] Okay.
And anyway, we have a plan.
If it works, we'll be able
to save the whole class.
You're the one who
made that possible.
[gasps]
I want to tell you
that I trust you.
[gasps]
[AYANOKOJI] So if you ever
happen to find yourself
in need of help,
just ask for me,
and I'll be there.
I appreciate that.
And I'm not the only one.
I'm sure that everyone
in class trusts you, too.
Horikita, Kushida,
Sudo, all of them.
Yeah.
Um. Listen.
I've got something on my mind.
There's really not
much you could do
to help the situation,
but I thought I'd try.
[phone chimes]
I'm sorry, Sakura.
I hate to cut you off,
but is there any way we
could talk about this later?
Yeah.
[KONDO]
So damn hot!
[KOMIYA]
Why the special annex?
What do you guys
think Kushida wants
to talk to us about, anyway?
[KOMIYA]
I bet she's gonna ask me out!
Yeah, right, keep dreamin',
ya big dummy.
[KOMIYA]
Ah! Not so hard, jerk!
Let me go!
Huh?
[KONDO, KOMIYA]
Uh!
[ISHIZAKI]
What the hell?
What are you doing in here?
You were expecting Kushida?
Huh?
[AYANOKOJI] That email
she sent was just a ruse.
I told her to send it to you.
And why would you do that?
I wanted to have a chat.
It was the only way
to get you here.
But, I'm glad I finally
have your attention.
Listen, last time we
got summoned here
was when Sudo beat us up.
You know that's the truth.
Sudo needs to take his
punishment like a real man.
We're out of here.
[SUZUNE]
I'd stay if I were you.
If you leave now, you'll regret
it for the rest of your lives.
Do you really want to ruin
your futures like that?
And what the hell is
your problem, lady?!
Whatever.
Maybe you should be
more observant.
What are you even talking about?
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
What's the matter?
You seem a little shaken up.
Is that a... security camera?
There's a science laboratory
in the special annex.
They work with all kinds of
hazardous chemicals in there,
so, of course there
would be cameras.
[grunting, gasps]
[ISHIZAKI]
But, how?
Wait a minute.
If there's footage
from those cameras
of what happened in here,
they'd know Sudo's
innocent and wouldn't
need to have a hearing
in the first place.
And you would definitely
have no reason
to tell us about it, either.
The moment that the
incident took place,
both parties were doomed to
suffer some form of punishment.
Regardless of why, the truth
is that Sudo beat you up.
That is an indisputable fact.
Oh, so that's why we're here.
You guys would also be hurt
by the camera recordings.
Of course, Sudo is still
going to be punished,
but what you three did
could get you all expelled.
[BOTH gasp]
[AYANOKOJI]
You told a malicious lie
and got the whole
school involved.
What did you expect
would happen?
Oh, yeah?
If that's true, then why hasn't
the school said anything to us?
The school has a habit
of testing its students.
They want to see
if we can work out
some sort of truce on our own.
That's why they're taking
a hands-off approach.
They want to see
what we'll achieve
with the extra time
we've been given.
[gasps]
I want you all to think back
on the hearing yesterday.
Don't you think it seemed like
they already knew everything?
[KONDO]
No way. I can't get expelled.
Ishizaki! Why don't we
tell them we made it up.
If we have a solution,
maybe they'll be more
lenient and not expel us!
[KONDO]
What are we even supposed to do?
Shut up, you idiots!
[AYANOKOJI] Don't be too hasty
in making your decision.
You know there is a way to
save both of our classes.
If you're open to hearing it.
Like hell there's a way, jerk!
[SUZUNE] Why not take the entire
incident off the table?
[MALE STUDENTS gasp]
It's quite simple, really.
If you three would only
withdraw your complaint,
it will be like nothing
bad ever happened.
[AYANOKOJI]
If no fight occurred here,
then how can the authorities
punish anyone?
All we have to do is get our
collective story straight,
then the school can't
pursue it any further.
So, do we have a deal?
Hold on a minute.
I just have to talk it
over with someone first.
[ISHIZAKI]
Hey!
What's the matter, can't make up
your mind without your master?
[ISHIZAKI]
Give it back!
How pathetic.
You bitch--
Resorting to violence?
Go ahead. Try it.
[ISHIZAKI gasping]
[ISHIZAKI]
Dammit!
Ishizaki.
Just admit it, we lost.
Let's accept Horikita's offer.
We can't afford to
get expelled, dude!
[ISHIZAKI growls]
[ISHIZAKI sighs]
[ISHIZAKI]
Fine.
We'll take everything back.
[SAKURA gasping]
[SAKURA panting]
Someone help.
[AYANOKOJI] You have my
word that I'll pay back
the points I borrowed from you
yesterday, with interest.
Let's discuss the terms.
[ICHINOSE]
You got it.
An eye for an eye,
a lie for a lie, right?
Glad I could help.
I never expected someone
with a mind like yours
to be in Class D.
I don't understand it.
Well, Horikita came up with
the Machiavellian scheme.
I'm just some guy
following orders,
to be perfectly honest with you.
Uh-huh.
Well, if you say so!
[phone ringing]
[AYANOKOJI]
Sakura?
Hey, what's up?
[SAKURA]
Ayanokoji, help!
[SAKURA screams]
[SAKURA whimpering]
[SERVICE MAN 5A]
Shh! Be quiet.
[phone vibrations continue]
Did you... Did you read
all the letters I sent?
You've got to know how I
feel about you, my darling.
Right?
[SAKURA gasping]
[SERVICE MAN 5A]
So, why?!
Why have you been
avoiding me like this?
If you know how precious
you are to me,
why are you treating
me this way?
You know how much
I love you, right?
Someone help me...
[AYANOKOJI] So if you ever
happen to find yourself
in need of help, just ask,
and I'll be there.
[SAKURA grunts]
Uh?
[SERVICE MAN 5A grunts]
Let me go right now! Ah!
Dammit!
[SAKURA whimpers]
[SAKURA panting]
[SERVICE MAN 5A]
Listen.
If you don't let me
do what I want,
I'll put the real you on the
internet for everyone to see.
You wouldn't like that, huh?
Huh? What's going on?
Why are you looking at
me that way, my darling?
[gasps] Stop!
Stop looking at me like that!
--[SAKURA screams]
--Stop it right now!
[SAKURA]
No! Let me go!
[SAKURA cries]
[SERVICE MAN 5A]
I'm going to show you
just how much I
love you, darling.
I know you'll learn to
love me, too, Shizuku.
You'll understand after this.
Just be quiet.
We are destined to be together.
I know you feel the same way.
[SAKURA cries]
[AYANOKOJI]
Local electronics store employee
caught in the act
of sexual assault.
You're gonna be famous.
No, infamous is more accurate.
[SERVICE MAN 5A]
W-Wait a minute!
That's not what this is!
[AYANOKOJI]
By all means, explain.
Remember, security cameras don't
lie, so be careful what you say.
Even if it was just an attempt,
she's still an underage girl.
With that on your record, you
would certainly lose your job.
The press is cruel.
They might even go
after your family.
[SERVICE MAN 5A gasping]
[AYANOKOJI]
Face it.
As of this moment,
your life is over.
[yelling]
[ICHINOSE]
You think you can get away
with committing such
a heinous crime?
Something like that
would never fly here.
[SERVICE MAN 5A grunting]
--[OFFICER 6A] Come quietly...
--Let me go! She loves me!
I didn't do anything wrong!
You can't interfere with
our love! It's destiny!
I'm Shizuku's number one fan!
She wants me, too!
Everything she does is because
of how much she cares for me.
She only updates her blog
to show me her new pictures.
Why can't any of you see that?
She loves me,
she just won't admit it!
She even came to this school
so she could be close to me.
Shut up. I don't even know you!
What? What's the
matter, Shizuku?
I want nothing to do with you.
A fan wouldn't
treat me like this.
Monster! I never want
to see your face again.
[SERVICE MAN 5A whimpers]
[SERVICE MAN 5A]
I can't believe this.
You're a dirty liar.
You're ugly.
This ugly bitch tricked me.
I'll make you pay for this!
Come on! You owe me
an explanation, bitch!
I never could love an ugly,
lying bitch like you!
Do you hear me?!
That's quite enough of that.
[SERVICE MAN 5A whimpers]
Damn you.
Damn you!
[SERVICE MAN 5A cries]
[AYANOKOJI]
I'm sure Ichinose and the cops
can handle it from here.
I'm glad I had
your contact info.
That's the only way I
could have found you.
[gasps]
[AYANOKOJI]
See? There you are.
I'm so sorry. I really
am the worst, huh?
I thought I could make it
on my own, but I can't.
Being an idol comes with
its own set of hazards.
[SAKURA]
But I am grateful for one thing.
You guys. I'm so happy.
You like me for me.
I'm done lying.
Sorry I didn't tell you before.
You have no reason to apologize,
but in the future, if you want
to talk to me about anything,
I promise I won't dismiss you.
I appreciate it.
[gasps]
Ayanokoji, um.
The look in your eyes.
I've never seen it
in them before.
What do you mean?
Oh, nothing at all.
[CHABASHIRA exhales]
[SUZUNE]
What do you want?
You called me out here
to talk, so talk.
[CHABASHIRA]
I'll get straight to the point.
How did you do it?
Sorry? How did I do what?
[CHABASHIRA]
Don't play dumb.
We both know those imbeciles
wouldn't withdraw their
complaint for no reason.
[SUZUNE] I'll leave that
to your imagination.
I'll rephrase the
question, then.
Who came up with
the brilliant idea?
What made them back off?
[SUZUNE]
I don't know.
Why does that even
matter to you?
[CHABASHIRA]
If you're truly serious
about advancing to Class A,
then allow me to offer you
a simple word of advice.
[CHABASHIRA] Learn as much
about Ayanokoji as you can,
while you still have the
opportunity to do so.
Otherwise, before you
know it, it'll be too late.
[KEN]
Hey, Ayanokoji!
[AYANOKOJI]
How'd the hearing turn out?
You'll never believe
what happened.
The guys in Class C, they backed
off for no apparent reason!
I see. That's incredible.
I know, isn't it?
Do you think Horikita
pulled some strings for me?
Yeah, probably.
She's awesome.
But also kinda weird.
Well, I gotta go. See ya!
[SUZUNE]
What is that supposed to mean?
[CHABASHIRA]
Why do you imagine Ayanokoji
would be going out of his way
to help the rest of you?
And why, despite
his superiority,
does he refuse to reveal
what he's capable of?
I don't know.
[CHABASHIRA]
To put it in the school's terms,
Class D is the place for those
with defective qualities.
The ones who barely had
the chops to get in at all.
It's just my opinion,
so take it with a grain of salt.
But out of everyone
in Class One-D,
the most effective student
is Ayanokoji.
Uh.
The students from Class C wanted
to withdraw their complaint,
and against my better
judgement, I allowed it.
Oh, did they, now?
It's a strange world
we live in, I guess.
Are you trying to prove a point?
That Sakura is not
in fact the fabricator
everyone thinks that she is?
Well done, sir.
Your little sister is
the one behind all of it.
I didn't do anything, really.
Tachibana. We have an
opening for a secretary?
Yes.
[MANABU]
Well, then.
You just say the word,
and the secretary position
on the council is yours.
What? Are you serious?
[MANABU]
Do you object?
No. I was just making
sure I understood.
I have no objections to that.
Ayanokoji.
Please join the student council.
No, thank you.
I don't like expending more
energy than I have to.
The student council
seems like too much work.
And honestly, I just want
to have a normal life.
I accept that for now.
Ayanokoji.
It would be in your best
interest not to disappoint me.
[gasps]
[RYUEN]
Which one of you was it?
Who withdrew the complaint
without consulting me?
We... We're all responsible.
Well, Albert.
[ALBERT]
Sorry, boss's orders.
I've got no beef with you.
[thuds]
[ISHIZAKI groaning]
[RYUEN] My plan was to get
one of those idiots expelled,
to see how the
school would react.
Now, I'll have to
find another way.
You're all worthless.
It's entirely reasonable that
you should suffer for your sins.
Give me the names of
the ones who set you up,
and Al will go easy.
[gasps]
Sakayanagi?
I recognize you.
You're from Class C, aren't you?
It appears you think you've
already been crowned
queen of the school.
Well, that's just adorable.
I never intended to be
queen of anything.
I'm going to crush Class D,
and then Class B.
And before it's said and done,
I'm coming for Class A, too.
[SAKAYANAGI] Do you really think
you can make that happen?
[RYUEN] There can be
only one ruler here.
[SAKAYANAGI]
I couldn't agree more!
It's a relief that your little
plan worked, isn't it?
[SUZUNE]
You manipulated me, didn't you?
Admit it.
[AYANOKOJI]
What do mean by that?
[SUZUNE] You pointed out
the lack of cameras
in the special annex,
which then led me to plant
the false evidence and
bear all of the risk.
[AYANOKOJI] Nah, you're
just overthinking it.
You made a promise to me.
You said that you would
help me advance to Class A.
Yeah, only after you
virtually forced me to.
[AYANOKOJI gasps]
Hold on.
I'm not quite finished
with you yet.
I want to know what's
going on inside your head.
What you're thinking.
Well, I just want to
live my life in peace.
Is that so hard to understand?
You wouldn't help me if you
didn't want to, deep down.
Yeah, you're right,
I suppose I just wanted to
help a friend out. Ya happy?
[SUZUNE]
That's a lie.
You've never cared about your
friends, and you know it.
Who are you?
Really. What's your game?
[MALE TEACHER 6A]
Line up!
[BOY 6A whimpering]
[crash]
[gasping]
[AYANOKOJI] I will help you get
to Class A, like I promised.
But...
But, what?
[AYANOKOJI]
Don't go prying into my life.