[bell ringing]
[footsteps]
[MAN 10A]
Kiyotaka.
[MAN 10A] No matter what,
you must always remember this.
To have great power and refuse
to use it to your advantage
is something only
a fool would do.
[IKE]
Hey!
Check out all the
fish we caught!
And look at all this delicious
fruit that we picked!
Nice work! You guys are awesome.
[KEN] Okay, Hirata, what do
you want us to do next?
If you two wouldn't mind
getting the fire started,
that would be really helpful.
[KEN, IKE]
Sure!
Kushida, I'd like
you and your group
to oversee meal rations.
[KIKYO]
Right!
[HIRATA] Anyone else who
isn't busy can come help us
collect drinking water.
All right, then!
Can you help me carry these?
Oh! Okay!
[AYANOKOJI]
Yosuke Hirata.
Class D's unofficial
leader. Huh.
[SUZUNE] It's unusual to see
you take initiative like this.
I'm almost suspicious.
I have nothing better to do.
It helps pass the time.
I don't mind doing recon,
but I don't wanna
burn undue calories
I could store.
Stamina is valuable
on a desert island.
So, I don't like
wandering around
without a clear goal in mind.
I understand that logic.
But on the flip side,
staying cooped up
does us no good.
And, besides...
Next time, I'll deal
with you personally.
I'm so looking forward to it.
It's clear that Class C has
put a target on your back.
We've gotta be
vigilant about this.
[sighs] Yeah, that's true.
I know!
This is amazing!
[ICHINOSE] There's so much
fruit in the forest,
it's almost like
someone planted it!
But if we need to, we can
go fishing right here!
And the waterfalls provide
all our fresh water!
Looks like Class B
hit the jack pot.
You're all incredibly
disciplined. I'm impressed.
[laughs] It was
pretty hard at first.
But we rigged some things up,
and it's really worked out!
Ichinose.
Is it safe to assume that
Class B can be trusted
to cooperate with Class D?
[ICHINOSE] Mm-hm. That's
definitely how I see it.
[KANEDA]
Sorry to interrupt.
How can I help you?
Oh, I was wondering
if there was anything
you'd like me to do to help out.
Well, why not join
Chihiro and the others
to see if there's
anything they need?
I'd be happy to.
Thank you very much.
He strikes me as a bit
distant for someone
who's in your class.
[ICHINOSE] Oh, he's not.
His name is Kaneda.
He got driven out of Class C
because of some falling out.
So, he asked to join
our camp, instead.
Oh, sorry.
I'd love to chat more,
but there's more work to do!
Come visit again soon, okay?
As much as you know
I hate to admit this,
this is way better
than our spot.
I can't see inside.
There's a curtain over
the opening of the cave.
[AYANOKOJI]
Let's check it out.
What are you doing?
There's no reason to be
intimidated by them
just because they're Class A.
What are you trying to achieve?
We don't stand to gain anything
by revealing our presence.
[AYANOKOJI]
Skulking around in the bushes
won't get us anywhere, either.
Might as well see what happens.
[grunts]
[YAHIKO]
What do you want?
[SUZUNE]
We came to scout your spot.
You got a problem with that?
Huh?
How very underhanded.
We're coming in.
[YAHIKO]
Hey!
What?
This place is
property of Class A.
You don't get to see it.
Oh?
Are you saying you've taken
possession of this spot?
That's right. Go away.
I'm sorry, is there some
rule I'm not aware of
that states I can't
enter this cave?
I can't officially use
an occupied spot,
but no one ever said
I couldn't look inside.
That would be considered
monopolizing this space.
I think you're
breaking the rules.
So let me have a look, okay?
[KATSURAGI] What do you
think you're doing?
Katsuragi!
I don't recall
giving you permission
to invite your friends.
Look, I only wanna
see what's inside.
I can't imagine that
being against the rules.
Well, go ahead and have
a look inside, then.
But, be prepared
for the consequences.
Each class chooses to occupy
one spot on the island,
and they must defend that spot
until the test is over.
If you decide to break
this unwritten rule,
then that will mean war.
You'd be better off to avoid
that kind of trouble.
I think you need
to reapply sunscreen.
[STUDENT 10G]
One, two, three, you're gone!
You've got to be kidding me.
What in the world does
Class C think they're doing?
[KOMIYA]
Um.
Ryuen wants to talk to you guys.
[RYUEN]
Hey, there.
You all seem to be
living the high life.
[RYUEN]
Oh, we are doing exactly that.
It's our summer
vacation, after all.
Why shouldn't we enjoy it?
Right?
[GROUP]
Uh--
That's right!
[SUZUNE] An incompetent
leader only ends up
hurting his subjects.
Ishizaki.
[ISHIZAKI]
Yes, sir?
[RYUEN]
It's warm.
I'm very sorry, sir.
[RYUEN] For a measly one
or 200 class points.
The rest of you are willing
to endure starvation,
heat, exhaustion.
[RYUEN] The very thought
of it makes me wanna laugh.
I was dumb to come
here with my guard up
against a fool like you.
[RYUEN] Who's the real
fool here? Is it me?
Or is it you?
Ryuen, sir.
This is the way
that I operate,
and I refuse to settle for
anything less than that.
I see. Well then,
do whatever you want.
It's way better for us if
you're out of the game.
Oh, there was one other
thing I wanted to ask you.
You're familiar with
Ibuki, aren't you?
[RYUEN]
Of course, she's in our class.
So? What's it to you?
[SUZUNE] Her face was
messed up pretty badly.
Do you know how it may
have gotten that way?
Disobedient servants are
of no use to a ruler.
I only doled out the
appropriate punishment.
[SUZUNE]
You used up all of your S-points
on the first day, didn't you?
That's exactly right.
I spent all our class's
S-points yesterday.
So it doesn't really matter.
Ibuki can do what she wants and
it won't affect our S-points.
[AYANOKOJI] The rules state
that, even if you lose
all 300 of your S-points,
you can't ever
get into negative numbers.
He used that to his advantage.
A simplistic way of thinking.
I guess you don't mind
losing all the class points
we were offered.
[RYUEN]
Forget all of that.
Why don't you just
come play with me?
I'll prepare a special
tent for us, Suzune.
[SUZUNE] Let's get
out of here, Ayanokoji.
If I stay any longer, this
guy's gonna make me vomit.
Suzune, come back
when you're ready
to have the time of your life.
You know you want to.
I'll blow your mind if you would
just give me the afternoon.
Absurd, isn't it?
But their bad
decision benefits us.
Yeah.
In this test,
you need to conserve
any way that you can,
or there's no way
you'll last the whole week.
He's not planning to
last the whole week,
which is the reason
he did what he did.
What do you mean by that?
[AYANOKOJI]
It's pretty simple.
He'll do exactly
what Koenji did.
Cut any losses and run.
All they have to do
is claim to be sick,
or that they can't
handle the stress.
Then they can all
go back to the ship
and enjoy the rest of their
summer vacation in comfort.
Hold on, so you're
telling me that he never
had any intention of
participating in the test?
Well, this exam is about
freedom of choice, isn't it?
Ryuen might have
the best answer.
After all, he chose comfort.
I don't know. That's beyond me.
[AYANOKOJI] A zero point
strategy. Fascinating.
[snoring]
Good morning to you, Hirata.
Oh, morning, Ayanokoji.
I'm sorry if I woke you up.
[AYANOKOJI]
No, you didn't.
It's just hard for me
to sleep very well
in this kind of environment.
My back is killing me.
[laughs]
[HIRATA sighs]
That feels great.
[AYANOKOJI] It must be
stressful to be the one
keeping the class together.
I only do it because I enjoy it.
If I didn't, there is
no way I'd take that on.
I just like seeing
the class happy.
[BOYS laughing]
[SAKURA panting]
Are you really sure you
wanna be paired up with me?
Yeah. I'm sorry.
I know that I can be a total
drag when we're searching.
And you're not the
least bit worried?
People might start
to talk about us.
No, I couldn't care
less about it,
to tell you the truth.
And, anyway.
When we first set
out on the cruise,
I was feeling really down
in the dumps about it.
I don't have a single friend so,
I didn't see how a
cruise could be any fun.
But now... Now, I'm
having a good time.
I'm actually happy that I came.
I see.
[gasps]
[SAKURA]
Man, it's too bad.
If I had my camera right now,
I could take an
amazing picture of you.
[ICHINOSE]
Weird.
I wonder where they all
could have gone to.
[KANZAKI] Ayanokoji,
were you out on recon, too?
No, we were just out
exploring the forest.
And we ended up here
on the beach.
[ICHINOSE]
Aw. I'm so disappointed.
I was hoping to get an idea
of who Class C's leader is.
The primary goal
here is to amass
as many S-points as possible.
Too bad Ryuen gave up,
and so, he lost everything.
The straightforward
approach is definitely
the best strategy for us.
Ichinose.
There's something I've been
wanting to ask you about.
[ICHINOSE]
What's that?
[AYANOKOJI]
Well, Katsuragi from Class A.
Do you know anything about him?
You're interested in Katsuragi?
Well, I know that Sakayanagi is
sitting out the test completely.
So Katsuragi has now taken
temporary leadership
over Class A.
[KANZAKI]
Katsuragi's an intelligent guy.
Even with Sakayanagi gone,
I doubt Class A will suffer
much internal discord.
[ICHINOSE]
Although...
I doubt anyone who is
on Sakayanagi's side
is having a very good time.
Those two are opposite
extremes, after all.
Opposite extremes?
[ICHINOSE] A reformist and
a conservative, essentially.
Their approach to everything
is the polar opposite,
and I hear they're always
butting heads over that.
[AYANOKOJI]
Sakayanagi.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[IKE] Looks like we made
it through another day!
By the way,
I thought I saw all
the Class C people
heading to the ship
this afternoon.
Hirata, you know
anything about that?
No. I wish I did.
They probably just got
sick of the island life
and decided to quit
and head back to the ship.
You think the whole class did?
Can they even do that?
Why would I know any
better than you do?
[KIKYO]
Hey.
Are you going to head
back to the ship?
The last thing I wanna look
at is those jerks' faces.
So I am going to stay here.
[KEN] Seems kinda
suspicious, doesn't it?
[KIKYO]
Sudo, don't.
Hey.
Do you know anything
about what they planned?
Huh? No, leave me alone.
[KEN]
Hold it!
[IBUKI] You keep your
filthy hands off me!
What the heck is your problem?
We helped you,
so you owe us one.
Or, did you conveniently
forget about that?
I didn't even ask for
your help, remember?
Your people just forced
their help upon me.
Wasting your points
on an enemy? Idiots.
--Say that again!
--[HIRATA] Sudo!
Go ahead and hit me, then!
Both of you need to calm down.
This isn't the time for us to
start fighting among friends.
We're friends?
How stupid can you be?
[KIKYO]
Ibuki. Are you okay?
[KEN]
Damn it! What's her problem?
[SHINO]
Hey, you guys!
Guys, wake up already, come on!
[HASE]
Seriously, get up, now!
What's going on?
Look, Hirata. I've got bad news!
[HIRATA] What could it
possibly be? It's so early.
This probably has nothing
to do with you, Hirata.
But there's something we need
to get to the bottom
of right now.
This morning,
Karuizawa's underwear
went missing from her bag.
[gasps]
[SHINO] She's in our tent right
now, bawling her eyes out.
Kushida and the others
are trying to comfort her
to no avail.
Hold on. What are you saying?
You can't possibly suspect--!
[SHINO] Well, why shouldn't
we suspect you?
One of you obviously
snuck in and stole them
in the middle of the night!
You've got to be kidding.
It was probably that Ibuki
girl trying to frame us!
[SHINO] A girl would never
do something like that!
[IKE]
But how can you be so sure?
Look, the point is,
we refuse to camp
in the same place as an
underwear-thieving pervert!
[GIRLS chattering]
[HIRATA] Hey, everyone,
just calm down for a minute.
What proof do you have that
one of the Class D boys
stole the underwear, anyway?
That's why we came to you.
We trust you to find
the culprit for us.
You want me to do it?
To begin, we request
to conduct a search
of all the boys' bags!
[HIRATA]
Okay, fine.
But to protect their privacy,
will you agree to allow me
to conduct the search,
instead of you guys?
Come on. I'm startin'
to get pissed off.
They don't even
have any evidence
that a boy actually
did it. It's crazy!
[stammering]
What's wrong?
[IKE]
Uh, nothing.
Wait just a minute.
You're the one who
stole them, aren't you?
Dumbass! No, man, I'm not!
Uh-huh. No way.
Don't tell me that...
Of course not. Don't
start suspecting me!
[YAMAUCHI] Show me what
you've got in there!
Cut it out! I'm
innocent, I swear.
I didn't do anything!
[YAMAUCHI]
Caught red-handed!
No! I don't know how
they got there, I promise!
It wasn't me, dude.
I swear it wasn't!
No need to lie,
everyone's got their kinks, man.
I don't know how
they got in my bag!
[GIRLS murmuring]
Hey, you!
You believe I'm
innocent here, don't you?
Under the current
circumstances...
I can't say with
any level of certainty
that you're not the culprit.
A-Ayanokoji, why?
But, if you were,
I don't think you'd be so
careless. You'd cover it up.
You're right!
So, you think someone else
planted the panties
in Ike's bag?
Yeah!
That's gotta be what
happened, don'tcha think?
Hey! Hurry, it up!
What do I do? What do I do?
I'm in major trouble!
Good luck, man!
Uh--
You're gonna have to
hide them somewhere.
Oh, will I? Hide them
where? Help me out!
If you think hiding
them is the best idea,
then you hide them
yourself, smarty-pants!
[AYANOKOJI]
Hold on. I didn't mean--
[IKE]
I'll be right there!
Huh. You're kidding me.
[HIRATA]
We searched all the bags.
For real?
[HIRATA]
Mm-hm. So, now we know.
None of the boys here
were behind the theft.
We can let them put their
stuff away now, right?
And then we can talk
about the next step.
I demand a pat-down.
Uh--?
An underwear thief must
have a very deviant mind.
No telling where he
might be keeping them.
What?
Could you give us
a break already?
[INO] Ike's been acting
suspicious this whole time.
[SHINO] You think he's
the one who did it?
[MIT]
So gross!
[IKE growls]
Fine, have it your way.
Why don't you guys
just search me, then?
[AYANOKOJI] No, don't lead the
conversation down that path.
Yes, why don't we?
Hirata. Go ahead.
[AYANOKOJI] This is the worst
thing that could happen.
There's no way of talking
myself out of it.
I'd be better off
if I just told the truth.
They might believe me.
[HIRATA] Sorry. I'll make
this as quick as possible.
[AYANOKOJI]
It's over.
[gasps]
[HIRATA] Ayanokoji doesn't
have them, either.
[AYANOKOJI gasps]
So you can rest assured
it wasn't one of us.
[SHINO] Really? Well, if you
say so, I can trust it.
[HIRATA]
Thanks.
Right.
I'll let the others know,
if that's okay with you.
[SATO]
Yeah. See you later, then.
[AYANOKOJI]
Hirata. Can we talk for a sec?
Why didn't you tell
them what you found?
I thought so. That was
the underwear, then?
Yeah.
Did you take them, Ayanokoji?
No. I didn't.
Good, I believe you.
You aren't the kind of person
who'd do something like that.
Well, that's quite
a relief, but I think
it would be best if I
took those off your hands.
Are you sure?
Yeah, it's the only way.
I'll suffer least for
being the culprit.
I'm her boyfriend, after all.
[HIRATA] I really do believe
you didn't do it, Ayanokoji.
That's why I saved you.
And, the way you answer
won't change that,
but I just have to ask. Will
you find the actual culprit?
Me, help find the culprit?
Yes.
Well, I'll try my absolute
best to, at least.
Thanks a lot.
And if you do, will you let
me be the first to know?
Please?
I don't want anybody
else to hear about it.
So I need you to promise
that you'll tell me
before anyone else.
Are you asking me to help you
cover up the truth in all this?
"Cover up the truth." Huh.
Yeah, I guess that
is what I'm asking.
Because, no matter who it is,
I think it would be best for
us to bury the real story.
[HIRATA] I don't want everything
to be ruined over this.
So that's why
I would like your mind
working with me on it.