[bell ringing]
[IKE yelling]
[MALE STUDENTS yelling]
[YAMAUCHI]
We owe it all to you, Kushida!
[KEN] Yeah, you totally saved
our butts on this one!
You guys, it's not like
I took the test for you!
[IKE]
You're an angel!
Kushida, you must have been sent
from heaven to help us pass!
[SUZUNE]
Ayanokoji.
Be honest.
What exactly did you do?
[FEMALE STUDENT 3B]
Nice serve!
[KEN]
You want some? Come and get it!
What, do you think you're in
some kind of gangster movie
with that thug act?
Man, you're ugly inside
and out, you pathetic loser.
[growls] Say that again, punk!
[AYANOKOJI] Kushida asked me
to try to get him
to come to her study group,
but I don't know.
[RYUEN] I can't wait to see
how many Class D idiots
get expelled after
they fail the next test.
[KEN whimpers]
I bet I know who will be first.
[whimpering]
[KEN]
I hope you've said your prayers.
All right, that's enough!
What? Who're you?
Keep your damn nose out of it!
As one of your fellow students,
I cannot allow violence
to be perpetrated on this
campus, understand?
If you all insist on
continuing to fight anyway,
I'm going to have
to call security.
Look, Ichinose.
There isn't even a
fight to continue.
Sudo's victimizing us.
Is that so?
Well, from where I'm standing,
you certainly don't look
like victims to me, Ryuen.
And if you don't cut it out,
I'm going to report
every one of you to
the administration.
Hey, monkey.
You son of a--
[RYUEN] I think you're going to
make a mighty fine plaything.
Hey, punk! You runnin' away?
Answer me!
I'm talkin' to you!
[AYANOKOJI]
Relax.
[ICHINOSE]
Listen, Sudo.
Don't let him get you all
wound up like that, okay?
Shut your mouth.
You don't rule me.
Sorry for all the drama, guys!
Everything's cool now!
[FEMALE STUDENT 3A]
Thanks a bunch, Ichinose!
Okay guys, do your best
to stay out of trouble.
See ya!
Dammit!
Sudo. Are you free
for the next hour?
Kushida wants you to come
to her study group.
No way. I've got practice.
[AYANOKOJI]
Ike and Yamauchi are both in it.
Hey.
Are you sure you'll be
all right on your own?
[KEN] There's no point in
cramming for it now.
I'll take my chances.
[MALE STUDENT 3A]
Sudo!
[MALE STUDENT 3A] What's
the matter with you today?
[KEN]
Sorry!
[SUZUNE]
Hey, Sudo.
Can we talk for a minute?
Are you seriously okay
with getting expelled
from this school?
Just get off my back.
So, you'd give it up, then.
Basketball?
I've summarized all
the information from class
in this notebook.
[SUZUNE]
Just so you know,
I'm only doing this for my own
sake. You really should study
for yours, if you know
what's good for you.
That way you won't get expelled
and you can keep playing on
the basketball team
at this school.
[KIKYO] Ayanokoji. I can't
believe you invited me to lunch.
This sure is a first!
Did you want to talk to me
about something?
Yeah, just promise you won't
breathe a word to anyone.
[KIKYO]
Mm-hm!
[gasps]
Let's go.
[AYANOKOJI] Excuse me.
Are you an upperclassman?
I'm Kiyotaka Ayanokoji
from Class One-D.
You're in the D class for
your grade, too, aren't you?
Well, yeah.
[AYANOKOJI]
The free food selection
is pretty abysmal, isn't it?
[SEN]
What do you want from me?
I wanna consult with
you about something.
Don't worry, I will make
it worth your while.
About what?
Do you still have any of your
class's midterm questions
from two years ago?
[gasps]
I want you to hand
them over to me.
Why are you asking me, and not
the other upperclassmen?
Is it that hard to see?
People like you, who're
short on class points,
are way more likely to see
the benefit of striking
a deal with us.
And don't think I didn't notice
how hard you were struggling
to eat that wild
vegetable lunch combo.
[SEN sighs]
[SEN]
How much will you pay?
[AYANOKOJI]
Ten thousand points.
It's as high as I'll go.
[SEN] I'd be taking
a big risk here, too.
I would need 30,000
at the very least.
[AYANOKOJI]
I'm afraid that won't work.
Sorry to disappoint.
You can forget making
a deal with me, then.
[KIKYO]
Please reconsider!
We're doing this to prevent
a friend of ours from
getting kicked out of school!
I'm begging you to help us.
[gasping]
[AYANOKOJI]
10,000.
No, 25.
[AYANOKOJI]
10,000.
20,000.
[AYANOKOJI]
10,000. That's it.
[SEN growls]
15,000.
I can't possibly go any lower.
I can live with that.
You've got a deal.
That is, if you
include your quizzes
from the first term as a bonus.
[SEN]
Okay...
I can't ever thank you enough!
[KIKYO]
But, still...
How do you know that
it'll be okay?
Don't worry about it.
This is all well
within school rules.
I suppose that could be true.
But studying old test questions?
That feels an awful lot
like cheating.
I disagree with you on that.
His reaction to our proposition
only confirmed my theory.
Trading old test questions
among students is
nothing out of the
ordinary at this school.
Maybe that's because they're
just that: old questions.
What if this year's exam
isn't anything like
the one from before?
The old test may not contain
the exact same questions,
but I'm willing to bet it'll
still cover the same content.
You think so?
Try not to worry about it.
This is our first
line of defense
against Sudo and the
others getting expelled.
[phone chimes]
[AYANOKOJI] Here we go.
He started with a quiz.
It's the same. Identical,
down to the letter.
Oh, that's great!
So, what does that mean
about the midterm?
It'll prob'ly be the same
as last years, too.
We should show that
to the whole class,
not just the people
in danger of failing.
Not yet.
We'll hold off on showing
it to them for now.
But, why?
Say we show them the
questions ahead of time.
What do you think they'll
do in that knowledge?
[gasps] They'll memorize all
the answers instead of study!
That's precisely it.
Ayanokoji, are you a lot
smarter than you let on?
I'd say I'm more
cunning than smart.
[AYANOKOJI] Hey. Do you think
you could do me a favor?
[gasps]
[AYANOKOJI] When we do this,
can you tell the class
that you're the one
who got the questions?
Sure, if you want, but
wouldn't you like to get credit
for your hard work?
I don't like to draw attention
to myself unnecessarily.
And anyway.
I think our classmates trust you
a little more than they do me.
Okay, then.
If you're positive that's
what you really want.
I appreciate it.
Well. I guess this
means you and I
have our own little
secret, don't we?
[KIKYO]
Hang on, everyone!
There's something
I want you to have
before you leave for the day.
What, test questions?
Did you make these up,
or something?
[KIKYO] Actually, they're
questions that were on
the midterm a couple years ago.
I got them last night from
one of the third years.
Seriously?
[KIKYO] Mm-hm. He told me
that the tests have been
pretty much identical for
the last couple of years.
So, I bet they'll be helpful
in studying for
tomorrow's test, too!
Are you freaking kidding me?!
Heck, I wish I'd had these
before I ran myself
ragged studying.
This is awesome!
[KIKYO]
Here you go, Koenji!
I beg your pardon, but I don't
need to resort to such tactics.
And I've got a hot date
tonight, so excuse me.
Have fun with your studying.
[KIKYO gasping]
Hey, Kushida.
I know things like this
might be beneath you,
but I want you to have one, too.
Can I ask you a question?
Thanks a million, Kushida!
I shall be forever in your debt!
[KIKYO laughs]
To be honest, I think the only
reason I might have done okay...
I can't say I'm surprised.
Kushida plays the role well.
That's an insult.
I must say,
I'm impressed with you.
I never imagined you'd be able
to bring your scores up
so much on this exam.
I acknowledge that you
must have put in the effort.
However...
[CHABASHIRA]
Sudo got a failing grade.
Too bad.
[KEN gasping]
[KEN]
What? You've got to be kidding!
How could I possibly
have failed?!
[CHABASHIRA]
The threshold for failure
on the midterm exam
was 40 points.
The average class
test score was 79.6.
When I divide that by two
then round up to 40 points,
I get the minimum
score needed to pass.
By less than a point?
We only knew each other
for a short time,
and I know you tried.
Your expulsion notice will be
issued after class anyway.
So, that's it?
I'm getting expelled?
Wait, Miss Chabashira!
Is there anything
we can do to save him?
[CHABASHIRA] A failing score
is a failing score.
Are you sure that's
the final word?!
We just can't let Sudo get
kicked out like this!
It doesn't seem right.
Rules exist for a reason.
Just get over it.
[gasps]
Homeroom is over for today.
Sudo, I'll be waiting for you
in the faculty office
after school.
[door slides]
Well, are we just gonna
let them do this? It's terrible.
Sudo is going to be expelled.
[KIKYO]
Ayanokoji?
Sorry. Gotta go to the restroom.
[gasps]
[door slides]
What do you want?
You'll be tardy if you don't
head back to class.
Yeah, I know.
But I have a question.
A burning question.
Make it fast.
Right now, in Japan,
do you believe
that our society is equal?
That's quite a question
for a boy of your age.
But is there any point in my
answering it this moment?
It's important to me.
I would appreciate an answer.
[CHABASHIRA] Well, speaking
from my own experience.
Our society is definitely not
equal. Not in the least.
[AYANOKOJI]
I'm inclined to agree with you.
The word "equality" is
a lie that we're told.
But still. Humans are rational.
We didn't become social
beings for no reason.
[CHABASHIRA]
What are you trying to say?
[AYANOKOJI] What I'm saying is,
for rules to be effective,
they have to at least appear
to apply equally to everybody.
Huh?!
So, what do you want?
Sell me a point on that test,
to add to Sudo's score.
[laughs]
You sure are an interesting kid.
Do you really expect me to
sell you a single test point?
Well, why not?
It goes along with what you
told us on the first day.
To make purchases,
you will spend points,
which are tracked using the
school's computer system.
At this school, you can buy
absolutely anything
on campus with these.
For rules to work, they must
be applied across the board,
even when it comes
to the midterm.
I see what you mean.
Maybe there is something to
your little idea after all.
However, that doesn't mean you
can afford that single point.
It's quite a lot.
So, give me a number.
[CHABASHIRA]
Let me see.
If you can cough up
100,000 points,
right here and now, then
we'll have an agreement.
That's just cruel,
Ms. Chabashira.
That's part of the rules, too.
[SUZUNE]
I'll help cover it.
[SUZUNE] We don't know what
the punishment is.
The price for losing one of our
classmates might be high.
I've determined that there
may be certain advantages
to us keeping Sudo around.
Horikita.
[CHABASHIRA chuckles]
I thought that you people
might keep me on my toes.
Very well then.
I'll sell you Sudo's test point.
You can tell him you saved him.
He won't be expelled after all.
[AYANOKOJI]
Are you sure about this?
[CHABASHIRA]
You made your case and I agreed.
I couldn't refuse now.
Just so you're aware, never
in this school's history
has a D class
managed to advance.
Do you think you'll
be the first?
I can't speak for him, but I
will ascend to a higher class.
Is that so?
And how do defectives
such as yourselves,
plan to achieve such a goal?
From what I've seen "defectives"
can sometimes be fixed
with only the slightest
of alterations.
At least in my experience.
[CHABASHIRA chuckles] I can't
wait to see how that turns out.
As your teacher, I sincerely
hope that you succeed.
[KATSURAGI]
Class C is gaining on us.
Looks like Ryuen must
be at work again.
He's dangerous for us.
Don't you find it all boring?
Class A has 1,004 points.
For some perspective,
we only have 87 right now.
To be honest, becoming Class A
feels like a pipe dream.
[SUZUNE]
I'm not going to give up.
I will advance to Class A,
no matter what.
If you say so.
What's that?
Well. I definitely owe ya one.
Thanks for jumping in
to help me save Sudo.
Didn't I tell you?
I did that to benefit myself
and for no other purpose.
[AYANOKOJI] Hm...
Is that really the only reason?
What are you talking about?
I think you care more
than you let on.
You knew Sudo would
get a borderline score
on the English midterm.
So you intentionally
lowered your score.
That's a very nice thing
to do for someone
you once fought with.
Wonder why you changed
your mind about him.
I told you, I only did it to
help us advance to Class A.
[AYANOKOJI]
Yeah, okay.
Just keep tellin' yourself that.
[SUZUNE]
Hey. You've got an attitude.
I don't like it very much,
Ayanokoji.
Uh...
[SUZUNE] You'll regret it
if it causes you to suffer,
or you'll regret it
if you feel despair.
Which of the above experiences
would you prefer?
[AYANOKOJI] Well, if it's up to
me, I think I'll take "neither."
But what's she doing
with that compass?
[thud]
[AYANOKOJI]
Ouch.
[STUDENTS]
Cheers!
[sighs]
Hey! Why the long face, man?
I have no objections to the
fact that we're celebrating,
and I'm glad to be a part of it.
But why does it have
to be in my room?
[YAMAUCHI] Man, that was
a close call, am I right?
If Kushida hadn't gotten
those old test questions,
Ike and Sudo would be long gone
by now, you know what I mean?
Hey. You just barely
squeaked by, too, y'know.
I just haven't gotten
my act together yet.
[IKE] Sudo, how did you
manage to fail...
[KIKYO]
Hey, Ayanokoji!
What is it?
[KIKYO]
How were you able to get them
to take back Sudo's expulsion?
Horikita talked to
the administration.
She told them that it wasn't
right to expel someone
as they're struggling to learn.
She said it's a process.
--Hey, wait a minute.
--Horikita, is that true?
I've never seen her speak so
passionately about anything.
It was quite impressive.
She presented this carefully
constructed indictment,
and none of them
could argue with her.
That's amazing, Horikita.
You're a real hero.
Wow, I guess I had the wrong
idea about you all along!
Can you believe it? All for you.
No, I can't. Why would she
do that for my sake?
Look, I didn't.
I was doing it for my own
benefit and nothing else.
[YAMAUCHI laughs] Wow, beauty,
passion, and brains!
[IKE]
I'll say!
[water running,
dishes clattering]
Thanks for helping me out.
I really appreciate it.
I should thank you!
You didn't have to let us have
the party in your room.
No prob.
[KIKYO]
Hey, can I ask you something?
Yeah, what?
[KIKYO]
Well, would you say that girls
like Horikita are your type?
I'm just curious.
I always see you two together,
and all the girls in class
are talking about it.
Horikita and I are just friends.
No, she's just my neighbor.
I see.
Okay, then.
I guess I should
head back to my room.
Right.
[KIKYO]
Well, goodnight.
Goodnight to you, too.
Uh?
[AYANOKOJI] I thought the girls
were on the higher floors.
[AYANOKOJI] Where could she be
going this late at night?
[AYANOKOJI] I don't see why
I should be hiding, but...
[KIKYO]
What a pain in the ass.
Uh?
[KIKYO] So, you think
you're better than me
just because you're prettier?
I hate your guts!
I swear to god, I hate you,
I hate you, I hate you!
I wish you would just
drop dead, Horikita!
I hate you! I hate you!
You stupid cow!
[phone chimes]
Who's there?
Is someone spying on me?
[AYANOKOJI]
It's just me.
Ayanokoji.
I'm sorry. You left
your phone in my room.
Did you hear me?
If I told you that I didn't,
would you believe me?
If you breathe a word about
this to anyone, you'll pay.
[AYANOKOJI]
How, exactly?
I'll tell everyone in the entire
school you attempted to rape me.
[AYANOKOJI]
But you know that isn't true.
[KIKYO]
You're wrong.
I have the evidence to prove it.
[gasps]
Your fingerprints and DNA
in a very telling location.
That's all the proof I need.
I'm deadly serious.
I understand. Can I please
go back to my room?
[KIKYO]
You got it?
If you betray me,
I'll make you pay.
[inaudible]
[KIKYO]
Ayanokoji.
I want you to answer
just one question.
Can you promise me right now
that you won't tell anyone
what you heard me say?
[KIKYO]
I'm glad to hear it,
and I choose to believe
you for the time being.
[exhales] All right, then!
Well, I guess this means
we have another secret!
[AYANOKOJI]
Kushida. I don't understand.
Who are you, really?