- Alastor:
THE AUTUMN FESTIVAL TURNED OUT
TO BE MORE EVENTFUL
THAN ANYONE HAD ANTICIPATED.
THE SILVER MATERIALIZED,
HECATE AWAKENED KONOE,
JOHAN BRIEFLY TOOK OVER
YUJI'S BODY,
AND PHELES
DEPARTED TO TAKE CARE
OF UNFINISHED BUSINESS.
AND SO BEGINS
OUR NEXT CHAPTER.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Boy: WE ALL CLEAR?
- Boy #2: ALL CLEAR!
- OKAY, YOU GUYS READY?
- All: YEAH!
- AND PULL!
WHOA WHOA, EASY!
- Boy: GOT IT!
- CLEAN UP'S GOING A LOT FASTER
THAN I THOUGHT.
- IT'S SURPRISING.
- NOT REALLY, WE STARTED
AS SOON AS THE FESTIVAL ENDED.
- BUT YOU WOULDN'T KNOW,
BECAUSE YOU WEREN'T HERE
TO HELP OUT.
- AT LEAST YOU GUYS
ARE HERE TODAY, UNLIKE SATO.
- DON'T LET WHAT SHE SAID
GET TO YOU, YOSHIDA.
ALL THAT MATTERS
IS YOU'RE HERE NOW.
- Fujita:
AHA! FOUND YOU, IKE!
WHY ARE YOU CLEANING
WHEN WE'VE GOT MUCH MORE
IMPORTANT THINGS TO DO?
WE'VE GOT TO TAKE DOWN
ALL THE FLIERS
AND MAKE SURE
ALL THE RENTED EQUIPMENT
GETS RETURNED.
LISTEN, I KNOW
IT'S A LOT OF WORK,
BUT YOU SIGNED UP FOR THIS.
- AREN'T THE UPPER CLASSMEN
IN CHARGE OF THAT STUFF?
- LIKE WE CAN TRUST
THOSE MORONS TO DO IT ALL.
IF YOU WANT SOMETHING
DONE RIGHT, DO IT YOURSELF.
- FUJITA MAY BE BOSSY,
BUT SHE SURE KNOWS
HOW TO GET THE JOB DONE.
- Ike: I CAN WALK ON MY OWN,
YOU KNOW.
YOU DON'T
HAVE TO DRAG ME AROUND.
- IF I DON'T,
YOU'LL START LOLLYGAGGING AGAIN,
AND WE DON'T HAVE ANY TIME
TO WASTE RIGHT NOW.
- ( protesting )
- Girl:
HEY, WHAT ABOUT THESE?
WHAT SHOULD WE DO
WITH THE COSTUMES
FROM THE PARADE?
- WE COULD KEEP THEM
AS MEMENTOS,
BUT WE'RE SUPPOSED TO
DONATE THEM TO THE DRAMA CLUB.
- WAIT.
WHOSE COSTUME WAS THIS?
- I BET IT BELONGS
TO ANOTHER CLASS.
MUST'VE GOTTEN MIXED UP
WITH OURS.
- WELL, NOW THAT FUMINA KONOE'S
DISAPPEARED,
IT'S AS THOUGH
SHE NEVER EVEN EXISTED.
SINCE NO ONE ELSE
REMEMBERS HER,
WE'RE THE ONLY ONES
WHO'LL EVER KNOW SHE'S GONE.
- HOW SAD.
- Yuji: THAT-- THAT THING
IS INSIDE OF ME.
- HERE YOU ARE, BEL-PEOL.
THIS BELONGS TO YOU.
- THANKS.
I HOPE IT SERVED YOU WELL.
- WE WERE CLOSE
TO DESTROYING THE MYSTES,
BUT I'M AFRAID
WE WERE INTERRUPTED
AND THEREFORE UNABLE
TO RETRIEVE
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD, MA'AM.
- WHILE I'M DISAPPOINTED,
I DON'T BELIEVE
THERE'S CAUSE FOR CONCERN.
IT SIMPLY
WASN'T IN THE CARDS TODAY.
BUT WE'LL GET OUR HANDS
ON IT EVENTUALLY.
- YES!
THAT'S THE SPIRIT!
( cackling )
WITH OUR FRIEND HERE,
WE CAN'T FAIL!
AND NOW I HAVE THE TIME
TO COLLECT MORE DATA ON HIM.
- WHAT FUN!
OHH, THIS IS TERRIBLY EXCITING!
NOW LET'S WAKE HIM,
SHALL WE?
- RISE AND SHINE!
WE HAVE BIG PLANS FOR YOU!
- IT APPEARS OUR INVESTMENT
IS ABOUT TO PAY OFF.
- HEY, ANY IDEA
WHERE WE'RE SUPPOSED
TO TAKE THESE?
UH, YUJI?
- HUH?
- WHAT IS THE MATTER?
- NOTHING.
I'M FINE.
- YO, YOU HAVE SOME FREE TIME
TONIGHT?
MARGERY SAID SHE WANTED
TO HAVE A WORD WITH YOU GUYS.
- SHE WANTS TO DISCUSS
OUR SITUATION,
BUILD OUR STRATEGY
FOR THE FUTURE, RIGHT?
- YEAH, SOMETHING
ALONG THOSE LINES, I THINK.
SHE ALSO MENTIONED
THAT SHE WANTED TO EXAMINE YUJI
ONE MORE TIME.
SHE'S TRYING TO PLAY IT SAFE.
YOU KNOW,
CONSIDERING EVERYTHING
THAT'S HAPPENED LATELY.
- I'LL BE THERE.
- YOSHIDA?
IS EVERYTHING OKAY?
- YEAH.
- YOU DON'T HAVE TO COME
IF YOU'RE NOT UP TO IT.
- NO, I'M FINE, IT'S JUST...
- I WANT YOU TO HAVE THIS.
- I NEED TO BE THERE.
- OKAY, THEN.
- WHY ARE YOU
GIVING THIS TO ME?
- AS A FLAME HAZE,
MY MISSION IS TO MAINTAIN
THE WORLD'S BALANCE.
IT WOULD NOT
BE AFFECTED BY THE LOSS
OF AN ORDINARY HUMAN.
- WHA-
WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
- THIS TREASURE TOOL
ALLOWS YOU TO SUMMON ME.
BUT IN DOING SO,
IT WILL CONSUME
ALL OF YOUR POWER OF EXISTENCE.
IF THAT MYSTES
IS EVER IN DANGER,
I WANT YOU TO SUMMON ME.
I'M BEGGING YOU.
MAKE THE SACRIFICE,
FOR JOHAN'S SAKE,
AND MY OWN.
- ( Marcosias laughing )
I CAN'T BELIEVE
BAL MASQUE PULLED ONE OVER
ON THREE FLAME HAZE!
PRETTY PATHETIC
IF YOU ASK ME, LADIES.
- FUMINA KONOE.
- Alastor: SHE WAS AFTER
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD,
JUST AS WE SUSPECTED.
WE SHOULD HAVE TRUSTED
OUR INITIAL INSTINCTS.
I'M ASHAMED
WE WERE SO EASILY FOOLED.
- GIVE IT A REST, WOULD YA?
HOW THE HELL WERE WE SUPPOSED
TO KNOW KONOE WAS A SPY?
WE ATE LUNCH WITH HER,
WE HUNG OUT WITH HER.
SHE WAS OUR FRIEND, DAMN IT.
- OKAY, I'M DONE.
- SO WHAT THE HELL
IS GOING ON WITH HIM ALREADY?
- EVIDENTLY
BEFORE IT WAS RESEALED,
A TRANSMITTER OF SORTS
WAS IMPLANTED
IN THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
- SO THEY'RE WATCHING
HIS EVERY MOVE?
- MM-HMM.
- RESEAL THE TREASURE TOOL.
- AS IF THAT RIDICULOUS KEEPER
WASN'T ENOUGH TO DEAL WITH.
I CAN'T GO DIGGING TOO DEEP
BECAUSE THERE'S NO WAY
OF KNOWING
WHAT ELSE MIGHT BE IN THERE.
JUST WHEN I THOUGHT
I FINALLY HAD THE BASTARD.
- WHO?  THE SILVER?
- MM-HMM.
HONESTLY, WE WOULD HAVE BEEN
SCREWED IF IT WASN'T FOR PHELES.
THE ONLY REASON BAL MASQUE
RETREATED
WAS BECAUSE SUMMONING JOHAN
SPOILED THEIR PLANS.
- CHANTER OF ELEGIES,
I DON'T UNDERSTAND HOW
HE WAS ABLE TO MATERIALIZE
AFTER THE TREASURE TOOL
HAD BEEN RESEALED.
I WOULDN'T THINK
THAT WAS POSSIBLE.
- AS FAR AS I COULD TELL,
IT LOOKED LIKE JOHAN
MANIPULATED A SPELL
I WAS USING TO SECURE YUJI.
IT WAS SUPPOSED
TO FORCE OUTWARD-FLOWING POWER
TO MOVE BACK INWARD,
BUT HE REVERSED IT
AND USED THE POWER FLOW
TO BREAK FREE.
- Marcosias:
HE ALTERED YOUR SPELL
TO BENEFIT HIMSELF?
GUESS HE'S A LOT SMARTER
THAN HE LOOKS.
- WELL, IT WOULD BE
A SIMPLE TASK INDEED
FOR THE CREATOR
OF THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD
TREASURE TOOL.
- HMMM!  WHATEVER.
HE'S JUST ANOTHER PROBLEM
LOCKED INSIDE THE POOR KID.
I FEEL FOR YA, BRO.
- ON THE BRIGHT SIDE,
AT LEAST NOW WE KNOW
THAT BAL MASQUE
IS STILL GUNNING
FOR THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
- I CAN ONLY ASSUME THEIR PLAN
FOR ACQUIRING THE TREASURE TOOL
IS DESTROYING ITS MYSTES.
- Tiamat: PROCEED WITH CAUTION.
- I'M NOT GOING TO LET THEM
TOUCH HIM!
I'LL PROTECT YOU.
- WE SHOULD PROBABLY
CONTACT OUTLAW FOR INFO.
CAN YOU DO THAT?
- INDEED I CAN, CHANTER.
- I'LL KEEP AN EYE OUT
FOR QUESTIONABLE ACTIVITY.
- Alastor: I HOPE I'M WRONG.
BUT WE'VE SEEN SO MANY DENIZENS
AND FLAME HAZE COME AND GO,
MISAKI CITY COULD BE
A MAELSTROM OF WARFARE.
- MAELSTROM OF WARFARE?
- I HAVE A SNEAKING SUSPICION
THIS CITY
IS SOMEHOW
ATTRACTING THE MISFORTUNE
THAT HAS BEFALLEN IT.
AND I FEAR
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD
MIGHT HAVE SOMETHING
TO DO WITH IT.
- Shana: SO YOU THINK DENIZENS
AND FLAME HAZE
ARE SOMEHOW BEING DRAWN HERE?
- THAT'S CORRECT.
AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED,
THERE'S NO OTHER EXPLANATION
FOR THE CALAMITY
WE'VE WITNESSED HERE THUS FAR.
I FEAR
WHAT THE FUTURE MAY HOLD.
- WHEN DO YOU THINK
YOU'LL BE HOME AGAIN?
- WHO KNOWS?
- THEN IT'S A GOOD THING
ABSENCE MAKES THE HEART
GROW FONDER.
- EVERY TIME I COME HOME,
YOU AND I PICK UP
RIGHT WHERE WE LEFT OFF.
BUT NOT SO MUCH WITH YUJI.
I LEFT AND ALL OF A SUDDEN
HE'S MR. POPULAR.
WOULD YOU GIRLS
KEEP AN EYE ON HIM FOR ME?
- SURE, NOT A PROBLEM.
- YEAH, WE'D LOVE TO.
- CHIGUSA,
HOW WOULD YOU LIKE
TO TAKE ME
ON A DATE TO THE AIRPORT?
- I'D BE HONORED.
THAT OKAY WITH YOU?
- YEAH, GO AHEAD.
- BE GOOD WHILE I'M GONE.
- THANKS.
TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF, DAD.
- YOU TOO.
- Yuji: I CAN'T HELP BUT FEEL
SO DISTANT FROM MOM AND DAD.
- YUJI.
- YEAH?
- WILHELMINA TOLD ME
SHE WANTS YOU TO LEND HER
A HAND WITH SOMETHING.
- SHE WANTS ME TO HELP HER?
BUT WITH WHAT?
- LET'S GO FIND OUT.
- 'KAY.
THAT'LL WORK FINE.
I WANT TO ASK YOU
AND ALASTOR SOMETHING.
AND WILHEMINA
MIGHT WANT TO WEIGH IN TOO.
- I GUESS THIS
IS WHERE I SAY GOODBYE.
- UH, YEAH.
THANKS FOR COMING
TO SEE MY DAD OFF.
- SURE.
- WELL, I'LL SEE YA.
- I WISH I HAD THE KIND
OF RELATIONSHIP WITH SAKAI
THAT SHANA HAS WITH HIM.
I'M SO JEALOUS OF HER.
I CAN'T HELP MYSELF.
- YOU ARE AN ORDINARY HUMAN,
WHICH MAKES YOUR EXISTENCE
IN OUR WORLD FUTILE.
HOWEVER, IF YOU'RE BRAVE ENOUGH
TO USE THIS,
YOU WILL PROVE
YOUR WORTH TO US.
THIS TREASURE TOOL
ALLOWS YOU TO SUMMON ME.
BUT IN DOING SO,
IT WILL CONSUME
ALL OF YOUR POWER OF EXISTENCE.
- DON'T SEE YOU IN THIS PART
OF TOWN OFTEN.
- YOU SURPRISED ME.
I WAS JUST ON MY WAY HOME
FROM SAKAI'S HOUSE.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
WHERE ARE YOU HEADED?
- ME?  I WAS JUST
GOING FOR A LITTLE WALK...
TO TANAKA'S.
- THIS PARK.
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- KONOE.
- WHO?
- SHE WAS A GIRL IN OUR CLASS.
AND SHE WAS OUR FRIEND!
DON'T YOU REMEMBER?
- WHOA.
CALM DOWN, KAZUMI.
DON'T BE UPSET.
I DON'T KNOW A KONOE.
- OH.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
FORGET I SAID ANYTHING.
- Yuji: ALL OF THESE REPORTS
WERE SENT FROM OUTLAW?
- YES, BUT I'M AFRAID MOST OF IT
IS USELESS INFORMATION
REGARDING EVERYTHING
FROM LONG-TERM WEATHER FORECASTS
TO MAJOR TRAIN SCHEDULES.
- ( grunting )
I WOULD LIKE YOU TWO
TO ORGANIZE THIS MESS OF PAPER.
WHILE YOU'RE DOING THAT,
I'LL START COMBING
THROUGH THE REPORTS
FOR APPLICABLE INFORMATION.
- Tiamat:
LET'S GET TO WORK.
- YEAH.
- HEY, SHANA?
- YEAH?
- WOULD YOU MIND
LENDING ME BLUTSAUGER?
- WAIT,
YOU MEAN SORATH'S SWORD?
- YEAH.
- WHAT DO YOU INTEND
TO DO WITH IT?
- I WANT TO LEARN TO WIELD IT
SO I CAN HELP YOU FIGHT.
- YOUR CALL, ALASTOR.
- HMM.
CONSIDERING THE AMOUNT
OF DANGER HE'S FACING,
IT MIGHT NOT BE A BAD IDEA.
VERY WELL.
- THANK YOU, ALASTOR.
- Wilhelmina:
BAL MASQUE WOULD NEVER
SEND THE SUPREME THRONE
JUST TO RESEAL
A TREASURE TOOL.
THEY MUST HAVE HAD
AN ULTERIOR MOTIVE.
- ( creaking )
- PERFECT.
IT LOOKS LIKE WE'RE
READY TO PROCEED.
AT THIS POINT,
EVERYTHING ELSE IS UP TO HIM.
- HA!
WELL, WHY SHOULD WE WAIT
WHEN I CAN BEGIN
TESTING HIS RESONANCE
AT THIS VERY MOMENT?
AHH, DOMINO, I COULD USE
YOUR ASSISTANCE HERE.
- AT YOUR SERVICE,
PROFESSOR!
- SO MANY SPELLS
IN ONE TREASURE TOOL.
THINKIN' ABOUT IT
MAKES MY BRAIN HURT.
- Marcosias: DON'T FORGET
YOU'VE STILL GOT TO FIGURE OUT
WHO THE SILVER IS,
HOW HE MATERIALIZES
OUT OF NOWHERE,
AND WHAT IT WILL TAKE
TO KILL HIM.
I HOPE YOU'RE READY
TO DO SOME HOMEWORK,
MY TIPSY LITTLE SCHOLAR,
MARGERY DAW.
- I'M READY.
IT'S TAKEN ME SO MANY YEARS
TO FIND THE BASTARD.
THERE'S NO WAY
I'M LETTING HIM ESCAPE NOW.
- I DON'T WANT TO DIE.
BUT I WANT THE OTHERS
TO RESPECT ME.
I-- I WANT TO PROVE MY WORTH
TO THEM.
ACCORDING TO PHELES,
THE ONLY WAY TO DO THAT
IS TO SACRIFICE MYSELF.
BUT I DON'T WANT THAT EITHER.
'CAUSE WHEN I'M GONE,
SAKAI AND SHANA
WILL STILL BE HERE TOGETHER.
WHY?
( sobbing )
- ( grunts )
- DON'T JUST SWING
WITH YOUR ARMS,
PUT YOUR WHOLE BODY INTO IT
AND FEEL THE FLOW OF POWER
OF EXISTENCE.
- RIGHT.
I'VE GOT TO DO IT.
I'VE GOT TO GET STRONGER!
- Alastor:
I NEVER IMAGINED HE WOULD FIND
SUCH COMMITMENT.
- MMM.
- ALL I WANT--
ALL I WANT
IS TO BE WITH SAKAI.
- Pheles: IF YOU'RE BRAVE ENOUGH
TO USE THIS.
YOU WILL PROVE
YOUR WORTH TO US.
- ( twittering )
- ( theme music playing )
- Yuji: EVEN THOUGH MARGERY
PERFORMED A RESTORATION
AFTER HER RAMPAGE
THAT DEMOLISHED THE SCHOOL,
SHE COULDN'T FIX EVERYTHING.
THERE'S STILL A LOT OF DAMAGE
DEEP WITHIN THE HEARTS
OF HER FOLLOWERS,
TANAKA AND SATO.
THE PATH THESE TWO HAD CHOSEN
TO WALK TOGETHER
IS ABOUT TO DIVERGE.
NEXT TIME
ON "SHAKUGAN NO SHANA SECOND,"
"RESPECTIVE PATHS."