- Alastor: YUJI WAS
CONFRONTED BY A JAEGER
FROM BAL MASQUE
NAMED ZAROVEE.
ONCE YUJI FIGURED OUT HIS PLAN,
HE ATTACKED
AND KILLED THE DENIZEN.
SHANA ARRIVED
IN THE NICK OF TIME,
DEFEATING ZAROVEE'S PARTNER,
THE WANDERER BIFRONS,
JUST AS HE WAS ABOUT TO FIRE.
- ( theme music playing )
- Yuji: ALL OF A SUDDEN,
THAT WEIRD FEELING'S
BACK AGAIN.
CAN'T WORRY ABOUT THAT NOW.
SHANA!  THERE'S SOMETHING
I'VE BEEN MEANING TO TELL YOU.
- AH!
- WHOA!
- ( fire crackling )
- Yuji: WHAT HAPPENED?
AH!  AHHH!
WHO THE HELL IS HE?
WHOEVER HE IS,
HE'S A LOT STRONGER
THAN THOSE OTHER DENIZEN.
AND HE'S SO POWERFUL.
WHY DIDN'T I
SENSE HIS PRESENCE?
WHO ARE YOU?
- Wilhelmina:
HIS NAME IS SABRAC,
THE DESTRUCTIVE BLADE.
- WILHELMINA.
- HE IS THE CRIMSON LORD
WHO WORKS AS AN ASSASSIN
THAT I WARNED YOU ABOUT.
- Yuji: SO THIS IS THE GUY
WHO CAST THE SPELL.
- SOMEHOW I KNEW
YOU WOULD BE THE FIRST
TO STAND UP TO ME.
OUR PREVIOUS BATTLES
MUST HAVE TAUGHT YOU WELL.
YOU'RE THE ONLY FLAME HAZE
WHO'S PREPARED TO COUNTER
MY ATTACK.
- SABRAC,
PREPARE TO BE DEFEATED
BY THE SPECIALIST OF EVERYTHING,
WILHELMINA CARMEL.
- Tiamat: GET HIM!
- YOUR SKILLS
ARE AS IMPRESSIVE AS I REMEMBER.
IT IS A SHAME
YOU'RE ON MY LIST
OF THOSE I WAS SENT HERE
TO ASSASSINATE.
AND IT IS MY DUTY
TO SEE EVERY NAME
CROSSED OFF THAT LIST.
- WHOA!
- I MUST BE MORE CAREFUL.
I LOST A SWORD IN THAT STRIKE.
SHE IS A STRONG ADVERSARY,
BUT THAT IS NO EXCUSE
FOR LOSING MY WEAPONRY.
I SHALL HAVE TO KEEP AN EYE OUT
FOR ANOTHER SWORD TO REPLACE IT.
I DOUBT IT WILL BE THE ONLY ONE
LOST DURING THIS BATTLE.
- AHHHH!
- THERE IS NO REASON
TO BE ALARMED.
- Tiamat:
SO PLEASE STOP YELLING.
- IT VEXES ME
THAT YOU ARE STILL ABLE TO FIGHT
AFTER RECEIVING
SUCH A POWERFUL BLOW.
I HAVE FACED COUNTLESS ENEMIES
ON THE BATTLEFIELD,
BUT YOU ARE THE ONLY ONE
WHO TRULY MAKES MY BLOOD BOIL.
I WAS CONSERVING MY POWER
IN CASE
A MORE FORMIDABLE OPPONENT
APPEARED.
IT SEEMS THAT STRATEGY
WILL ONLY INHIBIT MY WORK HERE.
- WILHELMINA!
YOUR-- YOUR WOUNDS--
- IT'S SABRAC'S
UNRESTRICTED SPELL.
STIGMA-- IT CAUSES
WOUNDS HE'S INFLICTED
TO WORSEN OVER TIME.
- BUT WHEN DID HE
EVEN HIT YOU?
AHHH!
- ( gasps )
- IT'S MY FAULT.
I'M SORRY.
YOU GOT HIT
TRYING TO PROTECT ME.
- PLEASE DO NOT BLAME YOURSELF.
THIS IS HOW SABRAC OPERATES.
- WHAT?
- IT'S ALL A PART
OF HIS PLAN.
- SHANA AND THE OTHERS.
GOOD.
I CAN STILL SENSE
EVERYONE'S PRESENCE.
THEY SEEM WEAK THOUGH.
PROBABLY FROM THAT BLAST.
- ( grunting )
WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED?
MARGERY.
- Marcosias: I WAS WONDERIN'
WHEN YOU'D WAKE UP, KID.
- MARCOSIAS.
- YOU'VE BEEN OUT COLD
FOR A WHILE.
THE BASTARD WHO ATTACKED US
SURE GOT US GOOD.
LOOKS LIKE MARGERY HERE
IS DOWN FOR THE COUNT.
- I GOTTA WAKE HER.
- AW, COME ON, JUST SLAP HER!
- NO, I CAN'T DO THAT.
I MEAN--
SHE'S WAKING UP.
- RISE AND SHINE,
SLEEPING BEAUTY.
HOW'RE YOU FEELING,
MY DEAR MARGERY DAW?
- NOT TOO GREAT.
THAT ROSE-MADDER COLORED FLAME.
COULD IT BE?
- YEP-- SABRAC,
THE DESTRUCTIVE BLADE.
TURNS OUT
HE WAS USING THE JAEGER
AND THE WANDERER TO LURE US
INTO HIS TRAP.
- IT LOOKS LIKE SAKAI'S SAFE.
BUT HOW'RE SHANA
AND WILHELMINA?
- I'M NOT SURE.
BUT I CAN STILL SENSE
THEIR PRESENCE. ( grunts )
- MARGERY!
- YOU'RE NOT LOOKIN' SO GOOD.
- IT'S SABRAC'S
DAMN UNRESTRICTED SPELL, STIGMA.
CAN'T GET WORSE THAN THIS.
- SAKAI.
- THIS IS NO PLACE
FOR AN ORDINARY HUMAN.
THIS TREASURE TOOL
ALLOWS YOU TO SUMMON ME.
- WHAT HAPPENED?!
SHANA?
- ALL THIS TIME
AND I'M STILL UNABLE
TO SENSE SABRAC'S PRESENCE.
- I COULDN'T EITHER.
SO WHY IS THAT?
- HE IS ONE OF THE FEW LORDS
WHO IS ABLE TO MASK IT.
THAT POWER ALLOWS HIM
TO ASSASSINATE HIS TARGETS
WITHOUT THEM EVER KNOWING
WHAT HIT THEM.
BACK THEN...
WHEN I WAS TRAVELING
WITH PHELES AND JOHAN...
I TRIED TO BE WARY
OF OUR SURROUNDINGS.
BUT I WAS NEVER ABLE
TO PREDICT SABRAC'S ATTACKS.
FINALLY,
AFTER YEARS OF PURSUING THEM...
HE INDEED AMBUSHED
THE ENGAGED LINK
WHILE I WAS AWAY
AND THEY BARELY ESCAPED
WITH THEIR LIVES.
HE DAZES HIS TARGETS
WITH A SURPRISE ATTACK,
THEN KILLS THEM
BEFORE THEY CAN FIGHT BACK.
THAT IS SABRAC'S...
- Tiamat: MODUS OPERANDI.
- IT'S QUITE SMART, REALLY.
INDEED IT'S IMPOSSIBLE
TO PREPARE FOR HIS ATTACKS,
WHICH LEAVES HIS TARGETS
AT AN EXTREME DISADVANTAGE.
IF THEY DON'T FALL
TO HIS SWORDS,
THEY'LL FALL
TO HIS UNRESTRICTED SPELL,
STIGMA.
IT'S HARD TO FIGHT
WHILE YOUR WOUNDS ARE WORSENING.
I WOULD KNOW AS I HAVE FOUGHT
THE DESTRUCTIVE BLADE
MANY TIMES BEFORE.
- THEN HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO DEFEAT THIS GUY?
OH!
THIS WEIRD FEELING--
IT'S COMING
FROM DOWN THERE.
- WHERE'S SAKAI?
- Alastor:
THERE'S NO NEED TO WORRY.
AS LONG AS HIS SEAL IS UP,
HE IS FINE.
- THAT'S GOOD.
BUT I WISH I COULD SEE HIM
FACE TO FACE.
I FEEL BAD
ABOUT WHAT I SAID TO HIM.
- PLEASE DON'T BE UPSET.
YOU HAD EVERY RIGHT
TO BE MAD AT YUJI.
YOU DID.
- YOU THINK SO?
- BUT NONE OF THAT
MATTERS ANYMORE.
'CAUSE HE'S FINALLY
BACK TO NORMAL.
- ARE YOU SURE?
- MM-HMM.
I JUST HOPE
HE'S SAFE OUT THERE.
I'M SURE WILHELMINA'S
LOOKING OUT FOR HIM.
- ( grunts )
- SHANA, ARE YOU OKAY?
- Yuji: HE NOT ONLY ATTACKS
WITH THAT WAVE OF FLAME,
HE'S GOT SWORDS
HIDING IN THERE?
SO HE'S MEGA-POWERFUL,
HE'S GOT THAT STIGMA SPELL,
AND WE'VE GOT
TO DODGE HIS BLADE ATTACKS?
THIS DOES NOT
SOUND TOO ENCOURAGING.
- THERE IS ONE THING
IN OUR FAVOR--
HIS ATTACKS MAY BE POWERFUL,
BUT THEY LACK VERSATILITY.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
- HIS LARGE-SCALE
SURPRISE ATTACKS,
LIKE THE EXPLOSION
HE CAUSED BEFORE HE APPEARED,
ARE LIMITED TO A SINGLE USE.
- THEN THAT MEANS
EVEN IF HE WANTED TO,
HE COULDN'T USE THAT ATTACK
ON US AGAIN?
- ALTHOUGH SABRAC
HAS THE ABILITY
TO EXPAND HIS POWER
TO COVER A LARGE AREA,
HE IS SO FOCUSED ON DEFEATING
THE OPPONENT IN FRONT OF HIM,
I GUARANTEE
HE WILL NOT EVEN THINK
TO ATTEMPT
ANOTHER LARGE-SCALE ATTACK.
- OKAY, YOU'RE SAYING AS LONG
AS WE KEEP HIM ON OUR TAIL,
SHANA AND MARGERY
WILL BE SAFE.
- THAT IS INDEED
WHAT I'M SAYING.
- Tiamat: WE RISK OUR LIVES.
- AT SOME POINT,
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
DO MORE
THAN DODGE HIS STRIKES.
IF ONLY WE COULD GET IN TOUCH
WITH THE OTHERS SOMEHOW.
BUT I LOST THE BOOKMARK
MARGERY GAVE ME
IN THE EXPLOSION.
- NOW THAT YOU MENTION IT,
MINE IS GONE TOO.
I BET HE DID IT ON PURPOSE.
WILHELMINA!
AHH!
- Tiamat: APPROACH FROM ABOVE.
- COULD THAT EARLIER ATTACK
HAVE BEEN A FEINT?
- YOU GOT HIM!
- I KNEW THAT ALLOWING YOU
TO LIVE
WOULD ONE DAY
COME BACK TO HAUNT ME.
THOUGH YOU MAY PESTER ME,
YOU WILL NOT PREVENT ME
FROM COMPLETING THIS MISSION.
I AM AN ASSASSIN.
THERE IS NO STOPPING ME.
ONCE I HAVE FULFILLED MY DUTIES,
I WILL GLADLY DISPOSE
OF ALL OTHER NUISANCES.
- Wilhelmina: SHOULD'VE KNOWN
THAT WOULDN'T WORK.
SABRAC'S DEFENSE
IS IMPECCABLE.
INDEED ANOTHER REASON HE IS
SUCH A FORMIDABLE OPPONENT.
- THAT'S CRAZY.
THIS GUY'S A MONSTER.
I COULD HELP HER.
- DON'T DO ANYTHING STUPID.
- BUT I--
- IF YOU TRULY
WANT TO BE OF ASSISTANCE,
I HAVE AN IMPORTANT TASK.
- I DON'T GET IT.
DON'T YOU HAVE
SOME KIND OF UNRESTRICTED SPELL
THAT CAN HEAL YOUR WOUNDS?
- I DO,
BUT THIS WOUND ISN'T ORDINARY.
- Marcosias:
SHE ALREADY CAST
SOME COUNTER SPELLS,
BUT THEY DON'T SEEM
TO HAVE ANY EFFECT.
- KEISAKU, LET ME
TAKE THIS OPPORTUNITY
TO DRIVE HOME A POINT
I MADE EARLIER.
YOU WANNA HELP ME,
NO MATTER WHAT THE RISKS MAY BE.
YOU SAY
YOU WANT TO WORK FOR OUTLAW.
- UH, YEAH.
- WOULD YOU STILL WANT TO
IF I WERE TO DIE?
- LURING ME
INTO A NARROW ALLEYWAY
WILL DO NOTHING
TO LESSEN THE POWER
OF MY ATTACKS.
PERHAPS THIS IS WHERE
THE SPECIALIST OF EVERYTHING
FANCIES
TAKING HER LAST BREATH.
AH, WELL,
I SUPPOSE THERE'S NO HARM
IN HUMORING HER.
DAMN.
I FELL FOR IT.
- AHHH!
- HOW IS IT
HE'S COMPLETELY UNSCATHED
AFTER THAT ATTACK?
IT SEEMS IMPOSSIBLE.
- Tiamat: INCONCEIVABLE.
- PROBABILITY OF ILLUSION?
- NIL.
- IN ALL HONESTY,
I'M SURPRISED THIS ENCOUNTER
HAS LASTED SO LONG, SPECIALIST.
I LIED BEFORE.
YOUR LEVEL OF SKILL
HAS IMPROVED SINCE LAST WE MET,
THOUGH SEEMINGLY NOT ENOUGH
FOR YOU TO ACTUALLY DEFEAT ME.
- LET ME GUESS, SABRAC--
YOU USED THE JAEGER
AND WANDERER AS BAIT,
HOPING TO LURE
OUT THE FLAME HAZE.
- CORRECT.
I ASKED THE TRI-CLOPS WOMAN,
BEL-PEOL, TO SEND THEM
BEFORE MY ARRIVAL.
IT GAVE ME AN OPPORTUNITY
TO SEE WHO I WAS UP AGAINST.
THEY WERE MERELY A MEANS
TO AN END.
THERE WAS PART OF ME
THAT NAIVELY HOPED
THEY MIGHT FINISH THE JOB.
BUT THEIR INCOMPETENCE PROVED
TO BE THEIR ULTIMATE UNDOING.
- SO IT WAS BAL MASQUE
WHO HIRED HIM.
THEN HE'S AFTER--
- Tiamat: THE MIDNIGHT
LOST CHILD.
- ( grunts )
- YOU'VE BECOME
A COMMENDABLE OPPONENT.
THIS JOB WOULD HAVE BEEN
SO MUCH EASIER
IF ONLY I HAD KILLED YOU
YEARS AGO WHEN I HAD THE CHANCE.
MY OWN IMPATIENCE IS TO BLAME.
I SHOULD HAVE DEFEATED YOU
ONE BY ONE
INSTEAD OF TRYING
TO TAKE YOU ALL AT ONCE.
NOW THAT THE BOY HAS FALLEN
INTO MY HANDS,
I'M AT A LOSS
ABOUT WHAT TO DO WITH HIM
WHILE IN THE MIDST OF BATTLE.
YOUR QUESTION WAS AN ATTEMPT
TO DIVERT MY ATTENTION
AWAY FROM HIM.
WHERE IS HE?
- I'VE GOT TO THINK.
THERE HAS TO BE SOME WAY
WE CAN DEFEAT SABRAC.
- HIS ATTACKS
LACK VERSATILITY.
HIS LARGE-SCALE SURPRISE ATTACKS
ARE LIMITED TO A SINGLE USE.
HE IS SO FOCUSED
ON DEFEATING THE OPPONENT
IN FRONT OF HIM.
SABRAC'S DEFENSE
IS IMPECCABLE.
- ( grunts )
THAT'S IT.
- YOU ARE WEAKENED,
APPROACHING YOUR INEVITABLE END.
SPECIALIST OF EVERYTHING,
ALLOW ME TO PUT YOU
OUT OF YOUR MISERY.
- I DO NOT KNOW
HOW MUCH MORE I CAN TAKE.
- Tiamat: DO NOT LOSE HOPE.
- ( theme music playing )
- Yuji: WILHELMINA STRUGGLES
AGAINST A SEEMINGLY
INVINCIBLE VILLAIN.
SHANA AND I
ARE REUNITED
AND WE COME UP WITH A STRATEGY
TO DEFEAT SABRAC.
NEXT TIME
ON "SHAKUGAN NO SHANA SECOND,"
"COMBINED STRENGTH".