- Alastor:
HECATE AMBUSHED YUJI
AND STOLE THE MIDNIGHT
LOST CHILD FROM HIM.
SUDDENLY, MISAKI CITY'S
CLOCK TOWER BEGAN TO TRANSFORM.
IT WAS BAL MASQUE'S
SECRET WEAPON,
THE TAIMEI SHIHEN,
BEGINNING TO TAKE SHAPE.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Bel-Peol: EVERYTHING
IS GOING AS PLANNED.
LET US HOPE
OUR GOOD LUCK CONTINUES.
- AT LAST
WE WILL ACHIEVE VICTORY.
- YES, WE WILL.
THEN BOTH THE CRIMSON
AND HUMAN WORLDS
WILL BE UNDER OUR COMMAND.
- ( heartbeat )
- Alastor: SEEKING RESEARCHER,
YOU CANNOT
ALLOW THIS CREATURE
TO PERMANENTLY RESIDE
IN THE HUMAN WORLD.
HAVE YOU COMPLETELY
LOST YOUR MIND?
- I WOULDN'T EXPECT YOU
TO UNDERSTAND, FLAME OF HEAVEN.
CRITICIZE ME ALL YOU WANT.
IT'LL ONLY MAKE ME STRONGER.
IT'S MY DUTY
TO PUSH THE ENVELOPE.
IT'S PIONEERS LIKE ME
WHO ADVANCE SCIENCE!
- YOU TELL HIM, PROFESSOR!
- YEE-HEE!  ONCE YOU
SEE THE STATUE OF PRIDE
IN ITS AWAKENED STATE,
ANY DOUBTS YOU HAVE
ABOUT MY SCIENTIFIC CREDIBILITY
WILL BE SQUELCHED.
MY BRILLIANCE
WILL BE RECOGNIZED.
- Tiamat: WE MUST STOP HIM.
- EASIER SAID THAN DONE.
- WE HAVE TO FIND
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD
AND GET IT BACK TO YUJI.
- AHA HA HA!
- ( steam whistle blowing )
- AHHHH!
( grunts )
- YOU MIGHT AS WELL GIVE UP.
- Margery: JEEZ.
WHAT WAS I THINKING
BLOWING ALL MY POWER LIKE THAT?
THERE'S A BATTLE
UNFOLDING RIGHT IN FRONT OF ME
AND I CAN'T DO ANYTHING
BUT WATCH IT HAPPEN.
( coughing )
- Marcosias: SHUT YOUR TRAP,
WOULD YOU?  DAMN IT.
THIS'LL TAKE A WHILE
TO HEAL YOU.
- YUJI.
- SAKAI.
- Alastor: I DON'T THINK
THERE IS ANY REASON TO WORRY.
EVEN THOUGH IT WILL NO LONGER
RENEW ITSELF,
HE CARRIES ENOUGH POWER
OF EXISTENCE WITHIN HIM
THAT IT IS UNLIKELY
HE WILL RUN OUT.
- Shana: BUT WHAT IF
WE DON'T FIND HIM IN TIME?
- Tiamat: HE'LL DISAPPEAR.
- WHAT IF SHANA
AND THE OTHERS
AREN'T ABLE TO GET TO HIM
IN TIME?
I HAVE THE POWER TO SAVE HIM,
BUT TO USE IT,
I HAVE TO SACRIFICE MYSELF.
- NOT QUITE.
SO THAT I CAN FIGHT
ALONGSIDE HIM.
- SAKAI'S LIFE
IS IN MY HANDS.
- ( grunts )
- HMMM!
- TRAPPED.
HE'S NOT ATTACKING?
THEY WON'T ATTACK US
BECAUSE THEY'RE AFRAID
OF DAMAGING THE CLOCK TOWER.
- HMM.
- Yuji: WILHELMINA.
THAT MEANS SHANA'S HERE,
BUT I'M NOT SENSING
HER PRESENCE.
FOR SOME REASON,
ALL I SENSE IS THE SILVER.
DAMN IT.
I HAVE TO KEEP MOVING.
I HAVE TO FIND
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
- ( scanning )
- Dominos:
INTRUDER!  INTRUDER!
- I THOUGHT THIS WAS GOING
TO BE A PIECE OF CAKE.
I DIDN'T REALIZE
HOW HARD IT IS
TO PROTECT SOMETHING
SO MASSIVE.
- I FIND IT IRONIC INDEED
THAT THE ENEMY'S WEAPON
IS WHAT'S KEEPING US SAFE.
- Alastor:
WE MUST NOT WASTE ANY MORE TIME
FIGHTING THOSE TWO.
WE HAVE TO REMOVE
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD
FROM THE BEAST.
THAT IS THE ONLY WAY
WE CAN PREVENT ITS AWAKENING.
- Tiamat: AND SAVE THE MYSTES.
- I'LL FLY INSIDE
WHEN I SEE AN OPPORTUNITY.
I KNOW HE'S IN THERE.
- Dominos:
SEIZE HIM!  SEIZE HIM!
- IF USING THIS
MEANS SAKAI WILL BE SAVED,
THEN I--
( gasps )
- ( traffic sounds,
people chattering )
- Shana: I'LL BRING HIM
BACK WITH ME
AND WE'LL SETTLE OUR RIVALRY.
- I HAD FORGOTTEN
WHAT SHANA TOLD ME.
SHE PROMISED
THAT SHE'D BRING HIM BACK.
WHAT'S WITH ME?
I WAS ABOUT TO GIVE MY LIFE
INSTEAD OF TRUSTING HER.
- Shana:
SO I CAN FIGHT ALONGSIDE HIM.
HE'S IN THERE
AND HE'S FIGHTING FOR HIS LIFE.
- Kazumi:
I HAVE FAITH IN HER.
THEY WILL MAKE IT
OUT OF THERE ALIVE.
AND WHEN THEY DO,
I'LL BE THERE
TO WELCOME THEM BACK.
- Dominos: SEIZE HIM!
SEIZE HIM!
SEIZE HIM!  SEIZE HIM!
MUST DETAIN!  MUST DETAIN!
MUST DETAIN!
- AH!
I'VE GOTTA BE MORE CAREFUL.
IF I DON'T CONSERVE MY POWER,
I'LL DISAPPEAR.
IT'S WEIRD.
ALL I'M WORRIED ABOUT RIGHT NOW
IS PROTECTING THEM--
MY DAD,
MY MOM,
MY FUTURE SIBLING...
MISAKI CITY
AND ITS CITIZENS,
YOSHIDA, WHO'S OPENED HER HEART
TO A MYSTES--
I WANT TO PROTECT ALL OF THEM,
- ESPECIALLY...
- AHA HA HA HA!
( laughing maniacally )
- SHANA!
( grunting )
I WILL PROTECT YOU!
- AHHHH!
- WHY HIM?!
WHY TARGET YUJI?!
- BECAUSE WE NEEDED
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
NOW THAT WE HAVE IT,
WE HAVE NO USE FOR HIM.
SOON HE'LL DISAPPEAR
LIKE ANY OTHER TORCH.
- I'LL KILL YOU!
- DO NOT EVEN
THINK ABOUT HARMING HECATE.
- AHH!
HMM!  DON'T WORRY,
I'LL GO AFTER HER.  MOVE!
- INDEED YOU WILL NOT
GET PAST ME.
- Dantalion: JUST FORGET
ABOUT THE GIRL, SYD!
ONE MEASLY LITTLE FLAME HAZE
IS NO MATCH
FOR MY ELITE ARMY OF ROBOTS.
IN FACT,
I BET THEY'RE ZEROING IN
ON HER COORDINATES AS WE SPEAK!
- I AM UNCERTAIN OF THAT,
SIR.
THEY HAVE NOT EVEN
CAPTURED THE MYSTES YET--
- SHUT UP!
ALL I NEED IS FOR YOU
TO BUY US SOME TIME
UNTIL THE STATUE OF PRIDE
HAS BEEN FULLY AWAKENED, OKAY?
OOOH!
SHOULD BE ANY MINUTE NOW!
- SURE, WHATEVER YOU SAY.
- I KNOW HE'S HERE SOMEWHERE.
- YUJI!
- SHANA.
- PLEASE DON'T DISAPPEAR
ON ME.
- I'LL BE OKAY.
- BUT YOU'RE STARTING TO FADE.
- YEAH.
SOMETHING'S DRAINING ME--
MY POWER OF EXISTENCE.
I CAN FEEL IT HAPPENING.
- Alastor:
THE SEEKING RESEARCHER
SAID THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD
IS THE "HEART"
OF HIS CREATION.
IT MUST BE THE STATUE OF PRIDE
WHICH IS FEEDING OFF
OF YOUR POWER OF EXISTENCE.
- ( heartbeat )
- Yuji: THE STATUE OF PRIDE?
- Alastor: BAL MASQUE
PLANS TO USE THE POWER
BEL-PEOL TRAPPED
BENEATH THE CITY
TO BREATHE LIFE
INTO THIS MANGLED IRON.
IT WILL BE THE FIRST DENIZEN
TO BE BORN
INTO THE HUMAN WORLD.
- Yuji: WHY WOULD THEY
DO SUCH A THING?
- Shana: I DON'T KNOW.
THE ONLY THING I DO KNOW
IS WE'RE DOOMED
IF WE DON'T STOP IT.
WHAT IF WE REMOVED
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD?
DO YOU THINK
THAT WOULD DO IT?
- WELL, THERE'S ONLY ONE WAY
TO FIND OUT.
- YOU KNOW WHERE IT IS?
- IT'S ABOVE US.
- YUJI.
- I'LL BE FINE.
COME ON.
- YOU SHOULDN'T FIGHT.
- BUT THERE ARE PEOPLE
I'VE SWORN TO PROTECT,
LIKE YOU.
THAT IS, IF YOU'LL LET ME.
- OF COURSE.
TOGETHER.  COME ON.
- ARISE, DENIZEN.
- IT'S MOVING.
- ( all reacting )
- I WOKE UP
IN THE NICK OF TIME, HUH?
- Marcosias:
IF YOU DON'T RELAX,
I'M NEVER GOING
TO GET YOU HEALED.
- WELL, I CAN'T
JUST LAY HERE AND DO NOTHING.
- Marcosias: GIVE ME A BREAK.
WHY ARE YOU
ALWAYS SO HARDHEADED?
- THIS SEAL
HAS STOPPED OUR NEWBORN DENIZEN
IN ITS TRACKS!
IT'S TIME TO PULL OUT
THE BIG GUNS.
DOMINO, I'M GOING TO ACTIVATE
THE EMERGENCY FUNCTION
I DESIGNED SPECIFICALLY
FOR CASES LIKE THIS.
- BUT, SIR,
WE HAVE NOT TESTED IT!
FOR ALL WE KNOW, IT COULD CAUSE
A MASSIVE EXPLOSION,
CASTING US OUTSIDE
THE OPERATIONAL AREA.
- NO PROBLEM-O!
I CAN'T THINK OF A BETTER TIME
TO TEST THE EMERGENCY FUNCTION
THAN WHEN WE TRULY NEED IT!
- IT HAS WINGS.
THEY'RE NOT GOING TO TRY
TO FLY IT OUTSIDE OF THE SEAL?
- Tiamat: IT'S UNSTOPPABLE.
- AHHH!
- THEY MUST BE STOPPED
AT ANY COST.
- Alastor: YOU HAVE TO HURRY!
THE DENIZEN HAS BEEN AWAKENED.
- ALMOST THERE.
- ( gasps )
- ( growls )
- ( Yuji shouts )
- IT'S HIM-- THE SILVER!
YUJI, WHERE IS
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD?
- HE'S GOT IT.
IT'S INSIDE OF HIM.
- ( shouting )
DAMN IT.
COVER ME!  I'M GOING IN.
- IF I HADN'T STEPPED IN,
YOU'D BE TOAST RIGHT NOW!
- I KNEW YOU WOULD.
- OH, YEAH?
- DISPOSE OF THEM.
- ( gasps )
- MARGERY, IT'S YOU.
- Marcosias: YOU'RE LUCKY
WE FOUND YOU IN TIME.
- I'VE GONE SOFT.
INSTEAD OF GETTING MY REVENGE
ON THE SILVER,
I'M OUT SAVING HUMANS.
- SHANA!
- I'VE GOT THIS.
- MY POWER'S
STILL BEING DRAINED.
AS IF IT'S BEING USED
FOR SOMETHING.
- Alastor: IT MUST BE
THE STATUE OF PRIDE
WHICH IS FEEDING OFF
OF YOUR POWER OF EXISTENCE.
- THAT'S IT-- THE HEART!
- I COMMEND YOU
FOR YOUR EFFORTS.
HOWEVER, NOW THAT IT'S AWAKENED,
YOU HAVE NOWHERE TO HIDE.
- I DON'T KNOW HOW
LONG I CAN CONTAIN MYSELF
WITH ALL OF THIS EXCITEMENT!
YOU'RE NOW FREE
TO SPREAD YOUR WINGS
AND MAKE THIS WORLD YOUR OWN.
- SMASH THE MACHINE!
IT'S WHAT'S PULLING POWER
FROM THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD
TO SUPPORT THE DENIZEN!
I'M RUNNING OUT OF TIME.
- AHHH!
- OH, NO.
GIVE ME BACK
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD!
AH!
- YUJI.
DID YOU GET IT BACK?
- MM-HMM.
Alastor: GOOD, NOW GET OUT.
- Fecor: HOW COULD THIS HAPPEN?
WE WERE SO CLOSE.
- I SUPPOSE
THAT SOME THINGS IN THIS WORLD
ARE NOT MEANT TO BE.
- WHAT HAPPENED, HECATE?
- I WISH I COULD TELL YOU.
- Sydonay: NO!
WHY IS THE STATUE OF PRIDE'S
SYSTEM MALFUNCTIONING
AT A TIME LIKE THIS?
IT MUST BE
SOME KIND OF PROGRAMMING ERROR.
DOMINO, PREPARE
TO INITIATE REMOTE CONTROL
OF THE DENIZEN IMMEDIATELY!
- CONNECTION LOST, SIR!
AH!  THE MYSTES
MUST HAVE TAKEN BACK
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
- WHAT?
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?!
WITHOUT ITS HEART,
THE STATUE CANNOT FUNCTION.
IT HAS BEGUN
A SYSTEM-WIDE SHUT DOWN.
- WE SHOULD BE ON OUR WAY,
PROFESSOR.
- I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE!
I WON'T ALLOW THOSE FOOLS
TO DISRUPT YET ANOTHER OF MY--
- Domino: EJECT.
- AHHH!
- Shana: WE DID IT.
WE PROTECTED THE CITY.
- YEAH.
YOSHIDA.
- YOU'RE ALIVE!
- YEAH, I'M FINE.
- TOLD YOU SO.
- WELCOME BACK.
- ( theme music playing )
- Yuji: ON THAT NIGHT,
WHEN WE SAVED THE CITY,
MY WORLD COMPLETELY CHANGED.
I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE
WHAT THE FUTURE HOLDS.