- Alastor:
THE DESTRUCTIVE BLADE, SABRAC,
MADE AN EXPLOSIVE APPEARANCE.
HIS SURPRISE ATTACK
LEFT BOTH SHANA AND MARGERY
INCAPACITATED.
HOWEVER, WILHELMINA
REMAINED STANDING
AND BRAVELY FOUGHT
AGAINST HER ARCH-NEMESIS
WHILE YUJI
RAN IN SEARCH OF SHANA.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( panting )
- YOU ARE WEAKENED,
APPROACHING
YOUR INEVITABLE END.
SPECIALIST OF EVERYTHING,
ALLOW ME
TO PUT YOU OUT OF YOUR MISERY.
- I DO NOT KNOW HOW MUCH MORE
I CAN TAKE.
- Tiamat: DO NOT LOSE HOPE.
- Alastor:
WHILE I THANK YOU
FOR YOUR HELP,
IT'S FAR TOO PERILOUS
FOR YOU HERE.
I'M AFRAID WE WON'T BE ABLE
TO PROTECT YOU
IF YOU COME UNDER FIRE.
- I'M STAYING.
- YUJI.
- YOU'RE OKAY.
- SHANA.
AND YOSHIDA?
PLEASE LEAVE.
IT'S NOT SAFE.
YOU'RE DRESSING HER WOUNDS?
USE THESE.
THEY'RE SPECIAL BANDAGES.
WILHELMINA SENT THEM.
- ( crashing sounds )
- PLEASE HURRY, KAZUMI.
I HAVE TO GET OUT THERE
AND HELP WILHELMINA.
- NO.  WE NEED
TO GO FIND MARGERY FIRST.
I HAVE AN IDEA HOW.
- IT DOESN'T LOOK AS THOUGH
YOU CAN TAKE MUCH MORE
OF THIS, SPECIALIST.
IT'S A SHAME
YOU WEREN'T THERE
WHEN I HAD
THAT FATEFUL RUN-IN
WITH THE ENGAGED LINK.
IT WOULD'VE BEEN NICE
TO DISPOSE
OF ALL OF YOU PESTS AT ONCE.
DAMN IT.
I THOUGHT STIGMA
WOULD'VE KILLED OFF
THE OTHER FLAME HAZE BY NOW.
BUT THAT CRIMSON FLAME
COULD ONLY BELONG TO...
THE FLAMING-HAIRED
BLAZING-EYED HUNTER.
- SHANA.
THAT'S THE NAME I GO BY!
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
STIGMA MAY NOT HAVE KILLED HER,
BUT IT SHOULD HAVE LEFT HER
COMPLETELY DEBILITATED.
SOMETHING IS AMISS.
- DO YOU TAKE ME FOR A FOOL?
I KNOW TO BE PREPARED
WHEN FACING MY ARCH-NEMESIS.
- Tiamat: OUR SECRET WEAPON.
- Wilhelmina:
A SPELL HAS BEEN CAST
ON THESE BANDAGES
WHICH COUNTERS STIGMA.
IT WAS CONCEPTUALIZED
BY A BRILLIANT MYSTES
WHO YOU RELENTLESSLY TARGETED.
I HAVE SPENT YEARS DEVELOPING
AND TESTING HIS SPELL.
AND FINALLY
I FEEL IT HAS BEEN PERFECTED.
YOU'RE ABOUT TO WITNESS
THE POWER OF THE ETERNAL LOVER,
JOHAN!
- NO!
- AHHH!
- HOW CAN THIS BE?
MY UNRESTRICTED SPELL
WAS NULLIFIED BY A LOWLY MYSTES?
- ARE YOU SURE
YOU CAN KEEP GOING?
- YES INDEED, MILADY.
- Tiamat: WE WILL SOLDIER ON.
- THE BATTLE AGAINST SABRAC
HAS ONLY JUST BEGUN.
- Yuji: Wilhelmina...
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
- Wilhelmina:
I thought I told you
to flee somewhere safe.
- JUST HEAR ME OUT.
MARGERY, SHANA, AND I
HAVE COME UP WITH A PLAN
TO DEFEAT SABRAC,
BUT WE NEED YOUR HELP.
- You have a plan?
- YES.
AND I THINK
IT JUST MIGHT WORK.
I'VE HAD THIS WEIRD FEELING
SINCE I WOKE UP THIS MORNING,
LIKE MY HEART'S TRAPPED
INSIDE AN OMINOUS CLOUD.
WHEN I WAS CONFRONTED
BY ZAROVEE,
I AUTOMATICALLY ASSUMED
I MUST'VE BEEN PICKING UP
ON HIS PRESENCE.
HE WAS SO WEAK
THAT AT FIRST
I DIDN'T EVEN REALIZE
HE WAS A DENIZEN.
THING IS,
THE FEELING DIDN'T GO AWAY
AFTER ZAROVEE AND THE WANDERER
WERE DEFEATED.
- YOU'VE FELT IT
ALL OVER TOWN.
- Marcosias:
AND IT WAS EVEN STRONGER
WHEN YOU WERE UNDERGROUND?
- SABRAC'S BEEN PULLING OFF
THESE HUGE SURPRISE ATTACKS
ON US.
AND NONE OF US
EVER EVEN SEE HIM COMING.
I THINK THAT'S
'CAUSE HE BLANKETS HIS PRESENCE
OVER A LARGE AREA.
BUT SOMEHOW
I CAN STILL PICK UP ON IT.
- WAIT, LET ME
GET THIS STRAIGHT.
ARE YOU SAYING--
- Marcosias:
HE'S SPREAD HIS PRESENCE
THROUGHOUT MISAKI CITY?
- IT MAKES SENSE TO ME.
'CAUSE GET THIS--
THE FEELING THAT STARTED
RIGHT BEFORE HE SHOWED UP
WAS THE SAME ONE I FELT
AT HOME THIS MORNING.
- UNBELIEVABLE.
THEN IF THAT
IS INDEED THE CASE,
THE SABRAC WE'RE FIGHTING
IS NOTHING MORE THAN--
- Tiamat: A FRAGMENT.
- Yuji: Yeah, I think so.
- INTERESTING.
THAT EXPLAINS
WHY NONE OF MY ATTACKS
SEEM TO EVEN FAZE HIM.
HE'S FEEDING OFF
OF AN ENDLESS SUPPLY
OF POWER OF EXISTENCE
HE'S STREWN
THROUGHOUT THE CITY.
- Tiamat: SNEAKY TACTIC.
- YES, BUT WE KNEW HE WOULD BE
A FORMIDABLE OPPONENT.
HOW ARE WE TO DEFEAT HIM?
- I HAVE AN IDEA.
- AHHH!
- YOU MAY
HAVE COUNTERED STIGMA,
BUT I STILL HAVE THE UPPER HAND
IN THIS CONFLICT.
AS A FLAME HAZE,
YOU ARE IMPULSIVE BY NATURE,
PUTTING YOU AT A DISADVANTAGE
IN A WAR OF ATTRITION.
- Both: AHHH!
- I ASSUME
THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES
HAS ALREADY BEGUN
LAYING THE GROUNDWORK
FOR THIS PLAN?
- Yuji: Yes, but we're still
gonna need someone
to distract Sabrac
until she's done.
- ( grunts )
- Please, will you help us?
- I'LL BE ACTING AS YOUR GUIDE,
WILHELMINA.
- Wilhelmina:
Miss Yoshida, is that you?
- I DON'T KNOW THAT I'LL BE
ANY GOOD AT IT,
BUT-- NO, I CAN DO THIS!
- INDEED YOU CAN.
I WILL DO MY BEST
TO KEEP HIM DISTRACTED
UNTIL THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES
IS FINISHED SETTING THE TRAP.
- Tiamat: A CAT AND MOUSE GAME.
- THE GOLD EGG IN THE SEA...
- Marcosias:
...WAS THROWN AWAY THEN!
- KEISAKU, WHERE TO?
- Take a left
at the intersection.
It's near the railroad ramp.
- OKAY.
THE ONE GOOD THING
ABOUT THIS CITY IS
IT'S NEVER BORING.
I CAN UNDERSTAND
WHY THE FLAME OF HEAVEN
WOULD SUSPECT THAT IT'S
A MAELSTROM OF WARFARE.
- Marcosias: FROM NOW ON,
IT'LL BE KNOWN AS SABRAC'S
ETERNAL RESTING PLACE.
THAT BASTARD
WON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT HIT HIM!
( laughs )
- Sato: IN 100 METERS,
YOU'LL SEE A MUSIC STORE.
THAT INTERSECTION
IS THE 13th POINT.
- 'KAY, WILHELMINA,
GO SOUTH TOWARDS THE MAIN ROAD
AND THEN PUSH HIM
TO THE RIGHT.
THAT SHOULD KEEP HIM
FAR ENOUGH AWAY.
- Yuji: YOU NEVER KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE CAPABLE OF
UNTIL YOU TRY.
FOR ALL I KNOW,
I COULD BE TOTALLY WRONG
ABOUT THIS, BUT--
- Margery: WHEN AN ODD FISH
BROUGHT HER...
- --WE CAN'T GIVE UP.
- Marcosias: ...THE EGG
BACK AGAIN!
- THIS MAY BE OUR ONLY HOPE.
WE'RE IN THIS TOGETHER.
AND TOGETHER
WE WILL WIN.
- AHHH!
( shouting )
DAMN YOU.
- THE FIRST RULE OF BATTLE
IS TO NEVER
LET YOUR GUARD DOWN, SABRAC.
- AFTER ALL THE TIMES
WE'VE DANCED THIS DANCE,
YOU SHOULD HAVE LEARNED
IT REQUIRES MORE THAN THAT
TO TAKE ME DOWN.
- SHANA!
- I'M OKAY.
- GOOD.
- I THINK OUR PLAN
MIGHT ACTUALLY WORK.
- YEAH?
- Marcosias:
LET'S GET TO THE POINT.
HOW DO WE
DEFEAT AN ENEMY
WHO'S SPREAD
THROUGHOUT THE CITY?
I KNOW IT'S A LONG SHOT,
BUT WE COULD SET OFF
GIANT EXPLOSIONS ALL OVER TOWN.
THAT WOULD WHITTLE AWAY
AT HIS POWER OF EXISTENCE,
RIGHT?
UNFORTUNATELY,
IT'D ALSO LEVEL THE CITY.
- YEAH, BUT WE CAN ALWAYS
RESTORE THE DAMAGE AFTERWARD.
- NO WAY.
IF WE ALL OF A SUDDEN
TAMPER WITH HIS SUPPLY
OF POWER OF EXISTENCE,
HE'LL START TAKING IT
FROM REGULAR PEOPLE.
I'M DETERMINED
TO PROTECT THIS CITY.
- SAKAI.
- I KNOW
HOW WE CAN DEFEAT SABRAC
WITHOUT CAUSING
ANY MAJOR DAMAGE.
- OH, YEAH?
THEN LET'S HEAR IT, KID.
- WELL,
AS YOU GUYS KNOW,
WILHELMINA'S
BEEN KEEPING SABRAC DISTRACTED.
BUT DON'T YOU THINK IT'S ODD
THAT HE HASN'T EVEN TRIED
TO ATTACK US YET?
A CRIMSON LORD AS POWERFUL
AS HIM
SHOULD BE CAPABLE
OF ATTACKING US
EVEN WHILE HE'S BUSY
FIGHTING SOMEONE ELSE.
WHY HASN'T HE TRIED IT?
WELL, 'CAUSE HE CAN'T.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN BY THAT?
- HIS LARGE-SCALE
SURPRISE ATTACKS,
LIKE THE EXPLOSION
HE CAUSED BEFORE HE APPEARED,
ARE LIMITED TO A SINGLE USE.
HE IS SO FOCUSED
ON DEFEATING THE OPPONENT
IN FRONT OF HIM,
I GUARANTEE
HE WILL NOT EVEN THINK
TO ATTEMPT
ANOTHER LARGE-SCALE ATTACK.
- SABRAC SPREADS HIS POWER
OF EXISTENCE OVER A LARGE AREA
TO MAKE IT APPEAR
AS IF HE HAS MORE OF IT.
BUT HE HAS THE SAME AMOUNT
AS ANY DENIZEN.
- Marcosias:
SO THAT'S HIS SECRET.
WELL, IF THAT'S THE CASE,
THEN ALL WE GOTTA DO
IS WORRY ABOUT THE "BRAIN"
OF THE OPERATION.
- YEAH, 'CAUSE HE'S ALREADY
SPREAD HIMSELF SO THIN,
HE CAN ONLY FOCUS
ON WHAT'S HAPPENING
RIGHT IN FRONT OF HIM.
HE DOESN'T
HAVE ENOUGH POWER LEFT
TO CONSTANTLY SCAN
THE REST OF THE CITY.
- SO HOW DO WE TAKE HIM DOWN?
- WE CUT OFF HIS SUPPLY
OF POWER OF EXISTENCE.
- THAT'S RIGHT.
IT SHOULD WEAKEN HIM
ENOUGH THAT WE CAN STRIKE.
- PERFECT.
I HAVE TO CONSERVE MY POWER
UNTIL IT'S TIME TO STRIKE.
- HOW'RE WE DOING, KEISAKU?
- Sato: We're lookin' good.
All the spells
are perfectly positioned.
- WHERE TO NEXT?
- Keep heading
in that direction.
You should see
a big parking lot.
That's the final point.
- ROGER THAT.
- About that question
you asked me earlier--
I don't wanna think
about what I would do
if you were to die.
TO BE HONEST,
I'M PRETTY TICKED
THAT YOU WOULD EVEN ASK ME
SUCH A STUPID QUESTION.
'CAUSE I'M NOT
GONNA LET YOU DIE!
I'M GIVING IT MY ALL
OVER HERE.
I'M GONNA MAKE SURE
YOU LIVE THROUGH THIS.
Now can we drop it?
- IDIOT.
- OH!
MARGERY IS ON HER WAY
TOWARDS THE FINAL POINT
RIGHT NOW.
WE'VE ALMOST GOT HIM,
WILHELMINA.
JUST A LITTLE LONGER.
- AHHH!
WAIT.
WHERE DID THE FLAMING-HAIRED
BLAZING-EYED HUNTER RUN OFF TO?
WHY IS SHE NO LONGER ATTACKING?
OH, DEAR.
SURELY YOU FLAME HAZE
ARE NOT SO FOOLISH
AS TO THINK
YOU CAN SET A TRAP FOR ME.
- I'VE NEVER WANTED TO SEE
THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES
SO BADLY IN MY LIFE.
- Tiamat: YOU MUST BE PATIENT.
- HERE HE COMES.
- WE ARE READY.
- I HAVE YOU NOW!
- THE TRAP IS SET.
LET'S GET THIS BASTARD!
- Marcosias:
THIS IS GONNA BE A BLAST!
( laughs )
- WHAT THE--
- Margery:
JACK'S MOTHER CAME IN--
- Marcosias:
--AND CAUGHT THE GOOSE SOON!
- AND MOUNTING ITS BACK--
- Marcosias:
--FLEW UP TO THE MOON!
- ( singing in Japanese )
- NO!
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE?
- ( Marcosias laughing )
- THE REST IS UP TO YOU,
MILADY.
- RIGHT.
YUJI?
NEVER MIND.
- Alastor:
YOU COULD HAVE TOLD HIM
HOW YOU FEEL.
I WASN'T GOING TO STOP YOU.
NOT ONLY DID HE
DEFEAT THE JAEGER,
HE SABOTAGED THE WANDERER,
AND REVEALED THE SECRET
OF THE DESTRUCTIVE BLADE'S
INVINCIBILITY.
IN FACT, HE EVEN CAME UP
WITH A PLAN TO DEFEAT SABRAC.
YUJI SAKAI--
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD'S
MYSTES.
WHO WOULD HAVE THOUGHT
HE WAS CAPABLE
OF SUCH GREATNESS?
- AHH!
- ( shouting )
- AHHHHH!
- THAT'S THE END OF HIM.
- Marcosias:
AND GOOD RIDDANCE, I SAY.
- A SWEET VICTORY INDEED.
- Tiamat: NEMESIS DEFEATED.
- IT LOOKS LIKE
THEY GOT HIM.
- THANK GOODNESS.
- Chigusa: I'M SORRY
I HAD YOU ALL WORRIED.
- WELL, I HAVE TO SAY,
YOU'RE LOOKING MUCH BETTER.
- THANKS.
I FEEL GREAT.
IT'S ALL BECAUSE OF YOU,
SHANA AND YOSHIDA.
AND WILHELMINA'S MEDICINE
HELPED TOO.
PLEASE TELL HER
I SAID THANK YOU AGAIN.
- WHAT ABOUT ME?
- THAT PORRIDGE WAS TERRIBLE.
- ( both giggle )
- I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
- THANKS AGAIN.
YOSHIDA?
I'M WORRIED
THIS'LL MAKE YOU ANGRY AGAIN,
BUT THERE'S SOMETHING
I NEED TO SAY.
REMEMBER WHEN I TOLD YOU
I'D DECIDED
TO LEAVE MISAKI CITY?
I REFUSED TO ACCEPT
THE FOOD YOU'D BROUGHT OVER.
THAT WAS SO RUDE.
I'M SORRY.
I HOPE
YOU CAN ACCEPT MY APOLOGY.
- I'M NOT MAD AT YOU.
FROM THE MOMENT
I HEARD YOU SAY
THAT YOU'RE DETERMINED
TO PROTECT THIS CITY,
I KNEW YOU WERE BACK
TO THE SAKAI I LOVE.
- THANK YOU.
- YUJI.
- SHANA.
- I'LL SEE YA TONIGHT.
WE PICK UP YOUR TRAINING
RIGHT WHERE WE LEFT OFF.
- RIGHT.
HEY, WAIT A SEC.
BEFORE YOU DEFEATED SABRAC,
YOU STARTED TO SAY SOMETHING.
WHAT WAS THAT ABOUT?
- UH, IT WAS NOTHING.
- COME ON.
- I SAID IT WAS NOTHING!
- SHANA.
- SHUT UP, SHUT UP, SHUT UP!
- ( theme music playing )
- Yuji: THEY SAY TIMES CHANGE
AND WE CHANGE WITH THEM.
SHANA AND YOSHIDA
DECIDE TO WRITE LETTERS TO ME
REVEALING
THEIR TRUE FEELINGS.
NEXT TIME
ON "SHAKUGAN NO SHANA SECOND,"
"CHRISTMAS EVE."