Alastor:
YUJI DECIDED IT'S BEST
HE LEAVE MISAKI CITY
WITH SHANA.
HOWEVER, HE WAS SURPRISED
BY THE REACTION
BOTH KAZUMI YOSHIDA
AND SHANA HAD TO THE NEWS.
STUNNED, YUJI WENT FOR A WALK
TO CLEAR HIS THOUGHTS
AND CAME FACE TO FACE
WITH A MYSTERIOUS DENIZEN.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- PLEASED TO MAKE
YOUR ACQUAINTANCE.
MY NAME IS ZAROVEE.
I AM KNOWN
AS THE COLLATION FLUX.
( laughing )
- YOU'RE A... DENIZEN?!
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
MY SENSES ARE SHARPER NOW.
WHY WASN'T I ABLE TO SENSE
THIS GUY'S PRESENCE?
IT MUST BE BECAUSE
HIS EXISTENCE IS PRETTY WEAK.
I DOUBT EVEN SHANA
OR WILHELMINA COULD SENSE HIM.
- NO NEED TO GLARE AT US
LIKE THAT, BOY.
YOU NEEDN'T WORRY.
WE DON'T POSE ANY DANGER.
AT LEAST NOT TO YOU ANYWAY.
- STOP PLAYING GAMES.
JUST WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
- I'M SAYING THAT,
WHILE YOU MAY
NOT BE IN DANGER,
THE REST OF YOUR CITY
IS ANOTHER STORY.
- NO WAY.
- WHAT IS THE POPULATION
OF MISAKI CITY?
ANY IDEA?
- BASTARD!
- ( grunting )
- WHOA.
BE CAREFUL, YOUNG MAN.
I'M WARNING YOU,
IF YOU DARE CAUSE US ANY HARM,
YOU WON'T LIVE LONG ENOUGH
TO REGRET IT.
- LET ME GUESS,
IF I TRY AND ATTACK YOU,
THE GUY YOU'VE GOT
HIDING IN TOWN
WILL START
CONSUMING PEOPLE'S SOULS.
- ( all grunting )
- ( horns honking )
( chuckles )
YES, THAT IS CORRECT.
IF YOU EVEN LAY A FINGER ON US,
I'LL SEND THE SIGNAL
TO OUR PINK FRIEND
TO EAT EVERY SOUL
HE COMES ACROSS.
YOU SEE NOW, BOY?
IF I WERE YOU,
I'D BE ON MY BEST BEHAVIOR.
YOU DON'T WANT
INNOCENT PEOPLE TO DIE.
- HE WAS ABLE TO CONFRONT
ME WITHOUT BEING SPOTTED.
YOU'RE A JAEGER
FROM BAL MASQUE.
- Both: HOW'D YOU KNOW THAT?!
- I KNEW IT.
I'VE READ ABOUT THEM
IN DOCUMENTS FROM OUTLAW.
THEIR WEAK PRESENCE
MAKES THEM PERFECT
FOR COVERT OPERATIONS,
BUT NOT SO MUCH FOR BATTLE.
SO THEY USUALLY GET PARTNERED
WITH WANDERERS,
DENIZENS WHO SPECIALIZE
IN COMBAT MANEUVERS.
THE WANDERER CAN'T BE
TOO FAR AWAY.
WHY CAN'T I SENSE
ITS PRESENCE EITHER?
MUST BE
AN UNRESTRICTED SPELL.
WISH I KNEW
WHAT THEY'RE UP TO.
BETTER PLAY ALONG
TILL I FIGURE IT OUT.
- I SUGGEST YOU DO
EXACTLY AS WE SAY.
YOU OBVIOUSLY KNOW
QUITE A BIT ABOUT US.
I'M SURE YOU KNOW
WHAT WE'RE CAPABLE OF.
NOW, IF YOU WILL,
WE'D LIKE YOU TO WALK WITH US.
JOIN US, MYSTES YUJI SAKAI.
- THIS WEIRD FEELING
I KEEP GETTING.
IS IT 'CAUSE OF HIM?
- HOW'S THE REMEDY?
DOES IT TASTE OKAY?
- CERTAINLY
TASTES LIKE MEDICINE.
WHERE'S WILHELMINA?
- SHE'S MAKING SOUP
TO HELP YOU FEEL BETTER.
IT SHOULD BE GOOD.
- ( water boiling )
- OH, AND KAZUMI
BROUGHT THIS BY FOR YOU.
- GOODNESS.
TELL HER I SAID THANK YOU.
OH, AND THE SAME
GOES FOR YOU, SHANA.
- Kazumi:
WHY ARE YOU APOLOGIZING?
- YOU'RE JUST LYING
TO YOURSELF.
I KNOW THAT DEEP DOWN,
YOU'RE REALLY WORRIED
ABOUT YOUR MOM
AND YOU DON'T WANT
TO LEAVE TOWN.
YOU WON'T FACE THE TRUTH.
FORGET IT.
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE
WITH YOU.
YUJI.
- ( footsteps approaching )
- HEY.
- YOU WANT TO TELL ME
WHERE WE'RE GOING?
- DON'T BOTHER
WITH SUCH QUESTIONS.
JUST CONTINUE TO FOLLOW ME.
- WHAT'LL YOU DO IF I REFUSE?
- YOU KNOW WHAT'LL HAPPEN.
- WHAT DO THEY WANT FROM ME?
NOBODY GETS KIDNAPPED
JUST FOR THE HECK OF IT.
CLEARLY
THEY'RE AFTER SOMETHING.
THEY COULD BE USING ME
AS BAIT TO LURE OUT SHANA
AND THE OTHER FLAME HAZE.
IF SO, I'VE GOT TO WARN THEM.
THE QUESTION IS HOW?
AHHHH!  AHHHHHH!
AHHHHH!  AHHHH!
- WHAT IN THE HELL
DO YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING?
- LET GO!
- STOP SCREAMING.
WHAT HAS GOTTEN INTO YOU?
- THIS IS A TRAP, ISN'T IT?
ARE YOU USING ME AS BAIT
SO YOU CAN CAPTURE THE OTHERS?
- UH, IS THAT A TRICK QUESTION?
- THEY'RE GOING
TO HEAR ME SCREAM.
- TRY THAT AGAIN AND I SWEAR
I WILL START DEVOURING SOULS.
- FINE, I GET IT!
- UGH, THIS KID IS A PAIN.
- WAS THAT SAKAI
WHO JUST WENT CRAZY?
- YEAH, THINK SO.
- I WONDER WHY
HE WAS SCREAMING LIKE THAT.
IT LOOKED LIKE HE WAS
ABOUT TO FIGHT THAT GEEZER.
- I KNOW HE SAW ME.
BUT IF HE NEEDED HELP,
WHY DIDN'T HE
JUST SAY SOMETHING?
WAS IT
'CAUSE OF THAT OLD MAN?
- HEY, WE SHOULD FOLLOW HIM.
SAKAI'S OUR FRIEND.
IF HE'S IN TROUBLE,
THEN WE HAVE TO GO HELP HIM.
- HE WAS TRYING TO KEEP HIM
FROM NOTICING US.
WHY WOULD HE DO THAT?
HE MUST BE DANGEROUS.
DON'T TELL ME--
THAT OLD MAN'S A DENIZEN?
- Ogata: HEY, SNAP OUT OF IT,
WOULD YA?
WE'D BETTER GET GOING
OR ELSE WE'RE GOING TO
LOSE TRACK OF SAKAI.
COME ON.
WHAT?
IS SOMETHING WRONG?
- I'M SORRY.  WE CAN'T.
- ARE YOU FEELING ALL RIGHT?
YOU'RE LOOKING KIND OF PALE.
SAKAI WAS WITH SOME GUY.
DO YOU THINK HE'S IN DANGER?
'CAUSE IF SO, THEN WE SHOULD--
- THERE'S MORE TO IT
THAN THAT, OGATA.
THERE'S NO MISTAKING IT.
THAT DENIZEN
IS HOLDING SAKAI HOSTAGE.
HE STARTED SCREAMING
'CAUSE HE SAW US
DOWN THE STREET.
HE WANTS ME TO WARN THEM.
- THIS IS A TRAP, ISN'T IT?!
ARE YOU USING ME AS BAIT
SO YOU CAN CAPTURE THE OTHERS?
- BUT TO DO THAT,
I'D HAVE TO FACE MARGERY.
THERE WAS A TIME
WHEN I WOULD'VE FOLLOWED HER
ANYWHERE,
BUT NOW?
WHAT IF IT HAPPENED AGAIN,
ONLY THIS TIME NOTHING
COULD BE RESTORED?
FORGET IT.
I'M NOT GETTING INVOLVED.
I DON'T EVER WANT
TO SEE HER AGAIN.
- WHAT'S WRONG?
- FOLLOW ME, OKAY?
- WILL YOU AT LEAST TELL ME
WHERE WE'RE GOING?
- HOW COULD I BE
SUCH AN IDIOT?
IF MY FRIEND'S IN DANGER--
I'VE GOT TO DO
WHAT I CAN TO HELP HIM.
STAY HERE.
I'VE GOTTA TALK TO THEM
REAL QUICK.
TRY NOT TO LISTEN, OKAY?
- UH, SURE.
- ( ringing )
- Sato: Who's there?
Tanaka!
- There's something
I need to tell Margery about.
Can I come in?
Please,
it's real important.
I THOUGHT YOU SHOULD KNOW
WHAT WAS HAPPENING.
- Marcosias: MMM. SOUNDS LIKE
A JAEGER FROM BAL MASQUE,
IF YOU ASK ME.
- I'LL ALERT THE OTHERS
RIGHT AWAY.
THANK YOU FOR COMING TO ME
WITH THIS.
KEISAKU AND EITA,
I NEED YOU BOTH
AT THE CRYSTAL ALTAR.
- WAIT, UH...
I'M SORRY.
I CAN'T HELP YOU.
YOU CAN CALL ME EVERY NAME
IN THE BOOK IF YOU WANT,
BUT I'VE GOT TO STAND UP
FOR MYSELF AND QUIT
BEING A COWARD.
I CARE ABOUT HER
AND I JUST CAN'T TAKE THE RISK.
- TAKE HER HAND
AND RUN FAR AWAY.
- CHIGUSA'S FINALLY
GETTING SOME SLEEP.
- THAT IS GOOD TO HEAR.
IT SEEMS THE REMEDY
IS INDEED WORKING.
- Tiamat: QUITE A CURE-ALL.
- HOW'S THE SOUP COMING ALONG?
- YOU CANNOT RUSH A RECIPE
FULL OF HEALING INGREDIENTS.
SNAPPING TURTLE, PIT VIPER,
GARLIC, AND WHAT WAS THE OTHER?
- Tiamat: KOREAN GINSENG.
- INDEED.
THAT'S WHAT I FORGOT.
- Alastor: SOUNDS DISGUSTING.
- WHY DON'T WE JUST RUSH IN
AND SAVE SAKAI
BEFORE THE ENEMY MAKES A MOVE?
I DON'T GET WHY WE'RE JUST
STANDING HERE WATCHING.
- DON'T WORRY,
I KNOW WHAT I'M DOING.
I'M NOT JUST STANDING HERE.
I'M ALLOWING THE ENEMY
TO SENSE THE PRESENCE
OF A FLAME HAZE.
- Marcosias ( laughing ):
LETTING 'EM SMELL THE BOOZE
ON YA, MORE LIKE-- OW!
- SORRY ABOUT THE LONG WALK,
BUT WE'VE ALMOST
REACHED OUR DESTINATION.
- OH, YEAH?
IS THERE A WANDERER
THERE WAITING?
- ( laughs )
SURELY YOU DON'T THINK
I'M STUPID ENOUGH
TO ANSWER A QUESTION LIKE THAT,
NOW DO YOU?
- I CAN TELL
BY THAT COCKY SMIRK
HE'S GOT SOMETHING MAJOR
IN THE WORKS.
I WONDER
WHERE HIS PARTNER'S HIDING.
I DON'T THINK HE'D BE IN HERE.
THESE CEILINGS ARE TOO LOW.
HE WOULDN'T
HAVE ROOM TO FIGHT.
FACING OFF AGAINST FLAME HAZE
IN A PLACE LIKE THIS
WOULD BE SUICIDE.
WE'VE WALKED ALL THIS WAY
AND I STILL CAN'T FIGURE OUT
WHAT HE WANTS.
I'VE GOT TO DO SOMETHING.
THE OTHERS ARE IN DANGER.
- WE HAVE FINALLY
REACHED OUR DESTINATION.
ALL I HAVE TO DO NOW
IS SET THE STAGE FOR BATTLE.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
ARE YOU SAYING YOU'RE GOING
TO CAST THE SEAL,
NOT THE WANDERER?
- YES, DO YOU HAVE A PROBLEM
WITH THAT, BOY?
I CAN ASSURE YOU
THAT WHEN THE FIVE OF US
ARE COMBINED,
WE HAVE MORE THAN ENOUGH POWER
TO COVER A SMALL AREA
SUCH AS THIS PLACE
WITH A SEAL.
- I DON'T GET IT.
THEY'LL NEED A PRETTY LARGE ONE
IF THEY PLAN TO FIGHT US.
AND NO WAY THIS GUY'S
STRONG ENOUGH TO DO THAT.
SO WHAT WOULD BE
THE POINT OF HIM
CASTING SUCH A SMALL SEAL?
WHY DID THE FIFTH GUY STOP?
WAIT A MINUTE--
A SMALL SEAL AREA.
STATIONARY FIFTH GUY.
THE SEAL
WILL ATTRACT FLAME HAZE.
THE WANDERER'S NOT NEARBY
AND ZAROVEE'S ABILITY--
THAT'S IT.
- WHY'D YOU STOP WALKING?
- HIS SMALL SEAL
WILL ACT AS A BEACON
TO LURE THE FLAME HAZE.
AND BECAUSE IT'S ENCLOSED,
THEY WON'T BE ABLE TO SEE
WHAT'S GOING ON IN HERE.
ZAROVEE IS GOING
TO USE THE FIFTH GUY
AS AN ESCAPE ROUTE.
SO THE WANDERER
MUST BE OUTSIDE.
IT'S GOING
TO ATTACK THE FLAME HAZE
ON THEIR WAY HERE!
- Bifrons: LET'S BEGIN.
WHAT'S TAKING YOU SO LONG,
ZAROVEE?
YOU SHOULD'VE SENT ME
THE SIGNAL BY NOW.
I'M STILL WAITING
TO SEE YOUR SEAL.
- YOU CAN'T STOP NOW, BOY,
NOT WHEN WE'VE COME THIS FAR.
I WARNED YOU
ABOUT WHAT WOULD HAPPEN
IF YOU CHOSE
NOT TO OBEY MY ORDERS.
- I WILL PROTECT IT.
I SWEAR.
I WILL PROTECT THIS CITY!
- DON'T HURT ME!
- ( grunts )
- AHHH!
- SHANA AND YOSHIDA
WERE RIGHT.
- WHY ARE YOU APOLOGIZING?
- FORGET IT.
I'M NOT
GOING ANYWHERE WITH YOU.
- ( bone cracking )
- I WAS LYING TO MYSELF.
I DON'T WANT TO LEAVE.
I WAS ONLY TELLING MYSELF
WHAT I WANTED TO HEAR.
- Margery: NOW, YUJI,
ONE THING TO KEEP IN MIND--
YOU WON'T FIND YOUR RESOLVE
IN YOUR HEAD.
YOU HAVE TO FEEL IT
IN YOUR HEART.
- Yuji: TRUTHFULLY,
I HADN'T FORMED ANY RESOLVE.
I HADN'T ACCEPTED MY FATE.
I DON'T BLAME SHANA AND YOSHIDA
FOR GETTING MAD AT ME.
I NEED TO APOLOGIZE TO THEM.
( grunts )
- AHHH!
- JUST AS I SUSPECTED--
THE WANDERER'S
NOWHERE TO BE FOUND.
THE FLAME HAZE ARE IN DANGER.
SHANA!
- YUJI!
ARE YOU OKAY?
- YEAH, I'M FINE.
THERE'S A PROBLEM W--
- GIVE US THE SHORT VERSION.
- UH, SURE.
THERE'S A WANDERER
SOMEWHERE IN CLOSE PROXIMITY
GETTING READY
TO LAUNCH A LONG-RANGE ATTACK.
- WE HAVE TO STOP IT.
- INDEED WE DO, MILADY.
PROMISE ME
YOU'LL KEEP YOUR SEAL UP
NO MATTER WHAT.
- YOU GOT IT. AHH!
- THAT'S IT!
- IT'S ABOUT TO FIRE!
- YOU READY FOR THIS?
- Tiamat:
IT'S TIME TO LAUNCH.
- I'LL HAVE TO STRIKE FROM HERE.
AHHH!
- AHHHH!
- THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE.
- Alastor: YES,
IT WAS SMART OF YOU
TO STRIKE WHEN YOU DID.
THAT WAS GOOD THINKING.
- I'LL ADMIT, HE HAS INDEED
PROVEN HIMSELF WORTHY
OF BECOMING
THE MISTRESS'S PARTNER.
DON'T YOU AGREE?
- Tiamat: BEGRUDGINGLY.
- ( sighs )
I DIDN'T GET ANY TIME
IN THE SPOTLIGHT TONIGHT.
WHAT A SHAME.
- ( Marcosias laughing )
YOU CAN'T ALWAYS
BE THE STAR, MY DEAR.
- I'M JUST GLAD IT'S ALL OVER.
WE CAN BREATHE EASY.
- HMM.
- Yuji: WHAT'S GOING ON?
THE JAEGER AND THE WANDERER
HAVE BEEN KILLED.
SO WHY DO I STILL
HAVE THIS WEIRD FEELING,
LIKE IT'S EMANATING
FROM THE EXPLOSION SITE?
SHANA!
THERE'S SOMETHING
I'VE BEEN MEANING TO TELL YOU.
- ( theme music playing )
- Yuji: A SUDDEN EXPLOSION
CAUSED BY SABRAC,
THE DESTRUCTIVE BLADE,
SEVERELY INJURES
THE FLAME HAZE.
I'M MORTIFIED
AS MISAKI CITY
IS ENGULFED IN FLAMES.
DESPITE HER INJURIES,
WILHELMINA FACES OFF
AGAINST HER ARCH NEMESIS.
NEXT TIME
ON "SHAKUGAN NO SHANA SECOND,"
"THE SCARLET BATTLE
TO THE DEATH".