- Alastor: AFTER LEARNING
HIS MOTHER IS WITH CHILD,
YUJI IS MORE DETERMINED
THAN EVER
TO PROTECT MISAKI CITY
AND ITS CITIZENS.
SHANA AND KAZUMI
DECIDED TO END
THEIR LONGSTANDING
RIVALRY FOR YUJI'S HEART.
AS YUJI MADE HIS WAY
TO MEET THE GIRL HE CHOSE,
HE WAS AMBUSHED
BY THE SUPREME THRONE, HECATE.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( grunts )
SHE TOOK
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
- WE FINALLY GOT OUR HANDS
ON THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD, SIR!
- MMM?
( laughs ) WHY DO YOU
SOUND SO SURPRISED?
IT WAS JUST A MATTER OF TIME,
DOMINO!
- YES, SIR!
- THAT FOOLISH MYSTES
COULD NEVER
THWART OUR PERFECTLY LAID PLANS.
NO!
NOT ONLY WERE WE ABLE
TO ATTACH A TRANSMITTER
TO THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD,
WHICH LED US TO HIM,
BUT WE ALSO FOUND A WAY
TO DISENGAGE THE KEEPER
THAT THE CAPRICE OF BEAUTY
PLACED ON THE TREASURE TOOL!
WE SHALL BE VICTORIOUS!
AS THEY SAY,
"PERFECT PLANNING
PREVENTS
PISS-POOR PERFORMANCE."
AND WE COULDN'T HAVE
PLANNED MORE PERFECTLY.
IT'S ALMOST BEEN TOO EASY!
I'VE BEGUN
TO LONG FOR CONFLICT
SOLELY BECAUSE
IT BREEDS SUSPENSE.
LET US BREATHE LIFE
INTO THIS SLEEPING GIANT
SO THAT I MAY ONCE AGAIN
FEEL THE THRILL
OF ANTICIPATION!
- Hecate: BECOME THE HEART
OF THE BEAST.
- ( heartbeat )
- ( engine whirring )
- AWAKEN.
- AHA HA HA!
- WHAT IS THAT?
- Alastor: UNBELIEVABLE.
- IT'S NOT A SEAL, IS IT?
- Alastor: NO.
BUT IT IS SIMILAR
IN THE SENSE
THAT HUMANS CAN'T SEE IT.
- HEY, MIDGET,
WOULD IT HAVE KILLED YOU
TO CAST A SEAL?
- Marcosias: ( laughs )
THE HUMANS WOULD FREAK
IF THEY SAW THIS!
- MILADY, DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA
WHAT MAY BE CAUSING THIS?
- NO CLUE.
IT WAS LIKE THIS
WHEN I GOT HERE.
BUT ONE THING I DO KNOW--
YUJI IS INSIDE OF IT.
( grunts )
- IT'S A SEAL.
THEN WHAT IS THAT BIG,
BLUE SPHERE THING?
( panting )
( heartbeat )
- Margery: WELL,
BRUTE FORCE ISN'T WORKING.
- Wilhelmina: INDEED.
OUR ATTACKS APPEAR
TO BE DOING LITTLE TO NO DAMAGE.
- Tiamat: IMPENETRABLE.
- WE'RE JUST GOING
TO HAVE TO KEEP TRYING!
- Alastor: ENOUGH.
YOU'RE WASTING YOUR TIME
BLINDLY ATTACKING IT.
THERE HAS TO BE ANOTHER WAY.
- WHOA, MARCO,
DO YOU FEEL THAT?
- Marcosias: YEAH,
LIKE THE GROUND UNDERNEATH US
IS PULSATING.
- COME FORTH.
THE FOUNTAIN SHALL FLOW.
- ARE THOSE BEAMS
OF POWER OF EXISTENCE?
WHY WASN'T I
ABLE TO SENSE ANYTHING?
- I DID.
IT WAS RELEASED
A FEW MOMENTS AGO.
IT SEEMS TO BE COMING
FROM UNDERNEATH THE CITY.
- Alastor: THE ONLY DENIZEN
CAPABLE OF PULLING OFF
A STUNT LIKE THIS
IS THE JUDGE OF PARADOXES,
BEL-PEOL.
- BAL MASQUE.
- OF COURSE.
WHAT ARE THEY UP TO NOW?
- THE FIRST STAGE OF OUR PLAN
IS NOW COMPLETE.
- THAT'S MUSIC TO MY EARS.
THIS IS THE FIRST
OF MANY LOFTY GOALS
THAT BAL MASQUE
WILL BRING TO FRUITION.
- MAY POWER GIVE IT LIFE!
- THE MOMENT OF TRUTH!
IT'S ALIVE-- ALIVE!
- ( rumbling )
- WHAT'S HAPPENING?
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
SOMEBODY MUST BE USING IT.
I CAN FEEL
MY POWER OF EXISTENCE FADING.
WITHOUT THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD,
IT WON'T RENEW ITSELF.
AND AS MY POWER RUNS OUT...
I'LL START TO DISAPPEAR.
- STRANGE PRESENCE.
IT DOESN'T FEEL
LIKE A DENIZEN.
- WELL, WHATEVER IT IS,
I DON'T THINK IT'S FRIENDLY.
- WE WON'T KNOW
WHAT WE'RE DEALING WITH
UNTIL WE GET INSIDE.
I'LL BREAK THROUGH.
I'LL JUST HIT IT
WITH EVERYTHING I'VE GOT!
- Alastor: IT'S USELESS.
- I HAVE TO TRY!
- EVEN IF YOU ARE ABLE
TO BREAK THROUGH,
WHO KNOWS WHAT'S LURKING
ON THE OTHER SIDE?
IF THIS IS A TRAP
SET BY BAL MASQUE,
YOU MUST KNOW THEY'RE GOING
TO BE EXPECTING US.
- Tiamat: ENEMY AMBUSH.
- Marcosias: IF WE CAN'T
BUST OUR WAY IN,
THEN WHAT ARE WE
SUPPOSED TO DO?
- WE'LL HAVE TO FIND
ANOTHER WAY.
- SHANA.
- KAZUMI?
DAMN IT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
- I-- I'M SORRY,
BUT I'VE GOT NEWS ABOUT SAKAI.
SOMEONE STOLE
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN, STOLE IT?
HOW IS THAT EVEN POSSIBLE?
NO.
YUJI'S BEEN KILLED?
- NUH-UH, HE'S STILL ALIVE.
THEY JUST TOOK IT
OUT OF HIM.
- BUT HOW?
THERE'S A KEEPER--
- THE SPELL
THAT CAUSED THE MUTATION
WAS BAL MASQUE'S.
- Marcosias:
THEY MUST'VE USED IT
TO DISENGAGE THE KEEPER.
IT HAPPENED
RIGHT UNDER OUR NOSES.
- KAZUMI, WHERE DID YOU
GET THIS INFORMATION?
- SOMEONE TOLD ME.
- WHO?
- THE ETERNAL LOVER.
- JOHAN?
HE SPOKE TO YOU?
- I HEARD HIS VOICE
THROUGH THIS.
- Wilhelmina:
THE TREASURE TOOL, GIRALDA?
- HE WAS ABLE TO SPEAK TO ME
WHILE THE KEEPER WAS DISENGAGED,
BUT IT WASN'T FOR VERY LONG.
- I AM AFRAID
I'M GOING TO FADE AWAY
BEFORE I CAN SEE PHELES AGAIN.
BUT NOW,
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD--
IT MUST BE RETURNED
TO THE MYSTES.
- JOHAN.
- GUESS WE'RE LUCKY
SHE SHOWED UP.
- BUT HE CAN'T SURVIVE.
HE NEEDS
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
- Alastor: I DON'T THINK
THERE IS ANY REASON TO WORRY.
EVEN THOUGH
IT WILL NO LONGER RENEW ITSELF,
HE CARRIES ENOUGH POWER
OF EXISTENCE WITHIN HIM
THAT IT IS UNLIKELY
HE WILL RUN OUT.
- BUT WHAT IF
WE DON'T FIND HIM IN TIME?
- Tiamat: HE'LL DISAPPEAR.
- ( both gasp )
- Sato: MAN,
THIS LOOKS LIKE BAD NEWS.
- Margery: Keisaku?
- YEAH?
I'M AT THE CRYSTAL ALTAR NOW.
- Good job, kid.
I need you to help me out
with something.
CAN YOU SEE WHAT LOOKS
LIKE A BIG, BLUE SPHERE
INSIDE THE SEAL I PUT UP?
- Yeah.
- WHAT DOES
THE POWER OF EXISTENCE
ON THE OUTSIDE LOOK LIKE?
- WELL, IT KIND OF LOOKS
LIKE A WHIRLPOOL.
- Okay, I want you
to take a closer look
and see if you can find
a hole or opening on it
anywhere.
- YOU GOT IT.
- ( Marcosias laughs )
SOUNDS LIKE
HE'S GOT THIS DOWN.
AND TO THINK, WE WERE TRYING
TO TALK HIM OUT OF-- OW!
- A STRUCTURE THIS SIZE
HAS GOT TO HAVE
A WEAK SPOT SOMEWHERE.
- INDEED IT MUST.
BUT DON'T YOU THINK BAL MASQUE
WOULD BE AWARE OF IT?
- Tiamat: THAT IS A RISK.
- Alastor: MMM.
ONE WE'LL HAVE TO TAKE
IF WE WANT TO GET INSIDE.
WE HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO JUMP IN HEAD FIRST.
- ( Margery laughs )
NOTHING WRONG WITH GAMBLING.
- SHANA.
- WE HAVE TO
GET INSIDE AND FAST.
- WHY?
SO YOU CAN SAVE SAKAI?
- NOT QUITE.
SO I CAN FIGHT ALONGSIDE HIM.
HE'S IN THERE
AND HE'S FIGHTING FOR HIS LIFE.
- SHANA.
- CAN'T SEEM TO FIND A WAY OUT
AND I CAN'T REACH ANYONE
WITH MY BOOKMARK.
I WONDER WHY SHANA
HASN'T SHOWN UP YET.
IT MUST BE TOUGH
TO GET INSIDE.
OTHERWISE I'M SURE
SHE'D BE HERE BY NOW.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT THIS THING IS,
BUT I CAN SENSE ITS PRESENCE.
AND IT'S RIDICULOUSLY STRONG.
IT HAS ENOUGH POWER
TO COMPLETELY LEVEL
MISAKI CITY.
IN THAT CASE,
I KNOW WHAT I'VE GOT TO DO.
I HAVE TO GET IT BACK.
I NEED THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD
IF I EVER HOPE TO PROTECT
THIS CITY!
- ( wind howling )
- ( steam whistle blows )
- EXCELLENT!
I CANNOT WAIT.
IT WON'T BE LONG
UNTIL OUR EXPERIMENT
BECOMES A REALITY!
- PROFESSOR,
INTRUDER DETECTED!
IT APPEARS TO BE...
- ( beeping )
...THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD'S
FORMER MYSTES.
- SEND THE TROOPS IN AFTER HIM.
HE MUST NOT GET IN OUR WAY!
AS YOU WISH, SIR.
- ( scanning )
- ( heartbeat )
- IT'S UP THERE.
- HA!
OW, OW, OW, OW.
- ( all barking )
( all screaming )
- ( scanning )
- Domino: IT SEEMS THE TROOPS
HAVE LOST TRACK OF THE MYSTES,
PROFESSOR.
- HOW COULD YOU DROP THE BALL
LIKE THIS, DOMINO?
I'VE EQUIPPED YOU
WITH AN ENTIRE ARMY.
I EVEN GAVE YOU
A RADAR ANTENNA.
- TRUE, SIR.
BUT YOU ALSO MADE THE INTERIOR
OF THE CLOCK TOWER SO
COMPLICATED THAT MY TROO--
- AHHH!  YOU MORON!
THAT'S THE LAMEST EXCUSE
I'VE EVER HEARD.
THEY SHOULD BE ABLE
TO NAVIGATE
THE INTRICATE PATHWAYS
I CREATED FOR THEM.
- I WILL REPRIMAND THEM, SIR!
- Sato:
MARGERY, I FOUND SOMETHING.
I SEE WHAT LOOKS
LIKE A SMALL VORTEX
TOWARDS THE TOP OF THE DOME.
YOU GUYS AREN'T GOING
TO GO INSIDE THAT THING,
ARE YOU?
- We've got no choice.
Well, that's all I needed
from you.
- 'KAY.
- Keisaku,
you've made me proud today.
THANK YOU.
LET'S DO THIS!
- THANK YOU FOR TELLING US
WHAT HAPPENED TO YUJI.
- BE CAREFUL.
- DON'T YOU WORRY.
I'LL BRING HIM BACK WITH ME
AND WE'LL SETTLE OUR RIVALRY.
HOLD ON, YUJI, I'M COMING.
- Kazumi: HOW CAN I COMPETE
WITH THAT?
I'M SO SELFISH.
I SHOULD BE PRAYING
FOR THEIR SAFETY.
- Margery: THERE IT IS.
- Wilhelmina: IT'S SMALLER
THAN I THOUGHT IT WOULD BE.
- Tiamat: MAKES IT A CHALLENGE.
- LEAVE IT TO ME.
- Marcosias ( laughs ):
I KNEW IT WOULDN'T BE LONG
BEFORE YOU TOOK THE REINS,
MY DEAR MARGERY DAW!
- I'LL CAST A SPELL
THAT SHOULD
HELP WIDEN THE HOLE A BIT.
JUST FOLLOW MY LEAD.
- Alastor: IT'S SUCH
AN OBVIOUS POINT OF ENTRY.
WE'RE CERTAIN TO BE AMBUSHED
BY THE ENEMY.
- Marcosias:
LIKE WE DON'T KNOW THAT?
BUT THE LONGER
WE SIT OUT HERE YAPPIN',
THE LONGER
THE KID'S IN THERE SWEATING!
- HE'S RIGHT.
LOOK, IF ANYONE ATTACKS US,
I'LL HANDLE IT.
- THANK YOU, AND GOOD LUCK.
- THE LION AND THE UNICORN--
- Marcosias:
--WERE FIGHTING FOR THE CROWN.
- THE LION BEAT THE UNICORN
ALL AROUND THE TOWN!
AHHH!
- THOUGH YOUR SPEEDY REFLEXES
ARE QUITE IMPRESSIVE,
THAT WASN'T ENOUGH TO--
- AHHH!
- THANK YOU, CHANTER.
WE WILL COME BACK FOR YOU.
- HA.  NO PROB.
- MARGERY'S DOWN.
- Sydonay:
SO SHE WAS JUST ACTING
AS A DECOY
TO GET THE TWO OF YOU INSIDE.
HOW NOBLE OF HER, YET STUPID.
DID SHE HONESTLY THINK
YOU COULD STOP US?
- WHAT IS THIS THING?
- Wilhelmina: IT APPEARS
TO BE THE CLOCK TOWER.
IT'S BEEN TRANSFORMED.
- ISN'T IT STUNNING?
IT'S MY LATEST CREATION.
- Alastor: I SHOULD HAVE KNOWN
YOU WERE RESPONSIBLE FOR THIS.
WHY DO YOU
KEEP ATTACKING THIS CITY?
- I HAVE MY REASONS.
ALLOW ME TO EXPLAIN,
FLAME OF HEAVEN.
I AM CONSTANTLY LOOKING
FOR WAYS TO PROVE MY WORTH
AS A SCIENTIST,
SO WHEN I WAS OFFERED
THIS OPPORTUNITY,
I SIMPLY
COULDN'T PASS IT UP.
BEHOLD!
AS YOU'LL RECALL,
BALL MASQUE ONCE CREATED
A FOUNTAIN
OF POWER OF EXISTENCE
THAT RAINED DOWN
UPON MISAKI CITY.
- WE DISABLED IT.
- YES, BUT NOT BEFORE
THAT POWER WAS ABSORBED
BY THE EARTH
AND THE LOVELY BEL-PEOL
CAST A SPELL
TO HIDE IT
FROM YOU SCOUNDRELS.
KNOWING WE HAD
A PLENTIFUL AMOUNT OF POWER
FOR THE EXPERIMENT,
WE THEN SENT IN A FAUX VESSEL
TO COLLECT HUMAN EMOTIONS.
- "FAUX VESSEL?"
WHAT IS THIS LUNATIC
RAVING ABOUT?
- FUMINA KONOE.
- YOU ARE ABOUT TO WITNESS
THE BIRTH
OF AN EVOLVED DENIZEN,
ONE THAT IS FUELED
BY POWER OF EXISTENCE
AND UTILIZES HUMAN EMOTIONS!
- ENOUGH WITH THE DRAMATICS,
PROFESSOR.
I THINK THEY GET IT.
- DON'T RAIN ON MY PARADE,
SYD.
CAN'T YOU SEE
THAT I'M ABOUT TO REVEAL
MY MASTERPIECE?
ITS HEART,
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD,
BEATS WITHIN ITS CHEST.
BEHOLD THE TAIMEI SHIHEN!
- THE TAIMEI SHIHEN?
- Alastor: WE CANNOT
LET THEM GET AWAY WITH THIS.
WE MUST DESTROY THE BEAST
AT ONCE.
- PERSONA-- TRANSFORM!
I'M READY.
- Tiamat: AS AM I.
- AHHH!
AHHHH!
SUPREME THRONE, HECATE!
- ASTER!
- Shana: YUJI,
I KNOW YOU'RE HERE SOMEWHERE.
I CAN FEEL IT.
YOU'RE STILL ALIVE.
TOGETHER, I KNOW
WE CAN PUT AN END TO THIS
BEFORE YOUR POWER RUNS OUT.
- ( Dominos barking )
- SOMETHING KEEPS DRAINING
MY POWER.
I CAN SENSE
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD,
BUT I CAN'T PINPOINT IT.
I JUST HAVE TO CONCENTRATE
AND KEEP MOVING.
- Domino: GO!
- GO!
- ( grunts )
DAMN IT.
- SECOND STAGE-- COMMENCE!
- ( laughs )
UNLEASH THE POWER!
- GO!
- AHHHHH!
- Dantalion:
WHAT YOU ARE ABOUT TO WITNESS,
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
IS A MIRACLE OF SCIENCE!
ITS VERY EXISTENCE
WAS ONCE THOUGHT IMPOSSIBLE.
MAY I PRESENT TO YOU
THE FIRST CRIMSON DENIZEN
BORN IN THE HUMAN WORLD?!
FROM THIS DAY FORWARD,
IT SHALL BE CALLED
THE STATUE OF PRIDE!
- THE STATUE OF PRIDE?
- ( theme music playing )
- Yuji:
BAL MASQUE'S SECRET WEAPON
HAS BEEN AWAKENED.
AS I PICK UP MY SWORD,
I CALL OUT THE NAME OF THE
PERSON I WANT TO PROTECT MOST.
ON THE FINAL
"SHAKUGAN NO SHANA SECOND,"
"WHAT MUST BE PROTECTED."