- Alastor:
YUJI SAKAI'S FATHER KANTAROU
SUDDENLY RETURNED HOME
SURPRISING EVERYONE.
CHIGUSA EXPLAINED
TO SHANA AND KAZUMI
WHAT IT FELT LIKE
TO BE IN LOVE.
LATER, KANTAROU TOLD THEM THE
SECRET TO A SUCCESSFUL MARRIAGE.
THEIR WORDS AFFECTED THE GIRLS
IN SUCH A WAY,
THAT AFTERWARDS THEY FOUND
THEIR FEELINGS
FOR YUJI REIGNITED.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- THERE YOU ARE.
GOOD MORNING, DEAR.
- OH, I DIDN'T HEAR YOU GET UP.
AND GOOD MORNING TO YOU.
I HOPE YOU'RE HUNGRY
'CAUSE I'VE GOT BREAKFAST READY.
- YUJI'S NOT EATING?
- HE ATE ALREADY,
BEFORE HE LEFT FOR SCHOOL.
- HE ALWAYS LEAVE THIS EARLY?
- NOT USUALLY, BUT
THEY'RE PREPARING FOR
THE AUTUMN FESTIVAL.
HE SAID THEY DON'T
EVEN HAVE CLASS TODAY.
AND THEY'LL BE STAYING OVERNIGHT
TO WRAP EVERYTHING UP.
- HMM, DOESN'T SOUND
LIKE MUCH FUN.
THANKS FOR THE FOOD.
- NOPE,
IT'S NOT QUITE STRAIGHT.
MOVE IT TO THE LEFT.
NO, YOUR OTHER LEFT.
ALMOST THERE.  THAT'S IT.
LOOKS GOOD.
- WE NEED ANOTHER DESK.
- WHY DON'T YOU GRAB ONE
FROM THE LIBRARY?
- YEAH, COOL.
- YOU GOT IT, DUDE?
- CAN YOU HAND ME
A THUMBTACK?
- HERE YOU GO.
- YEAH, NO.
I DON'T THINK THIS IS RIGHT.
- WHAT'S "THE PERILS
OF LOVE" MEAN?
- ( playing notes )
- FESTIVAL'S SHAPING UP NICELY
THIS YEAR.  I CAN'T WAIT.
- YEAH, ME TOO.
- SOMETHING WRONG?
YOU DON'T SOUND TOO HAPPY.
- NO, I'M FINE.
WHAT DO YOU THINK IT MEANS?
- I'M AFRAID I DON'T KNOW.
- SILVER!
I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE
PAINTED SILVER, NOT GOLD.
- OH, SORRY.  MY BAD.
- WELL...
NO REASON
TO WASTE MY TIME WORRYING.
- Boys:
ONE, TWO, THREE!
- AWESOME.
NOW ALL WE'VE GOTTA DO IS WAIT
FOR THE CREPE MAKING MACHINE
TO GET HERE.
- SO THE ONLY
MYSTERY'S MARGERY.
SHE GONNA SHOW?
- WHAT THE HELL IS
AN "AUTUMN FESTIVAL"?
NEVER HEARD OF
THAT KIND OF DENIZEN.
- THAT'S BECAUSE IT ISN'T ONE.
- IT'S AN EVENT AT OUR SCHOOL.
WE'D LIKE YOU TO COME,
IF YOU CAN.
- I'LL GO AS LONG AS
I CAN DRINK.
- SORRY,
THERE WON'T BE ANY BOOZE.
WE'RE UNDERAGE, REMEMBER?
- YEAH, NO, COUNT ME OUT.
- IF SHE CAN'T DRINK,
SHE WON'T SHOW.
- OH, YEAH.
- THIS IS GONNA LOOK SO AWESOME.
- DOES ANYONE KNOW
HOW TO MAKE A PATTERN?
- YOU FEELING OKAY? I DON'T WANT
YOU TO PUSH YOURSELF TOO HARD.
IF YOU WANT,
I CAN TAKE OVER FOR YOU.
NO, I'LL BE FINE.
DON'T WORRY.
- SO HOW ARE YOU
HOLDING UP, SHANA?
IF YOU NEED ANY HELP,
LET ME KNOW, OKAY?
- NAH, I'VE GOT IT.
- Chigusa:
IF THAT'S HOW YOU FEEL.
LISTEN TO YOUR HEART,
IT'LL TELL YOU WHAT TO DO.
- IF YOU FIND YOU'RE
FEELING LOST,
ALL YOU HAVE TO DO
IS REACH OUT.
YOU NEVER KNOW. THERE MIGHT
BE SOMEONE REACHING OUT
TO YOU AS WELL.
- I DON'T THINK IT'LL REACH.
AND I DON'T WANNA CUT IT
TOO SHORT.
CAN YOU HELP ME OUT?
- YEAH, SURE THING.
- ( sighs )
- ( laughing )
- ALL DONE.
CHECK IT OUT!
- OH, WOW!  YOU'RE SO FAST.
- IT'LL PROBABLY FALL APART
IN NO TIME.
- NAH, I'M JUST
A QUICK SEAMSTRESS.
BESIDES,
MAKING A LION COSTUME'S EASY.
TANAKA'S GONNA LOOK AWESOME.
- I CAN'T WAIT TO SEE HIM IN IT.
- ( laughs ) ME EITHER.
I COULD USE A GOOD LAUGH.
- AHA!
TALK ABOUT GOOD TIMING.
COME WITH ME
FOR A SEC, WOULD YOU?
- UH...
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- Nakamura: OH, YOU MAKE
A PERFECT COWARDLY LION!
WHAT DO YOU THINK, OGATA?
HE LOOKS PRETTY GOOD, HUH?
- YEAH, NOT BAD.
HEY, I JUST REMEMBERED
I GOT SOMETHING TO DO.
- ( Ogata falls, shouts )
- Boy: ( laughs ) NICE ONE!
- SORRY ABOUT THAT.
- I SWEAR, THAT GIRL COULD NOT
BE ANY MORE OBVIOUS
IF SHE TRIED.
- WELL, I GUESS
IT'S ALMOST TIME.
ARE WE ALL READY TO GET
THIS SHOW ON THE ROAD?
- WE DON'T HAVE LONG NOW.
- JEEZ,
WHAT ARE YOU FREAKED OUT FOR?
YOU REALIZE WE'RE ALL BASICALLY
GETTING TO SKIP CLASS.
SHOULDN'T YOU GUYS BE STOKED?
- Sato: YOU ALL RIGHT, IKE?
I'M WORRIED YOU'RE NOT GONNA
MAKE IT TO THE FESTIVAL.
- Yuji:
YEAH, RIGHT?  ALL THAT WORK,
I SURE DON'T ENVY
YOU COMMITTEE MEMBERS.
BUT AREN'T YOU WORRIED YOU'RE
WORKING A BIT TOO HARD?
- IT'S NOT ME.
IT'S THE PERSON WHO'S ABOVE ME
WHO'S WORKING ME TO DEATH.
WE'LL ASK LOCAL SHOP OWNERS
TO PUT THESE FLYERS UP,
THEN WE'LL SEE HOW THE PROGRAM
IS LOOKING
AND TALK TO THE BROADCASTING
CLUB ABOUT A POSSIBLE
RADIO COMMERCIAL.
- WOW, FUJITA.
YOU SURE HAVE A LOT
ON YOUR PLATE.
- GUESS SO.  THIS IS MY FIRST
TIME DOING COMMITTEE WORK,
AND I DON'T WANNA
LET ANYBODY DOWN.
I'M ONLY TRYING TO KEEP UP
WITH YOUR AWESOMENESS, IKE.
-NAH, I THINK
YOU'VE GOT ME BEAT.
- WE NEED TO STORE
THESE SPARE MATERIALS,
CONFIRM THE PARADE ROUTE
WITH THE CITY
AND DOUBLE CHECK
EACH DEPARTMENT'S PROGRESS.
THEN WE CAN GO
FINISH UP OUR MANAGING
REPRESENTATIVE'S REPORTS.
- ALL THIS WORK
AND YOU'RE STILL CHIPPER.
- WELL,
THE WORK'S GOTTA BE DONE
SO I MIGHT AS WELL DO IT
WITH A SMILE, RIGHT?
- YEAH, THAT'S TRUE.
I'LL TRY TO KEEP UP WITH YOU.
- WE'LL TAKE FUTONS
TO EACH CLASSROOM,
AND WE'LL INSPECT THE STANDS
OUTSIDE FOR ANY CODE VIOLATIONS,
THEN WE'LL WRITE UP THE BALLOTS
AND START PRINTING THEM OUT.
- DON'T YOU NEED A BREAK?
- NO, DON'T BE SILLY.
WHO HAS TIME TO THINK
ABOUT BREAKS WHEN THERE'S
SO MUCH WORK TO BE DONE?
- YEAH, RIGHT.  SILLY ME.
- NO, I TOTALLY FORGOT
WE STILL HAVE TO RESERVE
ALL THE PARKING SPOTS
OUTSIDE THE SCHOOL.
- OH!
- SOUNDS LIKE MORE TROUBLE
THAN IT'S WORTH.
- I KNOW YOU'RE BUSY,
BUT HERE.
I MADE SANDWICHES
FOR EVERYBODY 'CAUSE I KNEW
WE WOULDN'T HAVE
MUCH TIME FOR LUNCH.
YOU SHOULD EAT ONE WHILE YOU
HAVE A MOMENT.
- Ogata: YOU'RE THE GREATEST,
KAZUMI.  ISN'T SHE SWEET?
- SHE TOTALLY IS.
YOU HAVE NO IDEA.
THANK YOU FOR THE FOO--
- THERE YOU ARE, IKE.
WE'VE GOT BIG TROUBLE.  THE JAZZ
CLUB AND THE MANDOLIN BAND
ARE ARGUING OVER WHO'S GONNA
GET THE MOST STAGE TIME.
- YOU GOTTA FEEL SORRY
FOR HIM, YOU KNOW?
POOR GUY'S GOT
THE WORST LUCK EVER.
- THE MANDOLIN BAND GETS
THE STAGE FROM 10:00 TO 11:00.
COME ON, LET'S GO.
- Yuji: SEE YOU TOMORROW, KONOE.
BRIGHT AND EARLY.
- THANK YOU FOR COMING OUT
AND SEEING ME OFF.
I WAS THINKING.
I SURE WISH I COULD STAY
AND SPEND THE NIGHT HERE
WITH ALL OF YOU.
I BET IT'S GOING TO BE FUN.
- IT DOESN'T HAPPEN TOO OFTEN
AND WE'D LOVE
TO HAVE YOU JOIN US.
- I EVEN HAVE A DECK OF CARDS
IF WE GET BORED.
WHY DON'T YOU SEND
YOUR BUTLER HOME AND STAY?
COME ON, IT'LL BE A BLAST.
- WHILE I'M SURE SHE
APPRECIATES THE INVITATION,
I'M AFRAID MISS KONOE WILL
HAVE TO POLITELY DECLINE.
YOU KIDS HAVE
A GOOD EVENING NOW.
- Fujita: GIRLS, I'VE BEEN
LOOKING ALL OVER FOR YOU.
SHOWER TIME FOR SECOND YEARS
IS 6:00.
WE SHOULD HEAD THAT WAY NOW
OR WE'LL MISS OUR TIME SLOT.
- WHOA.  TIME TO HIT
THE SHOWERS ALREADY?
GUESS WE'D BETTER GO.
- MM-HMM.
TANAKA,
MAYBE I'LL SEE YOU LATER?
- MAYBE.
- IF YOU'RE FEELING LOST,
JUST REACH OUT.
LISTEN TO YOUR HEART.
IT'LL TELL YOU WHAT TO DO.
- Nakamura: WHOA, KAZUMI!  YOU
WENT AND GOT ALL CURVY ON US.
- EXCUSE ME?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN HIDING
THOSE BIG OLD BAZOOMBAS?
- ( laughing )
- OH, NO.
FUJITA,
CAN YOU HELP ME OUT HERE?
- NO CAN DO.  I DON'T HAVE
MY GLASSES ON RIGHT NOW.
- PLEASE LET ME SHOWER IN PEACE.
- OH, I JUST WANNA SQUEEZE 'EM.
- COME ON,
DON'T BE CREEPY, NAKAMURA.
- CUT OUT THE HORSEPLAY
AND JUST SHOWER ALREADY.
- I WONDER WHY IT'S
TAKING ME SO LONG
TO ACCUMULATE EXCESSIVE FAT
IN MY CHEST.
- OH, SHANA.
- ( gasps )
I SAID CUT IT OUT!
- ( laughing )
- SHANA, YOU STILL AWAKE?
- YEAH, I AM.
- I WANTED TO THANK YOU
FOR WHAT YOU SAID.
- YOU'LL PLAY ROMEO TO KAZUMI'S
JULIET, AND THAT'S THAT.
I LIKE YOU.
BUT I WON'T LOSE TO YOU.
- I'M FINE WITH THAT.
I'M NOT STUPID.
I SEE THE WAY YUJI LOOKS AT YOU.
HE MAY NOT HAVE MADE
A DECISION YET,
BUT I KNOW WHO HE'LL CHOOSE.
I'VE ALWAYS KNOWN.
YOU'D THINK I'D BE UPSET
ABOUT IT, BUT I'M NOT.
I THINK IT'S THE RIGHT CHOICE
FOR HIM.
THE TWO OF YOU HAVE BEEN
FIGHTING ALONGSIDE EACH OTHER
ALL THIS TIME,
BUT I WON'T GIVE UP.
- THE TWO OF YOU HAVE BEEN
FIGHTING ALONGSIDE EACH OTHER
ALL THIS TIME.
- Yuji: YOU NEED A HAND?
IT DIDN'T TAKE US VERY LONG
TO SET UP THE CREPE STAND.
SO I'M FREE TO HELP.
"THE ROAD BEFORE
THE STATION," HUH?
AH, THAT'S WHERE IT GOES.
ARE YOU OKAY?
- YEAH, JUST DAYDREAMING.
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS,
YUJI AND I
ALWAYS MAKE IT THROUGH.
WE ALWAYS WILL.
- I'M ALL DONE.
- ( gasps ) OH!
- ( laughs ) CAN YOU TRY IT ON
FOR ME REAL QUICK, KAZUMI?
- OH, I DON'T THINK SO.
- I JUST WANNA SEE
WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE ON YOU.
I GOTTA MAKE SURE IT FITS.
- CAN'T WE GO SOMEWHERE PRIVATE?
- COME ON,
NO NEED TO BE MODEST.
- BUT SOFT.
WHAT LIGHT THROUGH
YONDER WINDOW BREAKS?
IT IS THE EAST
AND JULIET IS THE SUN.
ARISE, FAIR SUN,
AND KILL THE ENVIOUS MOON,
WHO IS-- SORRY.
I WAS SAYING ROMEO'S LINES.
O THAT I WERE A GLOVE UPON
THAT HAND
THAT I MIGHT TOUCH THAT CHEEK.
- ( gasping )
- WOW, KONOE,
THAT WAS AMAZING.
- HOW MUCH SHAKESPEARE
DO YOU HAVE MEMORIZED?
- WHAT DO YOU THINK, ALASTOR?
- I AM AFRAID YUJI SAKAI'S
SILVER FLAME
MEANS THERE IS A CONNECTION
BETWEEN THE TWO.
I KNOW THAT'S NOT WHAT
YOU WANTED TO HEAR.
NO, BUT THAT DOESN'T
CHANGE HOW I FEEL.
- EVEN FLAME HAZE CAN
FALL VICTIM TO LOVE.
REMEMBER WHAT MRS. SAKAI SAID,
"LISTEN TO YOUR HEART.
IT WILL TELL YOU WHAT TO DO."
HER WORDS COULD NOT
HAVE BEEN MORE TRUE.
- I HAVE FINISHED MY
INVESTIGATION, MILADY.
- WILHELMINA.
- Yuji:
WHAT'S UP, SHANA?
CAN'T THIS WAIT UNTIL MORNING?
WILHELMINA.
- MY INVESTIGATION
OF THE KEEPER
ON THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD
LED ME TO INFORMATION
I THINK YOU NEED
TO HEAR REGARDING
A POWERFUL CRIMSON DENIZEN.
- A DENIZEN?
- Tiamat:
PHELES, THE CAPRICE OF BEAUTY.
- SHE'S ONE OF THE CRIMSON
WORLD'S MIGHTIEST LORDS
AND THE CREATOR
OF THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
LONG AGO, PHELES DECLARED HER
DEVOTION TO HER ETERNAL LOVER.
A HUMAN NAMED JOHAN.
WHO BECAME THE MIDNIGHT
LOST CHILD'S MYSTES.
TOGETHER, THEY ARE
THE PROMISED PAIR.
OTHERWISE KNOWN
AS ENGAGED LINK.
- WHY DIDN'T I KNOW THIS?
- Wilhelmina: PHELES WAS SO
IN LOVE WITH JOHAN,
SHE CREATED
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
SO THAT SHE WOULD NEVER
HAVE TO LEAVE HIS SIDE.
AMAZINGLY, SHE WAS ABLE
TO MANIPULATE TIME EVERY DAY
AT THE STROKE OF MIDNIGHT.
HER LOVER'S POWER OF EXISTENCE
WOULD REPLENISH ITSELF.
THEY WOULD STILL
BE TOGETHER TODAY
HAD THEY NOT LOST
A BRUTAL BATTLE.
- THAT MUST'VE BEEN WHEN
THE TREASURE TOOL WAS RELEASED
AND SOMEHOW FOUND
ITS WAY INTO ME.
- THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD
IS A TESTAMENT
TO THE ENGAGED LINK'S LOVE,
A MEMORY OF THE BRIEF TIME
THEY SPENT TOGETHER.
THE PROBLEM IS--
- Tiamat: SHE SURVIVED.
- INCREDIBLY, PHELES MADE IT
THROUGH THE BATTLE.
- SHE'S ALIVE?
SO WHAT'S THAT MEAN FOR ME?
I'M AFRAID IT MEANS SHE'S GOING
TO COME LOOKING FOR YOU.
TO COLLECT THE MEMENTO
OF HER ETERNAL LOVER.
I AM NOT CERTAIN,
BUT IT APPEARS PHELES PUT
THE KEEPER
ON THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD
IN HOPES
OF PROTECTING IT
FROM BEING STOLEN.
I HATE TO SAY IT, BUT YOUR LIFE
IS IN GRAVE DANGER.
IF PHELES EVER GETS A HOLD
OF YOU, YOU'LL BE DONE FOR.
- Tiamat:
IT'S INEVITABLE.
- DOES MY FLAME--
DOES THE COLOR OF MY FLAME
HAVE ANYTHING TO DO WITH THIS?
- PARDON.  I'M SORRY,
BUT I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
- Tiamat:
YOU'RE NOT MAKING ANY SENSE.
- MY SILVER FLAME.
I WAS FINALLY ABLE TO CAST
AN UNRESTRICTED SPELL,
BUT FOR SOME REASON
MY SEAL WAS SILVER.
- I DIDN'T HAVE THE CHANCE
TO TELL YOU.
WE WERE ALL COMPLETELY SHOCKED.
BUT IT DID HAPPEN.
- Wilhelmina: IMPOSSIBLE.
THERE'S NO WAY HE
COULD HAVE DONE THAT.
- Tiamat: DO NOT LIE TO US.
- WE'RE NOT LYING.
I SAW IT WITH MY OWN EYES.
ALASTOR DID TOO.
- BUT THE COLOR SILVER.
- Alastor: THE CAPRICE
OF BEAUTY'S SEARCH
FOR THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD
HAS ABSOLUTELY NOTHING TO DO
WITH THE SILVER.
THEY ARE TWO ENTIRELY
SEPARATE ISSUES.
I WILL WARN YOU, YUJI SAKAI.
YOU ARE ABOUT
TO FACE TWO TRIALS,
THE LIKES OF WHICH YOU HAVE
NEVER EXPERIENCED BEFORE.
- I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE
WE FINISHED IT ALL.
- I KNOW, RIGHT?
TOMORROW IS GONNA BE AWESOME.
- ( both laugh )
- ALL RIGHT, I HOPE YOU GUYS ARE
READY FOR A GOOD TIME TOMORROW.
- Both: YOU BETCHA.
- YOU FEELING OKAY?
YOU'RE NOT LOOKING
SO HOT, MAN.
- I'M FINE.
I JUST NEED SOME REST.
NOW THAT ALL OUR WORK IS DONE,
I SHOULD FINALLY BE ABLE TO--
- OH, THERE YOU ARE, IKE.
I'M GLAD I CAUGHT YOU.
WE DON'T HAVE ENOUGH ROPE
FOR THE PARADE TOMORROW
SO WE NEED TO GO BUY SOME.
- ( all groan )
- I SAID IT BEFORE.
WORST LUCK EVER.
- Wilhelmina: I'LL INDEED
SEE WHAT I CAN FIND OUT
ABOUT THE SILVER.
PHELES HAS ABSOLUTE POWER,
MILADY.
PROMISE ME YOU'LL BE CAREFUL,
AS YOUR LIFE MAY BE
IN DANGER AS WELL.
- ANYTHING ELSE
YOU WANNA TELL US?
I GET THE FEELING YOU'RE
HOLDING SOMETHING BACK.
WILHELMINA?
- FIRST THE SILVER FLAME.
AND NOW I'M BEING HUNTED.
I MEAN, COME ON, WHAT NEXT?
WHAT THE HELL AM I?
- YUJI.
I WANT YOU TO PROMISE ME.
WHEN YOU MAKE A DECISION,
I'LL BE THE FIRST TO KNOW.
- BUT, SHANA.
I PROMISE.
NO MATTER WHAT,
I'LL BE HERE FOR YOU.
- PHELES, I'M BEGGING YOU.
DON'T COME AFTER HIM.
I DON'T WANT TO FIGHT YOU.
- Pheles: JOHAN.
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- Yuji: THE AUTUMN FESTIVAL IS
UNDERWAY AND EVERYONE IS EXCITED
TO PARTICIPATE IN THE PARADE,
ESPECIALLY THOSE WHO ARE HOPING
TO WIN THE GRAND PRIZE.
IF ONLY TIMES LIKE THESE
COULD LAST FOREVER,
BUT ALL GOOD THINGS
HAVE TO COME TO AN END.
SUDDENLY AN UNPLEASANT WIND
SWEEPS THROUGH MISAKI CITY.
NEXT TIME ON
"SHAKUGAN NO SHANA II"...
"THE AUTUMN FESTIVAL BEGINS."