- Alastor: IKE MAY BE
THE BRAINS OF THE GROUP,
BUT HIS AFFECTION FOR
YOSHIDA PROVED TOO MUCH
EVEN FOR A BRIGHT YOUNG MAN
SUCH AS HIM TO HANDLE.
HE METICULOUSLY PLANNED
AN OUTING TO A THEME PARK,
ONLY TO WATCH HIS EVERY
CALCULATION FAIL.
FORTUNATELY, GOOD MEMORIES
CAN BE MADE FROM MISADVENTURE,
AND THE GROUP
WILL LONG REMEMBER THIS DAY.
- ( theme song playing )
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- ( moaning )
- ( yelling )
- STOP RIGHT NOW!  I WANT
MY REVENGE.  I'LL KILL THEM!
- ( gasping )
THAT WAS SOME DREAM.
DID I SAY ANYTHING?
- Marcosias: DON'T THINK SO.
- ( yelling )
- OH!
- COME BACK HERE.
- YOU CAN DO IT, YUJI.
- I'LL CRUSH YOU!
- WELL DONE.
- Yuji: THAT WAS
A PRETTY LOW BLOW, WILHELMINA.
WHY DID YOU PUT ME UP
AGAINST THAT RINNE?
- I HAD NO CHOICE.
THE FLAME OF THE HEAVENS
AND HIS PARTNER REQUESTED IT.
- Tiamat: OUR HANDS WERE TIED.
- ALASTOR?
- HMM, I SUPPOSE
IT'S TIME
FOR US TO MOVE ON
TO THE NEXT STEP.
- NEXT STEP?
- CASTING AN UNRESTRICTED SPELL.
- UNRESTRICTED?
WHO, ME?
- YES.  WHEN IT COMES TO
THE SENSING
AND CONTROLLING
OF POWER OF EXISTENCE,
YOU'RE ACTUALLY AT A PRETTY
ADVANCED LEVEL ALREADY.
- I'M NOT SO SURE.
OH, YEAH.
YOU FIND ANYTHING OUT
ABOUT THE KEEPER
ON THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD?
- INDEED, ALTHOUGH THE MATTER
REMAINS UNDER INVESTIGATION.
I'VE RECENTLY RECEIVED
INFORMATION FROM OUTLAW.
I AM CURRENTLY
ANALYZING IT.
- Tiamat: DO NOT BE
CONCERNED.
- Alastor: THERE'S NO REASON
TO WORRY ABOUT THAT NOW.
REMAIN FOCUSED AND CONCENTRATE
ON THE TASK AT HAND.
- YEAH, THAT'S EASY FOR YOU
TO SAY.  IT DOESN'T AFFECT YOU.
- ALASTOR'S RIGHT.
YOU NEED TO FOCUS
ON YOUR TRAINING.
WE'LL START WORKING ON CASTING
A SEAL FIRST THING TOMORROW.
- ( distant dog barking )
- LET ME SEE.
- Tiamat: THAT'S
AN ISOLATED CASE.
- I FAIL TO SEE
HOW IT RELATES
TO OUR CURRENT SITUATION
IN ANY WAY.
- ( ticking )
- WAIT, WHAT IS THIS?
IT CAN'T BE.
NOT PHELES.
- ( birds chirping )
- GOOD MORNING.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- I WILL INDEED BE LEAVING
FOR A SHORT TIME.
- ( Tanaka sighs )
WOULD YOU LOOK AT THIS MESS?
- Margery: OH, LIGHTEN UP.
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
( giggling )
- SATO.
TALK ABOUT GOOD TIMING.
GIVE ME A HAND.
- HEY, MARGERY,
I NEED A FAVOR.
- OH, YOU DO NOW?
WELL, THEN LET'S HEAR IT,
KIDDO.
- I WANT YOU
TO TRAIN ME.
- HMM.
DON'T BE STUPID.
I CAN'T DO THAT.
- I DON'T FEEL LIKE
WE'RE DOING ENOUGH TO HELP.
EVEN IF WE CAN'T INCREASE
OUR PHYSICAL STRENGTH,
THERE'S GOT TO BE
SOMETHING WE CAN DO.
- DUDE, WHAT'S GOTTEN
INTO YOU?  CHILL.
- I WANT POWER.
I'LL TRY ANYTHING.
- POWER FOR WHAT?
- WELL, SO--
SO THAT I CAN FOLLOW YOU.
I'LL LEAVE THIS CITY BEHIND
AND GO ANYWHERE YOU GO.
I WANT TO BE STRONG ENOUGH
TO BE ABLE TO HELP YOU.
- YOU REALIZE YOU'D DIE?
YOU POOR BOYS,
YOU JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND.
- ABOUT WHAT?
- ( ice clinking )
- VERY WELL.
I SUPPOSE
I SHOULD TELL YOU
A LITTLE BIT
ABOUT THE WORLD I COME FROM.
IT OUGHT TO GIVE YOU
SOME INSIGHT INTO WHO I AM.
SEVERAL YEARS AFTER
THE GREAT DEPRESSION...
NEW YORK CITY,
THE HEART OF THE CATASTROPHE,
WANTED TO REGAIN
ITS FORMER GLORY,
RESTORE ITS SPLENDOR.
- ( boat horn blares )
- ( chuckles )
- NICE TO MEET YOU.
BUT I CAN'T STAY LONG.
- Marcosias: SORRY TO BE ABRUPT,
BUT GOODBYE.
- I AM ANNABERG, THE CHASM
OF FASTIDIOUS IMPALING.
FROM THE COLOR
OF YOUR FLAME,
I ASSUME I'M IN THE PRESENCE
OF MARCOSIAS,
THE CLAWS AND FANGS
OF VIOLATION,
AND MARGERY DAW,
THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES--
TWO ILLUSTRIOUS NAMES.
- Marcosias: YEAH,
WHAT'S IT TO YOU, BUDDY?
- SHUT UP AND DIE,
DENIZEN.
- ( Marcosias laughs )
THAT WAS TOO EASY.
- HIS POWER OF EXISTENCE
WAS STRONG,
BUT HIS FIGHTING SKILLS
WERE NOT.
I'M ALMOST OFFENDED
HE DIDN'T TRY HARDER.
( gasps )
WHERE IS HE?
- BELOW US!
- SYDONAY,
THE THOUSAND CHANGES,
THANKS FOR THE TIMELY
ASSISTANCE.
- I WAS JUST DOING
MY JOB.
SHALL I
FINISH HER OFF?
I DON'T LIKE LEAVING A JOB
HALF-FINISHED,
ESPECIALLY THIS ONE.
- YOU KNOW HER THEN?
- WHILE I'VE NOT FACED HER
PERSONALLY UNTIL NOW,
I CERTAINLY KNOW
WHO SHE IS.
HUNDREDS OF MY MEN HAVE BEEN
KILLED BY HER ATTACKS.
- THE STRONG PRESENCE
I FELT BEFORE--
IT WAS HIM.
DAMN IT.
I'VE BEEN DECEIVED.
- Annaberg: THEN LET'S END HER
NOW AND BE DONE WITH IT.
WE CAN'T AFFORD
TO WASTE ANY TIME.
I SCHEDULED MY ARRIVAL
IN MANHATTAN TO COINCIDE
WITH THE DEPARTURE
OF THE FLAME HAZE.
BUT WHO KNOWS
WHEN THEY MIGHT RETURN?
- YOU'RE THE CLIENT.
I JUST DO WHAT I'M ASKED.
- HUMANITY,
YOU FASCINATE ME.
I PRAISE
YOUR INGENUITY.
BUT YOU MUST DO MORE.
YOU MUST MAKE MORE.
SHOW ME YOUR POWER.
SHOW ME THE CHANGES THAT ONLY
YOU CAN BRING TO THIS WORLD.
YOU TWO HAVE
FRONT-ROW SEATS.
OBSERVE AS I DESTROY HUMANITY
AND ACCELERATE CIVILIZATION.
IT WILL BE SOON,
VERY SOON.
- WELL, WE'RE NOT DEAD.
- WELL, DAMN IT.
AND I REALLY LIKED
THIS DRESS.
- ( Marcosias laughs )
YOU'RE LUCKY TO BE ALIVE
AND YOU'RE WORRIED
ABOUT A DRESS?
OH.
ARGH!
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
DO YOU HAVE TO
THROW ME AROUND LIKE THAT?
YOU'RE ROUGHING UP MY BINDING,
DEAR MARGERY DAW.
- SORRY BUT I THINK A LADY
HAS A RIGHT TO PRIVACY
WHEN SHE'S DISROBING.
THE PURIFICATION FLAME,
PLEASE.
- YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
- ( sighs ) I'D LIKE A SUIT
THIS TIME.
THE ONE I BOUGHT IN MARSEILLES
WILL DO.
- ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YOU'RE... NAKED.
- ( punch lands )
- ( man yells )
- ( car horns honking )
- ( man stuttering )
IT'S A PLEASURE TO MEET YOU.
I'M THE COMMANDER
OF WRAITHS,
THE FLAME HAZE OF VALAC,
THE MARSHALL OF LIZARDS.
MY NAME IS
YURI CHVOJKA.
LET'S SEE,
WHAT ELSE CAN I TELL YOU?
UM, I'M 16--
WELL, AS LONG AS YOU COUNT
THE YEAR I'VE BEEN
A FLAME HAZE.
- Valac: YOU NITWIT,
WHY DO YOU BOTHER KEEPING TRACK
OF YOUR AGE ANYMORE?
- OH, SORRY ABOUT THAT,
VALAC.
- DON'T BE SO QUICK
TO APOLOGIZE.
- SORRY.
UH, IF YOU DON'T MIND ME
SAYING SO,
I'VE ALWAYS ADMIRED YOU,
CHANTER OF ELEGIES.
I HEAR YOU'VE KILLED
HUNDREDS OF DENIZENS
IN YOUR TIME
AS A FLAME HAZE.
- ALL RIGHT, KID, HOW LONG
ARE YOU PLANNING TO FOLLOW ME?
MY BUSINESS IS WITH THE SUMMONER
OF STAR RIVER,
NOT WITH A LITTLE TWERP
LIKE YOU.
- OH, I'M SORRY, MA'AM.
- IF YOU'RE SO SORRY,
GET OUT OF MY SIGHT ALREADY.
- BUT I COULD BE
OF SERVICE TO YOU.
SEE, I WORK
FOR EAST EDGE.
I MEAN, I'M WORKING
AT HIS OUTLAW.
I CAN TAKE YOU TO HIM.
- HUH?
- THE SUMMONER HIRED
A PIPSQUEAK LIKE YOU?
YOU'VE GOT TO BE KIDDING ME.
( laughs )
NO FUN BEING A NEW RECRUIT,
EH, VALAC?
YOU GET STUCK
WITH ALL THE GRUNT WORK.
- Valac: I MUST BE BAD OFF
IF I'M BEING RIDICULED
BY THE CLAWS AND FANGS
OF VIOLATION.
- YOU GOT THAT RIGHT.
( laughing )
- ( Margery's voice )
SUDDENLY I HAD THIS FEELING
THERE WAS SOMETHING OFF
ABOUT THE BOY.
YURI WAS DIFFERENT
FROM OTHER FLAME HAZE.
HE DIDN'T POSSESS THE SPIRIT
NEEDED FOR KILLING DENIZENS.
HE HAD NEITHER THE FINESSE
TO HIDE IT
NOR THE CALMNESS THAT COMES
AFTER ACHIEVING ENLIGHTENMENT.
- YOU KNOW, KID,
YOU'RE NOT LIKE
OTHER FLAME HAZE.
- YEAH?
YOU REALLY THINK SO?
- ( car horn honks )
- Man: HEY, I'M WALKING HERE.
- THE ONLY REASON
I EVEN WENT TO NEW YORK CITY
WAS BECAUSE I WAS ASKED TO
DELIVER A LETTER TO EAST EDGE.
AT THE TIME,
FLAME HAZE AROUND THE WORLD
WERE GATHERING IN EUROPE.
THEY WERE COMING TOGETHER
TO FIGHT AN ARMY OF CRIMSON
DENIZENS CALLED REVOLUTION.
THAT GATHERING
WAS THE SUBJECT MATTER
OF THE LETTER
I'D BROUGHT HIM.
- EVERYONE
UP AND LEFT, HUH?
I THOUGHT IT WAS STRANGE
I COULDN'T FEEL THE PRESENCE
OF A SINGLE FLAME HAZE.
IT MUST BE ROUGH AROUND HERE.
- Marcosias: ESPECIALLY SINCE
THE ONLY ONE WHO STAYED BEHIND
IS THAT YURI KID.
EVEN WITH THE PRESIDENT
OF LIZARDS WITH HIM,
HIS INEXPERIENCE
IS A RISK.
- MM, BUT A NECESSARY RISK.
OUR OPTIONS
ARE LIMITED HERE.
WE HAVE YOU,
AND THERE'S US--
THE FOUR GODS OF EARTH.
HOWEVER...
- WE ARE STUCK RIGHT HERE.
WE CANNOT LEAVE.
- YEAH, WE KNOW.
BUT IF THAT DENIZEN
WAS TO ATTACK THE CITY,
IT WOULD BE DISASTROUS.
THERE'S NOBODY HERE
TO FIGHT HIM OFF.
- DON'T YOU WORRY.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF HIM.
- East Edge: ABOUT THE BOY--
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- HE ISN'T UP TO THE JOB.
I DON'T SENSE ANY ANGER
OR HATRED TOWARD DENIZENS
WITHIN HIM.
AND THERE'S SOMETHING...
STRANGE ABOUT HIM.
- ( record hissing )
- I TOO HAVE NOTICED
THE BOY CARRIES AN ABERRATION
IN HIS HEART
THAT HE SHOULD NOT POSSESS.
- NO BATTLE,
NOT FOR HIM.
WE CANNOT.
TOO DANGEROUS.
- INTERESTING.
SO HE WASN'T ORDERED
TO ENTER MY SEAL.
HE DID IT
OF HIS OWN ACCORD.
- I HATE TO ASK,
BUT WOULD YOU DO ME A FAVOR?
- LET ME GUESS:
TRAIN THE NEW RECRUIT?
FINE, BUT TRAINING
ISN'T REALLY MY THING.
I'VE GOT
MY OWN PROBLEMS.
I'VE STILL GOT TO FACE OFF
WITH THOUSAND CHANGES.
JEEZ, THAT'S GONNA BE
TOUGH.
- YOU COULD JUST BLIND HIM
WITH YOUR NAKEDNESS
LIKE YOU DID WITH THAT
POOR LITTLE BOY. ( laughing )
- SHUT UP, STUPID MARCO.
- OW!
- ( Margery's voice ) I CAN FEEL
A CRIMSON DENIZEN'S PRESENCE.
- Marcosias: I'M THINKING
SONAR UNRESTRICTED SPELL.
JUST GO IN GUNS BLAZING.
- WE COULD DO THAT.
I'M WORRIED IT MIGHT LEAD
THOUSAND CHANGES
STRAIGHT TO US THOUGH,
AND I'M NOT READY TO FACE HIM.
BESIDES, I DON'T WANT
TO ENDANGER
OUR PRECIOUS
LITTLE TRAINEE.
- OBSERVE AS I DESTROY HUMANITY
AND ACCELERATE CIVILIZATION.
- HERE.
UM, SORRY, WOULD YOU PREFER
SOMETHING STRONGER?
ARE YOU WARM?
YOU'RE LOOKING
KIND OF FLUSH.
- THIS WILL BE FINE.
- Yuri: IT'S TRULY AN HONOR TO
ACCOMPANY YOU ON YOUR SEARCH.
THANKS FOR
INVITING ME ALONG.
- IT'S NOT LIKE I HAD A CHOICE.
EAST EDGE ASKED ME TO.
- IT'S BEEN HALF A CENTURY SINCE
YOU WERE LAST IN NEW YORK,
RIGHT?  HAS IT CHANGED MUCH
SINCE THEN?
- YEAH, I GUESS.
I HAVE NOTICED THERE'S NOT
AS MANY PIGS AND HORSES
RUNNING AROUND THE CITY
ANYMORE.
- PIGS, HUH?
THAT'S WEIRD.
- BACK THEN THE STREETS
WERE COVERED IN CRAP,
TRASH PILED UP
EVERYWHERE.
HUNTER'S POINT
WAS A DEN OF TOXIC GAS.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE
IT WAS THAT BAD.
DAMN HIM.
THIS CITY HAS HAD TO OVERCOME
SUCH HARDSHIPS,
EVEN TODAY AS IT STRUGGLES
TO REVIVE ITSELF
AFTER THE ECONOMIC
DEPRESSION.
WHY DID THAT CRIMSON DENIZEN
HAVE TO COME HERE?
AND HE WAS SPOUTING
ALL THAT NONSENSE
ABOUT ACCELERATING
CIVILIZATION?
THEY'RE THE ONES WHO ARE
HOLDING HUMANITY BACK
FROM REACHING
ITS FULL POTENTIAL.
THEY WOULD PROGRESS FASTER
IF IT WASN'T--
- Marcosias: CALM DOWN, KID.
DON'T GET BENT OUT OF SHAPE.
- OH.
UM, I'M SORRY, SIR.
- Valac: YOU SPEND TOO MUCH TIME
WORRYING ABOUT HUMANS.
YOUR MISSION AS A FLAME HAZE IS
TO MAINTAIN THE WORLD'S BALANCE,
NOT TO PROTECT HUMANITY.
- Yuri: BUT HUMANS ARE
PART OF THE WORLD TOO.
- Valac: REMEMBER, YOU'RE NOT
ONE OF THEM ANYMORE.
- Yuri: YEAH, I KNOW.
- AM I REALLY ALL THAT DIFFERENT
FROM OTHER FLAME HAZE?
- YES, YOU ARE.
I DON'T KNOW WHY
VALAC ENTERED A CONTRACT
WITH YOU.
- I CAN EXPLAIN.
- NO NEED.
- A YEAR AGO I BOARDED
AN IMMIGRANT SHIP
BOUND FOR AMERICA.
THE JOURNEY
WENT SMOOTHLY
UNTIL WE WERE ATTACKED
BY A DENIZEN.
- ( people screaming )
- Yuri: I LOST MY FATHER,
MY MOTHER.
THE DENIZEN, A KRAKEN,
CONSUMED HUNDREDS OF SOULS,
THEREBY ERASING THEM
FROM EXISTENCE.
IN THE MIDST OF ALL THAT
CARNAGE, VALAC FOUND ME
AND I BECAME
HER FLAME HAZE.
I WILL ALWAYS BE HAUNTED WITH
REGRET FOR MY ACTIONS THAT DAY.
- WHY IS THAT?
DO YOU REGRET YOUR CONTRACT?
- OH, NO,
THAT'S NOT WHAT I MEANT.
I'M VERY GRATEFUL
FOR WHAT VALAC DID.
IT'S JUST
I WAS SO SELFISH.
INSTEAD OF DOING SOMETHING
TO SAVE THE OTHERS,
I WAS ONLY WORRIED
WITH SAVING MYSELF.
BUT IT WON'T
HAPPEN AGAIN.
ONE DAY I WILL SAVE
SOMEBODY'S LIFE.
- ( sighs )
- HUH?
- VALAC.
- YES, I KNOW.
BUT WHAT WOULD YOU
HAVE HAD ME DO?
- Margery: GO BACK TO EAST EDGE.
- HUH?
- YOU'RE JUST NOT FIT
TO BE A FLAME HAZE.
- BUT, MISS DAW, WE STILL
HAVE TO FIND THE DENIZEN.
- HOW IS A ROOKIE LIKE YOU
GONNA HELP ME DO THAT?
THE DENIZEN ASKED
TO BE OBSERVED,
YET HE'S CLEARLY IN HIDING.
SO WHAT IS HIS GOAL?
I HAVE A THEORY BASED ON
THE SEARCHING WE'VE DONE.
BUT WHAT ABOUT YOU?
- WELL, I DON'T KNOW.
- OF COURSE NOT,
'CAUSE YOU'RE AN AMATEUR.
YOU'RE OF NO USE
TO ME.
- VALAC.
- IF YOU CAN'T ANSWER HER,
WE'VE NO CHOICE BUT TO LEAVE.
- WAIT, WHAT?
- THE SUN'S SETTING,
SO I'D BETTER BE GOING NOW.
BYE, YURI.
- SEE YOU, MARSHALL OF LIZARDS.
GIVE OUR APOLOGIES
TO EAST EDGE.
- NO.  WAIT!
( grunts )
- I'M WARNING YOU,
DON'T FOLLOW US.
- Annaberg: WHAT AN INCREDIBLE
BUILDING.
TO THINK, A STRUCTURE
THIS GRAND
WAS BUILT IN A MERE
405 DAYS.
REMINDS ME OF ANOTHER
OLD TOWER.
IT'S AN ACHIEVEMENT
WHICH RIVALS THE BABYLONIANS'.
- Margery: FLAME HAZE
ARE DRIVEN BY THEIR HATRED
AND DESIRE FOR REVENGE.
BUT NOT THAT BOY.
HE JUST DOESN'T HAVE IT
IN HIM.
- WHAT THE HELL
WAS VALAC THINKING,
ENTERING INTO
THAT CONTRACT?
- HE WANTS TO SAVE
SOMEONE'S LIFE?
YOU CAN'T PAIR FLAME HAZE
RAGE WITH ALTRUISM.
THAT IS A BAD
COMBINATION.
- Marcosias: THE POOR KID'S
JUST NOT CUT OUT FOR THE JOB.
- WELL, LET'S NOT WASTE OUR TIME
WORRYING ABOUT HIM.
THE DENIZEN DESERVES
OUR FULL ATTENTION.
- Annaberg: THIS BUILDING
WILL BE RECORDED
IN THE ANNALS OF HISTORY AS THE
PINNACLE OF HUMAN ACHIEVEMENT--
NOT ONLY THEIR CAPACITY
FOR COMPLEX CONSTRUCTION,
BUT UNDENIABLE PROOF
OF MANKIND'S INFINITE POWER.
WHAT BETTER PLACE
TO BEGIN MY WORK THAN HERE--
THE EMPIRE STATE BUILDING?
- CAST A SEAL!
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- Yuji:
MARGERY HAS FOUND AN ADMIRER
IN A YOUNG FLAME
HAZE NAMED YURI.
THE BOY HAS AN INFALLIBLE
SENSE OF JUSTICE.
HOWEVER, MARGERY KNOWS
THIS IS A DANGEROUS QUALITY
FOR A FLAME HAZE TO POSSESS,
BECAUSE IT RENDERS HIM
VULNERABLE.
BUT YURI WILL NOT BE
HELD BACK
FROM ALLOWING HIS FLAME
TO BLAZE.
NEXT TIME
ON "SHAKUGAN NO SHANA II,"
"THE MILESTONE OF SORROW."