- Alastor: LIFE IN MISAKI CITY
SEEMED TO RETURN TO NORMAL.
BUT SHANA AND THE OTHERS
REMAINED CAUTIOUS,
KNOWING BALL MASQUE
COULD ATTACK AT ANY MOMENT.
KAZUMI YOSHIDA'S WORLD
WAS TURNED UPSIDE DOWN
WHEN PHELES GAVE HER
THE TREASURE TOOL, GIRALDA.
AND BALL MASQUE
CAME ONE STEP CLOSER
TO EXECUTING
THEIR FORMIDABLE PLANS.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- EH?
- Sydonay:
THE END OF THE DOREL PARTY.
I NEVER THOUGHT
IT'D BE THAT EASY
TO CRUSH
ONE OF OUTLAW'S MAIN POSTS.
I EXPECTED
MORE OF A FIGHT FROM SOMEONE
LIKE DOREL KUBELIK.
IF WE CAN DEFEAT THE PIPER
OF SORROWFUL DREAMS,
THEN I HAVE NO DOUBT
WE CAN TAKE 'EM ALL DOWN.
- Ike: WHAT DID YOU WANT TO TALK
TO ME ABOUT, OGATA?
- WELL, PLEASE TELL ME
IF YOU THINK I'M JUST
BEING SILLY,
BUT DO YOU FEEL
LIKE EVERYBODY'S BEEN ACTING
A LITTLE STRANGE LATELY?
- I DIDN'T THINK
ANYONE ELSE NOTICED.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT'S UP.
I'M STARTING TO FEEL
LIKE I DON'T KNOW THEM ANYMORE.
IT'S LIKE
WE'RE ALL STRANGERS.
EXCEPT THAT'S NOT THE CASE
WITH YOU AND TANAKA.
- HUH?
- THE TWO OF YOU
HAVE GOTTEN CLOSER.
YOU'VE BEEN ATTACHED AT THE HIP
EVER SINCE THE FESTIVAL.
- YEAH.
( chuckles )
HEY, LOOK AT THE TIME.
THANKS FOR LISTENING
TO ME VENT.
I REALLY NEEDED THAT.
- YOU HEADED TO PRACTICE?
- YEP, WE'VE GOT
AN IMPORTANT SCRIMMAGE GAME
AGAINST AMOAE NEXT FRIDAY.
HAVE TO WORK EXTRA HARD
SINCE I'M THE ONLY FRESHMAN
ON THE TEAM.
I'VE GOTTA IMPRESS 'EM!
- YOU SHOULD INVITE HIM.
INVITE TANAKA.
YOU KNOW, TO COME
AND WATCH YOUR GAME.
- I WILL.
GOOD IDEA, IKE.
- SATO.
HEY, WHAT'S UP, MAN?
IS THERE SOMETHING WRONG?
- NUH-UH.
- THAT'S GOOD TO HEAR.
WELL, I GOTTA JET.
I'LL CATCH YA LATER.
- ( door opens )
- Wilhelmina: I'VE COMBED
THROUGH ALL THE REPORTS.
WE HAVEN'T RECEIVED
ANY NEW INTELLIGENCE
REGARDING THE SILVER.
- Tiamat: NOT ONE LEAD.
- WE HAVE YET TO RECEIVE
A SINGLE REPORT
CONTAINING
PERTINENT INFORMATION.
THIS KIND OF MISTAKE
IS UNLIKE THEM.
- AND WHO ARE THESE REPORTS
COMING FROM?
- Tiamat: OUTLAW.
- I WAS THOROUGH
IN MY DESCRIPTION
OF THE TYPE OF INTELLIGENCE
DESIRED,
BUT AS YET, WE HAVE RECEIVED
NOTHING PERTINENT.
NOTHING AT ALL.
- THEY ARE INCONSISTENT.
- Marcosias: YOU'D THINK
THEY WOULD'VE IMPROVED
OVER THE LAST CENTURY.
GUESS NOT.
- THEY HAVE IMPROVED.
I SUSPECT
THEY'RE HAVING PROBLEMS
WITHIN THE NETWORK.
- INTERESTING.
YOU HAVE ANYTHING TO ADD,
KEISAKU?
I KNOW YOU'RE
OUT THERE EAVESDROPPING.
LET'S HEAR
WHAT EITA HAD TO SAY.
- HE DIDN'T SAY MUCH.
I'M SORRY.
- HA!  SO HE'S STILL
UPSET WITH ME, IS HE?
OH, WELL, LET'S GIVE HIM
SOME TIME TO THINK.
HE'LL FIGURE OUT
WHAT HE WANTS TO DO EVENTUALLY.
- YOU'RE RIGHT.
SO, UH, MARGERY?
- YEAH?
- I, UM, I NEED YOU TO TELL ME
MORE ABOUT OUTLAW.
I MEAN... NEVER MIND.
DAMN IT.
- Marcosias:
THAT WAS A COLD-HEARTED STARE
YOU GAVE HIM.
DON'T YOU THINK
YOU'RE BEING TOO HARD
ON THE KID, MY DEAR MARGERY?
- THOSE BOYS
ARE JUST CONFUSED.
THEY DON'T KNOW WHICH PATH
THEY WANT TO TAKE.
I DON'T WANT THEM
MAKING A DECISION LIKE THAT
HAPHAZARDLY.
IT'LL AFFECT
THE REST OF THEIR LIVES.
CALL IT TOUGH LOVE.
- THIS TREASURE TOOL
ALLOWS YOU TO SUMMON ME.
BUT IN DOING SO,
IT WILL CONSUME
ALL OF YOUR POWER OF EXISTENCE.
- Kazumi: I KNOW MY FEELINGS
FOR SAKAI ARE REAL.
SO IF THIS
IS WHAT IT'S GOING TO TAKE
TO STAND BY
HIS SIDE FOREVER...
- Alastor: YUJI SAKAI,
AS OF THIS EVENING,
WE WILL BE ADVANCING
YOUR LEVEL OF TRAINING.
- I'M GONNA COME
AT YOU WITH 20 SWINGS.
YOU'LL HAVE TO DETERMINE
WHICH ONE IS COMING
AT FULL FORCE
AND THEN
SUCCESSFULLY BLOCK IT.
DO YOU HAVE ANY QUESTIONS?
- ONE'S NOT ENOUGH.
YOU SHOULD INCREASE
THE NUMBER OF FULL-FORCE SWINGS.
- BUT, YUJI...
- Alastor: THIS IS NOT THE TIME
TO BE COCKY, YOUNG MAN.
YOU'VE NOT YET MASTERED
WIELDING BLUTSAUGER.
DON'T GET AHEAD OF YOURSELF.
- NOW THAT BAL MASQUE
HAS IMPLANTED A TRANSMITTER
INSIDE OF ME,
I CAN'T RUN OR HIDE
FROM THEM ANYMORE.
BESIDES, IF THIS CITY
IS A MAELSTROM OF WARFARE
LIKE YOU SAID,
I'M IN DANGER.
I MAY NOT BE ABLE
TO PROTECT MYSELF.
BUT I'LL TRY.
I HAVE TO, ALASTOR.
- MMM.
IT MAKES SENSE
WHEN YOU PUT IT THAT WAY.
- OKAY, HERE WE GO.
HOPE YOU'RE READY FOR THIS.
EN GARDE.
( grunting )
- YEAH SO?
WHY'D YOU DRAG ME
ALL THE WAY UP HERE?
- SORRY.  IT'S JUST,
I HAVE A QUESTION FOR YOU.
- WELL, THEN YOU CAN ASK ME
BACK DOWN IN THE CLASSROOM.
- NO, THAT WON'T WORK.
SAKAI'S DOWN THERE.
AND I DON'T WANT HIM
OVERHEARING OUR CONVERSATION.
CAN YOU PLEASE TELL ME
MORE ABOUT OUTLAW?
- TANAKA.
- HEY, WHAT'S UP?
- YOU BRING YOUR LUNCH TODAY?
- UH, NO.
I FORGOT IT AT HOME AGAIN.
I'D ASK YOU TO JOIN ME,
BUT YOU ALWAYS BRING YOURS.
- ACTUALLY,
I FORGOT MINE TOO.
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT FORGET YOURS
SO I LEFT MINE AT HOME.
HEY, TANAKA?
BE HONEST WITH ME.
YOU'VE BEEN FORGETTING
YOUR LUNCH ON PURPOSE, RIGHT?
- NO.
WHY'D YOU ASK?
- I GET THE FEELING
YOU'RE TRYING
TO DISTANCE YOURSELF
FROM EVERYONE, EVEN SATO.
- TH-- THAT'S NOT THE CASE.
- THEN WHY'VE YOU BEEN ACTING
SO ALOOF LATELY?
EVEN WHEN IT'S JUST YOU
AND ME.
I WAS WONDERING,
WHAT'RE YOU UP TO NEXT FRIDAY?
TANAKA?
ARE YOU EVEN LISTENING TO ME?
- OF COURSE I AM.
FRIDAY SOUNDS GREAT.
I'LL TAKE YOU ANYWHERE
YOU WANNA GO, OKAY?
YOU JUST SAY THE WORD.
- FORGET IT.
- SOMETHING WRONG?
- I DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S GOTTEN INTO YOU.
YOU'RE ACTING
LIKE A DIFFERENT PERSON.
- WHAT'S OUTLAW?
- THEY'RE A NETWORK
THAT SUPPORTS FLAME HAZE.
MARGERY'S MENTIONED THEM
TO US BEFORE.
THEY HAVE POSTS
ALL OVER THE WORLD
THAT ARE CONSTANTLY
EXCHANGING INFORMATION.
I FOUND OUT IT
ISN'T JUST FLAME HAZE
WHO WORK THERE.
EVIDENTLY THEY HIRE
PLENTY OF REGULAR PEOPLE TOO.
- WHAT DOES THIS HAVE TO DO
WITH ME?
- DON'T YOU GET IT, DUDE?
I FINALLY FIGURED OUT
A WAY FOR US TO HELP.
WE MAY NOT BE ABLE
TO FIGHT DENIZENS,
BUT AT LEAST
WE CAN DO SOMETHING USEFUL.
COME ON, MAN.
- I'M GLAD YOU FOUND THE PATH
YOU WANT TO TAKE IN LIFE.
BUT IT'S NOT FOR ME.
- ARE YOU GONNA MOPE AROUND
LIKE THIS FOREVER?
JEEZ, I THOUGHT
WE WERE IN THIS TOGETHER
AND NOW YOU'RE
JUST GONNA LEAVE ME BEHIND?
- HEADS UP!
- Girls: READY!
- YOU'RE ACTING
LIKE A DIFFERENT PERSON.
MAYBE I WAS
A LITTLE TOO HARD ON HIM.
- Girl: OGATA!
- ( grunts )
- KEEP YOUR EYE ON THE BALL.
YOU BETTER NOT
SPACE OUT TOMORROW.
- I WON'T, SORRY!
- Wilhelmina: IRRELEVANT.
IRRELEVANT.
AH.  THIS ONE CONTAINS
PERTINENT INFORMATION.
HOWEVER,
THESE TWO DO NOT.
I AM SURPRISED
BY THE LACKLUSTER REPORTS
SENT FROM OUTLAW RECENTLY.
IT'S AS IF
THEY'VE BEEN THROWN TOGETHER
WITHOUT ANY THOUGHT.
- Tiamat: COMPLETELY GENERIC.
- WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOU STILL HAVEN'T FOUND
A SHRED OF USEFUL INFORMATION
ON THE SPELL SEALED
WITHIN THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD?
- NO.
- IF IT WAS ABLE
TO AFFECT BOTH JOHAN
AND THE KEEPER,
THEN IT MUST BE
A POWERFUL SPELL.
- IT IS NOT THE SPELL
THAT SHOULD BE WORRYING YOU.
YOU SHOULD BE MORE CONCERNED
WITH THE POSSIBILITY
OF COMING FACE TO FACE
WITH THE SPELL'S CASTER, SABRAC.
- SABRAC.
HE'S AN ASSASSIN
IN THE CRIMSON WORLD, RIGHT?
- WE KNOW HE HAS AN ATTACHMENT
TO THE TREASURE TOOL.
I WOULD SAY AN EVENTUAL MEETING
WITH HIM IS INEVITABLE.
WE'VE YET TO RECEIVE NEWS
OF ANY SIGHTINGS OF HIM
IN MISAKI CITY.
THIS LEADS ME TO BELIEVE
HE'S HIDING SOMEWHERE,
PLOTTING HIS ATTACK.
- IS HE REALLY THAT DANGEROUS?
- HE IS INDEED.
HE'S THE DESTRUCTIVE BLADE,
ONE OF THE CRIMSON WORLD'S
STRONGEST LORDS.
HE'S NOT CONNECTED
TO ANY ORGANIZATION,
BUT IS HIRED BY THEM
AS AN ASSASSIN.
- Tiamat: OUR NEMESIS.
- Wilhelmina: AT ONE POINT,
I ALMOST FELL VICTIM TO HIM.
- WHAT, ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- IF PHELES AND JOHAN
HADN'T SHOWN UP WHEN THEY DID,
I'D BE...
- SO THAT'S WHY YOU AND PHELES
BECAME SUCH GOOD FRIENDS.
- BEFORE THAT FATEFUL DAY,
WE HAD TRAVELED TOGETHER
FOR YEARS,
ALWAYS PROTECTING EACH OTHER.
WHENEVER
SABRAC WOULD ATTACK US,
I WOULD DISTRACT HIM
WITH MY RIBBONS
AND THEN
PHELES WOULD BLOW HIM AWAY.
BUT ONE DAY,
SABRAC ATTACKED OUR CAMP
WHILE I WAS AWAY
AND MORTALLY WOUNDED JOHAN.
PHELES SAVED HIM
THE ONLY WAY SHE KNEW HOW.
- Yuji: SABRAC,
THE DESTRUCTIVE BLADE,
A DENIZEN POWERFUL ENOUGH
TO ALMOST KILL WILHELMINA,
IS COMING FOR ME.
- WHAT IS THIS?
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
- DID YOU FIND NEW INFORMATION?
- WHAT, WILHELMINA?
- MARGERY,
DO YOU HAVE A MOMENT?
IT'S ABOUT OUTLAW.
I'D LIKE TO GO
WORK WITH THEM.
I KNOW I'M NOT STRONG ENOUGH
TO FIGHT DENIZENS,
SO I CAN'T BE
ON THE FRONT LINES.
BUT AT LEAST I'D BE ABLE
TO HELP.
- THE SPECIALIST OF EVERYTHING
WAS JUST HERE WITH NEWS.
IT SEEMS
ONE OF OUTLAW'S MAIN POSTS
WAS ATTACKED BY DENIZENS.
- Marcosias:
IT WAS IN SWITZERLAND,
RUN BY A GUY
NAMED DOREL KUBELIK.
EVERYONE WHO WORKED THERE
WAS BRUTALLY MURDERED,
INCLUDING DOREL HIMSELF.
THEY KILLED FLAME HAZE
AND HUMANS.
- NO WAY.
- APPARENTLY OTHERS HAVE
BEEN ATTACKED AS WELL.
DAMAGE REPORTS
AND S.O.S. CALLS
HAVE BEEN COMING IN
FROM OUTLAW POSTS
ALL OVER THE WORLD.
- EXPLAINS WHY THE REPORTS
HAVE BEEN SUCH A MESS.
YEAH, SO I'M GUESSING
THAT WASN'T EXACTLY
WHAT YOU WANTED TO HEAR,
WAS IT?
YOU STILL WANT TO WORK
FOR OUTLAW NOW?
- IKE, WHAT'S UP?
- YOU'RE GOING, AREN'T YOU?
- HUH?
- OGATA'S GAME
THIS AFTERNOON.
SHE SAID
SHE WAS GONNA ASK YOU.
- HA!
- ( whistle blows )
- TANAKA.
- ( grunts )
- ( whistle blows )
- YEAH!
( laughs )
- ( whistle blows )
- Girl: YOU GOT THIS, OGATA!
( whistle blows )
- GOT IT!
- ( stick strikes )
- ( grunting )
- Alastor:
I KNEW YOU WEREN'T READY.
I NEVER SHOULD HAVE AGREED
TO ADVANCE YOUR TRAINING LEVEL.
- BUT I CAN FEEL IT.
I CAN FEEL HER INTENT TO KILL.
I'VE ALMOST GOT IT.
- ALL RIGHT, YUJI.
THEN LET'S GO AGAIN.
- ALL OF HER SWINGS ARE STRONG,
BUT ONE HAS MORE POWER
OF EXISTENCE BEHIND IT.
SHE CONCENTRATES THAT POWER,
MAKING HER SWING DEADLIER.
THIS IS IT!
- DON'T LET YOUR GUARD DOWN.
- NO JOKE.
LESSON LEARNED.
- Alastor:
MMM.  I MUST SAY I'M IMPRESSED.
I DIDN'T THINK
YOU'D BE ABLE TO DIFFERENTIATE
BETWEEN HER SWINGS.
WELL DONE.  I THINK
WE SHOULD CALL IT A NIGHT.
- NOT YET.
I'M JUST NOW STARTING
TO GET THE HANG OF IT.
KEEP GOING, PLEASE.
- YUJI.
- Sato:
THIS BETTER BE GOOD, MAN.
IT'S PRETTY LATE.
- I WANTED TO APOLOGIZE.
- YOU SERIOUSLY
DID NOT GET ME OUT OF BED
JUST FOR THIS, DID YOU?
DAMN.
CHILLY OUT HERE.
COME ON,
LET'S GO BACK TO MY PLACE
AND TALK IT OUT THERE.
- I'M NOT GOING TO YOUR HOUSE.
'CAUSE I DON'T
WANT TO SEE MARGERY.
- SHE'S WORRIED ABOUT YOU.
SHE REALLY IS.
SHE DOESN'T ACT LIKE IT,
BUT SHE DOES CARE.
- YOU BELIEVE WHAT YOU WANT.
BUT I DON'T EVER
WANT TO SEE HER AGAIN.
I WENT TO OGATA'S
VOLLEYBALL GAME TODAY.
SHE WAS KICKING ASS,
FOR REAL.
WHILE I WAS WATCHING
HER ON THE COURT,
I COULDN'T HELP BUT THINK
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED TO HER
THAT DAY.
I'M SCARRED FOR LIFE
'CAUSE OF IT.
IN THE BEGINNING,
I WAS INTO THE IDEA
OF FOLLOWING MARGERY.
BUT AFTER WHAT SHE DID,
I JUST CAN'T.
- I UNDERSTAND.
I'M GLAD YOU FOUND THE PATH
THAT YOU WANT TO TAKE IN LIFE.
- THANKS, SATO.
( sobbing )
- AW, CUT IT OUT.
BE A MAN, WOULD YA?
IN ALL HONESTY, I'VE BEEN
HAVING SECOND THOUGHTS MYSELF.
EVIDENTLY,
WORKING AT OUTLAW
IS A LOT MORE DANGEROUS
THAN I THOUGHT IT'D BE.
BUT, HEY,
I'VE ALREADY MADE MY DECISION.
I'D FEEL
LIKE A COMPLETE LOSER
IF I DIDN'T
FOLLOW THROUGH WITH IT.
YOU KNOW?
- HERE, TAKE THIS.
GIVE IT BACK TO MARGERY.
YOU CAN TELL HER
SHE WAS RIGHT.
I AM THE TWERP
SHE THOUGHT I WAS.
I'M JUST A GOOD FOR NOTHING,
WHINY COWARD.
- NO, BUT YOU'RE BEING STUPID.
TODAY'S THE DAY
YOU STOPPED BEING A COWARD.
- ( theme music playing )
- Yuji:
NOW THAT THE AUTUMN FESTIVAL
IS OVER
AND LIFE'S RETURNED TO NORMAL,
I'M DEVOTING
ALL OF MY FREE TIME
TO TRAINING WITH BLUTSAUGER.
SHANA'S WORRIED
THAT I MIGHT BE OVERDOING IT,
BUT I DON'T HAVE A CHOICE.
MY TRAINING WILL BE TESTED
WHEN A DENIZEN NAMED ZAROVEE
COMES TO MISAKI CITY.
NEXT TIME
ON "SHAKUGAN NO SHANA SECOND,"
"COMPLICATED YUJI."