- Alastor: SHANA AND YOSHIDA
ATTEMPTED TO FIND COMMON GROUND
WITH PHELES.
BUT WHEN THE REAL PHELES
SHOWED UP,
THEY REALIZED
THEIR EFFORTS WERE IN VAIN.
SHE CALLED TO HER LOVER JOHAN
AND ASKED HIM TO COME TO HER.
HOWEVER, WHEN SHE DID,
A HAND CLAD IN SILVER ARMOR
REACHED OUT FROM WITHIN YUJI
AND IMPALED HER.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
- JO-- JOHAN.
- THERE'S AN ARM
COMING OUT OF ME.
WHAT THE HELL?
- ( coughing )
YOU, TELL ME,
WHO ARE YOU?!
I'M GETTING WEAK.
- IT'S DRAINING
HER POWER OF EXISTENCE.
- JOHAN.
- NO!
GET AWAY FROM ME!
- I-- I CAN'T,
NOT WHEN YOU'RE RIGHT HERE.
( screaming )
- ( growls )
- WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- Marcosias: A POT OF BEER!
- Margery:
YOU'D BETTER STAY STILL
IF YOU DON'T WANNA DIE!
- Marcosias: NO NEED TO FREAK
OUT, PRINCESS.
WE'RE NOT ATTACKING
YOUR BOYFRIEND.
I'VE BEEN SEARCHING FOR HIM
FOR SO MANY YEARS.
FINALLY, THIS IS THE MOMENT
I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR.
- Marcosias:
THIS IS IT, MARGERY DAW!
SHOW HIM WHAT YOU GOT,
MY BELOVED HELL RAISER!
- DAMN STRAIGHT I WILL.
"WHERE IS YOUR MONEY?"
- I'VE FORGOT!
- AHHHH!
( screaming )
- PLEASE, PHELES,
TRY TO CALM DOWN.
- LET ME GO.
JOHAN!
- LISTEN TO ME!
- Taimat: SHE'S HYSTERICAL.
- ( weeping )
- PLEASE, I AM BEGGING YOU.
- JOHAN! ( weeping )
- Kazumi: SAKAI.
- ( panting )
NO, NOT AGAIN.
- ( grunting )
- YUJI!
- AHHHH!
- ( machinery humming )
- Fecor:
THE HEAD HAS DISAPPEARED.
AND THE LEFT ARM.
- IT WOULD SEEM WE'RE IN A BIT
OF A PICKLE, FECOR.
HE SHOULDN'T BE ABLE
TO TELEPORT, BUT LO AND BEHOLD!
- HOW DID THIS HAPPEN?
- WELL, I COULDN'T TELL YOU,
BUT THE TAIMEI SHIHEN
MIGHT HAVE SOMETHING
TO DO WITH IT.
- YOU THINK?
I THOUGHT WE WERE THE ONLY ONES
WHO COULD ACTIVATE IT.
- WE ARE.
AT LEAST, IN THEORY.
THERE IS
ONE OTHER POSSIBILITY.
- THE CREATOR
OF THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD
MUST BE IN CLOSE PROXIMITY.
- IS THAT THE CASE,
PROFESSOR?
- AHH!  THAT IS
A VERY DISTINCT POSSIBILITY.
- THE CAPRICE OF BEAUTY?
BUT THAT'S A PROBLEM.
AREN'T ANY OF YOU WORRIED
THEY MIGHT FIND OUT
ABOUT OUR PLANS?
- NO, THE ARTIFICIAL VESSEL
HAS SERVED ITS PURPOSE.
OUR CHARADE HAS GONE ON
LONG ENOUGH.
- ( screaming )
- Margery: I'VE GOT HIM!
- Marcosias: ATTA GIRL!
- YUJI!
- Margery: HE'S SO STRONG.
BETTER MOVE FAST.
LISTEN UP, KID!
I KNOW YOU'RE SCARED,
BUT I NEED YOUR HELP.
GRAB AS MANY OF THE SPELLS
AS YOU CAN
AND COMBINE THEM TOGETHER.
- ( grunting )
- THIS IS IT.
AFTER ALL THIS TIME,
I'LL FINALLY GET MY REVENGE.
- KONOE?
- WHAT THE--
THEY SHOULD BE FROZEN.
- GREAT.
WHAT'S SHE UP TO?
- KONOE, WHAT THE--
( grunts )
- Sato:
WHAT THE HELL'S HAPPENING?
- NO.  KONOE.
YOU CAN'T BE--
- I ORDER YOU
TO WITHDRAW.
- AHHH AHH AHHH!
- RESEAL THE TREASURE TOOL.
- AHHHH!
- ( growling )
- MAGNESIA!
- Alastor: THAT'S FECOR'S
UNRESTRICTED SPELL!
IT'S DANGEROUS
TO BE OUT IN THIS STORM!
YOU NEED TO TAKE COVER!
- YUJI.
- WE HAVE TO FIND SHELTER.
- Alastor: FECOR,
THE TEMPESTUOUS CLAW.
- AND THE SUPREME THRONE,
HECATE!
- Margery: I NEVER IMAGINED
THOSE TWO WOULD SHOW UP.
I'VE GOT A BAD FEELING
ABOUT THIS.
- Marcosias:
YEAH, YOU AND ME BOTH.
- YUJI!
- Alastor: SHANA, WAIT!
- I BEG OF YOU, PRIESTESS,
YOU MUST CAPTURE HIM.
- IT'LL BE MY PLEASURE.
- AHHHHH!
- PLEASE, HECATE.
WHAT--
WHAT IS THIS ALL ABOUT?
- AHHHH!
- Alastor: MAGNESIA
CREATES A PARTICLE STORM.
IT FORMS A NEARLY
IMPENETRABLE DEFENSIVE SHIELD.
- AHH!
- YOUR WORK IS DONE,
MY VESSEL.
OPEN YOURSELF,
RETURN TO ME.
- KONOE, NO.
- WHERE'D SHE GO?
- HOW DID SHE JUST DISAPPEAR?
THIS HAS GONE
FROM BAD TO WORSE!
- YOU RECOVERED THE FRAGMENT
OF YOUR CONSCIOUSNESS.
PLUS WE WERE ABLE
TO PREVENT THE SILVER
FROM MATERIALIZING
AND RESEAL
THE MIDNIGHT LOST CHILD.
WHAT'S NEXT?
- WE DESTROY ITS MYSTES.
- OVER MY DEAD BODY!
- ( roaring )
- YUJI!
- ASTER!
- AH!
AHHHH!
- ( heartbeat )
- ( grunting )
- ASTER.
- AT LAST, I'M FREE!
- HUH?
- ( all gasping )
- PHELES, MY LOVE.
- OH, JOHAN!
- SORRY I KEPT YOU WAITING.
- IT'S FINE.
YOU'RE HERE NOW.
- YOU HAVE NO IDEA
HOW MUCH I'VE MISSED YOU.
- I'VE MISSED YOU MORE.
- IMPOSSIBLE.
- IT'S TRUE.
- NO WAY.
- DAMN IT!
- ASTER.
- WHAT HAVE I
EVER DONE TO THEM?
ALL I WANT
IS TO BE WITH MY LOVE.
- YOU'RE FREE NOW.
LET'S GO.
- JOHAN.
- Johan: I'M SORRY.
- YUJI.  YUJI.
- Margery: WHERE'S SHE GOING?
- Marcosias: YOU GOT ME.
I CAN'T KEEP UP
WITH THESE YOUNGSTERS.
- NO.  JOHAN!
- STOP IT!  STOP IT!
YUJI'S GONNA DISAPPEAR!
AHH!
- WHAT SHALL WE DO?
- WE'LL TAKE OUR LEAVE.
- WHAT?
ARE YOU SURE, PRIESTESS?
- WE HAVE ACCOMPLISHED
EVERYTHING WE SET OUT TO DO.
THERE'S NO NEED
TO TAKE THIS ANY FURTHER.
- RIGHT.
THE POOR KID.
- Alastor: SHANA.  SHANA!
- ( gasps )
- YUJI!
- EASY.
YOU'RE HURTING ME, SHANA.
- YUJI.
YUJI!
- WHAT'S WRONG?
DON'T WORRY, I'M FINE.
SO PLEASE DON'T CRY, OKAY?
- Kazumi:
I WISH IT WAS ME UP THERE
HOLDING HIM.
- Sato: HEY, MAN.
YOU SURE
YOU'RE FEELIN' ALL RIGHT?
- Yuji: I'M COOL.
I'M STILL NOT TOO SURE
WHAT JUST HAPPENED TO ME.
BUT I'M GLAD
TO BE BACK TO MYSELF.
I GAVE PHELES A LOT OF POWER
OF EXISTENCE.
I'M PRETTY EXHAUSTED.
- I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
I TOUCHED MY BELOVED JOHAN.
- IT'S NOT GONNA HAPPEN AGAIN.
- NO, IT WON'T.
I KNOW THAT.
YOU SEE,
JOHAN ALREADY TOLD ME
THAT IT COULD
NEVER HAPPEN AGAIN.
ALSO HE ASKED ME
TO DO HIM A FAVOR.
I SHOULD BE GOING.
- Alastor: PHELES,
WHAT ARE YOU NOT TELLING US?
- I'M SORRY,
BUT I CAN'T SAY ANY MORE.
IT WOULD PUT US IN DANGER.
- ARE YOU CERTAIN?
- I AM.
YUJI, I'LL LEAVE YOU HERE
WITH THEM FOR NOW.
BUT I'LL BE BACK.
- Wilhelmina: PHELES,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
BEAR THIS ALONE.
I'LL HELP YOU.
- YOU'RE A GOOD FRIEND,
BUT YOU DON'T NEED
TO GET INVOLVED.
- I WANT TO HELP YOU.
- THANK YOU.
- HEY, WHERE'D THOSE LAZY BUMS
SATO AND SAKAI RUN OFF TO?
THOSE PUNKS.
- Yuji: I WONDER WHAT'S GOING
TO HAPPEN TO ME NOW.
- I'M GOING TO PROTECT YUJI
NO MATTER WHAT.
- SO MANY STRANGE THINGS
HAVE HAPPENED LATELY.
THINK THINGS'LL
CALM DOWN NOW?
- HMM.
NO, WE'VE ONLY JUST BEGUN.
- ( woman singing in Japanese )
Yuji:
AFTER THE AUTUMN FESTIVAL,
OUR SCHOOL LIFE
GRADUALLY RETURNS TO NORMAL.
IT'S KIND OF STRANGE
THAT NONE OF OUR CLASSMATES
REMEMBER FUMINA KONOE.
BUT SOON, THE MEMORIES
OF OUR LOST FRIEND
BEGIN TO HAUNT US.
KAZUMI REVEALS
THAT SHE RECEIVED
A TREASURE TOOL FROM PHELES,
ONE THAT COULD
CAUSE PROBLEMS.
NEXT TIME
ON "SHAKUGAN NO SHANA II,"
"EVERLASTING LOVE."