[KAMIJO] In the midst of
the Daihasei Festival,
Oriana Thomson continued her
flight across Academy City...
Stiyl and I gave chase,
but she eluded us,
instead moving to take
down Tsuchimikado.
She then injured Himegami,
whose only crime
was wearing the wrong necklace.
Damn it...! Oriana, I swear!
You will pay for this!
♪ [Opening Song] ♪
Ugh, great!
[phone beeps]
[phone rings]
It's Kamijo... I'm sorry.
Looks like I lost Oriana.
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Where'd you lose her...?
Any clue where she was headed?
The bus she got on appears to
circle all around
School District 7...
but where would she get off?
Wait a sec.
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
What is it, Kami?
[KAMIJO] I... I was
just wondering why
she was walking around town.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Well...
The fact we were chasing her
might have something
to do with--
No, before we
were onto her.
If there's no deal for
the Croce di Pietro,
it's not like she's
here to meet anybody.
So why would she stroll
around the city, then...?
All that's gonna do
is increase her risk.
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
I see what you mean.
There must be a reason she's
been acting alone all this time.
[KAMIJO] And that is...?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] This is just a
guess. I don't know for sure...
but she may have been
searching the city
for the conditions they need
to use the Croce di Pietro.
Conditions? They can only use
it under certain circumstances?
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Stiyl would know more.
I asked him to
check into it for us.
Oh yeah, that's right...
I almost forgot about the e-mail
he sent me from Orsola...
I'll forward it to you now.
[phone beeping]
[dial tone]
Yeah, I was able
to read it...
It appears to be a record
regarding the cleaning of
the vault where the Croce
di Pietro was being held.
[KAMIJO] All right...
so what did it say?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] When the cross
was first stored there,
they were almost
neurotically concerned
about it being touched
by any natural light.
They did not want
that to happen.
[KAMIJO] Light?
They must've been
trying to keep it
from activating inadvertently.
[KAMIJO] Which would mean it
activates when the sun hits it?
If that were the case,
then wouldn't Oriana's
job be done already?
Not to mention...
the record says that cleaning
should be done
during the daytime.
So then, sunlight has
nothing to do with it.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Nope.
However... the Cross's
caretakers apparently
had some odd habits...
While they were on duty
they demonstrated a
rather strong interest
in horoscopes and astrology.
Astrology...? They made
sure to do all their cleaning
during the daylight hours...
because it was the night
sky they were wary of...
Or, more specifically,
the stars.
You got it, Kami.
By incorporating
the constellations
into magical arrays,
they would be able to yield
an enormous amount of power.
♪
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
If the Croce di Pietro acts
as an antenna designed to draw
in light from the night sky,
it follows that Oriana is
probably out searching the area
for the optimum spot
in which to set it up.
However... biblical
records tell us
Peter died on June 29th.
Besides which, our current
longitude and latitude
isn't the same as
the Vatican's...
unless they can find some
way around those issues,
I just don't see how they
can use the constellations.
Well... we can't
spend any more time
thinking about it now...
At this point, we should
just get moving...
If we assume they are
using the night sky...
can you guess what
our deadline is, Kami?
Sundown, right...?
Okay, then. What is it
you want me to do?
[INDEX] Toma!
Why are you up here?
Isn't there an event
you need to get to?
Index...?! What are
you doing here?
It looks like Kaori
Kanzaki won't be
making an appearance, after all.
[ORIANA] Lidvia...
[LIDVIA] I already know
what you're going to ask.
The girl you engaged
was a civilian,
not a member of Necessarius.
Her name is Aisa Himegami...
She does possess an extremely
significant power...
but she cannot be
considered a magician.
That Celtic cross she wore
was nothing more than
an accessory to keep
her power hidden...
She is not the
least bit aggressive.
[ORIANA] That's horrible...
[LIDVIA] Yes, it's
horrible indeed...
We struck out at an
innocent bystander
who had nothing to do
with this operation...
That's two times now.
These are sinners who
may stray and do wrong,
but who are ultimately
deserving of salvation...
It is our duty to protect them.
We must be careful not to
make any more mistakes...
We act for their sake now...
we must succeed.
We must use the Croce
di Pietro to bring
Academy City under our control.
I am starting to doubt whether
our plan is truly the best one.
[ORIANA] If we have sole
dominion over Academy City...
will everybody's problems
really be solved?
[INDEX] You still
haven't answered me.
Why aren't you with everyone
else in your class?
You haven't competed in one
event all afternoon, have you?
Why, Toma?
Oh... I... I've
been helping out
with the steering committee.
You mean you didn't know...?
I sent a text to
the guys in my class.
They could've told you.
A text?
That's weird. Maybe it
didn't go through...
I have noticed that cell service
has been a bit spotty lately...
[KAMIJO] Oh, well,
in any case...
why don't you go on back
to where the others are?
Why should I go back...?
The event program says that
group gymnastics is up next...
Are you going to be there?
Yes, I will... I just
need to finish up here...
I'll try to be
really quick.
I'll be there...
Will you be waiting for
me in the stands...?
Can you promise me that?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Sorry.
I know this is hard.
Let's just get this done...
The sooner the better
for all of us.
[KAMIJO] So many people!
This isn't going to be easy.
[LAST ORDER] "Hey, wait for me!"
"Please!" says Misaka Misaka,
as she runs to catch up.
"What's the big deal? Misaka was
only looking at the souvenirs,"
says Misaka Misaka, not
understanding what the hurry is.
Is that Misaka?
[phone rings]
Hello? Stiyl...?
How'd it go?
I've done everything I
can for your lady friend.
[KAMIJO] How is she?
I'll be happy if
I never have to use
that particular spell again...
We did our best to keep
her from going into shock,
for the time being.
It's all up to the doctor
at this point, though.
Thanks for that.
[STIYL] Watch it... I don't want
you getting sappy with me...
It's not like this makes
us friends or anyth--
[KOMOE] You were incredible...!
I don't think I can
ever thank you enough!
If you hadn't been here,
Himegami probably would have--
She probably would have died!
[KOMOE sobs]
Stop that...
Nothing's certain yet.
For all I know,
she could still die.
[KOMOE] Even so, I...
I want to thank you!
Sounds like you're a
little busy right now.
I'll catch you later.
[STIYL] You need to
call Tsuchimikado!
It sounds like
he's onto something.
I'm headed that way, too,
once I can get rid
of this crazy woman.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] It looks like my
initial assumption was right.
But something's still off...
So what are we supposed to make
of all these discrepancies?
[phone rings]
[KOMOE] Hi! Are you
there, Fukiyose?
How are you feeling?
Are you on the mend yet?
I'm doing fine,
thanks for asking...
Never mind me. How's the
Daihasei Festival going?
Any problems?
[KOMOE] Oh... well... Himegami
has been seriously injured.
[gasps] Did someone
play too rough?
I'll punch 'em in the face!
Actually, she was
attacked by somebody
and she needed to be
taken to the hospital.
Who would attack Himegami?
I'm just glad Kamijo and
his priest friend showed up.
I hate to think what
the outcome could have been
if they hadn't
arrived when they did!
[gasps] Hey...! There goes
the priest right now!
M-Mr. Priest, sir!
Uh--Wait, a priest...?
That's weird.
[FUKIYOSE] What is going on...?
This city is turning
into a madhouse.
[KAMIJO] Okay...
So it's like you thought...
The constellations hold the
key to activating the Cross.
Seems that way...
but when they used
the Croce di Pietro before
it was during the summer...
I doubt they'd be
able to substitute
with the autumn
constellations.
There's something
else going on here...
Something we haven't
figured out yet.
A trick of some kind.
I get that...
but we're running out of
time for brainstorming.
[phone rings]
The English Puritan Church?
[ORSOLA] Hello, uh...
Good afternoon...
Have I reached the cell
phone of Mr. Stiyl Magnus?
[BOTH] Wrong number!
[ORSOLA] Oh, I'm terribly sorry.
Wait... I know that
voice. Orsola?
[ORSOLA] Oh, my,
I know your voice, too!
I can't tell you how grateful
I am for all your help...!
I'm feeling right at home here,
and it's all thanks to you
and your kind friends.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Hey... Could we
skip all the pleasantries
and just get straight to
what you've learned, please?
Oh...! Yes. I learned about
this restaurant the other day.
I haven't gotten to try it yet,
but Kanzaki says it's delicious.
[KAMIJO] He means what
have you learned about
what Oriana intends to do?!
Right... I have learned
more about the conditions
necessary for the Church to put
the Croce di Pietro into play.
It is said to be some sort
of large-scale antenna
for harnessing the power
of the constellations.
Hate to tell you...
but we actually
knew that already.
[ORSOLA] Oh...?
I didn't realize.
If you're aware of what the
Cross is and how it functions,
then you more than likely
already know that it can be
activated anywhere in the world,
regardless of what
season it may be.
When Sherry and I
figured that out,
I really thought we
were onto something.
But I guess not, huh?
[KAMIJO] Whoa, hold on...!
What're you talking about?
[ORSOLA] In order to use
the Croce di Pietro...
the practitioners must
be suitably familiar
with the area in which
it will be employed...
They must select
the most fitting
of eighty-eight constellations
for that vicinity
before the conditions to
activate the Cross can be met.
So, that would mean...
Yes... There are
various restrictions,
practically speaking...
but they're not that limiting.
The Cross is very
vulnerable, indeed...
The Roman Orthodox
Church can harness
its power from
anywhere in the world.
We get what
you're saying...
As far as the location
of his martyrdom,
Peter's willing to
allow some latitude.
Okay, then... say
they've chosen a location,
what about the day?
[ORSOLA] The day that
Saint Peter was put to death
was on June 29th.
And it just so happens...
that was the exact date
the Croce di Pietro
was used at the Vatican.
So you're telling us
they intentionally took it
on that date?
They were prepared
to die for it.
Not an unlikely tale
when you think about it.
So, Orsola, given all this,
have you narrowed down
where they would
be using it...?
Do you know what location
they're most likely
to choose in this area...
today, September 19th?
[ORSOLA] Yes.
But of course I have
that information for you!
[MISUZU] Wow...!
Hold on a sec. Look at this!
A quasi-five-dimensional
kaleidoscope!
Man... this stuff
is fascinating.
Those are gimmicky buys for
tourists to ooh and ah over.
You want to pick something
more memorable for a souvenir.
[MISUZU] Aww...! Are you getting
a little "girly" on me?
Hey...! Why don't
you just be quiet!
[MIKOTO] Uh oh... I'd know the
feel of that gaze anywhere.
[KUROKO] Ahem.
Excuse me, Sissy...
but is this nice lady
a relative of yours?
[KUROKO] Wow...!
So powerful!
Like Sissy! But her... "aura"
is so much more substantial!
Ooh... I'm so lucky...
I came to the underground mall
hoping to do some shopping,
but I never expected two
for the price of one!
Easy... You're scaring
me a little.
When I called you
"girly," I didn't know
I was describing
your preferences.
[MIKOTO] Huh?
This is my roommate!
Hey...! Get a grip, Kuroko!
Time to come back to
reality! I'm serious!
[MIKOTO] Snap out
of it, do you hear me?
Let's wake up now and
come back from dreamland!
Oh... that boy again.
So... Oriana was
wandering around the city
to find a location
that would provide them
with the necessary viewpoint?
Yeah. Everywhere
we've been up to now
has had buildings or roadside
trees blocking out the sky...
which leaves us with
one possibility.
I'm sure this is
where she's going.
[KAMIJO] The airport
in School District 23?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] It all fits.
There's nothing in the way
that would obscure the sky.
[STIYL] Sorry I took so long.
I couldn't shake her...
Seriously. What is
with that lady...?
I used one repel
spell after another,
but every time I left
the affected area,
she would show up again.
Focus. We need a plan...
School District 23
is known for having
incredibly tight security.
How are we even going to get in?
Hm. That shouldn't
be a problem...
I've got a little something
I like to call the
"just this once" privilege that
should help us get in the door.
What does that mean?
Heh, ha!
This is strange.
It's about time for
final preparations.
[LIDVIA] Isn't there a while
before the appointed hour?
There has been a change
with the security situation.
If I had to guess, I'd say
they know I'm nearby.
[LIDVIA] In that case, the
location of the belvedere...
Yes, you're probably right...
Even so... it seems to be
the most practical place.
[ORIANA] It will
also help us avoid
any additional
civilian casualties.
[LIDVIA] Very well, then.
[ORIANA] That means you
should get ready, too.
It's time to take control...
Academy City will be ours.
[ORIANA] This city has
been blind for so long...
Now it's our responsibility
to show them the light.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] I had them
alter the security status
of School District 23 a bit...
We'll take advantage
of that confusion.
We know the Cross will be
activated just after sundown...
Most likely between the
hours of six and seven.
It's ten minutes to the
District 23 station...
That means once we
get there, we'll only have
twenty-five minutes
before our time is up.
So we're all clear
about the risks...
You intend to face Oriana with
us, even in your condition?
Heh. I can't tell
you how much
I'd like to
get some rest...
But the district's
security isn't that lax.
Without me, I seriously
doubt that the two of you
would even be able to break in.
Have it your way.
[horn honks]
Once we set foot
inside this train,
there'll be no turning back.
[STIYL] Saving Academy City
may mean taking a life.
I'm prepared for
what comes, Kamijo...
...but are you?
Yeah... I'm prepared to do
what needs to be done...
[KAMIJO] One thing, though...
[STIYL] What?
No killing... As far
as I'm concerned,
there's always another
solution besides death.
[TOYA] Toma isn't with you?
[KOMOE] No... I'm sorry.
[SHINA] Sorry...?
Why do you say that?
[KOMOE] There are
things I can't say.
As his teacher, I feel like your
son's welfare is in my hands...
Yet I can't tell you where
he is or what he's doing.
May we at least ask
you one question?
Yes... please feel free.
Whatever Toma's up to
now, it was his decision
to get involved, right?
He wasn't dragged into
something against his will?
O-Oh... no... it was
his own choice.
Hmm...
Then, it must be
important to him...
If he thinks it matters
more than competing,
then I trust him.
[TOYA] I can't think of any
reason we should stop him...
Can you?
[SHINA] No.
[LIDVIA] We look to the
heavenly skies for aid.
That we might establish
peace in this land...
Thus, I now call
upon the blessing
of the Holy Twelve Apostles.
The security around here
is focused on the sky.
It's not like there
are many places
a person could hide, after all.
How do you think Oriana's
gonna get into the airport?
My guess is that
she's already in there.
Then we need a plan...
We don't exactly
have a lot of time.
Hey... I've got an idea.
We'll use that.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] We're close
to the public airport...
Which means the skies
around here are crowded
with both passenger planes
and experimental devices.
With all that traffic,
the monitoring craft
have to regularly alter
their patrol routes
to prevent mid-air collisions.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] If we can sneak
in under their blind spots,
we should be able
to make it through.
♪
No, hold on...!
Tsuchimikado!
What's wrong now?
[KAMIJO] Say something!
Are you okay...?
Tsuchimikado!
Keep going... I'll be fine.
Destroy the spell
she's got on that fence...
And go finish the job.
What about you?
You're hurt...!
Come on, Stiyl...
Can't you heal him
with your magic
or something?!
We don't have that
kind of time left.
Go on and do your thing!
♪
Ahhh!
In my hand I hold the fire.
Its form is that of a sword,
and its purpose is conviction!
[STIYL] Hurry!
[ORIANA] Hm.  I doesn't look
like you have a saint with you.
Poor things, facing me alone.
I almost feel sorry for you.
[STIYL] That's a
barrier spell...
Which means she's cut
off all communication.
Stiyl!
[ORIANA] You should be careful!
It's true you're not as pretty
as your blonde friend...
but given how you fight, your
looks may be your best asset.
Break apart!
Ah!
[ORIANA] You'll have to
do better than that.
I'm barely breaking
a sweat, here.
[KAMIJO] I will stop you,
here and now...
I won't allow you to
use the Croce di Pietro.
[KAMIJO] You've already messed
up the Daihasei Festival...
and now you intend to screw
with the entire city, too.
I swear, I'm not
gonna let that happen!
[ORIANA laughs]
What a nasty way of putting
it; screw with the city!
We're going to use the
Croce di Pietro to remove
the wall between
magic and science.
Doing that will allow
us to lead the people
of the world to true happiness.
[KAMIJO] Happiness, huh?
Sounds nice... Really...
I can almost understand
why you believe
that you've come here
to do a good thing...
but not quite.
[KAMIJO] See, you
just have one problem...
Whatever your intentions,
I won't let you use
the cross in this city...
Not when doing so means ruining
the Daihasei Festival.
[KAMIJO] So many people
treasure this event.
It's a symbol of our unity...
I don't care how noble
you want to pretend
this plan of yours is...
It's clearly the wrong
thing to do if it means
undermining something
so precious to us.
[ORIANA] Your argument is
all emotion and no logic...
Do you really think
that's going to sway me?
The needs of the many outweigh
the needs of the few...
A simple decision honestly.
You think so...? I'd
like to hear you say that
to the two innocent
girls you've hurt already.
I think I've made myself clear.
That's all I have to say...
Except this:
You and your employers
may think you can
take control of this city...
but that's nothing more
than an illusion...
and I will destroy it!
♪ [Ending Song] ♪
[KAMIJO] I don't care how
lofty your goal is...
I don't care how
admirable your cause...
What you're doing is wrong,
and I will stop you...
I won't let it end like this!
Next time, "Croce di Pietro."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.