Agnese?
[ORSOLA] Stop! Can't we handle
this in a civilized manner?
What are you two doing on
the Queen of the Adriatic Sea?
Oh, well. We just happened to
end up on this ship by chance.
[ORSOLA] You said the
"Queen of the Adriatic Sea."
Is that the name
given to this fleet of
extraordinary ice ships?
No, it is called
the Queen's Fleet,
and the ship we're on is
one of the escort vessels.
It would seem that you're every
bit as clueless as you look.
Yeah, yeah.
So, do you feel like telling
us what you're doing here?
Searching for intruders,
as I was instructed to.
And what do you know?
I found some very
interesting intruders, indeed.
Hm. I might be able to
work this to my advantage.
We aren't involved with
whatever's going on here.
If you're going to
keep yammering like that,
I'll be forced
to sound the alarm.
I would advise staying
on my good side if you
and your friend want
to have any chance
of getting out of here alive.
[sighs]
[ORSOLA] For now, I don't see
any choice but to obey her.
Tell me, what's in this for you?
What possible incentive can
you have for letting us escape?
That's easy.
See, you're gonna do
something for me before you go.
[exhales]
♪ [Opening Song] ♪
[KAMIJO] The Queen's Fleet.
What exactly is it for anyway?
[AGNESE]
Well, it's a patrol fleet.
It was built to keep
an eye on the Adriatic Sea.
Strange that I've
never heard of it before,
given my time
with the Church.
On the contrary,
that isn't so strange.
Very few departments
even know it exists.
Patrol fleet?
The men on this boat
came out of nowhere
and attacked us.
If you ask me, it looks
as if they're doing
a lot more than "patrolling."
[AGNESE] Seems like you fell
in their laps while they were
out doing their normal rounds.
Hm?
[AGNESE] Or maybe
they were after you.
You have gotten in
the Church's way recently.
And as two foreigners from
two different countries,
you're not exactly
inconspicuous.
Well, enough chit chat.
Let's get to the point.
This is a labor camp
as well as a guard fleet.
It's where they send
people who have screwed up.
We're supposed to use
the sweat of our bodies
to make up for our failures.
[AGNESE] That's why
all of us are here.
Me and my squad, or rather, my
former squad of warrior sisters.
So... here's the
deal I'm proposing.
In return for
letting you get away,
I want you to find Sister
Lucia and Sister Angelene.
You must rescue them before
something awful happens.
[gasps] You mean
they're going to...?
They're in trouble.
They used a spell to confuse
the men standing guard,
then broke out of the lockup.
[AGNESE] They were going to
make the necessary preparations
and then come rescue the
remainder of the squad.
[BOTH whimper]
[KAMIJO] So, the two of
them were brought back
and now they're going
to be reprimanded?
They will take steps to keep
them from breaking out again.
And that most likely
means they'll be processed
so they can no longer
use their spell.
[KAMIJO] Processed?
It's horrible! They're
going to have their ability
to form thoughts
taken from them!
[ORSOLA] The very
structure of their brains
will be compromised.
I want you to get them away
from here before that happens.
That is the price
for my silence,
and if you reach them in time,
you can use their escape spell.
Do you think
that will work?
If the spell has already
been used before,
won't the guards
be expecting it?
[AGNESE] The Queen's Fleet
has a major operation ahead
of them right now.
They're pretty distracted.
I doubt they'll
worry about you.
Additionally, I'll
head to the flag ship
and do what I can
to create a diversion.
I expect you can
handle the rest of it.
It surprises me
that you're helping us.
I'm not helping
you, I'm using you.
You're a prisoner
here too, aren't you?
Why don't you come along?
[AGNESE] What the overseers
here are most worried about
is an uprising of the laborers.
That's where I come in.
I'm something of a
mental safeguard against
that possibility.
And that comes with perks.
[AGNESE] For example, I have
the authority to walk freely
aboard the ship. I am
also exempt from all labor.
It's surprisingly
comfortable living here.
Unfortunately,
Sisters Lucia and Angelene
don't have it as easy as I do.
They should've gotten away
when they had the chance.
It would have
been better that way.
If you do get out
of here in one piece,
you'll probably
want to stay away
from the Roman Orthodox Church.
I figured that one out.
But I don't know
how good our chances
of escape will be,
given how badly
outnumbered we are.
That's strange coming from
someone that singlehandedly
went up against so many
sisters the last time we met.
Well, thank you.
[AGNESE] Ah!
[ORSOLA] They altered
your habit, didn't they?
The designs that adorn
your dress were placed there
in order to create a kind
of magical restraining effect.
Ah--
[ORSOLA and KAMIJO] Shh!
[INDEX] If that's the
Queen's Fleet out there,
which is what I'd guess,
it won't do me any good
to go after them alone.
It looks like there's no
one around, doesn't it?
Yeah. Then again,
Agnese did say
the ship was
mostly unmanned.
[KAMIJO] Over there.
That's where Lucia and
Angelene are being held.
What's that?
What do you see? Is
something in the way?
Orsola! Stand back!
Ah!
That was close. This
suit of armor is like
some magical robot?
Yes. It's part of the
ship in altered form,
likely for defensive purposes.
[gasps]
[ORSOLA] Don't move!
Unless you want to
meet the same fate
as your frozen bodyguard.
Oh, my! Very sorry. I don't
usually speak so forcefully.
This is important, though.
[ORSOLA] If you
don't heed my warning,
I'm afraid I'll
have to use this.
[ORSOLA] Don't be frightened.
We've come to rescue you.
You can't really think
we're stupid enough
to believe a word that you say.
Well, here's the thing,
Agnese's the one who
sent us to find you.
She says the two of you
have a spell that should
be able to get all
of us off this ship.
[KAMIJO] It'll work out best for
everyone if we can cooperate.
Sister Agnese sent you
here to rescue us? Ah...
Don't be so naïve!
This could easily be a trap.
We're enemies of the Church,
and the Roman Orthodoxy
controls this fleet.
Do you think we would
come here and put ourselves
[ORSOLA] in such danger
just to play a trick on you?
Please! I don't like it here.
We'll go with you.
I have to admit, your arguments
have some logic to them.
So, can you tell
us how exactly
we're gonna
get out of here?
It would take far
too long to explain.
[LUCIA] Sister Angelene.
Oh, uh, okay.
[KAMIJO] Whoa!
[LUCIA] A subclass of the
magic that was used to build
these ships can open
up voids within them.
We'll take advantage of
that solidifying seawater,
and then using it to
create seabed coasters.
[BOTH whimper]
What's wrong?
I-I think it's the restraining
habits they made us wear.
They must be equipped with some
kind of countermeasure spell.
We'll need to rip apart
the seams in a particular way.
That should disrupt part
of their functionality.
Tear them apart
at the seams?
Uh, I think I might
know a quicker way.
[KAMIJO] Ugh!
Now, now! Exactly how
many sisters are you trying
to strip naked in one evening?
♪
[ANGELENE]
Aren't you guys scared?
I wish I knew what was
gonna happen to us.
More importantly,
I wish I knew why
tonight's supper
bothered me so much.
What do you mean,
"more importantly"?
Nothing is more important
than serving Mother Church.
Yeah, supper kinda
bothered me, too.
Three days in a row
they've put olives in it,
and I don't even like them. Oh!
What about the baths?
Aren't they too hot?
Who cares about what
they put in the food?
And the bathwater is
lukewarm, if anything.
Oh, do you really think so?
I guess if there was
actually something wrong,
the grown-ups would
take care of it, huh?
So, that must mean--
[AGNESE sighs]
What? Is something the matter?
[ANGELENE] If you're going
to talk to somebody about it,
I'll come with you.
Talk to somebody.
[AGNESE] Yes. That
might not be a bad idea.
[ANGELENE] What's the plan?
When can we meet up
with Sister Agnese?
[KAMIJO] Well, Agnese
won't be coming. Sorry.
[LUCIA] Uh!
She only wants
us to rescue you.
She's gonna
create a diversion.
[KAMIJO] I'm pretty sure she's
headed to the fleet's flagship.
You can't be serious!
The Queen's Fleet is equipped
with large-scale magic
designed to protect
the Queen of the
Adriatic Sea ritual grounds.
The Queen of
the Adriatic Sea?
I don't know much about it.
Just that it's held on
a ship of the same name.
[LUCIA] A specific
spell is required
in order to activate it.
It's known as the Rosary
of the Appointed Time.
Also, Sister Agnese is
involved in casting the Rosary.
They need her for the spell.
[gasps] Wait.
What's going
to happen to Agnese?
[LUCIA] Not even we can
be sure of all the details.
However... it is
likely that her brain
will be completely destroyed.
Her heart will still beat,
but other than that, well.
[AGNESE] The Queen's Fleet
has a major operation ahead
of them right now.
They're pretty distracted.
So I doubt they'll
worry about you.
[rumble]
Someone's attacking us!
But where's it coming from?
[LUCIA and ANGELENE scream]
Impossible!
[ORSOLA] From one
of their own ships?
♪
[cannon fire]
[AGNESE] The holy cannon
fire of St. Barbara?
But what are they aiming for?
[MAN] Surely you
can deduce the answer
to that, Sister Agnese.
[AGNESE] Bishop. Do you mean?
[MAN 15A] Ship number
thirty-seven has been sunk.
Any further fire could
draw attention we don't want.
[BISHOP] Let another department
deal with public relations.
Worrying about such
issues is beyond my purview.
We must keep you
well protected.
[BISHOP] It would distress me
if anything were to befall you.
Well isn't that ironic.
The much-vaunted Rosary.
[BISHOP] I find it almost
tragic that an apostate like you
is the key we require
to unlock this spell.
[MAN 15B]
Bishop Biagio! It's urgent!
What is it now?
[MAN 15B] Sir, we're detecting
a giant structure underneath
ship thirty-seven. It appears
to be retrieving the wreckage.
It's a submersible spell.
[KAMIJO] Where are the others?
I'm sinking fast!
[KAMIJO] This could
be it. I could die here.
You're awake!
Is that you, Index?
It's me. How are
you feeling? Okay?
Yeah.
[KAMIJO] Wait,
Tatemiya, you did this?
Yeah. Deputy Pope
of the Amakusa Church
at your service, my good man.
Although nowadays we've added on
"of the English
Puritan Church," too.
[ITSUWA] Hot towel?
Uh, great, thank you.
[ITSUWA] Not a problem.
Where are the
girls who were with me?
[KAMIJO] Orsola and the others?
Oh, we were able to extract
all of you from the wreckage.
The other nuns are just fine.
We're questioning
the men separately.
Well that makes sense.
So, are we hiding out
in a top-secret
Amakusa base or something?
[chuckles]
Don't let the walls fool
you; this isn't a building.
Huh? Then what is it, exactly?
[TATEMIYA] See for yourself.
I really wish I could call it
a submarine, but that would
be grossly overstating things.
More accurately,
it's a wooden ship with
limited submersible capability.
Basically a
glorified diving boat.
You came here to
help Orsola move.
And you brought along
something like this?
Yes, well, we find
it helpful to have
a secret weapon
close at hand.
Besides, naval warfare happens
to be one of our specialties.
A natural affinity.
Spell paper is made of wood.
Just like boats. Makes
sense if you think about it.
Poor Agnese.
[grunts]
What? What is it now?
Nothing at all.
I expect you to give me
a detailed account of whatever
it is you're going to do next.
Oh yeah? Then you
should probably talk
to Angelene or Lucia.
[KAMIJO] Well, uh. I-I mean.
Huh?
I'm glad everyone
made it out okay!
Oh, these ladies
are just a little bit
embarrassed, that's all.
The habits they were
wearing were imbued with
magical restraints, courtesy
of the Roman Orthodox Church.
Naturally, they had
to be destroyed to ensure
a successful escape,
which meant making use
of your right hand
while you were unconscious.
So, you're saying...
[chuckles] Yep, that's
exactly what I'm saying.
Uh...
I'm gonna kill you!
Whoa, hold on, you can't
be mad at me for that!
[KAMIJO] It isn't fair!
Please! Let's calm down!
This is no time
for us to be arguing.
[ANGELENE] Sister Agnese
is still out there!
Could you please tell your
friends that we have to
carry out another
rescue mission?
[ANGELENE] Someone's
life hangs in the balance!
[INDEX] Waaah!
[ITSUWA] Uh...
Itsuwa! Go for it!
Now's your chance!
Give him a smooch.
He's at your mercy!
Would you please
tell them about Agnese?
So much yelling!
All right! Now this is
what I call entertainment.
Why won't you listen to
me? This is important!
Over here!
♪
Oh! Sister Angelene,
how could you?
All the noise and chaos
were starting to remind me
of how our squad room was.
So, I did what I always did to
get people's attention in there.
Hm. That's an
interesting tactic.
[ANGELENE] I don't care
much for coffee or tea.
I'd prefer a cioccolata
con panna if you have it.
[KAMIJO] What's that?
The most delicious
thing in the world!
Ah, chocolate and cream!
A follower of the
cross does not obsess over
food and drink! You
should know better than--
Take it easy, huh?
[ITSUWA] Hot towel?
Oh, thanks again.
Not at all!
[MALE AMAKUSA 15B] You
don't think it might be time
to try something new?
[MALE AMAKUSA 15C] It's not
really working for ya.
[MALE AMAKUSA 15D] Hey,
she's just taking it slowly.
That's one of Itsuwa's charms.
[KAMIJO] I'm curious. Can you
give us a bit more background
on the Queen of
the Adriatic Sea?
It's a long story, but we can
try and summarize it for you.
Venice and the
Roman Orthodox Church
weren't always on good terms.
So the Church decided that
it would be best to come up
with a way to obliterate
Venice in a single strike.
And thus, the Queen
of the Adriatic was born.
"Obliterate," huh?
How does it work?
Like a bomb or something?
This weapon
doesn't just destroy.
It's been specially
designed to steal all of
the city's culture
and history, as well.
That's extreme.
[ANGELENE] I can't imagine
that Sister Agnese knows about
any of this, though.
I'm certain she doesn't.
If she did, she would try
to do something about it.
[TATEMIYA] So basically,
we need to go back
and rescue Agnese Sanctis.
Preferably before she can
be used to start
up some crazy weapon.
Well. That's easier said
than done, don't you think?
Difficult or not,
we have to do it.
Unless we find
a way to save her,
Sister Agnese's
mind will be shattered.
Do you expect us to
stand by and do nothing?
We have to help! As
long as I've known her,
Sister Agnese has
been there for me.
Now she's in need, and there
is no way I'm going to fail her!
That's great. Don't
suppose you have a plan?
We might be able to
use our own magic to stop
the fleet before they
can get any farther.
You think that's all there
is to dealing with the enemy?
Making sure they can't move?
[ANGELENE]
Well, I know there's more.
[KAMIJO] Take it easy, Tatemiya.
I think that you've
said enough, don't you?
[TATEMIYA] Hm?
[KAMIJO] We've been looking
at things the wrong way.
The question we should be
asking ourselves now isn't
"Why should we rescue her?"
Because we know the
answer to that already.
[KAMIJO] Agnese selflessly
gave up her own chance
to escape the ice fleet.
A sacrifice she
made for her friends.
If we don't do something her
mind is going to be destroyed,
and she'll just become
another one of their victims.
[KAMIJO] The question is
"How can we not rescue her?"
We'd be preventing the
destruction of Venice, right?
Think about it.
There's only one answer.
Is the Amakusa Church in
on this mission or not?
'Cause I'll do it
by myself if I have to!
Enough. We've been in
on the rescue mission
from the first time
it was mentioned.
In fact, we've even come up with
a plan if you'd like to hear it.
I just wanted to
make sure you were ready.
But after that speech,
I've got my answer.
Tatemiya.
Listen up! We're
heading back out onto
[TATEMIYA]
the battlefield, everyone!
I know that we can succeed!
What teaching did the
Priestess give to the Amakusa?
[AMAKUSA MEMBERS] The hand of
redemtion to the irredeemable.
Hm.
Here, this is for you.
Oh!
[INDEX] I think it
might come in handy.
I can't use it, so you
should take it, okay?
Hey, Index.
Is something wrong?
Nothing at all.
Okay. Let's get
this party started.
[alarm beeping]
Bishop Biagio, sir!
We've got an urgent reading.
Many craft approaching.
They're just under fifty
seconds from our coordinates
[BIAGIO] Sink them if you can.
Roger that.
They haven't fired
a single return shot.
Which could mean--all
hands, defensive positions!
[BIAGIO] What's happening?
Fire ships!
[WOMAN] An unmanned fleet,
designed to self-destruct.
Ha--ugh!
[WOMAN] Large object at
a depth of forty meters.
Probably a submarine.
[MAN 15A] Confirmed
hit on the submarine.
[MAN 15B] Enemy forces
on ship twenty-nine!
It's the Amakusa!
[gasps] That was the plan!
The sub was just a decoy!
[TATEMIYA] Don't worry about
gaining control of each ship!
All we need to focus
on is destroying
their main force.
Everyone understand me?
You guys head for the
Queen of the Adriatic Sea.
Right.
[TATEMIYA] Go on! Hurry!
Time to move!
[INDEX screams]
♪
[gasps]
[SISTERS scream]
--[LUCIA] Come this way!
--[KAMIJO] Right!
[LUCIA]
What, are you idiots?
Help us! We've come
to rescue Sister Agnese!
They've started shooting.
I think they're
trying to sink the ship!
[LUCIA] It looks like
they're aiming directly at us!
I call you, Matthew
the Apostle, publican,
holy enemy of magicians,
and humble servant.
Uh-oh!
Uh...
[ANGELENE] I call you,
Matthew the Apostle!
[ANGELENE] Look out!
Ahhh!
Sister Angelene!
[LUCIA] Sister Angelene!
♪ [Ending Song] ♪
[KAMIJO] We must storm
the flagship to keep
the Queen of the
Adriatic from activating.
As more mysteries are revealed,
Index rises to the occasion.
Next time, "Rosary of
the Appointed Time."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.