[KAMIJO grunts]
[KAMIJO] Kazakiri!
Uh, Kazakiri!
Please wake up!
[KAZAKIRI whimpers]
[KAMIJO] Ah, thank goodness.
You had me worried...
Are you feeling okay?
[KAZAKIRI] The city...
Look at it!
[KAZAKIRI] The destruction...
How did things
end up like this...?
I know it must be
all because of me...
And yet here I am: apparently
the only one left untouched.
No matter what, I'll never
be like everybody else...
So why did I even have to
be born in the first place?
The power of the espers
changed things a little...
I was able to exist,
even if it was as a freak...
And then that girl came along...
She was kind enough
to call me her friend...
I thought maybe that made me at
least a little bit more human...
I'm so tired of this!
Will you please
just touch me
and put an end to all of it?
[KAZAKIRI gasps]
[KAZAKIRI] What is it?
Why are you smiling at me?
Because I'm
relieved you're okay.
[KAZAKIRI gasps]
I don't know why I have
this strange power
or where it
comes from. However...
If it meant obliterating one
of my friends with this hand...
I would chop it off...
That would be better than
losing someone I care about.
[KAZAKIRI] But... I...
You protected the others,
didn't you...?
You did what you could
to keep everyone safe.
Can't you see, when
all is said and done,
that's what counts?
You can be proud.
Hold your head up high...
After fighting so hard for the
sake of complete strangers...
and managing to pull
everyone through...
You have absolutely
nothing to be ashamed of.
[KAZAKIRI sobs]
[KAMIJO] I'm going to look
around and see if there's anyone
out there who needs help.
And then, let's head home.
There's no telling when
you're going to vanish on us.
Before that happens,
you need to meet up with Index.
And don't go asking me why,
okay, I think it should be
pretty obvious by now.
It's because that's
what friends do.
Hey...! That was
crazy! You okay?
What was that stuff that
came out of your back...?
It looked a lot like telesma.
[MIKOTO] Hello...! Wanna tell
me what happened over there...?
Those freaky wings in the sky
seem to have disappeared...
I'm done here, so if you
need help, I can head your way.
[INDEX] I need to get a doctor
here as soon as possible!
[MIKOTO] Hey, hold on!
[departing footsteps]
[ACCELERATOR sighs]
[SHADOWY MAN] Accelerator...
I would like a word with you...
Do you think you can manage?
[ACCELERATOR]
Huh? That was telepathy...
and I have a small amount
of computing power back, too.
[SHADOWY MAN] How observant...
I made arrangements for
several telepathic espers.
[ACCELERATOR] Whatever.
What do you want?
[SHADOWY MAN] I would like to
talk to you about the series
of disturbances you caused,
as well as the damage
Academy City has suffered
as a result of recent events.
[ACCELERATOR] Is my punishment
to be sliced and diced
for research purposes?
[SHADOWY MAN] That is
one route we could take.
But how do you like
this idea, instead...?
Come and work with us.
[ACCELERATOR] Is Academy
City preparing for
a war or something?
[SHADOWY MAN]
I cannot answer that.
[ACCELERATOR] You can't, huh...?
Then there's only one thing
I'm gonna say...
Screw you and your offer.
[SHADOWY MAN] This is a critical
moment in the life of the city.
We want to ensure
the best outcome possible,
and for that, we would
like your assistance...
Imagine if Academy City
was completely wiped out...
Is there any other place
for espers like us to go...?
What would we do without
this scientific haven?
[ACCELERATOR] Tch...
Will you tell me one thing?
[SHADOWY MAN] What is that?
[ACCELERATOR]
The name of the person
responsible for tonight...
I'm going to kill
whoever thought they could
get away with putting
the kid through this.
[SHADOWY MAN] I don't
see how that could help...
He would be a scapegoat,
nothing more.
[ACCELERATOR] You don't say.
[SHADOWY MAN]
So... what will it be?
[ACCELERATOR] Suit yourself.
[SHADOWY MAN]
An excellent answer.
I look forward to
working with you...
Until then...
[gunshot]
[phone rings]
[phone beeps]
[ACQUA] That you, Terra?
[TERRA] Yes, Acqua of the Rear,
this is Terra of the Left...
Are you finished
with your current task?
[ACQUA] Vento is
out of commission...
I just recovered her and
ordered the detached squad
in Academy City's
outskirts to stand down.
[TERRA] That sounds
like a good night's work.
Can you tell me
our next move...?
I have no objections
to lopping off
the target's head if
it should be necessary.
[TERRA] Let's not
take that step yet...
It would be wiser at this point
to hear your entire report
and then reconsider
how best we can
bring about the
fall of Academy City.
[ACQUA] The fall of
Academy City? Heh.
[TERRA] You don't care
for that idea, Acqua?
Cheap tricks aren't my style...
I find that defeating
the enemy face-to-face
is the simpler and
more honorable method.
[TERRA] It's possible
some of the players on
the opposing side
may still be useful.
The fallen angel,
for example.
[ACQUA] I do not approve of
plundering the battlefield.
[TERRA] You knights pick
inconvenient times to get
prickly about your honor.
I am no knight...
You know quite well
I'm simply a
washed-up mercenary.
[TERRA] Call yourself
whatever you'd like,
it doesn't matter to me...
Just get Vento back
here immediately...
Those instructions
are courtesy of
Fiamma of the Right,
in case you were wondering.
Understood. I'm on it.
[phone beeps]
[ACQUA] Interesting... I wonder
if Academy City really is
as frail as you seem
to think, Terra...
I suppose we'll see, won't we?
[FROG DOCTOR]
Good morning, Aleister...
There's something I wish
to discuss with you,
and I hope you'll
take it seriously.
[ALEISTER] Yes, what is it?
[FROG DOCTOR] I want you
to stop treating my patients
like your playthings.
[ALEISTER] Hm... And if
I don't, what will you do?
[FROG DOCTOR] Those are my
patients and I am their doctor.
Do you understand the
importance of that...?
Do, you, Aleister?
I think you should,
considering that
I saved your life once.
[ALEISTER] Is that
something you regret?
That can't be a
serious question.
[ALEISTER] My plans
are in motion...
and I have no intention
of stopping them.
So, I am sorry...
my kind-hearted enemy...
but this is goodbye for us.
[bell rings]
[STUDENTS chattering]
[KAMIJO's stomach growls]
[KOMOE] Hey, stop!
You know better than that!
No running in the hallways!
[HIMEGAMI] Hello.
You look excited about
whatever you brought.
I'm guessing you've
probably got something
really tasty there, too.
I'm not sharing
my lunch for free.
If you want to try
some, we can trade.
Ya' know I've always
been impressed by how
you fix yourself such
great lunches every day.
Ah. Careful. Your broth is
leaking into your rice area.
Well... Actually,
I think the rice is better
when it's got some
broth on it like that.
Nice and soggy, huh?
No, it's not...! Here,
if you're going to doubt me,
give this a try!
Go on taste it!
Okay... I guess
it's not all that ba--
[KAMIJO] Uh...
[HIMEGAMI grunts]
Uh... What's happening?
Are you okay?
[HIMEGAMI grunts]
You're saying... you want me
to rub your back, is that it?
[HIMEGAMI] Mm-Hm...
There you go...
Does that help?
[HIMEGAMI grunts]
[KAMIJO] Okay, should
I do it harder, then?
[snap]
[HIMEGAMI gasps]
[KAMIJO] Huh?
[KAMIJO grunts]
[FUKIYOSE] What are
you doing down there?
[KAMIJO wearily]
Hi, Fukiyose.
Question... Why do you
eat that bread all the time?
It looks like it's
made of cardboard.
Whadaya' mean...?!
It looks just fine, thank you!
"Ability-boosting bread,
with twelve nutrients
for energizing the brain. Eat
up, and be the best you can be!"
[KAMIJO chuckles]
Well, would you like to
try some of my lunch?
Hmm... Just
so you know...
I'm wearing a bra that
hooks in the front today.
[BOY STUDENT 23A] Seriously?
[BOY STUDENT 23B] Yeah, and
they say we might not get to go
on field trips anymore
once they tighten security
in and out of the city.
[BOY STUDENT 23C]
I wonder if this'll affect
the Ichihanaran Festival.
Did you hear...? The teachers
are going to be so busy
making preparations we might
not have to take any midterms!
Isn't that great?
[GIRL STUDENT 23B] Awesome!
[FUKIYOSE]
Preparing for a war...
If it happens, it'll
change everything...
Know what I mean...?
Things'll get crazy around here.
Super early curfews. Maybe
even food rations, too...
Soon enough prices
everywhere will sky rocket.
[KAMIJO sighs]
Hey... Where'd you go?
[KAMIJO] Hm?
You're awfully quiet...
Are you daydreaming?
Oh... sorry...!
I heard what you said.
I was just thinking
maybe we should
have a nice meal now
while we still can.
You know, so we won't regret
not doing it later
on or anything...
Okay, I suppose
that we could...
What's this
I hear...?
You're going out for
dinner tonight, Kami?
Hey...!
Let's all go!
I know of this really
great cheap restaurant!
Hey, what're you
guys talking about...?
You going out someplace tonight?
We can't let you
have all the fun!
We're coming along, too.
[STUDENTS chatter]
What's happening...?
When exactly did
the entire class decide to
go out for dinner tonight?
Is something wrong?
Yes!
It looks like she's
got her game face on!
Hey...! This party's
gonna need an organizer!
That's me, people,
so shut up and listen.
[YOMIKAWA] So, rumor has it
you've taken in another girl
in need of a home.
How's that going so far?
[KOMOE laughs]
You know how I am!
I started to get really
lonely after Himegami
moved into the dorms...
Having Musujime around
really cheers me up!
How are things at your place?
It's looking like
I'm on my own again...
After the recent chaos,
my tenants decided
to move elsewhere.
[STUDENTS cheer]
[KOMOE] Aaahh!
[FUKIYOSE] It's decided!
Tonight, we are all officially
going out for a dinner party!
Ah! What are
they doing?!
I need to get these
wayward kids under control!
[KOMOE] Quiet...! What is the
meaning of this, you hooligans?!
[BOY STUDENT 23B]
Ah...! Hey there, Teach...!
I love this place...
There's never a boring
moment around here.
[FUKIYOSE] Okay, guys...
[STUDENTS]
Everybody dig in! Woo-hoo!
[SPHINX meows]
[KOMOE sighs]
The requests are
starting to pour in...
Parents are getting more
and more nervous about
the possibility of war
breaking out in Academy City...
They're asking
for their kids to be
sent home before
things get ugly.
Wow... I didn't realize it
had gotten that serious yet.
Come on...! Honestly,
what's wrong with you?
Could you possibly be
taking any longer to do that?
Huh?
Gaaaah!
I can't take it!
I'll show you
how it's done.
Wah...! Okay!
[PIERCE] Hey, Kami...
Have you taken a look at
the prices on the menu...?
They don't seem to have gone
up at all, war or no war.
[KAMIJO] Yeah... You're right.
Here!
[KAMIJO] Oh... thank you...
You know... just because
they haven't gone up
doesn't mean they won't.
I feel ya, man.
You're basically saying that
we should eat up while we can.
Don't mind if I do!
[KAMIJO] Wha...?! Not cool!
You can't just
take all the meat!
[INDEX] I need more meat,
Toma! Find some for me...!
[KAMIJO] Jeez...
that's not fair...
I haven't eaten a single bite,
and you're already
through with yours.
[KAMIJO sighs]
[KAMIJO] So, war is coming...
I should do something,
but... what?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Cheer up.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] I know
what you're thinking...
That the war that's
about to break out
is because of you somehow...
But, you've got it wrong...
You've been protecting those
around you this entire time.
Well, maybe... yeah...
This war is happening
because the people
who are in charge screwed up.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] It is happening.
[KAMIJO] Yeah.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] It'll be
battle on a new scale...
From this point on...
getting through it
by the skin of our
teeth won't be enough.
Yeah, I know what
you're saying...
Really... it's a miracle
we've even made it this far...
We've all been
pretty lucky.
Everyone has
been carrying me.
There've been too many
things I know nothing about...
So I've just left it
all to other people...
but that's over...
I can't afford to do that
anymore... Starting now...
I'm going to explore a world
that's been foreign to me...
One that I've been too
nervous to learn about.
Do you understand...?
I've made a decision.
[TSUCHIMIKADO sighs]
You're sure?
Yes... Very sure...
It's final. I'm going to
learn another language!
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Uhh...
[KAMIJO] I mean... I've tried
to pick one up before,
but you know how it goes...
You learn some stuff,
but then there are
all those cognates and idioms...
He's gonna learn a language?
That's his plan?
I let other
people translate
when I don't
understand...
but I can't expect everyone to
keep coddling me like that...
You get it...
This is just something
I have to do.
[punch lands]
[KAMIJO] Ow...
What was that for?
[buzzing]
[FEMALE VOICE 23A]
Target ready...
Drill number
forty-two... Begin now.
[FEMALE VOICE 23A]
Target ready...
Drill number
forty-three... Begin now.
[ACCELERATOR]
Did you want something?
Or were you just lurking?
Very impressive shooting.
I was trying to
be inconspicuous,
but clearly it didn't work.
It's okay... I still have
a lot to learn in that area.
Mitsuki Unabara, right...?
That's what they call you.
Yes, though the
name and the face
are both fakes, I'm afraid.
Have you decided
on a weapon yet?
[ACCELERATOR] None of them
feels quite right to me.
You could bring in guns
from all over the world,
and I still might not find one.
[UNABARA] What if you made
a list of gear compatible
with your ability?
That might help you
find the right weapon.
[ACCELERATOR] Stop acting
like such a know-it-all.
It's annoying. My problem is,
this thing is unreliable.
I've seen Group's engineering
report on that device...
They've extended your ability
usage time to thirty minutes.
That's a significant
improvement.
So... it's
called Group.
Are you dissatisfied
with the tuning
of your electrode?
Ha...! The use time
could be thirty minutes
or three days...
Once a glitch comes up,
it's all over,
lights out...
A single malfunction means
that I can't fight anymore...
and you don't survive
long like that.
Is that what you came
here to chat about?
Actually, I sought you
out because Group has
received an assignment
from the governing board
and its being given to you.
[footsteps]
[UNABARA] War is coming...
Academy City will soon be
pitting itself against
the Roman Orthodox Church.
Which means the city's
internal defenses
are being thinned out,
making us highly vulnerable
to attack from inside.
Our assignment is to
neutralize one group that
would seek to take advantage
of that vulnerability.
Heh. Man, I knew I was
being brought here so
I could fill in for that
useless bastard Kihara...
But I didn't realize
I'd be getting stuck with
jobs that were this
boring and trivial.
It matters very little
whether you like the job...
Besides, you came here on
your own. Nobody forced you.
[ACCELERATOR grunts]
Listen up, kid...
There's something
you really ought to know.
The human body is an
incredibly fragile thing.
Fragile enough that
a single touch from me
can do permanent damage.
So you might want to choose
your words more carefully.
Otherwise, I could
break something you
really don't want broken.
Yes, of course.
[ACCELERATOR] Tch.
[UNABARA] May I continue
briefing you on your assignment?
[ACCELERATOR]
Whatever. Go ahead.
[UNABARA] Your target
will be a group
that's known as Skill Out...
I'm not very
familiar with them.
Perhaps you
know more than I do.
Yeah, I know them...
They're an armed
gang made up of
a bunch of sad,
pathetic Level Zeros.
That's correct...
We're getting involved now
because it seems they've
found some new toys.
What kind of toys?
[UNABARA] They're rockets,
made of hollowed-out wood
that has been packed
with explosives...
If it helps you
form a mental picture,
think of them as
high-tech fire arrows.
Skill Out has been very busy
for the last few days...
getting ready to play with
their new toys, most likely.
They've been taking
abandoned bicycles
and placing them
along emergency routes.
And using piles of
garbage to block up
the sewage drains around
a few certain VIP facilities.
Not the kinds of things
that are considered
security problems
in and of themselves.
So this is what
Group does...?
Do they take on contracts to
stop children's pranks as well?
[UNABARA] As I was saying,
there have been more than
twenty thousand incidents.
That many will flood the
system, and before long,
the security network will start
classifying them as errors.
So, where do the fancy
fire arrows come in?
That number of erroneous
reports will cause
the server to crash,
and Skill Out will be able
to wreak havoc in the city
without Antiskill even knowing.
[ACCELERATOR] Can't they
just shut down the alerts
that will cause the errors?
[UNABARA] If we weren't
getting ready for a war, maybe.
[ACCELERATOR] Nothing but
enemies within and without...
Great. We're real popular
these days, huh...?
Is there anybody
out there who doesn't
have a beef with Academy City?
I couldn't say, but
right now your assignment is
to track down one of
the people who does.
Your target's name
is Ritoku Komaba.
This is what he looks like.
He is currently the
leader of Skill Out...
and he's the brains, too.
Dispose of him quickly...
Our goal is to derail
Skill Out's plans
before they can
proceed any further.
[ACCELERATOR] Any reason
we're taking a garbage truck?
[UNABARA] You'd be surprised
how handy they are...
It'll be great for
getting rid of the body.
A garbage truck
going around picking up
the bodies of scumbags...
Well, that's one way
to take out the trash.
[UNABARA] He will return for
recovery in twenty minutes,
as planned... Be careful.
[phone beeps]
[ACCELERATOR sighs]
So no matter how this goes down,
I'm stuck riding
in that thing...
Though whether it'll be
in the front or the back,
I don't know yet.
[ACCELERATOR] Hiding
from security robots...
And using little
tricks to escape
the gaze of
observation satellites.
Well, it's nothing
I'm not used to.
[phone buzzes]
[phone beeps]
That you, Tsuchimikado?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] I figured
your first mission
would be starting soon...
I just wanted a quick
word before it did.
Let me guess:
a warning...? Yeah...?
Some advice for the
new guy...? What'll it be?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Whatever
you do... don't trust us.
[ACCELERATOR] Huh?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Group is an
organization that can only
function in the shadows.
If word of our
existence got out,
there would be trouble...
We have no inspiring
mission statement
and no noble or lofty goals.
[ACCELERATOR] Did you think
that I would be expecting
some kind of reward
for my service?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] If you do
nothing but play by the rules
established by
the governing board,
you'll never get the
upper hand in this game...
I'm saying there's
one question
you should be asking yourself...
"What do I need to do to win?"
You and I have
something in common...
We both have things to protect.
Was there anything
else you wanted to say?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Finish up
quickly and get back here...
Musujime's got
a job in that area
and she'll be getting
started pretty soon.
Another Group member?
[rumbling]
No one mentioned anything
about this being a contest.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] The target she
was assigned isn't a person;
it's money.
[ACCELERATOR] Musujime, huh...?
I'm surprised she's
fit to take on a job.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] You and
she are ranked the same...
She's been upgraded.
[ACCELERATOR] Oh, has she...?
That's great to hear.
[phone beeps]
What am I waiting for?
Might as well get
started on this job.
[beep]
[ACCELERATOR] It's cleanup time.
I should have this
wrapped up in ten minutes.
[clang]
[SKILL OUT yell]
[MUSUJIME chuckles]
That makes nine...
These guys could
stand to toughen up.
[KOMABA] If we're so weak,
then maybe you should
take it easier on us...
little esper girl.
[MUSUJIME] Heh.
Ritoku Komaba.
This could get sticky.
It looks like I accidentally
ran into the target first.
[KAMIJO] Members of Group
and Skill Out clash...
Misaka's mom gets caught
in the middle of the chaos...
and Accelerator
and I meet once again.
Next time, "Skill Out."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.