[LAURA humming]
[sighs]
[door opens]
I've got a question for you!
Stiyl!
Uh, ah!
Can you please look at
this report, Archbishop,
[STIYL] and confirm
whether it is true?
I wouldn't be surprised.
They do say the world
moves at your word.
What do you think you're doing?
You cannot
simply barge into
the ladies' bathing
room in this manner!
Especially not as
a man of the cloth!
[STIYL] Forget about
propriety and answer me!
[LAURA] Ah...
Uh!
[STIYL] Well? Will you kindly
fill me in on the details?
Right now!
[LAURA] Whatever shall I do?
My vestments are clinging
to me in a most immodest way!
This is just so wrong!
Look away, Stiyl!
I can feel myself being
tainted by your gaze!
I cannot allow a man to look
upon my body in this state.
♪ [Opening Song] ♪
[KANZAKI]
What was she thinking?
Why would the
archbishop elect to buy us
such an unnecessarily
complicated device?
[SHERRY] Give up already. Go
wash your clothes in the river.
That ought to be simple enough.
[KANZAKI] Now that
would be too primitive.
[ORSOLA] Well, let me see.
According to the instructions,
we just press this
button right here.
[beeping]
Hand-washing it is, then.
I call dibs on the tub!
Let's keep trying.
I'm sure we can do it.
It's always been a
dream of ours to have
a fully-automated
washing machine!
Isn't this a waste of time?
I thought the laundry
had already been done.
Yes, that's right.
Let's forget about
the machine for now.
[ORSOLA] Wait.
We will have some
more laundry to do
in just one moment.
[KANZAKI] You don't need
to take your clothes off
to make another load
of laundry for us!
And that goes
for you two, as well!
I have noticed something
about that garment you wear.
It almost seems like it
was designed specifically
so it would be
easy to remove.
[screams]
[KANZAKI] Hey! Don't do that!
Oh... I see that you
are one of those people
who "goes commando."
Is that the correct saying?
[KANZAKI] That's just how
you wear this type of kimono.
It's amazing
how quiet it is.
A soothing, gentle hum.
I just wanted to see
one work. That was all.
[sighs]
Hey, ninja lady, I just
thought of something.
As a matter of fact,
I'm a retired ninja now,
but please continue.
This section in the manual,
[SHERRY] it says that you
should make sure to separate
colored items that may bleed.
I'm wondering about
that kimono sash of yours.
Do you think it's
gonna be a problem?
Cancel! Please cancel!
How're you supposed
to stop this thing?
[grunts]
Ah!
[ANGELENE] Oh. She was right!
You really don't have
any underwear on, do you?
[crying]
[MIKOTO] Oh! Gekota!
Gekota! Gekota! Gekota!
[laughing]
That is just pathetic.
[yawns]
So, did you finish
the paperwork? Uh, wait.
[MIKOTO] Huh? I can get a
Pyonko together with my Gekota?
Woo-hoo!
Nope, she's still there.
So I'm gonna guess that
makes you Misaka's sister?
"Yes, your guess is
correct," confirms Misaka.
"My serial number is 10032,"
Misaka adds to clarify.
[KAMIJO] I didn't recognize
you without your goggles on.
"Can you tell
me if you've seen
a shorter Misaka, one
roughly this height? Please,"
adds Misaka, careful to observe
the proper social etiquette.
A shorter one?
You guys can change sizes now?
[MISAKA 10032] "Judging
by your ignorant response,
you have not
seen her," says Misaka,
disappointed by your
failure to be of any help.
"Misaka's goggles
were stolen from her
not very long ago.
It is important that they
[MISAKA 10032] are recovered
as soon as possible. Please?"
Misaka asks again,
this time widening her eyes
to look vulnerable.
Well, um, it'd be easier
if I could tell you apart.
If I find something, how will
I know which sister is which?
[KAMIJO] Whoa! What
are you doing that for?
You can stop now!
That's going a little too far!
I know. You could
wear some kind of
accessory to distinguish
you from the others.
What kind of accessory?
[KAMIJO] Oh, I don't
know. A ring, maybe.
Really? A ring?
"That's right. And
the magazine discussed
the importance of
getting a ring from
a boy one likes and wearing
it on the left ring finger.
[MISAKA 10032] Once a
girl has that, she wins."
[KAMIJO]
Nah, a ring wouldn't work.
It doesn't stand out enough.
Huh?
Something that's
noticeable at a glance.
[LAST ORDER] "Right now,
Misaka is playing tag with
one of the lower-number
units," says Misaka Misaka,
offering a status report.
"I can't make it
home at the moment,
but I hope you'll
save me some dinner
for when I do get back,"
says Misaka Misaka,
placing her order.
[beep]
[growls] That dirty brat!
She's nothing but trouble!
It would be great
if you could avoid
destroying my
material possessions.
This would be a lot easier
if she had called my cell.
Then we could find out
where she made the call from.
Okay, enough already.
Let me go, will ya?
[ACCELERATOR] Ugh!
[YOMIKAWA]
Well, best if we split up.
Kikyo, you stay here.
You and I will head out
to look for her? Sound good?
If I can analyze
the background noise,
I might be able to narrow
the list of possible locations.
With my training
and credentials,
[YOMIKAWA] we shouldn't have
very much trouble finding her.
Doesn't this constitute
an abuse of your authority?
If finding a lost kid's
not part of my job, what is?
Okay, let's get going.
Tch.
[MISAKA 10032] A necklace, then.
Instead of a ring
on Misaka's left hand.
Hey, you know, if you
don't like that one,
we can always exchange it.
"Please, do not take
anything from Misaka.
She has lost enough
today," says Misaka
in an earnest voice, lowering
her eyes for more emphasis.
[sighs]
[KAMIJO] "Animal Donuts," huh?
[KAMIJO] Don't mind if I do!
Wow, these look delicious!
"Cheep-cheep-cheep-
cheep-cheep-cheep.
They must be sweet-tempered,
not to move around
or peck at all," says
Misaka, very impressed
[MISAKA 10032] with
the creatures' behavior.
[gasps]
They said these are
a brand new product,
still in the
experimental phase,
but they're really yummy.
Why does it matter that
they are experimental?
[MISAKA 10032] They're still
real. Misaka thinks their
lives should be respected.
[KAMIJO] Uh, what's wrong?
What's with the sparking?
[MIKOTO] Hey, you guys.
What's going on over here?
[KAMIJO] Er, nothing.
[MISAKA 10032]
"Oh. Misaka needed help.
She asked this boy's
assistance in finding
the goggles that were
stolen from her," says Misaka.
[MISAKA 10032] "There may have
been more to it than that,
but now I cannot take my
eyes off these little frogs,"
gushes Misaka while
inspecting the Original's bag.
[MIKOTO] Hands off!
Your bogus explanation
isn't working on me.
How did you end up
down here, and why do you
care so much about your gogg--?
What are those things?
They're adorable!
"If you are going to be
protective of your frogs,
I'll be the same
way about my chickens,"
says Misaka in a
reasonable tone of voice.
Oh, come on. I can
have a look, can't I?
"If Big Sister
wants them so much,
she can get her own.
These chickens belong
to Misaka and the boy,"
[MISAKA 10032] says Misaka,
forcefully staking her claim.
[MIKOTO] Staking your claim?
Ah!
Hey, you remember that
whole thing where we made
a bet and then you lost
the bet and now you have
to do whatever I tell
you to, no matter how
difficult or
demeaning it might be?
Uh...
[MIKOTO] 'Cause here you are in
the middle of our penalty game
spending your time with
someone who is not me!
You're one of those
jerks who always goes
for the sister instead, huh?
[MISAKA 10032]
"Out of curiosity,
what are you doing
here?" asks Misaka,
looking for relevant
background information.
Ah... Well, you see.
We made a bet during the
Daihasei Festival, and
obviously I was the winner.
I'm sorta' dragging him around
with me as his punishment.
Ah, maybe that's
not the right word--
"Basically, you find
yourself unable to be
honest with him
at present. Right?"
asks Misaka,
after analyzing the data.
[MIKOTO] Huh? I don't know
what data you're analyzing,
but you're totally wrong!
What could I possibly
have to hide from him?
And anyway, this guy's
so stupid he wouldn't
know what to do with the truth!
[MISAKA 10032]
A strong reaction.
Interesting. Misaka will
try a more direct approach
[MISAKA 10032]
than her sister employs.
Huh?
Wha--?!
"What do you think about
this?" asks Misaka,
[MISAKA 10032] casually
showing Big Sister the
heart-shaped necklace
the boy bought her.
"Misaka runs up to hug
him from the other side
as well!" says Misaka
Misaka, not wanting to be
left out of the
fun everyone's having.
So you're a Misaka,
too? Another sister?
[MISAKA 10032]
Serial number 20001.
"You have some
nerve showing up here,
considering your brazen
theft earlier today,"
scolds Misaka, adopting the
tone of a disapproving sister.
[LAST ORDER chuckles]
"That game was fun for a while,
but Misaka is tired of
it now," says Misaka Misaka,
preparing to head
off in search of
a new way to entertain herself.
"You think you're
getting away that easily?"
scoffs Misaka, arming herself
for the upcoming chase.
"If you think that's
going to scare me,
you're stupider than you look,"
says Misaka Misaka,
making fun of Misaka.
"The real fun is just getting
started," threatens Misaka,
making the final transition
to Misaka Full Boost.
[gun cocks and fires]
[KAMIJO] Seriously?
The underground mall?
[YOMIKAWA] We performed a
full analysis of the message
she left on the
answering machine
and we came up
with some frequencies
that were pretty distinct.
They indicate that
she's in Area U,
and that essentially
means the underground mall.
[ACCELERATOR] Fine.
So that's where you're
telling me to go, then?
[YOMIKAWA]
That's the plan for now.
But we'll see.
She moves fast on those
little legs of hers,
so who knows if
she'll be there by
the time you arrive.
[YOMIKAWA] Hey, Accelerator?
Yeah, what is it?
[YOMIKAWA] Why are
you so afraid to show
kindness to other people?
[ACCELERATOR] Say what?
You take it in stride
whenever Last Order
is affectionate
or sweet with you,
but you seem to draw
the line when it comes
to showing her any
kindness on your part.
[YOMIKAWA] I think it's because
you're afraid that once you do,
there will be no going back.
Thanks for the lecture.
[YOMIKAWA] I know.
It's not like I can ever
completely understand where
you're coming from, is it?
Not with the things
you've been through,
the way you grew up.
[ACCELERATOR] Tch.
The old X-S.
The Exceptional Esper
Multi-Modification
Technical Research Institute.
Home sweet home until
I reached the age of nine.
The place was like a landfill
for disposing of human beings.
You must've heard
the stories, right?
[YOMIKAWA] It was my squad
that neutralized the Institute.
I oversaw its dismantling.
[ACCELERATOR] Thanks for that.
[YOMIKAWA]
I saw it, too, you know.
What they kept hidden away
on the other side
of those heavy doors.
[ACCELERATOR] And just think,
I was such a monster
even the X-S Institute
couldn't handle me.
I'm sure Yoshikawa
told you...
about what I did in
those "experiments."
Showing kindness isn't
exactly my strong suit.
You were young, they didn't
give you much of a choice.
But you still hate
yourself, even now.
There's a rule that I follow.
Not Antiskill's,
but one I made for myself.
[YOMIKAWA] I will never
turn a weapon on a child,
no matter what. Not even if
that child's a powerful esper.
Do you know why that is?
[YOMIKAWA] Yeah.
I thought you would.
And, sure, maybe it doesn't
even compare to your situation.
But the fact of the matter
is that we're both indebted.
You and I, we've got
quite a lot to pay back
before we can
hope to rest easily.
In some ways, I envy you.
At least you have
power to work with.
That gives you more
options than I've got.
[ACCELERATOR]
What if I'd used my power
to stop the experiments?
Or found a way to
keep them from rushing
headlong toward
their inevitable deaths?
What if even now, after
all this, it's not too late?
[ACCELERATOR] What if...?
This is a buncha crap.
[YOMIKAWA] Well, you know, it's
hanging on to that kind of crap
that pushes us to
make good on our debts.
Hm.
[ACCELERATOR] Damn it all.
[CROWD chatter]
Isn't this what the
report said to look out for?
[ANTISKILL B]
It's an impressively made
3D image, all right.
[ANTISKILL A] These pranks get
more convoluted every year,
don't they?
Well, let's contact HQ
and get the names of espers
who could pull this off.
[KAMIJO] Man, am I beat. What
was that all about, anyway?
[MIKOTO] That big, stupid jerk!
[breathing heavy]
Does he think he can
get away with this, huh?
[MIKOTO] What am I,
chopped liver?
[gasps and cheering]
[breathing heavy]
How is it I always end up
in the middle of these things?
Just my luck, I guess.
"Why are you sitting
with your shoulders
all slumped like
you're exhausted?"
asks Misaka Misaka.
Uh!
[LAST ORDER] Stealthily
coming up behind you
and giving you a hug
to make you feel better.
[KAMIJO] Hey!
The Mini-Misaka from
earlier. Wow you are tiny.
♪
[thud]
[INDEX groans]
I'm so hungry.
[ACCELERATOR] Huh?
What do we have here?
[stomach growls]
[INDEX] So anyway, I was
out looking for Toma,
but then I got hungry
and I couldn't keep going.
You can eat or you
can talk. Pick one.
Well, anyway, when you're
done stuffing your face,
I've got a question for you.
Sure, you can ask me anything!
Man, you're disgusting.
Thank you for the food!
My name is Index, by the way.
It's nice to meet you!
[ACCELERATOR] First, wipe off
your face. Then we can talk.
[phone beeping]
Here, take a look.
Have you seen this kid
wandering around anywhere?
[INDEX] Nope, sorry.
You barely even looked.
But I don't need to.
I never forget the
faces of people I see.
Well, I should
get back out there!
I'll have a much
easier time of it
now that my stomach is full.
[INDEX] Though, of course,
now that I'm not so hungry,
my need to find Toma somehow
doesn't seem quite as pressing.
[ACCELERATOR]
Well, nice to meet ya.
Hope you find someone
else to help you look.
'Cause I'm not gonna.
[INDEX] Why not? Are you busy?
Yeah. That's it.
I'm incredibly busy.
[KAMIJO] So what
you're saying is,
you're essentially
like a host computer,
with all the Misaka
Sisters tied into you?
[LAST ORDER] "Probably more like
a console than a host computer,"
says Misaka Misaka,
correcting your statement.
"The Misaka Network has
no central point anywhere.
So it doesn't really mean
anything for there to be
a specific individual acting
as the Misakas' 'core,'
so to speak," says Misaka
Misaka authoritatively,
enjoying the chance
to give a lecture.
[sighs]
"Well, anyway, the
reason I came back was
to say thank you for all
the help you gave Misaka
when those awful
experiments were going on.
Even thinking about
them gives me the shivers,"
says Misaka Misaka,
shivering illustratively.
Sure. What are you
actually doing here?
"You don't believe me?
You're such a jerk!"
shrieks Misaka Misaka,
stomping her feet to show
just how angry she is.
Then she decides to swing
[LAST ORDER] her fists around
in your face for good measure!
My bad, okay I'm
sorry? Hey, I know.
[KAMIJO] If you
promise to forgive me,
I'll buy you some popcorn.
"You actually think
offering to buy a girl
a snack will make her forget
that you hurt her feelings?
What kind of an idiot
are you?" asks Misaka Misaka,
unable to look at you anymore.
So, like I was saying,
Toma is always
running off somewhere,
leaving me behind.
He doesn't even give
me an explanation.
It's like his feet don't
know how to stay in one place,
[INDEX] he heads out before
he even knows he's going.
[grunts]
Heh. So, why did you want to
come to the underground mall?
I'm looking for someone.
The girl in that picture
you showed me, right?
Wow. You catch on quick.
I wish I could find
a way to thank you
properly for feeding me.
Here's an idea. How about
you shut up and go away?
[INDEX] I really don't
know how I can repay you.
I just gave you a
perfect suggestion.
Why don't you take it?
[INDEX] You're worried
about that girl, huh?
[giggles]
Let's work as a team!
I'll help you look
for her until I find Toma.
Huh?
[INDEX] 'Kay?
Uh. Damn it all.
Ah!
Wanna know something?
"Misaka snatched
these from somebody.
Somebody tough!"
says Misaka Misaka,
[LAST ORDER] happily
bragging about her trophy.
Oh, really? I'm finally
starting to relax,
and now you're
gonna tell me you're
some kind of bandit?
Hold on. I recognize those.
[KAMIJO] Misaka's sister
was looking for them.
"Unfortunately, these
goggles were made to fit
a person a lot
bigger than Misaka.
So she can't put
them on to use them.
It's really disappointing,"
says Misaka Misaka regretfully.
Hey, uh, you know you
can just shorten the length
of the band, don't you?
[LAST ORDER] Huh?
Ahhh!
Uh, are you okay down there?
[whimpers]
[INDEX] Hm...
You know, I almost
feel like I recognize her
from somewhere,
but there's something off,
and I can't put my finger on it.
Nope, I have no idea
who she is. I'm sorry.
Then give me my
phone back already!
Ya good for
nothin' little brat.
[growls]
[KAMIJO] There, all done!
Ah...!
"That's great!
Misaka can see perfectly!"
says Misaka Misaka,
delighted by the change.
"But Misaka remembers
what you said before,
and she hasn't forgiven you,"
Misaka Misaka asserts,
[LAST ORDER] taking time to
scold you for your rudeness
before returning to
her celebratory dance.
Yeah, yeah.
"It's almost time. Misaka
can't stay much longer.
She has to get going,"
Misaka Misaka says
[LAST ORDER] in a somber tone,
delivering the bad news.
Oh, I didn't realize
what time it was.
"It makes me sad.
I wish we could spend
more time together," says
Misaka Misaka, with a sigh.
"Maybe some other
time, though."
"Misaka admits our
encounter was coincidental,
but the part about
wanting to thank you
for your help was the
truth," says Misaka Misaka,
hoping you know how
sincerely she means it.
"I really have to
get home soon, though,
or he'll be worried."
Who'll be worried?
[LAST ORDER] "If Misaka
stays out too late,
he'll probably think he
needs to go look for her."
"And Misaka doesn't want to be
an inconvenience or anything.
You know?" asks Misaka
Misaka with a smile.
[KAMIJO] Well, sounds like this
friend of yours is a nice guy.
"He's had a hard time.
He was hurt physically,
mentally, and emotionally.
It may be too much for
one person to heal from.
He wants to be strong,
but Misaka knows that
in many ways,
he's still very weak.
[LAST ORDER] So if she can
help it, she doesn't want
to add to his burden.
Misaka will protect
him like he protected her!"
declares Misaka Misaka,
baring her heart.
[KAMIJO] I see.
Ah! It's him! It's Toma!
That the guy you've
been looking for?
Mhm.
[grunts]
Well, I'll see ya.
[INDEX] Huh? But what
about your friend?
Don't you still need help?
I think I can
handle it from here.
I've got a pretty
good idea where she is.
I'll get going, then.
It was nice to meet you!
Last Order, come here!
[giggles]
[INDEX] Toma!
[LAST ORDER] "Good to
see you!" says Misaka Misaka,
offering the
standard greeting.
"Hey, ow! Are you
going to say something,
or are you just going to
keep swatting me like that?"
asks Misaka,
generating fake tears
to encourage
greater leniency.
Save your crying for
somebody who cares.
What've you've been up to?
Uh... "Playing
with somebody I just met.
It was fun!" says Misaka
Misaka, answering honestly.
[sighs]
Huh?
[INDEX] Finally! There you are!
I've been looking
for you everywhere!
I bet I can guess why.
You were hungry, weren't you?
[INDEX] Actually,
I was starving!
But it turned
out all right because
I ran into that
guy and he helped me.
[KAMIJO] Yeah? What guy is that?
[LAST ORDER] Accelerator!
Huh?
You better hurry or
you'll be left behind!
Pipe down ya' dirty brat.
♪ [Ending Song] ♪
[KAMIJO] A man from a
familiar family appears,
and the city has
a scent of danger.
Then, as if things
weren't bad enough,
the Right Seat of
God enters the fray.
Next time, "The Researcher."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.