[SASHA] "Precautions
for when angels descend
and take on human form.
One instance of
telesma habitation
stands out above all others.
It occurred, needless to say, at
the time of the Annunciation."
[SASHA] "The amount of
telesma needed was great.
Enough to be transferred into
the womb and create a being
who would then provide spiritual
guidance for the world.
Accomplishing this
required a great deal--"
[WOMAN] Hello, Sasha!
[SASHA] Mm.
Oh! You have your nose buried
in those musty old books again.
All this dreadful reading and
you still haven't identified
what went wrong with your body?
You know, if you'd like,
I'd be glad to give you
a physical exam.
Oh, my. That hurt quite a bit.
All this time and you
still haven't learned
your own strength, I see.
[SASHA] A couple
points of inquiry.
Question one:
Which do you prefer,
hammers or screwdrivers?
Neither, actually, and
I would have appreciated
being asked before you hit me.
[WOMAN] Tell me, Sasha, the
telesma dwelling within you
is that of Gabriel,
is that correct?
And wouldn't that
normally be unthinkable?
Your earthly container
now holds more telesma
than all twelve Apostles.
Question two:
So what if it does?
What is the point you
are attempting to make?
[WOMAN] Let's not forget the
fact that the power within you
comes from the angel who
saw to the Annunciation.
Moreover. Considering
the amount and source
of the telesma squeezed
into your tiny female body
isn't there a danger that
your tummy might swell?
[whimpers]
Okay, I'm sorry.
You're right, of course.
[WOMAN] The clothing you
wear isn't exactly indicative
of somebody who is
keen to breed without
experiencing the fun part
of the process, after all.
Question three is
more of a statement.
Your filthy words
sully the purity
of our divine purpose
on this earth.
Furthermore, wasn't
I forced to wear
this type of clothing
by you, my superior,
in what amounts to an active
abuse of your power?
Oh! You really dislike
them that much?
Well. We'll just change
your outfit, then.
[SASHA] Huh?
[WOMAN] As I'm sure you know,
I've been looking into
Academy City lately.
They have their own
unique culture there.
It's fascinating, really.
[SASHA] Uh...
[WOMAN] Now, tell me, Sasha.
Have you ever heard of
Magical Powered Kanamin?
[thud]
[WOMAN] Ah, come on now.
Was that truly necessary?
♪ [Opening Song] ♪
[LAST ORDER laughing]
"It's raining!
It's raining! It's raining!"
Misaka Misaka loudly shouts,
looking up at the sky.
Sure is. Now do me a favor
and stop dancing
around like a lunatic.
[LAST ORDER] "Misaka wishes she
could see the moon, though,"
says Misaka Misaka,
somewhat disappointed
but not totally deflated.
[ACCELERATOR] Hey!
I told you to stop
scampering around, didn't I?
So do it, you brat.
"Misaka was fine
on her own.
There is no need to start
over-protecting her now,"
reports Misaka Misaka,
emphasizing her need
for personal freedom.
What kind of hippy-dippy
crap are you talking about?
Did you get that out
of a parenting book?
And whatever I am,
it's not overprotective.
"No, of course you aren't.
Come on, there's no need
to be embarrassed about it,"
Misaka Misaka declares, jabbing
you with her index finger.
[LAST ORDER] "Why are you
clenching your fist like that
and making such a scary face?"
asks Misaka Misaka,
offering an irresistible smile,
hoping it will take
the edge off your
swiftly building temper.
[sighs]
[LAST ORDER laughs]
"Rain, rain, rain!
I love the rain!"
Misaka Misaka squeals as she
resumes dancing around for joy.
[LAST ORDER]
This is so much fun...
[YOMIKAWA] Why are you
so afraid to show kindness
to other people?
You take it in stride whenever
Last Order is affectionate
or sweet with you,
but you seem to draw the line
when it comes to showing her
any kindness on your part.
I think it's because you're
afraid that once you do,
there will be no going back.
[LAST ORDER] Ow!
"I fell and it hurts,"
cries Misaka Misaka,
sitting on the wet ground,
looking pitiful.
You idiot.
I warned you, didn't I?
[LAST ORDER] "I may
need some disinfectant,"
Misaka Misaka points out,
as her eyes well up
with tears of pain.
Just rub some spit
on it. You'll be fine.
[LAST ORDER] "Disinfectant is a
good idea," says Misaka Misaka,
repeating herself since
you ignored her before.
[ACCELERATOR]
Look, for right now,
let's just get back
to Yomikawa's place.
[LAST ORDER] "All right, I'm
coming," says Misaka Misaka,
calmly accepting the situation.
"It really hurts, but
I'll try to keep up,"
Misaka Misaka sighs resolutely
putting on her goggles
and bravely following
you in spite of the pain.
Huh?
Uh--Aaah!
"Hey!" says Misaka
Misaka, "Why--"
[ACCELERATOR]
Wait right here, got it?
Take one step
without my permission,
and you'll regret it.
Why do I even bother?
[ACCELERATOR] Tch.
Who cares, anyway?
What?
[ACCELERATOR] You know, I had
a feeling some idiots like you
would be coming along.
Maybe you're here 'cause
you have a beef with me,
or maybe you want my help
with some experiment.
But it doesn't really
matter either way.
Now say goodbye.
[HOUND DOG A screams]
[laughs]
[HOUND DOG A] Ugh!
[HOUND DOG B grunting]
[laughs]
[ACCELERATOR] Man, this is fun!
You're screwed now!
There's no stopping me
when I get like this.
You're gonna die!
[gunshots]
[HOUND DOG B screams]
Huh?
Tch. Uhhh...
This is tedious.
[chuckles]
[ACCELERATOR laughing]
Thanks for the
entertainment, guys, really.
I hope you appreciated the show.
I gave you some
of my best stuff.
[MAN] They should've
listened when I told them
it wasn't going to work.
You won't bring such a fine
specimen of an esper down
with an ordinary show of force.
You'll have to bring out the
big guns if you wanna beat him.
[ACCELERATOR laughs]
Hello, hello, Amata Kihara!
You know, that
was a pretty damn
flashy entrance for you.
I guess you've changed
a little bit, huh?
'Cause I remember you as
the shy, intellectual type.
More a man of brains
than of brawn.
[AMATA] To be completely
honest with you,
I was personally against
staging this reunion.
But, at the end of the day
orders are orders ya' know?
What's a guy to do?
They said it was an emergency
situation and they didn't
have the luxury of being picky.
So, here we are now,
just you and me.
It'd be a lot easier if
you'd give up quickly.
After all, don't you owe me?
If you look at it
in a certain light,
I am sort of your creator.
Sorry, what's that?
My creator, huh?
Getting a little sentimental
as you get older, are you?
I just hope you're not
expecting the same from me,
because you'll be
so disappointed.
I should feel a sense
of duty? Man, is that rich.
I don't have any room
to spare for you up here.
Do you know how many of
you damn white-coated
researchers have screwed
around with my body?
Even I stopped keeping track!
I'm not wasting precious
brain cells remembering
every moment of the
experiments that were
done by all of you crack pots.
[AMATA] You are one of
the most vexing little punks
I've ever had to deal with.
Ending your miserable life
isn't going to be a chore
for me; it'll be a pleasure.
I'll actually be correcting
the egregious mistake
I made by not killing you before
when you were under my control.
I should have put you
down then. Oh well.
[AMATA] I can make up for
it now... with interest!
[ACCELERATOR]
What does this idiot think
that's gonna do to me?
So, how do I want to deal--
[AMATA grunts]
Uh!
[ACCELERATOR] My reflection.
It didn't work!
[AMATA] Do I have
your attention now?
Maybe you'll want to
take a moment to reflect
on the role I played
in developing the power
[AMATA] you've come
to depend upon so much.
Well, kid, is your
memory coming back?
Huh?
That's not like you.
[AMATA] Well, don't worry,
we'll take good care of her.
I'm going to beat you until
you're a stain on the ground,
but we'll keep the girl company.
Does that make
you feel better?
I know how sensitive you are.
[grunts]
[ACCELERATOR] Shut your damn
mouth. Don't you mock me.
You dirty bastard!
[AMATA] Sorry, kid.
That's not gonna do it.
[laughing]
[ACCELERATOR grunts]
You're an esper. Is that it?
You developed an esper
power in yourself.
[AMATA] What?
[laughs]
Oh, no.
That's not it at all.
Do you really think I
would experiment on myself
like I do on you lab rats?
I don't have to resort to
using that kind of power.
[AMATA] I can defeat you easily
enough without debasing myself.
These little guys'll be
enough to finish you off.
[ACCELERATOR grunts]
[screams]
I don't think so!
You're the one going down
tonight, you son of a bitch!
[AMATA]
One mistake after another.
You thought my gloves
contained the secret
to my power, didn't you?
Hate to tell you,
but you got it wrong!
[AMATA laughs]
[ACCELERATOR retches]
Are you still convinced
you're the strongest man here?
You piece of crap!
[ACCELERATOR grunts]
Your reflection isn't some kind
of immutable wall, you know.
In reality, it only
alters the vectors
of power sent at it from
the other direction.
That makes outsmarting
it pretty simple.
[AMATA] All I have to
do is yank back my fist
right before a direct hit.
Sometimes winning a
fight's all about knowing
when to pull a punch.
[AMATA] Basically, I just have
to stop short of hitting you,
and your reflection
does my work for me.
You get it now, my
accidental masochist?
Is that clear enough yet
for you, or would you like
some further explanation?
Think about that wind
you stirred up earlier.
At its most basic level,
your ability is the product
of vector formulas.
Meaning, I can render you
defenseless by disrupting them.
Jamming your power's easy.
I just have to call on
special sound waves.
[AMATA] I know everything
about you. Your character flaws,
your formulas, even your
own Personal Reality.
I made your power
into what it is.
I know you better than
you know yourself.
Now tell me, Accelerator,
do you understand the reason
we used her and not you?
[AMATA] I'm talking
about Project Radio Noise.
For our template we used
Railgun, the third-ranked.
Why wasn't it you,
when you're ranked first?
There's something there.
Some hidden bit of information.
Something you don't have
the first idea about.
Screw you, bastard.
Profound as always, I see.
Look, she seems pretty
thrilled about it herself.
[groans]
[AMATA] A successful recovery,
I guess you could say.
At least, I think so.
We were supposed to take
her alive, but looking at her
I'm not so sure we managed
that part of it now.
[AMATA] No way am I writing
up the mission report for this.
[ACCELERATOR] She's still
alive. She has to be.
I'd know if she were dead.
My sister's proxy calculations
would be affected.
I don't know where
they're taking her,
but... if I don't do something,
I doubt I'll ever see her again.
[ACCELERATOR grunts]
Last Order!
[HOUND DOGS groan]
[AMATA] Tch.
[ACCELERATOR retches]
[AMATA] Well, that was
a little melodramatic.
You could really stand to
work on your manners kid.
You know, most people don't like
to be sent flying like that.
Great, and who exactly is
supposed to track her down now?
'Cause it sure
isn't going to be me.
[HOUND DOG F] Orders, sir?
Eh, let me think a second.
Split yourselves
into three squads.
One of the squads will
go after the girl.
I want the other
two to stay with me.
[HOUND DOG F] But sir,
our first priority is
to recover Last Order.
[AMATA] Oh, yeah? Is that so?
You're the new guy, right?
You were only recently
assigned to Hound Dog.
[HOUND DOG F] Um, I...
At ease, man, it's okay.
It's not like I'm
doing a background check
here or anything.
However, you don't
seem to know the rules,
so let me educate you.
You guys matter about
as much as pond scum.
That's how much I care
about your opinions.
The other thing about scum--
no one gives a crap
about what happens to it.
[AMATA] So interfere with
my mission if that's what
you really wanna do,
but killing you isn't
gonna make me lose any sleep.
Do we understand each other?
Your life is worth
less than nothing.
Well, speak up, man! Do you
understand what I'm saying?
[HOUND DOG F] Uh.
[AMATA] All right!
I'm glad that's clear.
Take a squad and search
the rivers and reservoirs,
and any other large
bodies of water.
He wouldn't have blown
the kid sky high unless
he'd already calculated a
safe place for her to land.
[HOUND DOG F] What should
we do about the esper boy?
Take him back with us?
No, go ahead and kill him.
There's no reason to
take him into custody.
Looking at him just reminds
me of the mistake I made
in not doing away
with him sooner.
He's nothing but a moody,
self-absorbed little brat.
Let's do the world a favor and
eliminate him here and now.
[ACCELERATOR] Shut up.
[AMATA] Huh?
You don't get it, do you?
And you're not gonna.
Not as long as you live.
Yeah? That's a shame.
[AMATA] Well, I hope
you don't mind those being
your last words, 'cause
now's the part where you die.
[ACCELERATOR] Damn it. Somebody.
Someone please show up.
I don't care who you are.
I don't even care if
you want to trample me
and laugh while you do it.
But somebody, anybody
at all... save the kid.
[INDEX] Excuse me.
What's going on over there?
[KAMIJO panting]
Ah, Index, why do
you always do this?
One second you're
there, and the next
you've disappeared
all over again.
I don't understand why you
can't be more considerate.
[INDEX] When I couldn't find
you earlier, the nice boy with
the white hair
bought me a hamburger
and he didn't even know
the first thing about me.
I hope you meet
each other someday.
You could learn a thing or
two from him about manners.
Yeah, whatever. I'm sure
this Prince Charming
was real impressed by your
manners, too. Speaking of.
I don't suppose you
remembered to thank him
for buying you food?
[INDEX] Yes! Unlike you, I care
about other people's feelings!
What's the matter?
I did forget something.
He let me borrow these.
Wasn't that nice?
Yeah, that's just
a packet of tissues.
True! But it says
here that this is
a "convenient product for
everyday use," so he could
need one any moment now,
couldn't he? I have to go.
I'm sure he would like these
back as soon as possible.
That's the kind of thing
people don't want back.
Hey!
[KAMIJO] Here we go. I feel like
I'm always running after her.
[KAMIJO] Oh, great.
And it's raining.
She didn't have an
umbrella with her.
She must be getting
soaked to the bone.
[KAMIJO] There're more Antiskill
out than there normally are.
I hope I can find Index quickly
before there's any trouble.
[thud]
[gasps]
Excuse me sir, are you okay?
Can you hear me? Officer?
[bodies thud]
[whispering] Whoa.
[KAMIJO] What's going on here?
At least it doesn't seem
to be life-threatening.
This many. I wonder what the
hell happened to all of them.
[radio static]
[ANTISKILL A]
In the metro area. Repeat.
Gate destruction confirmed.
Intruders in the metro area.
We're under attack, but the
assailants are unkn-- Ahh!
Intruders nearby?
I need to hurry!
[sobs]
[gasps] It's you!
"I need your help!"
"Hurry, come with me!
There's something
that we have to do!"
pleads Misaka Misaka,
begging with all her heart.
[WOMAN laughs]
[WOMAN] Hi! You there, Aleister?
[WOMAN] I know you make a
habit of secretly listening in
on communications, so there's
no point in playing coy.
Seriously, this would
go a whole lot faster
if you would say
something already.
[radio static]
[ALEISTER]
Very well. Let's chat.
Ha, ha. I just completed a
mission that involved disgracing
three members of
the governing board.
I expect you'll be wanting
to retaliate soon.
[ALEISTER] They can be replaced
as many times as necessary.
Huh. I had thought
for sure that doing away
[WOMAN] with your puppets
on the board would finally
motivate you to take some
action. It seems like I may have
misread the situation,
however. Oh, well.
You do know to whom you
are speaking, don't you?
[ALEISTER] I'm afraid not.
The Right Seat of God.
[WOMAN]
If you want to play dumb,
that's completely fine as well.
I just don't want you to
have any regrets later.
[ALEISTER]
Don't you think you may be
underestimating this city?
[WOMAN] I think that you
are overestimating it.
Which is really quite sad.
Antiskill and Judgment.
Your two shields.
You've ended up with your
head in a noose because
you relied upon those toothless
outfits to protect you.
Without them, you're finished.
And they'll hardly
be a challenge.
[ALEISTER] If you and your
organization truly believe
that is all it will
take to bring down
Academy City's defense network,
you are sadly mistaken.
It's becoming obvious
you have no idea
what this city's true form is.
Oh, yeah?
[ALEISTER] Whether you like it
or not, you aren't the only one
with a trick or two
up your sleeve.
Of course, I don't imagine
you're going to have
the chance to use
any of those tricks.
[WOMAN] Say what you want.
I will crush anything or
anyone who stands in my way.
That has been written in stone
from the moment I was born.
You say you don't know me?
Well, I am Vento of the Front.
I am the deadliest weapon
among the Roman Orthodox
Church's two billion faithful.
Nothing can stand before me
when I decide to destroy it.
That includes your
precious Academy City,
and the List of
Prohibited Books,
and Imagine Breaker, as well.
You will all fall before me.
[ALEISTER] Interesting.
It looks like I'll finally have
the chance to use one of
those tricks I've been saving.
[ALEISTER] It may be too soon,
but we'll try it out.
After all, it's these
unexpected events that provide
for the greatest amusement.
Call Hound Dog. Amata Kihara.
[AMATA] This is Kihara.
[ALEISTER] Imaginary
Number School District,
Five-Element Agency--
the AIM diffusion field.
It is a bit earlier
than we expected,
but we will crush them easily
enough using Fuse Kazakiri.
Once you have successfully
retrieved 20001,
bring her to the
designated location.
[ALEISTER] Do it swiftly
but courteously.
[AMATA] Roger that.
[ALEISTER] Now then.
I have been looking forward
to this for quite a while.
It's show time!
♪ [Ending Song] ♪
[KAMIJO] A running battle
for Last Order has begun.
What lengths will Accelerator go
to in order to protect one girl?
Next time, "Hound Dog."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.