Behind you!
I call you,
Matthew the Apostle.
Publican, holy enemy of
magicians, and humble servant.
Ah, ahh!
Index!
Damn!
What are you doing,
Sister? Be careful!
Uh-uh! It
wasn't me! I swear it!
C-T-R-T-T-O-P.  A-O!
[wimpers]
Come on! If you
don't pay attention to
what's around you,
then you're that much
easier to defeat in battle.
Did she just use
Spell Intercept?
[distant whistle]
They've sounded
the retreat signal!
It's time to go,
Sister Angelene!
[ANGELENE] Right! Coming!
[KAMIJO groans]
[TATEMIYA] Now you have
seen it with your own eyes.
This is how they act when they
think that nobody is watching.
[TATEMIYA] This is the true face
of the Roman Orthodox Church!
♪ [Opening Song] ♪
[STIYL] If everything
the Amakusa said is true,
his last point
likely is, as well.
It's very improbable they
will kill Orsola right away.
There are
restrictions that will
make it difficult to do so.
What restricts
the Catholic Church?
[STIYL] Somebody deciphering
"The Book of the Law"
poses a threat to them.
However, Orsola Aquinas
is not guilty of anything.
[INDEX] "Thou shalt not
kill those who believe
the teachings of
God and of the Church."
So, if Orsola was
in no danger from them,
why were the Amakusa
worried about her safety?
[STIYL] Because of
the obvious exception.
They aren't allowed
to kill those who believe
the teachings of
God and the Church.
That gives them plenty
of latitude, though.
It means that they are
perfectly free to kill somebody
who has been excommunicated
from the Church for
not properly following their
teachings or honoring God.
The long and
short of it is,
they're going to label
her an enemy of God
and the Church so
they can kill her.
But the power of a
grimoire is tainted.
It is something that can never
bring happiness to anybody.
It causes only conflict.
In its wake is a trail
of destruction and death.
Yeah, well screw that!
Unfortunately, it
doesn't matter now.
There's nothing more
that we can do to help her.
[KAMIJO] Erh!
Doesn't matter? You
know this is a human life
we're talking about?
No, what we're
talking about is
the Roman Orthodox Church
applying their own rules
to one of their own people.
If we get more involved
than we already are,
it will mean starting
a religious war.
Is that what you want?
Of course not.
Don't worry so
much, young man.
Everything will be all right.
The English Puritans
may have no reason
to fight the Catholic
Church over this,
but the Amakusa
certainly do.
I was already planning
on paying their base
a little visit, anyway.
While I'm there rescuing
my own lost children,
I can save
Sister Orsola, as well.
Don't tell
me you plan on
going up against
them by yourself?
Hmph!
If I have to, then yes.
That's exactly what I'll do.
[distant dog barking]
[STIYL] Okay, well I
guess that settles that.
[STIYL] We should split
up and lay low for awhile
to be on the safe side.
Once we get back to Academy
City, Index'll go with you.
[KAMIJO] Yeah, okay.
[STIYL] Oh.
There is one thing
I want to ask you
before we part ways, though.
Ask away.
The crucifix that I gave
you earlier during the fight.
[STIYL] You don't
seem to have it anymore.
[gasps]
Oh, sorry about that.
I gave it to Orsola,
and she's still got it.
[KAMIJO] I... hope it
wasn't too expensive.
No, with something
like that,
the value lies in
having it with you.
It's okay. Our work
is done for the night,
so it's nothing you
necessarily need right now.
[STIYL] Let's go.
Uh... right.
♪
[KAMIJO] What am
I supposed to do?
Poor Orsola.
There must have been something
more I could have done for her.
It's an issue for the
magicians to deal with.
You shouldn't feel
responsible for what happens
in a case like this.
Maybe.
[INDEX] You've already done
everything you need to do.
Now it's somebody else's turn.
You can't expect to solve every
problem in the world, you know.
[KAMIJO] I guess.
♪
[KAMIJO] Oh. I forgot.
[INDEX] Hm?
Our refrigerator's
almost completely empty.
I'll find a convenience
store and get us something
to last the night.
If you're going
to the store,
maybe we should
all go together.
[heavy exhale]
Do you even know where
the nearest store is?
Not really. Finding
it may take a while,
so you guys go on without me.
♪
[beeping]
[KAMIJO] Orsola's Church?
Yes. She did
excellent work spreading
the Church's teachings
throughout three heathen lands,
so she deserved to be
recognized appropriately.
[AGNESE] She was granted
special permission to oversee
the building of a church
that would bear her name.
I'm certain it must be
around here somewhere.
Auhhh!
[wimpering]
[AGNESE] Come, now. You
really shouldn't make this
difficult for us, you know.
Unfortunately,
we do not have time to
draw this process out
the way that I would prefer.
Be grateful for that
and accept your punishment
without a fight. Uh!
[AGNESE] Are you listening?
I said, are you
listening to me, sister?
[coughing]
Auhhh!
I have to admit I
almost feel sorry for you.
It's obvious that you have
no true friends to rely on.
If you did, you wouldn't
have fallen so readily
into the arms of
the Amakusa Church
simply because
they offered to help.
The Amakusa and
the English Puritans
are both unworthy.
I find it disgusting
that they would ever dare
to include themselves
as church of the cross.
You were weak, and
now you are going to
reap the reward
for putting your life
into such incompetent hands.
It took very little
convincing on our part.
They were easily duped
into bringing us our quarry.
[ORSOLA] You said
they were duped?
You mean you lied to them?
You deceived them, and
that's why they helped you?
[AGNESE] That's right.
[ORSOLA] Then that means they
weren't working with you.
You tricked them!
I don't see how that
makes any difference!
They personally delivered
the woman they were
supposed to protect
into enemy hands.
Your friends are beyond hope.
I suppose we'll
have to disagree.
[AGNESE] Hey! What
are you smiling about?
[ORSOLA] Am I smiling?
Well, why shouldn't I?
After all...
You have just given
me a very precious gift.
[ORSOLA] You helped
me realize something
I didn't know until now.
Your words and actions
have revealed to me
the true nature of the
Roman Orthodox Church.
What?
[ORSOLA] The ones
who helped me earlier,
they act on what they believe
with their innermost hearts.
Whether it be a person,
or a thought, or a feeling.
If they believe in something,
then they will fight for it.
By contrast, where
they act on their beliefs...
we, sisters, act on
our fears and our doubts.
And what an ugly thing
that has turned out to be.
[wimper]
[AGNESE] If you
want to die so badly,
by all means, continue talking.
[ORSOLA] Ahuhhh!
[AGNESE] But as you breathe
your last breath,
know who is responsible.
Regardless of what you
think, the blame lies
on the shoulders of
those who brought you here.
[ORSOLA] Is that so?
And just what am I
supposed to blame them for?
[AGNESE] Everything.
Once again, we see
things differently.
They had no personal reason
to involve themselves in this.
But even so, they
came rushing to the aid
of a complete stranger.
They put their lives in
danger in order to help me.
[ORSOLA] Tell me, can there be
any act more worthy of praise?
Because if there is, I
certainly cannot think of it.
And you expect
me to lay blame
on the shoulders
of these people?
The people who gave me
the most magnificent gift
I could ever receive.
[gasping]
How could anyone possibly
get past our barriers?
[AGNESE] Damn!
Which organization?
♪
[AGNESE] Hmph. You
expect me to wonder how
you managed that, but I
think I might have an idea.
My guess is you have
something in your possession
with the power to
neutralize our barrier.
Well, did I guess correctly?
[KAMIJO] I don't
enjoy being lied to.
So, I suggest that
you don't do it again.
[AGNESE]
What would be the point?
At this juncture, it should
be pretty clear to you
what's happening here. Right?
[AGNESE] The English
Puritans realized they have
no place in this and ran off.
So why is it you
haven't given up yet?
Come now.
This is your last chance.
Your fate hangs in the balance.
I think you know
what you ought to do.
[KAMIJO] Yeah, you're right.
This is my last chance
to do what I need to.
I am very
well aware of that.
Well, in that case...
[running footsteps]
[KAMIJO grunts]
You filthy heathen!
What exactly do
you think you're doing?
[KAMIJO] What I ought
to do, obviously. Come on!
Stop playing the idiot.
I came here to rescue her!
I admit, I find you...
fascinating.
Go on, take a look around.
How much do you really think
you can accomplish alone?
Maybe you would like to
give us a demonstration?
[weapons clinking]
[fire roaring]
[NUNS screaming]
How rude. You just had
to start without me, huh?
Why are you here?
What? The English
Puritan Church?
[AGNESE] You should go.
This is a matter for the
Roman Orthodox Church alone.
You don't want to interfere in
our internal affairs, do you?
No, but as it turns out,
this isn't actually so internal.
[STIYL] Look at
Orosla Aquinas' chest.
You do see that
English Puritan crucifix
that's hanging there, don't you?
She has asked someone
to place it around her neck.
That act signifies an acceptance
of English Puritan protection.
Orsola Aquinas is no
longer a Roman Catholic.
In fact, she is now a member
of the English Puritan Church.
I get it.
So, that means...
[AGNESE] Hm! Do
you honestly think
that kind of sophistry
will work here?
[STIYL]
Not entirely, no. However...
I'm sure you realize that
if you plan to submit her
to an inquisition,
there will be consequences.
Now that she's one of us,
the English Puritan Church
cannot stand by and do nothing.
[STIYL] Given that,
I hope you'll think twice
before turning your
blades against her.
Or have you mistaken me
for a man so chivalrous
he won't fight a woman when
the situation calls for it?
Uh! Fine, so we fight
two instead of one.
[TATEMIYA] It would
be unwise to assume
it's just the two of them.
[TATEMIYA] I get
that you're not really
the smartest kid in the world,
but you don't have to ask
what I'm doing here, do you?
Tatemiya?
[TATEMIYA] And here I thought
we'd arranged our plans
with the Puritans so carefully,
acting quickly so we could
get here before you
decided to play the hero
and make a move on your own.
Clearly, you're an even bigger
fool than I had imagined.
[chuckles]
But, hey, at least
you're foolishness
is always fun to watch.
[INDEX] You know,
Toma, when I said this
wasn't your responsibility,
I was hoping you'd
take the hint and butt
out for once in your life.
[KAMIJO] Good to see you, too.
[INDEX] But now you've
left us no choice, have you?
We're all here, aren't we?
So what do you say we
save Sister Orsola together?
Yeah!
Go! Kill the heathens!
[yelling]
[KAMIJO] Come on, let's go!
Do you think you'll be okay?
I'm fine.
She didn't do much.
Nothing that I can't
bear for now, anyway.
[KAMIJO]
She's amazing. So brave.
If I ever needed
a reason to fight...
I've got one now.
♪
[yelling]
Oh, uh. Thanks a lot!
Hmmm.
[TSUCHIMIKADO chuckles]
You up here for appreciation,
inspiration, or exhilaration?
Or all three, maybe?
Tsuchimikado.
C'mon, it's a
relief, isn't it?
Finding out that your old
pals weren't part of a plot
to kidnap Orsola and
use "The Book of the Law"
for their own nefarious
ends. That must be nice.
Right, you like the
sound of your own voice.
Why do I get the feeling
that you and your employers
were hoping to use
this opportunity to snatch
"The Book of the Law"
out from under them?
Hm.
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
You know the whole story
up to this point, right?
The Amakusa Church
did not, in fact,
steal "The Book of the Law."
That was a false charge
fabricated by the Catholics.
Which means... there was
never any need to bring
the Book all the way
here in the first place.
The Book that was brought
into this country is a phony.
The original
text remains hidden
deep in the stacks
of the Vatican Library.
So... are you satisfied now?
Hmph. Yes, I am.
As long as he's leading
them, they'll be fine.
[KANZAKI] The Amakusa
will follow the right path,
even without me.
[KAMIJO breathing heavily]
♪
[KAMIJO] Huahhh!
[NUN wimpers]
[ALL grunting]
Uh!
[KAMIJO] Ahhh!
[BOTH groaning]
[ORSOLA] Oh! That was quite
a fall. Are you alright?
I think... so.
Damn her!
[weapons clinking]
♪
Huh?
Ahhh--Uh!
♪
So many of them
taking on one little girl?
I don't think so!
[STIYL] No, stop!
[NUNS scream]
[STIYL] We don't want to get too
close to her right now, Amakusa.
[STIYL] If we interfere,
she won't be able to do
what she needs to as easily.
Haaahhh!
[NUNS scream]
[NUNS groan]
Whoa. What did
she just do to them?
[STIYL] That is "Sheol Fear."
It's a song that uses
all of the knowledge
that is laid out in the
one hundred and
three thousand volumes
and denounces the contradictions
those doctrines contain.
[STIYL] That song is a strong
defense against those who
blindly follow
doctrines of faith without
considering what is right.
[STIYL] Upon hearing it, their
minds collapse in on themselves,
albeit temporarily.
[STIYL] Grimoires are
not simply texts to be read.
Even without any magical power,
she has mastered the volumes.
I doubt there could ever be
a better candidate than her
to serve as the
librarian for the grimoires.
What I'd like to
know is if she had
this kind of trick
up her sleeve,
why didn't she use it
before things got ugly?
It is a peculiar attack.
[STIYL] It works on what
is called the "group mind,"
breaking down
collective mental barriers.
Accordingly, the
make-up of that group mind
is a factor to consider.
[NUNS screaming]
[STIYL] For example,
when we were fighting
your people earlier, Kamijo
and I were in the way,
so the purity was diminished,
and the attack would've
performed poorly.
[TATEMIYA] Well, I'm
glad that we weren't on
the receiving end of that.
[rumbling]
[chatter]
[ANGELENE] We shouldn't be here!
Stop clucking like
a bunch of scared hens.
[AGNESE] You're only
making fools of yourselves.
Especially you,
Sister Angelene.
[ANGELENE] It's just
that I'm worried about
our fellow sisters.
It's been more than ten minutes
since the fighting got underway.
It should have
been over by now,
but it keeps getting
more intense out there.
And what's worse is we
don't know what's happening.
There! See?
[ANGELENE] Was that
explosion just now
caused by our side or theirs?
There's no way for us to know
when we're waiting in here.
[ANGELENE] Please, don't you
think we should do something?
They can use all the
help we can give them!
[sighs]
[AGNESE] Very well. I release
you from your detail
as my bodyguard.
You may go outside and
join the lines of battle.
Oh! Thank you Sister Agnese,
we won't let you down!
♪
That filth
cannot avoid justice.
[AGNESE] There will
be no escape for them.
Those who do evil
shall be punished.
Such is the way of the Church.
[NUN screams]
[NUNS scream]
Forget about defense.
Sisters, we must attack.
[LUCIA] We must do
what is necessary to
defeat the enemies
of the Church.
[INDEX] Some kind
of magical attack?
[gasps]
♪
[INDEX] Did they? That's crazy!
[INDEX] They would go that far.
Just to avoid the Sheol Fear?
♪
♪ [Ending Song] ♪
[KAMIJO] The final
battle has begun.
We are surrounded on all
sides, under constant attack.
Is there any way to
get out of this alive?
Next time, "Lotus Wand."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.