[WEATHER LADY] And now
the weather for tomorrow,
September 14th.
Things look clear
throughout the day tomorrow,
but we are expecting to
see an increased chance
of scattered showers in
the evening and over night.
Hey, Toma!
I don't understand.
Yeah? Understand what?
[INDEX] It looks like
someone drew tree rings
all over the
weather lady's map.
But how does that tell what
the forecast is for tomorrow?
Oh, those are called
isobaric lines.
They look at the peaks
and valleys of pressure
to determine what the
weather's gonna be like.
[WEATHER LADY]
Now for local weather.
Okinawa will
be cloudy today...
[INDEX] So let me
get this straight.
Academy City has
found some artificial way
of making feng shui
readings come true?
Here ya' go.
Try it out Sphinx.
[meow]
[KAMIJO]
It's right off the stove,
so it's going to be
really hot. Be careful--
[meow]
Toma!
[KAMIJO] Ahhh!
[INDEX] No fair! You get mad at
me whenever I snatch food early,
but you just go
and give it to the cat?
He's not going to eat
everything in the pot
like somebody else I know.
Hey, I'm still confused.
Yeah?
[INDEX] Why does the
weather lady get it wrong?
Ya' know like, when she
says it'll rain one day
and then it doesn't.
Is it cute to be
scatterbrained or something?
Well, weather
forecasting's not
an exact science. Though,
until a little while ago,
[KAMIJO] it sure
seemed like it was here.
[INDEX] Hm?
[RADIO MAN] This is
Shuttle Two-Five-Eight.
Now retrieving
the Remnant. Over.
♪ [Opening Song] ♪
[MIKOTO] I don't know
how long I'm gonna be able
to put up with this.
Just because the Daihasei
Festival's coming up
doesn't mean they can have us
in gym class all day every day.
[KUROKO] I don't see
what choice they have.
Hm?
[KUROKO] I mean, Tokiwadai
Middle School did take a
humiliating second place
at last year's festival.
They want to make certain that
doesn't happen to us again.
I was wondering, Sissy,
do you have any
plans after school today?
Why do you ask?
[KUROKO] Oh, you know, once
in a while I'd like to go
shopping with you like
most friends would do.
Or maybe even just sit down and
have a little snack together.
We're like ships passing
in the night lately.
We barely spend
any time together.
I always seem to be busy
with my Judgment duties,
and you spend an inordinate
amount of time going
all over town looking
for Gekota accessories.
[KUROKO] To be perfectly
honest, it's been making
me feel pretty
lonely, you know.
[MIKOTO] Really?
[KUROKO chuckles]
I knew this was
the right approach!
I oh-so-subtly lay
on the guilt, and--
whether she wants
to admit it or not--
Sissy is totally considering
opening her arms to me
and welcoming my advances!
Excellent plan, Kuroko!
[laughing]
[MIKOTO] How could
we get a snack together?
You stuff your
face after Judgment,
so by the time you get
home, you aren't hungry.
And as for shopping,
we don't usually
like the same stores, so--
You're mine, Sissy!
[thud]
[KUROKO] Ahhh!
♪
[KUROKO] Checking the news?
There sure have
been a lot lately, huh?
If I recall correctly,
France, Russia, and Spain
have all had
shuttle launches.
Sissy, there seems to be
something bothering you.
Huh?
You can be honest
with me, you know.
Are you upset
about something?
Well, of course I am!
You pounced on me out
of nowhere, buck-naked.
That's not the kind of thing I
expect when I'm in the shower.
Now, just hurry up and finish
your shopping already, okay?
This isn't the kind
of store I normally go to.
[MIKOTO] It's embarrassing!
[KUROKO] You should take this
opportunity to find something
to wear that's worthy
of Tokiwadai's Ace!
[KUROKO] Like this little
number. Or this, maybe.
Or something like this.
Ohhh!
This looks like
bra padding!
I've never seen
you show any interest
in stuff like
this before, Sissy.
Wait, hold on. Are you
trying to impress a boy?
[MIKOTO] No! It's not like that!
Of course. How
could I ever think it?
You're not the type
to let yourself get
carried away with
a boy, are you, Sissy?
Ah-haaa!
[KUROKO] Wait a sec. Am I
forgetting what happened
on the last day
of summer vacation?
Oh no. I'm sure that
didn't mean anything to you.
[KUROKO] Right, Sissy?
It didn't, did-- Uh!
[KUROKO] She's got
that dreamy, dumbstruck,
far-away look in her eyes!
But that's impossible!
She can't actually be with
that troglodyte, can she?
Seriously though.
I was just browsing.
I'm not interested in those.
What's the point
in wearing them?
You'll get found out eventually
when you take
them off, won't you?
Say it's not so! You're
not just buying them,
you're already planning
on taking them off?
No, you're completely
misinterpreting this!
I was talking about
changing in the locker room!
[KUROKO'S phone ringing]
Oh no, your phone's
ringing. Better get it.
Perfect! Honestly, guys,
this is not the time!
Kuroko here. Uiharu,
what's up? A robbery?
[KUROKO] Big deal, Antiskill
can take care of it, can't they?
[KUROKO] In School District
23? You mean the one
that's working on
aerospace development?
[KUROKO] I'm sorry I have
to leave you like this, Sissy.
And after you so
kindly came along.
[MIKOTO] Don't worry about it.
But you should really
try to make it back
to the dorm early tonight.
You heard the weather report.
Things might get
ugly out this evening.
[KUROKO] Okay. I'll be careful.
[door opens]
Oh! Shirai, you're here!
Holding down
the fort, Uiharu?
Everybody else is out in
the field at the moment.
Hey, I know! Why don't
I put some tea on for us?
I do appreciate
the offer,
but I think I'm
going to pass for now.
Oh, really? But I
was looking forward to
acting like mature,
refined young ladies!
If you want to practice
your etiquette that badly,
we can do it another
time, I promise.
For now, just give me
an overview of the case.
[UIHARU] Here it is.
[KUROKO] What's happening there?
[KUROKO] That's not a phone.
It's a radio. Very interesting.
Looks like they're not the only
ones up to something, huh?
Look at this.
There's something else.
[KUROKO] That's School
District 23's emblem.
I've isolated the
model number, too.
The travel case that guy
in the video is carrying
is specially designed
to be completely airtight,
and what's more, to
counter cosmic radiation.
You know it sounds like
they were planning on
bringing their
cargo into space.
Either that or
they were actually
bringing it
back from space.
The quickest way to
find out what's going on
will probably be to
track down the robbers.
What escape
route did they take?
Looks like they
abandoned the cars
and went underground.
Huh?
Most likely because there
was some traffic signal
trouble in that area. Seems
like a heck of a coincidence,
don't you think?
Fortunately, it
should work in our favor.
Huh?
I want you to start hunting
down the men who got away.
Hey, wait! Come back!
[car horns honking]
[SUIT MAN 6A] Hurry it up!
Am I interrupting something?
Who the hell are you?
She's a teleporter!
[KUROKO] Hey, boys!
I'm over here now.
I'm with Judgment.
Do I really have to
explain what I'm doing here,
or can we go ahead
and skip the small talk?
[MEN grunt]
Hmm.
[SUIT MAN 6B] Damn!
[sighs]
[KUROKO] This guy's carrying
a low-tech hand gun.
Are they from outside the city?
[phone ringing]
[KUROKO] You have an
update for me, Uiharu?
[MIKOTO] Uh, Kuroko.
[KUROKO] Oh Sissy, it's you!
[MIKOTO] Yeah, it's me.
And I need a little favor.
Where are you?
[KUROKO] Oh, uh, I was just.
[MIKOTO] You're still at work,
aren't you? I'm sorry!
I didn't mean to bother you.
[KUROKO] No, no. Go on.
What's this favor you needed?
[MIKOTO] Well... I heard from
one of the underclassmen
that there's going to be
a surprise room inspection.
I was hoping you
could hide some of my,
you know, personal things.
[KUROKO] You haven't made it
back to the dorm yet, either?
[MIKOTO] Anyway, forget it.
Maybe I can ask somebody else.
You should try to get
back home soon, too.
It's supposed to
start raining tonight
and then all through
the day tomorrow! See ya!
[KUROKO] Wait, Sissy! Uggghhh!
I cannot let her turn to
someone else for a favor!
Especially when it's
personal! There's no choice.
I have to teleport to
the dorms immediately!
[KUROKO] Huh?
Ugh!
♪
[KUROKO] Just who
do you think you are?
[KUROKO] You're a teleporter.
My, my. You figured
me out already?
Guess it's not too
surprising coming from
someone who's
the same esper type.
[GIRL] Yes, I'm a teleporter.
My power is Move Point.
And unlike you.
I don't need to touch
an object with my
hand to relocate it.
Come on now. That must
impress you a little...
Miss Kuroko Shirai
from Judgment's
one hundred and
seventy-seventh branch.
[KUROKO] It'll
take more than that!
[KUROKO] Sorry.
Still not impressed!
[shaky breathing]
I tried to warn you.
I can move an object without
[GIRL] laying so
much as a finger on it.
You know, I'm surprised.
I know she's backed
into a corner and all,
but I really didn't
expect her to drag a friend
into her messy personal
affairs like this.
Mikoto Misaka, that is.
How do you... know that name?
[KUROKO] What does this
have to do with her?
[KUROKO] How do
you know that name?
What does this
have to do with her?
[MUSUJIME] Oh, come on. Don't
tell me you're out of the loop.
No way. She would
never involve somebody
without their knowledge.
I know that.
[GIRL] The Railgun of
Tokiwadai is the high and mighty
noble type, after all.
Wasn't it an awfully
convenient coincidence?
My people getting
caught in a traffic jam
after a signal outage?
[GIRL]
Let's review, shall we?
What kind of esper
is Tokiwadai's Ace?
You can't tell me
you don't know that.
I have no idea what
you're even talking about.
[GIRL] I'm talking about
the Remnant, though you don't
know what that means, do you?
And I suppose the
word "silicorundum"
is beyond your grasp as well.
I know. "The wreckage
of Tree Diagram."
Does that make sense to you?
The supercomputer
that's said to be
the brains of Academy City?
Though the machine itself is
derelict, its computational core
still has tremendous
potential remaining within it.
There's no way.
It can't be derelict.
It's still in its orbit.
This was attached to the report
about it being shot down.
Pretty clear, huh?
[GIRL] You see, Tree
Diagram has been destroyed
for some time now.
[GIRL] And now the entire
world is after its wreckage.
Otherwise known as the Remnant.
This must be a difficult
time for the Railgun.
The destruction of Tree
Diagram actually made her life
much easier. Her nightmare
was almost over.
If it can be
restored, however,
then the experiments she hates
so much will be held again.
[GIRL] So of course
I can understand why
she would be
fighting against it.
What experiments?
You're not playing
dumb, are you?
You actually don't have
any idea what's going on.
August 21st mean anything?
[GIRL] Looking at you right
now, I can't help but wonder
if things had turned
out differently,
would you and I have
possibly become friends?
[LAST ORDER] Cannonball!
Misaka Misaka executes
an expert landing!
And then it's
splash-splash-splashy-splash
as she kicks her way out
to freedom in the open sea!
[ACCELERATOR] I get that you're
tiny. But I can't believe that
this crappy little bathroom
could feel spacious to anyone,
not even a small fry like you.
"Can't use Reflection.
I Bet that's no fun. Aww,"
says Misaka Misaka,
with a pretend look
of pity on her face.
[LAST ORDER] "And now it
looks like you're crying!
Is the shampoo too harsh?
Does it hurt the poor esper's
eyes?" asks Misaka Misaka.
I'm not crying, you brat!
And you know what else? If
I could use your network
to calculate my
reflection, I just--
[ACCELERATOR] Yomikawa!
Why do I have to take care of
this filthy little urchin?
It's not like we have a choice.
What a drag. Damn that Kikyo.
Why is she always dumping
her problems on me like this?
Oh well, I guess
it is what it is.
At least these kids don't seem
to need too much looking after.
[ACCELERATOR] Yomikawa!
[UIHARU] Good news. I've
determined the name of
the esper who
attacked you, Shirai.
[UIHARU] Awaki Musujime.
She's a second year from
Kirigaoka Girls'
School and a Level 4.
Her ability is
called Move Point.
As you reported, she is
able to relocate objects
from a distance,
without touching them.
Technically speaking,
spatial replacement
from coordinate A
to coordinate B.
I know that. Did you
find out anything else?
[UIHARU] Let me see. It
looks like she's no good
at blocking espers of the
same type. And it says here,
she seems to have hesitations
about teleporting herself.
Likely because she was badly
hurt doing so two years ago.
[UIHARU] And one more thing,
though this is unconfirmed,
she's supposedly
one of the Guides.
Guides to what?
[UIHARU] To the building that
doesn't have doors or windows.
You mean the
Academy City Governing
Board Director's home
office? How can that be?
I thought that was
just an urban legend--Auh.
[UIHARU] Are you okay?
It sounds like
you're hurting, Shirai.
[KUROKO] Never mind.
Just keep reporting.
If you're sure.
According to Antiskill,
the victims of the
robbery, the men in suits,
are all secure now.
And as for their identity,
[UIHARU] it says
they're couriers who were
hired by School District 23.
Apparently a
psychometrist was called in
to read their memories,
but as to what's
inside the case,
they knew nothing.
[KUROKO] To sum up, the
suit guys were delivering
the contents of a
travel case to some
research facility
for School District 23,
but their cargo was stolen
from them by Musujime's group.
[KUROKO] The Remnant.
Tree Diagram's wreckage.
This must be a difficult
time for the Railgun.
To think, her nightmare
was almost over.
But you should really
try to make it back
to the dorm early tonight.
You heard the weather report.
Things might get
ugly out this evening.
[UIHARU] Are you still there?
[gasps]
[UIHARU] So, um. Don't you
think it would be better if
we go ahead and let
Antiskill take over this case?
I'm starting to think
maybe this is more than
we can handle by ourselves.
[distant door opens and closes]
[KUROKO] I have to go.
[UIHARU] Huh?
[MIKOTO] Kuroko?
[KUROKO] Oh, hi, Sissy.
You're finally back!
[MIKOTO] Monopolizing
the bathroom, huh?
Is it too much
trouble for you to
turn on the room
light when you get home?
Hey, I'm just doing my
part to conserve energy.
You know how concerned
I am about the environment
and things like that.
[MIKOTO] Hmm. But Academy
City is mainly powered
by wind energy,
so there's not really
much to conserve, is there?
[KUROKO] Yeah. Okay,
I give. You caught me.
I admit I turned the room
light off in the hopes that
I could then lure
you into the bathroom,
where we would share a
romantic interlude together.
[MIKOTO chuckles] Yeah, right.
[KUROKO] So, anyway, where
have you been all evening?
[MIKOTO] Oh. I guess you
could say I've been out
collecting accessories I haven't
been able to get 'til now.
But I'm having a
hard time finding them!
I just came back
here to get something
that I had forgotten
to take with me.
So I'm gonna be heading back
out for a little while longer.
Okay. Well, stay dry.
The weather is so
unpredictable lately,
and you really
can't put any stock in
the forecasts anymore,
have you noticed that?
[MIKOTO] Uh, yeah. Well,
thanks for worrying about me.
I'll try to head back
home as soon as possible.
[door opens and closes]
[KUROKO] What's wrong, Sissy?
[KUROKO] Why did she
bring up August 21st?
That evening, an
unexplained windstorm
swept through the city.
A rail switchyard in School
District 17 was devastated,
and then the next day...
Huh?
♪
[KUROKO] Uiharu. Let's
look into Musujime's group.
I think they're working
with an organization
outside Academy City.
[KUROKO]
Can you run a simulation
of their escape route?
I'm really sorry
about this, Sissy.
[KUROKO] Whatever is
going on behind the scenes,
I think it's hurting
you more than
any of the rest
of us can imagine.
[KUROKO] And you're
doing everything you can
to keep us from
getting involved.
So I feel like I should
apologize upfront because
I fully intend on sticking
my nose into your business
and putting a stop
to the nightmare
that Musujime talked about.
[distant explotion]
[KUROKO] I'm coming, Sissy!
[electric charge]
Come on out of there
already, you coward!
Or do you plan on
sneaking around all night?
[MEN] Ahh!
Alright, Sissy.
[MUSUJIME] chuckles
So much taunting.
You're in quite a hurry today.
You really must be desperate
to prevent the Remnant
from being reintegrated.
The thought of the experiments
starting up again
must terrify you.
You should shut up.
Ha. You could try to
forget about them, you know.
The experiments
were the only reason
they were created
in the first place.
[MUSUJIME] Why not
let them be destroyed
like they were meant to be?
You can't really mean that!
[MUSUJIME] Let's be honest.
In the end, you're doing
all of this for your own sake.
Personal pride, your
honor, your sense of duty.
Every action you're
taking right now
is because you're pissed off.
[MIKOTO] You're right.
I am pretty damn pissed off.
No matter what I do,
I can't seem to stop people
from getting hurt! That idiot.
Did she really think
I wasn't going to notice?
Just hearing her, I
knew something was wrong.
She's hurting.
All because of me.
[MIKOTO] So, yeah. You figured
it out. I'm pissed off.
At my sweet,
ridiculous roommate,
at the scum sitting before me,
but mostly at the person
who started all of this.
Which is me by the way!
You're so self-sacrificing
it makes me sick.
Why can't you act like
any halfway normal person
would in your situation
and play the victim?
At any rate, I can't sit around
and chat anymore right now.
[MUSUJIME] You're not
going to capture me.
One way or another,
I'm leaving.
[MIKOTO] You really
think you can get away?
I know everything you've
got up your sleeve.
So you're not going anywhere.
What, you think that I
won't attack your friends?
Look more closely.
They may be mine or they may
just be innocent bystanders.
[MUSUJIME] How do you propose
to tell the difference?
Okay, enough observing
from the sidelines.
I think It's time
for me to get involved.
Well, I sure hope you're
ready for this, Kuroko.
You're heading right into
the heart of the battlefield.
And once you're there,
turning back is not
going to be an option.
"If this is
really true, then...
I need to hurry. This
is no time to be in bed,"
says Misaka, reassessing
her priorities
in a practical manner.
[MISAKA 10032] "It is past
curfew, and thus against
the rules to be out and about.
But I cannot simply remain
here," rationalizes Misaka,
using her emergency
excuse to convince herself.
"Every last moment
counts at this point.
Matters are going
downhill rapidly,
and action must be taken
at once," says Misaka.
♪ [Ending Song] ♪
[KAMIJO] Kuroko Shirai
and Awaki Musujime.
The battle between
teleporters begins.
The Sisters set out
in search of the Remnant,
and then there's her.
Next time, "Move Point."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.