♪ [Opening Song] ♪
[gasps]
[ANGELENE] I call you.
Matthew the Apostle!
[ANGELENE] Look out! Ah!
Ahhh!
Sister Angelene!
[LUCIA] Sister Angelene!
[TATEMIYA] Pathetic.
Only the lowliest forms
of life turn on their own.
We'll squash you
like the bugs you are.
You can use this.
What is it?
It's a submersible
craft for quick getaways.
[TATEMIYA] You should get the
injured sister off this ship.
Good. You're all
right, Sister Lucia.
But it feels like
your hand's trembling.
How could it not be?
Don't be worried.
I'm not going to die here.
I'll make it. I will.
[ANGELENE] We're all going
back together, aren't we?
You and me, Sister
Agnese, The Amakusa,
and the strange
people who brought them.
We're in this together,
working for the same goal.
With so much to
live for, I can't die.
So please don't worry about me.
[ANGELENE] Leave me here
and fight with the others.
Carry out the
mission we came for.
[gasp]
[KAMIJO] Go ahead and
say something to her, Lucia.
I'll look out for
you two while you talk.
I'm happy to stay here
and hold off these traitors
for as long as it's necessary.
[KAMIJO] So take
whatever time you need.
Reassure Angelene
that she's done more
than we could ever ask of her.
Let her know that in
the end, whatever happens,
everything she's fought for
tonight has been worth it.
[LUCIA] Right. I swear to
you, I'll fight to protect
the others, and that means
the only person you need
to fight for
right now is yourself.
Mmm.
[grunts]
♪
[BIAGIO] We still haven't
dealt with the intruders?
Ridiculous! We can reduce
an entire city to rubble,
but a handful of heretics
gives us this much trouble?
[BIAGIO] Hmph,
that face of yours.
Unbelievable. After
everything that's happened,
you still have the
self-assured look of someone
who expects to be rescued.
You really think I need
somebody to rescue me?
[BIAGIO] Ha. I'm about
to relieve you of your
comforting illusions.
Don't worry. There's not
much time left for fear.
[TATEMIYA] Go! Do
whatever you have to do.
Come back here when
you have the girl.
[KAMIJO] Let's go!
We need to find Agnese.
♪
I'm confused. There doesn't
seem to be anyone here.
The absence of personnel
indicates this ship is
the magical control
center for the fleet.
You think that's
why the other sisters
have stopped pursuing us?
[INDEX] Give me a minute.
I'm gonna see if I
can unlock this door.
[KAMIJO] I'm tired of waiting.
Why don't we try a more
direct approach instead
and see if that
gets quicker results.
That was strange.
It's made out of blocks.
I wonder if this ship is
different than the
escort craft in that
the whole thing has
magical significance.
[ALL gasp]
[KAMIJO] The suits
of armor! Damn it!
[ORSOLA] Inside!
[KAMIJO] Hold on!
[ALL heavy breathing]
You two go ahead, okay?
[INDEX] Toma!
How are you doing back there?
Are you feeling better?
Don't worry.
I'll be all right.
[LUCIA] Now, then.
How do I get past them?
[TATEMIYA] Disgusting!
And dishonorable!
[gasps]
You should be ashamed.
What kind of vermin
threaten an injured girl?
[KAMIJO] Oh, great! A dead end!
[yells]
[KAMIJO] Where am I?
[distant rumble]
[KAMIJO] Whoa! Another one?
Ah!
[grunts]
Is that all of them?
[phone ringing]
[beep]
Uh, hello?
[ORSOLA] Oh, good!
Your phone is still working.
Is that you, Orsola?
Yeah, it's us. Can you
confirm that a spell
called the Rosary of the
Appointed Time is required
in order to activate the
Queen of the Adriatic Sea?
[KAMIJO]
That's what I was told.
[INDEX] Well, there's nothing
in any of the grimoires to
indicate that such a spell
is necessary for activation.
Yeah? Why do you think they
would need to do it, then?
[INDEX] I'm guessing
it's something specific to
the Roman Orthodoxy,
but I'm not exactly sure what.
[KAMIJO yells]
[gasps]
[BIAGIO] Your hand is powerful.
Ha. Don't tell me
that you're jealous.
[BIAGIO] On the contrary,
I find it disgraceful.
It rejects the blessings
bestowed by the Lord.
But even more
unacceptable than its nature
is the way you
brandish it like a weapon.
Were I you, I would not be
so proud of such an appendage.
[BIAGIO] Clearly you are a
heathen who has never heard
the voice of the Almighty.
If you had a shred of decency,
you would do all in your power
to receive the
blessings of the Lord,
even if it meant
severing your hand.
But I don't expect
my words to help you
find your way to the path.
And so, as a bishop, a
different sort of duty calls me.
To help you shuffle off
that burdensome mortal coil.
You're the bishop
in charge of this fleet?
Then you know where
Sister Agnese is, don't you?
I'm afraid that won't
help you very much, however.
Knowing and telling you are
two completely different things.
[heavy exhale]
The cross is the symbol
of the struggle against
that which is evil.
[yells]
Uh!
Ah!
[BIAGIO] The cross
is mighty. It stands firm
against the enemy, endowing the
believer with holy strength,
its reach is long indeed.
Allow me to show you.
Despite its greatness, the
cross is a symbol of humility,
given to man to remind
him of his weaknesses
and capacity for failure.
Which you will
understand in a moment.
[KAMIJO groans]
He's crazy!
[BIAGIO] Filthy heathen.
Must your kind always
be so destructive?
I wouldn't want you to interrupt
the preparations for the spell.
Yeah, what spell is that?
[BIAGIO] The Rosary
of the Appointed Time.
Surely you won't deny
knowledge of it at this point.
Who cares? It doesn't
matter, because I'm gonna
find Agnese and
get her out of here.
Once again you make clear
your intention to deny
the will of the Lord. Thus
proving that you are evil.
And I have already shown
you how my crosses fight evil.
Who do you think you are?
What the hell makes you
think you have the right
to reduce Venice
to rubble? Megalomaniac!
Fool, I have no interest in
destroying the City of Water.
What are you saying?
[BIAGIO] What I have planned
is infinitely more interesting
than whatever it is
you seem to have in mind.
Here's a question for
you, what do you suppose
the Church of the
Cross considers to be
the most important
instrument in the world?
Huh?
[BIAGIO chuckles] Give up?
The instrument of execution!
The sympathy of Simon
led him to bear the cross
to the crucifixion.
[groans]
What the...?
The cross is the symbol
of the struggle against
that which is evil.
♪
[ORSOLA] What is this?
[INDEX gasps]
A defensive spell's
been set here!
Huh?
C-A-H.
You go and find Agnese.
[INDEX] Go on! I'll
try to draw them away!
[ORSOLA] Be careful!
♪
[door opening]
[AGNESE] Orsola Aquinas?
I'm so glad you're all right.
Why are you here?
You and the boy were supposed
to find the other sisters
and get away from the fleet.
[AGNESE] You know what
they're planning, don't you?
Anyone who can,
should get out now!
Everybody knows
what's going on here,
but even the Amakusa agreed
we should come and rescue you.
[ORSOLA] No one will even
consider leaving you behind,
especially not the
sisters you were so willing
to sacrifice yourself for.
The Amakusa? They can't
have forgotten my involvement
in the Book of the Law fiasco.
After everything I've done,
how could they possibly
be willing to help me?
I don't have
the answer to that.
You'll have to
ask them yourself.
[ORSOLA] Of course, it may
have helped that Sisters Lucia
and Angelene were
determined to rescue you,
whatever the cost.
They knew the
situation was dangerous
and might turn desperate,
and that they were
risking their own lives.
But to them it was worth it.
As long as it meant the three of
you could all be together again.
If that's not reason enough for
you, I don't know what will be.
[BIAGIO] You don't think
I'd let you get away
that easily, do you?
[BOTH gasp]
You aren't all
that important to us.
Our plans will proceed,
with or without you.
[BIAGIO] However, finding
another suitable candidate
would be such a nuisance.
And I do hate nuisances.
I find them to
be so very annoying.
[ORSOLA] Is that blood?
From another nuisance I
ran into a short while ago.
[BIAGIO] I was forced
to crush that one
rather violently, I'm afraid.
I sincerely hope
we can avoid that here
and opt for a
more peaceful solution.
It wouldn't do to have
you severely damaged
before it's time.
[ORSOLA] This weapon you're
planning to use against Venice,
why choose to activate it now?
You are opposing us,
and yet you don't even realize
what it is we're actually doing.
You're a bunch of blind fools
but in my beneficence,
I will enlighten you.
[BIAGIO] As you may know,
the Queen of the Adriatic Sea
is a weapon created solely
for use against Venice.
It is capable of
unleashing incredible power.
But that isn't
much good as long as
its targeting
restrictions are in place.
Then what are you planning t--
[gasps]
Ah, finally figured
it out, have you?
[BIAGIO] Removing the
geographical limitations
of the Queen of
the Adriatic Sea.
That is what the Rosary of the
Appointed Time is designed for.
So, you plan to use
the spell not on Venice,
but on a city that you
believe stands in the way
of the Church's domination.
[BIAGIO] Now you
are on the right track!
Thanks to the weapon's
ingenious design,
every shred of that
place will be destroyed.
And, as you said,
it is not just any city,
but one whose philosophies
stand in direct opposition
to the Church's advancement.
[ORSOLA] You're talking
about Academy City!
[laughs]
The city that's at the
heart of all scientific
and technological
advancement in the world, yes.
With all of that eliminated,
things will change
for Mother Church. Our
path will be clear at last.
The heathens who
have stood in our way
for so long will be no more.
Their flock will find itself
lost and will turn to
the Church for guidance.
[ORSOLA] You think the
church taking over will
bring happiness to everyone?
[BIAGIO] No, of course not!
There are impure people
on the side of magic
as well as science.
But they are
less of a concern.
And, in due time,
they too will be purged.
Your plan is evil!
I act out the
will of the Church.
My every move is sanctified.
[BIAGIO] The cross is the symbol
of the struggle against evil.
Uh! Ugh...
[BIAGIO] Give up, Sister Orsola.
All of your fighting is futile.
The cross was given
to man to remind him
of his capacity for failure!
[yells]
[BIAGIO] Sister. It's
a bit earlier than I had
intended to start,
but let us proceed.
You should be rejoicing!
Yours will be the
honor of killing more of
the Church's enemies
at one time than anyone
has done in all of history.
Oh? You're leaving
something out of
your description, aren't you?
Sister Agnese herself is among
the enemies you wish to kill.
[BIAGIO] You truly
have become a member of
the English Puritan
Church, haven't you?
That is why you're worried.
[ORSOLA] Your actions are
dictated by Church dogma,
wholly controlled by
your religious affiliation.
So you cannot understand
it when someone acts
based on their emotions.
Or, you understand
but you can't
bring yourself to believe it.
Stand aside, Orsola.
[gasps]
Whatever you do, you
won't be able to stop him
from going through with this,
but if you don't resist,
there is a chance you'll
live through what's to come.
Please, I can't sit
back and do nothing!
[BIAGIO] You really should
listen to her, Sister Orsola.
And as for you, Sister Agnese.
Prepare yourself for your part
in the Church's
greatest triumph!
What do you
think you're doing?!
All things in harmony.
Fifth of the Five Elements,
symbolizing peace and order,
deploy this crosier!
Stop this immediately, Sister!
You'll gain nothing by trying
to stand in the Church's way!
Ha! That's where you
and I disagree, old man.
[AGNESE] I will
fight you to the end.
And if you think
you can continue holding
the welfare of Sisters Lucia
and Angelene over my head,
you'll have to think again.
They're beyond your reach now,
but even if they
weren't, I know they would
want me to oppose
you and your plans.
[AGNESE] And that's
what I intend to do!
Heh.
In your heart, you know
that standing with the Church
is the right thing to do!
The sympathy of Simon led him to
bear the cross
to the crucifixion.
[AGNESE struggling]
[struggling]
[AGNESE] Uh!
[groans]
[chuckles]
[AGNESE] As I recall, the
scripture does not indicate
that Simon chose to shoulder
the burden of the Son of God
because his heart
was moved to pity.
Indeed, he was
given no choice at all.
The Romans compelled
him to carry the cross.
So you say.
Forcing others to bear
the burden of your sins,
that's what you're doing.
Still, the stench of
corruption clings to you.
However you might try
to hide behind the will
of the Church, you are the
architect of this unholy plan.
The responsibility will
rest on your shoulders.
You can't escape divine justice.
Ah!
Oh dear, you seem to have
dropped your crosier.
You'll need to keep a
better grip on your weapon
if you hope to defeat me.
[KAMIJO] Is that so?
'Cause I've got a pretty
decent grip on my weapon.
Nuisance!
Why are you still here?!
Next time you kill someone,
you should really
make sure they're dead.
So, should we pick
up where we left off?
You know, pitting my right
hand against your crosses
and your big mouth!
Too slow!
I'm not falling
for that one again!
♪
Agnese.
Uh. Yes?
Thanks for your help.
[KAMIJO] If you hadn't
been protecting Orsola,
things might have turned
out a whole lot worse.
Hmph.
[KAMIJO] Okay then.
[giggles]
So. What do I have to
do to make sure the Bishop
[KAMIJO] is unable to
go forward with his plan?
[AGNESE] Let me think.
He did imply that this room,
at least, was irreplaceable.
If there was some way
to demolish it entirely,
that could work.
I think, anyway.
Ah!
Agnese!
[whimpering
[KAMIJO]
What's happening to her?
[chuckles]
[ORSOLA] It's the Rosary
spell! He's activated it!
He's using that
glowing charm he's got
to do something
to Sister Agnese!
Heh. I can't
activate the spell.
Looks as if I'll
have to change the plan.
[BIAGIO] We'll have to
settle for a different outcome,
but still spectacular.
The Roman Orthodox
Church worried that
someone might co-opt the
Queen of the Adriatic Sea
and find a way to
turn it against them,
so they put all kinds of
contingency plans in place.
[BIAGIO] And what do you suppose
the very last option was?
Go on, I bet
you can figure it out
if you just give
it a moment's thought!
[KAMIJO gasps] Self-destruct!
♪
[BIAGIO] Impressive, no? This
is a large-scale magical device
fueled by the labor of sinners
sentenced to this fleet.
I tell you now, it's
virtually indestructible.
So if you're hoping to
stop it by smashing the walls
or the floor, I'm afraid
you're out of luck.
Once the device is activated,
the explosive force
will devastate anything
in ten kilometers.
[ORSOLA] The casualties
will be astronomical!
[groaning]
[KAMIJO] Agnese!
[screaming]
[KAMIJO] Orsola take her
and go on without me.
Round up the Amakusa, and
all of you get out of here.
But what are
you going to do?
Find a way to
stop this bastard.
I'll catch up
with you guys later.
I promise, okay? Now get going!
[ORSOLA] No, I--
[pained whimpers]
Fine, we'll go. But you
better keep your promise.
[BIAGIO] I didn't want to do
it. Those bastards said it was
a great deed that would
go down in Church history.
I told them that the world
wasn't ready for something
as extreme as this...
but they didn't listen,
and now here I am.
And you're dragging
everyone down with you.
You really can't stand bearing
the burden alone, can you?
I have devoted myself
wholly to the Church.
There is no turning back now.
[BIAGIO] That is what
it means to have faith,
never abandoning the path!
It is my beliefs and not
my emotions that guide me!
I am a soldier taking
orders for a righteous cause.
No matter the
consequence, I will do
what I have been
instructed to do.
[KAMIJO] You're insane!
That is the true
power of the Church!
The inexhaustible
tenacity of its followers!
Soon I shall be counted among
the truest and most faithful!
And so, with this final
attack, I offer my entire self
to the Church body,
mind, and soul!
I don't think so!
The cross is the symbol of
the struggle against evil!
The cross was given
to man to remind him
[BIAGIO] of his
capacity for failure!
[KAMIJO yells]
The cross is the symbol
of the struggle against evil!
[KAMIJO groans]
I confess I am surprised
you would go to these lengths
for one such as Sister Agnese.
[BIAGIO] No one person
is worth such a sacrifice,
much less a filthy
traitor like her.
I will never be
able to understand you.
You dirty heretic!
[KAMIJO] I wouldn't expect
you to. This ends now!
The cross is the symbol
of the struggle against evil!
It's over, Biagio!
[BIAGIO] Your left hand?
[BIAGIO] What's this? You're
using my own attack against me?
[yells]
[BIAGIO yells]
[KAMIJO] Don't forget this.
[KAMIJO] If you even think
about coming after Agnese
and the others, I'll be
there to make sure you pay.
♪
Look, he's opening his eyes!
You've been unconscious.
How are you feeling?
Are you okay?
You look pretty pale!
You're in an awfully
good mood considering
I'm in the hospital.
[KAMIJO] Let me guess. It's
because I didn't leave you
behind this time?
Uh. I don't know
what you're talking about.
My mood is normal.
Oh, hey. You have a phone call.
[FROG DOCTOR] Listen.
You need to make your way back
to Academy City at once.
Huh?
[FROG DOCTOR] Having an
outside hospital checking out
that unusual body of yours
might not be a good idea.
There should be a
supersonic passenger plane
at the airport,
courtesy of Academy City.
[KAMIJO] But, I haven't even
been in Italy for a whole day!
Oh, and one more thing.
A girl was here looking
for you and asked me to
pass on a message.
Seemed important.
Hm?
[FROG DOCTOR] "Hope you haven't
forgotten the Daihasei Festival.
You better be ready
for the penalty game!"
[KAMIJO] No! Anyone but her!
Wait, where are you taking me?
Please, I don't
wanna go back there!
[KANZAKI] So, it went well.
Is that the whole story?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Yeah.
You know, if you want a full
debriefing report, you
can always ask the Amakusa.
I hardly think
that's necessary.
I'm not a member of
the Amakusas anymore.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, anyway, you sure
caused Kami an awful lot
of trouble again, didn't you?
I don't see how you
can possibly pay him back
without some serious nudity,
or a little role-playing, maybe.
Hey, I know! I've got
this fallen angel maid outfit
you could use. Totally sexy!
Kami won't know what hit him!
I think you're taking this
a little too far, don't you?
And if you do own
an outfit like that,
I really don't
want to know why!
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Come on
now! I know you're one of
less than twenty
saints in the world,
but you still need to know
how to show proper grat--
[panting]
[sighs]
♪ [Ending Song] ♪
[chuckles]
Hi. I'm at your service, Toma.
[door bell rings]
Hey! Well, I made
it back from Italy.
Oh.
And, funny story,
I seem to have picked up
a little extra
baggage along the way.
[POPE] I have to say,
I am not entirely satisfied
with how things
have proceeded so far.
[WOMAN] And I'm not entirely
satisfied with your tone.
That level of insubordination
borders on blasphemy.
Do you know to whom
you are speaking?
Sure old man;
you're the Pope.
And do you know how much I care?
Make one move to
threaten me and it'll be
the last thing
you'll ever do.
The Right Seat of God.
You people don't
respect anybody, do you?
[WOMAN] I'm just gonna need
you to look this over real quick
and then sign it.
[POPE] Should I
assume that's an order?
[gasps] Hold on!
This document says...
Oh, it's nothing you weren't
thinking of ordering yourself
when the time
was right. [chuckles]
Hmm...
[KAMIJO] Academy City
calmly enters in to autumn.
Everything seems peaceful, but
I still have a promise to keep.
What have I gotten myself into?
Next time, "Penalty Game."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.