♪
[AGNESE] We've established
that the Amakusa force
is stationed within
Parallel Sweets Park.
However, we were
unable to find Orsola
or "The Book of the Law."
Do you think...
that Orsola's been...?
[AGNESE] Mm.
The Amakusa's
objective during the course
of this mission
will be to figure out
how to decipher
"The Book of the Law."
And you can bet as long as
that's what they're after,
[AGNESE] Orsola will
be completely safe.
Okay.
So, here's the plan:
we'll distract the main
Amakusa force by
charging them head-on.
Meanwhile, you
will sweep the park.
If you locate either
Orsola or the Book,
I ask that you
take them into custody
until I can arrive
and secure them.
Unless we destroy
the vortex for
their Microcosmic
Pilgrimage, they may still
be able to
escape with her.
Unfortunately,
we can't affect
the vortex itself until
it opens at midnight.
[AGNESE] And the window
during which we can
operate is smaller
than I'd like.
Approximately
five minutes, correct?
Yeah.
If five minutes have
passed and you haven't
found either target,
get out of the area at once.
After successfully
neutralizing the Amakusa,
we will personally
search the park, if need be.
Finding a nun and a grimoire,
destroying a vortex...
in five minutes.
[STIYL] Sounds like
we're going to be
on a pretty tight schedule.
[weapons clanking]
What they have
done is unforgivable.
[AGNESE] The church of the
cross's influence spread because
its original purpose was to
help people who were in need.
To turn that idea
around like this.
The use of force
for personal gain
is not the way of the Church.
♪ [Opening Song] ♪
♪
[KAMIJO] Can we do this?
[STIYL] Do what?
The plan. You think
we can really accomplish
everything we need to
in the time that we have?
[STIYL] It'll be a close
call, that's for sure.
And one more thing.
There's a piece of information
I didn't give
our sister friends.
Huh?
Kanzaki is supposed
to be in England.
But she seems to have vanished.
Kanzaki?
Helping her
one-time subordinates,
or rather, I mean
colleagues, of course.
It's possible
that the Amakusa
are hoping to
inflict critical damage.
If that's the case, their
saint may come calling.
So, no. I'm not
at all certain we can
accomplish everything
we're supposed to.
[KAMIJO] Okay, then.
If we have to choose,
Orsola should
be our top priority.
That should work
as well as anything.
Without someone
who can decode it,
"The Book of the Law"
is virtually useless.
I agree with you, too.
We put Orsola first.
I've decided that I'm
coming into the park as well,
whether you
like it or not, Toma.
There're already
so few of us as it is.
We need to stick
together to do this!
All right, you win.
We'll do our best.
"We'll do our best." Come
on, man, couldn't you have
found something
less cheesy to say?
[distant rumbling]
The diversion is starting now.
Then we're up.
[ALL breathing heavy]
[breathing heavy]
[bang]
Ah!
[KAMIJO] Get down!
[STIYL] Kamijo!
Heads up!
What's this?
If you wanna
get out of this alive,
carry that on your person!
Huh? Whoa!
I'm coming!
Stiyl! Index!
Where'd they go?
Wait... if the
plan was to retreat,
shouldn't we have
decided on a signal?
I see now. I'm the decoy!
♪
[sigh]
I wonder why he gave me this.
What am I supposed
to do with it?
[distant rumble]
[KAMIJO] Ahhh!
[running footsteps]
Uh... Auhhh!
♪
I hope Index and Stiyl
are doing okay.
Now, how am I
supposed to find Orsola?
Huh?
[KAMIJO grunts]
[muffled wimpering]
[KAMIJO] Orsola?
Ah! You're the
boy who helped me
at the bus stop, aren't you?
[ORSOLA] What are you
doing here? It's dangerous!
[heavy exhale]
I came to rescue you.
Why else would I be here?
Oh! Really? You're
risking your life to
help somebody who is
virtually a stranger to you?
Yeah.
You're not doing it for
"The Book of the Law"?
I don't really care
about some dusty old book.
Look at me. Do I seem
like the type of guy
[KAMIJO] who goes hunting
in amusement parks
for secret religious texts?
Oh...
I suppose you don't.
I should thank you
for your kindness.
Yeah, don't worry about it.
Now, what are you doing here?
[ORSOLA] Uh...
Something was happening.
So I took advantage
of the distraction
and managed to slip away.
[KAMIJO] Hmm...
Oh. Thank you.
It's nice to
have my hands free.
But how did you do that?
It should have
been more difficult.
Uh...
That's a bit hard to explain.
It's kinda just
this thing that I do.
If I tried to
tell you everything,
it would only
sound more complicated.
She couldn't have
gotten very far.
Find her!
From the sound of it,
they're looking for you.
Yeah.
Well, fortunately, I happen
to know they can't use
their special transport
until twelve oh five.
So we should be alright if we
just hide here until time is up.
[ORSOLA] Oh, dear!
Uh...
Let me dry you off.
We don't want you catching
a summer cold, now do we?
Um... no.
There's something I've
been wanting to ask.
Are you affiliated with
the Roman Orthodox Church?
Well. I do have a friend
who is English Puritan.
[ORSOLA] Do I
have this correct?
You are not a member of
the Roman Orthodox Church.
However, you are affiliated
with the English Puritans?
No. I wouldn't exactly
say "affiliated."
I understand wanting
to live a secular life.
I know from experience
how complicated
the world of the church
can be. It's not always easy.
You're probably better
off in the temporal sphere
than you would be
in the religious one.
Hmmm.
Of course, given
the company that I keep,
it's probably not surprising
that I'm carrying this.
[ORSOLA gasps]
How lovely. Did an
English Puritan friend
of yours give that to you?
Yeah. You're welcome to
hang onto it if you would like.
I don't know what to
do with it, myself.
That is very generous
of you. But are you sure?
[KAMIJO] Yep.
Oh...!
Then I would ask just one
more favor of you, if I may.
Um, okay.
If it's not too much
trouble, I would be grateful
if you would personally
place it around my neck.
Yeah. I suppose I could.
[shaky breathing]
What is it? Is
something the matter?
No! Nothing at all.
Everything's fine.
[KAMIJO breathing heavily]
So what's your story, anyway?
From what I've
heard, you know how
to read "The Book of the Law."
Oh. It's not so much
that I can "read" it.
Rather, I can decipher
its cryptography--
[gasps]
Oh, no, sorry! I was
really just wondering why
you would want to be involved
with a book like that at all.
[KAMIJO] I hear it's
actually pretty dangerous.
It began as a desire
for power. As much as
I'd like to, that is something
about my motives I cannot deny.
But the power of a
grimoire is tainted.
It is something that can never
bring happiness to anybody.
It causes only conflict.
[ORSOLA] In its wake is a
trail of destruction and death.
Why did I learn
how to decode it?
Because by investigating
its inner workings,
I hoped I would find a
way to destroy the grimoire.
[distant rumble]
[KAMIJO] Stiyl!
[STIYL groan]
Wha-What are you doing?
[STIYL] Hurry and get out--
[MAN chuckles]
Why are you lounging
around in the dirt?
Is that just how you
English Puritans fight?
Well, come on.
Get back up on your feet,
and let's see what
you're capable of. Do it now.
Nobody denies Saiji
Tatemiya of the Amakusa.
[TATEMIYA] A nice try but
not especially impressive.
You can't even defend
one small girl, huh?
[gasps]
Hey, Stiyl, you want to
tell me what's going on here?
It appears that
you know more than I do.
Looks as if you've managed
to take custody of Orsola,
and, like always,
it's difficult to judge
whether your luck is
a blessing or a curse.
[TATEMIYA] I've told you this
over and over again, Orsola.
Why won't you
hear what I'm saying?
We are not the enemy.
We do not intend to
harm a hair on your head.
I hear you. I understand
what you've told me
so many times now, and I
think you may even believe it.
[ORSOLA] Unfortunately.
I have a hard time believing
that a man's
intentions are peaceful
when he is
brandishing a weapon.
Well, that's a real shame.
I guess you'll have
to run back into the arms
of Mother Church
then, won't you?
What? An unarmed kid now?
[TATEMIYA] That looks
like Uragami's sword.
Did you take it from her?
You mean the girl who
attacked me, she's over there.
[KAMIJO] Don't worry. She's
not dead. Only unconscious.
Still breathing or not,
you harmed one of my people.
I want her returned safely!
[KAMIJO] You must
not be too bad a guy.
not if you care so much about
one of your subordinates.
Why don't you
put your sword away?
It'll be for the best.
I'd rather not fight somebody
who I could maybe respect.
[TATEMIYA] Trust me,
I'm not excited about
having to fight you either.
After all, our true enemy
is the Roman Orthodox Church.
but since it appears that
you are in league with them,
I guess I'll have
to take on all of
the English Puritans, as well.
You won't find it
easy, but you can try.
You've got attitude
and confidence.
Under different conditions,
maybe we'd be friends.
Unfortunately, today, I'm
going to have to fight you.
[TATEMIYA] This will
be your last day to live.
[grunts]
Ahhh!
[KAMIJO] How did he--?
Ha!
Magic, is it? Okay.
No, Toma! Don't
charge him like that!
[INDEX] It isn't just magic!
Index! Get back, now!
Oh, primordial flame.
Bestower of light.
Lend me the strength
of your blade.
With its power to
protect and give judgment.
[KAMIJO] He did it again?
That has to be magic!
[groans]
[INDEX] Toma!
Do it now!
We can take him
together! Let's go!
Heh.
[grunts]
[TATEMIYA] This
shouldn't be difficult.
My basic protections
are all in place.
I need only be wary
of the flame sword.
Now, to compose
my counterattack.
[grunts]
Ahhh!
[quiet chatter]
[exhales]
That was a close
one! Are you okay?
Does anything hurt?
Are you injured anywhere?
No. Not really.
You're sure? Absolutely
no injuries at all?
Yeah, I'm fine. I mean
it. Nothing's wrong!
Okay, that's good to hear.
[INDEX] Know why?
Uh...?
Because now I can
chomp on your head
as punishment
for your stupidity.
[KAMIJO screams]
[KAMIJO] Okay, okay, geez!
This isn't necessary!
I admit that I was wrong.
I should've listened
to you, all right!
I know that now!
Please just get off of me!
Fine, I'm done.
You're still an idiot,
though. Reckless, too.
Yes. I know.
But, Index, I'm... uh...
Sure is quiet, huh?
I mean, it's hard to believe
how crazy things were
just a little
while ago, isn't it?
You're right. It is.
[TATEMIYA] Hey.
I hate to interrupt
but could you please
take these things off?
I can't leave Orsola
undefended like this.
I have to do something!
Huh? You want
to defend her?
Oh, you don't
know, do you?
You really don't have
any idea what they're
going to do to her once they've
got her in their clutches?
Uh?
No. Don't
listen to him, Toma.
He's trying
to confuse you.
This is a man who
uses words as weapons.
She's gonna die,
do you hear me?
They're gonna kill her!
[TATEMIYA] Listen to me.
You must not hand her over
to the Catholic nuns
who came with you tonight.
The Roman Orthodox Church wants
to see her captured and killed.
You and your people were
the ones who kidnapped her
along with stealing
"The Book of the Law."
Wrong and wrong again.
The Amakusa didn't steal
"The Book of the Law."
[KAMIJO] What?
[TATEMIYA] You have heard
the consequences, right?
The day that the book's
power is used will be the day
that the church of
the cross comes to an end.
Think about
it for a moment.
The members of the Amakusa
Church go to great pains
to remain hidden. So why,
then, would we want to
exploit such a
conspicuous power?
[TATEMIYA] The Roman Catholics,
on the other hand,
would have no such qualms.
And as the largest sect
of the church of the cross,
they have an obvious
incentive to make sure
the Book is never used.
Church authorities
have given secret orders
to have Orsola
Aquinas eliminated.
She found out about these
orders and she sought out
the Amakusa to ask for
our help and protection.
Do you get it yet? The theft of
"The Book of the Law" is just
a fiction that the Roman
Orthodox Church has fed you.
Yeah, right. I still
don't see why
I should believe you.
Then you're a fool.
If you're right--
if everything you told me
actually is true,
one thing doesn't fit.
[KAMIJO] Why did
she run from you?
[chuckles]
Because she's like you.
What do you mean?
[TATEMIYA] She was skeptical.
Right up until the very end,
she believed that
we were only helping
for our own selfish reasons.
She was certain
we would demand that
she decode the book as
payment for our assistance.
Yeah? Why were
you helping her?
[TATEMIYA]
Because she needed help.
It's that simple. But
apparently hard to believe.
That's your reason? Really?
[TATEMIYA] We think
always of the Priestess.
She has left us for
now, but she is still,
and will forever be, our guide.
We will continue to follow
her. As long as we do so,
we will not stray
from the path of right.
We will not cause undue harm or
be mistaken in our use of force.
And when you say Priestess,
you mean Kanzaki?
[TATEMIYA] Yes. That's
right. She was our leader.
But, to our sorrow,
we let her down.
Haaahhh!
[KANZAKI gasps]
[TATEMIYA] Our
deaths, our weakness,
saddened the Priestess,
and she saw no choice
but to abandon us.
However, we have never
stopped hoping that
she will one day return
to her rightful place.
[TATEMIYA]
We follow the Priestess.
That is why we offered our help
to Orsola when she sought it.
[distant scream]
Orsola? Oh, no!
Did you inform her? Did
she know that you intended
to place her in the hands
of the Roman Orthodox Church?
[TATEMIYA] You told her you
weren't a Catholic, right?
You did and because of that,
she thought she could trust you.
[KAMIJO] Damn!
[TATEMIYA] Don't be hasty.
[TATEMIYA] I won't pretend
the situation isn't serious,
but even the Catholic Church
won't kill her here and now.
So, what are you saying?
We understand each other.
I think we both
finally believe the other
wasn't trying to take
advantage of or harm Orsola.
[TATEMIYA] I want a promise.
I want you to swear that
you will get her back
from the Catholic Church
and take her somewhere
she will be safe.
Someplace where neither they nor
we will be able to reach her.
♪
[WOMAN] We are here to take
charge of the heretics' leader.
You will hand
him over at once.
[WOMAN] Unless you are
an enemy of the Church.
[KAMIJO] Hey. Just a second.
Yes, what is it?
I was wondering,
could I please just
tell Orsola goodbye?
That won't be possible.
I'm afraid I must decline.
That loud scream a
minute ago. It was her.
It was Orsola,
wasn't it? Where's Agnese?
[KAMIJO] I should
speak to her.
[gasps]
Behind you!
[KAMIJO] Ahhh!
Ah!
Sister Lucia! We
were told to limit our
contact with the outsiders.
Maybe we should go.
[LUCIA] You will keep quiet,
Sister Angelene.
[LUCIA] Heathen! How dare
you place your hand on me?
Festering! Unclean! Evil!
Nothing is worse than
the touch of a heathen!
I could say that the Amakusa man
resisted and in the process,
he ended up killing all of you!
It will be simple enough.
And we'll silence
the other Amakusa.
[KAMIJO groaning]
Toma!
Sister Angelene, do it now.
Uh... Okay!
I call you,
Matthew the Apostle.
Publican, holy enemy of
magicians, and humble servant.
Ah, ahh!
[KAMIJO] Index!
[KAMIJO] Damn!
[LUCIA] You really ought to
be more worried about yourself.
Worried about how much
pain you will suffer
before you die!
What are you doing,
Sister? Be careful!
Uh-uh! It
wasn't me! I swear it!
C-T-R-T-T-O-P. A-O!
[wimpers]
Come on! If you
don't pay attention
to what's around you,
then you're that much
easier to defeat in battle.
Did she just use
Spell Intercept?
[distant wistle]
They've sounded the
retreat signal!
It's time to go,
Sister Angelene!
[ANGELENE] Right! Coming!
[KAMIJO struggling]
[TATEMIYA] Now you have
seen it with your own eyes.
This is how they act when they
think that nobody's watching.
[TATEMIYA] This is the true face
of the Roman Orthodox Church!
♪ [Ending Song] ♪
[KAMIJO] An all-out battle
involving magicians from
three different
religious sects?
Not even that
is going to stop me.
I swear, Orsola.
I will help you!
Next time, "Sheol Fear."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.