[STIYL] Please, Archbishop!
I have asked before.
Call me not by that name.
[LAURA] It does not suit.
Fine but, shouldn't you
have more guards with you?
If you want to talk to me,
can't we do it at
St. George's Cathedral?
[LAURA] No, I think not.
I have no desire to be
confined within
that dusty old minster.
We can talk whilst
we take in the air.
[STIYL] Well... I suppose
that will have to do.
Are you always such
a dour fellow, Stiyl?
Why should a brief
constitutional on a pleasant
afternoon unsettle
you to such a degree?
If it's alright, Laura Stuart,
maybe I could
ask you a question?
No need to be so
formal. What is it?
Fine, then. Is
there any reason you
speak in such a
ridiculously archaic way?
Oh, I... Well...
Is it truly strange?
I even checked with
a local to be certain
my speech was acceptable!
Who exactly was this
local you spoke with?
'Twas a gentleman named
Motoharu Tsuchimikado.
That guy is
neither a gentleman
nor a good example
of a "local."
A communications
talisman?
[LAURA] It should help.
Now, what do you know
about "The Book of the Law"?
[STIYL] For starters,
it's a grimoire, and if I
remember right, it was
written by Edward Alexander.
The original text
is currently said
to be held in Vatican Library.
However, it is believed
that no one can decipher it.
[LAURA] Not even the
Index Librorum Prohibitorum,
who has memorized
so many others.
[LAURA] But what if somebody
who could decipher
"The Book of the
Law" came forward?
Please tell me you're kidding!
[crowd gasps]
Shh!
[LAURA] The person who
can decipher the grimoire is
a Roman Catholic sister by
the name of Orsola Aquinas.
[STIYL] Are you saying
"The Book of the Law" has
become an instrument
in the power struggle?
[LAURA] Thankfully, no.
For the time being, at least.
[LAURA] "The Book of the Law"
and Orsola Aquinas
have both reportedly
been spirited away.
[LAURA] Shall we
go inside to discuss
the matter in greater detail?
♪ [Opening Song] ♪
[MAIKA] Second term is always a
busy part of the year, you know?
We have the Daihasei
Sports Festival,
the Ichihanaran
Cultural Festival,
the Arts Appreciation Festival,
[MAIKA] and the Field
Trip Festival all in a row.
[meow]
Aw, poor Sphinxy.
Are you dizzy?
I don't care how many
stupid festivals there are!
Toma never plays with me
and I'm bored all the time!
I'm sure there are
reasons he doesn't have
as much time to spend
with you as you want.
It's not like he goes
to school and does homework
because that's what
he enjoys doing.
You don't seem to spend
much time at school
or doing homework!
Hm. The vocational
training I chose makes me
an exception to the rule.
The fundamentals of
[MAIKA] a maid's studies
are practical, after all.
Hey, I know! I'll
become a maid, too!
Then I'll go and
visit Toma at school
[INDEX] in my
cute maid's uniform.
Becoming a maid isn't
something to take lightly!
It's too difficult a
profession for a girl
with zero
housekeeping skills.
Okay, then Toma
can become a maid.
Then he'll have time to visit
me in his maid's uniform!
If I were you, I
would avoid mentioning
[MAIKA] that
particular idea to him.
He might not understand.
[STIYL] Yes, I
imagine you're right.
I'm sorry about this.
But right now you don't
have time to become
a maid or to try and
convince anybody else
to become one, either.
[KAMIJO]
"The Daihasei Festival."
A sporting competition
in which all of
Academy City's
schools participate.
The main purpose of the
festival is to encourage
more interaction between
espers on a larger scale.
It's the one day of the
year all espers are urged
to exercise the full strength
of their abilities, 'kay.
[KAMIJO] Due to
unfortunate circumstances,
I had my memory
wiped out a while ago.
[KAMIJO] So thoroughly
wiped out, in fact,
that I don't even remember
an event as big as this one.
Now let's see.
I wonder what I should
pick up for dinner tonight.
[MAIKA] Kamijo, come quick!
This is an
emergency situation!
The silver-haired sister
has been stolen away
by a creepy man! Well?
Huh?
Are you listening to me?
I'm talking abduction!
A guy just showed
up and took her away?
Yeah, and then the
kidnapper gave me this
to give you upon your return.
"Dear Toma Kamijo.
If you value her life,
[KAMIJO] come to the site
of the "Twilight Theater,"
an abandoned playhouse
outside Academy City
tonight at seven o'clock.
Come alone and do not
alert the authorities."
[KAMIJO] Alright. Can you tell
me what this creep looked like?
[MAIKA] Uh. Well, first
of all, he was tall.
Like, taller than five-ten.
His hair was deep red,
and of all things, he had a
barcode under his right eye.
[MAIKA] There was a
cigarette in his mouth
and lots of
piercings in his ears.
Oh, then there's
nothing to worry about.
This particular
kidnapper is someone
Index and I already know.
[MAIKA] You know the kidnapper?
Oh, I see. Is it a
case of love gone wrong?
Uh... no. It's, uh, it's
complicated, that's all.
[BOTH] Hm?
An exit pass.
Well, that's helpful.
[STIYL] That about sums up the
situation. You get all of that?
Mmm. "The Book of the Law"
has been stolen
from the Vatican.
[INDEX] The only person
who can decipher it,
a nun named Orsola Aquinas,
has disappeared too.
And it seems that the
Amakusa Church is responsible.
[STIYL] Vatican security is no
joke. How did they get it out?
It happened in transit while
the Roman Orthodox Church
was relocating "The
Book of the Law" to Japan.
Are they complete morons?
Moving something as
dangerous as that! And, what?
Now the Catholics are looking
to the English Puritan Church
for assistance with
their own stupid blunder?
[LAURA] Not so. Something has
actually come up on our end.
[STIYL] And that is?
We're currently unable
to reach Kaori Kanzaki.
[LAURA] Kanzaki was once the
head of the Amakusa Church.
If she finds out that
the Amakusa are at odds
with the Roman
Orthodox Church...
Let's just say
I do not want her
to interfere in this matter.
[LAURA] Use any methods
you deem necessary.
Kanzaki is a saint--
one of fewer than
twenty in the world.
Are you saying that you
expect me to fight her?
[LAURA] If the
situation calls for it.
There is much work to do.
Go and get in touch
with Academy City.
Oh, and Stiyl... I would
like for you to take this.
Hm.
And this is...?
I suppose you could
call it a modest gift from
the English Puritan
Church to Orsola. Now...
Find the List
of Prohibited Books.
It would be good to have a
specialist, don't you think?
I don't get why you're
dragging Toma into this.
Yeah, me either.
It's not exactly like
I love his company.
[INDEX] Well, can you
at least tell me why
we're going to the
Amakusa's headquarters?
[STIYL] Actually,
the situation's changed.
Uh.
[footsteps]
[KAMIJO] Damn it.
Where is the
"Twilight Theater"?
[KAMIJO] He had
to pick this spot?
Outside of Academy City, I
don't know where anything is.
[sigh]
That looks like a nun.
[KAMIJO] I wonder if there's
any chance this sister
is a friend of Index's.
[WOMAN] Pardon me.
What? But of course.
[WOMAN] I wonder
if you could help me.
Is this the bus
I should be taking
if I'm going to Academy City?
[KAMIJO] Academy City, huh?
Sorry, but no bus is
going to take you there.
Really?
All modes of transportation
into the city, including buses,
have been discontinued.
But there is a pedestrian gate
[KAMIJO] right over
there that you can use. Uh.
[WOMAN] Thank you for
taking the time to assist me.
I do appreciate it.
[KAMIJO] I just said
not to get on the bus!
[WOMAN] Oh, right,
so you did. Thank you.
Like I told you,
you have to walk through
that gate over there.
You got it now?
[WOMAN] Please forgive me.
I am very sorry
to have bothered you.
Yeah. Uh... eh?
[KAMIJO] Hey, nun!
Were you just smiling and
pretending to listen to me?
[sighs]
It looks as if
something has upset you.
May I help in any way?
Oh, it's nothing.
Pardon the familiarity
and I hope you'll forgive
me for saying so,
but you're
sweating quite a lot.
Thank you. I'm fine!
But, uh, just out of curiosity,
why are you going
to Academy City?
[WOMAN] Ah... Oh, well...
it's a rather long story.
There are some people
chasing me, you see.
Why would they do that?
[GIRL It's all
a mess! All of it!
We can't even be sure of
our intelligence right now.
[GIRL] We don't know if
"The Book of the Law" is secure.
I'm sorry, I should
give you my name.
Agnese Sanctis. A sister of
the Roman Orthodox Church.
A pleasure. So,
can you update us
on the situation
with the Amakusa?
Sorry, no. You've
hit upon yet another gap
in the information
that we have available.
[INDEX] The Amakusa Church
is known for their secrecy.
Their distinctive feature
is that they don't use
incantations or magical arrays.
All of their rituals and
processes are concealed
within normal behaviors.
[INDEX] So even the most
discerning magician would have
a difficult time
identifying who they are.
Uh-huh. They're definitely
an annoying group.
Yay! It's Toma!
[AGNESE] With Orsola Aquinas?
[KAMIJO]
What were you thinking?
Was there a reason for
pretending to kidnap her?
Oh, my. Have I upset
you? Here's the thing.
We needed to find
somebody who was missing,
and we thought you might
be able to help us out.
Find someone?
[STIYL] Don't worry
about it now, though.
If you'll just hand over
the sister you've got there,
we can call it a done deal.
Wha--?
Hand over the nun.
You see, as it happens,
[STIYL] the woman
accompanying you
is our missing person, Orsola.
So, yeah. Good
work and all that.
We're done here.
You're free to go.
Wha--Uh...
So, um... Do I get
some kind of reward for
dragging myself all the
way down here in the hot sun?
[STIYL] I already told you
you did a good job, right?
So, what? You want me to
buy you a snow cone now, too?
[KAMIJO]
I've had enough of this.
I've done my best to at
least try and keep the peace,
despite the fact that we
rub each other the wrong way.
But this is it!
I'm done playing nice!
Uh...
Wow. What an incredibly
pathetic cry for attention.
Sorry, but I can't
do anything about your
lonely little life. Even
if I cared enough to try.
Now, please release
Orsola into our custody.
You did say that
someone was chasing you;
maybe it's
not a bad idea.
You're shaking. Is
something the matter?
[MALE VOICE] Hate to interrupt.
But I really can't allow you
to hand the sister
over to these people.
That's right, Orsola Aquinas.
You will not be returning
to the bosom of
the Roman Orthodox Church, but
coming with me to live a more
meaningful and productive
life among the Amakusa.
Amakusa's here?
[KAMIJO] Orsola!
[INDEX] No, you
can't go after her!
In my hand, I hold the fire.
Its form is that of a
sword, and its purpose is to--
[STIYL] Looks like I'm
too late for that to work.
Alright, out with it!
Explain to me what's
going on here. Everything!
[STIYL] An explanation?
That's something
I wish I had right now.
[INDEX] "The Book of the Law."
It's a grimoire written in a
code that supposedly no
one in the world can break.
It's said that if
it ever was deciphered,
the person who managed it would
be granted absolute power.
[KAMIJO] You're kidding,
right? I mean, after all,
it's just a book.
How powerful can it be?
[STIYL] Something
else is said about it.
If the book is decoded,
it will also mean
the end of the Church of
the Cross' religious rule.
So why not just
burn the thing then?
Grimoires aren't normal
books so they don't burn.
Just to seal them requires
an immense amount of power.
[AGNESE breathing heavy]
Oh, uh. I'm sorry.
I wanted to explain
our analysis of
the situation. If you--
[screaming]
Uh-ahhh!
Be careful!
[thud]
Ugh. Uh...
Uh.
Uh. Uh...
[screams]
Hey, stop it!
What are you doing?
Get away! This is wrong!
[INDEX] Toma! I don't think
she needs your help anymore.
Maybe you should get up!
Quit screwing around.
We have things to do.
[KAMIJO] Uh...!
[AGNESE] What we know for
certain right now is this.
Orsola Aquinas is in
the hands of the Amakusa.
According to our latest
estimation, the number of
Amakusa Church members involved
in this is less than fifty.
There is also
the possibility that
they are no longer underground.
So basically, what you're
trying to say is that
we don't know very much?
All we have to work
with are magical traces
and what we know of
the group's tendencies.
[INDEX] The Amakusa specialize
in hiding and fleeing.
It's what they do. It won't
be easy to catch them.
That's true, but I
think even they will have
a difficult time
breaking out of our net.
Do you know their
transfer technique?
[INDEX]
"Microcosmic Pilgrimage."
[INDEX] It's a process they can
only use inside this country.
Essentially, there are
forty-seven specialized vortices
across Japan and the
Amakusa practitioners can
freely come and
go between them.
If they manage to send
her through a vortex,
it's all over.
[AGNESE] So why are
we sitting around here?
Because at the moment,
there's no reason to hurry.
[AGNESE] Huh?
[INDEX] Microcosmic Pilgrimages
are reliant upon the movement
of the stars. Which
means that there are only
certain times the Amakusa
can use the vortices.
The transport they
likely have planned for Orsola
won't be available to them
until just after midnight,
so that gives us about four
and a half hours to work with.
One more thing.
Toma, may I borrow
your gadget with the map?
Hm? Oh. Yeah, sure.
[beeping]
[KAMIJO] Here.
[INDEX] Okay. Look at this map.
There's only one vortex
they can use in the area.
[INDEX] It's right there.
[KAMIJO] Well, here we are.
Wonder if I can help
out with something. Uh...
[GIRL] And after I told
you to double-check, too!
That was incredibly
careless of you, sister.
I know. I'm
really sorry.
Look at that.
I guess the nuns
have got their own troubles.
[KAMIJO] Hm?
So, this one must
be Index's tent.
What the--?
She's gone. Well, great.
Now where did she go?
[distant scream]
[KAMIJO] Over there?
Aw, damn it!
Index!
The Amakusa!
Are they here? Ah...!
[AGNESE wimpers]
Uh... Oh, I,
uh... What's up?
Over there.
Over there!
That thing? It's
just a slug, isn't it?
A slug? There's
a slug in my tent?
Whoa, hey! Get a
hold of yourself!
[INDEX] Toma?
Uh...
[KAMIJO] I was... I-I thought
the Amakusa were attacking,
so I came over here
to check things out.
[crying]
[KAMIJO] Uh... Uh...
Wait. Hold on,
Index, take it easy!
Normally, you
don't cry like this.
[KAMIJO] Most of
the time you would be
chomping on me right about now.
Can we explain that
to these good people?
Nghh!
[KAMIJO] Ahhh!
Hey can we talk?
[STIYL] Seriously?
I'm sleeping, here,
and you want to start bonding?
Are there any girls
that you're interested in?
[STIYL coughing]
What? Hard question?
[STIYL coughs]
I have always had respect
for Queen Elizabeth the First.
And, of course, St. Martha.
I've heard about the
Amakusa Church before.
It's the one
Kanzaki belonged to.
Yeah, who told you that?
Was it Tsuchimikado?
Some of the Amakusa
we're up against
are probably Kanzaki's
friends, aren't they?
But despite that, you're
still going to fight them.
[STIYL] I am.
Don't you get it? I've
made a promise to myself
to do anything to protect
that girl. Anything.
I'll kill anyone. I'll
burn them alive if I have to.
Whatever I need to do.
That isn't the kind
of promise you forget.
[STIYL] It doesn't matter to me
if she has forgotten everything.
I can hold the
memory for both of us.
"I will live and die for
you." That's what I said.
[STIYL] Now go to sleep.
[KAMIJO] Stiyl.
Not him. So that means--
Uh...
Come on, Index! What
are you doing down there?
What did you say, Toma?
[KAMIJO] Huh? Agnese?
Is that you?
Whoa, hey.
[KAMIJO wimpering]
[INDEX] It's a dream.
This is a dream, so it
doesn't matter how much
I bite Toma. It won't kill him.
I can work through
the stress of today,
and there will be
no future consequences.
No. I'm begging
you not to do it, Index.
This is very
definitely real life.
[crunch]
[KAMIJO] Rotten luck!
Heh.
[WOMAN] Your Holiness.
All of the
preparations for the
Microcosmic
Pilgrimage are complete.
Mmm.
[MAN] Now then.
Kaori Kanzaki.
I hope you will see
this and understand...
that we are what the church
of the cross should be;
multilateral and integrated.
We are the united
Amakusa Church
and we are doing
what needs to be done.
♪ [Ending Song] ♪
[KAMIJO] We head to the vortex
with the Roman Catholic sisters,
but the truth Tatemiya
reveals may change everything.
What will happen to Orsola?
Next time,
"The Amakusa Church."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.