[KAMIJO] Not long after
tranquility had been restored
to Misaka's life,
darkness returned.
This time, darkness
has taken the form of
a shadowy organization
jostling for control
of Tree Diagram's wreckage.
And now Kuroko Shirai has
caught a glimpse of Misaka
as she wages her
lone, secret battle.
♪ [Opening Song] ♪
Wait.
[MIKOTO] Are there
any civilians in here?
[sighs]
[MUSUJIME struggling]
To your detriment you
underestimated me.
You assumed that I
wouldn't teleport myself.
I can do it anytime.
Provided I'm motivated enough.
As long as the
goal's important,
the trauma isn't too bad.
[gasping in pain]
[KUROKO] I'm not sure you truly
understand how trauma functions.
It's not that easily
overcome, I'm afraid.
[KUROKO] Two years ago you
were seriously injured in
the process of
teleporting your own body.
If I had to guess, you
most likely miscalculated
your coordinates and ran
into a wall or something.
[KUROKO] And what a pathetic
sight that must have been!
[KUROKO] I'm sure
it hurts a lot,
but there's no reason to panic.
I made certain to
avoid anything vital.
See, all I wanted to
do was to pay you back
for the injuries
you gave me earlier.
Here is some styptic gel.
It's quite effective,
go ahead and try it.
[KUROKO] Now. I would like
to see you writhing in pain
on the cold floor while
you treat your own injuries.
You do that, and I think we
can actually call things even.
[MUSUJIME chuckles]
You are quite
concerned about the fate
of Tokiwadai's
Ace, aren't you?
But really, what is it you're
trying so hard to protect?
Dear, sweet
Railgun's delusions?
The sentimental,
selfish, fantasy world
that only she can see?
[KUROKO] That's exactly
what I want to protect.
However selfish
she might be sometimes,
what Sissy wants is
something truly good.
A world where you and I wouldn't
have to fight like this;
that's what she's working for!
[KUROKO] Don't you get it?
All she needs is a single coin
and she could blow either
of us up where we stand.
But even with all that
power at her fingertips,
she holds back
because she honestly
believes the world
would be a better place
without so much violence.
So you better
believe I find that to be
a future worth fighting for?
[KUROKO] And now I'm telling
you, in no uncertain terms,
to leave her alone.
Do you understand me, Musujime?
I want you to leave
Sissy and her dreams alone.
[MUSUJIME] Is that so? And
what if I don't give a damn
what you want? What are
you going to do about it?
[plate breaks]
[KUROKO] I won't fall
for the same trick twice.
[thud]
Ahhh!
[KUROKO] I can't teleport!
[crash]
[MUSUJIME] What's the matter?
Were you in so much pain
you weren't able to teleport?
[MUSUJIME] Here let me
tell you a little story.
Once upon a time in
a place not so far away,
there was an organization
interested in a powerful esper.
[MUSUJIME] The organization's
leaders thought about
how strong they would
be if they had more espers
like her under their control,
and so they decided
to manufacture clones.
[MUSUJIME] Unfortunately,
things didn't go as planned.
They wound up with a whole
bunch of near-useless sheep.
Colossal failures,
every last one of them.
Nowhere near as strong
as the Original esper.
[MISAKA 10032] "Okay then.
Shall we organize all of
the information we
have gathered so far?"
asks Misaka 10032
over the Network
to an unspecified
number of units.
"Currently, there
is a single Remnant
that can reestablish
Tree Diagram.
[MISAKA 10032] It is
somewhere in Academy City."
"The name of the organization
that is after it
is the Science Society.
There is no question
about that, correct?"
Misaka 10032 asks,
seeking to confirm
current information.
[MISAKA 10044] "Information
confirmed," replies
Misaka 10044,
without any doubt.
[MISAKA 10744] "However, 10032,
you of all units have suffered
the most severe damage.
You are still recuperating.
Shouldn't you concentrate on
healing?" asks Misaka 10744,
expressing apprehension
with your involvement.
"It doesn't matter,"
replies Misaka 10032
without hesitation.
[MISAKA 10032] "The
reintegration of Tree Diagram
is something that
must be stopped,
no matter the consequences."
says Misaka 10032,
remembering the faces of
the boy and girl, thus
renewing her determination.
[MISAKA 14458] "Acknowledged.
We will leave it in your hands,
then," says Misaka 14458,
agreeing with 10032.
[MISAKA 19002] "We
appreciate your efforts,"
adds Misaka 19002,
with gratitude.
[LAST ORDER] "Misaka
thinks you are really great,"
Misaka Misaka
says emphatically.
Misaka wishes that
she could help, too!
Misaka Misaka
really doesn't like
sitting around doing nothi--
[ACCELERATOR] Hey!
[ACCELERATOR] Shut it, will ya?
What're you babbling about
over there, you noisy brat?
[LAST ORDER] "Nothing at
all," says Misaka Misaka,
covering her mouth.
[sighs]
Tsk.
What do you think went wrong?
The clones are all genetically
identical to the Original,
and they have
undergone the exact same
ability development
as she has.
[MUSUKIME] So how is it
possible, then, that they are
mere shadows of
her strength and power?
[MUSUJIME] Could it be that
there's something else involved
in the process besides
brain composition?
And, once we can identify
that, do you suppose
non-humans will be able to
master abilities, as well?
[MUSUJIME] Something equal,
or even superior to people.
The day they exist could be a
lot closer than you'd expect.
What in the world
are you talking about?
[KUROKO] You cannot
mean machines that
possess esper abilities!
A machine is just a machine.
But machines can
make predictions.
Suppose there was one that
could perfectly simulate
any hypothetical situation
that was put to it.
[MUSUJIME] You could
ask it to assess
the possibility of anything.
Like whether or not
abilities can be developed
outside of humankind,
for example.
Look at the animal kingdom.
Dolphins are called
the humans of the sea.
Ant societies are more orderly
and disciplined than ours.
[MUSUJIME] Surely
esper abilities are not
the sole province of men,
but if that's the case,
why haven't we seen
them anywhere else?
I want to know.
I have to find out.
[MUSUJIME] And that
is why I am doing this.
Why I want the Remnant,
so I can build a new Tree
Diagram and learn the answers.
[KAMIJO] Ee-yow!
I didn't do anything!
Why are you biting
me? Geez! Just let go!
Uh, I mean, "Pretty
please, let go, Index.
If you don't mind."
[INDEX] Ah!
[INDEX] You can be
really mean, you know that?
Eh?
I spent a lot of time and
effort trying to think up
a personalized
tongue twister for you.
How did it go again?
"Toma traipses topless
through the town in a tutu?"
That doesn't exactly sound
complimentary, now, does it?
[KAMIJO] Uh, well,
what I meant was...
[doorbell rings]
[BOTH] Hmm?
[KAMIJO] Misaka? Hi.
[MISAKA 10032]
"I have a favor to ask."
"Please," says
Misaka, staring you
directly in the eyes,
opening her heart up to you.
Misaka and Misaka's sisters'
lives are in danger.
Will you come and help us?
[running footsteps]
[MIKOTO] I won't allow it.
[MIKOTO] Those
horrible experiments.
[MIKOTO] I can't let them
start up again, no matter what!
[MIKOTO] "Extensive property
damage to an Area F restaurant,
in what appears to be a
skirmish between espers."
[MIKOTO] Eh! That idiot!
[breathing heavy]
There you are... Zapper.
You were looking
for me? What for?
Why are you doing
this to me again?
[KAMIJO] Hey...
Enough talk. Let's go.
[KUROKO] That is
why you collaborated
with an outside organization.
[MUSUJIME] Yes. Possessing
the Remnant is more than
half the battle, but I can't
restore the thing by myself.
So I needed an
outfit to partner with.
One that could
bring technical skill
and intelligence to the table.
I'm curious, I want to know
something personal about you.
[MUSUJIME] How did
it feel the first time
you used your ability?
To be honest I
was actually afraid.
Possessing that kind
of power was scarier than
anything I'd ever experienced.
[chuckles]
Why does it have to be me?
Why does it have
to be a person at all?
Are humans really the best
candidates to possess abilities?
[MUSUJIME] The members of the
organizations I've partnered
with have the same
concerns and hesitations.
You see, they curse
their own abilities.
And like me, they've
been seeking answers.
We're all working together
for a common cause.
[MUSUJIME] That's why they were
willing to act as my shield.
You know what I'm
talking about, right?
That sick feeling you got
when you used your ability
and ended up
hurting somebody.
You aren't alone in that.
In fact, I suspect
that we're a lot alike.
So, what do you say then?
Would you like to work together
with me to find the truth?
We'd love to have you.
You could be part of
something truly revolutionary.
[KUROKO] Sorry, I'll
have to decline.
Did you really think that
was going to win me over?
A self-pitying,
self-involved monologue
and a lame
attempt at bonding?
All you've managed
to prove so far
is that you like
to hear yourself talk.
Don't you understand?
The powers that we espers
possess make us something
akin to mutant monsters.
These abilities
are too dangerous.
Oh, don't be absurd!
Abilities are abilities;
neither good nor evil.
How the power is used
depends on the person.
[KUROKO] How foolish do
you need to be not to have
realized something so obvious?
[KUROKO] You are
afraid of your power
because you don't
want it to hurt others?
You have so totally
missed the point.
[KUROKO] Whether
you have power or not,
nothing is going to change
the fact that you, Musujime,
are somebody who
hurts other people.
You make me
sick to my stomach.
Acting like a victim,
pretending to be ashamed
of your own ability. That's
just to hide your belief that
you are superior
to everybody else.
[KUROKO] So I'm going to
disabuse you of that notion.
By beating it out
of you if necessary.
Uh...
No! Stay back!
Aaahhh!
[KUROKO] Ugh!
♪
[breathing heavy]
[pained outcries]
[wimpers]
[furniture crashing]
I'll kill you.
[MUSUJIME] I wouldn't
have cracked like that,
but you forced me to.
This's all your fault!
If it weren't for you,
I could have been somebody!
[laughing]
[MUSUJIME] My Move Point
can relocate a maximum of
four thousand five hundred
and twenty kilograms.
I can hit this place,
even from far away.
This entire building
will be destroyed,
and I can't imagine that
you'll fare any better!
Wait a sec. Don't
you need the contents
of that case
for your evil plans?
[MUSUJIME grunts]
I'm going to destroy you.
[MUSUJIME] Because you're
the one who destroyed me.
I'm going to pay you
back in full for that!
[KUROKO coughing]
Sissy. I'm sorry.
[rumbling]
I guess it's coming, then.
Four thousand,
five hundred and twenty.
♪
That light! Oh, no!
Don't, Sissy!
Please don't come
up here! It isn't safe!
[screaming]
[MIKOTO] Kuroko!
[KAMIJO] Uh!
Aaahhh!
♪
Who in the world... are you?
[distant tires screeching]
[MUSUJIME]
This is A001 calling M000.
Status report to
follow code confirmation.
[gunfire through phone]
[YOMIKAWA] Swindling a
kid and then watching from
a safe distance?
You really are scum, huh!
[gunfire through phone]
[MUSUJIME] Now what?
What do I do?
[distant footsteps]
[ACCELERATOR] Well,
this is pretty lame.
I went to more than a
little trouble to get out,
and it ends up being for what?
Dealing with a
scrawny, pathetic,
third-string fool like you?
There's no way. Accelerator?
[MUSUJIME] The guy even
Railgun couldn't defeat.
The highest-ranked
esper in Academy City!
I can't! He's too strong!
[MUSUJIME] I can't go up
against someone of his caliber!
[MUSUJIME chuckles] But wait!
Huh?
[MUSUJIME] On August 31st,
you were shot in the head,
which resulted in
the loss of your power.
Yeah, you no longer
have the ability
to calculate
like you did before.
You're washed up! I don't
have to be afraid of you!
Ya know, I feel bad for you.
Really, if you actually
believe what you're saying,
I feel so bad for you I
could almost give you a hug.
It's true that I was
involved in a scuffle
that left me with
some brain damage.
So nowadays I
outsource my calculating.
Here's the thing, though...
I may be a bit weaker
because of that,
but it's still a far cry
from being as weak as you are.
You really think I'd
fallen that far? Huh?!
♪
[ACCELERATOR chuckles]
[ACCELERATOR grunts]
[ACCELERATOR] It's all over.
Unless you want me
to accelerate your death,
I suggest you surrender
like a good little girl,
go back to wherever
it is you came from,
and accept your defeat.
Auhhh!
[MUSUJIME] Ugh!
[painful gasps]
[glass breaking]
[ACCELERATOR] True. My power
has diminished somewhat.
I may even need to step
down as this city's top dog.
And yet, here I am.
[ACCELERATOR] As long as the
kid's around, for some reason,
I'm still determined
to act like top dog.
Damn it all.
[clinking]
Hey, look, look, look!
I finally mastered the art of
buying drinks from a machine!
[INDEX] Isn't it exciting?
Yeah.
Hmmm?
What, is something
the matter?
Hah! At this point,
what isn't the matter?
[KAMIJO] I came here to
see how Shirai was doing.
Errr!
[KAMIJO] Real bad idea.
So I went to visit
Misaka's sister, instead.
[machines beeping]
[sighs] It's just my luck.
[INDEX] So? What
about the object at
the middle of this whole mess?
You rescued that girl
with the ponytails like
the big-shot hero
you are, but you didn't
get the Remnant, did you?
No, the girl
responsible for it
had been beaten
up by someone.
And the contents of the case
were scattered everywhere.
[KAMIJO] So far, nobody knows
who might've attacked her.
[LAST ORDER] "So, that's
about it. Yomikawa says she was
off dealing with the members
of the Science Society.
According to her, they had
contact with Ao Amai, too,"
Misaka Misaka
concludes her report.
[yawns] That's nice.
"Hey! How can you act
like this is no big deal?"
inquires Misaka Misaka.
Shut up already.
That's how you can
show your gratitude;
[ACCELERATOR] by just sitting
there quietly for a little bit.
Mmmm.
Clear blue sky.
The weather forecast
was wrong, huh?
Hmm. Sure looks like it.
I realized something.
I think I understand
it better now...
why you feel the need
to keep things to yourself
and fight some
battles on your own.
Kuroko.
I didn't know enough
about the situation,
so my involvement
didn't help at all.
[KUROKO] I promise I'll
try to be more careful
in the future, Sissy.
But do you think
you could promise me
something, as well?
I want you to always remember
that I'm there for you!
[MIKOTO] I promise.
And thank you.
♪ [Ending Song] ♪
[KAMIJO] A magician uses
the Daihasei Sports Festival--
the most anticipated
event of the year--
as an opportunity to
sneak into the city.
But what is she after?
Next time,
"The Daihasei Festival."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.