[KAMIJO sighs]
[FEMALE humming]
[MALE humming]
[KAMIJO grunting]
Oh! I give up!
[KAMIJO] Prereques for
the ESP Card Experiment.
A great Level Zero like
me is really supposed to
know something about that?
Ugh...!
[KAMIJO] Imagine Breaker.
The marvelous power
attributed to my right hand.
This baby can
cancel out any other
extraordinary power
with a single touch.
[KAMIJO] Great as that
sounds, though, it doesn't do
a damn thing to help with
summer vacation homework.
[KAMIJO] It's been a
busy day to say the least.
Mikoto Misaka pressured me
into playing her boyfriend,
and then I was chased
around by some Aztec magician.
Just one crazy
thing after another.
[KAMIJO] And, what it
all comes down to is...
my homework is
nowhere near complete.
[INDEX humming]
I get it! Magical
Powered Kanamin takes
the Parts of Ether
and the lotus staff for
the Elementals and
reproduces them in smaller,
plastic counterparts, right?
How perfectly representative...
Index. Do me a favor, huh?
I won't ask that you stop
watching TV altogether.
Think you could
turn it down, though?
[INDEX] Toma, you never
do anything fun with me!
[INDEX] Why else do you
think I'm always escaping
into the world
of television, huh?
[KAMIJO] Auh!
Hey! Why are you
picking now of all times
to bug me about this? I'm
busy! Uh, speaking of which.
What happened to that
sheet I was working on?
[KAMIJO] And that problem
set? And my math book?
[INDEX] Ah, hey, Toma!
Yeah? You find something?
[INDEX] Did you know
it's after three o'clock.
Huh?
It's past time for
my afternoon snack.
Rotten luck.
Soon I will have you,
Index Librorum Prohibitorum.
The List of
Prohibited Books. Yes.
♪ [Opening Song] ♪
Oh, wow. It sure was a
lot of trouble locating
this worksheet in the
pile of comic books it had
found its way into.
So, Toma, am I great,
or am I great? Just say it.
[INDEX] Come on, I know there's
something you want to say to me.
Isn't there?
Yeah? How about
you just tell me what it is?
[chuckles]
You want to say thanks
for the work I did
to help you and you would
like to show your gratitude
with an appropriate reward.
You already ate my pudding!
Is that not enough?
Maybe that would be good!
In just five short hours,
you can make your
own tofu hamburger!
I already told you, I don't
have time for that sorta thing!
It's after five now, so there're
about seven hours 'til midnight.
So even if I don't
plan on sleeping at all,
that's less than fifteen
hours before school!
[KAMIJO] Fifteen
hours to finish all my...
It's not healthy to put so
much pressure on yourself.
Your brain has to work
harder than usual when you're
on the edge of a nervous
breakdown. Take it easy.
[KAMIJO] Of all people,
she tells me this?
The time has come.
Wind Magic Bowstring!
Striking Bowstring!
[KAMIJO gasps]
[MAN] Not here.
I just felt a
chill down my spine.
[INDEX giggles]
Toma! Toma! Can I order
anything I want from the menu?
Why say it like that?
What do you want, exactly?
How about, uh, the
most expensive thing!
How about whatever
gets here the fastest
and shuts you up?
That's not nice!
[KAMIJO] So there we were at
a restaurant, hoping to fill
the endless void that
is Index's stomach.
And I was busy
plugging away at what was
left of my homework.
♪
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Eh, eh, ahhh!
[MAN] There you are.
Now... time for battle.
[KAMIJO] My report on the
development of esper abilities!
[WAITRESS] I'm so sorry!
I'll be right back
with something to clean it up!
Well, think
about it this way.
You can still make out
the letters, can't you?
I had three whole
pages completed.
[INDEX] ...to a
new sheet of paper.
You don't have to
think it all up again,
just rewrite it, so
it shouldn't take you
nearly as long
as the first time.
With this shot
the battle begins.
Sunder Magic Bowstring!
Ahhh!
[KAMIJO] Hyah!
[KAMIJO] Damn it!
What the hell are you--
Behind you now.
I did not foresee
this possibility.
[MAN] I would like to limit
unnecessary loss of life.
Surrender yourself,
and I will take
no further action against you.
So long as I achieve
my objective, I--
[KAMIJO screams]
M-My homework.
It's been turned into confetti.
Hey, you jerk! This
is all your fault!
You better have pen and paper,
'cause you're gonna fix this!
Yeah! You're gonna
redo my homework!
That's not my concern.
[laughing]
Oh, yeah? Well,
unfortunately for you,
I'm feeling a little
bit violent today.
[KAMIJO] Where'd you--?
Ah--!
[MAN] Allow me
to put this simply.
I am not interested
in childish games.
So what are you doing here?
And what is it
you want with Index?
Think it over, boy.
If you're aware
that this girl's mind
[MAN] contains the one
hundred three thousand volumes
of the List of
Prohibited Books--
I see. You're a magician, huh?
Indeed I am.
Transparent Bowstring!
Hold it, you bastard!
[INDEX] Ah!
[KAMIJO] I feel something
small and soft.
Uh, is that you, Index?
[HIMEGAMI] Uh!
What... was that?
[running footsteps]
Damn, where did he go?
[WAITRESS]
Um... excuse me, sir.
[KAMIJO] Eh...
[phone ringing]
This wasn't really
what I had in mind
when I got her a
cell phone, but...
Why'd I expect her
to answer? Damn!
Where do I
even start looking?
[meow]
Hey, Sphinx!
[KAMIJO] Hey! Where
are you going, cat?
Wait up, will ya?
[KAMIJO] A hotel? It must
have a thousand rooms!
Is that where Index is?
[meow]
[heavy breathing]
[KAMIJO] Over
there? Hey, Index!
[meow]
You stupid feline!
Don't you have any sense
of obligation to your master?
Index gave you a home, and
this is how you repay her?
[KAMIJO] Come on, you. We're
gonna keep looking for her.
[meow]
♪
[wind blowing]
[MAN] I am impressed.
In this short of a time, you've
already untied two knots.
You can tie this rope in however
many painful knots you want,
[INDEX] but I refuse to give in
to your stupid
torture techniques.
[MAN] As I
have already said,
causing you pain is not
my primary objective.
My desire is to
obtain a grimoire.
And to accomplish that,
I'll need your assistance.
Now, then.
[MAN] I must first
raise a magical field
for amplification purposes.
[KAMIJO] What is that magician
planning to do with Index?
[KAMIJO] Ugh! Where am
I even supposed to look?
[KAMIJO] Whoa!
Hey, sorry! Uh...
♪
It's you! What the heck
are you even doing here?
I mean, geez! It
seems like you're always
frantically running
around somewhere.
And would it kill you to call
and let me know you're okay?
Oh. I guess you
don't have my number,
so that would probably make
it kinda difficult, huh?
[MIKOTO] Wha--Hey... wait!
[MIKOTO] Honestly!
You're always doing this!
Stop messing around
with me! Hey, what's wrong?
[MIKOTO] Really, you
look like you're about
to cry or something.
Can't you see
I'm in a hurry?
First there's
the homework,
and the restaurant,
and the kidnapping!
So what? What
is it you want?
Oh. Well, I, uh.
It's--It's nothing.
It's just that after
everything that happened,
I thought, well...
Ya know, forget about it.
There's nothing specific
I want from you or anything.
[MIKOTO] I mean, after all,
what would there be right?
[KAMIJO] Sorry!
Are you kidding me? All
of that and you run off again?
Seriously, you jerk!
[INDEX] Is this a
ritual staging ground?
[MAN] Putting it that way
is perhaps a bit melodramatic.
I would prefer to
consider it more like
the dance grounds
for a festival.
And why did you go to
all of this trouble?
Are you gonna have me
possessed by something?
[MAN] Once again, that
is not how I would put it.
I only raised the magical field
to increase the power of this.
The Azusa Yumi bow. A
ceremonial item used in Shinto.
Ah... How magnificent.
Your magical library contains
a wealth of knowledge. Including
my cultural background.
Hey Index? Is that you?
[MAN] ...level of
power is only great enough
to shock the mind or
to rectify any imbalances.
However, with the
proper preparations.
[MAN] it can be used
to read the contents
of another's mind.
Yes. It can reveal even
that which is most hidden,
including the prohibited
volumes that reside within you.
Think this through!
Even you must know
what the consequences are
if anyone other than me comes
in contact with the grimoires!
Of course.
I am well aware.
Ah!
What was that?
[static through phone]
That's the hotel
we passed by earlier!
[meow]
Damn!
[MAN grunting]
Ahhh!
♪
[INDEX] That's the Baopiaozi.
The grimoire dealing
with eternal youth.
It also discusses the process
of alchemy, by which an elixir
can be created that will
cure any disease or curse.
[coughing]
[MAN] I thought being
a magician meant having
the power to do
anything you wanted.
That's why I took the oath
and became what I am today.
So nothing could ever
stand in my way again.
That's the reason. I did this
for myself and no one else.
[MAN] It has
nothing to do with her.
That woman dying
from a cruel curse.
A powerless, pitiful woman who
doesn't fight but smiles softly
and accepts death as it closes
its fist around her heart.
[groaning]
[MAN] If I couldn't help
her, then clearly that meant
I did not possess
the boundless power
that I believed to be
a magician's right.
[MAN] That's
why I am doing this.
Not to save her but to prove
that my power is absolute
and nothing can
stand in my way.
[MAN] Ah, ahhh!
[MAN] I am here for
myself, not for that poor,
pathetic woman.
It's not about her.
It was never about her.
You're wrong.
You're lying to yourself.
Your bow's power.
It's been amplified too much,
and the contents of your mind
are beginning to
bleed out into mine.
[INDEX] That's how I know.
I know the truth. You're
simply in love with her.
That's why you're risking
your life to prevent her
from dying.
You're willing to do
anything, to hurt anybody
who gets in your way,
as long as you can save her.
[INDEX] But you're
afraid if you admit that,
then the blame for your
actions will fall on her.
So you need to stop this now
before you go any further.
I'm sure using a
grimoire is not the way
she would want you to help her!
Toma!
[KAMIJO] Ah!
♪
Toma. Toma!
[KAMIJO] Geez, you sure
know how to make a guy worry!
[INDEX] You know, I never
did get to eat my snack.
[KAMIJO] I'll feed you all
the food you can eat later.
[INDEX] No, now!
Is this truly wrong?
What I've done. Choosing to
protect somebody else's life
even if it means
losing my own.
Is that really so wrong of me?
♪
You fool. Of course it is.
[KAMIJO] Do you
know how it feels...
to have somebody you
care about die on you?
[KAMIJO] To see them in pain...
To watch them suffer...
And know there's
nothing you can do.
You know that powerless
feeling, don't you?
You feel it for her.
[KAMIJO] To know that
she's dying makes you
panic and grieve,
and it scares you so much
that it shakes you
to your very core.
It makes you want
to scream as the tears
are running down your face.
And that's exactly
why it's wrong!
You'd be passing
all of that to her.
And you don't get to
choose that for somebody!
[MAN coughs]
[MAN] Pathetic.
Look at me, after
reading just one volume.
I'm broken. How could
I actually have expected
this poor vessel to
contain the knowledge
and power of even a
single one of the grimoires?
[MAN chuckles]
My story is just a series
of futile fights for power.
Three times now I've
given up on my life.
But when I did,
there was still one thing
I couldn't give up on...
One reason, one person
to keep fighting for.
♪
[Sphinx screeches]
Ahhh!
[MAN] Ah-haha! Ah-ha!
[KAMIJO] After everything
you've put us through,
you don't get to
end it that easily.
[KAMIJO] That was for
destroying my homework.
Jerk. Do you have any idea
how much trouble
I'm gonna be in?
What?
[KAMIJO] Now then...
Where's this woman you
want to save so badly?
[coughing]
I don't.
Where is she?
We're gonna see if there's
a way we can help her.
Without using a grimoire.
You saw my right
hand, didn't you?
I'm no magician, of course.
And I don't know all
that much about curses.
But if I'm right...
one touch from my hand
should be enough to save her.
[gasps]
What? No.
That's crazy.
I know it may
be hard to believe,
but I have done this
sort of thing before.
All right, then. Let's
go. You can lead the way.
I promise, we're going
to help the woman you love.
But we can't do it alone;
were gonna need you, too.
[KAMIJO] So get up
and dust yourself off.
You do want to help her, right?
No matter what it takes?
[crying]
Oh, honestly.
Now I have to deal
with a magical curse.
How do I keep getting myself
in to these situations?
Well, there's no
time like the present.
Why don't we get going?
We've got a curse to kill.
♪ [Ending Song] ♪
[water sloshing]
[metal clinking]
♪
[groaning]
[KNIGHT 1A] Do you even know
who exactly it is that...
ah... that you...
just attacked?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Sad, isn't it?
England's vaunted knighthood.
Brought down so brutally.
Did you come here
to try and stop me?
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Actually, I was never told
to personally stop you.
Besides, I have my
own task to see to.
[KANZAKI] And where are
your orders coming from?
The English Puritan
Church or Academy City?
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
That's a good question.
Though, if you think about it,
I'm sure you
can figure it out.
Well, I guess it would
be more accurate to say,
if you think about
whose spy I am.
[KANZAKI] In any case,
I'm leaving now.
Feel free to report
to your superiors.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Oh, yeah? Eh...
I'll just take
care of this bunch.
[KANZAKI] I owe you one.
So anyway, I have to admit,
I'm kind of curious.
What would make you travel
all the way here from England?
[KANZAKI] Good question.
[KAMIJO] The arrival of
an old friend brings news of
a missing grimoire
and a kidnapped nun.
With so many factions fighting,
things are bound
to get complicated.
[KAMIJO] Next time,
"The Book of the Law."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.