[KAMIJO] I am without a doubt
a seriously unlucky person.
[blop]
[KAMIJO] For example, let's
look back over the events
following the Daihasei Festival.
Things started out
badly enough, but they only
seemed to get worse
as time went on.
I accidentally walked
in on my teacher
changing her clothes.
Received a solid hair
yank from Fukiyose,
now fully recovered.
Was hit with a surprisingly
accurate gumball,
launched at me by Himegami.
And was forced to do
some weird kind of dance
around a bonfire with Misaka.
Which lead to a kick
in the back of the head
from her friend Kuroko.
Needless to say, I am
now bruised, beaten,
and utterly exhausted.
As I said before, I am
one seriously unlucky gu--
[LADY] Congratulations!
We held a special raffle
on the final day of
the Daihasei Festival,
and the number you picked took
the grand prize, you lucky boy!
And your prize is a
thrilling seven day,
six night trip
to Northern Italy!
[cheering and clapping]
Huh? I really
won a trip to Italy?
♪ [Opening Song] ♪
[KAMIJO] I know I sound
like a broken record,
but I am an unlucky person.
[KAMIJO] Do I have a passport?
Hm? I don't know.
What's a passport?
[chuckles] I knew
something would go wrong.
I knew this trip was
too good to be true.
There're only two
days left 'til I leave.
Even if I requested a
passport today, it wouldn't--
[KAMIJO] Well, what
do you know! My passport!
Let's take a look.
I wonder how many foreign
countries I've been to.
[INDEX] Oh, hey, you know what?
I've got a little book
that looks a lot like that!
Hm?
What? All these
pages are blank.
There isn't a
single stamp in this!
Hm?
Well, I'm confused.
How'd you get here
with a blank passport?
Does it really matter?
The important thing
is that I have one.
And since I do, can I come
along with you on your trip?
You wouldn't leave me
here all alone, would you?
Ah... Well, um.
[KAMIJO] There's no reason
not to invite her, right?
I mean, what could go wrong?
[KAMIJO] Haven't forgotten
anything, have you?
Your wallet, passport,
and plane ticket,
your necessary documents, your
toothbrush and toothpaste.
Uh, what else is there?
Why are you being such
a worrywart about this?
I thought vacations were
supposed to be relaxing.
Yeah. You know
what, you're right.
I should try to calm down
and just enjoy the ride.
That's exactly
what I'm gonna do!
Relish the moment!
Italy, here I come!
I hope you're ready
for Toma Kamijo!
Yeah!
[beep]
[footsteps]
[KAMIJO] Um, is there
a problem, ma'am?
Yes, I'm afraid there is.
[KAMIJO] Huh?
[KAMIJO] Damn!
We have to hurry, Index!
You need something
to wear that's not
held together with
pieces of sharp metal!
What? You're taking
me shopping, Toma?
Aww, that's so sweet of you!
[KAMIJO] All the shops are
more than a kilometer away.
And there are only twenty-eight
minutes 'til takeoff!
Damn, damn, damn! Damn my
stupid, awful, rotten luck!
[aircraft noise]
[birds chirping]
[KAMIJO] Wow, we sure
are close to the sea, huh?
We're surrounded by the sea.
That's probably a more
accurate way to put it.
To be more specific,
the town of Chioggia,
where we currently are, is
on an island in the Adriatic.
Yeah?
♪
[KAMIJO] Whew!
You know how
after we landed,
we spent so long running
around, looking for
giant safety pins that our
tour guide left us behind?
I admit, at that point I
was really starting to worry,
but we made it
here after all.
Well, you wouldn't
need a guide
if you spoke the language.
One should be at least
trilingual in a modern,
international
society like ours.
I don't want to be
lectured by someone
who can't even make it
through airport security.
Ahh!
We can eat after we drop
off our luggage at the hotel.
I know that!
I'm not stupid.
But you can't blame
a girl for looking!
[INDEX] Is that
authentic squid ink gelato?
The food looks great.
We'll totally get some,
but once we're all
checked in, I think that
we should head into Venice.
I've always wanted to ride
in a gondola, you know?
[chuckles]
Uh. Where'd she go?
Hey! Index, where are you?
C'mon this isn't funny!
[KAMIJO] Index!
Are you out there?
I should be careful,
or else I'm the one
who's gonna get lost.
[ITALIAN LADY] Ciao!
Hai qualche problema?
Sorry?
Ah, non sai
parlare Italiano. Eh?
[ITALIAN LADY]
C' e un ristorante la e il
direttore e giapponese.
"Hola, me llamo--"
No, that isn't it.
[nervous laughter]
[ORSOLA] Scusi.
Lui è un mio amico.
La ringrazio per
la sua gentilezza.
[ITALIAN LADY]
Hm. Prego. Ciao!
[ORSOLA] I'm sorry. Maybe I
shouldn't have interrupted you.
You seemed lost. I thought
you could use some help,
but you probably had it
under control, didn't you?
[KAMIJO] Um, Orsola?
Hi there!
[ORSOLA] I didn't expect to
see you. What brings you here?
[KAMIJO] Oh. I kind of won
a trip to Italy in a raffle.
So, uh, what are you doing here?
I thought you were in London.
[ORSOLA] I still kept a
residence here under my name.
I'm moving out of it now.
As I'm sure you can imagine,
things were a bit hectic
when I switched
my allegiance from
the Roman Orthodox to
the English Puritan Church.
I have quite a few
things that still
need to be moved.
But fortunately for me,
some of the Amakusa
offered to help out.
Isn't that kind of them?
[KAMIJO] Wait,
when you say "Amakusa"
do you mean the Amakusa?
[ORSOLA] So, anyway,
what is it you were
doing back there?
Some shopping?
[KAMIJO] Huh?
Oh, no, that's not it.
I brought Index with me,
and everything was going fine,
and then she just disappeared.
[ORSOLA] I'm starting
to think we were fated
to run into each other!
I mean it. This couldn't
have been better timing!
Maybe I can
even talk you into
helping us move my things?
[KAMIJO] Uh.
Well, it's like I said,
Index disappeared
and I need to find her.
[ORSOLA] Oh. That should
be easy enough to do.
Huh?
[INDEX] Toma! Toma!
Toma! Look at this!
I got a discount because
I bought the economy size!
Can you believe it? All
of this gelato, just for me!
Yum!
[KAMIJO] Ugh...
There, you see. I ran into
her a little while ago too.
She was pressed up against
the window of a gelato shop.
So I asked a friend of
mine to invite her here.
I thought she would be
much safer if she wasn't
on her own in
a strange place.
Why, Index?
Why must you do this to me?
[INDEX] Ah, Orsola!
Will lunch be ready soon?
Ah!
[ORSOLA] Yes. It shouldn't
be much longer now.
[INDEX] Hooray!
[KAMIJO] Just my luck.
[MALE AMAKUSA 14A] That's the
guy that His Holiness holds
in such high
esteem? Look at him.
How powerful can he really be?
You're only asking
that because you weren't
with us when we helped
rescue Sister Orsola.
If you were there,
then you would know.
That guy pitted himself
against the Roman Orthodox
Warrior Sisters when he
was unarmed and alone.
Do you suppose you'd have the
guts to do something like that?
I don't think so.
You wanna know what's
even more impressive?
He saw the Priestess
without her clothes on,
and he didn't need to
be hospitalized after she
beat him with the scabbard of
her Shichiten Shichito sword.
[ALL] That guy's a freak.
[KAMIJO] I can't tell. Was that
supposed to be a compliment?
[INDEX and KAMIJO]
Wow! It looks great!
We don't deserve this.
We haven't even
helped you move yet.
You shouldn't have
gone to all this trouble.
Please, I would offer
you two my hospitality
whether you helped or not.
In that case, thank you!
Care for a hot towel?
I appreciate it.
Oh, no problem.
[FEMALE AMAKUSA 14A]
Well, Itsuwa?
How did operation Hot Towel go?
[MALE AMAKUSA 14A]
Don't be stupid.
It's too soon
to see any results.
We need to let things
run their course.
[FEMALE AMAKUSA 14B] Isn't
there a more direct way
to go about this?
Aren't the Amakusa
going to eat with us?
I guess not. They said
something about being
in training and needing to
observe a strict meal regimen.
Toma!
Go ahead. Please,
you should both eat
before your food gets cold.
Okay, then.
[INDEX and KAMIJO]
Thank you for the food!
[INDEX and KAMIJO] Yummy!
Incredible! I never knew
pasta could be so good!
[INDEX] I know! This is about
five hundred times better
than what you usually
make at home, Toma!
[KAMIJO] Why do you
complain all the time?
Oh, who cares? This
food is freaking amazing!
[INDEX] So good! So good!
So, you two...
since you're in the area,
I'm guessing you'd like
to take a look at Venice?
Yeah, we really want to.
We can't get a hold of our tour
guide, though, so I don't know.
But you have to see it.
You'd be missing out
on something special.
"The City of Water,"
"The Queen of the Adriatic."
People have given many
different names to Venice.
[ORSOLA] It's too
beautiful for just one.
Well, I guess we'll
have to take a look.
Right, Index?
[INDEX] I couldn't care
less what we do just as long
as I get to keep
eating like this!
[KAMIJO]
What are you even saying?
[KAMIJO] Uh! There we go.
[vacuum humming]
So, packing dishes
is next on the list.
Orsola! I need
to wrap the dishes.
Where did you say
the newspaper is?
[ORSOLA] It should be in one
of the rooms down the hall.
Hm?
[shower running]
[INDEX humming]
[KAMIJO] That tune combined
with the sound of water
can only mean...
Wah! Look at me!
There's dirt and
dust all over the place!
I'm getting filthy!
You're more than
welcome to take a shower
if you would like.
You must be worn out from
your trip and all this packing.
Back away, Toma!
I know what this is!
The ol' bathroom trap! Whew!
And to think I almost
fell for it, too!
[ORSOLA humming]
[KAMIJO] That same song again?
Something's not right.
What the hell is going on here?
[INDEX and ORSOLA humming]
[KAMIJO] Surely there
wouldn't be two bathrooms
across from each other.
One of them will contain a
naked girl, and the other won't.
Damn. What kind of
screwed-up choice is that?
[KAMIJO] Right,
no, left. No, wait!
I only hear the shower
coming from the left.
So, the correct
answer is, the right!
Yep! Got it! Here we go.
[KAMIJO] As the reality began
to sink in, I had to wonder...
Why didn't it occur to me
to just knock on the door
and ask what was going
on before I walked in?
[humming]
Uh...
♪
[stuttering]
[ORSOLA] Um, hello.
Uh, I was sure that the
other door was the bathroom.
I'm really sorry!
[INDEX screams]
What is this crazy contraption
that keeps blowing hot air?
Ahhh!
[KAMIJO] Wait! You mean,
there are two bathrooms?
And they're right across
the hall from each other?
[ORSOLA] Yes. One was
already here, of course.
And, as for the other...
I had it installed
for religious
use when I moved in.
[ORSOLA] It functioned as
a separate area for baptisms.
Now that I'm leaving
it is no longer needed.
[KAMIJO] This is
ridiculous! I call foul!
[INDEX] Toma.
What are you
doing poking around
behind closed doors, anyway?
And also, Toma, why
wasn't the first thing
out of your mouth
an abject apology?
Well, uh, you see,
Index, it's like this.
I was just--I was looking
for some newspape--
[INDEX growls]
[KAMIJO] Ahhh!
[KAMIJO] Damn my luck!
You two! You're so cute!
[trunk running]
[truck door closing]
[ORSOLA] There we are. I believe
that is the last of the boxes.
[ORSOLA] Thank you so much. I
really appreciate all your help.
I'm sorry to have kept you from
enjoying your
vacation for so long.
Well, what are you up
to for the next few days?
You could always
come with us.
We'll just be
seeing the sights.
No, really I couldn't.
Before long, you two will
be heading back to your hotel.
And you don't want
me around for that.
Like they say, two's company,
but three is a crowd.
What? Why is three a crowd?
That's not really
a topic we need to
discuss any further, Index!
And, anyway... I'd like
to take a little time to
go around Chioggia and
say goodbye to some people.
I've lived in this city
for quite a while, you see.
[ORSOLA] And, to be honest,
that's really the sort of thing
I'd prefer to do on my own.
I hate goodbyes, so I'm afraid
I may be a bit of a basket case.
[KAMIJO] I see.
[ORSOLA] Okay. I should be on
my way. I hope to see you again.
If you have the chance,
you should definitely
visit me in London sometime.
[KAMIJO] Yeah.
You, too, if you're ever
in our area again, I mean.
[INDEX] You're going to
need to do a lot of cleaning
before we can have guests, Toma.
Hold on a second.
There's something--
Get down, you guys!
A-A-T-R.
[gasps]
[KAMIJO] Orsola!
[ORSOLA] Oh, my!
[KAMIJO] Index could
tell that something was up.
And that means.
It's magic!
[ORSOLA] Magic?
[groans]
[KAMIJO] Where's it coming
from? Who's attacking us?
[KAMIJO] Ah...!
[INDEX] Toma!
♪
[INDEX] I-S-I-C-B-I.
Ah...
[KAMIJO grunts]
[gasping for air]
[breathing heavily]
What about the sniper?
No need to worry. It's
being dealt with already.
What do you mean dealt
with? What did you do?
[INDEX] If we're being attacked
so accurately from a distance,
there must be
someone on the ground
relaying the situation to him.
And that means that no
matter where they're located,
they must be taking in my
spell intercept, as well.
[ASSASSIN groans]
[ASSASSIN] Abbandoniamo
l'avanguardia! Torniamo subito!
La ucciderò sulla nave!
That must be the
sniper up there!
[ALL gasp]
♪
Whoa! What's happening?
[BOTH] Ah!
[INDEX yelps]
♪
What? This is nuts!
Something like this can't
just pop out of the canal!
[ORSOLA struggling]
Our best bet is probably
to get into the ship.
[ORSOLA] Uh. Right.
What is this, glass?
No. I think it's ice.
[BOTH gasp]
[INDEX] Toma! Are you okay?
Where are you going?
What do you think
a huge ship like this
is doing sailing the canal?
♪
[ORSOLA] The canal! It appears
that we're heading out to sea.
[KAMIJO] Yeah. I wonder
what the final destination is.
[running footsteps]
[BOTH gasp]
[ASSASSIN 14B] Cerca!
Devono essere in dentro!
[ORSOLA] What should we do?
It sounds like that man
is deploying people
to search for us.
[KAMIJO] I know,
but unfortunately...
jumping overboard doesn't
look like a good option.
I say we hide for now and
wait for a chance to escape.
[INDEX] They're gone.
Damn it! What in
the world is going on?
[distant footsteps]
We should go.
[ORSOLA] I do hope
we aren't intruding.
[distant footsteps]
[sighs]
[ORSOLA] I don't
understand why anyone
would feel this
was necessary;
sending an enormous ship
like this to attack me.
Well, you know, the robes
those men were wearing
do look a lot
like your habit.
Yes. It is reasonable for
you to assume they are
members of the Roman
Orthodox Church.
And we know what that means.
It's about the Book of the Law.
I don't understand, though.
That incident should
have been settled already.
It's one of the
reasons I crossed over
to the English Puritan Church.
[crash]
♪
[ORSOLA] It looks like the
ship we're on is far from alone.
The enemy has
an entire fleet
of magic vessels
at their disposal.
I guess they couldn't
all deploy until
we got to open water.
[gasps] Index is back
there all alone--Wait!
[beep-beep]
Good thing I can
still use my cell phone.
Aw, damn it. She didn't
bother to charge hers, though.
[KAMIJO] I wonder how much
longer 'til the signal fades.
[ORSOLA] I'm afraid
I have no idea.
[KAMIJO] The door!
Not good! Find
someplace to hide, Orsola!
Yes, all right.
Um, was there a particular
place you had in mind?
Uh! Come here!
Maybe it's just a draft
blowing the door op--
Uh--
[KAMIJO] Agnese?
♪ [Ending Song] ♪
[KAMIJO] An insane
ritual involving Agnese.
A powerful secret weapon called
the Queen of the Adriatic.
And now Tatemiya
and the Amakusa, too?
Next time, "Queen's Fleet."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.