[KAMIJO] The leader of Hound Dog
easily overpowers Accelerator.
However, his top priority
is to recover Last Order.
Accelerator is able to save her,
but is left helpless
himself, and then...
[INDEX] Excuse me.
What's going on over there?
♪ [Opening Song] ♪
[wheezes]
Huh?
Tch.
[HOUND DOG F] What do we do?
Huh? You need
me to tell you?
[AMATA]
We've gotta eliminate her.
[grunts]
[ACCELERATOR screams]
[pained gasp]
[ACCELERATOR]
You should start driving.
If you don't get to the hospital
soon, it'll be too late for you.
[wheezes]
[tires screech]
You waiting for an invitation?
Start shooting already!
[HOUND DOGS] Yes, sir!
[INDEX] Ah!
[ACCELERATOR]
Don't try anything.
Just keep on driving,
nice and fast.
[ACCELERATOR] Time is running
out for both of us, right?
Right. So, where would
you like me to go?
[ACCELERATOR] Lucky for us,
I know a good doctor.
Okay. You know what
I'm gonna need.
Get it for me now.
[AMATA] That was a nice try.
But by jumping in
a car like that,
you're sending me a
pretty clear message that
your wind control
isn't working anymore.
[AMATA] Adios, scumbag.
Huh?
Alright.
[VENTO] Nice city, huh?
Can't say I care much for
the inhabitants, but they have
some interesting architecture.
Who the hell are you?
You might say that we're
rivals in the killing game.
Ugh. You deal with her.
Good. I'm glad to see you're
not taking this personally.
[AMATA] If you want
my personal attention,
you'll have to try
harder than that.
[car engine starts]
Wow, what a guy.
Your boss sure knows how to
make a girl feel special.
[VENTO] I'm curious to see how
well he chooses his minions.
[chuckles]
"These are the people
who attacked him,"
says Misaka Misaka,
calmly reporting the facts
as she remembers them.
[KAMIJO] Did he do all of this?
If so, it doesn't seem
like he needs help.
[LAST ORDER] "I don't think so.
He is short-tempered
and violently efficient in
a fight. It seems unlikely that
his retaliation would
be so minor. No way,"
says Misaka Misaka,
coming to a conclusion.
In any case,
we need to report this.
[LAST ORDER] "I think they're
coming back! We should hide,"
states Misaka Misaka,
taking cover behind a car
and forcing you to do the same.
Who are "they"?
[MAN quiet grunts]
[ACCELERATOR] Hey, driver.
What's this thing?
[MAN] Oh, that's
an osmatic sensor.
We use them to track
down our targets.
So it's basically like
a mechanical police dog.
[ACCELERATOR] The city
seems unusually quiet.
I wonder if it's all a part of
whatever Kihara's
bigger plan is.
[INDEX hums]
Anyway, what were
you doing back there?
You got some
kinda death wish?
Hmm? Oh, I just came to
give you back something
you let me borrow.
Here you go!
I'm sure you must've
been missing these.
What the hell are
you talking about?
Those things are disposable.
Huh? Hmmm.
[INDEX] "And so
the ugly duckling,
who had always been
teased for her appearance,
grew up and became
a fine-looking duck.
Everyone loved her and she
was happy. Forever and ever."
Um, so what exactly does
"fine-looking" mean?
[ACCELERATOR] What was that?
That's not how the ugly
duckling story goes.
Then how is it
supposed to go?
Well, gimme a second and
let me think about it.
[ACCELERATOR]
From what the kid said,
the ugly duckling was
teased by the other ducks
because she
didn't look like them.
But in the end she grew up and
it turned out she was a swan,
not a duck, so that's
why she looked different.
And it didn't matter that
the ducks were mean to her
because she wasn't
one of them, anyway.
Tch.
When you say "the kid"
do you mean the little girl
in the photo you
were looking for?
It's kind of a long story,
but I'm actually
still looking for her.
[INDEX] You two got
separated again?
Yeah, and that's why
you and I are gonna
have to part ways. I've gotta
find another little brat.
I can help you
look for her!
I don't mind. Really, I can tell
you're super worried about her.
[INDEX] I think
Toma would understand
why I wanna help you.
You can pull over
anytime now.
There's a huge hospital
somewhere around this area.
I need you to go there and
find a doctor whose face looks
a whole heck of
a lot like a frog.
When you find him,
tell him this:
As soon as humanly possible,
he needs to get a battery
ready for the Misaka Network
connection electrode.
He'll know what that means.
I think I got it.
One battery for the
Misaka Network connection
electrode coming right up!
[SPHINX meows]
[INDEX] I'll see you soon.
[ACCELERATOR] Huh?
You're going to wait
right here until I get back
so we can keep looking together.
Yeah, whatever. Just get
going already, will ya?
[INDEX laughs]
[ACCELERATOR] Come on.
Let's move.
I'm losing a lot of blood.
Aren't you going
to let me go soon?
[groans]
Want to lose it faster?
Stop whining and just go.
[KAMIJO shaky exhale]
Hang in there, okay?
I'm gonna get you out of here.
[KAMIJO heavy breathing]
Of course.
Of course it's locked.
There may be a
way to unlock it.
[buzz]
[KAMIJO] It would be best if we
could get to a populated area.
I seriously doubt they're eager
to draw attention to themselves.
[LAST ORDER] "If we're on the
run, too, how are we supposed to
find a way to help him?
What can we do? Well?"
asks Misaka Misaka, frustrated
by her total helplessness.
I don't know. However,
one thing's for sure.
[KAMIJO] We can't
help him if we're dead.
So if you want to find
a way to save your friend,
you should concentrate
on surviving first.
[LAST ORDER] "Mm. You're right,"
says Misaka Misaka,
accepting your logic.
[KAMIJO] Okay.
Then let's do this.
[KAMIJO gasps]
Whatever happened here,
it doesn't look good.
Let's get outside. Come on.
[KAMIJO grunts]
[gunfire]
[FROG DOCTOR]
Why are you calling me
at this hour of the night?
[ACCELERATOR] Listen, doc,
there's trouble, major trouble.
One of the Misaka sisters
gave me a run down
on the basic situation,
so I'm better informed
than you may think.
[FROG DOCTOR] It's
actually quite useful.
Seems they perform a kind
of information exchange
across their electrical network.
[ACCELERATOR] Good.
I'm glad you're up to speed.
Can you tell me what's
happened with the kid?
[FROG DOCTOR] Well, it appears
that she's currently being
pursued by a separate
Hound Dog unit.
Word is she's with a bystander
who just happened
to be there with
her at the time.
[ACCELERATOR] Tch.
Where are they?
[FROG DOCTOR] Unfortunately,
she doesn't seem
to know that herself.
[ACCELERATOR] Did a weird
kid wearing a nun's habit
show up there yet?
Yes, she did.
Would you care to explain
how she knows about
your proxy calculator?
[ACCELERATOR] You don't
need to worry about that.
Just keep her there
with you, okay?
[siren wails]
[FROG DOCTOR sighs] Very well.
So, just how far are you
planning to take this?
I'll find Kihara
and kill him.
And I'm gonna bring down
all of Hound Dog, too.
After that's been dealt with,
I'm taking the kid
home, unharmed.
[FROG DOCTOR] You'll never
succeed. I mean it.
Stop and think this
through for a moment.
You've got too many objectives
for one person to achieve.
There's simply no way
you can do it all.
Don't tell me what
I can and can't handle.
--What do you know ab--
--I know what kind of hell
you've been through,
but I've seen worse.
Which is why I have
no problem saying this.
Don't take on too much.
If you do, you're only
[FROG DOCTOR] setting
yourself up for more failure.
Make saving Last Order
your only priority.
Do you understand?
As long as she's still alive,
I'll be able to heal her,
but Accelerator, if you don't
do your part, I can't do mine.
[ACCELERATOR] Heh. All right
doc, you've got a deal.
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
The Right Seat of God, huh?
I never believed they
would actually go this far.
Hm?
This is Yomikawa
calling HQ.
[YOMIKAWA] Requesting
additional details
on call three-three-four.
[radio static]
Who is this girl?
[gasps]
What's happening?
[MAN] Renewable Resource
Treatment Plant
number three, huh?
[WOMAN] The target's scent
continues in there?
You're absolutely sure of that?
You want to get out of here
in one piece, don't you?
Then I'd recommend sitting
still and being quiet.
[ACCELERATOR] There, a
cleaning agent. That'll do it.
Now I just need to
wash away my scent
and get out of here before
they track me down.
Damn it. That's them.
They made it here
quicker than I expected.
[MIKOTO sighs]
I guess they only have
the small umbrellas.
[phone rings]
[KUROKO] Sissy! Sissy! Sissy!
[MIKOTO] What do
you want, Kuroko?
[KUROKO] I'm tied up
with Judgment duties,
and I'm not going to be able
to make it home quite yet,
so I need you to talk to
our dear head resident
and ask for an extension.
I know it's already
past curfew...
Uh, well, I'm kind of at the
convenience store right now, so.
[KUROKO] Augh!
Of course, tonight
of all nights,
Sissy is breaking
curfew, too.
We're getting
demerits for sure.
The only question
now is how many.
That is unfortunate.
What do you think could have
possibly kept her out
so late this evening?
Ah! Wait, I might
have an idea.
It's possible that she has
a date with a troglodyte.
This is absolutely awful!
That lousy jerk! Taking
advantage of the evening rain
to enjoy a romantic
interlude. It's brilliant!
I cannot stand idly by and
allow this charade to continue.
I have a duty to
preserve Sissy's virtue.
Sorry, but you can't go.
You see that mountain of
paperwork over there, right?
There's no way I can
get through that alone.
I'm going to need help.
Aahhh!
[KAMIJO] What's
happening out there?
Why aren't they coming in?
[VENTO] Hello!
[KAMIJO gasps]
[VENTO] I hope I didn't
startle you or anything.
Really, don't be scared.
Come on out.
We've got things to
talk about, you and I.
Plus, if you don't show yourself
soon, I'll be forced to act.
And the kind of methods I use
aren't pleasant for anybody.
[KAMIJO gasps]
Tell me who you are!
A member of the
Right Seat of God.
I am known as
Vento of the Front.
[VENTO]
Target has been located.
I hope you're ready.
Because it's time to meet
your maker, Toma Kamijo.
[WOMAN] Well, Rod?
What's the sensor say?
[ROD] Hang on.
It's still working.
[HOUND DOGS gasp]
[loud clang]
[clang]
[WOMAN breathes heavily]
[gunfire]
[HOUND DOGS scream]
Like I told you, there's
no reason to be frightened.
It'll be over so quickly, you
won't have time to feel pain.
You need to get
out of here and find
some place to hide, okay?
[VENTO laughs]
Quite a show! There's the right
hand I've heard so much about!
[VENTO] It's nice to know
you'll give me a challenge.
From above?
This is fun! I see
you're pretty good at
defending yourself
with that hand.
Just like the report
they gave me said,
that's quite an effective tool.
[VENTO] My favorite
strategy is to attack
from multiple directions,
but I guess that
won't work with you.
I guess not.
It's funny, but I don't
exactly know how
this weapon functions. It may
take some experimentation!
Damn!
[VENTO] Ha! So that's
what that move does!
Sorry about that. I didn't know.
Well, it's starting to look as
if my promise of a painless end
won't be fulfilled, after all.
So unless you happen
to be a masochist,
I'm afraid this won't
be much fun for you.
[KAMIJO] How do
these attacks work?
They don't follow the
movement of her hammer.
Wait, I know.
It's the cross!
Aww! My secret is out, eh?
[KAMIJO] Yeah!
Deflected again. This is
becoming less fun for me
by the second. Here!
[KAMIJO] Ahhh!
Run for it!
[VENTO] Heh...
[LAST ORDER gasps]
Go on! Get outta' here!
Go find some help!
Forget the phone!
[LAST ORDER gasps]
Well, that was awfully
cruel, don't you think?
Making a poor, defenseless
girl run off into the dark
for reinforcements all
on her own like that?
It would be kinder to
put her out of her misery
swiftly and let
her die beside you.
I'll find her as soon as you
and I are finished here.
All the more reason
to stay alive.
How very noble of you.
Unfortunately, when you
and I are finished here,
your insides will
be turned to pulp.
You won't exactly
be feeling heroic.
[VENTO] Now then.
That's enough chit-chat.
This has already taken
quite a bit longer
than I had anticipated.
How about we go ahead
and get it over with, okay?
[yells]
[groaning]
You won't really do it.
I won't? Is that
what you think?
[ACCELERATOR]
Let's see if you're right.
[laughs]
Nope. I guess you were wrong.
You should get to
know your enemy better
before you start
issuing challenges.
[KAMIJO breathes heavily]
[VENTO] Concerned
about a stranger?
Wouldn't you be better
off worrying about
yourself right now?
That's enough!
Heh, heh.
Getting all wound up about it
isn't going to do you any good.
You're aware of everything going
on in Academy City, aren't you?
[VENTO] You have no
idea how valuable you are.
My top priority here
is to kill you.
Everything else is
just icing on the cake.
Even the List of
Prohibited Books is
of secondary importance.
There is no doubt you're
an enemy of the
Roman Orthodox Church.
And we use whatever means
necessary to defeat our enemies.
That includes wiping
out your city.
Or your entire country, for
that matter. Here, take a look.
As you can see, it was
signed by the pope himself.
What are you talking about?
[VENTO] I'm gonna have to
spell it out for you, huh?
All right, then. Maybe it'll
become clearer to you
once I kill every
person in here.
Don't do it!
And, away we go!
[WOMAN] This is Vera.
Status report. Over.
[radio static]
[VERA] Ugh... Great.
[VERA gasps]
Nancy!
[VERA sobbing]
[ACCELERATOR laughs]
[VENTO] Damn it.
[gasps]
[coughs]
[KAMIJO] What happened?
A side effect of the magic?
[VENTO grunts]
[heavy exhale]
[UIHARU] Dinner's here, Shirai!
I didn't know what you wanted,
so I got a couple options.
[KUROKO] It should be me!
That dirty, rotten troglodyte
is out there right now, enjoying
the evening with my Sissy.
Oh! I almost forgot! It's
time for "Sudden Variety."
What channel is it on, again?
[KUROKO] Who cares?!
We've just received word of
a disturbance created by
an intruder here
in Academy City.
It is not yet clear if
there is a connection,
but we have also
received reports of
widespread damage in the area.
Ah! We now have footage.
Have we gotten any
reports tonight that might
correspond to the
video we just saw?
If one person was able
to completely overpower
Antiskill single handedly.
That tells us something about
how dangerous this
intruder must be.
[KUROKO] If it does
get out of hand,
I'm sure Antiskill will request
that we come and back them up.
But until then, let's get as
much paperwork done as possible.
Huh? Uiharu?
[ACCELERATOR] That oughta make
it next to impossible for them
to sniff me out.
Hm?
[ACCELERATOR] Him, huh?
[ROD] Help me! I need
protective custody!
Heh. Just in time!
I won't die after all!
[ROD] You'd better play
nice with Hound Dog,
or you can say goodbye
to that little girl!
[ACCELERATOR grunts]
[ACCELERATOR screams]
Whoa. What the hell was that?
[ROD] Wait! Please,
Accelerator, I'm begging here!
You don't have to--
Aahhh!
You! Step away from him
and put your hands up!
Things are looking
worse by the minute.
So that's it, huh? This is how
the Roman Orthodox Church
[TSUCHIMIKADO] is planning
to bring down Academy City?
First incapacitating
everybody and then
impaling them with
these giant spikes.
Heh.
That's no good, is it?
Aiho!
[beep]
[RADIO VOICE] School District 5.
Testimony provided at the
scene has produced a suspect.
This person is wanted for
questioning in connection
with a case of
attempted murder.
[gasps]
♪ [Ending Song] ♪
[KAMIJO] People are
collapsing left and right.
Accelerator continues on his
mission to rescue Last Order.
And then, out of nowhere.
Whoa! What's going on?
Next time, "Testament."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.