[booming]
[FEMALE REPORTER 8A]
In just a few minutes,
the Daihasei Festival's
opening ceremony will begin.
Academy City is
filled with spectators
and students' families all here
to watch the sporting events.
[MAIKA] Come and get it
while it's fresh, everybody!
One of Academy City's
famous Maid-made lunches.
You don't want
to miss your chance!
[MAIKA] The maids at
Ryoran Household Arts School
know how to make lunch!
Or, to be more accurate,
the probationary maids
[MAIKA] know how
to make a great lunch!
My goodness! They
sure have a wide range of
schools here in Academy
City, don't they, dear?
Well, yes, of course.
That's the point.
The concentration of educational
organizations into one place.
[BOTH] Uh!
Oh, I'm so sorry!
[MISUZU] I should really
watch where I'm going.
I'm sorry. But, uh,
would you happen to know
where Tokiwadai
Middle School is?
Uh...
Oh, if you just
give me a moment.
Let's see here, shall we?
Tokiwadai Middle School.
It's not here. It's
possible that it's just not
open to the public
during the festival.
[WOMAN] Are you sure?
But if that's the case,
then how am I supposed
to find Mikoto?
So this Mikoto
you're looking for,
is she, y'know, your
younger sister or something?
[SHINA] Oh, my goodness!
Doing it again? Honestly, Toya!
[WOMAN] Ah! It
really isn't on here!
Um... "again"?
Doing what now?
[SHINA] Oh, look. Isn't
that Toma right over there?
[KAMIJO] Okay, I'm in!
That's a bet I'm more
than happy to take.
If I lose to you, I'll
play your penalty game.
I swear to do whatever
you tell me to do.
Okay, then,
we have a bet.
Anything I say, right?
Anything at all?
Those are the terms. And,
of course, if you lose,
the same will
apply to you too.
Wha--? Wait. So then,
that means if I lose to you,
I have to do
anything that you say?
Hey, what's wrong?
You didn't have any trouble
talking trash a second ago.
What happened to
your absolute certainty
that you could beat me?
Okay, fine. The bet
is officially on now.
[MIKOTO] But don't come crying
to me when you lose, got it?
Oh, my, my.
I guess she's doing okay.
♪ [Opening Song] ♪
[LAURA] The Daihasei
Festival's opening ceremony
is about to start, is it not?
And you have no
interest in participating
in the festivities, Aleister?
[ALEISTER] You cannot
actually believe that I go out
in public looking like I do.
[LAURA] Very well. Then shall
we proceed with our discussion?
[ALEISTER] We were speaking
about the magician who has
made her way inside the city.
Thanks to the carelessness
of city security measures.
We've actually identified
two persons of interest so far.
[LAURA] An officer of
the Roman Orthodox Church,
and a courier who
is in her employ.
They are said to be here
to conduct a transaction
for a certain big ticket item.
[ALEISTER] And that
item would be...?
[LAURA] This is
what it looks like.
[ALEISTER]
Appears to be a sword.
[LAURA] Naturally,
this is just a replica of
what is called the Stab Sword.
It is claimed this sword
once pierced a dragon,
binding it to
the ground forever.
We don't want it falling
into the wrong hands.
If that were to happen,
it would be a dire predicament
for the English Puritan Church.
[ALEISTER] It sounds like
whoever possesses the sword
will have a tactical advantage.
Our greatest problem
at the moment, however,
is where the transaction
for the sword will be held.
It is unfortunate that it will
occur within Academy City.
[ALEISTER] Oh, yes, I see.
Because of its location,
you are obliged
to involve a certain
young man as a travel guide.
Hey, Toma?
I think I might be
starting to get hungry.
Really? How's
that possible?
You just
finished breakfast.
What difference does
that make when you're
walking down a street
with incredible aromas
wafting around
you everywhere?
[meow]
[INDEX] Ah! How is a
girl supposed to choose
when everything looks so
delicious? I want it all!
Yeah. Okay, fine.
I'll take you around to
all the different
food stands later on.
Did you say "later"?
Yep. The first event is
about to start, you know.
Uh!
[KAMIJO] Have a pamphlet. The
events I'm taking part in
today are marked in there.
Now come on. Let's go.
Strange. This isn't like Toma.
He's in a very
no-nonsense mood today.
♪
[ALL groaning]
[PIERCE] I'm done.
I don't wanna do this.
[KAMIJO] It's only the
first day of the festival.
How can everybody be
so exhausted already?
We spent all morning
arguing about our strategy
for beating the other schools.
Unfortunately, the lively
debate seems to have
sapped all of our
strength. So, here we are.
What a stupid
waste of energy!
Welcome to
student competition.
That's just how
these things work.
[KAMIJO] Just my luck.
[GIRL] What's everybody
doing laying around
on the ground?
Let me guess, Kamijo.
You were being
lazy again, as usual
and they decided to
follow your example.
Hey, don't go
blaming this on me.
I just got here.
So then, you showed up
late and your tardiness
sucked the enthusiasm
out of everyone else.
[KAMIJO] Fukiyose, you
got here later than I did!
'Cause I was taking care of
steering committee
business, you idiot!
Just lay off of me, will you!
I'm having a difficult
enough time getting back
on my feet without you
publicly humiliating me.
Your blood sugar
is probably low.
Here. Have a sports drink
and suck it up, dude.
Go on, be a man.
And I don't want to hear
about any "bad luck."
I can't stand it
when people use
that as an excuse!
[FUKIYOSE] Your attitude
affects the attitudes
of everyone around you!
So shut up and put
on your big boy face!
Uh...!
Um... sorry. I... Uhhh.
Do you have
something to say?
No ma'am,
I don't! Nothing!
[sighs]
And we're supposed
to work together
for the tower toppling event.
This may turn out
to be a weird day.
[KOMOE] Like I said,
you have to acknowledge that
there are deficiencies
in our facilities.
That's a result
of the school budget
and in no way a
reflection on the students.
[TEACHER IN SUIT 8A] But
isn't the subpar quality of
your students the reason
your school receives
such little funding
from the board?
Ha! It must make going
to work in the morning
extra hard,
being stuck with rejects.
I don't think of
them as "rejects."
They are neither
successes nor failures.
In fact, I don't think of them
as a group but as individuals.
Whatever you
need to tell yourself
to make it through the day.
We'll see the truth
of the matter soon enough.
[TEACHER IN SUIT 8A] If you
need me, I'll be in the stands,
watching as your
kids get crushed
to pieces in the tower topple.
[TEACHER IN SUIT 8A laughing]
No you won't, you big jerk.
[KOMOE] My students
aren't rejects!
You just don't know them.
[KAMIJO] All right, that's it.
Let's go out
there and take this.
[KAMIJO] So what do you say,
are you guys with me?
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER 8A] The first
event is the tower topple.
The schools are
now taking the field.
[crowd cheering]
[MIKOTO] What was he
thinking taking that bet?
There's no way that his
school is going to beat ours.
[INDEX] Uuuhhh...
I'm dying. So hungry.
Uh...
Are you sure you're not
suffering from heatstroke?
Here, have some water.
Ah!
[stomach growls]
That answers that.
You really are just
super hungry, aren't you?
Thanks for the
drink, short-hair,
but why are you here?
Come to cheer on Toma?
Uh. Gimme a break!
Why would I be doing that?
Do I look like a
cheerleader to you?
We've got a bet about
which team is going to win.
That's the reason I'm here.
Not that I'm worried--
I obviously
have it in the bag.
But what then?
What am I supposed
to do when I win?
I mean, he said he would
do whatever I told him to.
Hey! It's Toma!
[MIKOTO] He looks like he's
taking this really seriously.
Don't tell me he actually
plans to win this! Oh, no!
What is he going to make
me do if he wins the bet?
Everyone ready? Begin!
[ALL] Ahhh!
[crowd cheering]
What--What's
going on, you guys?
I don't think I've ever
seen you try so hard
for something before.
Honestly, I am somewhat
concerned about how beat-up
and run-down you all look now.
But more than that...
But more than
that I'm so proud!
[KAMIJO] Hey, Index,
you around here?
Honestly, why can't
she just stay put?
Oh, my cell phone.
It's still in my bag.
[footsteps]
Ah-uhh...
Huh?
♪
Um... I just came here
to get my cell so I could
track down a friend
of mine because
she wasn't where she
said she was going to be.
[KAMIJO] I had absolutely no
intention of seeing you naked!
Uh...
Huah!
Huh? Oh, finally!
There you are!
Hey, what's wrong?
Your eyes are all watery
and your nose is red.
Tell me, Index.
Where's your cell?
Right here, see?
Yeah! So why
didn't you answer it?
Uh--Uuah...
Right. The battery's dead.
Who cares about
phones and batteries?
I'm hungry!
If you don't give me
something to eat
soon, I might die!
[sighs] Let's go to
the concession area.
They'll have plenty of
food for you to choose from.
'Kay! Let's go!
Oh, sorry, but you're
gonna have to turn back.
The parade is starting soon,
so we're blocking off the area.
[KAMIJO] Um, but we just need
to cross over there real quick.
There's an
underground mall about
three kilometers
to the west of here.
[YOMIKAWA] You guys
can get across that way.
[KAMIJO] Three kilometers?
But, I can almost
taste it from here.
Yeah. You're gonna
have to tough it out
until the giant
ball roll is over.
To... ma...
Whoa. Easy, now. Ah!
[KAMIJO] Use your words!
Hah! I got you!
That's the last
thing on the list!
Victory is mine now!
[MIKOTO laughs]
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER 8B] First
place in the scavenger hunt
goes to Tokiwadai Middle
School student Mikoto Misaka!
I'm on the scavenger hunt list?
[MIKOTO] Kind of. It said
"A high school student
who competed in
the first event."
It just so happens you
fit that bill perfectly.
Yeah. Me and a whole bunch of
other people
who were competing.
It's not like I'm the only guy.
Ahh. Ah, ah, ah!
Hey, get off!
What are you doing?
[coughing]
Uh...
Sorry. Here, you want
some of my drink?
You know what?
Just take the whole thing!
♪
[UIHARU] So...
While the rest
of us were outside,
toiling under the
blazing sun today,
I thought about
you, stuck inside
and trying to recover
your strength.
I felt so bad that you
weren't getting to be
a part of all this.
That's why I came;
to see if you wanted
to give us a hand at work.
[giggles]
Hm. How very
kind of you to drag me
out of bed and into the field.
So, have there been any
problems to deal with so far?
[UIHARU] No, it's been quiet.
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER 8B] In first
place, contestant Mikoto Misaka.
She walks calmly,
waving and smiling.
It looks like the race
wasn't arduous enough
to leave her winded.
Look at her! I'm so proud!
My beautiful Sissy!
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER 8B] And,
of course, she's never too
caught up in the competition to
care for a fellow contestant.
Huh?
I'll kill him!
[KAMIJO breathing heavy]
It's been a while
since I've seen Index.
I hope she's still doing okay.
♪
[KAMIJO] Stiyl's here?
City security has been
relaxed a bit lately
to make spectators
from the general public
feel more at ease, right?
Yeah, I bet that's it.
And now some magicians
have taken advantage
of that fact in
order to sneak in.
We've identified two
such magicians so far.
Lidvia Lorenzetti of
the Roman Orthodox Church
and a courier she hired by
the name of Oriana Thomson.
She needs a courier?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] They're
here attempting to conduct
a transaction for
a relic that's been
handed down through the Church.
That doesn't make any sense.
Academy City's
got less to do with
the occult than
anywhere else I know.
All the more reason.
Don't you see?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Here,
representatives of both
the scientific and magical
communities will have
a difficult time interfering.
[STIYL] That said, this can't
be allowed to go forward.
We must do
something to stop it.
[KAMIJO] Well why don't
you give Kanzaki a call?
She's a saint or
something, right?
We can't use her. Not Kanzaki.
Especially not for this.
Not when it's this particular
relic we're dealing with.
Why? What's so
special about it?
Here's the thing,
the magicians are here
for an item called
the Stab Sword.
And if the
rumors are correct,
it spells instant death for
any saint who's struck by it.
[GIRL STUDENT] Look out!
[BOY STUDENT] Heads up!
Huh? What's going on?
What are you doing, Kamijo?
[FUKIYOSE]
Get back on your feet!
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Everybody
knows that Jesus Christ
died on the cross,
but do you know how
he was actually killed, Kami?
[KAMIJO] You mean it
wasn't... the crucifixion?
He was speared
to death by a Roman.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] The Stab
Sword distills the religious
significance of the crucifixion
and spearing and amplifies,
condenses, and focuses it
to an extreme degree of power.
It would have
little effect on
a normal, everyday person.
But for a saint,
things are different.
A single strike from
it, and she's dead.
Obviously, it's
no ordinary weapon.
What are the
magicians planning for
to need something like that.
Stocking up their
arsenal for a war.
In the magical world,
saints are basically living,
breathing tactical weapons.
Yeah, okay. But there are
still plenty of magicians
who aren't
saints though, right?
I get the feeling you
guys could hold your own
even without Kanzaki.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] That isn't
the real issue here, though.
Huh?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] It's not about
which side will actually win.
It's about the illusion of
one side having the advantage.
That's when wars
are likely to break out.
[KAMIJO] But, if the
problem is this serious,
shouldn't we be enlisting
Index's cooperation?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] No can do.
Unfortunately, we can't use
the List of
Prohibited Books for this.
We can't let her get
anywhere near the site.
Nor can we allow her
to have any information
regarding this incident.
[KAMIJO] But why?
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Because outside magicians
will concentrate
their search on her,
thinking that if
anything is happening,
she must be at
the center of it.
If she so much
as lifts a finger,
she'll be swarmed
by magicians.
They'll descend on her like a
plague of malnourished locusts.
Basically, we have
to do everything we can
to keep her from
noticing what's happening.
Great, because that
shouldn't be difficult at all.
After Yomikawa
alerted me,
I got to you as
soon as I could.
You were lying there as
limp as week-old lettuce.
I was really
worried about you!
Ahh!
That was delicious.
Thank you!
I really do wish
Toma had told me
where was running
off to, you know?
I need to find him.
I mean, it's almost
time for lunch.
Uh, you meant dinner,
right? Wasn't this lunch?
[INDEX] I hate this.
Toma hasn't spent
time with me all day.
It's really
starting to feel like
we're growing apart, you know?
I understand. You
two are good friends.
It makes sense that
you'd want to spend
the Daihasei Festival
with him. I'm sorry.
[gasps]
I have an idea! You
might feel better
if you were able
to participate!
Oh yeah?
Not here. I wonder if I
should report her missing.
Is something the matter?
You've just been
standing there with
a look on your face
like you're about to
begin a final boss
battle or something.
Yeah. Kind of like
you're expecting
to die at any moment.
If you'd like a last
meal, I can offer you
a special maid
made lunch.
Never mind me.
Have you seen Index
around anywhere?
Huh?
If you're talking
about the sister,
she was wandering
in that direction.
[KAMIJO] Really? Thank you!
If it helps, it
seemed like she was
with that teacher
from your school.
You know, the
one who looks like
she'd be at home
in Munchkinland.
[bird caws]
Is she in there?
[meow]
Oh, it's just you, Sphinx.
Have you seen Index?
[KOMOE] I'm really
sorry about this.
I just couldn't think of
anywhere more convenient
for you to change,
so I thought that we--
♪
Uh...
Geez, Toma. How
many times is it that
you've walked
in on me changing!
Are... you...?
Oh! Ohhhhhh!
Index? Uh, hey.
What's the big deal?
[KAMIJO] It was an accident.
I mean, there's really
no need to be embarrassed.
Uh-oh.
[FUKIYOSE] Kamijo! I come here
on steering committee business,
looking for Miss Tsukuyomi,
and what do I find?
[scream]
Care to tell me what
exactly you're doing here?
You moronic,
perverted slacker!
[KAMIJO screams]
[FUKIYOSE] Honestly!
Would it be too much to ask
for you to put just
a little effort into
making this tournament
a success for us?
So, which event
is our school
participating in right now?
You can't even remember
that? Are you kidding?
I know! Maybe your brain
isn't getting enough nutrients!
You should up
your vitamin intake!
I, um... I don't think
there's enough vitamins
in the world to cure
me of my stupidity!
Sounds like you don't
need my help to insult you.
It's the second-year
girls' tug of war
and the third-year
boys' all-star triathlon.
Which do you want to cheerlead
for? Aw, who am I kidding?
The girls, right?
You are you, after all.
Could you please not grab
me by the collar again?
Uh.
[FUKIYOSE] Okay.
[FUKIYOSE] Come on, already!
[FUKIYOSE] Out of
curiosity, do you find
the sports festival boring?
[KAMIJO] Huh?
[FUKIYOSE] You just seem
erratic and distracted today.
Like your mind is on
something else entirely.
And if you find it
boring, then it's at least
partially my fault, as a member
of the steering committee.
We were the ones
who organized it.
Maybe I failed you and
all the rest of the students.
I swear I don't find the
Daihasei Festival boring.
It's just that I spent
a lot of time helping
to plan everything for this.
I worked really hard.
I just want to make
sure everybody who comes
enjoys it as much
as possible, you know?
Maybe that's a
little selfish of me.
Ugh. I don't
know why I try,
you're not even listening.
I am, though; really!
[GIRL STUDENT] Oh, sorry!
[BOTH] Uh.
Get away from me
right now, you pig!
Ah!
Oh!
Waaahaha!
I'm really sorry!
I'm not accustomed to
being around so many people.
Nah...
[WOMAN] Are you
alright? Did I hurt you?
Your forehead's
turning a little red.
No, I, uh...
I'm sorry again for
running into you.
Shake? Or maybe you
would prefer a kiss?
Yeah, sure!
I kiss sounds--
[KAMIJO] Never mind.
Well then.
[gasps]
Excuse me.
I really do need to be
getting back to
work. Good-bye now!
Hello, are you there?
This is Oriana
Thomson checking in.
[ORIANA] Can you hear me?
[LIDVIA] Do not
use your real name.
Especially not when
you're within earshot
of who knows how many people.
That's not our main concern.
I've run into some trouble.
You know that oh-so-helpful
spell you used on me?
Well, it appears that
it's no longer working.
[LIDVIA] Why? What happened?
I'm not sure,
but you know...
I'm feeling sort of naked now.
[LIDVIA] I'm not interested
in your lewd observations.
What will you do?
Give me a sec.
Before I do anything else,
I'll need to find
a way to give this boy
who's following me the slip.
♪ [Ending Song] ♪
[KAMIJO] A game of cat and
mouse, but which one is which?
Catching Oriana is so
important that Stiyl is
willing to risk his life.
But will we succeed?
Next time, "Route Disturb."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.