♪
[KAMIJO] The Croce di Pietro
is a nasty piece of work.
It can be used without regard
to location or time of year.
Unless we do something,
Academy City will fall
under Roman Orthodox
control at sundown.
[KAMIJO] But there's no way
I'm gonna let that happen!
♪ [Opening Song] ♪
[KAMIJO yells]
Yaaa!
[ORIANA] Oh, thanks! That's
exactly where I want you!
[KAMIJO coughs]
[chuckles]
Well, look at that! It's
starting to get dark already.
[ORIANA] Shouldn't
you be getting home soon
like a good little boy?
Or are you staying?
I'm sure you and I can find
a stimulating way to
spend our time together.
[KAMIJO] One mistake.
[KAMIJO] That's all I need. For
her to screw up. Just one time!
♪
[STIYL] I call upon fire
to serve me as my sword.
Manifest thyself!
Feed upon me that
thou shall gain power!
Witch Hunter King. Innocentius!
[roar]
Let's go. We've got
work to do. I am Fortis 931.
We'll prove the greatness
of my magic, you and I.
[STIYL] Now, fight as
you were created to!
[roar]
We can die together.
[KAMIJO] Watch out, you idiot!
Oh, no!
Ashes to ashes and dust to dust.
[STIYL] Vampire Killer
Crimson Cross Attack!
Haaaa!
Uh!
Hey klutz, why
don't you go home.
I'll take it from here.
Why don't you shut up.
[grunts]
[STIYL] Innocentius, strike!
Stay out of my
way, ya' jerk!
You stay out of my way!
[ORIANA] What is
with these two idiots?
I can't predict their next move.
[BOTH grunt]
[ORIANA groans]
[ORIANA] Black and white.
That's how this ridiculous
world should be ordered.
[ORIANA] No more gray areas.
No more impossible questions.
No more tragedies resulting
from conflicting ideas of
right and wrong. A simple,
happy, peaceful world.
That is what I'm fighting for
and I want it
badly enough to win.
So here I go.
My name is Basis 104,
and I will triumph!
Get down, you moron.
[roar]
[KAMIJO] Stiyl!
[ORIANA]
Aww, where are you going?
Not so fast. I don't think
we're done playing yet.
[KAMIJO] So this
is just a game to you?
How many more people do you
plan to hurt before it's over?
[chuckles]
Whatever you may think of me,
I don't get a kick
out of hurting people.
But I have a job to do,
and I won't let you stop me.
[ORIANA] Now. Come here.
Once I defeat you, my
business will be complete,
and I can be a spectator.
Everything else is up to
the Roman Orthodox Church.
I get to witness them
using the Croce di Pietro
to create the
world that I desire.
[KAMIJO] So it's
up to the Church, huh?
Do you have any idea
how foolish you sound
when you say
something like that?
You're letting other
people determine your future!
[ORIANA] You're right.
I most certainly am.
And... you wanna
know something else?
I don't even care who it is.
As long as their goal
is to unite the world
under one harmonious vision,
I will continue to defend them.
I want the world to be at peace.
How can you possibly
see that as a bad thing?
[KAMIJO] World peace.
That's what you're after?
As far as causes go,
that seems like a noble one.
However, I don't agree
with your methods at all.
Not when the first
step in your plan
is subjugating Academy
City. That isn't noble.
The more you talk,
the more I realize
just how ignorant you are.
You don't know what
it's like to be at the mercy
of powers that are
beyond your control.
You don't understand
how desperate
that can make somebody.
[ORIANA] You don't have
any idea what it's like
to be truly helpless.
[KAMIJO] Even if I don't,
it still doesn't give you
the right to attack this
city because you feel like it.
Your premise is flawed.
You want to save some people
by causing harm to
others and that isn't right.
In fact, it's evil!
Everyone's a victim
of circumstance.
Everybody struggles
at some point.
We've all felt desperation.
We've all been afraid
before. Don't you get it?
It's about falling down
and getting back up.
No matter how difficult
and frightening things may
seem at the moment.
You have to get back up.
You can better your own life,
but don't ruin other
peoples' along the way.
[KAMIJO] So, which path will
you choose, Oriana Thomson?
Will you victimize
others because you don't
want to be a victim yourself?
Or will you help others?
Why not reach out a
hand to those in need
if you truly desire
to create a better world?
Ha...
Maybe this will
answer your question.
I call upon all the
power that lies within me.
Unleash the force of my soul
and strike down my enemy!
[yells]
[chuckles]
[groans]
[KAMIJO] Damn it. I can't.
Honestly! Would it be
too much to ask for you
to put just a little
effort into making
this tournament
a success for us?
[HIMEGAMI] We've got a bit
of a problem to deal with.
Come on.
Don't expect miracles.
This isn't my area
of expertise, either.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] You need to keep
going, Kami. Leave me here.
[KAMIJO] You guys. You fought
so hard to get us this far.
I promise I'll
try to come visit you
before the night parade begins.
So you'd better hang
in there for me, okay?
[KAMIJO] Now it's my turn. To
continue the fight you began.
I promise, all you've done
hasn't been for nothing.
I will do my part!
[gasps]
[grunts]
[aircraft noise]
[KAMIJO] Stiyl!
[STIYL] Never mind me. Worry
about the Croce di Pietro.
You need to get Oriana
to tell you where it is.
[STIYL] We have to keep it
from activating. Or all is lost.
[LIDVIA] There is no need
to go to so much trouble.
All this unpleasantness
will be over soon.
[STIYL] Lidvia Lorenzetti.
[LIDVIA] Before much longer,
the Croce di Pietro will begin
to do its holy work.
And then all of
Academy City will be
converted to Roman Orthodoxy.
[KAMIJO] And what about those
of us who get in the way?
Are you saying that we're
all going to be purged?
[LIDVIA] No my child.
I am saying that we will
care for your injuries and
watch over you while you heal.
Of course by that point,
you will have seen
the error of your
ways and converted.
You're insane!
[STIYL] Don't listen
to what she says.
It'll only distract you.
Lidvia must be
around here somewhere.
The relic will be with her.
[LIDVIA] In the interest
of full disclosure,
I feel I should tell you.
Despite your assumptions,
the Cross is not
currently in Academy City.
[heavy exhale]
[LIDVIA] The Roman Apostolic
State that was created
by the Croce di
Pietro was, at its peak,
fourty-seven thousand
square kilometers.
Even if the Cross is
activated outside the borders,
all of Academy City
will still be affected.
Damn, we've been tricked.
Oriana was a decoy.
[LIDVIA] It is a shame
that she was defeated,
but some sacrifices
are necessary
on the path to righteousness.
All will turn out as
it should in the end.
What truly matters right
now is that, at long last,
science will be forced
to bow to religion.
By denying science's power
and demonstrating our own,
we can restore the authority
of the Lord to this wanton land.
[STIYL] We need to
find her and stop this.
But, at this point,
we can't ask Tsuchimikado
to use his magic again.
[KAMIJO] Damn! What the
hell are we supposed to do?
[LIDVIA] It is not
as if our mission is
the destruction of Academy City.
Once you've renounced science
and its attendant heresy,
we'll gladly embrace you as our
beloved friends and comrades.
[STIYL]
Get Tsuchimikado on the phone.
We'll use his divination circle
to determine Lidvia's location.
Then use my communication
magic to contact
our forces outside the city.
[LIDVIA] You do
not have time for that.
The Cross's conversion of
the world will begin very soon.
In one hundred
and seven seconds.
Checkmate, gentlemen.
Isn't there something
else we can do?
Maybe another
trick up our sleeve?
Or a final trump
card we can play?
The cross uses constellations
from the night sky.
It's here on the ground when it
collects the starlight, though.
[beeping]
[ringing]
Tsuchimikado. There's something
that I need to ask you.
Where outside the city
could the Croce di Pietro
be placed and
still affect everything?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Why, what's up?
Just answer, okay? Better
yet, with those conditions,
what would the
farthest point be?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] I'd say Academy
City's northern perimeter,
by about seventeen
hundred meters.
Why do you need to know?
[beeping]
[KAMIJO] Let's see.
In twenty seconds.
[LIDVIA] It is over my son.
[KAMIJO] Yes. It's over, all
right. I have lost this fight.
And the Roman Orthodox
Church has triumphed.
[KAMIJO] So how
does it feel, Lidvia?
You know what bugs me most
about this whole situation?
That I couldn't keep a
promise to my classmate.
[LIDVIA]
Huh? What is happening?
[gasps]
[LIDVIA] How?
You scheduled the Cross to be
activated at exactly 6:30pm.
Shoulda done your research.
Because that's also the time
when the night parade begins.
With this much
light in the sky,
I'm guessing the stars will
be pretty well blotted out.
[KAMIJO] It doesn't matter
that we didn't find you.
[KAMIJO] You've been
defeated by the people who
came together to celebrate
the Daihasei Festival.
It was no contest, really.
They outshine you by far.
You can't hold a
candle to their faith.
So, what d'you say?
Let's make a deal.
First, you promise to
destroy the Croce di Pietro.
[KAMIJO] Then you assure
me that you'll never again
mess with Academy City.
And in return,
I'll let you go in peace.
[LIDVIA] You cannot be serious.
Have you forgotten that
I am a devout believer of
the Roman Orthodox Church?
[KAMIJO] I see.
[KAMIJO]
All right. In that case...
This field day, I guess we'll
just have to keep playing tag.
Until I catch you.
So, to sum up...
you got beat black and blue
by a female magician. While you
were fighting her for access
to a relic that would determine
the fate of the entire planet.
You got yourself pummeled
while saving the world
and did it all
without a word to me.
Can you blame
me for worrying?
Whenever magic is involved,
you just walk right into
the situation without
stopping to think first.
[INDEX] The way you say
that makes me sound like
some kind of foolish
child. I don't like it!
Pffft.
You should be able to
admit that you're impetuous.
The fact you can't
makes you seem really--
Oh, dear, look at this.
[KUROKO] You two seem
to get physical a lot,
if you know what I mean.
[INDEX] We were in the middle
of a serious discussion,
so get out of here, short-hair!
[MIKOTO] Kuroko.
There's no rule against
an ordinary citizen helping
a member of judgment fulfill
her security duties, is there?
[KUROKO] Not here, Sissy.
We're inside a hospital.
We don't want
to endanger anybody.
Damn. Okay, fine. I'll stop.
Did you see the
final results, though?
It's no surprise that our
school easily surpassed yours
to come out on
top in the festival.
[MIKOTO] I hope you
haven't forgotten about
the terms of our bet.
No, I haven't forgotten.
But I can't really do much
in my current condition.
The doctor says I'm
very fragile, you know.
Oh? Well...
[MIKOTO] We'll see about that.
[cuckles]
Poor Oriana, I certainly
do not envy her fate.
However, we all have our parts
to play in the Lord's plan.
Hers may be over, but
mine is just beginning.
[LAURA] Excuse me.
Attention, please.
This is Laura Stuart, archbishop
of the English Puritan Church.
Now, I do hope you have
enjoyed the flight so far
because I am afraid
you are about to hit
some turbulence, Lidvia.
[LIDVIA] What did you do?
This is a private jet.
[LAURA] Hm-hmmm. You made
a stop to refuel, remember?
I had something pasted to
the wall of your fuselage.
[LAURA] You're as
unbalanced as ever, I see.
The more cornered you feel,
the louder that cackle
of yours gets. It's
actually rather creepy.
I wonder if there's anything
to be done about that.
[LIDVIA] The more
difficult the situation is,
the greater the joy I feel when
I break free of it and triumph.
That laughter is my way
of giving thanks to the Lord.
[laughing]
[LAURA laughs]
Why do you laugh?
[LAURA] What you just said.
That the greater the
obstacle before you,
the more intense the thrill
is when you overcome it.
[LAURA] I couldn't help
but think how appropriate
that description is for you.
A swine trying
to ascend to Heaven.
[struggling]
Ah!
[LAURA] Lidvia. If you
agree to kiss my feet
and renounce your
Roman Catholic faith,
I will save you from
falling to your death.
My life is nothing
compared to my soul.
[LAURA] I see. Then you
and the Cross will be
smashed into pieces together.
[LIDVIA] The Croce di Pietro!
It must not be destroyed!
[LIDVIA] Even at this speed,
I should be able to save it.
I have to. There is no
acceptable alternative.
It will be a close call,
indeed. All the more thrilling!
[yelling]
[LAURA] What now, Lidvia?
Which option do you choose?
Save the world's
greatest religious relic.
Or save a poor,
lost little lamb?
♪
[LAURA] The more difficult
the situation is, the greater
the joy you will feel when you
break free of it and triumph.
Those were your exact
words, were they not?
Perhaps you will find your
triumph in the afterlife.
I will, you'll see.
[MAN yelling]
I will triumph over you!
I will!
[yelling]
[laughing]
[screaming]
[LIDVIA laughing]
[ALEISTER] Our situation
seems to be growing
even more tenuous than before.
The development of
the Imagine Breaker,
who is to be our key,
is as of yet unstable.
I am unsure whether or not
we should proceed as planned.
There is another possibility
I may be forced to consider.
I myself may have to
go forth into the fray.
[birds chirping]
♪
[HIMEGAMI] Um, hi.
What are you doing here?
[INDEX] I was sleeping
peacefully on the bench in
the waiting room. But,
come morning, the nurses said
I couldn't stay there,
so I came to rest with you.
I didn't think you would mind.
[INDEX] How are you
feeling? All better now?
Soon. The head doctor says
I'm recovering quickly.
I should be able to go home
either today or tomorrow.
[INDEX] You know,
I'm not sure what it is,
but you seem a little
lonely. What's wrong?
How's Kamijo? Did he
go off and do something
crazy and reckless like usual?
[INDEX] Yep, he sure
did. You know him.
I haven't heard all the details
of what happened out there yet.
Apparently it involves magicians
from the Roman Orthodox Church.
They were using
the Daihasei Festival
to launch some sort of attack.
[INDEX] So naturally,
Toma ditched me to chase after
the magicians without
even stopping to think
how worried or sad or lonely
that would make me feel!
Then he acts like he
didn't do anything wrong!
[growling]
[HIMEGAMI] Of course. I don't
know what I was thinking.
He's the kind of guy
who helps out whenever
there's a problem
that needs solving.
It has nothing to do with me.
[HIMEGAMI] I must
have seemed so stupid.
Just one more person
asking for his help.
Well, I seem to have a real
knack for inconveniencing
the people around me, don't I?
No, that isn't true!
Huh?
You mean Toma?
Don't worry about him.
He has a good time
when he's with you.
[KAMIJO] I don't want
to be rude, Fukiyose,
but I don't think you're
supposed to go into
people's hospital
rooms and slap them.
[FUKIYOSE] You can't blame
me! How do you expect me
to react to the sight
of some guy stark naked?
[KAMIJO] You're the one
who walked in when I was
in the middle of changing!
[FUKIYOSE] Excuse me?
[HIMEGAMI] Hey, do you
know why he goes around
getting into fights and
defending people all the time?
[INDEX] Nope. I did
ask him about it one time,
but all he told me is
that he does it for himself.
Maybe that's just the
kind of thing that makes
Toma happy, you know?
[laughs]
♪
♪ [Ending Song] ♪
[KAMIJO] For better or worse,
Index and I are off to Italy.
I hope we have time to
relax and do some sightseeing.
Wait! What's Orsola doing here?
And the Amakusa?
Next time, "City of Water."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.