[KOMABA] If we're so weak,
then maybe you should
take it easier on us...
little esper girl.
Ritoku Komaba.
[MUSUJIME] It looks
like I accidentally
ran into the target first.
We split all our money up to
avoid this sort of thing...
Yet here you are, tryin'
to make off with our stash...
Thanks to you, that's a whole
lot of hard work up in smoke.
It isn't personal, you
know, I'm like a weapon--
I just shoot
where I'm aimed...
And your secret
war chest just happens
to be what I'm
aimed at right now.
Your ability
is Move Point ...?
That's an annoying little power.
I think you'll find
that "annoying" doesn't
do it justice.
[KOMABA] Yeah... You might
be right about that...
Maybe it's more "despicable"
than "annoying."
[MUSUJIME] Either way,
you're going to end up with
a corkscrew between the eyes.
[grunts]
[KOMABA] You're too slow.
I came to this fight with
some tricks of my own.
[MUSUJIME] Ah!
It's not smart to play
by the rules when fighting
a monster like you...
I brought some extra
equipment to even
the playing field a bit.
Ugh!
[KOMABA] Nope. Missed me.
[beeping]
[MUSUJIME] You've got
some serious moves.
So, what's your secret?
Some of that tape
they use on
mechanical powersuits?
[chuckles]
It's actually special military
sonic elastic taping, but close.
Acquiring it wasn't
easy, let me tell ya.
I hear that stuff is
defective, and you're using it
on your own body...?
That could do some
long-term damage.
That should tell you
how far I'm prepared to go.
Do you think we
could stop chatting
and get this over with already?
I'm a very busy man...
My boys and I still have
a lot to do when I'm done here.
Don't make me laugh.
[KOMABA] Really, a flimsy
piece of metal...?
You think that's going
to be enough to stop me?!
[KOMABA] Didn't
even break a sweat.
[ACCELERATOR]
This place is a mess...
Looks like Musujime's
met her quota
for this mission... My turn.
So many better ways
I could spend my time.
[KOMABA] Then why don't we
get this over with quickly?
[ACCELERATOR] What?
You're Accelerator,
aren't ya?
And you're Ritoku Komaba...
Just out of curiosity, why
the hell are you doing this?
You're asking me why
Skill Out goes after espers
like you and your buddy...?
We have our motives, but I
doubt you'd understand them.
Heh! So your big
plan is to throw the city
into chaos by attacking
indiscriminately?
No, not indiscriminately...
We have reasons to
picking the people we do.
[ACCELERATOR] You
seem pretty confident,
given the situation...
You do know what I
came for, don't you?
Girl's already dead.
[KOMABA] I've heard stories,
but you're different than
what I expected...
Outcasts like you are
usually more reckless
in their attacks.
[ACCELERATOR] They are, huh?
You know, it's funny...
scumbags like you are
usually more respectful...
But that's before I
turn them into mincemeat.
That device
you've got there...
it's a transmitter
for some kind of
electrical information, right?
[chuckles]
What the hell...?
What's happening?
It's called Chaff Seed...
It's used to disrupt
electromagnetic waves.
Uh--Ugh!
[groans]
Bastard!
[KOMABA] Mine's a lot bigger.
[ACCELERATOR grunts]
[yells]
[KOMABA]
It's over. Stop fighting.
I'll give you one
courtesy, though...
You can choose where in
this alley you'd like to die.
[grunts]
[ACCELERATOR] You're unhappy
with your miserable life,
so you've decided
to make up for it
by ruining the lives
of innocent people?
I'm not gonna let
that happen this time!
You dirty bastard!
[gunshot]
[KOMABA] How...? Your
Reflection... it came back...
I don't... get it.
[ACCELERATOR]
You're as dumb as you look.
You used Chaff Seed.
Don't you even know the
basics of how it works?
You scatter metal
foil through the air,
creating EM interference...
Which makes things simple...
All I had to do was shift
the foil out of the way...
perhaps by...
getting the air moving...
[grunts]
[ACCELERATOR]
Now... where were we?
Yeah, that's right.
We were going to see
how things turn out when a
Level 0 challenges a Level 5.
I'm just on pins and
needles over here, aren't you?
Didn't get there fast enough!
[KOMABA groans]
[ACCELERATOR] What's
that you said before?
"It's over. Stop fighting."
[ACCELERATOR] When are you
losers gonna realize that people
don't hate you just
'cause of your Level?
[ACCELERATOR] Wake up already...
The reason Zeroes are treated
like crap is because
you clowns in Skill Out
go around making
trouble for everybody.
You think you're
protecting your rights...?
Guaranteeing your safety...?
You're all idiots...
You're basically
doing the opposite.
These stunts of yours
as good as put nooses
around your esper-hating necks.
You think our whole
purpose is to go around
[KOMABA] causing trouble...?
Think for a second.
Espers are espers
because of their abilities,
not 'cause they're
such good people...
You end up with
some ugly specimens
of humanity wielding
some serious power.
So, what's to stop espers
like that from attacking
powerless Level Zeros just
'cause they feel like it?
I'll tell you.
The answer is an armed group
like Skill Out...
That's the reason we exist.
Hmph.
[KOMABA] There's always
a price for being a leader.
I knew I'd have
to pay it eventually.
What do you want,
sympathy? Tch.
[KOMABA] From you? No.
It is sort of
interesting, though...
I feel like you and
I have more in common
than I would've thought.
So here's a gift...
A pathetic sight to
burn into your mind...
something to remember me by.
[gunshot]
[UNABARA] Excellent work.
Your part is done.
We'll see to
disposing of the body
and destroying any evidence...
I'll send the garbage
truck your way...
It'll be your ride back.
Nah. I can find
my own way back.
[UNABARA] It makes
no difference to me.
Just avoid contact
with anybody you know...
It's important
that Group remains a--
You might as
well come out now...
I know he didn't kill you.
Nice fight. I started
watching about halfway through.
So, when did I
give myself away?
Please... Did you think
no one would notice...?
That stunt of yours
was pretty obvious.
[MUSUJIME giggles]
Hey, now... Is that any
way to talk to the person
who saved your life
just a few minutes ago?
You really think I
needed your help...?
Keep telling yourself that...
You leaving...?
Our ride'll be here soon.
Yeah? Well don't
worry about it...
It's just some overtime.
[beeping]
[ACCELERATOR] Something
I need to take care of.
[ACCELERATOR] Ugh...
That ended up taking a
lot longer than I expected.
Tch.
[ACCELERATOR] I need coffee.
The convenience store
should be open.
[moan]
Ugh... I'm not
feeling so good...
[ACCELERATOR] Mm?
That woman's face...
It's like I've seen
it somewhere before...
[chuckles]
[ACCELERATOR] Who is this lady?
Huh?
Uh.
W'ello there...!
I'MisuzuMisaka.
Nice a meet you--Uuuhhh...
[thud]
Hey... get off me!
I like long walks on
the beach at sunset...
and getting
caught in the rain...
and have you seen my boobs,
'cause they're really big...
Oh, I forgot. I'm married...
I really shouldn't say
stuff like that, huh?
[MISUZU] That's right.
Hands off, buddy.
My husband wouldn't
like this at all.
Hey... I'm looking
for Dangai University's
Database Center.
Do you know where it is...?
If you could tell me
that would be a big help.
[MISUZU] Hey...!
Don't walk away from me.
That isn't nice!
[MISUZU] You don't get it?!
That's where I
have to go now...!
It's really important
'cause that's where they do
all the studying
and stuff, you know?
[laughs]
Here's an idea.
How about you get off me
and pour yourself into a taxi?
Don't tell anybody,
but I've got a thing
for younger men. I could
just kiss you all over,
you young stud, you! Ahhh...
[ACCELERATOR] Come on, lady. For
both of our sakes, stop talking!
[KAMIJO] Fine,
if I have to choose...
I'd say the croquettes were
my favorite part of the meal.
I mean, little breaded
patties that you fry in oil...
What's not to love about that?
They are tasty.
It's a lot of work to
fry them yourself, though. Ah!
[INDEX] I know! Next time we
go to a restaurant like that,
I'll have you fry
them for me instead!
Then it won't
be any work at all,
and they'll taste much better!
[MISUZU] Hey! Kid!
Don't I know you?
[KAMIJO] Are you okay?
[MISUZU] I'm just fine.
It's getting late, though.
Time for bed, isn't it?
Mhm.
Oh... wait a sec...
I haven't washed my face or
put on any moisturizing cream.
That's unacceptable...
[MISUZU] You skip just
one day, and that's when
the wrinkles start to show...
Uh-oh... I'm gonna puke.
[KAMIJO] Uh... Can I... Huh?
[MISUZU] Ahhh...!
Oh yeah...! Hands off,
ladies! He's mine...!
Wait, what are you
doing wandering around
at this late hour...?
And where's my daughter?
Where's Mikoto? Ahhh!
[KAMIJO] Ack! Please!
Do something! Help me, Index!
I know you...! What was
your name again, little girl?
[SPHINX meows]
Humph...! As if I would
give personal information
to someone behaving
like you are now!
Oh yeah, you little
brat, I'll show you.
Ah! Okay, it's Index...!
My name is Index!
Thank you... Now,
if you could just point me
towards the Dangai
University's Database Center?
[KAMIJO] Huh?
You see, I'm writing a
report for this class I'm in,
and the materials I
need for it can only be
found in Academy City...
So I had no choice but to drag
myself back to this place.
[KAMIJO] Ah... gotcha.
[gasp] I know...!
I'll get your contact info
and we can stay in touch!
Uh, I don't know...
We're gonna be
such good friends.
I can already tell!
I'll call you as soon
as I get home, okay?
[ACCELERATOR] Her name was
Misaka... A coincidence...? No.
She's got something to
do with the kid. But what?
[beep]
[phone rings]
[SHADOWY MAN]
Hello, Accelerator...
Did you need something?
[ACCELERATOR] Tch...
They've tapped my phone, huh?
[ACCELERATOR]
You're a sneaky bastard...
Is this Group's
mysterious leader?
[SHADOWY MAN] You picked
up your phone because
you had a question.
[ACCELERATOR]
It's nothing important...
I'll figure it
out on my own, thanks.
[SHADOWY MAN] If that's what
you want, suit yourself...
I don't really care...
There is a certain
matter I would like
to discuss with you, though.
Huh?
[SHADOWY MAN] This
should work out well...
The timing is almost perfect.
Oh yeah?
[rumble]
[SHADOWY MAN] That woman
you just ran into...
She recently submitted
a request to use
the Dangai University
Database Center.
So that's where the
attack is taking place.
An attack ordered by you?
[SHADOWY MAN] Yes.
And who exactly
is this Misaka woman?
[SHADOWY MAN] Her full
name is Misuzu Misaka...
She is the mother
of one Mikoto Misaka.
Are you familiar with
the "retrieval campaign"?
Sure. It's the thing where
parents are getting their kids
away from Academy
City before war breaks out.
[SHADOWY MAN] That's correct...
and if too many students
leave Academy City, it will
create any number of problems...
Misuzu currently
occupies a leadership role
among the retrieval
campaign parents...
So... the decision has
been made to remove her.
Would you be willing
to assist with said removal?
[ACCELERATOR]
Why do you want my help?
[SHADOWY MAN] The assignment
has actually been given to
members of Skill Out... but
they lack a certain... finesse.
Things would go more smoothly
if you were to assist...
I don't think so.
[ACCELERATOR] It's my life.
I still call my own shots...
This mission
doesn't interest me,
so thanks,
but I'm going to pass.
[SHADOWY MAN] Very well, then...
In that case,
please hurry back...
Your ability will be restored
to you upon your return.
[beep]
What...? You bastard...!
What did you do
to my electrode?
[SHADOWY MAN] I'm afraid I'm
going to have to let you go...
Goodbye for now...
I'm sure I'll see you soon.
Tch.
[ACCELERATOR] Misuzu Misaka...
you're in luck...
I'm gonna go rescue you...
That oughta piss off
the mystery boss man.
[KAMIJO panting]
[gasp]
[growls]
[ACCELERATOR]
That bastard again?!
Tch... No time now.
Deal with it later.
[ACCELERATOR]
Well... here we go...
I'm gonna make
this the bloodiest
rescue operation ever...
They're gonna need
to hose the place down
[ACCELERATOR] by the
time this is over.
[SKILL OUT A] What
is this, amateur hour?
Which of you idiots
forgot the security key?
[SKILL OUT B] Forget
about it. We don't have time.
Let's just find the woman.
[MISUZU] Uh...
What's going on here?
I know I dialed Antiskill,
so why can't I get through?
[gasps]
[distant footsteps]
[beeping]
From the sound of it,
they're probably with Skill Out.
[MISUZU] What's Skill Out?
[KAMIJO] They're basically a
gang made up of Level Zeroes.
They tend to be armed.
[MISUZU] But why
would they be after me?
As to that, I have no idea.
Miss Misaka... Have you tried
giving your daughter a call?
Huh?
[KAMIJO] The fighting skills of
a Level 5 could come in handy
right now... If she's
still in the cit--
No way! Keep
Mikoto out of this...
[MISUZU] I'm her mother. I
won't drag her into my problems.
Please... I can't...
I'd never be able to
look her in the eye again.
[KAMIJO] I understand.
[KAMIJO] Then stay put.
I'll be right there.
[MISUZU] Huh? I can't
ask you to risk--
[beep]
Haven't any of you
morons found her?
[SKILL OUT] Huh?
[MAN] I asked you guys
a question, damn it...!
Answer me!
Yeah... Komaba got off easy...
Nobody expects anything
from a dead man...
but what the hell are the
rest of us supposed to do?
[MISUZU gaps]
[chuckles]
Hamazura here...
I've located the target...
We can take care of her...
Do you copy me?
[SKILL OUT C] Hey! Back off!
[gunshots]
Antiskill's there?
[ACCELERATOR] Sorry...!
Your friend had to go...
If it'll make you feel better,
I can stay on the line
and keep chatting
with you instead...
I've got a few things to
wrap up here before I come
and kill the rest
of you scumbags.
[gunshots]
[KAMIJO] Five of them... And,
sure enough, they all have guns.
[KAMIJO]
This is bulletproof... Right?
[MISUZU] Huh?
[SKILL OUT gasps]
[KAMIJO] Why not
just point and shout?
[KAMIJO] Damn... I need to make
a move before they regroup...
If I could reach the
bag with the gun in it...
Shoot him!
You're kidding me, right?
[KAMIJO] Here we go!
Ah!
[MISUZU and
SKILL OUT D grunting]
Damn you!
Uhhh...
[SKILL OUT A groans]
[SKILL OUT B] Another one?!
[KAMIJO] I'll untie you
and then we're out of here.
Ready to run?
[KAMIJO] Hurry up!
Heh.
Quite the diligent one,
aren't you...?
Carrying out your duty
in spite of adversity,
like a good little soldier.
[SKILL OUT D]
This way! Come on!
Ugh!
[KAMIJO] Good, we're out...
Let's keep going...
We'll go somewhere more crowded.
[HAMAZURA] What's going on here?
Who are you? Why are
you doing this...?
Are we being set up or
something, is that it?
Was the job just
a sham all along?
What did you say?
[HAMAZURA] That bastard Komaba
went and got himself killed...
We knew the ones
who did it were bound
to come after the
rest of us soon...
So we agreed we would
do whatever they asked us.
Damn...! They were
planning to screw us over
from the beginning!
I'm not with those guys...
I'm here because
this woman called me.
[chuckles]
That's almost funny.
[HAMAZURA] I totally screwed the
pooch on this one, didn't I...?
There's no one to
blame for it but me...!
It wasn't some big conspiracy...
We weren't double-crossed
by some strategic genius.
[chuckles]
My life is worthless now...!
If somebody's gonna kill
me... might as well be you.
Just stay back!
[grunts]
[KAMIJO groans]
Hey, wait... If you're not
with them, that means...
I might still have a chance
to get out of this alive...
I just need to bring
them the target's body...
That'll show 'em that I'm
not completely worthless.
[chuckles]
[KAMIJO] By all means,
you go right ahead and try!
[HAMAZURA groans]
[groans]
What's wrong with you?
How can you treat a person's
life as if it's nothing?!
What choice did I have...?!
How are Level Zeroes
like us supposed to
survive if we can't
prove ourselves?!
[KAMIJO] I don't
need to prove myself.
What?
[KAMIJO] Don't lump all Level
Zeroes in with criminal bastards
like you and your group.
You're one, too...
This whole time,
you didn't use an ability.
[KAMIJO] There are plenty of
Level Zeroes in this city...
and most of them
aren't in stupid gangs...
They go to school
every day and do their
homework and make friends
just like everyone else does...
They live perfectly
normal lives.
You're the ones making
Level Zeroes look like
a bunch of idiots!
You're really a Level Zero...
You're just like me.
[KAMIJO]
I am nothing like you...
No, I don't have
an ability, either...
but I also have no intention
of becoming cruel...
I won't hurt people to
make myself feel better!
You call us cruel...?
Take a closer
look at this city...
The people with power
keep it for themselves,
with nothing for
the rest of us...
They're a hundred
times more cruel than
Skill Out could ever hope to be!
Will you accept
no responsibility?
You ever try asking for help?
Or just lashing out?
Huh?
[KAMIJO] If you had
dedicated half as much time to
helping others as you
have to fighting espers...
There's a good chance
that the people of
this city would
have accepted you.
And your lives would
be a lot different now.
Screw you! Did you
ever hear about Komaba...?
He was the leader of Skill Out,
and he was a good person...
He did the things you said...
and he's dead now...!
He was killed
protecting the weak!
Sounds like he
was a good guy...
So why don't you try
following his example...?
He fought against injustice
until the very end, didn't he?
[KAMIJO] Did he
fight to protect...
or to indiscriminately harm?
You don't know anything...!
You're just a
Level Zero, like me...
You're nothing! You don't
have any power in this city!
Don't look down on us like
you're something special!
[KAMIJO] The reason people
look down on you has nothing
to do with power...
or your lack of it.
That's just an illusion,
a lie you tell yourself...
At some point you'll
need to let it go...
How about right now?
[sirens]
[MISUZU] Want to know
why I'm really here?
I came to take Mikoto home,
far away from the city.
But I don't think I
need to worry anymore...
Not as long as there
are still people around
like you and that other boy...
If you're watching out for her,
I know she'll be fine.
I'm sorry... "Other boy"?
[footsteps]
[ACCELERATOR] Were you told
to track me down and punish me
for disobeying orders?
So melodramatic!
The Misaka situation
has been resolved...
She seems to have
lost the desire to
remove her daughter
from Academy City.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Her death
is no longer necessary.
Is that the kind
of conclusion our boss
is likely to be okay with?
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
I doubt he'll object...
Mainly because Unabara here
has been working so hard.
Oh... I'm just pleased
that young Kamijo
has kept his promise...
He has continued
to look after the girl
[UNABARA] that I care very
much about and protect the
fragile world
in which she lives.
In fact, his valiant
actions inspired me
to try a little bit
harder, myself...
My only hope is that,
in the end,
everything turns out
for the best, you know?
Don't worry.
We don't really know
what he's talking
about, either.
He just keeps saying
vague stuff like that...
Personally I'm betting
that whatever he was
up to must have
been pretty ugly.
Anyway, that's that...
Good work on
your assignment...
That goes for
the overtime, too.
Damn you people.
Remember... you can't
play by the rules here...
if you do, you'll
never win this game...
We're all in the
same boat, you know...
We're not here by choice.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] For whatever
reason, the people upstairs
seem to consider you
a precious commodity...
We could all work together...
What do you say?
[ACCELERATOR] Okay, sure. Why
not? One thing, though...
If you guys slow me down,
I'll leave you behind
without so much
as a second thought.
Ha... there's plenty of
fight left in this one...
Let's go guys...
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Time to strike
back at the powers that be.
[grunts]
[ACCELERATOR]
This should be fun...
It's always nice to
have a goal in life...
and this one I can get behind.
[MIKOTO] Come on!
I mean, really!
How long has it been
since I sent that text...?
I at least deserve
some kind of response.
No matter how much
we try, the mountain of
paperwork isn't
getting any smaller.
There's nobody
else to do it...
All the rest of them
were knocked unconscious...
We've got another
few days of this, easy.
It's best if you
just accept that.
[screaming]
[KOMOE] Wow! You're going
to be a booth bunny
at a weapons show?
That sounds exciting!
Let's not make too
big a deal of it.
They're just doing powered
suit demonstrations.
So in other words,
what you're saying is...
you'll be their mascot.
Well... I don't know if
I'd put it that way...
[sighs]
This pudding is great...!
Especially considering
it was purchased
from a convenience store.
You should be careful
eating sweets late at night.
You'll get fat.
"He's not here. Where is he?"
asks Misaka Misaka
right after she wakes up.
Don't worry he'll be
back soon... I promise.
"Misaka can't wait
to see him... Soon,"
repeats Misaka Misaka,
hoping you're right.
Hm.
Just rest now.
[panting]
Toma!
[INDEX] There you go again...!
Wandering off by yourself
and ending up hurt!
You have no sense
at all, do you?
How can one person wind
up in the hospital so much?
Well... you know...
It's a funny story...
Remember that woman
we ran into...?
[growling]
Uh...
[SPHINX meows]
[KAMIJO] Damn my rotten luck!