♪
[giggles]
It's a penalty game,
and you know what that means!
You lost, so you have
to do whatever I say.
[KUROKO] Uh! I've had enough!
She's been like
this day and night
since the Daihasei
Festival! I have to know!
Who is she talking
to, and why is she
using that sweet,
enticing voice?
Uh...! Huh?
So many options.
What should I have
you do first, huh?
[KUROKO] She's snuggling.
I must know. Who is it?
Sissy! Who are
you imagining when
you rub your cheek
against that pillow?
A-hah...
♪ [Opening Song] ♪
♪
[LAST ORDER] "Look, look, look!
While we were in the hospital,
everybody started wearing
clothes with longer sleeves,"
Misaka observes
from the window of the--
Ahh!
People's sleeves are
longer 'cause the weather's
gotten cooler, idiot.
And next time you
want to look outside,
find a vantage point that
doesn't require climbing over
a guy who just got
out of the hospital, okay?
Don't be mean!
You aren't the only one
who is under the weather.
Misaka just got out
too, you know, and she--
Okay, let's all calm down now.
I'll let you two finish
this adorable little squabble
of yours when we get to
where you'll be staying.
So... where is this
new residence you've got
lined up for us?
For the near future,
at least, you're going to be
staying with a friend
of mine. It should work.
You are still dropping out of
your current school, aren't you?
All they care about is their
stupid Level 6 experiment.
And I'm through
with that crap for good.
Well, my friend
isn't like that at all.
She's not the
scientific researcher type.
As a matter of fact, she's
almost sure to take your side.
Hmph.
Great, so basically
we're going to be
crashing with another
know-it-all do-gooder.
[KAMIJO sighs]
I want to meet somebody.
[groans]
What did you do that for?
Oh, come on. When you
say that, you sound like
a sap. It make us
uncool by association.
Yeah, man, and add
in that pathetic sigh
like you just did and
you're guaranteed to attract
all the Grade A
wierdos in the area.
I'm telling you, Kami. Keep
it up and we'll be mobbed
by everything from
hyper-intelligent computer
nerds to socially
awkward fangirls.
And I don't think
that'll make anyone happy.
Now, take a look,
my inexperienced friend.
The "stiff shoulder holder"?
I know I look chill and relaxed,
but my shoulders are so tense.
Maybe this handy device will
give me the relief I need.
You think I
should try it, Kami?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Ha! That
thing is obviously a scam!
Next week when you call
to get your money back,
the number will
be disconnected--
It's not like this
is my first choice.
I'd much rather have a pretty
girl rub my shoulders for me.
And I know what you're going
to say, so shut up already!
If you're waiting for a pretty
girl to give you a massage,
you're gonna have stiff
shoulders for a long time.
Then maybe I'll get
a pretty girl to try
the "stiff shoulder
holder" for me.
Well, in that case,
I know someone
you could probably ask.
[BOTH] Hm?
She's a pretty girl who's
basically tense all the time.
[KAMIJO] And she's a
sucker for those ridiculous
mail order products.
So you agree? We should be
focusing on world peace, right?
Yeah.
[door opens]
[KAMIJO]
You feelin' tense, Fukiyose?
Uh...?
[KAMIJO]
We can solve your problem!
How would you
like a nice massage?
[FUKIYOSE grunts]
Hello, everybody. I hope
you're ready to learn,
because it's time to turn
our focus to chemistry.
[screams]
[KOMOE] My classroom! This
hallowed place of learning
has become a fight club
for juvenile delinquents!
[FUKIYOSE] It's all for
the sake of World peace!
[FROG DOCTOR] All right, ladies.
Today you will all be starting
your physical
rehabilitation programs.
Are there any objections to
wearing the Tokiwadai uniform?
If so, I'll see what I can do.
"The uniform is fine,"
Misaka 10032
helpfully answers
the question.
[FROG DOCTOR] And the four
of you are the same size?
"There is no
need to measure.
We're clones, as you know,
so we were made identical,"
replies Misaka 13577.
"There has not been
enough time to allow
for any difference in
sizes," adds Misaka 10039,
for greater clarity.
[MISAKA 19090] "Mi--"
"Misaka isn't sure."
"Is there something you
need to report, 19090?"
inquires Misaka.
[gasps]
"This skirt is showing definite
signs of being too large,"
Misaka 10032 reports in
a tone of serious concern.
"But all Misakas
are supposed to be
exactly the same size.
It's how we were created,"
says Misaka 13577,
registering her dismay.
"What about other areas,
such as the bust?"
asks Misaka 10039, proposing
a thorough physical exam.
Well, individual
differences will surface
due to diet and exercise.
"In other words, without
informing the other Misakas,
she has been engaging
in what is commonly known
as dieting," explains Misaka
10032, with mild disdain.
"Now that we're on the subject,
I do recall seeing 19090
with her nose
buried in one of those
women's magazines,"
Misaka 13577 reports,
eager to relate all
the relevant information.
"That's right. And
the magazine discussed
the importance of getting
a ring from a boy one likes
and wearing it on
the left ring finger.
Once a girl has that, she
wins," concludes Misaka 10039,
explaining the rules
of the strange contest.
[MISAKA 10032]
Get a ring, and you win.
I-It was nothing.
Honestly, I can't see
why it makes that much
of a difference, but if
it's that important to be
exactly the same, then maybe
you can find a compromise.
"Uh...
Misaka's crisis
response is kicking in.
It is telling her
to flee immediately!"
Misaka whimpers pitifully!
[MIKOTO] You can't hide
anymore! I've got you now!
Hm?
What to say? Ah, I know.
Rotten luck!
That's some greeting!
I know dogs who have
better manners than you.
Well, what's up, Zapper.
Need something, or you
just buzzing around?
Y'know, if I were you,
I'd really reconsider taking
that kind of tone with me.
Why?
The penalty game, chump!
Huh? Oh.
Seriously, I'm still
on the hook for that?
You don't think I'm
gonna let you blow it off
like it never happened.
Like it or not, a bet is a bet,
and you have to do
anything I tell you to do.
I'll be fair, though.
I know someone like you
only has limited capabilities,
so I won't ask very much.
[MIKOTO]
I really hope you'll still
give it your best try, though.
You'll do that
for me, won't you?
Hm?
[KAMIJO] All right, all right.
I shall do it!
You may ask anything
of me that you so desire.
Huh?
[KAMIJO] Milady,
if it pleases you,
let me first
ensure your comfort.
As incompetent as I am,
I beg you to forgive
my shortcomings.
Allow me to fan you!
[MIKOTO] Okay you idiot,
I get the point.
Enough with the fanning already!
[KUROKO] What is this?
[MIKOTO] Hey, Kuroko.
[KUROKO] Down on his knees in
a posture of abject servitude.
I must remember
not to underestimate
this troglodyte. Enough!
You are stealing the job
that rightfully belongs to me!
Come on!
Stop it, both of you!
Are you crazy or something?
I didn't plan on
showing the world
what's under my skirt today!
[YOSHIKAWA] Well, here we are.
This is the woman who'll
be looking after you.
Uh.
What the hell is this?
Is that any way to
greet an old friend?
Or have you
forgotten me already?
I'm not talking about you.
I'm referring to this thing.
[ACCELERATOR] This absurdly
miniscule creature over here.
Hey! That isn't a very nice
thing to say to somebody,
you know. I may be short,
but I'm a teacher,
thank you very much!
So, they've found a way
to halt cell aging entirely.
I didn't know the
research was going so well.
Uh. No, you see. It's not
like that at all, I--
[LAST ORDER]
"Oh, you poor thing!"
"Everything they must
have put you through!
All of those experiments,
with no time for yourself!"
Misaka Misaka cries, dabbing at
her eyes with a handkerchief.
Please, stop for a moment and
listen to what I'm telling you!
[laughing]
Wow, they've really got
your number, don't they?
[KOMOE] Is this why you brought
me here? To be humiliated?
Well, I guess there's
no sense standing around.
I'll show you to my
apartment in a sec.
First things first, though.
I'll go ahead and
bring the car around.
You sure about this?
[ACCELERATOR] About letting me
crash at your apartment, I mean.
[YOMIKAWA] It's no problem.
I've got an extra room,
so there's plenty of space.
That's not what I'm saying.
Sheltering me could
be bad for your health.
It's more or less like
volunteering to take on
the whole Academy
City underworld.
You really want
that kind of heat?
[YOMIKAWA] I'm the best
landlord you could have.
My line of work puts
me in a unique position.
I don't think there are
too many criminals out there
who would be foolish enough
to attack the residence
of an Antiskill officer.
When they show up to kill you,
don't say I didn't warn you.
Don't worry, I'll be fine.
Don't act like
this is no big deal.
By doing this, you're
putting a big, fat target
in the middle of your back.
Again, thank you
for your concern,
but I'm a big girl.
I'll be okay.
[grunts]
I'm prepared
for any eventuality.
Anyway... I don't think
this job is going to be
half as difficult as I expected.
Oh, yeah? How do you figure?
[YOMIKAWA] Think about
it from my point of view.
My tenant hasn't moved
in and he's already
started worrying
about my safety.
Sounds pretty nice.
I can think of worse things
than someone
trying to protect me.
[giggles]
[heavy exhale]
Yeah, I can already
tell we're gonna have
a great time living together.
♪
[MIKOTO] He's late!
What is he up to?
Seventh Mist at one o'clock!
And you better not be late!
You know what'll happen!
[MIKOTO] Come on! Ugh!
I bet he just wants to
make me look like an idiot.
No, we're having noodles.
Don't wanna! This is all
we've had to eat lately!
Can't we have
something else, just once?
Seriously, Toma, are you trying
to drive me to starvation
by feeding me only one
type of food every day?
Look, they were a
present and we're not
gonna waste them.
[KAMIJO] Personally,
I think I've done a good job
of coming up with
different ways to use them.
There was the noodle
salad, the noodle soup,
the deep fried noodles!
[grunts]
[door bell rings]
[MAIKA humming]
Hey Maika. What're
you doing here?
[MAIKA] I am just
so happy, and I have to
share my joy with somebody!
[BOTH] Huh?
[MAIKA]
Look! Aren't they pretty?
In general, maids are
supposed to look alike,
all blending in together.
But I discovered I could
change my sleeves and collar
just a bit thereby secretly
expressing my individuality.
[MAIKA] The result,
as you may have noticed,
is that I'm now in a
very good mood and would
be happy to lend my
services if they're needed.
[BOTH gasp]
[INDEX and KAMIJO]
Can you please teach us
some new ways
to prepare noodles?
[ACCELERATOR] Nice digs. I
thought they were cutting back
on the salaries of
government employees.
[YOMIKAWA] Well, this
building also serves as
a structural engineering
field test site.
Fortunately for me,
that means the university
picks up part of the rent.
[ACCELERATOR] Ah, gotcha.
"So pretty! And so clean, too!
There isn't a speck
of dust anywhere!"
exclaims Misaka Misaka
as she tests the sofa.
It is clean.
You had to write another
apology letter, didn't you?
[chuckles]
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Hm?
It's her coping mechanism.
Whenever something
goes wrong at work,
she obsessively
cleans her place.
She does it without
thinking, and as a result
she often loses her keys
and other important items.
Hey! Is that any way
to talk to the person
who's helping you
look for a new job?
You should be
nicer to me, you know!
As clean as it is,
I'm guessing things
in the kitchen haven't improved?
[YOMIKAWA] Well, as I recall,
Kikyo, you're always
perfectly happy to
eat the food I offer.
[YOSHIKAWA] Yeah, as
long as I don't have to
know how it's made.
[LAST ORDER] "Wow! You've
got a lot of rice cookers!
Why are there so many?"
asks Misaka Misaka,
counting all of them.
[YOMIKAWA] The rice
cooker is nothing short
of a modern day miracle!
Oh well. [sighs]
[UIHARU] Hey, Misaka!
[MIKOTO] How's it goin', Uiharu?
Good, thanks. I'm just
here to meet up with Shirai.
You know how it is at Judgment.
They're always
keeping me so busy.
[MIKOTO] Yeah. Of course.
Shirai, too. As a matter
of fact, she's even shoved
some of her workload
onto m--I mean, uh.
She's especially busy
because she's so competent.
Well, I guess I
beat her here, huh?
Yeah, it looks like it.
[UIHARU] So, how are things
going for you at Tokiwadai?
Huh?
I hear they're teaching
you to play the violin.
That's so cool!
[MIKOTO] It's not that big a
deal. You wanna give it a try?
Huh?
[MIKOTO] There. Support
the instrument between your
collarbone and jaw.
Gently hold the neck with
your left hand, like this.
Hold the bow so the
strings are perpendicular,
and then slowly pull it.
[violin]
See? Simple, isn't it?
It's amazing.
And you know...
I almost feel
like I'm in a dream.
You're a great teacher!
Ah! Uh!
[MIKOTO] What's the matter?
[trembling]
[KUROKO] Uiharu!
[screams]
[KUROKO] What do you think
you're doing? We've got work!
Hey, I know
I'm late. Sorry!
[MIKOTO] Sorry, huh?
If this is how you make good
on all your bets, you're
a dirty, welshing rat!
Do you really think I don't
have anything better to do
than wait here for over an hour?
Well, no. I didn't
mean to be late.
I got caught up--Wait, an hour?
But I'm pretty sure we agreed
on one o'clock, didn't we?
Hang on, did you show up thirty
minutes early or something?
[KAMIJO] Wow, you have
been here a long time.
I, uh. I was in the
area anyway, so I figured
I would just wait here
until you showed up.
In the area. I see.
Well, I was, uh, shopping.
You're so eager to see
me suffer you showed up
thirty minutes early.
Huh?
[KAMIJO] You really get off
on other people's pain, huh?
[grunts]
You almost got me.
Stop complaining so much!
You lost a bet,
now it's time to pay.
You agreed to
do whatever I said!
Yeah. About that.
Could we be more
specific about "whatever"?
You will do what I say.
[MIKOTO] Now, come with me!
[KAMIJO] Where are we going?
[MIKOTO] Just come along
and do it without talking.
That's the first penalty!
[KAMIJO] The first? You
mean there's more than one?
[KAMIJO] The Handy
Antenna service?
Ah. I see where this is going.
You're looking to replace
the antenna base on your cell.
Yep. Subscribers
can use them to create
their own networks
and everything.
[MIKOTO] Also, if you
sign a couples' contract,
the rate is
substantially cheaper.
A couples' contract?
Yeah but wait there's
more, everybody who signs
a contract right now will get
a Lovely Mitten
Gekota strap for free!
Huh?
That's where you come in.
We're going to
sign up today.
[sighs] All you really want
out of this is the strap.
Don't you have enough
cartoon frog stuff already?
Uh!
You are signing
up with me today.
Yeah, okay. But isn't
a couples' contract
usually something that
a boyfriend and girlfriend
would sign up for.
What? Oh, please!
You're jumping to conclusions!
It has to be
a boy and a girl.
But I don't think that
means you actually
have to be going
out or anything.
For example, I'm sure they'd
sign up a married couple.
Marriage, now?
I think this relationship
is moving too quickly for me.
You--You shut up! I'm
in charge and we've got
a contract to sign! C'mon.
Ah...
Okay! That's about it.
We just need a photograph
to complete the paperwork.
Oh, you mean
like a picture ID?
[FEMALE CLERK 17A]
No, something that proves to us
that you really are a couple.
It doesn't have
to be anything fancy.
You can use your
cell if you want to.
Wait, together?
[KAMIJO] So, uh. Want to
use the camera on my phone?
[MIKOTO] Sure, that'll work.
Okay, then, here we go.
Just so we're absolutely
clear about this,
you're the one who wants
this contract so badly.
I am. I know that, thank you.
I'll do this for you, Gekota!
Well, here we go.
[MIKOTO] Let's do it.
Whenever you're ready.
[phone beeps]
[KAMIJO] It looks like
you're just joking around.
[MIKOTO] What about you?
Looking the other way.
Probably not what
a couple looks like.
Yeah, you're right.
Let's try it again.
[phone beeps]
[KAMIJO] You're making the exact
same face that you made before!
Please! You look
like you'd rather be
poking your eyes
out with a fork!
This is only gonna work
if we can get a photo
of us that makes it
look like we're in love!
Proximity should help.
[KAMIJO] Now, just smile!
This is only a picture
for some paperwork, right?
As long as we think
about it that way,
it shouldn't be a problem.
Right. You're right.
We can totally pull this off.
[MIKOTO]
It just has to look like
we have feelings for each other.
It isn't like it's
real or anything!
[KAMIJO] Say cheese!
[MIKOTO] Cheese!
[phone beeps]
[KUROKO] Haaa!
It's my fault. I have no
one to blame but myself.
I underestimated
this talking baboon
and now here you are,
traipsing around town
and taking dirty
photographs with him.
No! You've got the
wrong idea about this!
I'm only using him to get a
Gekota phone accessory, okay?
And we had to take a photo
pretending to be a couple.
[KUROKO screams]
What are you thinking?
If you needed to
be part of a couple,
I should have been the very
first person you contacted!
I'm much better suited
for the job than him.
[MIKOTO] Wait! Stop it!
[KUROKO] Let's go
take some pictures!
They'll look a lot better than
anything you two could get.
[MIKOTO] Hey,
where are you taking me?
The shop is back there!
[KAMIJO] Looks
like you've got a plan.
Does this mean that
I get to go home now?
[MIKOTO] Like I told you,
it has to be a boy and a girl!
[FEMALE INTERVIEWER]
I'm here with Hajime Hitotsui.
Now, Hajime, I know
you're busy with concerts,
as usual, but the
word on the street is
that you'll be appearing
in a movie soon, as well.
[ACCELERATOR]
Must've fallen asleep.
I can only imagine
how excited you must be!
Would you like to tell
us a little bit about...
[ACCELERATOR] Tch. You're
letting yourself get sloppy.
Even with this thing on,
you're lucky if you can
fight for a full fifteen
minutes these days.
[HITOTSUI]
...process was new to me.
I was truly lucky to be working
with such a talented director.
And not only was he
talented, but patient, too!
[HITOTSUI] He really
helped me adjust.
That goes for the production
crew and my fellow
cast members, as well.
The spirit of camaraderie
on set was incredible.
I don't know exactly
what I was expecting
going into it,
but I ended up having
a pretty amazing experience.
If all films are like this
one...
Doesn't look like
anyone's around.
[HITOTSUI] I hope to be doing
many more in the future.
All right. I'll
grab a shower, then.
[GRILS gasp]
"Hey! What are you thinking,
barging in like that
without bothering to knock?"
Misaka Misaka yells,
reaching for a towel
attempting to
preserve her modesty.
There's a lock on
the door for a reason.
Yeah, sorry about that.
I'm used to living on my own,
so I don't usually
lock the door.
You might want to go ahead
and cover yourself up, too.
"You don't seem
to mind very much that
a boy just saw you naked,"
says Misaka Misaka,
observing your
attitudes with confusion.
Hm. I don't really
see what there is
to make a big deal about.
Nudity is natural.
Then again,
we're mature adults.
[LAST ORDER] "Adults? I think
you two qualify as old ladies,"
says Misaka Misak--Ow! Ow, ow!
Next time,
save us all the trouble
and just lock the door, okay?
[door shuts]
[LAST ORDER] "And that's
everything that happened,"
says Misaka Misaka,
completing the incident report.
"If it is a formal
incident report,
that means it has already
gone out over the network,
so there appears
to be no clear purpose
for repeating it
verbally," says Misaka,
stating what she
thinks is obvious.
"Venting isn't as effective
unless it's done verbally,"
replies Misaka Misaka,
literally shaking with rage.
"I see, and getting
yourself locked out of
the apartment does
not seem to have
improved your mood, either."
"If Misaka had not
happened by, you might have
been stuck outside in this
state of undress for a while,"
observes Misaka seriously,
although she is
laughing on the inside.
[LAST ORDER]
"It isn't Misaka's fault!
The stupid apartment
door locks automatically!"
yells Misaka Misaka
in exasperation.
Hm?
Hey. Where did the
little brat go? Huh?
[BOTH] Hm?
That's a good question.
[MISAKA 10032] "Are you talking
about these?" asks Misaka,
verifying your meaning,
as the question
has come out of the blue.
"All of the other
Misakas have those
exact goggles. Misaka is
the only one without a pair,"
says Misaka Misaka, looking
enviously at your headgear.
"Those Misakas
are those Misakas,
and this Misaka
is this Misaka. See?"
says Misaka, hoping you'll
give up without arguing.
"No fair! Misaka really,
really, really wants
some of her own,"
wheedles Misaka Misaka,
using her small
stature to augment
her spoiled brat
negotiation skills.
"I know that you're
trying to achieve
'endearingly adorable,'
but such tactics do not tend
to be effective on adolescents
of the same gender,"
says Misaka, kindly offering
you some much-needed advice.
Mmm.
"Can I ask a favor, 10032?
Will you show me
how to bow properly?"
asks Misaka Misaka curiously.
Hm?
[LAST ORDER] "You fell for
it!" Misaka Misaka exclaims,
enjoying the success
of her brilliant plan.
"Ha ha! If you want
them back, you'll have to
come and get them from
me!" laughs Misaka Misaka,
[LAST ORDER]
basking in the glory of
running away with her prize.
"Something will have
to be done about her,"
Misaka 10032 declares
in a serious, deadly tone.
♪ [Ending Song] ♪
[KAMIJO] First Misaka
and now Misaka's sister?
No way, there's a
pint-sized Misaka, too?
What's going on here? Wait!
Now Index is getting involved?
Next time, "Serial Number."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.