[NURSE 10A] How is the
critical care patient?
[NURSE 10B] She still hasn't
regained consciousness.
[NURSE 10A] Do you
think it's heat stroke?
[FUKIYOSE] I have heat
stroke...? Oh, right...
I collapsed on the field.
That doesn't make sense...
I was sure to
hydrate all day...
I got plenty of sleep
the night before.
[FUKIYOSE] No way
it's heat stroke.
Please, Fukiyose!
You have to wake up!
[KAMIJO] Just open your eyes!
[FUKIYOSE] Oh, perfect...!
Will he think of me as some
fragile damsel
in distress, now?
I hope not.
This sucks. I worked
so hard to make sure
everybody had a good time.
Please, doctor...
am I going to live?
We should have you back
on your feet in no time.
♪ [Opening Song] ♪
♪
[STIYL] I have one
"off" day... one...
and this is what
happens to me? Pathetic!
[phone buzzing]
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Kami's taken care of it.
He's destroyed
Oriana's Shorthand.
How're things on your end?
Feeling better yet?
Up and running...
There doesn't seem
to be any problem here.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Oh, yeah?
In that case, maybe
you could do me a favor
and cast the "Four
Ways to Truth Spell."
[TSUCHIMIKADO] It should
still be ready where
I set it up before. You
know how to use it, right?
Give me a little credit.
Everything turn out
alright on your end?
What about the spell?
It was supposed to
be on an event ground.
Was there any damage?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] The
damage was limited.
But one of the
students did get hurt...
We took advantage
of the commotion
to get ourselves out
of there inconspicuously.
[STIYL] I see.
And how's the kid doing?
Is he keeping it together?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] If you're ready
for the spell, get to it.
There's a girl in the
hospital and we've got to
make this up to her...
Don't forget that, okay?
[phone beeps]
[STIYL] Obviously,
no magician is perfect.
But sometimes I really can't
stand being so unseasoned.
Now then...
An unforeseen and
unfortunate turn of events.
[STIYL] I've identified
Oriana Thomson's location.
School District 7,
near Futsuka Subway Station.
We've got her!
Futsuka Station!
Wait--Futsuka...?
Then we've
already gone too far.
I've still got eyes on
her. She's moving north.
[STIYL] The street ahead
forks in three directions.
There she is...! You ready...?
You're closing in.
[KAMIJO] We've spotted her.
♪
A bus?!
Damn her!
Hey, hold on a second...
What'd you see?
Were there any other
passengers on the bus?
I don't really get
how that matters!
Kami, wait!
No other passengers.
And no driver, either!
That makes things easier...
'Kay, Stiyl. Number 514457.
Turns out the rune
Stiyl stuck on it
at the service center was
still along for the ride.
♪
[ORIANA chuckles]
Nice try. I'm sorry to
disappoint you fellas,
but flames like that aren't
what's going to get me hot.
[ORIANA] Might dry
me off, though...
I got a bit damp from
all the rushing around.
Want to see...?
I'm not kidding.
Even my panties are soaking.
What you did back
there was unacceptable...
That spell of yours injured
an innocent bystander.
[KAMIJO] She wasn't
involved in this.
You can't honestly say you
thought she was a magician!
As far as I'm concerned,
everyone in the whole
world's involved in this.
With something of
global importance,
there's no such thing
as an innocent bystander.
So you do know
what happened to her.
[ORIANA] For whatever it's
worth, injuring that girl
was not my goal.
This next bit is
intentional, though.
[pained outcries]
Tsuchimikado!
[ORIANA] Oh, my...
I knew one of you
was already injured,
I just figured it
was the chatty one.
[ORIANA] Never know what to
expect here in Academy City...
You sure are
some unusual kids.
Stop it... Tell me
what you did to him!
[ORIANA] I just cancelled
out his flame attribute,
the symbol of regeneration
and restoration,
with blue lettering...
It's a neat little spell, one
designed to target somebody
who has already been
injured to a certain degree.
[KAMIJO] Here!
Damn! I guess I have to
destroy that card to help you.
[ORIANA chuckles]
If you want to save
your friend, good luck.
I recommend you try to defeat
me as quickly as possible.
[ORIANA] Of course,
there's no guarantee
he'll be able to hold out.
The time he has remaining
may be surprisingly
short, indeed.
[KAMIJO] Damn you!
I don't have the slightest idea
what the Stab Sword is worth...
And I don't exactly know
how it fits into the
grand scheme of things.
How it may change
the course of history
or influence the
whole world, but...
I do know...
that nothing is worth
hurting somebody like this...
If that's what this
stupid relic of yours does...
if all you can
accomplish with it is
bringing pain and
misery to people...
then I'm going to find it
and smash it into pieces,
I promise you!
What do you
want, an explanation?
Saying I had no choice
and I'm just doing my job
would be cowardly.
And dishonest...
After all, they left how
I should carry
this out up to me.
Stop screwing around
with people's lives...
or you'll get what you deserve!
Ahhh!
Where is she?!
[KAMIJO] This is bad. If she
uses that same spell on me...
[ORIANA] Next I think
I'll use the shadow sword.
I like to keep
things interesting.
Ha!
[KAMIJO] Auh!
[KAMIJO] Always
a different attack.
[ORIANA chuckles]
I prefer not to use
the same spell
over and over again.
It gets so monotonous.
[chuckles]
Huahhh-uh!
[KAMIJO struggling]
[ORIANA] You're not
doing so well, huh?
This is just a
little foreplay...
but maybe you've had
all you can handle for now.
[KAMIJO] Ahhh!
[thud]
[KAMIJO] Euhhh... Damn...
[KAMIJO] She wasn't kidding...
She never uses
the same spell twice.
How does she have
so many combinations
right at her fingertips?
Next up is one that
I call Blade Crater.
[ORIANA] Just so you know...
if you move,
you're going to die.
[KAMIJO] If I move... I die.
What am I supposed to do,
just sit here and wait?
It's the Daihasei Festival,
the event Fukiyose has
[KAMIJO] worked so hard for...
and this magician
wants to ruin it.
[KAMIJO] And I'm just
supposed to let that happen?
I'd never forgive
myself if I didn't try
to stop you... So that's
what I'm gonna do!
♪
Aaahhh!
Get back... You're a fool.
Ahhh!
He did that with his hand...?
Is it that powerful...? Fine!
[ORIANA] Drop Rest!
Haaa!
[KAMIJO] Ha!
[ORIANA] Ugh!
Ah...!
Uh!
[heavy breathing]
[sighs]
[KAMIJO] Tsuchimikado!
Are you alright...?
Hang in there, okay.
[ORIANA scoffs]
[ORIANA sighs]
Such a violent young man!
Oh, no... Looks like
my button's fallen off.
You know, that was
a pretty well executed
punch for an amateur...
I am woman enough
to admit that...
However, having someone
respond to my spells
with counterattacks isn't
a new experience for me.
Although I confess it isn't
usually this frustrating.
[ORIANA] Well... I have to run.
I'll leave that
bit of cargo with you
for the time being.
But don't make the
mistake of thinking
the game is over yet, okay?
Things are just beginning
to heat up in this city.
[KAMIJO] Hold on...!
What about my friend?!
Calm down. The spell
only lasts twenty minutes...
It'll be over before too long.
[ORIANA] Goodbye,
my anxious little esper.
[STIYL] All right.
In that case, you're
going to have to
destroy the Stab Sword.
[STIYL] Your right
hand should be able to
take care of it, no problem.
[KAMIJO] But... are you
sure that's what I should do?
If they attack Academy City,
wouldn't it be a
good thing to have?
[STIYL] If Oriana
and her employer attack,
they're the ones who're
going to be in trouble.
[STIYL] This is
still Academy City...
The center of enemy territory
for all magical forces.
They'll more than
likely pull out and then
come up with another strategy.
You think so?
[STIYL] Hurry up. I'll be busy
figuring out our next move.
Alright.
Here we go...
♪
[gasps]
[KAMIJO] What the--?
What's this?
But, I don't understand...
[KAMIJO]
What the hell is going on?
[ORIANA] Well...
there were a few hiccups.
But I can report
that all the necessary
checkpoints
have been cleared...
So you're free to relax now.
[LIDVIA] What kind
of hiccups, exactly?
[ORIANA] Well... you just let
me worry about that, alright?
Oh, and they
have possession of
the signboard I was
lugging all over the city.
So, at this point...
they've probably found out
about the Stab Sword, as well.
[LIDVIA gasps]
Aw...! Come now,
don't you worry,
I would never let
anything happen that would
interfere with the deal--
you should know that!
[ORIANA] And because I will
not allow it to happen...
it follows that
it will not happen.
And especially
not with this deal.
There's far too
much riding on this
to allow any
more mistakes. Right?
"The original Stab Sword
does not, in fact, exist...
All that remains of the
sword are the folk stories
containing peoples'
speculations about it."
Well...
[LAURA] Charles Conder,
you came bearing this note...
So tell me...
Are its contents true?
[CONDER] I am terribly sorry.
Even the British Museum
was unaware of this.
We only found out the
truth of the matter today.
But the relic...
If it's not the Stab Sword,
then what is it?
[CONDER] Ma'am... the
lore regarding the relic
is quite often
confused and vague...
thus the regrettable lack
of conclusive evidence.
But we do not believe
that it's a sword.
It's not?
The locals refer to it as
"Croce di Pietro."
[CONDER] I'm sure I don't
need to tell you this,
but in our language,
that translates to
The Cross of Peter.
[LAURA] We're dealing
with the Cross of Peter?!
In that case...
this is no simple matter
they have been trying
to set in motion...
It is far more
serious than we believed.
[LAURA] The conclusion
of this "deal" could mean
the demise of Academy City.
No... It could be
something far worse than that.
Man, nothing can
ever be easy, can it?
So I take it
we're dealing with
something
dangerous, then?
The item in question
is the Croce di Pietro.
Or, to translate for
you, the Cross of Peter.
[STIYL] Long ago, the
Vatican, the main basilica of
the Roman Orthodox Church,
is said to have been
built where the body of Peter
is buried, with a crucifix
erected overlooking
a vast expanse of land.
[STIYL] But there
is a corollary.
Meaning?
Anywhere the Croce di Pietro
is planted is theirs...
It comes under exclusive
Roman Orthodox Control...
Even if it's somewhere
like Academy City.
But, how does that work?
Everything will
play out in a way that
only serves the Roman
Orthodox Church... and...
everyone will
happily go along,
because they won't sense
that anything is out of place.
[STIYL] It means that no
matter how unjust life becomes,
no matter the burdens that
people are made to carry...
no one in the world
will be able to feel
anything but happiness.
Seriously?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] If they
succeed in this first step
and Academy City comes under
Roman Orthodox control,
then the world as we
know it will change.
There will no longer be
an equal balance between
the scientific
and magical spheres.
The scales will tip
toward the side of
the Roman Catholic Church.
So you mean...
this transaction is...
You got it...
They're orchestrating
the takeover of Academy City
and the whole
world along with it.
[TSUCHIMIKADO yawning]
Let's get going...
We've got a deal to stop.
If we don't succeed in this,
the world will face a
fate worse than collapse
[STIYL] and something far more
insidious than domination.
[INDEX] Ah!
[INDEX] Toma!
A world in which
nobody can feel anything
other than happiness
and contentment?
To...! Ma!
[INDEX] Errrh!
[sighs]
I just can't wrap my head
around it for some reason.
[INDEX] Toma!
[grunts]
That can't be Index.
She would never be
wearing that outfit.
[INDEX] Toma!
Ahhh!
Why are you ignoring me?
I couldn't even get
you to turn around!
Out of curiosity,
what's up with
the skimpy outfit?
Eh! Never mind...
Uh...!
Be honest now, Toma. What
were you just thinking...?
You were picturing
something dirty
in your mind
right then, I know it!
[INDEX]
And how do I know it...?
Because your
cheeks are bright red
and you look awfully
pleased about something.
I'm not pleased!
Really! I swear!
Um... I was
just wondering where
your nun's habit
is, that's all.
Hmph... I'm letting
Komoe hang onto it for me.
Well, uh...
You look mad...
Can you tell me
what's got you so angry?
[meow]
Oh...! I know what it is!
You're hungry, aren't you?
I can solve that problem!
We're about to meet up with
my mom and dad for lunch.
If you can hold on
just a little longer...
Sorry... Does that
not sound... good?
It's not about that,
you giant idiot!
Then what is
bothering you?
You know why I changed clothes?
It was so I could stand in the
bleachers and cheer for you!
I was there, so why did I
have nobody to cheer for?!
Oh... about that... I was...
I worked so hard trying
to be close to you today,
but nothing I did was any use!
[INDEX] You were always running
off on your own somewhere...
So what should I have done?
What else should I have tried?
Oh, I'm sorry... Um...
I just figured you
were cranky because
you were hungry, since
that's usually the ca--
You figured
wrong, you jerk!
I'm angry because you
never pay attention to me!
I certainly never get
cranky due to hunger!
I didn't mean to make
you mad, I promise!
And what's
with the beating?
Don't you usually
prefer to bite me?
Um... what I mean is...
You're acting a
little different today...
How could you say that?
[KAMIJO] Wha--?!
Wait...! I didn't mean it
in the way you think.
It wasn't an insult...
You do literally bite
me a lot, you know...
[KAMIJO] Ahhh!
[SHINA] It doesn't seem like
we've seen very much of Toma
at all since we've been here.
Well, now... there's not
a lot going on, after all...
We can't expect him to
spend every second with us.
[WOMAN] Hey!
[SHINA] Hm?
Hello again... I'm
glad I ran into you.
Oh, of course...
From this morning.
That's right. I just
wanted to say thanks
for your help before...
with finding
Mikoto, I mean.
Who're they?
Some friends of yours?
Hm. No...
Better than that, dear...
They're the parents of that
boy you're so interested in.
Errhhh...
Nice to meet
you, young lady.
The name is Kamijo.
Pleasure to meet you!
Er, I, um...
Come on, dear...
Say something,
already. Charm them!
Wait...! It isn't
like that at all!
You don't know
anything!
Have you two had lunch?
Oh, lunch...?
No, we haven't.
In that case,
you're more than welcome
to join us if
you would like...
[WOMAN] I know
the perfect place!
Really? You
wouldn't mind company?
Sounds great. We'd love to!
[BOTH] Ahhh!
Whoops...!
Sorry, are
you all right?
Oh! I'm sorry... I hope
you can forgive me.
I'm not accustomed to
being around so many people.
No... it's no
problem at all. Really.
[ORIANA] Sorry again.
If you'll excuse me...
[SHINA] Oh, my goodness!
Doing it again...?
Honestly, Toya!
[TOYA] No...!
It's not like that...!
I wasn't staring or
anything... I was just...
Eh. You know... Uh...
[TOYA] I'm sorry!
Please forgive me!
No doubt about it.
That's his father, alright.
[TOYA] Hey...! Toma!
We're over here! Come on!
[KAMIJO] I'm surprised you guys
were able to find this place.
Well... I admit, we
did have a little help
from our new friends.
[MISUZU] Hi, I'm Misaka.
[KAMIJO]
It's nice to meet you...
and thanks a lot
for helping my folks.
Oh man... I'm so hungry
I could eat a horse!
[MIKOTO] Hey, what's
your problem, huh...?
We've known each other
a while now, right?
And after all this
time, you've still never
bothered to call me?
Oh, well... I
figured we'd naturally
end up stuck like this.
We're not "stuck"
like anything!
And "natural" is
the last word I'd use
to describe
something involving you!
You know, while we're at it,
there's another thing
I'd like you to explain...
Who's this girl
who's always with you,
and where
does she live?
Who is she?
Well, uh...
She's got a
point there, Toma...
I think it would
be nice to know
who this young lady is, too.
[TOYA] She was with you
when we spent that night
at the beach, but
that's all we know.
[MIKOTO] Th-The beach?!
You... You spent
the night with her
at the beach?!
Why don't we interrogate
you, short-hair?
Who are you, and
where do you live?
What's your
relationship to Toma?
Are you his girlfriend?
Huh...? No... Um ...
It's not like that.
I just know the guy.
But you came to
cheer on his school.
Don't deny it! I saw you!
Eh...
[INDEX] Unless I'm mistaken...
it was the tower topple event.
You've got it all
wrong...! That's it...
I think you should shut
your bratty little mouth!
Now, girls... Why
don't we all sit down
and get something
to eat, huh?
So, then...
We haven't formally met,
but you're Toma, aren't you?
Yes, ma'am, that's me...
So, um... are you Misaka's
older sister or something?
[WOMAN chuckles]
Sorry. My name is
Misuzu Misaka...
and I'm Mikoto's mother...
Nice to meet you!
[ALL] Her mother?!
♪ [Ending Song] ♪
[KAMIJO] Solving one
riddle after another,
we slowly draw closer to the
center of the sinister plot...
But will a chance encounter
with Himegami end in tragedy?
Next time, "Stab Sword."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.