[KAMIJO] The Daihasei
Sports Festival
has Academy City bustling.
Which gives the Catholic
Church the perfect chance
to conduct a transaction
involving a powerful relic.
[KAMIJO] To obtain the
Stab Sword, they are using
a courier named
Oriana Thomson.
And I may have just accidentally
come into contact with her.
♪ [Opening Song] ♪
[beeping]
[dial tone]
Kami, hey.
How's it goin'?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] As we speak,
I've got eyes on a spot
Oriana is likely
to use for the dea--
[KAMIJO] Tsuchimikado...
I just shook hands
with a woman...
and when I did, I felt my
Imagine Breaker do something.
For now I can't tell
you who she is, exactly...
[KAMIJO] but I think it's safe
to say that she's not a student.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] This woman...
is she carrying
a large package?
[KAMIJO] Yeah... She's got
what looks to be a signboard.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Okay,
where are you right now?
Right now? I'm following
her, of course...
I'm going to send
you my GPS coordinates
so you'll be able to
see where we are, kay?
She saw me!
[KAMIJO breathing heavy]
Where is she? Which one?
Over there...
wearing a work uniform...
Woman with
the blonde hair.
[ORIANA] Looks like we've
got two pros on the scene.
My instructions were
not to engage anybody,
but something tells me
they won't make it easy.
♪
I'm not sure why,
but her behavior feels off.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] I wonder
if she's changed her mind?
[heavy breathing]
She's in the bus terminal?
Nah, this's just a
servicing station.
It's a trap...! Get down, Kami!
[STIYL] Actually, you're up.
[KAMIJO] You screwing with me?
Nope... In fact, I think
that was an excellent
example of teamwork.
Having a clear division
of labor makes things
go more smoothly.
Ehhh.
If you're playing
games with me...!
Well I'm not,
kid. So go ahead
and finish
your job, already!
And what exactly
is my job here?!
♪
Okay, Stiyl...
You post the necessary
runes and stand by here...
As for me... I'll
pin down the courier.
Roger that.
Well...? What are
you gonna do now, Kami?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] I think
it's probably safer
for you to stay here.
I don't know...
I agree with him...
I think it'll definitely be
safer for you to remain here...
But I'm talking about
my safety, not yours.
Aghhh.
These are decoys.
She's just buying time.
If you take on all of them,
she's going to get away.
Yeah? Well what else do
you expect me to do? Ah!
Euhhh...
[KAMIJO] Got her!
[rumbling]
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Whenever
you're ready, Kami...
Huh...? What am
I supposed to do?
[grunts]
[power yell]
♪
[grunts]
A note from Oriana Thomson,
also known as "Route Disturb."
Now she's toying with us!
[chuckles]
Ah!
[BOY STUDENT 9A]
Oh...! Excuse me!
Are you alright, miss?
Ah...
Oh, no... I should be
the one apologizing to you.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] This spell is
called "Four Ways to Truth."
Using this, we'll be able
to pinpoint Oriana's location.
But, won't it hurt you?
I thought you weren't
supposed to use magic.
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
And that is why...
I'm gonna' go get some help.
Hm?
[STIYL] Traveling on the wind...
conveying not air but will
to the specified location.
♪
Uh.
"Traveling on the wind...
conveying not air but will to
the specified location." Right?
[screaming]
Stiyl!
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Kami!
Go give Stiyl
a pat on the back.
[STIYL screaming]
[STIYL heavy exhale]
[breathing heavy]
That hurt...! What
did she just do to me...?
Some kind of trace prevention
spell or something...?
Just as general protection?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Nope...
I don't think it's
something that simple.
What I think...
is that there's a specialized
interception spell...
One that has been
specifically designed to react
automatically to
Stiyl's personal magic.
So what does that mean...?
Stiyl's been singled
out so he can no longer
direct any magic
towards Oriana?
[STIYL] This is serious...
That's a hell of a
thing to have prepared.
It's a pretty big deal
for one person to be able to
detect a specific life
force, trace it back...
and then apply
a counterattack...
But I guess that's
Route Disturb for you, huh?
Sorry? Route Disturb?
The other name that
Oriana Thomson goes by.
[STIYL] This may sound crazy,
but there's something about
her particular method that
strikes me as familiar.
I must be wrong though,
don't you think...?
There's no way she could
be in possession of one.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Well...
oddly enough... I was just
thinking that there's no
other possible explanation.
[STIYL] Are you serious...?
But if it's really true,
that would mean
Oriana's a sorceress,
not a magician
like we thought.
What are you
guys talking about?
What is this thing she has?
Something
that is a receptacle
for magical knowledge.
It can function on its
own as a magical array.
It works independently
of the magician's will.
An original grimoire.
[STIYL] You think so...?
Creating a grimoire to fit
these exact circumstances.
That would be quite difficult.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] The
original text could just be
a scribbled note. It would
have limited effectiveness...
and it would break down quickly.
Let's call it "Shorthand."
That should be accurate enough.
Okay, fine. But what does
that mean we should do?
First thing...
we have to take out
the automatic intercept spell.
For that, we're going to need
to be able to use Stiyl's magic.
And what are the
chances of her fleeing
the search area while
we're doing that?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] If she
was so sure that she could
get away cleanly, I
don't think she'd go to
the trouble of setting
up an intercept spell, do you?
[STIYL] Hmm...
Okay, Stiyl...
You need to try using
your magic on something.
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
A divination circle.
This is a yet-unused
magical array,
and it doesn't
employ anyone's magic.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] It will
activate in response to
the power of the intercept
spell, providing us with
the direction and distance.
Now then...
[KAMIJO] Hold on,
Tsuchimikado...
To make it work, won't he have
to use his magic one more time?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Are you kidding?
Who said anything
about one time...?
If we don't find the
Shorthand's location
the first time around,
we'll have to keep
trying over and over.
[KAMIJO] You bastard!
Easy... You seem to have
forgotten something,
so let me remind you...
There are many lives
at stake in this battle.
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
It's that serious...
The entire world
may even be at risk.
[STIYL] Let's get on with it.
[gasps]
No, Stiyl you can't!
Now is not the time
to worry about me...
If I can put a stop to all this,
it's a small price to pay.
But if I do it, you had
damn well better pinpoint
the location of
the intercept spell.
I know your terms.
We must preserve the life Index
leads here in Academy City...
That was your
stipulation, wasn't it?
[STIYL] Toma Kamijo...
I am not entirely pleased
with the fact that you
are here right now...
It seems like you
ought to be at her side.
If this ends in
sadness for her...
It will be your fault.
[STIYL screaming]
♪
[INDEX] Oooh...
I was really hoping that
this would work...
That changing clothes would
get Toma's attention!
But it looks like
he just wandered off
somewhere without me.
[KOMOE] Oh,
come on now, sister!
There's no need to
be so disheartened...!
I'm sure he must've had some
important reason for
running off like he did!
Errr.
[sighs]
[FUKIYOSE] That guy's
getting on my last nerve!
I take my eyes off him for
one second, and he disappears.
I mean, honestly! Uh.
[FUKIYOSE] What's the matter?
Oh, hi, Fukiyose!
Is there something
wrong with that girl?
Does she need
some first aid?
If she's feeling
mentally overwhelmed...
a little of this ought to
help snap her out of it...
It's a powdered herb that ca--
[KOMOE] No!
I mean, thank you...!
But I think this is something
I can handle on my own.
[FUKIYOSE]
Okay, if you're sure.
[INDEX] Where's Toma?
All I want to know is
where he could've gone?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Here it comes.
The divination circle is
beginning to respond now...
Hey, Kami!
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
You have a map don't you?
Yeah... you know...
that GPS map on
your cell phone?
Well, come on. Bring it here.
[KAMIJO] Tsuchimikado!
How can you be so
calm about all of this?!
Stiyl is being tormented
repeatedly all because of you!
Stay cool...
He is a professional
magician, you know.
He's got enough
attack resistance to
handle this spell,
and he knows it.
[shaky exhale]
[KAMIJO] What's going on?
You're bleeding!
The divination circle...
responds to the magic
power of incoming spells,
allowing us to determine
their distance and direction.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Obviously,
such a handy little tool
can't be activated
without the expenditure
of some magical effort.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Of course,
if my ability to use magic
wasn't so handicapped...
Stiyl wouldn't have
to go through this.
That much is true...
So you can go
ahead and blame me.
Although... I will
not be stopped from
finding the Shorthand
and destroying it.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] I also
intend to catch Oriana
and personally see to
it that the Stab Sword
deal is off for good...
Now, Kami... Your map.
I want to know
what's three hundred
and two meters
northwest of here...
Because that's where we can
find the Shorthand grimoire.
Uh... okay...
[KAMIJO] Looks like...
[gasps]
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
It's a middle school?!
Great, a festival!
And the event's
about to start...!
All of the spectators
and cameras
are already there by now.
Guess sneaking around
isn't going to do us
any good this time.
Okay then,
what's the plan...?
We're not gonna sit back
and do nothing, right?
I suppose
we'll just have to
pretend to be contestants.
[KAMIJO] Don't you
have a better idea...?
We're in high school, man!
How're we gonna pass
for middle schoolers?
[KAMIJO] Damn!
We need to get in
there, and quickly.
There's a decent risk
that the intercept spell
might turn on others, too.
[KAMIJO] Huh?
Do you know what the
easiest and most common way
of triggering a
magic ritual is, Kami?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] By touching.
A regular person with
no knowledge of magic
still has a chance of
activating the intercept
spell by touching it.
Now, they don't
have the kind of
defenses a magician
has, so if that happens,
they'll be in real danger.
At any rate, let's hurry...
We've gotta get to
that intercept spell
before it hurts anyone.
[KAMIJO] All right!
[TSUCHIMIKADO] And to
help us with that...
[lauhging]
Egh!
Cannon ball!
Uuhhh.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] I'm sorry,
sir. Excuse me...
Our event is the next one
up, but were kinda' hopin'
we wouldn't have to
go into on to the field
lookin' like this,
ya know what I mean?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] My mom
wants pictures and stuff...
Doesn't everyone's?
And I suppose that you're hoping
to change your gym clothes.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Ahhh
Yes, sir...! We are...!
But obviously, they're
in the locker room.
Yeah... you can go in,
just make it quick.
But rules are still rules...
I'll need to check
your IDs before you pass.
You know, I--
[TSUCHIMIKADO chuckles]
Okay...! Here ya go, sir!
Ugh...!
Come on, kid...!
Would it have killed you
to wipe off your muddy hand?
Oh, well... Go on...
They usually don't
let students enter late.
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Thank you so much, man!
Well...? We're not
exactly gonna blend in
looking like this, you know.
Yep... I'm guessing
there are changes
of clothing in the nurse's
office. We'll look there.
[FEMALE ANNOUNCER 9A]
The next event will be
the ball toss competition.
This event will see
two hundred students from
Minamizawa Middle
School pitted against
twenty students from
Tokiwadai Middle School.
[crowd cheering]
[GIRL lauhging]
You can smell fear
radiating from them
like a fine perfume...
I like your scent, gentlemen.
[GIRLS giggle]
[MIKOTO] What exactly
is the meaning of this...?
What is he doing?!
[MIKOTO] He doesn't even
belong in this event...! Jeez!
No...! Tokiwadai?
You're kidding me!
They've got some
serious espers over there!
Oh, do they...?
Well, I guess we should
watch out for stray
shots, then, shouldn't we?
If the Shorthand is
here, where would it be?
Where should we look?
I'd say the baskets are
the most likely place.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] They probably
borrowed some from elsewhere,
so they could have
been rigged before
they were even brought here.
I'm going to go through and
check each basket in order.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] As for you,
your work begins once
I find the Shorthand.
[crowd cheering]
Everybody ready...?
Get set! And, go!
[BOYS yelling]
What're you
standing there for?
Get moving, Kami!
Oh... Right!
♪
[KAMIJO] Is that the one?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] No, this isn't
it... Let's keep on moving.
Huh?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Not that
one, either... C'mon!
[KAMIJO] Ah!
[BOYS yelling]
[KAMIJO] Watch out!
Hey, Kami! You can
use my back to jump!
[KAMIJO] Quick,
you need to move!
[STUDENTS gasping]
[rumble]
[crowd cheering]
[breathing heavy]
You know, I really
can't believe this!
[MIKOTO] That you
would take it this far!
Just so I would lose
our bet and have to play
your dumb penalty game!
[GIRL screams]
[MIKOTO] Honestly! I had
to do something, you jerk,
or you were gonna
get yourself hurt.
[KAMIJO] Misaka!
Don't touch that!
Huh...? What's wrong?
[KAMIJO] Listen to me, okay...?
I'll explain
everything, I promise.
Just move away from there!
What...? Move away? Why?
What are you talking about...?
I still don't know
what you're doing
competing in a
middle school event...
How about you explain
yourself and then--
[KAMIJO] You stay
out of this, kid!
[KAMIJO] Don't argue!
Just come over here, please.
Uh?
You're in danger
standing there!
[MIKOTO] What...? You're
being stupid! Please...!
You don't really
think I needed you
to defend me from that guy?
I can take care of myself!
Now, how about that
explanation you offered?
Like I said,
I'll tell you later!
[KAMIJO]
That spot is dangerous.
I don't want you getting
hurt. It's that simple!
[MIKOTO] Me? Get hurt? I don't
need you protecting me...
I don't care how sweet
you're being. I'm fine...
That's it! You startled
me and now I'm babbling.
Just leave me alone
already, will you?
Uh--What the--?
[KAMIJO] Just keep quiet...
Hold still for a second.
[MIKOTO] Um... I, uh...
I'm too late...! C'mon!
Talk to me, Misaka.
Do you have a fever?
Does it hurt?
Ugh!
What do you
mean?! I'm fine!
Hey, Tsuchimikado...!
It's over here on this pole!
[KAMIJO] I was wrong!
[wistle blows]
You again, Kamijo...?
This is ridiculous!
Why are you even here?
I was wondering why you ran
off in such a hurry before,
but I didn't expect
this! Explain yourself!
Now we'll have to
restart the whole event!
[screams]
Fukiyose!
Whoa... What happened?
Hurry up. You need
to go and touch her.
She's got no magical
defense. She won't last...
Get over there, now!
Please, Fukiyose...!
You have to wake up!
[KAMIJO] Just open your eyes!
♪
Fine, Oriana Thomson...
I've had enough of this.
You're not gonna
be dictating the terms
of this fight anymore.
You lost that
privilege when you
started involving
innocent people...
If you think I'm
going to stand around
and let you keep
hurting them, then...
[KAMIJO] I'll show you
just how wrong you are.
I hope you're ready...
'cause I won't be showing
any mercy when I come for you.
♪ [Ending Song] ♪
[KAMIJO]
Fukiyose has collapsed...
Stiyl and Tsuchimikado are
in the line of fire, too.
If the Stab Sword is the
reason for all this...
I swear I'm gonna destroy it.
Next time, "Shorthand."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.