[TSUCHIMIKADO] Three is for
heaven, four is for earth,
and twelve represents
the entire world.
You attach meaning to specific
numbers like that, don't you?
The practice of
numerological divination.
It's a very useful system,
but it didn't start
with the church of the cross.
In fact, the ancient Greeks used
it back in Pythagoras' day.
Which would make
that date BCE.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] That's a bit
earlier in history than you guys
usually like to dabble.
[screech]
There's no point getting
involved in a drawn-out battle.
It's quite a shame, really.
A finely-wrought
spell like this.
It nearly breaks my
heart to destroy it.
[grunts]
[ACCELERATOR] I'm screwed if
I have to fight too many times.
[ACCELERATOR] I don't have
even four solid minutes of
ability mode left on this thing.
[ACCELERATOR] I plan on
using them well, though.
Whatever else,
I'm gonna save the kid.
[MAN] The whole building is
clear. There's nobody around.
It's all here in the report.
It's because we're
under a terrorist threat.
They evacuated the staff and
the patients temporarily;
all of 'em.
Which means they're
onto us, then.
Yeah, not good for us.
[phone ringing]
What d'you think?
Could it be a trap?
Doubt it. I haven't
spotted any wires
or infrared anywhere.
[phone ringing]
[FROG DOCTOR] About time.
It took you long enough.
Heaven Canceller?
[FROG DOCTOR] We're in a hurry,
so I'll keep this brief.
Leave Kihara behind and get
yourselves out of there.
If you don't go, your
lives will be in danger.
Leave now? Are you serious?
[FROG DOCTOR] Accelerator is
headed in your direction.
[sighs]
[FROG DOCTOR] Trust me when
I say he's not holding back.
You should steer clear of
him if you value your life.
It's that simple.
Heh. You're overreacting.
[FROG DOCTOR] Very well.
Try to stay alive.
If you're still breathing,
I can save you.
[HOUND DOG screams]
[laughs]
[coughs]
[FEMALE NEWSCASTER] We are
currently receiving reports from
all over the country of people
suddenly losing consciousness.
Law enforcement
officers say they are
identifying the cause
as swiftly as they can.
The phenomenon does not appear
to be limited to our country...
It appears to be spreading
to other countries as well.
[VENTO] All we really
needed was to have
Academy City under our control.
[phone buzzes]
Last Order's calling?
No, it must be Kihara.
[KAMIJO] Oh, good! I didn't
think I was gonna reach anyone.
[ACCELERATOR] I've heard this
voice somewhere before.
[KAMIJO] I've been going through
and calling all the numbers
in Last Order's cell phone.
You're the only one
who answered so far.
You probably don't
know the situation,
but to put it plainly,
she and I could really
use some help right about now.
[KAMIJO] Last Order's in danger.
What exactly
is the situation?
[ACCELERATOR] You had to split
up at the restaurant, huh?
I can take care of all
this from here on out.
You're all done.
Just get rid of that phone
and go back to your
regularly scheduled life.
Sorry, but that's
not happening.
I'll help save her.
Just tell me what to do.
Okay, fine. You know that huge
bridge in School District 7?
Last Order and I set that
as our rendezvous point
in case
anything happened.
If she's still on the run,
that's the first place
she'll be headed.
Okay. I'll go there!
Something is going
on in Academy City.
There have been some
strange intruders
coming in from the outside.
Meanwhile, people here
are dropping like flies,
Antiskill included.
This attack seems fairly
indiscriminate so far.
So watch your back, okay?
Tch. Just keeps
getting better.
[KAMIJO] I'm sorry about this.
I never should have let her
go out there on her own.
Well, you're not
the only one.
I just meant to leave the
kid alone for five minutes,
and look what happened.
[HOUND DOG A] We've lost
contact with multiple squads.
[AMATA] Which means...
Either they ran
away or they're dead.
Whatever the case, I'll be
collecting all their hearts
when we're done here.
[AMATA] Have you recovered
the group we sent out as decoys
when that woman got in our way?
[HOUND DOG A] Yes.
We're not completely sure
what happened, sir.
Their oxygen levels had
dropped extremely low.
Sounds like some kind
of induced asphyxia.
[sighs]
That woman's responsible.
Damn her! If she's
the reason our boys
are out cold, we'll
teach her a less--
[AMATA] Huh?
[HOUND DOGS chatter]
[AMATA] Her again, but how
is she locating her targets?
Not with science. Is it magic?
Listen up, Hound Dogs.
Whatever else is going on,
our plans haven't changed.
Is the Testament rig ready?
[HOUND DOG B] Yes, sir.
[HOUND DOG B] Right here.
[ACCELERATOR pained exhale]
I've seen that before.
It belongs to her.
[phone buzzes]
[AMATA] Hey, Accelerator!
How're things going?
[laughs]
[ACCELERATOR] I'm a little busy.
Was there something you wanted?
[AMATA] Well,
I was just wondering
if you'd found the present
I left behind for you.
If not, you should
keep your eyes open.
It's a small bit of fabric
from a child's shirt.
On a totally different subject,
Testament is really
something else, huh?
It just isn't normal to cram
a virus right into a
person's head, you know?
[laughs]
[ACCELERATOR]
So, what kind of reaction
are you expecting from me?
[AMATA] Huh?
Am I supposed to start shaking
and laugh a crazy laugh?
Or what?
[AMATA] You should be careful.
I'm the one holding
all the cards.
The kid's life is in my hands.
Heh! So why haven't you
gotten around to killing her,
I wonder? Were you
given an order
from the people who hired you?
Was it that standard line about
not damaging the merchandise?
I know you're not always
good at following directions.
Your bosses must
be hardcore.
Can't believe they've got
you shaking in your boots
at the thought of hurting
a little kid like her.
[AMATA] She will die.
[ACCELERATOR] Not yet she won't.
I know that bastard.
After everything I've said
to him, he should have
at least taken one of
her eyes out already,
and that's if he
was in a good mood.
Since he hasn't, that
can mean only one thing.
Well, well. Amata Kihara's
actually under someone's thumb.
A backer powerful
enough to keep even
that dog on his leash?
In Academy City, that
leaves one possibility.
It must be the
governing board.
If I look into them--
Heh, heh, heh!
That's what I'm talking about.
I'm finally making some
headway now! Ha, ha, ha!
Fine. You wanna
screw with me?
Then I'll screw
with you right back!
[grunts]
[yells]
[gasps]
[ALEISTER] Hm. There seems
to be some kind of commotion
going on out front.
This is of no consequence.
The deployment of
the Imaginary Number School
District Five-Element Agency
is complete.
If any magic is invoked within
the limits of Academy City,
the magician wielding it will
lose control and self-destruct.
Vento of the Front,
did you say your name was?
You're no exception.
You'll be destroyed, as well.
At our current output,
we cannot yet envelop
the entire world, but
with the activation of
the powerful Fuse Kazakiri,
things are going to change,
quite dramatically.
[VENTO coughs]
[pained gasp]
[VENTO] I don't
understand what's going on.
There's a presence that I
can detect but not identify,
and it's still expanding.
[gasps]
Her again? What the
hell are you doing here?
[VENTO] Nice of you to find me
so I could finish
the job I started.
[KAMIJO yells]
Tell me what you've
done with Last Order!
What are you
talking about, boy?
A last order of what, exactly?
[gasps]
[KAMIJO grunts]
What's happening?
I see it. It's the Imaginary
Number School District
Five-Element Agency.
You just became a
much lower priority.
[VENTO] Who the hell do they
think they're messing with,
pulling a dirty stunt
like this? I'll show them!
[grunts]
[KAMIJO] She disappeared.
What did she see that
freaked her out so much?
You're kidding, right?
[FEMALE COMPUTER VOICE]
Deployment of Imaginary
Number School District,
Five-Element Agency commencing.
Currently authenticating code
for host individual, Last Order.
Authenticated. Fuse Kazakiri
will now emerge.
Attention all personnel.
Please prepare yourselves
according to the guidelines.
This is impossible! An angel?
It's too dangerous to stay
out here, but Last Order.
I still haven't found her!
Where is she?
[phone rings]
Uh, hey. I came to the
bridge like you said,
but Last Order isn't here.
Have you had any luck?
[ACCELERATOR] Heh, heh.
What are you, an idiot?
You actually believed
what I told you before?
Don't worry about it.
I'll have the kid's
location figured out soon.
You weren't ever
going to find her
blindly running around the city.
I've got it from here.
You run along home.
Can you see the
sky right now?
And those giant wings of light?
[KAMIJO] I have to go do
something about that angel.
So I really won't be able to
help you and Last Order anymore.
I think we'll be okay.
I'm sorry.
Don't get
yourself killed.
Sure thing.
Right back at ya.
[grunts]
[TSUCHIMIKADO] So he finally
used it, then. That bastard.
He's attempting to wipe out
the enemy completely!
[MISAKA NETWORK]
Signal confirmed
from host individual 20001.
Estimated danger level of five.
Misaka 10032 rejects.
Rejection denied.
Accepting signal on
channels R, V, and Y.
Heavy load on thought
functions. Rejection denied.
We will do everything
we can without
opposing the given order.
Do you understand?
Our goal is simple:
to diffuse the current
situation if possible.
[groaning]
[ACCELERATOR] Mister Thomas
Platinaburg. One of the twelve
members of the governing
board of Academy City.
[ACCELERATOR] Eyes-only
operation. Code name: Angel.
To be used in an emergency
to quell an unknown threat.
Operation involves planting
a virus in Last Order
that will counter said threat.
Are they serious with this?
[ACCELERATOR] At the very least,
it has to mean that the kid
is still alive somewhere.
You bastard, Kihara.
Where the hell
are you hiding her?
What's going on?
The sky looks crazy!
Uh. Hey, what are you
doing out so late?
You have to let me go!
[INDEX] I have to hurry!
Hyouka's over there,
and she needs me.
Who's Hyouka?
[footsteps]
[INDEX] No, you can't, Toma!
Don't kill Hyouka, please!
Huh?
[KAMIJO] Index? Misaka?
[car doors close]
[KAMIJO] This way!
[MIKOTO] Huh?
[INDEX] Please just
listen to me!
Don't do what you were planning!
That angel is someone we know.
It's Hyouka. I'm sure of it!
Wait, so you're saying
that's Kazakiri?
I know it sounds crazy,
and I don't understand
how they're making it work.
Just tell me you won't
go over there, okay?
If you touch her,
she's gonna disappear.
You know she will!
[INDEX] I'll figure
something out. I promise.
Let me handle this.
You stay out of it, okay?
[KAMIJO] I can't, Index.
I have to stop her,
and you know it.
Besides, there's more
going on than just that.
[INDEX] But weren't you
listening to me at all, Toma?
If you do this, she'll die.
I won't let that happen!
I'm going in
there to save her.
How could you even think for a
second that I would kill her?
[KAMIJO] Is that what
Kazakiri normally looks like?
You know full well it isn't!
Which means she's in
some kind of trouble.
So let's go.
You and me, Index.
Whatever's going on
with Kazakiri right now,
I think I'm going
to need your help.
Mm.
[MIKOTO sighs]
I don't exactly know
what all this is about,
but it seems pretty obvious
to me that, once again,
you've managed to get
yourself into trouble.
[MIKOTO] So, I take it there's
an acquaintance of yours
at the center of that thing?
She isn't an acquaintance.
She's a good friend.
Okay, then just
so we're clear.
This Hyouka girl
isn't evil, is she?
Of course not. Like Index
said, she's a friend.
We'll do anything we can
in order to save her.
[MIKOTO] Your friend. Got it.
Alright, then I take it those
men there are the bad guys.
Yeah. Okay.
Just give me a minute.
I'll see what I can do.
Hey, wait--!
I don't think so.
[MIKOTO] This'll be easier
if you don't try to stop me!
[HOUND DOG C groans]
What was that?
Watch out!
They're armed!
[MIKOTO]
Don't forget our bet, now.
The penalty game's in effect
for the rest of the day,
so your next task is to
go rescue your friends
and then come back here.
You understand?
Yeah, I understand.
Try not to wreck the entire
city while we're gone.
All of a sudden, I'm in
an extremely foul mood.
[INDEX] You're pretty quiet.
What's going through your head?
Is it that magician from
the Right Seat of God
you fought before?
Yeah, it is. I want to
know how she knocked
all those people unconscious.
[KAMIJO] And if there's
anyway to reverse the effects.
Well, my guess, is it's
Divine Retribution.
[KAMIJO] What does that mean?
[INDEX] Its potency comes from
one very strong emotion.
The person who feels it can
take out multiple targets,
regardless of location or
range. It's very powerful.
When you fought her, did
you get any indication of
what she might
have been feeling?
Did she seem to be projecting
one particular emotion
to the exclusion
of all others?
Let me think.
A particular emotion.
[KAMIJO] Disgust. No,
hostility, or animosity.
You mean that's it?
So then her anger is
the key to making
her magic function?
[INDEX] Yeah. As for
the people who have been
knocked unconscious,
I don't think they'll be able
to recover until the magician
decides that Divine Retribution
is no longer needed.
And what about the way
Kazakiri's angel works?
Do you think that she's gonna
make it through this okay?
I really can't be sure.
Some of the magic does feel
familiar to me. But then
she's also doing some stuff
that I've never seen before.
I don't know what to
make of it. I feel lost.
There is one thing, though.
I don't know how much
it really tells us,
but the angel over there
and the core
that's directing it
[INDEX] are in two
different places altogether.
It tells us she's still on
our side, and that's enough.
[phone rings]
[INDEX] What's going on now?
Who are you calling?
[KAMIJO] Damn! No answer.
Is there anybody
besides Miss Komoe
who would understand this?
[phone rings]
Hey, Misaka?
[MIKOTO] Uh--Kinda busy here!
I think I may have an idea
about how to stop the angel.
I'm probably gonna need
your help with it, though.
[gunfire over phone]
Hey, what's going
on over there?
You didn't get shot, did you?
[MIKOTO] Not yet. You know,
talking on the phone while
I'm fighting doesn't
work so well.
Do you think we could chat
about this another time?
[KAMIJO] No. All right, Index.
If there's anything you don't
understand, then just ask her.
Huh?
[AMATA] Ha-ha!
Awesome light show.
I wonder what the hell it is.
Damn that Aleister.
What is he thinking?
I always knew he was
insane, but seriously.
Where does he get off
calling himself a scientist
when his methods are
so very unscientific?
You guys know what I'm saying?
[AMATA] He's messing with
things outside his scope!
Hmm?
[HOUND DOG B grunts]
Heh, heh, heh.
I found you, Kihara!
[HOUND DOG D grunts]
Whoopsie. That aim
could use some work.
If you're going to kill me,
[AMATA] you'll have to
try a lot harder than that.
[ACCELERATOR grunts]
[HOUND DOG F] Uh!
[HOUND DOG G] Don't move!
[ACCELERATOR grunts]
[HOUND DOG G whimpers]
[HOUND DOG G yells]
Well, bravo!
I think I just fell in love
a little bit, Accelerator!
Okay, enough. I'm done
screwing around now.
Die, you dirty son of a bitch!
[KAMIJO] Kazakiri.
Kazakiri!
I'm coming!
I'll help y--[grunts]
[KAMIJO] Damn it!
[VENTO] Well, well,
look at this.
Two despicable sinners
together in one place.
I guess like really
calls to like.
I was planning to save
you for some other time,
yet here you are again.
Just couldn't stand waiting
any longer, could you?
[VENTO laughs]
I get it. You figure if
you're the next one to die,
you won't have to bear witness
to more sorrow and misery.
I won't let you hurt Kazakiri!
[VENTO] Then I'm afraid
we're at an impasse.
Because as a member of
the Right Seat of God,
I cannot turn a blind eye
to that monstrosity.
That thing is
blasphemy personified;
sacrilege on two legs!
Its very existence
is an affront
[VENTO] to all loyal
followers of the cross!
Shut up! That's enough!
[VENTO] Oh, calm down. I'll
show some mercy and kill you.
You and that fallen angel
you care so much about.
[KAMIJO] You won't touch
a hair on her head!
She's been through
enough already.
I won't let her fall into
the hands of someone
who thinks she's a monster!
You want to come after her,
you'll have to get through me.
[KAMIJO] Do you understand?
For the last time, stay
the hell away from my friend!
[KAMIJO] The fight for the city
intensifies on every front.
Will Index be able to find
an answer in the chaos
created by magic and science?
Next time, "The Divine
Retribution Spell."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.