[TOYA] Oh... You're her mother?
I'm sorry. I thought
I heard you say
something about college earlier.
[MISUZU] That's right.
I've decided to go
back to school again.
I find it very
stimulating so far.
[TOYA] So, uh, Toma,
what do you think?
[KAMIJO] What do you mean...?
What do I think about what?
[SHINA] Hmm?
Obviously, something's
not right...!
Toma seems to be surrounded
by unnaturally young adults.
Doesn't it feel kinda creepy
and out of the ordinary
to anyone else?
Why don't we table that for
now and concentrate on eating?
I brought a little
something with me.
You know how mothers are!
Ta-da!
On today's menu, my
special cheese fondue.
You shouldn't be sneaking
hazardous materials
into the city!
But... dear... If you
don't eat enough food,
you'll never get
the proper nourishment
to the places that you need...
...developing,
if you know what I mean!
[MIKOTO] Uh--
What, exactly,
needs "developing"?
Oh, I don't know...
Whatever could I
be talking about?
Oh my goodness!
Are we at it again?
Surely not!
[TOYA] Huh? "At" what?
So, eating a lot
helps you develop, huh?
[INDEX] Hmm...
Toma!
Oh crap!
Geez, Toma!
[KAMIJO]
I may hate being bitten,
but this is a completely
unique kind of pain.
♪ [Opening Song] ♪
[ORIANA] Here.
[BOY] Wow, thanks!
Bye!
[ORIANA chuckles]
[LIDVIA] I thought I told you.
Avoid contact with private
citizens as much as possible.
Those were your instructions.
[ORIANA sighs]
And I maintain that I am.
As much as possible...
How are things on your end?
No one has found
you yet, right?
[LIDVIA] No, of course not.
I am sitting still...
inconspicuously.
[ORIANA] Sounds comfortable.
I'd like to be taking
it easy right now...
Maybe having a little
hotel workout.
I've asked you to refrain from
such indecent conversation.
[ORIANA] No, no... You're the
one who read into that... Oooh!
Lidvia's got such
a dirty, dirty mind!
I'll admit, though...
I am glad not to
be in your shoes.
Waiting around isn't everything
it's cracked up to be.
Toma, let's go
to that one...!
I wanna try the juice
they're selling.
It sounds really refreshing,
don't you think?
[KAMIJO] Are you kidding?
We just got finished
eating a really big lunch.
If you don't start regulating
your consumption,
you're gonna get fat.
[INDEX] Hey...! No, I will not!
Are you so sure? How
much do you want to bet
you've upped your armor class
and you just haven't
quite realized it yet?
Okay, fine. If you don't believe
that I haven't gained weight,
you are more than welcome
to measure my tummy!
Right, because I always walk
around with a measuring tape.
Then improvise,
why don't ya?
What?
[KUROKO] Sissy, wait up!
I'm coming, Sissy!
Stepping aside at the
last moment like that
wasn't very nice.
Sorry, it was just a
reflex. I'm in a hurry.
What exactly are you in
such a hurry to do, Sissy?
[gasps]
Please don't tell me
you are on your way to
cheerlead for that
troglodyte you've been
keeping company with recently!
Cheerleading?
Of course not...!
I forgot to tell my mom about
a change in the program.
That's all, really!
Are you sure
that's the truth...?
Quite a coincidence, isn't it,
considering he's
right over there.
[MIKOTO] Uh?!
[laughs]
So do you suppose
they're expecting...?
Perhaps he's trying to listen
for the baby's
heartbeat even now.
How dare he!
[running footsteps]
You creep! I hope you die!
[KAMIJO] Ahhh!
What's this?
[KAMIJO] Damn my luck!
[SHERRY] Stop that, Orsola...!
I told you, you can't eat
muffins inside the library!
[ORSOLA] But these
were a gift...!
The Amakusa made them for me...
Isn't that sweet?
[SHERRY] Not when you're getting
crumbs everywhere, it isn't!
You two realize the gravity
of our current situation
[STIYL] and the
need to move swiftly.
[SHERRY] Yes, of course we do!
There is no need to worry.
I am, after all,
a cryptology specialist.
Sifting through large
amounts of data
is all in a
day's work for me.
I can be of assistance in
this matter, too, Sherry.
I am rather adept
at decoding, as well.
Anyhow, we'll get to
the report data later--
[SHERRY] I told you to stop!
You're getting
crumbs everywhere!
Dingbats...! When did
Necessarius become a safe haven
for the erratic and
the emotionally unstable?
No you don't!
I'll have you know, the
walkways of Academy City
are non-smoking
areas at all times!
[KOMOE] You're endangering
others as well as yourself!
Haven't you heard of
"secondhand smoke"?
[STIYL] Pretty sure
everyone has by now.
[KOMOE] Ah!
In that case, how can you
light another cigarette
like you don't
know any better?
[KOMOE] Hey! Look at me!
Are you even listening?
Please! This is
a serious subject!
What's got her upset?
Whew! I got away!
It's a miracle.
[HIMEGAMI] There you are.
I'm glad I found you.
[KAMIJO]
What's up, Himegami?
[HIMEGAMI] We've got a bit
of a problem to deal with...
Come on.
[KAMIJO] Oh... Okay...
[KAMIJO] So... We, uh...
[HIMEGAMI] What?
Is something wrong?
[KAMIJO] Er, well...
It's just that it's kinda...
Never mind. It's no
big deal, really.
[KOMOE] Please cooperate!
Come on! I need to
confiscate those!
Please hand them over!
There's no need to make
trouble, is there?
Nah, I wouldn't worry
too much about that.
Are you sure?
[phone rings]
Yeah, hello?
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
This is it, Kami...
Oriana's on the move.
I saw her myself...
About three minutes ago...
She was at Seibusan station...
the one in School District 5.
Stiyl there?
No... but he's close by.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Good... Go get
him and come to the station.
[KAMIJO] I'm on it.
Come back here!
[KOMOE] Our conversation
is not over, you hooligan!
Himegami, think you
can take it from here?
[HIMEGAMI] Gotcha.
[KOMOE] What do you
think you're doing?!
Put me down this
instant, Himegami!
[STATION MAN 11A] Got that?
We need to avoid all
unnecessary hold ups.
What are you doing? Hurry up!
[horn blows]
[KAMIJO] Two more stops.
Whatcha looking at?
Some material from the
British Library regarding
the history of
the Croce di Pietro.
[KAMIJO] Read anything
interesting so far?
[STIYL] It would take too long
to read it all to you...
I'll just send the
data to your phone.
That'll be easier.
[KAMIJO] 'Kay... Sounds good.
[KAMIJO] How am I
supposed to read this?!
Uh... Stiyl...
[STIYL] Why aren't you here?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Sorry, on my way.
The bus I'm taking got
stuck in some bad traffic.
[STIYL] How far away are you?
I think I could run
there in ten minutes.
We can't wait that long.
She could escape
the search perimeter
by the time he gets here!
I realize that.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Stiyl... if I
send instructions on drawing
a Four Ways to Truth pattern,
could you do it?
There's no way...
I don't know anything about
those eastern spells
you people do.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Well... can you
do a search with a western one?
If I could, then I
wouldn't need you...?
It's not my area of expertise.
All right, fine...
Then I'll have to invoke
a Four Ways to
Truth array here...
When I'm done I'll send
the results to your phone
and you guys can
take it from there.
[KAMIJO] Hold on a sec!
Are you sure that your
body will be able to
handle it if
you use more magic?
[STIYL] Well? The kid
raises a good question.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Heh.
I'm a magician...
A practitioner is only as
good as the magic he uses.
♪
[ORIANA] Whoa...
You really want to know
where I am that badly, huh?
Well, I guess it's my turn.
I wonder what my
next move should be.
[KOMOE] What is it, Himegami?
You're awfully quiet...
Is there something
bothering you?
[HIMEGAMI] Oh, no...
I'm fine, really.
I was just thinking
about Kamijo.
He was acting strangely
when I saw him before.
Hmm. It's probably the
festival that's getting to him.
There's a lot of pressure
to do well, you know.
I'm not sure. I can't
put my finger on it.
He seemed like he was
worried about something.
[HIMEGAMI] I've seen it before.
It's hard to explain,
but I don't think he'd get
that way over a festival event.
It's sweet of you to worry.
I had no idea you were
even interested in Kamijo.
[HIMEGAMI] I think
I would prefer it
if you didn't phrase
it like that...
He and I aren't all that close.
We don't know each
other very well.
If there was some
misunderstanding about
how I feel toward him,
he might get freaked out.
Here, have a look at this...
Go on, what does it say?
[HIMEGAMI] It's about
the night parade.
The usually dark evening
skies of Academy City
will be illuminated by the glow
of fireworks and laser beams.
It's surely going to be
an evening to remember!
What if you were
to ask Kamijo if
he wants to go see it with you?
[HIMEGAMI] I couldn't.
An invitation out
of the blue like that
would seem weird to him.
More than anything, I think he
would be completely confused...
It just isn't his style.
No... I think you should
really give him a chance...
It wouldn't bother him
in the slightest to be
invited to an event that
you're exited about.
I bet he would be
delighted to go.
[KOMOE] That's just
the kind of guy he is.
[HIMEGAMI] I said I won't
invite him, and I stand by that.
I don't see why you're being so
obstinate about this, Himegami!
[HIMEGAMI] I'm not inviting him.
Drop it already.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] She's on to us.
She just changed directions...
Now she's headed northwest.
Well, can't you use that Red
Spell of yours or something?
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Nope, sure can't.
I'd have to interrupt the
Four Ways of Truth spell
to put that one in action.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] If I do then
I can't track Oriana anymore.
Right now she's still
heading northwest...
I don't know why...
but it appears that she's
moving in a straight line.
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
You'll have to hurry...
She'll be out of
effective range soon.
I'm well aware of that.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Hold on...!
She changed direction again!
And it looks like
she's speeding up, too.
Tsuchimikado!
He's in big trouble.
What makes you say that?
There's no way Oriana
would know how far
she'd have to go to escape
the Four Ways to Truth spell.
So, what would she do?
What's the next best plan?
You don't mean...
I do... She'd head for the
person at the exact center
of the spell
and take him out.
C'mon then,
we need to hurry.
Where to?
[KAMIJO] To wherever
Tsuchimikado is!
Fantastic idea. So
tell me, where is that?
Right. We don't know...
We have no clue
where Tsuchimikado is.
[ORIANA] How disappointing.
Can't you do any better?
When you use your little spell
to sense where my location is,
it means that I can
sense where you are, too.
You're the most
resourceful and dangerous
of the people chasing me, so
I came here to put you down.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Tch.
I'm Fallere 825...
You should probably
remember that.
It's my magic name.
Yeah...? My magic
name is Basis 104...
And now that I've said it,
I'm even more motivated
to win this fight.
[grunts]
♪
[ORIANA] I'm not gonna lie,
the whole "rough and
tumble bad boy" thing
you've got going on
is kind of doing it for me.
You've got an unusual
way of fighting.
Is it part of your style to use
your magic as little
as possible?
Because if you keep that up...
you're not gonna live long.
When I decided to pay you
a visit, I thought it would
be prudent to raise
a barrier around us...
You don't have help
coming anytime soon.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] You fools have
grown complacent in peacetime.
Better wake up
if you wanna live.
Sorry. Too late.
[ORIANA] Well, that
takes care of that.
Hm? Impossible! The barrier
has been disrupted?
What's wrong?
You surprised the
"rough and tumble bad boy"
brought down your barrier?
[ORIANA] I guess I
spoke to soon, huh?
You can handle a lot more than
your appearance would suggest.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] I have to make
sure word of what's happened
here reaches a wider audience.
Hmph... Silly boy, if those
two friends of yours show up,
I can easily deal with them.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] They're not
the ones I'm talking about.
What are you getting at?
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Are you that dense...?
Do you think there
aren't other members
of Necessarius I can
call upon for help?
[ORIANA laughs]
Do you honestly expect me to
believe such an idle threat?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Heh, heh...
Tsukebumi Tamazusa--
usually an accessory
spell designed to
make its target see illusions...
But, depending on
how it's used...
[ORIANA]
A communications spell?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Now that we know
you don't have the Stab Sword,
there's no reason
for us to have such
a powerful weapon
sitting out of the game.
Yes--I mean Kaori Kanzaki!
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Did you stop
to consider the possibility
there would be
a saint nearby...?
As it happens, Kanzaki has some
personal friends
here in Academy City.
However strong you might be,
I seriously doubt
she's someone you'd
want to piss off.
Give up already!
I destroyed the search spell,
which was my primary objective
in tracking you down.
[ORIANA] It would be foolish
to linger any longer
just to trade blows with
a pathetic teenage boy.
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Damn,
that was close.
I would have liked to see
Kanzaki take her down...
Of course, that show down was
never going to happen today...
Not with this.
Not with a fake
Tsukebumi Tamazusa.
I can't believe
she fell for it,
but I'm sure glad she did...
Well, time to get moving.
So much for that...
and another search
spell won't work...
Time to make a phone call.
[phone rings]
Tsuchimikado?
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
So, here's the deal.
Thanks to a little bluff I made,
Oriana should be
trying to get out of here
as quickly as possible.
[phone beeps]
The closest thing to
your location is the subway.
She could be headed there.
Looks like I've lost my shadows.
The time for the Croce
di Pietro preparations
is still a ways off.
However shall I amuse myself?
[ORIANA] Coming up with some
spells to use against a saint
could be an interesting
way to pass the time.
Hurry! We'll have
to take a short cut
if we want to be in time---
[HIMEGAMI] Ah! You should really
watch where you're walking.
I am a complete mess now!
I am, so sorry!
I didn't mean to!
Oh...! And what about you?
Are you all right, miss?
[ORIANA] Uh... Yes.
Don't worry, I'm just fine.
I think your friend's definitely
worse off than I am right now.
Ah! She's not kidding!
You're soaking wet!
I can see right through
your shirt, Himegami,
[HIMEGAMI] Yes, and
I would appreciate it
if you'd please stop looking.
[ORIANA gasps]
[ORIANA] A Celtic cross...!
Necessarius?!
[KOMOE] Is it that bad?
Are you okay...?
You're really shivering!
[screaming]
[KAMIJO] The closest transfer
point to us is...
Looks like it's a bus stop
about three hundred
meters north of here.
Three hundred, huh?
[crowd murmurs]
What is that smell?
Hey... What's going on?!
Oh... It's awful.
Miss Komoe,
What's the problem?
[KAMIJO] Himegami, no...!
What happened to her?!
[KOMOE] We were walking,
and we bumped into this woman...
First she was nice...
Then she made this scary face,
and the next thing I know--
poor Himegami!
It was Oriana.
Why would she
do this...?
What's the point of
attacking Himegami?
Do you see that?
The "Walking Church" she
wears around her neck...
it's a very special item.
Oriana must've taken
it to mean she was
a member of Necessarius
and concluded that
Himegami was chasing her.
It was a mistake?
She did all this to Himegami...
and you're telling me it was
because of some
misunderstanding?!
T-P-I-M-I-M-S-P-F-T.
[STIYL] An ambulance
has been called, yes?
You should wait for them at
the entrance to the path...
They won't be able
to see you here.
Hold on!
What is it?
She got caught up in this
and injured because of us!
And we're just supposed
to leave her here?!
[STIYL] What do you think
you can do for her?
Exactly how
arrogant are you?
[STIYL] She's severely injured.
There's not a damn
thing you can do!
There's one way we
can be useful now...
That's by going
after Oriana.
[STIYL] If you really
want to help people,
learn to accept
your limitations...
Your right hand has the
power to destroy illusions.
But as far as I know,
it doesn't have the power
to make people whole again.
[KAMIJO] Ugh!
This is so screwed up!
You can rage all you
want, but don't think
you're the only
one who's angry.
What are you doing
with those things?
I'm not sure, exactly,
but it seemed...
to help the
sister... before.
Wait a minute...
you don't mean...
[KOMOE] I don't get it.
Why isn't she getting better?
Shouldn't it be helping by now?
I can't believe this.
A few minutes ago,
we were talking about
the night parade...
and now she's...
[STIYL] That won't work.
You've got it wrong.
Think of it as trying to
carry water in a bucket...
You're not going
to get very far if
the bucket you're using
has holes in it, right?
[STIYL] Listen up, Kamijo...
I want you to go after Oriana.
You mean that...
you're gonna try to...?
Don't expect
any miracles...
This isn't my area
of expertise, either.
We're going to use the
knowledge your teacher gained
from her time with the
List of Prohibited Books
[STIYL] to do what we can.
But if you want this whole
situation to be resolved
once and for all, you need to
leave us behind and stop Oriana.
All right. I'll go.
Stiyl... you take care of her!
[STIYL] Hm.
I'm sorry, Himegami...
I promise I'll try to come
visit you before the
night parade begins.
So you'd better hang
in there for me, okay?
♪ [Ending Song] ♪
[KAMIJO] Finally,
I've learned the secret
of the Croce di Pietro...
Oriana must be in the spot
where the cross will be used...
But... where exactly is that?
Next time, "Belvedere."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.