[ACCELERATOR] I'm down to
sixty seconds of control time.
But as long as I kill
this guy, it'll all be over.
Redemption is always going
to be out of my reach.
And if I'm going to
be stuck in darkness
then I might as well take
this guy to hell with me!
[laughs]
[grunts]
[AMATA] Why are
you even fighting?
Haven't you figured it out yet?
You'll never get the best of me!
Having an off day, huh?
Aren't you motivated?
I thought you came
to save the girl.
Go to hell.
Do I have it wrong?
Maybe you came 'cause
fighting me will make you
seem like the hero
you're never gonna be.
[AMATA] Here you are, standing
in the face of a powerful evil
dashing in to rescue a helpless
girl from an uncertain fate.
Do you really think that's
going to make up for all
the horrible things you've done
during your miserable life?
[AMATA laughs]
You'll never be more
than what you are now.
[ACCELERATOR] Shut up, damn you.
I already know that.
I know there are some
debts I can never repay.
A hero's trophy isn't
what I came here for.
You and I are
going to hell.
There's no question about that.
But don't even
think about dragging
the kid down with us!
You dirty, twisted bastard!
[beep]
[ACCELERATOR] Uh.
[laughs]
Ha!
[KAMIJO grunts]
Ah!
[coughing]
I have to say, you're really
starting to annoy me.
[VENTO] Swinging around
that right hand of yours.
Protecting that despicable
thing over there.
How much longer do we
have to play this game
before you admit defeat?
I'm really sick of
listening to you.
[KAMIJO] So set in your
beliefs, you think anyone who
doesn't agree with you is wrong.
Why can't you accept that
there are people out there
who may see the world
differently than you do?
[VENTO] Science is something
I'll never accept!
I detest science!
[KAMIJO yells]
[VENTO] Science and scientists
have never brought me
anything but grief.
[KAMIJO grunts]
Science is the reason that
my brother isn't here anymore.
Science let him die!
[KAMIJO grunts]
[KAMIJO] Oh no!
Hey!
Kazakiri!
This is the kind of
mess scientists make,
and you're proud of
being on their side?
How can you not find
everything they do disgusting?
[AMATA] Ha! When your battery
dies, you're useless,
just a broken toy that can't
move on its own anymore.
[thud]
Huh?
[wheezes]
[distorted]
It's almost hard to believe.
You managed to fight off
quite a few of my guys earlier
[AMATA distrorted] and yet here
you are seemingly helpless.
[gasps]
[KAMIJO] How could you?
[VENTO laughs]
Hm?
What's going... on?
[grunts]
[KAMIJO] Kazakiri...
Damn. You little hypocrite!
What are you trying to pull?
[laughs]
I can't help but laugh.
Just about every day
I'm alive, I curse my luck.
But compare it to
something like this,
and I'm pretty
damn lucky. Right?
Uh, you lost me there.
What are you even
talking about, freak?
Hang in there, okay?
You'll be fine. I promise.
Index is gonna figure out
a way to put a stop to this.
[KAMIJO] You know
you can count on her.
Because she's your friend.
She's going to come
through for you.
So just hold on.
In the meantime, I'm here.
You'll be safe with me.
[KAMIJO] I won't
let her hurt you!
[ACCELERATOR wheezes]
Tch. Enough! This ends now!
Say goodbye, you gimpy bastard!
[AMATA] Aw, damn!
[AMATA screams]
[chuckles]
[AMATA] Ahhh! You've
lost it! You're crazy!
[chuckles]
[AMATA grunts]
[wheezes]
[grunts]
Stay the hell
away from me! Uh!
[ACCELERATOR laughs]
[AMATA] Damn it! Let me go!
[AMATA] Crap! I forgot.
If he can't use his ability,
I'm screwed too.
My countermeasure won't
work against him anymore.
Damn it. He's willing to fight
to the death at this point,
but maybe if I can rob
that death of meaning.
And how the hell am
I supposed to do that?
[AMATA chuckles]
[chuckles]
Take a look. It's the
original script of the virus
[AMATA] that was input
into the girl's brain.
You need this.
Without it, there's no way
you'll be able to save her.
[grunts]
[laughs]
[AMATA] And now it's
gone! I destroyed it!
She's as good as dead!
With one squeeze of my hand,
I took away the only thing
in the world that
mattered to you.
You hear that? It's over now!
[AMATA] No reason for you
to bother fighting anymore!
Oh, yeah. This is gonna
be the end for you.
[AMATA] You might want to start
preparing your last words.
Or praying that you'll somehow
avoid ending up in hell.
[chuckles]
Huh?
[footsteps]
Whew!
[INDEX] There she is!
[yells]
[VENTO] Uhhh!
[KAMIJO] I've got it! When I
moved to grab the hammer
with my right hand,
she made sure I missed.
Which means, I can cancel
the thing out. Alright.
I guess fighting you
up close and personal
isn't gonna gain
me any advantage.
It's kinda nice having
an angel on my side.
It makes a guy feel
pretty invincible.
[VENTO] Ha! The way you're
going on, you almost make it
sound like that
monster is helping you!
[KAMIJO] It's more than that.
Kazakiri is really helping me!
[VENTO] Yeah, right!
Pathetic! Is that
the best you can do?
[VENTO] I am with the Right Seat
of God! Do not underestimate me!
[VENTO yells]
[gasps]
I can't see!
[grunts]
[VENTO coughs]
[groans]
Vento!
Heh, heh. Why waste your
energy pretending to be
concerned about me?
You've made it clear your
[VENTO] allegiance is
to the side of science.
Something else happened with
the appearance of the angel.
An anti-magic defense
was activated
in this entire
region of the city.
[VENTO] Quite effective.
It's causing what you might call
a magic circulatory failure.
That Aleister has some dirty
tricks up his sleeve, all right.
[KAMIJO] So just give up!
Why do you keep fighting
if it's only going to kill you?
[VENTO] You obviously
don't understand
anything, science boy!
[KAMIJO] Crap.
I couldn't dodge that.
[clang]
[VENTO pained breathing]
[KAMIJO] Ha! It looks
like you're the one
who needs to be rescued.
Sorry, I'm actually a
little busy right now.
But I'll make sure someone comes
to take you to the hospital.
Don't you dare!
I have no desire to be
in the hands of
science ever again.
[VENTO] I've detested
science ever since
it killed my younger brother!
Huh?
[VENTO] It happened one day when
we were at an amusement park.
There was a glitch in
one of the attractions.
Riding it had no risks.
It was scientifically
proven to be sound.
It had multiple layers
of safeguards and
a fully-automated
speed control program.
We were scared, but
they made it sound like
the safest ride in the world.
Well, they were wrong!
[VENTO] They didn't
know anything!
Wait, you mean...?
[VENTO] At the hospital, it was
just one screw up after another.
They only had enough blood
to do one transfusion.
Which meant there
would be no way
for the doctors to save us both.
And do you know what
my little brother did?
He told the doctor,
"Please save my sister."
There you have it. That's
why I'm here and he's gone.
You look so surprised.
You don't think a member of
the Right Seat of God
should be fighting
for a reason like revenge?
[VENTO] Don't you see?
That's how much I hate science.
I'm willing to do
anything to bring
its practitioners
to their knees.
Science not only
blinds its followers
to that which is right,
it also tries to coerce the
faithful into doing wrong.
It takes what is pure and
overwrites it with blasphemy.
[VENTO] Don't you get it? That
is the very essence of science!
It defiles all it touches!
And that is why I'll fight
against it even with
my dying breath!
Your science is soulless.
Devoid of all spirituality.
Those who I fight beside
seek to replace it with
laws that can warm the
heart and bolster faith.
That's my duty! I owe
it to the world for
[VENTO] having ended
my brother's future!
[KAMIJO]
You've got to be kidding.
What?
[KAMIJO] It wasn't science
that killed your brother.
You can't actually
believe that the doctors
in the hospital
wanted him to die.
If there had been any
possibility of saving
both of you, they would have.
[KAMIJO] And the park attraction
where you guys got hurt?
It's not like their goal
was to harm children.
Exactly the opposite, in fact.
Shut the hell up!
[KAMIJO] Your brother
knew the situation, right?
The doctors explained
that one of you would die.
But he deliberately chose to
sacrifice himself and save you.
Think about him for a second.
Would somebody like that
want you wasting your life
trying to get
revenge on science?
[KAMIJO] My guess is,
more than anything,
he'd want you to be happy!
I told you once
already, shut up!
Why'd they let him
throw his life away?
They were adults, and he was
a child on the verge of death!
If there was only
enough blood for one,
they should have given
it to him, instead.
As far as I'm concerned,
they could have used
[VENTO] my blood as
well if they needed to!
His life wasn't wasted.
[gasps]
[KAMIJO] He had the facts,
and he made a decision.
And it's because of that
decision that you're alive now.
You think that
doesn't have value?
I think you understand
the real value more than
anyone else ever could.
You know nothing! What do
your reassurances mean to me?
He was my brother and
I stole his future!
If somebody else was
in your situation,
would you tell them
the same thing?
Ah!
[KAMIJO]
You wouldn't, would you?
So stop saying it to yourself.
The life you're leading
is both pointless and wrong.
[KAMIJO] Your brother
made a choice.
His decision was incredibly
selfless and courageous.
Do you really want
to disgrace that?
Are you gonna spend the
precious time he's given you
being consumed by your anger
and hatred toward science?
Ha! Don't waste your breath.
I chose my path a long time ago.
And what are you?
A faithless idiot who
knows nothing about me.
You can twist my words
however you want,
it won't change what I must do.
[KAMIJO grunts]
[VENTO yells]
[KAMIJO yells]
[VENTO grunts]
[retches]
[KAMIJO] The crisis
that both Academy City
and Kazakiri are facing now.
The hatred for science
that holds Vento hostage.
These are illusions and
I am going to destroy them!
[KAMIJO] Are you ready, Vento?
Compared to the sacrifice
your brother made,
this is nothing, but at least
it should help you a little.
This is your chance
to start over.
So don't waste it like an idiot!
[VENTO groans]
Uh!
[KAMIJO panting]
Huh?
[INDEX] Those men from before.
Do they have something
to do with her, I wonder?
Huh?
[ACCELERATOR groans]
[AMATA] Hey!
Come on. What do you want?
I'm a little busy here.
[ACCELERATOR growls]
[AMATA] What are you doing?!
She's in my care!
Leave her alone!
[INDEX] This girl is at
the core of everything.
Based on angel architecture,
but made of formless telesma,
all tucked neatly away
inside a human-shaped pouch.
I know that much.
What I don't know is
what to do from here.
Hello? Short-hair?
A question.
[MIKOTO] Call me
Mikoto, you brat!
Well? Whaduya want?
What's your question?
What can you tell me about
an electronic network
that utilizes brainwaves?
Huh? Let me think. I guess
there is a possibility that
electricity-generating espers
could use identical brainwaves
[MIKOTO] to construct
an EM network of sorts.
Okay. Then let me ask
you about something else.
There's an AIM diffusion field
spread out over Academy City.
[MIKOTO] Yeah,
that's no big deal.
It's the power field naturally
generated by the city's espers.
[HOUND DOGS yell]
[INDEX] If I understand
what she's saying,
there's a special power
that fills the city,
and it's this girl who
acts as the administrator.
By restricting her mind,
they're just twisting that power
to create the "angel." In which
case, that should mean...
Yes, that's it!
All we have to do is find
a way to untie the "knot"
they've created
inside her head. Yes!
But, turning that
plan into a reality
will require a unique approach.
Like a song.
[INDEX] A song can
convey ideas more clearly
than simple words can.
Using rhythm and tone, it can
communicate on multiple levels.
[MIKOTO] Whoa, really? Something
that low-tech can actually
help us out of this mess?
Yes, absolutely. It'll
be a very strong prayer.
And if all goes well,
it should save everybody.
[INDEX] This young girl, my
friend Hyoka, the entire city!
[ACCELERATOR] Ugh!
Bastard!
Haven't you had enough?
Stop moving and die!
[laughing]
[ACCELERATOR wheezing]
[ACCELERATOR] Kihara...
Kihara!
Ha! This should be amusing.
[AMATA] You know,
I'm glad, actually.
If you were defeated so easily,
this wouldn't be nearly
as entertaining for me.
It's really nice
to see you being so
considerate for once,
Accelerator.
I've been hoping for the
opportunity to punish you
for a long time. I'll enjoy
teaching you a lesson
with my fists
before killing you!
[yells]
[AMATA] It takes more
than that to hurt me!
I'm having a good time,
how about you? Ha-ha!
What d'you say we shake things
up a bit, keep 'em interesting.
[AMATA] You're ready for
anything I throw at you, right?
[laughing]
Huh?
[AMATA] What's going on? You
shouldn't be this strong.
Why are there wings
growing out of your back?
[AMATA] You experimental freak!
Where is this sudden
strength coming from?
It seems that you've acquired
a new clearance. But how?
What value did you enter in
for your Personal Reality?
[AMATA] Wait!
This strange new power,
is it of the angel variety?
You monster. Do you even
realize what's behind you?
Kill, kill, kill, kill.
[AMATA grunts]
Kazakiri?
Hold on, I'm co--
I can't touch her.
So what am I supposed to do?
I don't want to hurt the real
her along with the illusion.
[distant explosion]
[grunts]
[KAMIJO] Who are you?
Excuse me.
Sorry to interrupt,
but I have business
with this girl.
[KAMIJO] I asked you
who you are!
[MAN] I am Acqua of the Rear.
Like Vento of the Front.
I am a member of
the Right Seat of God.
[ACQUA] Hmph. I won't
interfere with you further.
This is the only business
that I have to conduct here.
[KAMIJO] Let her go!
Hm. Unfortunately, I don't
see that as an option.
If I left her here to be
captured by the side of science,
she would no doubt be executed.
[ACQUA] You can have
that if you wish.
It's been thoroughly
destroyed by your right hand.
It is nothing but junk now.
Vento can no longer
use Divine Retribution.
The people she neutralized
should soon make
complete recoveries.
Do not worry. You can
rest easy, knowing that
you have protected Academy
City from further harm.
You expect me
to accept that?
You would be well served
to watch your tone.
[ACQUA] I think you
should know I am a saint.
Do not seek a fight with me.
It will only shorten your life.
Hey, get back here!
[explosion]
[KAMIJO] One battle
has come to an end.
But the footsteps of another
greater battle can be heard
closing in on the city.
Is war approaching?
Next time, "Prewar."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.