[KAMIJO] I went by myself to
save Orsola from Agnese
and the Roman Orthodox Church.
[KAMIJO] Or so I
thought, but then. Stiyl?
Tatemiya? Even Index?
[KAMIJO] In the end,
I had it wrong.
It turns out I wasn't the
only one willing to fight
in order to ensure a
better outcome for Orsola.
♪ [Opening Song] ♪
Sisters, we must attack.
Forget about defense.
[LUCIA] We must
do what is necessary
to defeat the
enemies of the Church.
[BOTH gasp]
[gasps]
They--? That's crazy!
[INDEX] They would go that far
just to avoid the Sheol Fear?
[STIYL] Damn!
[screams]
[distant scream]
So many.
Is there no
end to them?
[KAMIJO] This way!
Toma!
[KAMIJO] C'mon, hurry!
[KAMIJO] We're safe,
at least for the moment.
Do you think you
can walk alright, Orsola?
I take it you're
the worrying type, huh?
Yes, I should be just fine.
I'm not injured too severely.
Well, any bright ideas?
Mmm. With their
eardrums punctured like that,
I seriously doubt my Sheol Fear
will have any effect on them.
And as for Spell Intercept,
I can only use it
against one person at a time.
My people seem to be
holding their own so far,
but now this?
Those nuns have committed
to a suicide attack.
[TATEMIYA] Nothing is
harder to counter.
[ORSOLA] If only...
[ORSOLA] If only I had
"The Book of the Law" here,
things would be different.
I might even be able to find
us a way out of this mess.
Yes, you're right.
It could enable us
to open up negotiations.
All we'd have to do is
say the seal had been broken
on the Book's angel techniques.
Unfortunately,
that's a moot point.
We all know the
theft of the Book was just
a fiction being
circulated by the Church.
[TATEMIYA] It's not here,
and there's no way
we're gonna be able
to get our hands on it.
[BOTH] Ah! Hey!
If it's true what they say,
you know, that even you
can't decipher the Book.
[KAMIJO] That means, well,
they must have attempted to
have you read it at some
point, wouldn't you think?
And if that's the case, "The
Book of the Law"'s original
text must be stored intact
somewhere in your memory.
[INDEX] It's in there,
all right. Still untouched.
I had no way to
decipher it 'til--
[STIYL] That's unacceptable!
I won't allow it.
If she accesses that memory,
then she'll be stuck with it.
[STIYL] Which means even
more magicians will be
coming after her
than there already are.
Huh. It sounds like
you're worried about me.
[grunts]
You listen to me!
Yeah, I'm listening.
You had better protect her!
If this whole thing goes
sideways and she gets hurt.
I will burn you until
not even ashes remain
[STIYL]
for your family to bury!
[STIYL] Damn.
Okay. So how do you
decipher "The Book of the Law"?
Can you explain the process?
Oh, yes. I don't mind
disclosing my method
because I trust
all of you now.
[ORSOLA] Fortunately, we
shouldn't actually have to
make use of the power
contained within the book.
All we really need to do is
demonstrate our willingness
to use it if we should
deem it necessary.
It's based upon
Temurah, which is basically
a method of
letter substitution.
Except that, in this case,
there is an irregular rule
that has to do with
the number of lines.
[INDEX] This method
involves first placing the
twenty-two Hebrew
letters into two lines.
being sure to take note of
the line number above them.
Uh?
That's plenty, thanks. I
understand the situation now.
I'm sorry,
but what "situation"
do you mean, exactly?
This method
isn't the correct way
to decipher
"The Book of the Law."
It's actually a dummy
solution set up as a trap.
That's the truly frightening
thing about the Book.
There are more than a hundred
possible ways
of deciphering it.
[INDEX] The crazy part is
that every method results in
different sentences, all
of which are also dummy texts.
It's not that nobody can
read "The Book of the Law."
In fact, plenty of people
can, but the grimoire tricks
every reader into deciphering
its text in a different way.
[ORSOLA] Really?
[chuckles]
Man, if only we'd
known that sooner,
we could have saved
ourselves a lot of trouble.
Hey, you think if we
tell them that Orsola here
doesn't actually know
how to decode the Book,
they'll forget any
of this ever happened
and let us go in peace?
Probably not, no.
They've strayed too far into
darkness to turn back now.
They have to see this through.
[door breaking]
There must be a back door!
[gasps]
[distant fighting]
[door opens]
[heavy breathing]
[AGNESE chuckles]
There's no way you
could have defeated
all the troops I sent, and
they wouldn't have let you
get away unless
they were distracted,
so you must be playing
a deeper game here.
Actually, I've come
up with a new strategy.
Strategy? Oh, is
that what you call it?
And they actually believed you?
You come strutting in here
like you're some kind of hero
who's going to save
the day, but really,
your friends are
taking all the heat
while you go and
claim all the glory.
[AGNESE] Hm. Orsola made
you out to be so noble.
You should have heard
her going on and on
about the beauty of
belief and trust. Really!
[AGNESE laughs]
But we can be honest
with each other, can't we?
You didn't make it
this far because of some
grand notion of trust.
You're here because
you tricked your friends
into being your decoys.
[KAMIJO] You're wrong.
I do trust my friends.
I believe in them,
and in return, I have
asked them to believe in me.
To trust me to settle
my problems in my own way.
[AGNESE gasps]
You think that by eliminating
me as commander
you can end the whole battle.
[AGNESE] Well,
that's fine by me.
I was starting to get a little
bored doing nothing, anyway.
I'm happy to
keep myself occupied
by shattering your naïve
illusions once and for all.
[AGNESE] All things in harmony.
Fifth of the Five Elements
symbolizing peace and order.
Deploy this crosier.
In accordance with
the Church defend against
that which is
heathen and unclean.
Stand strong
against the heretic.
Lend me your power!
Ah!
[KAMIJO] A coordinated
attack? Teleportation maybe?
Transference!
I see you finally
figured out how it works.
When you do harm to this staff,
it in turn does
harm to something else.
Here. Why don't
I show you again?
[KAMIJO] Damn it!
How does that thing work?
Where are the
attacks coming from?
[KAMIJO] Aw, crap!
[groans]
[KAMIJO groaning]
[AGNESE grunts]
Ahhh!
Aaahhh!
Now do you see just
how ridiculous it was
to think that
you could defeat me?
[AGNESE] I only have to
anticipate your next move
and set up an attack.
You do the rest of the
work by walking right into it.
What they have
done is unforgivable.
[AGNESE] The church of the
cross's influence spread
because its original
purpose was to help people
who were in need.
To turn that ideal
around like this,
the use of force
for personal gain
is not the way of the Church.
I thought you said that using
force for a personal gain
was not the way of the Church.
[laughing]
You think my use of the staff
goes against the Church?
The bishop's crosier is
an adaptation of the mace,
a weapon once used in battle
to smash through
an opponent's armor.
What could be objectionable
about me using a tool
made for beating
people to beat you with?
Modern magic practitioners
rely on deception
as a means to an end when
necessary, just like the church
of the cross is forced
to do from time to time.
The difference is, when
we do it, it's justified.
From anybody else
it's unacceptable.
[AGNESE] Ultimately, dogma
outside of the Roman Orthodoxy
is no dogma at all!
[AGNESE] I'm getting tired
of you. It's time to end this.
Do us both a favor, okay?
[AGNESE] Quit whining
and just die already!
[KAMIJO grunts
There it is! The attack
I've been waiting for!
[grunts]
♪
[AGNESE] This can't happen.
I'm not helpless.
Not anymore. I'm strong now.
[AGNESE gasps] No!
I won't be helpless
again. Not ever, ever again.
It won't happen!
[chuckling]
Huh?
[AGNESE] You know,
I actually feel bad for you.
You really have tried so hard,
but it looks like
it's all over now.
[KAMIJO] It's gone
completely quiet outside.
I guess that
ingenious plan of yours
didn't work out so well, huh?
I'm sure they put up
a decent fight for you,
but in the end, your
decoy buddies let you down.
And just like that,
the fantasy crumbles
[AGNESE] into
tiny little pieces.
[KAMIJO] Yeah.
That's exactly right.
You've reached the
end of the line, Agnese.
[KAMIJO]
Your fantasy is over!
Huh?
[STIYL] This attack required
forty-three hundred cards.
They may not be a match for
you in terms of sheer numbers,
but still, the Amakusa
aren't the kind of people
you want to cross.
I mean, they suggested
using the placement of
rune cards to construct
an enormous figure.
Which, in turn, transformed
the entire church
into a giant magic array.
Whether you like
the guys or not,
you have to admit that
was pretty impressive.
Sneaky and very effective.
I just wish it was my idea.
[roaring]
Eh.
[KAMIJO] Like I told you.
We had a strategy.
These guys weren't
running around
being decoys for me.
They were surrounding the entire
premises with rune cards.
[AGNESE] Oh yeah? I don't
care how clever you are.
Have you forgotten
that we outnumber you?
If we all come at you at once,
you don't stand a chance.
What are you
morons hesitating for?
Attack them now! Uh!
[AGNESE]
Their faith. It's wavering.
Even though we could easily
beat them with one united push.
[gasps]
[ORSOLA] The ones who helped
me earlier, they act on
what they believe with
their innermost hearts.
Hm. Things are
starting to heat up, huh?
[AGNESE] What now?
What am I supposed to do?
Which attack? Which
approach? Which weapon?
[AGNESE] How do
I pick my next move?
Come on. Time to
give up, Agnese.
Even you must have
realized it by now.
[KAMIJO] Your self-confidence
is just an illusion!
Uh.
♪
[KAMIJO grunts]
[ANGESE] Ahhh! Uh!
[breathing heavy]
♪
[shaky breathing]
Oh no!
[INDEX] Toma! Can
you hear me? Wake up!
[car horns honking]
Oh you finally
decided to wake up.
That you, Kanzaki?
[KANZAKI] I had planned
on being gone by now, so...
[KAMIJO] "So" what?
You left me a note?
No. This is nothing.
Just forget about it.
I mean, since you're up now,
I can talk to you directly.
[KANZAKI] There's no
need for this anymore.
Call it an
after-action report.
I thought that you
might appreciate an update
on Orsola Aquinas' status.
Maybe I should have let
you keep resting, though.
Go on. I'm listening.
Orsola Aquinas.
Together with the Amakusa.
Did what was necessary
and affiliated themselves
with the English
Puritan Church.
[KANZAKI] This decision
seems to have been influenced
by a desire to avoid
Roman Orthodox retaliation.
[KAMIJO] So even after
everything we've done,
nothing's really changed?
Orsola's life
is still in danger?
It shouldn't be. The
English Puritans disclosed
the fact that Orsola
was using an incorrect
decryption method all along.
They figure if it's known
that her interpretation
was erroneous,
concern regarding her
and "The Book of the Law"
should fade quickly.
That accounts for her,
but you said the Amakusa
were affiliating with
the English Puritans, too?
Yes. It seems that a
segment of them has been
hoping such a development
would take place.
I gave them
strict instructions.
I told them not to follow me,
but I guess they didn't listen.
Oh, yeah. That's
right, you're with
the English Puritans now, too.
Those idiots.
[gasps]
[KANZAKI] So anyway,
I apologize for all of this.
Uh... but why?
Because this, um,
this was sort of
personal for me, you know?
And I got you involved
in the situation
without ever asking if
that's what you even wanted.
Heya, Kami!
How is the patient doing?
[TSUCHIMIKADO] I brought
you some pudding to snack on,
just in case
the hospital ran out.
Oh! Hello there, missy.
You came to offer
Kami your sincere
and abject apologies,
didn't you?
And I bet you're
being super cheesy,
"I owe you a greater
debt than I can pay."
Or "Ask anything of me!"
I'm right, huh?
That's what you're
about to do, isn't it?
[laughing]
[TSUCHIMIKADO]
Yeah! Like you don't know
what he's gonna ask for!
Ughhh! Don't be stupid!
Oh, come on now. There's no
need to play the coy ingénue.
Huh? I've never
been coy in my life!
And just what the
hell is an ingénue?
Whoa! Wait, so you
mean you were gonna
offer him your body
with no pretense at all?
I gotta say, that's
refreshingly direct.
[KANZAKI]
Shut up and get out. Now!
[breathing heavy]
[TSUCHIMIKADO] Okay, okay. I
don't want to be a third wheel.
You're not a third
wheel! Get back here!
[KAMIJO] Hey, sorry, but...
Uh. I sort of wanted to,
you know, double check.
All of that stuff
Tsuchimikado was talking about,
he was really just
messing with you, right?
About owing me a
great debt or something?
I do owe you.
After everything that's
happened, how could I not?
I always seem to ask
you to place so much
responsibility on
your own shoulders.
Even when the matter at hand
does not directly concern you.
[KANZAKI] I think we're way
past the point where a simple
"Thanks for your help" will
settle things between us.
Yeah? 'Cause, I don't
really see it that way.
[KAMIJO] We had a
problem and we solved it.
That's all that
matters, isn't it?
"We" had a problem?
Huh? That's right;
me and the Amakusa.
Oh, and the English
Puritans, too, I guess.
And of course we shouldn't
forget Orsola, Index, and Stiyl.
And you, obviously.
[KAMIJO] I think that's pretty
much who "we" are right now.
[KAMIJO] The division
between English Puritan
and Roman Orthodox
means a lot to you.
But for an outsider like me,
the differences
are hard to pick out.
[KAMIJO] I mean, to
be completely honest,
it's not like I'm really on the
side of the English Puritans.
It's a lot more
accurate to say
that I'm on Index's side,
which just so happens
to align me with
the Puritans for now.
Really. It's likely
that if Agnese
asked for my help,
I would give it to her.
She may have been
on the wrong side
of things this time around,
but there's no rule
saying she has to stay
on the wrong side, is there?
[KAMIJO] Everyone can change.
[STIYL] The Roman Orthodox
Church plans to wash its hands
of all responsibility for
this by declaring it the work
of a rogue militant faction
led by Agnese Sanctis.
[STIYL] They're maintaining that
it was never their intention
to assassinate
Orsola for her supposed
knowledge of
"The Book of the Law."
[LAURA] Well, at the very least,
they'll still receive some
criticism for failing to
keep their people in line.
[STIYL] Looking back, I think
you were fully aware of
the Roman Orthodoxy's
true intentions all along.
In which case, why didn't
you brief me about what was
really going on instead
of sending me into it blind?
That would have been nice.
[LAURA] I didn't
really know everything.
I had no idea that Orsola's
decryption method was incorrect.
But things worked out anyway,
regardless of what
you were briefed on.
[LAURA] Think about it, Stiyl.
If you and the others had
indeed failed to rescue
Orsola from Agnese's people,
would the outcome really
have been all that different?
If she had been taken
back to the Church,
she would have been executed.
Instead, she was saved and
her decryption proved faulty.
Regardless of the
outcome for Orsola,
"The Book of the Law" would
never have been deciphered.
[STIYL] If you truly didn't
care, why did you personally
request that the crucifix go
to Orsola? Say what you will,
but saving her was always
part of your plan, wasn't it?
[LAURA]
No! It certainly was not!
The nun doesn't concern me.
I only got involved
because it was
in the interest of the
English Puritan Church.
[STIYL] And that
interest would be?
[LAURA] Kaori Kanzaki.
[LAURA] Because Kanzaki
possesses tremendous power and
a well-developed
sense of justice,
she is the kind of person who
is likely to act on her own.
As a matter of fact,
she came very close
to crossing the line this time.
You received the
reports about what happened
to those poor fools in the
knight's order, did you not?
[STIYL] Yes.
[LAURA] So then, you
understand why we need
a means of controlling her.
And where Kanzaki is concerned,
a threat is more likely
to provoke her than to
ensure her good behavior.
Better by far that we offer
to take the Amakusa into
our protection in exchange
for her cooperation.
[LAURA] You see? It all
worked out according to plan.
[STIYL] She is
one sly little vixen.
♪ [Ending Song] ♪
[KAMIJO] A dangerous
artifact lies hidden in
the darkness of Academy City.
When Kuroko Shirai
comes into contact with it,
she will learn
a terrifying truth.
Next time, "Remnant."
When science and magic
cross paths, a story is born.