Okay, go ahead and introduce yourself.
U-Um...
M-my name is H-Homura Akemi.
And, uh...
I, uh...
It's really nice...
I mean, I'm pleased to meet you...
Miss Akemi was in the hospital for
a while due to a heart condition.
Since she's been away from school for so long,
she might need some help adjusting.
So, let's all help her out, okay?
So, what school did you go to before coming to this one?
Were you in any cool clubs?
How about sports?
Were you in a team?
Wow, your hair's like so super long!
That must take a lot of time to braid, huh?
I, uh...
um...
I don't...
I'm not...
Hmm...
Miss Akemi.
Uh?
Didn't you need to go the nurse's office right now?
Do you know where it is?
Huh?
Um, no...
I can take you there if you want.
I'm the Nurse's Aide for our classroom.
Sorry, guys.
But every break time,
Miss Akemi is supposed to go to the
nurse's office for her medicine.
Really?
Sorry about that.
We didn't mean to keep you.
Yeah, we can talk some more when you get back, okay?
Hah...
Don't mind them.
They're harmless, I swear.
They're all just excited because we don't
usually get many transfer students here.
Oh, um...
Thank you very much for that.
Hey, you don't have to be so nervous around me.
I mean, we're classmates now.
Oh, I'm Madoka Kaname.
But you can call me Madoka.
Huh? But...
Isn't that too...
It's fine.
Anyway, would you mind if I went
ahead and called you Homura?
Well, I...
I, uh...
I don't really get called by my first name very much.
It's...
kind of weird name.
What?
It's not weird at all!
It means "flame" like you flare
up passionately or something!
I think it's cool.
I'm not really like that though...
Oh...
Come on, how can you say that?
If you were blessed with such an awesome name,
then you have to make your mission to be just as cool!
Um....
All right, why don't you try solving this one?
You've been out sick.
Ask one of your friends for
their notes and try to catch up.
Can you believe it?
She got dizzy just from doing warm-ups.
Oh, she has been stuck in the bed for half a year.
So, go figure.
Ha...
Ah!?
Um?
Where am I?
Oh, no...
Ah, what's that?
What's going on?
No!
Ah!
That was a close one, wasn't it?
Don't worry. You're safe, Homura.
What are you doing here?
Why? They're magical girls.
They're girls who hunt witches.
Oops. Our secret's out.
Just don't tell anyone else in class, okay?
Miss Kaname...
I-I was wondering,
do you fight those things all the time?
Hmm...
Not all the time.
Mami is pretty much the veteran around here.
You wanna know the truth,
I already made a contract with Kyubey about a week ago.
You handled yourself very well today.
It was the best performance I've seen yet...
for a rookie.
But doesn't it bother you?
I mean...
don't you get scared?
Oh, sure bothered by it.
And yeah, that's kind a scary.
But when you look at it,
the more witches we take out,
the more people we save.
So, it's worth the effort, isn't it?
Mm-hm.
Uh...
It won't be long until Walpurgisnacht gets here.
So, the goal is to get Madoka fully-trained
as a magical girl before then.
Well, I'd better get going.
But...
Miss Tomoe...
That thing killed her...
I know.
But someone has to stop Walpurgisnacht.
And I'm the only one left who can.
No!
You can't beat it by yourself, it's too strong!
It'll kill you too, Miss Kaname!
Even so, I have to protect everyone.
It's my job.
I'm a magical girl.
Please...
You can run away...
I mean...
this is hopeless!
No one will blame you if you did, Miss Kaname.
Homura...
It's okay.
I'm glad I got to become friends with you.
Saving you from that witch
was the best thing I ever did.
And I'm always gonna be proud of that.
You see?
That's why, in the end,
I'm glad I became a magical girl.
I really am.
Miss Kaname...
Good-bye, Homura.
Take care.
Wait.
No!
Don't go!
Miss Kaname!!
Why...?
You knew you were gonna get killed all along...
It wasn't worth saving me...
if you're not alive...
I want you back...
Is that really what you want, Homura Akemi?
Would you trade your soul to
have a wish like that come true?
If there is something you want badly and
you're willing to accept the destiny battling witches,
then I can help you get what you want.
If I make a contract with you,
would you really grant me any wish?
Absolutely.
You have more than enough potential.
So tell me, what is the one wish you'd have
that will make your Soul Gem shine?
I wish...
I wish, I can meet Miss Kaname all over again.
But this time, instead of her protecting me,
I wanna be strong enough to protect her!
Ugh...
The contract is complete.
Your wish has overcome entropy.
Go now...
Go and unleash your new magical power!
Ah!
Where am I?
I...
I'm still in the hospital?
Uh...
Ah!
It wasn't a dream!
Ahem.
Why don't you tell us a little bit about yourself?
I'm Homura Akemi.
I'm very pleased to meet you!
Okay, people, Miss Akemi's been
in the hospital for a wh...
Ah...
Miss Kaname!
I've become a magical girl just like you!
We're gonna work together from now on!
Uh... um...
Umm...
Okay, here I go!
Yahh!!!
Well, Mami.
What do you think?
Hmm...
She can stop time.
That's pretty amazing,
but she still has to figure out how to use it in battle.
Huh, I know...
Ahhh...
Mami!
Your turn!
I'm on it!
Ha!
Homura, go for it!
Okay!
Huh?
Uh, did I do it?
Look you did it!
You did well.
You were amazing, Homura!
Urgh...
What's wrong?
Miss Kaname, say something!
Why is so...?
Ugh!
Ahhh!
Ahh...
Oh, no...
But, why...?
How could this...
happen?
Ah!
I have to tell everyone!
We're all being tricked by Kyubey!
Okay, look.
Why would Kyubey do something like that?
What'd he get out of it?
W-Well...
I bet you're just saying that
so we'll turn against each other.
Oh, wait a sec.
Are you and Kyoko chick working together?
Is that what's going on?
No, I'm not!
Sayaka, wait.
Stop trying to pick a fight with her.
Fine. Whatever...
Do what you want, but I'm not teaming up with that girl.
You and Mami use long-range weapons,
so it's no biggie for you guys.
But when I'm fighting, I don't like
when explosion's going off in my face.
She comes this close to blowing me up every time.
She has a point there.
Are there any weapons you can use besides bombs?
Um...
Okay, I'll think of something.
Dammit!
What are you?
What have you done to Sayaka?
Sayaka, please stop!
Try to remember, please!
I know you never really wanted to hurt anyone.
Sorry...
Miss Miki.
Sayaka...
Dammit!
How could this happen?
It's awful...
This isn't right... It's horrible!
Aw...
Miss Tomoe?
If Soul Gems give birth to witches...
then we have no choice but to die!
Both me...
and you...!
Stop it!
Aw...
I don't want this...
I can't take it any more...
It's okay.
We can finish this.
The two of us can destroy Walpurgisnacht on our own!
Mm...
Mm.
This is it...
It's over for us too...
Mm...
Do you have any Grief Seeds?
...'Kay.
I have got an idea.
How about we both become witches...
and we can tear this rotten world together?
Until there is no more evil,
no more sadness,
until there's nothing left.
We'll break, and smash,
and pound it into dust.
What if we did that?
Wouldn't that be great?
Ah!
Sorry, I lied.
I guess I still have one left.
You should've used it!
It's better this way.
I want you to do something that I couldn't do.
You can go back in time, right, Homura?
You can go back and change everything...
so that we don't end up like this...
Okay?
Then save me from being stupid, from getting tricked.
Don't let Kyubey fool me again.
I swear I'll save you!
I'll do whatever it takes to keep you safe!
I'll come back again and again and again!
I'll save you!
I swear!
Thank you...
Urgh!
Can I ask...
one more thing?
Don't let...me turn into a witch...
There's awful...
horrible things in this world...
I know that now...
that there's a lot of things worth protecting, too...
Finally, you called me by my first name.
I'm so... happy...
Ahh!
Huh?
Wh-who's there?
Madoka...
If someone comes and says they'll
grant any wish you want, it isn't true.
Don't believe anything they say!
Um... But I...
That's horrible...
You can't help it.
One person can't handle this alone.
No, this isn't right, it's too much for her...
No, Madoka!
Don't listen to anything it says!
If she gives up, it's over.
But, you have the power to change this destiny.
All this tragedy, all this destruction,
you can change it, if you want.
The power to do so lies within you.
I can change it?
It's trying to trick you!
Don't listen to it!
Even someone like me can do something to help?
Can I really change how this ends?
Of course, you can.
Just make a contract with me,
and become a magical girl!
Noooo!
When Madoka transformed,
that was really amazing, wasn't it?
I never had any doubt she'd become the
most powerful magical girl in the world.
But I never dreamed she'd take
down Walpurgisnacht with one shot.
Did you know what would happen...
afterwards?
Her fate was bound to happen sooner or later.
She was the strongest of all magical girls,
and she destroyed her greatest enemy.
It's only natural she'd turn into
the wickedest witch of them all.
And in her current state,
I'm estimating it'll take her no more
than ten days to destroy the planet.
Oh, well, it's humanity's problem now.
We pretty much filled our quota
and have more than enough energy.
Uh...
Aren't you going to fight her?
No.
My fight is somewhere else.
Uh...
Homura Akemi...
You're...!
Ah!
Homura...?
You spent all that time with them.
Didn't you ever feel anything?
Didn't you ever try to understand?
Couldn't you see how much pain they were in?
The only thing I have left to guide me.
Oh, that's right.
Huh...?
Uh-huh?
But why?!
Madoka!
You have to make your mission to be just as cool!
No way...
Not me.
I can't do anything right...
I just embarrass myself and cause trouble for everyone.
Why?
Is this...
the way...
I'll always be?
Maybe it would be better if you just died.
Maybe it would be better...
That's right.
You should just die...
I should just...
die...
No one will believe me about the future.
No one will accept the truth about the future.
I know what to do now.
I won't rely on anyone anymore!
I don't care if no one understands.
I won't let Madoka fight.
I'll destroy every last witch by myself if I have to.
And this time...
I will defeat Walpurgisnacht,
once and for all!
I'll do it over...
no matter how many times it takes.
I'll relive it over and over again.
I will find the way out.
The one path,
that'll save you from this destiny of despair.
Madoka...
My one and my only friend.
I don't care...
because if it's for you,
I'll stay trapped in this endless maze,
forever!