[theme song in japanese]
-Why would the third have
tried to eliminate Yakumo?
There's no way
that could be true.
But if it is, if Kurenai
sensei did carry out
that kind of mission,
that would explain
why she's acting so weird.
Nah, that's crazy.
It couldn't be.
-How you doing Kurenai sensei?
Are you OK?
-Yes.
You did a good job
patching me up, Sakura.
I feel much better now.
-So what do you think, you guys?
Who do you figure
she's covering for?
-Well, it was the
third Hokage who
told her to look after Yakumo.
-So what was her actual mission?
-What the hell?
-You guys seeing this?
Look, it's a Hidden
Leaf Village.
It's--
-Oh.
-It looks like the aftermath of
some gigantic war or something.
-Hinata.
-Uh, right.
Byakugan.
-There isn't anybody
in the village.
-This isn't good.
-What the hell's
going on around here?
-Kiba, Hinata you two
picking anything up?
-No sign of enemies
in the vicinity.
-Akamaru hasn't caught a
whiff of anything either.
-I don't understand
what happened here.
How could this even be?
-Let's just get Yakumo
and Kurenai sensei back
to the hospital for now.
We can take a look around
the village after that.
-Yeah, you're right.
This is bad.
-Come on, let's get
these two inside.
-Don't worry about me.
Take care of Yakumo.
-Right.
-You're totally safe now.
Huh?
Oh, no.
She's unconscious.
-Her vital signs are dropping.
Hopefully, there's
still medicine.
Naruto, we need to
see what we can find.
-Yeah, but shouldn't we--
-Naruto, come on.
-All right.
-I don't smell any blood.
Looks like they've all been
evacuated to somewhere.
-Let's go have a look
around the village.
-Right.
-Make sure you
act as a team, OK?
And I don't care what
you find out there,
I want you back
here in 30 minutes.
-Got it.
Hmph.
-What?
What is it?
-Heh, heh.
Aw, nothing.
Just feels good to be getting
orders from you again,
you know?
-Hey, we're looking
for medicine, remember?
Snap out of it, will you?
-Sorry, I'm just worried about
Kurenai sensei, that's all.
-All the more reason
to keep looking.
-That's not what I meant.
She came to eliminate her.
You know, Yakumo.
-Eliminate?
-Oh, uh, never mind.
I just spaced out
there for a second.
Sorry.
-Huh?
Wait, did you just see that?
-See what?
-We're not the
only ones in here.
-Huh?
Sakura, you look after
Kurenai and Yakumo.
I'm going after him.
-Got it.
-Stop right there.
Multi-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
What?
It didn't activate.
Hmm?
-Aaah.
Aaaah.
Hold on.
We haven't the time to
be fighting right now.
-You the guy who attacked
us back at the villa, right?
-My name is Unkai.
I'm from the Kurama clan.
-Kurama?
You mean the same
one as Yakumo's?
Why would her own
clan be after her?
-Listen to me.
If you don't, then
everyone will die.
[barking]
-What the hell's
that smell in here?
-Byakugan.
-What?
Kiba, muzzke Akamaru.
Hinata, stop using the Byakugan.
-Huh?
-Why?
What is it?
-None of this is real.
We're caught in the
middle one big Jutsu.
-What do you mean?
-It's true.
We're inside of Yakumo's
genjutsu right now.
I know it seems as if Hidden
Leaf Village has been ravaged
by war, but everything
you see here
is nothing but an illusion.
-So what?
-The entire village
isn't real then?
We're all just trapped
in one big genjutsu?
I'm not buying it.
There's no way
that could be true.
-Oh, no?
But if her latent powers
have finally awakened,
it would be easy for her.
-The whole village?
The ground we're standing on?
The sky, everything is genjutsu?
-Heightened senses can
occasionally be a weakness.
No matter how superior
one sight or smell may be,
it's ultimately the human brain
that receives and interprets
information.
The mind is a vastly intricate
network of electrical impulses.
There's a lot of room for error.
But the senses of the
insect are minimal.
Unlike the human
brain, the insect mind
utilizes the barest amount
of information necessary.
Look, my insects are
still under control.
They can't be deceived.
-Within the confines
of Yakumo's genjutsu,
she'll often call down
lightly or start fires,
and our human minds perceive
those phenomena to be real.
Our brains are turned against
us causing actual damage
to the body.
-So grandma's mansion, that
was Yakumo's power, too?
-And that's not all.
Were she feeling
so inclined, she
could easily kill
anyone she chose to.
-So these tremors--
-Are just genjutsu as well?
-Just wait.
-A serpent.
-It's gigantic.
More genjutsu, huh?
-It's an image of terror
created in our cerebrums,
but it can't harm us.
That would be unthinkable.
Impossible.
-Yakumo?
Kurenai sensei?
[scream]
-So tell me the truth.
Yakumo can kill using genjutsu?
So is that why the Third
Hokage tried to get rid of her?
[scream]
-Yakumo.
Yakumo.
-Kurenai sensei.
Kurenai sensei.
I'm over here sensei.
-No way.
I don't believe it.
Yakumo would never
do such a thing.
-Every few generations or
so, within the Kurama clan,
children of a special nature
are born to us, such as Yakumo.
Most terrifying
of all is the fact
she doesn't control this power.
It is ruled entirely by the
girl's unconscious mind.
-Man, it's getting
kind of hot in here.
-Don't do it!
-I don't know what's behind
this door, but it can't be good.
-You can't open it.
-What the heck?
Well, there's something
you don't see everyday.
-It's an illusion our
brains have created due
to Yakumo's genjutsu.
But illusion or no,
were you to dive in,
your mind would
determine it to be real,
and your body would burn up.
That is the power Yakumo wields.
-So that's what this
is all about, huh?
The Third Hokage and Kurenai?
That's why they wanted her gone.
-Nothing of the sort.
They never meant
to kill the girl.
That's not what they were after.
What they wanted was to kill
the monster inside of her.
-A monster?
-She was growing stronger
and stronger everyday,
and out of that ocean of
power, a creature most terrible
was born.
If left unchecked, it will
eventually take hold of Yakumo
absorbing her
consciousness into its own.
The Hokage and Kurenai
came to a decision.
They believed that the only
way to keep Yakumo safe
was to seal away
the girl's power.
-Trapped inside of her.
No kidding.
So, that's what's going on.
Well, I'm not
sitting around here.
What?
Aaah.
Hiragana, that was
all the money I had.
-I told you.
If you fall in that lava,
your body will be incinerated.
-So what are you saying?
We can't get out of here?
-No, there is one way.
-OK, then what is it?
-If you seal off
your five senses,
the genjutsu will no longer
have any effect on you.
You must escape from this world
of illusion and attack her.
-Attack Yakumo?
Aaah.
Huh?
It's Satomi Hill.
How'd I get here?
Huh?
Unkai?
-Well, it looks like you made
it out of her illusion safely.
Did you?
-What the hell happened here?
-From the very moment
you brought Yakumo out
of that lodge, you
were immediately
caught up inside
of her genjutsu.
-Huh?
Hey, guys, come on.
Snap out of it.
Hey, Kiba.
Shino.
-Where are we?
-You've got to get up.
Come on, hurry.
Old man Unkai is wounded.
-Unkai?
-What happened?
These burns are awful.
The old man here
is the only reason
we were able to break
free of Yakumo's genjutsu.
You should have seen it.
-That's not true.
Actually, we were
all driven out.
Yakumo doesn't care about us.
Her only target here
is Kurenai Yuhi.
-So wait.
Where is she now then?
-I think I may know.
-What are you doing?
-What do you think
of my work, sensei?
Amazing, isn't it?
-Yakumo, what did you
do with the others?
-You needn't worry.
They're not hurt.
I just send them away.
I'm not in a hurry.
I'll have my revenge
on the Hidden Leaf
Village in due time.
But first, I have some
business with you, sensei.
-Yakumo, leave the
village out of it.
I know that you're angry, but
this is between you and me.
-You're not fooling anyone.
So, impressive, huh?
I could let you live, or
kill you in a heartbeat.
Your fate rests
entirely with me.
Tell me the truth.
My father and mother were both
eliminated, and then my clan.
And once they were all gone,
the village set its eyes on me.
All by order of the third.
-No.
Yakumo, the Third
Hokage would never
have ordered such a mission.
-Why are you lying to me?
Tell me the truth.
Now.
If you don't Kurenai sensei,
I'll send you into oblivion.
-You poor, sad child.
If killing me will put an
end to all your suffering,
then you should just
go ahead and do it.
So long as this deep hatred
can finally be put to rest.
-Oh, save it.
Your crocodile tears
aren't fooling anyone.
-1,001, 1,002,
1,003, 1,004, 1,005.
Whoa, Nellie.
Rain or shine, there's
nothing like breaking
a sweat with a little training.
Huh?
There's more them, huh?
All right then.
Get ready Kurama
clan, here I come.
Huh?
I see.
So you were caught in
their genjutsu as well.
-Yes, sir.
-Well, you're alive, and
that's all that really matters,
am I right?
Whoa-ho, you got
back in no time.
So, uh, where's the cavalry?
-Sorry, you guys, but there's
no time to explain right now.
-Huh?
Hey.
Hold on a second.
What was that all about?
Hmm?
So who's this?
You want to fill me in?
-You'll just have to wait.
This man needs help.
-Yeah, but--
-Please, just hurry.
-OK.
-Byakugan.
-Them again.
-Yakumo, stop this.
-They're together
right now in a room
in the center of the building.
-Come on.
-Wait a sec.
Hold on!
Kiba!
[theme song in japanese]
-What's the situation now, guys?
-We haven't seen Naruto
since he went in.
-My insects have
detected something odd
and returned to me.
-Hinata, is your
Byakugan any help?
-There's some kind of powerful
force getting in the way.
And all we can do
is watch and wait.
-So what?
We just cross our fingers
and hope for the best?
Next time, the Supposed
Sealed Ability.