[MUSIC - SNOWKEL, "NAMIKAZE
SATELLITE"]
-Any sign of Naruto?
-I looked, but I can't find him.
-I see.
-He must be pretty
far away by now.
Either he drifted
away or swam off.
Anyway, with the fog
as thick as it is,
there's no reason to stick
around and keep looking.
Let's find the closest shoreline
and start again when it clears.
-Fine.
-It's been far too
long, Lord Orochimaru.
-Indeed it has.
How fortunate that I
dropped by and happened
to find you still here.
-I'm lucky.
For now I have the opportunity
to stand in your presence
once again.
--[laughs] And I assume the
reason you remain here is that
you are continuing our research.
-I am.
I still believe that someday
it will be very useful to you,
sir.
-I certainly hope so.
-Of course, I only continue
out of loyalty to you.
-Well, carry on.
Do as you wish.
-I'm grateful, my lord.
By the way, is he the
one you spoke of before?
-Yes.
The younger brother
of Itachi Uchiha.
-Really?
-Yes.
And also my--
-Some things are
better left unsaid.
[laughs]
[insect buzzing]
-It appears that Naruto
is nowhere to be found.
-Hey.
You don't think-- I mean,
Naruto's still OK, right?
-He wouldn't be
beaten so easily.
After all, he is a Leaf ninja.
-I am the ship's
financial administrator.
Welcome.
My name is Hitode.
I am well aware
of the situation.
Your colleague is
missing and I'm
sure you're very
worried about him.
-Yes.
Have you gotten any information
at all about where he is?
-Unfortunately, I have
received no reports yet
from any shipwreck survivors.
-I see.
-That's not all the bad news.
I'm sorry, but the schedule for
our ship delivering the money
has been moved up.
-You're leaving earlier?
-Our new departure is
scheduled for tomorrow morning.
My apologies for
such a late notice.
As you can imagine,
the relationship
with the Land of
Water is fragile.
Hence the decision was made
to push our departure forward.
-We understand.
Even so, we need to spend as
much time here as possible,
trying to find our teammate.
-Of course.
-Good.
Then we'll meet your ship
tomorrow at the port guard duty
with or without him.
-Thank you for your cooperation.
One more thing.
As you can see, our nation
is not a wealthy one,
and recently the
fisherman of our land
have been especially nervous
about this demon of the ocean.
Anything you could do would
be greatly appreciated.
-We'll give it our all.
-Wait, that's right.
Somebody--
-I see you're awake.
-Uh, yeah.
-Hey, you're that
girl from yesterday.
I remember.
You're the one who saved me.
Thanks a million.
-It was just a coincidence.
-No way.
You seriously saved
my butt out there.
Oh yeah, I'm Naruto Uzumaki.
What's your name?
-Isaribi.
-Got it.
Isaribi.
I guess you're my hero now.
[laughs]
-So what were you doing
in such a remote area?
-Oh, I had a mission.
To get rid of the demon
of the ocean that's
been causing so much trouble.
-Then it would be best
for you to give up.
If you're able to find the
beast, you'll never survive.
-You don't need
to worry about me.
Yeah, I've had tough
missions before.
I was a little
careless yesterday,
but next time I'll catch
that demon of the-- yikes!
That's hot!
-So, you feeling a
little better now?
-Yeah.
Thanks to you and this awesome
food, I'm feeling fine.
-Very well then.
When you're finished with
your meal, please leave.
-What?
Huh?
Hold on, Isaribi.
Slow down.
What gives?
What?
What the?
Who did this?
-Some children from
the village did it.
But I can't let it bother me.
-Wait, Isaribi.
Remember I owe you one.
-Look, it's the monster.
-What monster?
-Get out of here.
-You're a bad omen.
-Yeah, take this.
-Isaribi!
Leave her alone!
-She won't talk.
-Look at her.
-Say something.
-Knock it off, you twerps.
I'm not going to let you take
your stupid pranks too far.
-Yeah, and who are you?
A friend of the monster?
-The monster?
-Everybody knows it's true.
-Yeah, Isaribi secretly
went up and joined up
with the demon of the ocean.
-You shouldn't make
up things like that.
-It's the truth.
[grunting]
-What a doofus.
-Hey, who are you
calling a doofus?
-Let them go.
-What?
But they--
-It's all right.
You should just leave me alone.
-Leave you alone?
No way.
If those kids keep
doing that all--
-Don't you get it?
It's none of your business!
They're right.
I was taken away by the spirits.
It's only natural people
think I'm strange.
-But that wasn't your fault.
It's not like you want
to be taken or anything.
-That doesn't matter.
The truth is most
humans would never
associate with someone
as different is I am.
you don't know.
[neighing]
-So you say your
friend was lost at sea?
-Yeah.
We thought that if a boat
left port last night,
someone here probably
would have seen something.
-I'm sorry, but I don't think
I can be of any help to you.
Lately the villages
have been staying away
from the port at night
because they're all
scared of the demon.
-Oh, I see.
-He's been taken by the spirits.
I'm afraid the
demon of the ocean
has taken yet another victim.
-Mother.
Don't frighten them like that.
-Taken by the--
-I heard that
phrase at the port.
This taken by the spirits.
Can you tell us
what you know of it?
-I can, but what
good will it do?
Talking won't bring
your friend back.
-But still--
-Please, you must forgive us.
This subject isn't something
we can discuss with outsiders.
-We might be able to
help your village.
Don't you see?
We came here to get rid
of the demon of the ocean.
-You came to do what?
All right then.
For as long as I've known,
generations of fishermen
have told the legend
of Demon Island.
-A legend?
-Yes.
The legend warns against even
going near the isolated place
they call the Island of Demons.
From the beginning the
waters off Demon Island
were rich in fish.
But the hidden reefs there made
it too dangerous for boats.
Most people headed the
legend and stayed away.
But one unusually cool
summer 10 years ago, the fish
disappeared from the sea.
We had no choice,
so my husband and I
ventured into the
treacherous waters.
We caught many fish.
But when I returned to
the surface with our haul,
I was stunned.
The boat was empty.
My husband was
nowhere to be seen.
Since then, one by one, everyone
who approaches that island
has disappeared.
Even those who go to
search for the missing.
No one will go near
the island for fear
that they too will
be taken away.
-An island where
people disappear?
-It's such a bizarre story.
-Wait a second.
We heard something
about a girl who
returned from being taken away.
-Oh, yes.
Isaribi.
-Ma'am, I have
one more question.
I want you to tell
me where she lives.
-Lady Tsunade.
Lady Tsunade.
I brought you that
information you requested.
Is that about the
Land of the Sea?
So you are worried after all.
-You see, when Orochimaru
abandoned Anko,
she was found in
the land of the sea.
[panting]
-Hey.
Are you OK?
-It's no use.
I don't remember anything.
I should know this, but
everything-- it was dark,
empty.
My body was in so much pain.
I can't.
-Just calm down.
Take as much time as
you need to think.
-I'm not even sure if I got this
weird mark while I was there.
-The damage is deep.
Everything she knew
may have been erased.
-Rest easy.
I know you must have been
through quite an ordeal.
It's going to be fine.
Don't worry about remembering.
Our priority is
treating the curse mark
before it gets worse.
-Lord Hokage.
I--
-She never did
remember anything.
Even to this day, part of
Anko's memory is simply gone.
-So that's what happened.
And this mission
is the first time
Anko has set foot in
the land of the sea
since she went
through all of that?
-Yep.
That's right.
I had hoped this
trip might bring back
some of her lost memories, but--
-What?
I just missed them?
You're telling me they
came right through here?
-Yeah.
If you hurry, you might
be able to catch them.
-OK.
Which way did they go?
-Off that way.
-No way, that's the
direction I just came from!
They better still be there.
-The delivery ship is en route.
-Interesting.
So she's the only person
who ever came back
after disappearing?
-Yeah.
That's why I figured we should
at least go check it out.
-She may have some useful
information about Demon Island.
-Hold it.
-What?
It's her.
What do we do now?
-Let's find out
where she's headed.
-She's cautious.
-Let's follow.
But make sure she
doesn't see us.
-Hey!
Where'd you go?
Aw, great.
If I keep going
backwards like this
I'm going to end up
at Isaribi's house.
-Look at those features.
So you must be the
demon of the ocean.
Ah!
-What the?
-It's getting away.
-But Lord Orochimaru--
-I'm going to teach you
something very special today.
This is one of the secret
chambers where I develop jutsu.
I was hoping you would help me
with this specimen, my dear.
-But if the villagers
knew about this.
-This one is going quite
as smoothly as I planned.
Only more step and she's done.
Don't be silly, little one.
There's nothing you
should be afraid of.
There's only one thing
we ever need fear,
and that's neglecting
our duty to pursue
this kind of knowledge.
-Could it be the same girl?
-Give up.
There's no escape.
-We've got you now, demon.
-Hey!
Everyone!
Hey!
I've been looking all
over for you guys.
-Naruto!
Thank goodness.
We were worried about you.
-Unfortunately you're
a bit too late.
-What are you talking about?
-We captured the
demon of the ocean.
Take a look for
yourself over there.
-Whoa.
Wow.
So that's the demon?
Isaribi?
-Huh?
-It's you.
You really are
Isaribi, aren't you?
-Naruto, what the heck
are you talking about?
-Hold on.
Isaribi, answer me!
-She's loose.
-Get back here!
-Wait, we can't
be rough with her.
She's not strong.
-Explanations will have to wait.
We can't let her escape.
[laughs]
-Who do you think you are?
Hand over Isaribi.
-You must be dreaming.
This girl's an
important lab rat.
If we lose her,
I'm the one who's
going to be held responsible.
-You jerk!
-Don't chase that guy too far.
Remember yesterday.
-We'll lose him!
[laughter]
-No way.
-No question about it.
That was her.
[groans]
-Sensei!
-Now what?
What in the world is
going on around here?
[music - chaba, "parade"]
-You're nuts.
What the heck are you thinking?
You can't rescue
her by yourself.
-I can't just let her go.
I owe her.
-Even if you did
go after her, you
wouldn't have any
clue where to look.
-No, that's not true.
-What?
-Do you remember the
island at the heart
of these disappearances?
-That's right.
Demon Island.
-Then let's get going.
There's no way I'm letting
that guy get away with her.
Next time, Infiltration,
the Set Up.
[music - chaba, "parade"]