[theme music]
-What do you think, Aoi?
What should we do?
I will be accompanying
Fukusuke at sea.
I want you three
to go after Idate.
-Right.
-Hey, Hayate.
The ocean is the other way.
Where the hell do you think
you're going, you idiot?
You have to turn around.
-You can forget about it.
There's no way I'm
turning around.
-Let's go.
-Yes sir.
SAILOR (VOICEOVER): What does
that kid think he's doing?
-It looks like the little
fool is running away, Sir.
Not surprising, Idate has
always been like that.
SAILOR: You know him?
-I guess you could say that.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
The Race is On.
Trouble on the High Seas.
-I knew that little
bastard would run away.
-I guess it really
shouldn't have
come as a surprise knowing
him as long as we have.
-It was a mistake
to let him run.
-You idiots.
Idate is a better man than that.
-Yes, boss.
-I believe in Idate.
he must have some sort
of plan up his sleeve.
-Jirocho.
-Chief counselor.
-So tell me, how
will you settle this?
You just turned this
most hallowed tradition
into little more than a farce in
the presence of a feudal lord,
no less.
-Your Excellency, this race
has only just now begun.
Do me the honor of seeing
it through to the finish.
-If you're that insistent
then you'd better win,
no matter what.
Because if you
lose, I'll see to it
your entire family is
scattered to the wind.
-You have a deal.
I'm a man of my word.
If Idate should end
up losing, then you
have free reign to
do whatever you wish.
-That is so like you,
Jirocho, stubborn as an ox.
I hope you're ready to pay up.
JIROCHO (VOICEOVER): I'm
counting on you Idate.
IDATE (VOICEOVER):
Hold on, Boss.
Give me all your money.
Don't you move a muscle.
-Huh.
Well, a starving thief, huh?
-Shut your mouth.
-This is the grownups game, kid.
You couldn't even peel an apple
with bad thing, could you?
Here.
Take it, and remember,
kid, the blade
wasn't invented for the
purpose of hurting people.
You live out on the
street, don't you, son?
I'm Jirocho, the
head of the Wasabi
family in Port Degarashi.
-Jirocho of the Wasabi?
-How about it?
Why don't you come stay with me?
-Huh?
But why when I was
just trying to--
-When a man is starving,
it's easy for him
to make a mistake like that.
It's of no concern.
-Um, this is--
-Forget about it.
That was a gift.
Keep it.
But no more thieving antics.
Do we have a deal?
-Mister.
I wish to follow you.
Make me your disciple.
I mean, please, Boss.
-What's your name?
-Idate.
Idate Morino.
-Shall we go then, Idate?
IDATE (VOICEOVER):
Have faith in me, Boss.
I promise I'll win this for you.
-We'll catch up to
him pretty soon.
-But it's too late
now. he won't be able
win this far away from the port.
-I don't know.
He might have planned
to come this way
from the very beginning.
-Huh?
-(LAUGHING) Well,
this was lucky.
Let's see we put an
end to this right here?
It's funny, isn't it?
-Yeah, who'd have thought those
three would be escorting him?
Double lucky.
Now I can pay them back
for the Chunin exam.
You two go on ahead.
I'll keep them tied up here.
-You got it.
-Finally caught up to ya.
Hey, wait up, will ya?
So what gives?
Why the heck did
you come this way?
-Will you shut up?
It's none of your
business anyway, kid.
-What's with the attitude, pal?
-I said shut up!
-Watch out!
-I don't think they've
even noticed it.
This is genjutsu.
-Are you going to
slow down or what?
-I've already been here.
Great, I'm trapped in
some sort of genjutsu.
-Say what?
-In this case, release.
Over there.
-Hey.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
No, don't go that way.
-Huh?
What's going on around here?
-I'm out.
[yelling]
-Just hold still.
I'll have them pull us up now.
-Oh man, that was a close one.
-Somebody set up one
genjutsu one top of another.
That's not very
easy to pull off.
-You idiot, if you had just
stopped for two seconds,
we wouldn't be in this mess.
-What did you say?
-Hey, knock it off.
Stop.
Ah.
No, all of my ninja tools.
-Look, I didn't
need your help, OK?
-You didn't need it?
Hey, listen, you fat head,
how about a little thanks
for saving your life?
-You only saved me because
you're bound to by duty.
There's no need for
me to thank you.
-What did you say?
-Stop it, Naruto.
He's absolutely right.
But look, if you don't
want to wind up dead,
then I suggest you
stick close to us.
-Hey, where you going anyway?
What happened to Port Degarashi?
-What about it?
Forget that port.
I'm heading north from here.
-You are?
So does that mean
it's faster that way?
-That's right.
-Yeah, maybe.
How do we even know if
we can trust this guy?
-That's the problem
with all you ninja.
-What?
-Look, at this time
of the year, there
are some pretty
strong seasonal winds
blowing hard across the sea.
Back at the starting point,
I noticed the clouds.
I could see the wind
was blowing toward us.
On top of that, there's a port
to the north where the ocean
current flows directly
into Nagi Island.
That's what I was saying.
You ought to use this a
little more right here.
-Looks like it's going
to get it a bit rough.
-Hey, let's not push our luck.
Get us turned more
towards the south.
-That will eat up too much time.
-Just get to land.
There's no one on earth
who's faster than me.
My victory is inevitable.
-As you wish then.
-Hey, I can smell
salt on the wind.
SAKURA: It's the ocean.
What's that out
across the water?
-It's the halfway
point, Motaroki Shrine
over on Nagi Island.
We can probably get ourselves
there within an hour from here.
One sec.
Hey, Gramps, it's me.
Idate of the Wasabi.
-Hey, there.
I've been waiting for you.
-It's going just as
I thought it would.
I'm gonna need you
to lend me that boat.
-You bet.
I have things all ready for ya.
You can use that one
right over there.
There isn't a
faster boat around.
-Thanks a lot, Gramps.
-It's not a problem.
Jirocho has done a lot
for me over the years.
Just make sure you don't
lose to the Wagarashi.
I've had about all I
can stand from them
and the way they rule this land.
-Don't worry about a thing.
I may be the
underdog, but you're
looking at the right
hand man of the Wasabi.
Leave it to me.
I won't fail you.
I promise.
-Yeah.
Right.
Whatever.
IDATE (VOICEOVER): We
Should be able to see
the port at Nagi Island soon.
Hope we get there
before Fukusuke.
-Hey, Naruto, what do you think?
-What about?
-About Idate.
I mean, he's not just
some ordinary guy.
The level of speed he
runs at is extraordinary.
He's probably received some
sort of special training.
-What kind of training?
-It's possible he's spend
some time in one of the hidden
villages.
-Get real.
That blockhead could
never be a ninja.
-Look who's talking?
Last time I checked.
You were the reigning
king of stupid.
-Well, yeah, but
I mean, come on.
I did make it to the final round
of the Chunin exams, didn't I?
-You didn't really make it
to the final round, did you?
-Yeah, that's right.
And if I hadn't been
interrupted in the middle of it,
I could have won the
tournament and become a Chunin.
-Yeah, well, whoever
your proctor was must've
been a real push over.
Sounds like the Chunin exam
has lowered its standards some.
-I see.
So that means you were--
-I remember now.
-Idate Morino.
-Morino.
Oh yeah, that's right.
Wasn't he the proctor
of the first exam?
-All right, you
baby-faced degenerates.
Pipe down and listen up.
It's time to begin.
I am Ibiki Morino, your proctor.
And from this moment,
your worst enemy.
-Ibiki Morino.
-What'd you say?
My brother, he's alive?
-Yes.
-Well, of course, he's alive.
Why wouldn't he be?
He threw such a curve ball
at me the 10th question in.
-Seriously?
He's really alive then?
-Ah, that's great.
Now what?
-It's an ambush.
-How we doing?
-See for yourself.
They're just up ahead.
-All right then.
Let's get rolling.
-Naruto and I will
fend these guys off.
Sakura, you keep
an eye on Idate.
-Maybe we should all just run.
-It's too late for that.
Start working on these ropes.
I'll cover you.
-Yeah, you've got it.
Shoot, I'll have to cut these.
That's perfect.
I had to lose all my gear.
hey, lend me that, will ya?
-What?
-Come on, hand it over already.
-Forget it, you imbecile.
This is more precious to
me than my own life is.
There's no way I'm
giving it to you.
-Look, get over yourself.
We don't have time
for this right now.
-Get away from me, you idiot.
-Hurry up already,
you knucklehead.
-Well, that was a piece of cake.
-Ah!
-Don't worry, Sakura.
It's just a bunch of clones.
Only the real one can
actually attack us.
We're going to be fine.
-Sharingan.
-Sakura, Naruto, watch out.
One of them isn't
a shadow clone.
Be careful!
-Just tell us where, Sasuke.
You'd better stay close
to my side, Idate.
-No way.
Why would I want to need
help from a bunch of ninja?
-Look around you, pal,
beggars can't be choosers.
-Naruta, behind you.
-Naruto.
-A clone?
Aw, crap.
-Go for clone.
Great, the real one got away.
SAKURA: Nice work, Naruto.
-That shadow clone
kid is a handful.
Switch to plan B, Kagari.
We'll kill every
last one of them.
Oboro style.
Black rain jutsu.
-Susake, they've changed
into water clones.
-I know.
-It's raining?
Wait a sec, I think this is oil.
SUSAKE (VOICEOVER):
Enough already.
I'll take them all
out in one shot.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): A
tiger seal hand sign.
SAKURA: Susake, don't!
-Aw, nuts.
-Ah, unlucky.
-Don't be so sure.
-Fire attack.
-Brother?
-Get out of here.
You'll only get in my way.
-Brother!
-What's wrong, Idate?
-Nothing.
I'm fine.
-What are we going
to do, Susake?
The fire is out of control.
-We dive into the ocean.
We're just going to have to
swim to the port at Nagi Island.
-You're right.
It's our only option.
Idate, do you know how to swim?
-Of course.
-OK, you go first.
Then I can cover you.
With all this smoke
everywhere, we
shouldn't have any problems
slipping away unnoticed.
Idate.
-You can forget about it.
What do you think, I'm stupid?
You three probably just
want to use me as a decoy.
-What are you talking about?
-You want them to focus
on me while you guys get
the hell out of here.
-Stop talking nonsense.
-I said forget it.
I don't trust ninjas.
-Get out of here already.
We don't need you
getting in our way.
-Get out of here.
You'll only get in my way.
NARUTO: Hurry up and go!
SAKURA: There's no way
we'd use you as a decoy.
-No.
I won't.
-Son of a-- Get down!
You've got to trust me, Idate.
I promise we'll protect you.
Watch out!
Ah!
-Sakura!
-S-- Sakura.
-Hurry, go on ahead.
I promise, we'll be
right behind you.
-Uh-huh.
-Well, shall we cut out?
-Cut out?
We haven't even gotten
to the best part.
-They're surprisingly tenacious.
-Yeah.
-But we're not letting
them get away this time.
-I should be OK now.
Huh?
-Long time no see, Idate.
-You.
You're the one who--
-Really?
How many times do
I have to teach you
that you can't trust anyone.
[grunting]
AOI: Such a fool you are.
[theme music]
SAILOR: It doesn't matter
what you were like before.
That's water under the bridge.
This race is far from over.
You'll never know the
truth unless you see it
through to the end.
Your boss believes in you.
You've got all this time
to stall things and act
like a big shot, then show me
some guts while you're at it.
Next time, Run, Idate, Run.
Nagi Island Awaits.