[panting]
-Naruto and the others
are fighting and risking
their lives, while the
rest of us do nothing.
We've got to fight, too.
The weapon's known as shinobi.
[knocking]
-Uncle Giichi,
Uncle Giichi, hurry.
Come to the bridge with me.
We don't have to
hide any longer.
If we all fight together, we
can finally take Gato down.
I know we can.
[click]
-No, Inari, I've
given up fighting.
Fighting is for heroes,
like your father.
You see what good it did him.
Isn't one dead hero enough?
-Uh--
-What will more
fighting bring us
but more fallen heroes
and more regrets?
No, Inari, my heart is
already full of enough regrets
to last a lifetime.
-Well, I don't want to live
a life of regrets, either.
And that's why
we've got to fight!
-Live your life so you
have nothing to regret.
-I know you care about
everyone in the village,
and so do I-- you and mother
and grandfather and everyone.
That's why we have to fight.
All my life, I've been
a coward, but now I
know that crying, and hiding
from things that we're
afraid of doesn't
make them go away.
-Hurry!
Come to the bridge!
-Our little Inari
has become a man.
And you, dear, are
you sure you want
to send him off all on his own?
-Is anyone there?
[knocking] Hello!
Come to the bridge
with me and fight!
[panting]
-What do I do now?
Not one of them will even
open their door to listen.
Uh--
-Cuz, you really are brave.
Well, then, if no
one will help--
[panting]
[roaring]
-Poor Zabuza, see where
your ambitions got you?
You're always pushing
things too far.
It was the failed
Mizukage assassination,
and your attempted coup d'etat.
You were forced to flee with
the few followers you had,
your country's tracker
ninja hot on your heels.
You became a rogue ninja
whose name was quickly known,
even in the village
hidden in the leaves.
Now you're crazy enough to want
to go back and try it again,
but for that you need money.
And to get it,
you've stooped so low
as to be the hired thug
of a swine like Gato.
All right, Zabuza enough talk.
Time to finish it.
But it won't be with
Sharingan imitations
of some other ninja's tricks.
No-- it's time I introduced
you to my own Jutsu.
[crackling]
-Lightning blaze!
-His chakra's so
strong, it's visible!
He holds it in his hands.
-I won't allow you
to kill Tazuna.
He's a brave man
with a noble dream.
The bridge he's
building is the hope
of this land, and
all its people.
You're like a disease.
By attacking one, you infect
all, and you don't care.
That is not the
way of the shinobi.
-You're right.
I don't care.
These useless little people
and their petty, little dreams.
Why should they matter to me?
I have a dream of my own!
[crackling]
-But to have a dream, you
need to have a future.
You don't.
Your future's all
used up, Sabuza.
-Go on.
Finish it.
Kill me.
[grunting]
Why do you hesitate?
- [panting]
I thought you wanted
to be a mighty warrior.
[grunting]
-That's not what it's about.
Do you really believe that's
all there is to it, just
fighting and killing
until there's
only one man left standing?
There's a lot more to
being shinobi than that,
and there are other ways
of showing your strength
than just by beating
someone in battle.
-I had a feeling all along,
from the first moment
we met in the woods.
We are a lot alike.
-Huh?
-I'm sure you know what I mean.
I'm only sorry that it
must be your hand that
is tainted with
my unworthy blood.
-Sure about this?
And you're positive
that it's the only way?
-Yes.
[grunting]
-The weird thing is, if we
met in another time and place,
I think that maybe we
could have been friends.
-Yes, that's right.
Hold fast to your dreams.
-This is for Sasuke,
because he also had a dream.
[yelling]
-Thank you, Naruto.
Strike true.
-At last, I think this
blasted fog is lifting.
-Look-- they're standing still,
like they're squaring off.
-Yeah?
I can't see a thing.
-Which one of them's
Kakashi Sensei?
One's moving!
Huh?
[yelling]
-Huh?
-Sorry, Naruto, change of plan.
[grunting]
-I'm not ready to die quite yet.
-Is this the end?
[yelling]
[panting]
[screaming]
[inaudible]
-Oh!
[gasps]
[crackling]
[tinkling]
-Oh.
Oh.
Zabuza.
-So my future is
all used up, huh?
[laughing]
-Wrong again, Kakashi.
-Don't be ridiculous.
You are not going to the
bridge all by yourself.
-I have to go by myself,
because none of the others
will come with me.
I have no choice.
-You shouldn't go at all.
Stop this.
You're only a child.
What do you think you can do?
-You're right.
I am just a kid.
But a kid who knows what it
means to stand and fight.
I'm my father's kid.
-Kaiza.
No, Inari, wait.
-Hmm?
[gasps]
-Huh?
What?
Where'd he go?
Huh?
Hey!
Uh!
The fog's lifting.
Wait, is that him?
[panting]
-What?
I don't get it.
What the heck's going on here?
-Isn't that-- the young
man in the mask, the boy
threw himself in
front of my attack.
He saved your worthless
life, at the cost of his own.
[laughing]
-Well done, Haku.
[grunting]
[shouting]
-Professor Sensei, watch out!
-He attacked right through
the boy to take me down.
I knew I'd found a treasure
when I found you, boy.
You've not only given me my
life, but Kakashi's as well!
[grunting]
-My time here is done, Haku.
Tonight, I cast aside
the land of water.
One day, I will return
and seize this land
and hold it in my hands.
Many things must be done
before that day comes,
and you will help me to do them.
But I warn you, friendship,
comfort, encouragement--
I do not need these things-- nor
should you expect them from me.
-I understand.
I am yours, Zabuza.
I am only an instrument
of your will.
Think of me as a weapon
to be kept at your side
and used as you see fit.
-Well said, child.
[screaming]
[laughing]
-Not bad for having a
corpse in your arms.
-You'll pay for that!
-No, stay out of this, Naruto.
-This is my battle.
Zabuza's mine.
-Naruto?
Naruto!
Over here!
-Sakura.
-So you and Sasuke
are all right?
-Uh, um--
-What's wrong?
Where is Sasuke anyway?
-Uh, uh--
-No.
-Sakura.
-Kakashi, I'd stay
focused if I were you.
[grunting]
-Let me take you to him, Sakura.
As long as we stay
together, you won't
be disobeying your
Sensei's orders.
-Thank you.
-Sasuke?
[gasps]
-Uh!
Oh, his body's cold.
This isn't just one of his
genjutsu tricks, is it?
-Go on.
You don't need to be
brave on my account.
Go ahead and let your
feelings out, Sakura.
It's all right.
-I was the best, aced
every test at the academy--
the perfect student.
-Hmm?
-Did you know there are
more than 100 principles
of shinobi conduct?
I memorized every single one.
I used to love it when they
tested us on them-- gave me
a chance to show
how smart I was.
I remember so clearly
this one exam.
They asked us to explain
the 25th principle.
I got it right, of course.
[sobbing]
A shinobi never shows
his feelings, no matter
what the circumstances.
Feelings are a weakness that
only cloud his judgement
and weaken his sense of duty.
[sobbing]
Sasuke!
-To put such a unbearable burden
on a young girl's shoulders--
if that's the shinobi
way, you can have it!
[sobbing]
[grunting]
[panting]
-Why, why can't I
keep up with him?
[grunting]
I'll split you in half!
-Look at you!
You're falling apart.
I knew you didn't have what
it takes for the long haul.
-What did you say?
-You have no idea
what real strength is.
[panting]
Well, well.
So this is how it
turns out, huh?
Game over.
You lose.
-Uh.
-Huh?
-Now both of your
arms are useless.
What now?
You can't even make hand signs.
[grunting]
-Hmm?
[gasps]
-Did quite a job on
you, didn't he, Zabuza?
You look like
yesterday's sashimi.
I must say I'm disappointed.
-Haku gave his life
for you, and you
act like nothing happened--
not a single tear, no sign
that you feel anything at all.
I knew you were low, Zabuza,
as rotten as they come.
But that-- man, you're
going to pay for that.
Believe it.
I only hope someone else
doesn't get to you first.
-Next time, The
Demon in the snow.