[music playing]
-This is a custom
in which balance
is preserved by
fighting and dying.
In the world of the
Shinobi, that is friendship.
The third exam is
a fight for life
with the pride of your village
and your own dreams at stake.
-Well, he sure convinced me.
-Any test is fine.
Just tell me what the details
of the exam are already.
I can handle anything
you throw at me.
-Very well then.
Now listen closely.
I'm going to tell you
exactly what you'll all
be doing on the third exam.
-Lord Hokage, before you do,
please allow me, Hayate Gekko,
to speak first.
-So be it.
-There's something I
would like all of you
to do before the third exam.
We have to have a
preliminary exam
before we can move
on to the real one.
-Huh?
A what?
-Preliminary?
Just what do you mean by that?
-I'm sorry.
Sensei, excuse me, but I
really don't see the point.
What's this
preliminary all about?
Why can't we just move
on to the third exam?
-Well, you see, the
first and second exams
might have been too easy.
The fact is, we never
expected so many of you
to still be here.
According to the rules
of the Chunin Exams,
a preliminary round can be
held at any stage in order
to reduce the number of
candidates remaining.
-But is that fair?
-It's just that
at this stage, we
have to speed things up a bit.
As Lord Hokage said, a
lot of important guests
will be watching.
We can't afford to
waste their time.
They've come to
see only the best.
So if there are
any of you who feel
you're not in top
physical condition,
now's your chance to--
-Talk about not being in
top physical condition.
-That proctor doesn't
look so good himself.
-Sorry about that.
As I was saying, any of you who
don't feel up to this, now's
the time for you to bow out.
The preliminaries will
be starting immediately.
-Come on, you mean right now?
-We just finished barely
surviving the last exam.
Don't we get a break?
-Man, what a drag.
When do we eat?
-Narrowing the Field:
Sudden Death Elimination!
Well, they pulled a fast one.
But I'm in.
All the way, no matter what.
I gave my word to Kabuto.
-Oh yeah.
The winners will be determined
by one-on-one combat,
sudden death.
So like I said, if there's
anyone who doesn't feel up
to it, now's the time
to raise your hand.
-Does he really think
anyone's going to quit?
-Sasuke?
-Waves of pain, they're
coming sooner and sooner.
-Oh no.
I knew it.
Sasuke, listen to me.
You have got to quit.
-Huh?
-You've been like
this ever since you
tangled with Orochimaru.
And it's getting worse.
It's that mark he
put on you, isn't it?
-Mark?
-You can't deny it, Sasuke.
-I just gave him a
little parting gift.
Sasuke will definitely
seek me out.
He'll desire my power.
-It looks like you're
the only one left.
-Please.
-Huh?
-Please, Sasuke, quit now
before-- I don't know what.
I'm scared.
-Sakura.
-It's just as I feared.
-What do we do with him?
-We take him out of the exam,
hand him over to black ops,
and let them keep him locked up.
We have to keep that
seal under control.
-And he's just going to quietly
go along with all of this, huh?
You really think so?
You're forgetting, he's
of the Uchiha Clan.
-I don't care what
the heck he is.
If he stays, he's a
danger to everyone.
Don't you see?
As he gets stronger,
so does the curse mark.
That thing is feeding
off his chakra.
It's a forbidden Jutsu that
devours the one who bears it.
It's incredible the
kid is still standing.
By now, he should be dead.
Lord Hokage.
-Come on, you know
as well as I do.
We are in no condition
to keep on fighting.
-Shut up, Sakura.
-You think I'm
blind or something?
-Will you please be quiet?
-You think I don't see the
suffering you're going through?
-That's enough, Sakura.
-I'm sorry.
I can't let you
do it to yourself.
I'm going to tell
them about that mark.
Then maybe you'll--
-Hm.
-What the?
-OK.
You got me.
I'm out.
-But Kabuto--
-Kabuto Yakushi of the
Leaf Village, right?
OK.
You can go on and step back.
-Gotcha.
-Kabuto!
Hold on a second!
You can't quit.
I don't get this.
What's going on?
-Pathetic.
-Oh, Naruto.
I'm sorry, but my
body's just too beat up.
I can't hack it.
The fact is, ever since
orientation and that dust up
with the sound
village team, I've
had no hearing at
all in my left ear.
And now to have to put
my life on the line,
to fight again right
away without a break?
I can't do it.
-Seems to me I've
seen that one before.
If memory serves, this
isn't the first time
he's dropped out
before a battle.
What kind of game is he playing?
-Anko.
-Oh, right.
Kabuto Yakushi.
Says here he's failed
six times in a row.
-What do you have
on his background?
-His time at the academy was
not what you'd call impressive.
Average grades.
Took him a full three tries
before he passed the graduation
exam.
As far as the missions he's
carried out since then,
there's been two C
ranks and 14 D ranks.
It's not exactly a battle
record to write home about.
However--
-Go on.
-There's something before
his time in the academy.
-Huh?
-Do you remember the child?
The one who was found after
the Battle of Kikyo Pass?
The only survivor.
-I remember the story.
It was said a
small boy was found
among the enemy dead
on the battlefield.
He was found barely alive
and brought back by a Jonin
from the medical unit.
You're saying this is that boy?
-Kabuto, what do you
think you're doing anyway?
Have you forgotten
Orochimaru's orders?
-I'm leaving all that to you.
What's the problem?
For someone with your abilities,
it should be no trouble.
This is your chance to
prove yourself, Yoroi.
After all, you've always wanted
to take my place, haven't you?
Go for it.
-You may be
Orochimaru's favorite,
but be careful you
don't push it too far.
-Thanks for the advice.
I'll keep it in mind.
-Huh?
-Sorry, Naruto.
Sorry, Sasuke.
Wish I could stick around
and play a little longer.
But if I did that, the old
me might get stirred up.
Can't have that.
Might blow my cover.
Wouldn't be much use
as a spy after that.
Besides, I've
already done my job.
With you here looking after
things, you don't need me,
do you, Lord Orochimaru?
Guess I'll just have to
save my fun for later.
Until we meet again, Sasuke.
Oh, and you too,
of course, Naruto.
-Now then, does anybody
else want to quit?
-I can't let this go on.
I have to tell them.
-Don't you even think of
telling them about this mark.
-I don't get what
you're trying to prove.
Am I supposed to just stand
by and watch you tear yourself
apart?
I can't bear to watch it.
-Then don't watch.
But stay out of it.
This has nothing to do with you.
I told you before.
What I am is an avenger.
For me, this is something
far more than just an exam.
Whether I become a Chunin or not
means less than nothing to me.
Am I as strong as I can be?
All I want is the
answer to that.
I can only find out by fighting
the strongest, the best.
-My name is Gaara of the desert.
-Hey you, over here.
What's your name?
-Accept it.
You have no chance against me.
Your skills are inferior.
-For the moment, we're even.
But if it should happen that
we ever meet again in combat,
I promise you we
won't run or hide.
-And the best of the
best are all here.
This is the path I walk.
Not you or anyone
can change that.
-Oh, Sasuke.
-Man, you don't
know when to quit.
What are you butting your
head up for, you idiot?
It's just because
she cares about you.
-Naruto.
-Huh?
-You're one of the ones
I want to fight the most.
-Huh?
-I'm still concerned about
what all Orochimaru said.
Allow the boy to continue
with the exam for now,
-and we'll see what happens.
-What?!
-But Lord Hokage--
-However, at the first sign
of the curse mark growing
or his power getting
out of control,
he will step in and stop it.
-Right.
-But-- as you wish.
-All right, then.
We will now begin the
preliminary round.
This round will consist of
one-on-one individual combat
at full battle intensity.
This is not an exercise.
There are 20 of you
remaining, so that
means we will need ten matches.
The surviving candidates
from these ten matches
will advance to the third exam.
As for the rules,
there are none.
You will fight until one dies or
concedes defeat or is rendered
physically incapable of
continuing the contest.
Naturally, those
who are losing are
urged to concede defeat promptly
to avoid a fatal outcome.
Furthermore, as proctor,
I'm given a certain amount
of leeway in
judging the matches.
I might occasionally
intervene if a match seems
hopeless to save as
many lives as possible.
Now it's time to reveal what
fate has been chosen for you.
-Open the panel.
-The names of each
pair of opponents
are chosen completely at random.
Before each match,
these names will
appear on the display behind me.
As there's nothing more
to say, let's begin.
In a moment, the names of
the first two opponents
will appear.
YOROI AKADO VS SASUKUE UCHIHA
-Didn't waste any
time, did they?
-I couldn't ask
for anything more.
-No!
Why did it have to be Sasuke?
-All right now.
Those whose names have
been drawn, come forward.
-You have been chosen for
the first match, Yoroi Akado
and Sasuke Uchiha.
Are there any objections?
-None here.
-No.
-Wow, that's it.
All I can do now is watch.
-You better win, Sasuke, if
you ever hope to take me on.
-Something is wrong.
He's acting strangely.
-Could it be the curse mark?
-Sasuke, good luck.
-Now we just sit back
and see what happens.
-The pain won't go away.
-That curse mark
giving you trouble?
-All right then.
Let's begin the first match.
OK.
Everyone other than the
two opposing candidates
will now clear the area and
move to the upper level.
-Hey!
Kakashi Sensei!
-Sasuke.
Don't use your Sharingan.
-So you know about it?
-If that mark on your
neck gets out of control,
your life could be in danger.
-I'm aware of that.
-Just to let you know,
if it gets to that point,
I'll have to step in
and stop the fight.
Good luck.
-Stop the fight?
This thing, it seems to be
responding to my chakra.
Got to try.
Use the last of my chakra.
Sharingan!
[screams]
-Sasuke, please!
Stop using your Sharingan!
Don't do it!
-Every time I use my
chakra, this thing
gets a little stronger.
It gains a little
more control over me.
I've got to fight him without
using my Sharingan,
and even my own
Jutsu is off limits.
Maybe I can make him
laugh himself to death.
-The thing is, Sasuke,
Yoroi's unique skills
are going to be
disastrous for you.
-Whatever.
Let's get on with this.
-Watch yourself, Sasuke.
Don't push it.
-Then if you're ready,
let the match begin.
-Oh, I'm ready.
-So am I.
Already?
-Huh?
-Hey, he got him!
-Really?
-What's happening?
All my strength,
suddenly it's gone.
-Sasuke, no!
-[laughs]
-Sasuke!
-What the-- my chakra,
what are you doing?
-[laughs]
You're just noticing it now?
[music playing]
-It's like fighting with both
hands tied behind my back.
If I try to defend myself, this
mark on my neck will take over.
But if I don't,
they'll call the match
and give Yoroi the victory.
That is, if he
doesn't kill me first.
Either way, my whole purpose
for being here is lost.
I've got to find a way.
I can't let it end like this!
Next time, Bushy Brow's
Jealousy- Lions Barrage
Unleashed!