[theme song]
-Hm.
Breakfast time.
Shadow clone fishing jutsu.
Bombs away.
Ah.
-Well?
Come on, is that it?
I only got three.
Now, go and do it again.
-What!
SASUKE: I could eat
three fish myself.
-Well, if you think it's so
easy, why don't you get wet
and I'll stand on the shore.
SAKURA: Sasuke.
The fire's ready to light.
I could use one
of your fireballs.
-Ugh, I've got to do
everything around here.
-Huh?
You do, huh?
What have I been doing?
The Scroll's Secret:
No Peeking Allowed.
SASUKE: It's already
been four days
since the second exam began.
SAKURA: That's right.
-We're sure not going
to break any records.
And we only have 24 hours left.
-I wonder how many
of the other teams
have already got their
scrolls and finished.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
I wonder when
this fish is going to be done.
I could eat a whale.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): If we
don't get a break soon,
we are finished.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Almost ready.
If I move fast, I bet
I can snag the biggest
one before the others get it.
MAN: What are we doing?
Who are we chasing?
There's probably no one
left in this forest anyway.
MAN: So what do we do?
-You're right.
The other teams must
have all finished by now.
-Yeah, it's been four days.
Anyway, we've been
going since dawn.
No need to kill ourselves.
I'll go and try to
find something to eat.
You guys rest.
-Hey.
-Yeah?
-If I remember right, I
think the other scroll,
it had heaven written on it.
And it was different
from this one
because it had white
around the edges, right?
-I don't know.
I guess so.
I wasn't really paying
too much attention
when they showed them to us.
Anyway, why?
What's the big deal
all of a sudden?
-Ha-ha.
-Whoa.
You're not really thinking--
-We have to face
it, there may not
be anymore heaven scrolls left.
-Well, that's a
cheerful thought.
-Maybe so, but it's true.
Look, you said it
yourself, Sasuke.
This is the fourth day
we've been out here.
That means we've already
used up 80% of the time
we've got to complete the exam.
Only 13 teams can pass
because there are only
13 pairs of heaven
and earth scrolls.
And you've got 26
teams, 78 candidates out
looking for them.
-Huh?
-And if those odds
weren't bad enough,
things have gotten even worse.
Don't forget that creep
Orochimaru burnt the heaven
scroll we had.
-Yeah, I remember.
-The number of complete pairs
of scrolls that could be found
was reduced by one right there.
-Hm?
SAKURA: Not to
mention all the ones
that had been found and secured
by other teams since then.
-Maybe we gave
ourselves too much time
to rest and recover from our
last fight, I don't know.
What I do know is that we've got
to get serious now and make up
for lost time.
The next enemy we face
could be our last chance.
I'm going to get water.
NARUTO: Hey, Sakura!
I know how we can do this
without having to fight anyone.
-Huh?
-Look.
SAKURA: Look at what?
NARUTO: What do you
mean, look at what?
Scrolls.
I've got tons of them.
You know, manuals of
ninjutsu and stuff like that.
We could change one of
these to look exactly
like the heaven scroll.
-Stop, don't even.
Even if you cold
fake the outside,
how do you fake
what's written inside?
You couldn't know
without reading it,
and that's against
the rules, idiot.
-I've got it all figured out.
I think these things have a
secret code written in them
that only makes sense if
you put them both together.
Yeah.
And that secret code
is like the password
you need in order to
get into the tower
at the end of the exam.
Get it?
-All I get is that
you're a nimrod.
-Huh?
-We've never even had a heaven
scroll, so how in the world
are we going to fake
what's inside it?
-Uh.
Oh.
-The next brilliant
idea you get, how
about keeping it to yourself?
We got enough problems.
-But wait.
We do have a clue to what's
inside the heaven scroll,
the earth scroll.
-You wouldn't.
-It's our only chance.
I'm going to open
and read this scroll.
-Ah!
-Naruto!
Can't you get it
through your empty head?
We're expressly forbidden
from opening the scrolls
before arriving at the tower!
-I know.
But if we don't do anything,
we'll never make it.
MAN: Careful.
Take it slow.
It might be booby-trapped
or something.
-Yeah, I've thought of that.
[screaming]
-Hey.
What's wrong?
Guys?
Hey, what's the
scroll doing there?
What happened?
What did you guys do?
-I wouldn't do
that if I were you.
-Huh?
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): An enemy.
I can't believe you, guys.
KABUTO: If I hadn't
come along when I did.
-Sorry, Sasuke.
-I'm [mumbling].
-There have been others
who have broken the rules
and tried to peek
at the scrolls.
I've seen what happens to them.
They're protected by
a powerful hypnosis
jutsu, a kind of
booby-trap for anyone
unwise enough to
try to read them.
It will knock you senseless.
And by the time you wake
up, the exam is over.
-Kabuto, right?
We met at the registration.
What are you doing wandering
around all by yourself?
KABUTO: Don't worry, I'm
not after your earth scroll.
-I guess not.
I suppose if you were, you would
have just swiped it from Naruto
when you had the chance.
So you're looking for a
heaven scroll too, huh?
-Not really.
You see, I already
have them both.
I had a run of luck.
I was just on my
way to the tower
to wait for my
teammates to show up.
So if you'll excuse me.
-Hold it.
I'll fight you for it.
MAN: What a lucky break.
-You'll fight me for it?
-But Sasuke.
-Hold on a second.
Is this a joke or what?
-Are you serious?
-Perfectly.
Sorry, but I don't
have time to play nice.
-Back off, Sasuke.
In case you've forgotten,
this guy saved our butts.
-Naruto has got a point.
We don't want to be
ungrateful or anything.
-Shut up.
-But Sasuke.
-It can't be helped.
It's either him or us.
Out here, it's all about
surviving and winning.
Nothing else matters.
-Hm.
You're lying.
-He is?
-Come on, admit it.
For all your tough talk, your
heart really isn't in it.
If it was true, if winning
was really the only thing that
mattered to you, why openly
challenge me to a fight?
Why announce it and
put me on my guard?
Why not just jump me
when my back is turned?
After all, that's
what a ninja would do.
-Hm, that's pretty deep.
KABUTO: It's OK.
Actually, I admire you for it.
So here's what I'll do.
I'll show you the path
you should follow.
But let's go, it's best
we get out of here.
The smell of that
cooking fire is
going to draw every wild
beast in the forest.
And not only animals,
but the competition, too.
Hm.
SASUKE: You think
there are still
other candidates out here?
KABUTO: Oh, yeah.
Just think about it.
What do you think is
the most efficient way
of finding the scrolls in
an area as large as this?
To go searching through
the forest for them?
SAKURA: Uh, no.
KABUTO: No.
You wait for them
to come to you.
The tower at the center of
the forest is the goal, right?
So on the last day of
the exam, that area
will be crawling
with teams converging
on the tower with their scrolls.
-Oh, yeah.
I get it, like an ambush.
So we just head for the
tower, find a hiding place,
and when a team comes
along with a heaven scroll,
we jump them and take it.
KABUTO: That's one
third of the problem.
SAKURA: Huh?
-You guys aren't going to be
the only ones thinking of this.
Every other team
that's lacking a scroll
will be lying in
wait just like you.
-So what?
The more the merrier, I say.
Whoever they are, we'll
take care of them.
Wouldn't want this
to be too easy.
That wouldn't be any fun.
OK, so we grab
someone else's scroll
and keep those losers
from grabbing ours.
And bingo, we'd pass
the second exam.
KABUTO: That's two
thirds of the problem.
SAKURA: Well, at least
we're getting closer.
What else?
-Well, there's bound to
be some collectors lurking
around at the finish line.
-Collectors?
-Even when you think
you're home free,
you can't relax your
guard for an instant.
This kind of exam always
brings them out-- collectors.
They gather extra
sets of scrolls
to use for various ends.
For example, to bribe their way
out of unexpected situations,
or to provide their village
mates with the scroll
they're lacking.
Some steal them to keep
candidates from rival villages
from passing, or
to help out teams
from their own
village who couldn't
find the scrolls on their own.
Others steal them for
their own dark purposes.
They'll hang onto them to use
against the stronger teams
farther down the line.
They'll be there all right,
and they're bad news.
The closer you get to the
tower, the more likely
you'll be to run into them.
-I see.
And I think I'm
starting to understand
why you brought us
along with you, hm?
It's because you're
frightened, aren't you?
-You bet I am.
There's the tower, and that
means the end is in sight.
Now comes the hard part.
-Well, it's about time.
Bring it on.
-There's someone back there.
Ha, false alarm.
It's just a centipede.
-Just a centipede?
That creepy thing's
as big as a bus.
-Hey, Naruto.
-Hm?
-Do us a favor and try to
keep it down to a dull roar,
will you?
-Hm?
-See, the whole idea is not
to let anyone know we're here.
If you go crashing through
the forest like an elephant,
you're going to draw
collectors like flies.
We want to find them
before they find us.
-Oh, yeah.
I see your point.
KABUTO: Take it slow and quiet.
Let's use all the
time we've got left.
-OK.
-Right.
-Got it.
-Hm, that's more like it.
OK, we're getting closer.
-A trap, huh?
-Yeah.
And it only gets
worse from here on in.
-Hey.
Ah!
Kabuto!
KABUTO: Well, that was close.
NARUTO: A substitution jutsu.
-Like I told you, it only
gets worse from here on in.
SAKURA: For crying out loud.
NARUTO: Sakura.
-How far have we walked?
That tower's not
getting any closer.
-Now that you mention it,
I was thinking that, too.
It's weird.
KABUTO (VOICEOVER): Maybe not.
It would seem
we've been spotted.
Somebody is playing
games with us.
Look.
Ring a bell?
-Huh?
Oh man, no way.
It can't be.
Hey, what's the big idea?
-What's going on?
-Genjutsu.
-That's what it looks like.
And we fell for it completely.
We were so concerned with
not being seen by anyone,
we didn't see we were
walking around in circles.
-What's their game?
-They're probably trying to
wear us down and then strike
when we're frustrated
and physically exhausted.
SASUKE: You mean like
we are right now?
KABUTO: Right.
They'll be coming soon.
[gasps]
-Well, Naruto, you
wanted a fight.
-Hm.
4 against 40.
I like those odds.
[theme song]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Look at all these guys.
It's like a clone convention.
Well, I've got news for them.
They're not the only
ones with a clone jutsu.
You want to see clones?
I'll show you clones.
They think they can
steal our scroll
after all we went
through to get it?
Get real.
I don't care if
there's 400 of them.
By the time I'm
through with them,
they're going to need
400 hospital beds.
Believe it.
Next time, clone versus clone.
Mine are better than yours.
Ya!