[theme music]
NARUTO: "Follow My Lead!
The Great Survival Challenge!"
-Well, I just hope
I don't mess it up.
-I can't wait!
What about you, Konohamaru?
--[chuckling] This
is gonna be fun.
Ha!
NARUTO: No way!
No way!
You gotta be kidding!
-Hmm.
--[growling] I wanna be
sent on a real mission,
not get sent with babysitting.
That's not what I signed up for!
No way, forget it!
-The team assignments
have already
been announced and
posted at the Academy.
-Hey, I'm sorry.
That's not my problem.
Now, I've gotta get
back to my training.
-That's right.
Because you're going to
be hokage some day, right?
-I-- wha?
-I wouldn't have thought that
disappointing those eager,
young kids is something
a future hokage would do.
Being a leader, that's
what this mission is about.
Achieving a goal
while protecting
the lives of the
people on your team.
In fact, of all the
missions I could assign you,
this one's the ideal
training for becoming hokage.
-The deal training?
Really?
-But, if you don't want to do
it, you don't want to do it.
I'll just reassign your team.
-Hey!
Can't you take a joke?
I was kidding!
Joke.
[chuckles] I was only
pullin' your leg,
Grandma Tsunade, that's all!
I mean, come on!
Hokage training?
Like I'd ever miss that!
I was gonna do it
all along. [laughing]
CHOJI (TO HIMSELF): She
played him like a drum.
KIBA (TO HIMSELF):
Man, what a sucker.
HINATA (TO HERSELF): Oh, Naruto.
-All right, then.
Lemme just see who
I've got on my team.
Ugh.
[chuckling]
NARUTO: So, it's you guys, huh?
Hmm?
Hey!
What're you doing over there?
How'd you get out of this?
-Hey, it wasn't my decision,
but I'm glad they made it.
I knew this mission
would be a drag.
-We asked Shikamaru to
help the instructors keep
track of you and the students.
Now this will be an
outdoor training mission
that will take place over
two days and one night.
Your goal is the
great stone face
of Warudakame on the
summit of Mount Takurami.
Now it's important
that all team leaders
stick to the routes indicated
on the map, no deviations.
This is to ensure the safety
of the Academy students
accompanying you.
Along the way, you will
encounter instructors posing
as enemy ninja as well as other
obstacles, It won't be easy,
but you Academy students
will be fine, just as long
as you obey your team leaders.
You should see the great
stone face of Warudakame
after you've gone
about 80 kilometers.
There's a secret document
hidden there, and only one.
You see, this is a competition.
The team that
finds that document
and brings it back
safely to the village
will have successfully
completed the training.
NARUTO: You hear that?
That's us he's talking about!
OK, team!
Let's hear it!
You guys ready?
EVERYONE: Yeah!
-One of the most important
rules of survival in the wild
is learning how to
live off the land.
For instance, shinobi's
beef sashimi grass.
You can find it
all over this area.
You can eat it raw, which comes
handy if you're really hungry.
Om nom.
-Really?
-Awesome!
-Cool!
-OK, team!
Fan out and search for food!
[cheering]
-Here we are.
Heh.
Chow down.
-Hold it!
That's shinobi's blow
fish sashimi grass.
That stuff is poisonous.
[CHUCKLING[ If you
look carefully,
the shape of the leaf is
a little different, see?
-Oh yeah.
-Ha ha.
Everyone be careful
of what you pick, OK?
EVERYONE: Yes, sir!
-Mmm.
[chuckling]
-And that, my friends, is
the first rule of survival.
Knowing how to
find your own food.
MALE SPEAKER: Isn't going
to a store kinda cheating?
-This is so disappointing.
-I'm getting a bad feeling.
NARUTO: [singing to himself]
-That's funny.
-The geology in the
area throws magnets off,
makes it difficult
to use a compass.
I see you're wearing a watch.
-Uh, yes, sir.
NEJI: Look at it.
Draw an imaginary line bisecting
the angle between 12 o'clock
and the current position
of the hour hand.
Good.
Now if you point that
imaginary line toward the sun,
south will be at 12
o'clock, approximately.
Have you all got that?
EVERYONE: Yeah!
Got it.
-Hmmm, uh.
Uh.
Huh.
Mmm.
-You thinking what I'm
thinking, Konohamaru?
-We're in trouble,
that's what I'm thinking.
He's definitely got us lost.
-Yeah, definitely.
NARUTO (TO HIMSELF): Man,
this is embarrassing.
Wait, there!
That's the way!
Come on, team!
Forward to victory!
FEMALE SPEAKER: You--
you sure that's the way?
--[sighing] Well, that was
tougher than I thought,
but I knew we'd get there.
-Get to where?
We're nowhere!
We're back where we started!
FEMALE SPEAKER: We were
counting on you, Naruto,
and you really let us down!
-Hmph.
OK, if you're so
smart, you try it.
-Sure!
Give it here.
Come on, it's that way.
[laughing nervously] OK, I
guess it wasn't that way.
-Hey, what's wrong, Konohamaru?
You lost or what?
Ugh.
-What's the matter?
Don't you know
how to read a map?
Let me try it.
-Sure, OK.
Knock yourself out.
-Hmm.
Let's see.
It's this way, obviously!
Boy, you guys are helpless.
-Great.
Right back where
we started again.
-Wah!
We're lost!
We're doomed!
We'll never get
out of here alive!
-Guess I'll try.
Heh.
For what it's worth.
I don't feel so good.
Aaugh.
-Ahh!
-We're sure off
to a great start!
-Good job!
Everyone OK?
EVERYONE: Yes, sir, Lee-sensei!
--[gasping] What
did you just say?
EVERYONE: Why, yes,
sir, Lee-sensei!
LEE: Lee-sensei!
The sound of it!
Music to my ears!
This is the power of
youth, I can feel it!
Forward, men!
Forward into the setting sun!
EVERYONE: Yes, sir, Lee-sensei!
LEE: Let its golden rays shimmer
in the sweat of your efforts!
EVERYONE: Yes, sir, Lee-sensei!
-Ah.
They finally made it!
All right!
It's time we put Naruto
and his team to the test.
[gasping]
IRUKA: Listen up, Team Naruto!
Let's see what you've
learned so far!
Attack!
-All right, guys!
Formation One, hurry!
Sexy Jutsu!
[poof]
-I've never known a man who
could resist this jutsu.
Wahh!
-Knock it off, you idiot!
[poof]
--[chuckling] Leave
it to us, Naruto!
-We'll show you how
it's done. [laughing]
-We've got a whole
new formation.
ALL: It's a cheesecake Jutsu!
[poof]
-Fashion model, yoohoo!
-Movie star, yoohoo!
-Tanning salon
receptionist, mmm.
ALL THREE: Cheesy,
cheesy, cheesecake!
-[burbling] Ahhh!
-Nicely done, guys!
It really looks like you're
starting to get the hang of it.
You just need to work on
perfecting your va-va-voom.
[clang]
-Ahh!
-Sheesh.
I keep thinking that one
of these days, Naruto,
you're gonna grow up.
-Hey, Iruka-sensei.
-Yeah?
What is it?
-I got a report from
the weather observatory.
[thunder cracking]
-Ahh.
It's nice and warm in here.
Boy, it sure was a good thing
we stopped and got ready ahead
of time.
-We'd be out there right now,
getting soaked and freezing
if we hadn't listened to you.
-A ninja always keeps
an eye on the weather.
Now do you see how
important it is
to be ready to take precautions
before any trouble starts?
-Yeah.
[giggles]
[thunder cracking]
-Ahhh!
NARUTO: Get a grip, Moegi.
And pull out that tent flap.
Hurry!
[thunder cracking]
-Ahh!
I don't wanna do this anymore!
-This isn't just about
you, now come on!
Get a hold of the tent!
-I don't-- wahhh! [crying]
-Are they sure about this?
-Yeah, it's a big one.
And it's making a bee line
straight for the village.
-Terrific.
Now they tell us!
-The word from the
observatory was probably
delayed due to the storm.
-Well, I guess
that's that, then.
We're calling off the exercise.
Tell the teams to return
to the village at once!
-Right.
[thunder cracking]
MOEGI: I don't get it.
Why'd we pack up the tent?
KONOHAMARU: I don't remember
this trail on the map.
In fact, is this even a trail?
Where are we going, Naruto?
Why are we doing this?
-We Don't have time to rest.
We've fallen to far
behind the others.
This is the only way we're
ever going to catch up.
-Huh?
You mean we're--
-Yeah.
We're going off the map and
we're gonna take a short-cut.
EVERYONE: Ahh!
-Uh, are you sure about this?
[thunder cracking]
[rain pouring]
--[breathing heavily] Hey,
there's no point in taking
a short-cut if you
guys don't keep moving!
KONOHAMARU: Are you crazy?
We haven't learned how
to walk on cliffs yet.
-That's right.
We don't learn how to master
chakra control until we're
seniors!
-Oh, come on!
A person can do
anything if you just
put your heart and soul into it.
Now let's go!
-Easy for him to say.
[wind gusting]
-Whoa!
-Hang on!
-Ahhh!
-I thought I told you
to zip that tent shut!
MOEGI: Let go,
Konohamaru, let go!
KONOHAMARU: If I let
go, it'll blow away!
NARUTO: Hold on.
Let go of the tent!
-I can't!
It's caught!
Oh!
-OK!
-Nngh!
I can't hold on any longer!
[shing]
-Wahhh!
-Oh, man.
That was a little
too close for me.
MALE SPEAKER: We've called
back all the teams camped
near the foot of the mountain.
-All right, That's good.
Then that leaves Naruto's team.
MALE SPEAKER: Iruka-sensei!
-Huh?
-I found one of their backpacks
left on an unmarked trail.
-Naruto!
You wouldn't, would you?
[thunder rumbling]
FEMALE SPEAKER: What
are we gonna do now?
We lost our tent, our
packs-- everything.
-It doesn't do us any
good to complain about it.
-Listen, you!
If you hadn't gotten your
foot stuck in my backpack
and nearly got me killed--
-Hey, whaddya mean?
If I hadn't, we would
have been blown away!
-Now, now.
Come on.
Let's not fight with each other.
-It's all because of you, Udon.
If you'd closed that
zipper like you were told--
-Yeah, I know.
-It's no one's fault.
We're all on the same team.
-It's your fault really.
You're the one who
led us off the map
on this wild goose chase!
-Yeah!
Konohamaru's right!
-Hang on.
-The only reason we had to
take that stupid short-cut
in the first place is because
you got completely lost!
-Who got lost?
-What, are you gonna
try and deny it?
-Well, you guys are the ones who
led us around in a big circle!
-We're not supposed
to be leading!
You are.
-A wise guy, huh?
-Stop it!
You're both acting silly.
-Stay out of this!
-I will not!
[stomachs growling]
-Ugh.
-I'm too hungry to fight.
What do you say we call a truce?
[rain pouring]
MALE SPEAKER: This
is where I found it.
IRUKA (TO HIMSELF): Naruto!
Can't that little fool
ever follow instructions?
The wind would have carried
from somewhere, right up there.
Come on, Shikamaru.
Let's find them.
-Right.
-That's it?
You need boiling water
to eat this stuff!
-The cake's the only thing
that doesn't require cooking.
-Not even a cracker.
-Will you guys stop complaining?
-This is supposed to
be survival training!
And you bring food you
have to make in a kitchen?
Yeah, what's the point of that?
-Careful, or I won't share
any of this with you.
[gasping]
[clink]
[stomachs growling]
KONOHAMARU: I want the biggest
piece, that's all I know.
MOEGI: I'm gonna
get the biggest one!
UDON: Please cut me one.
Please cut me one!
-Huh?
-Eat up, everyone!
-But, that's not right!
-How come you cut
it in threesies?
-You forgot about you.
Aren't you gonna have some?
-I was thinking about
back in the day when
I went without food one
time because I messed up
in my training.
Kakashi-sensei was mad because
my team had botched a mission.
We hadn't been pulling together.
Ahh!
How are we supposed to know
why you picked three people?
We didn't make the rules!
KAKASHI: It's so basic.
Teamwork!
NARUTO: I finally got
what he was talking about.
A ninja can't just think about
himself and being the best.
You've got to think
about your comrades
and what's best for the team.
-Here,
-Sakura?
-You sure, Naruto?
--[laughing] I'm not that
crazy about cake, anyway.
I'll just hang here
and-- [stomach growls]
-Oh.
-Your tummy doesn't
seem to agree with you.
-Why'd you bring it
if you don't like it?
-Here, come on, Naruto.
Eat up!
[laughs]
-The footing's treacherous!
Watch your step, Shikamaru!
-Got it.
IRUKA: What the devil
was he thinking,
leading those kids up here?
SHIKAMARU: Thanks a lot, Naruto.
Just what I wanted to be
doing on a night like this.
[water dripping]
-It looks like it
couldn't have been
very long ago that they left.
--[sighing] I'll say
this for Naruto.
He keeps you on your toes.
-Eyes on the prize, gang!
We're almost there!
-Not so fast!
We can't keep up
with you like that.
-It was a mistake
sharing our food!
We should have let him starve!
-Ooh.
-What's wrong, Udon?
-Come on, or you'll
get left behind!
-Ugh, I've got a feeling.
Something's wrong.
-Huh?
[rocks crumbling]
-Ahhh!
-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
[poof]
-Nngh!
Don't just stand there!
Get out the way!
-OK!
To the right, everyone!
-Hurry!
I can't hold this thing forever!
[rocks crumbling]
-Naruto!
-Naruto, you OK?
-Hang in there, all right?
-What do we do, Konohamaru?
-We're gonna go
help him, what else?
-Yeah, but-- it looks
like the whole mountain's
about to come down!
-Then we've got to hurry up.
Come on, you two!
Let's do it!
[thunder cracks]
-Ahh!
-Oh!
Look, he's awake!
He's awake!
[wind gusting]
-Ahhh!
-Nngh.
Whoa.
I sure am lucky I fell
into this gap in the rocks.
-Don't worry, Naruto!
We're coming!
-Don't be an idiot!
Get out of here!
-You know, he
could have a point.
-We can't do this alone.
Maybe we should go for--
-No way!
Didn't you hear what he said?
We've got to act like a team!
And Naruto's one of
our team, isn't he?
-Konohamaru, that's-- Forget it!
There's nothing you can do!
Instead of saving
me, you'll only
end up bringing this whole
mountain down on top of you!
-What's the matter, Naruto?
Have you forgotten what
you told us last time?
-A person can do anything--
-If you put your
heart and soul in it!
-Did I really say that?
-OK, ready, Team Konohamaru?
Forward to the rescue!
-Yeah!
-Ahhhh!
[rocks crumbling]
-Be careful, you guys!
-Toss him over,
but easy does it!
-Just hurry.
Nngh.
[grunting]
-You did it!
Way to go!
Just don't drop it.
All together now, over the side!
-On three, guys!
-One, two, aaugh!
-Yeah!
-We did it, we did it!
-We can move
mountains! [laughing]
--[sighing] Glad to be
out of that tight spot.
IRUKA (FROM BELOW): Naruto!
Are you all OK?
NARUTO: Iruka-sensei!
Shikarmaru!
IRUKA: Naruto!
Above you!
[rocks crumbling]
-Ahh!
-Multi-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
[poofing]
-Down the mountain,
as fast as you can!
-Ahhh!
[crashing]
-Naruto, watch out!
-Nngh.
-Is he alive?
-Rasengan!
[explosion]
[poof]
-Well, that's typical.
He's not happy unless he's
giving people a heart attack.
-Nice, Naruto!
That was really cool!
-Whoa.
Glad that's over.
-You said it!
[chuckles]
TSUNADE: So, who's going to
tell me how this happened?
-Well, you see,
it was like this--
-It was all on account of
our team leader, ma'am.
It was entirely his idea.
He took a short-cut
that was not on the map,
even though that was contrary
to the rules of the exercise.
-We tried to make
him see that this
was both dangerous and wrong.
-But he did it.
-Naruto insisted on going
ahead no matter what.
-Huh?
The verdict seems
to be unanimous.
Have you any last words, Naruto?
-You rehearsed that!
[laughing]
-That's not what I
meant by team work!
Thanks a lot.
-Naruto!
-Not another lecture!
I can't take it!
-Don't you dare!
Where do you think you're going?
Naruto!
[theme music]
NARUTO: Out of the
wilderness, he came.
Tall and thin as a whip cord!
A bounty hunter armed with
two wakasashi blades and eyes
cold as steel.
His target?
The master thief, Gosunkugi.
His methods?
Ruthless!
But what the
sidewinder doesn't know
is that another
hombre is already
hot on the master thief's trail.
Me!
And I always get my man!
Next time, "The Bounty
Hunter From the Wilderness!"
[theme music]