[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Sasuke?
No.
Who is he?
The same Sharingan as Sasuke's.
-Hmph, hard to believe
that such a child carries
the Nine-Tailed Fox.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
How does this guy
know about the Nine-Tailed Fox?
-Naruto, you're coming with us.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Roar, Chidori!
Brother vs. Brother.
It's him.
He's here.
-Big brother, do you think
you could help me out
with my shuriken jutsu
after school today?
-No, I can't.
I'm busy.
Why don't you go ask
father to help you?
-Aw, come on.
You're better at the shuriken
jutsu then father is.
I mean, even I can see that.
Big brother, why do you always
treat me like such a pest?
-I'm sorry, Sasuke.
Some other time, OK?
[grumble]
-Hm?
-I don't have time
for this today.
-You're always doing this to me.
You jab me in the forehead and
then say, "I'm sorry, Sasuke."
And you never have time.
It's always the same story.
Father?
-Hm?
-How come-- how come big brother
never pays any attention to me?
-Your brother's always
been a little strange, son.
He has a hard time dropping
his guard around other people,
letting them in.
-What do you mean?
-I don't know.
Even I can't read him.
And I'm the boy's father.
That kid.
-K, here's your lunch, Sasuke.
And as for your
shuriken practice,
I can help you work on it
when you get home if you want.
-It's not just practice.
It's actual training.
See you later.
-Good morning, Sasuke.
Heading off to
school now, are you?
-Uh huh.
-I saw your brother earlier.
He's grown into such a man.
He's an excellent
shinobi, isn't he?
Graduating the Academy
at the age of seven,
and first in his class.
And he was a Chunin
at 10, wasn't he?
-Yeah, and he could use
Sharingan by the time
he was eight.
-That's right.
How could I forget?
That boy is the pride
of the Uchiha clan.
No doubt about it.
What about you, Sasuke?
How old are you now?
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): I'm the
same age as my brother when he
graduated, and I'm--
-What's the matter, child?
-Honey, stop talking nonsense
to the boy, will you?
-What do you mean, dear?
-Sasuke, both you and Itachi
are of the Uchiha clan,
the brightest gem of
the Hidden Leaf Village.
Have faith in yourself.
Some day, you'll be an
outstanding shinobi, just
like Itachi.
-See you later.
-Just do your best.
-Study hard now
and you'll do fine.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): It's true.
I come from the Uchiha
clan, just like my brother.
I won't lose to him.
I'm so late.
What was that?
I could've sworn there
was someone there.
The lights-- it's too early
for everyone to be in bed.
What is this?
Wh-- what is going on?
What is happening?
Uncle?
Auntie?
Oh, no, father and mother.
-Father?
Mother?
Are you guys here?
[clattering]
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
Somebody's in here.
Move.
-Father!
Mother!
Big brother.
Itachi.
Father and mother are
both-- I don't understand.
Who could do all this?
What a sec, what are you--?
Oh no, what have you done?
-Foolish little brother.
I almost pity you.
Mangekyo Sharingan.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
I can't move my legs.
[screaming]
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
Stop it, Itachi,
why are you showing me all this?
Why?
Why did you do this, brother?
No!
Auntie!
Uncle!
Father!
Mother!
Stop it, Itachi!
Father and mother!
No!
[screaming]
-Why?
Why did you do this?
Itachi, why?
-To test the limits
of my ability.
-To test your ability?
That's why you did this?
You're telling me that that was
the reason that you butchered
every single member of our clan?
-It is of great importance?
-What are you saying?
You're out of your mind!
[gasps]
[groans]
[whimpering]
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): I'm scared.
I'm scared.
[crying]
-Please, I don't want to die!
Please, don't kill me.
-You're not even worth killing.
Foolish little brother, if
you wish to kill me one day,
foster your hatred
and despise me.
Surviving in such an
unsightly manner as this.
By all means, flee.
Cling to your wretched life.
Why don't we take a walk?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): These
guys look like the real deal.
-Hey, Itachi, it'll
be a pain in the neck
if this kid makes a run for it.
Maybe I ought to chop
off a leg, just in case.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Say what?
-Right.
-It's been a long time--
-Hm?
-Sasuke.
-Itachi Uchiha.
-Itachi Uchiha?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): That guy
looks exactly like Sasuke.
-Well, the Sharingan.
And he looks an
awful lot like you.
Itachi, who is this kid?
-He's my younger brother.
-That's strange, because
the way I heard it,
the whole Uchida clan
was wiped out by you.
-Itachi Uchiha, I hope
you're ready to die.
I'm going to restore my clan,
and destroy a certain someone.
He's still out there.
My brother.
I promised myself I'd stay
alive until I killed him.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
This is who he
was talking about-- the
one he wanted to kill.
-It's just as you said, brother.
I've fostered my hatred
for you all this time.
I've lived my life for
one single purpose--
to see you die!
It ends here!
-Sasuke!
-Chidori?
-Enough!
You're dead!
Die!
-I-- I don't believe it.
He brushed off Sasuke's
attack like it was nothing.
We've got trouble.
I gotta do something.
-Ah, the air is
ripe with chakra.
This must be it-- the
power of the Nine-Tails.
-Enough.
[bone cracking]
[screaming]
-Sasuke!
All right, that's it.
Ninja art summoning--
-Too slow.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I
can't feel my chakra.
Damn it.
What the hell is going on?
-Sorry, kid.
My blade, Sharkskin, cuts
through chakra and devours it.
We don't need the hassle
of this kid whipping out
any more jutsu.
Forget the legs.
Maybe I ought to start off
with those arms of his.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Damn
it, why isn't it coming?
-You're wasting your time.
[clang]
-What the--?
JIRAIYA: You two don't
know me at all, do you?
Should have done your homework.
Jiraiya, the Toad Sage falls
victim to no woman's charm.
Rare beauty is dropped for
me like blossoms in a storm.
It isn't in my nature to be
duped by the wiles of women.
When you reach the
stature I have,
the ladies kneel and
worship at your awesomeness.
[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Sasuke, look out.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
Naruto, stay out of it.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Yeah,
but Sasuke needs my help.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
Naruto, it is not
for you to get involved here.
It is your duty to only
bear witness to this battle.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Huh?
What do you mean?
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
This is his fight.
He must bear the
burden of alone.
It is everything he
has struggled for.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next
time, Hate Among the Uchihas--
the Last of the Clan.