[theme music]
-Naruto, wait!
-I don't wanna wait!
-I'm giving the orders.
You can't just run
off on your own.
-So you want me to just
let Sumaru get away?
-You know, Sumaru did have
a strange look in his eye,
back there.
-It's pretty obvious he went
to get his revenge on Akahoshi.
-If he raises a hand
against the village chief,
not only will he be
ostracized from his people,
but he will probably
lose the fight.
Poquito, wait!
-Mother!
Not now.
You're finally together.
Mother, don't go.
-Hey!
What's the big idea?
-Shh!
You can't run off
when you feel like it.
-But something really
weird is going on in there!
-He's right.
That many ninja means something
pretty serious is happening.
-It looks like they've mobilized
all the Star Villages' ninja.
-That's why we're going
to hang back and observe,
before we move in.
-Right.
-Sumaru's inside that
training chamber.
-And Sumaru's mom-- is she OK?
No way!
-[gasp]
-Sumaru.
-So do we really have to go
in there, and finish him off?
-He's only a little kid, sir.
Maybe we should let
the whole thing slide.
-That boy is a danger
to our village.
Letting him live is not
a risk we can afford.
-B-but sir, Sumaru has always
been the most effective Genning
in our entire village!
-Humph, there are more
pawns at our disposal.
We can just train another one.
-Another one?
-I can't listen to this!
Someone needs to do
something, right now!
-No!
You'll stay put!
-Let go of me!
I'm gonna kick that
Akahoshi's butt!
-This matter is a
Star Village concern.
We must stand back and
allow the villagers
to resolve it themselves.
-But there must be something
we can do to help out!
-Exactly!
In fact, I have a good mind
to charge over there and punch
Akahoshi's lights out, myself!
-What the heck are you saying?
You're starting to
sound just like Naruto!
-Are you telling me we're
gonna sit on our butts,
and let them tear
the guy to pieces?
-I am.
Unless the village orders
us to attack Akahoshi,
there is nothing that we can do.
I'm sorry, Naruto, but
our hands are tied.
-Archers!
Take aim!
[gasps]
-Fire!
-For my entire life, I
resented you, mother,
for leaving me all
alone as a child.
But now, I understand why.
I know now what made
you stay away from me
all those years-- Akahoshi!
I will not forgive him!
-Sumaru
[gasp]
-[growls]
-Heh, pretty pathetic
way to go, huh?
(LAUGHING) What are
you talking about?
A young boy and his mother
buried side by side?
There's not a happier
ending than that!
-That chakra's incredible!
-Stop!
-But this jerk's an enemy!
He attacked me out of the blue!
-Huh?
-Ah, you're a Leaf Ninja.
Don't try to act nice with me.
Foreigners are all the same.
They're all trying
to get to our star.
They think if they
get its power,
they can rise above the
other hidden villages.
-So does that mean
that chakra of yours
is fueled by the power
of the Star, too?
I mean, if someone
else had the Star,
wouldn't they have the
same chakra as you do?
-No!
The more power you draw from
it, the more hard work and skill
you need to control it!
-Yeah, but--
-And that's what I'm gonna
do-- nothing but hard work!
I will become the Hoshikage!
-Great!
I can't wait to work with ya!
-Huh?
-'Cause I'm gonna become
Hokage of my village, too!
-You know, you're kinda weird.
-You think?
Take a look at that red one.
Pretty, isn't it?
-Natsuhiboshi-- never alone, the
star on high watches over me.
-How can we do nothing
and just let this happen?
-Sumaru!
Sumaru?
-Listen to me!
If you continue with
the Star training
you're all going to die!
The person who stole the Village
Star-- it was Sumaru's mother!
But the only reason
she did it, was
because she knew was the only
way to protect you from it!
-Lord Akahoshi?
-Is it really true that the
Star training will kill us?
-Don't tell me you all
honestly believe this nonsense!
The only people who cannot
withstand this training are
the ones who don't love
this village enough!
Those with enough
loyalty to the village
will become true shinobi.
And one day, our humble
land will finally
surpass those of the five
great hidden villages!
-Either Hokuto or
Lord Akahoshi--
I don't know which one
--is telling us the truth.
-Misura!
-What's he doing?
He's in no condition to--
-Everyone!
Please, wait!
Listen to me.
There's something that all
of you here need to see.
-Oh, Misura.
-Wh-- what is all that?
-What happened to him?
-Is that an effect
of the Star training?
-That's horrifying!
-Lord Akahoshi, you
know that my heart
is filled with pride
for the Star Village.
The incredible pain I was in?
I endured it for
the Star training.
How?
How can you say I
failed, because I
don't love this village enough?
-Misura!
-There's no way he's lying.
An innocent child whose body
has been through all that?
-This must be the reason the
third Hoshikage prohibited
the Star training from
continuing for so long.
He was worried that
this might happen.
-Maybe we've been
wrong this whole time.
We got so carried away trying
to make this village great,
that we were led
down the wrong path.
-You weak little loser!
Your lies will cause the
downfall of this village!
-No, Akahoshi, don't do it!
-Those kids aren't traders, sir!
-For goodness sake!
They're just children
from our village!
-We won't let this happen!
-You dare betray our village?
-Lord Akahoshi, I'm sorry,
but I won't follow you
blindly any longer!
-Me too!
-And me.
-I'm with them!
-They have turned their
backs on their own people!
They have betrayed us.
Execute them all!
-Lord Akahoshi,
have you gone mad?
-You would have us wipe
out all of the children?
That's horrific!
The village would
have no future!
-Sir, please.
I think you've
taken this too far.
-Perhaps, you should
listen to your people,
and back down for the moment.
-Keep your mouth shut!
You have a lot of nerve
playing the innocent!
You have just as much blood
on your hands, as I do!
-Stop, sir, don't!
Don't you say another word!
-Akahoshi, whose
blood do you mean?
-We should take
pride in our Star!
It sets us apart
from all others.
I couldn't stand by and
allow some foolish leader
to prevent our village from
ever using our strongest weapon!
-You mean--!
So you killed the
third Hoshikage?
-Of course!
That explains the mysterious
circumstances around his death!
-What do you have to say
about this accusation?
-Answer the charges, and
then accept your fate!
-Yes, it was the
three of us, who
assassinated the
third Hoshikage!
We had to do it!
It was the only way we
could save the village!
-You've gone mad!
-You're the ones
who betrayed us!
-Traitors!
-Wait, we can explain all this!
-It was his idea.
We just went along with it.
-Shut up, you idiot!
Don't acknowledge anything!
-Lord Akahoshi, we can
no longer recognize you
as village leader.
Our allegiance is not
with you criminals, now.
The heart of this village
is inside those children.
-Everyone, listen!
For the honor of the great
Star Village, let us rise up
and stand together
with the children!
-Yeah!
-Please accept our apologies.
We were completely taken
in by Akahoshi's fast talk
and deceptive ways.
-From this point on, we pledge
that we'll fight with you.
[cheering]
Lord Akahoshi, let's give up.
-It's over, sir.
We're finished.
-Shut up!
I say when we're finished!
-Ah!
Ah!
-Misura!
-Poquito, keep on
fighting for me.
-Don't go!
-Akahoshi!
You can't do as you
please any longer!
-You really think
you can stop me?
-Have you gone
completely insane?
-Akahoshi, you've already lost!
Accept your fate like a man!
-Oh, is that so?
How can I lose, when
I possess the Star?
-The Star?
-With the Star's power, I shall
become the fourth Hoshikage!
[grunting]
[heart beating]
-Such power!
No amount of training
could ever produce
this kind of immense power!
I should've done this from
the start-- made my body
one with the Star!
[evil laugh]
-What is this?
What's going on?
Aah!
-What's happening to him?
-Byakugan!
All of the chakra
from the Star--
it's being poured into
his chakra network,
and causing an overload!
-What?
-Yah!
[yelling in fear] [groans]
[crunching sounds]
[roaring]
[gasps]
[screaming]
-Poquito!
[roaring]
[evil laughter]
[moaning]
-Aah!
-[grunts]
-Ugh!
-Come on, Neji, you've
got to let me fight back!
Hey, Neji!
-Naruto, you cannot.
-I don't care what
our orders are!
I'm gonna go pound
that jerk to pieces!
-Do what you want.
I won't be responsible.
-Right on!
When we get back,
just tell them I
disobeyed you like I always do!
[evil laughter]
-No!
Lord Akahoshi!
-Don't even think about it!
Lucky [inaudible] jutsu!
Aah!
He's strong!
Take this, nut job!
[roaring]
-Aah!
[grunts] He's gonna get it.
--[female voice singing]
Natsuhiboshi, why are you--
-I know that voice.
That sounds exactly
like Sumaru's mom.
What?
[female voice singing] --I
had a sad dream last night.
My eyes are red from the tears
I've shed, swollen as I cry.
Natsuhiboshi, why have
you lost your way?
I'm--
-Sumaru?
[female voice singing]
He can't be
found, though I search all day.
-She must have used the ninja
hakushaku to let her chakra be
controlled even after her death.
It can't be!
She's protecting Sumaru
from beyond the grave.
-Aah!
[female voice singing]
Natsuhiboshi,
why are you so red?
Because I had a sad
dream last night.
My eyes--
-Sumaru's mom.
Hold on, does this mean you're
gonna help me fight this guy?
Yeah!
Let's do it, then!
-Rasengan!
-Impossible!
-Here it goes!
-Aah!
-The assignment was to
protect the village's star.
Yet, you destroyed the very
thing we were hired to protect!
Not only did you completely
fail the mission,
but the damages we'd have
to pay would be huge!
-Aw, come on, grandma!
There was no other way, but
to smash that star thing!
-I was the mission
leader, so it's my fault
for not being able to stop him.
-I am responsible, as well.
-And you should punish
me for this, too.
-Nah, I think we can
let this one slide.
-Huh?
LADY TSUNADE: So far, we've
received no formal complaints
from the Star Village
over the loss.
[sighs]
-In fact, since the culprit who
was behind the whole nefarious
plot turned out to be
the deputy Hoshikage,
and our client--
well, the mission
was canceled altogether.
-Speaking of which, what
happened to that jerk, anyway?
-Apparently, Akahoshi
and his 2 accomplices,
Yotaka and Shiso are being
held in the Star Village, where
they face severe punishment.
-That's good news!
I guess that means the star village
will become peaceful again!
[knock on door]
-What is it?
-Excuse me, Lady Tsunade.
We've completed the
examination of the genin
from the Star Village.
-And--
-With the proper
course of treatment,
they should all make
a full recovery.
-And Misura?
-Yes, he should be
healthy again in no time.
-All right!
So where is everyone?
-They've all been checked out,
and are on their way back home.
-Woo hoo, Naruto, get back here!
This lecture isn't over!
-(CHUCKLING) Never
changes, does he?
-Hey!
Guys!
It's great to see ya, Misura.
Looks like you're
doing better, huh?
-Yeah.
-I'm still not gonna
lose to you, you know.
-What's that mean?
-It means I will become
Hoshikage before you.
Even with the power of
our Star taken from us,
I will turn my village
into the strongest
of the mighty hidden
ninja villages.
-Oh yeah?
There's no way I'll lose!
I'll become Hokage
way before you!
-Shut up!
I'm gonna be first!
-I'll be first, and
that's a promise!
[theme music]
SHIZUNE: Kiba Inuzuka
has escaped with Akamaru!
NARUTO: No way!
Kiba?
-Fine.
Assemble a special pursuit team
for the worst case scenario.
SHIZUNE: Yes, ma'am.
-Hey!
Hold on, isn't that kinda harsh?
LADY TSUNADE: We have no choice.
Public safety must
take precedence!
NARUTO: But Akamaru
is Kiba's partner!
LADY TSUNADE: I'm aware of that!
NARUTO: Then you can't--
LADY TSUNADE: Quiet, Naruto!
I have an obligation to
protect this village.
NARUTO: Next time!
Kiba's Long Day.
[theme music]