[theme music]
KIBA (VOICEOVER):
Where'd other one go?
Boo.
Looking for someone, kid?
Go wash your eyes in that river.
I'll take care of the rest.
A unique ability, I know.
Helps with assassination.
A sharp sense of smell
and a set of claws
aren't gonna be
enough to beat me.
Face it.
You're in over your
head, little dog.
KIBA (VOICEOVER): Akamaru.
Sorry, Akamaru.
We've always been a team,
together, wherever we went.
But I think this time,
we're sunk, old friend.
-My cells are swimming
freely throughout your body.
I can even generate parts
that are solely yours.
In other words, we're
slowly fusing together.
We'll be sharing a body.
-Sharing a body?
-That's right.
I'm going to snuff out
your life as only I can,
by eradicating all the cells in
your body from the inside out.
-I see.
In that case--
-Huh?
-What if I do this?
Then what happens?
-Suicide?
You're crazy!
-It's time for you to die.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): To
Each His Own Battle!
-Are you mad?
What are you doing?
-If we really share
the same body,
I guess you feel whatever
I feel, don't you?
-Damn you.
Invading my opponent's
body has always
the surest way of
avoiding attack.
It's my jutsu's
greatest advantage.
No one before has ever turned
it against me like this.
-It hurts, doesn't it?
Well, come on.
I know one way to stop the pain.
-No!
You fool!
Stop!
-Sorry.
Too late!
-No!
That's not enough
blood for a fatal blow.
Huh?
Where is he?
The little brat!
Huh?
So, he ran away and left
his little doggie behind.
A logical decision, but pretty
coldblooded, even for me.
What?
No, it can't be!
KIBA (VOICEOVER): It's OK.
He's still breathing.
What a relief.
Good boy, Akamaru.
You really gave it your all.
Thanks to you, we were
able to stall the enemy.
We beat him up pretty good, too.
You rest now.
You've done enough, boy.
WOMAN: His name's Akamaru.
-Huh?
Mom?
Sis?
You're taken care of him
from now on, all right?
-Really?
I am?
[barking]
-Nice to meet you, Akamaru.
My name's Kiba.
[barking]
-Gee, thanks a lot, little guy.
[whimpering]
KIBA (VOICEOVER): Seems like
we've been together forever.
Heck of a catch, Akamaru!
All right!
Way to go, little guy.
Here we go!
WOMAN: Stop playing around.
Grow up!
When are you gonna get serious?
-But Mother--
-Listen, Kiba.
Play time's over.
The time's come
for you and Akamaru
to get stronger together.
-I don't know what you mean.
Stronger together?
Akamaru?
[bark]
-That's right, Kiba.
-Atta boy, Akamaru!
You nailed it!
Now that's aerodynamic marking!
Now try it while spinning!
Watch your aim!
Way to go!
Ya hoo!
[barking]
KIBA (VOICEOVER): And we'll
be together for a long time
to come, boy.
I'll see to that.
I'll take better care
of you from now on.
-Cursed brat.
And to think that I was fool
enough to fall for his trick.
I'll kill you!
Hey!
Sakon!
Where are you?
-Yeah, yeah, I hear you.
Stop shouting.
My head's already
beating like a gong.
Brother!
-Right now, all I want
to do is find that brat
and tear him to pieces.
But that will have to
wait, because now it's
time for me to rest.
If you find him or that
mutt, keep them alive.
I'll kill them when I wake up.
Understood?
-You've got a deal, brother.
Only, we'll do the
killing part together.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Gotta
be careful with my attacks.
He just dodges them and
they end up hitting me!
-Now, behold.
The Willow Dance!
-What is this?
-Now you know.
This is my Kekkai Genkai.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Wh--
What the heck is he?
Bones sticking out of
him like a porcupine.
How does he do that?
-Won't be long now.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): He's gonna
use his own bone as a sword?
-It's no use.
This is no ordinary bone.
It's of the highest density.
As hard as tempered steel.
-So what?
I'm still gonna break every
bone in or out of your body.
-You think you know the
limits of my powers, do you?
I have five dances
in my repertoire.
You've only seen one.
-Yeah, whatever.
-All right, if
that's what you want.
Next I'll show you
the Camellia Dance.
-Ha.
-Come.
-What are you waiting for?
Bring it on!
[flute playing]
-Gotcha!
No!
A substitution!
There.
-Gotta get out of here.
KIBA (VOICEOVER): I can
smell them, coming this way.
They're close.
I left a trail of blood
leading right to me!
Well, Akamaru, that trick
bought us some time,
but it looks like I may
have gotten a little carried
away with it.
Well.
That scent.
Wait a minute.
Why?
What the hell would
they be doing here?
I don't know what's going
on, but one thing's for sure.
We gotta beat it-- fast.
No way.
I'm too dizzy.
I've lost too much blood.
Afraid I'm in no better
shape than you are, boy.
Sorry, Akamaru.
[shout]
-Where did the rest of him go?
Huh?
So he's traveling
by water now, huh?
What a clever boy.
-What a drag.
Uh-oh!
-It's over.
There's nowhere
to run this time.
You're trapped like a rat.
-Gotta admit, that wasn't bad.
Timing was perfect.
You got all three of them
right where you wanted them.
That's quite a tricky tune.
Something like that must
take a lot of practice.
-It does, actually.
So you figured out I
was manipulating them
with my flute.
You're not as dumb as you look.
Not that it'll do you any good.
Knowing what I've
been doing isn't
the same as knowing
how to stop me.
-You've got a point there.
I never was very musical.
Just ask my mom and dad.
(VOICEOVER) With that flute,
she can manipulate her buddies
like puppets.
That song's comprised
of sequences
of modulated sound waves,
each sequence controlling
a specific movement.
Great, Shikamaru.
You can analyze it fine.
But what are you going
to do to counteract it?
She's right.
The fact remains I've
got no ear for music.
-No one's ever heard
this song and lived.
Here's the finale,
Ninth Passage.
Demon Revolution.
[flute playing]
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
She changed the tune!
[theme music]
SHIKAMARU: Gotta hand it to her.
She's playing this chess
game like a grandmaster.
With those three
pawns she's summoned,
she's got me outnumbered,
outwitted, and out of position.
I feel like I'm already
down two rooks and a queen.
And with worse to come.
So what now?
Pack it in?
That's be the smart move, but no
one's ever called me a genius.
I gotta wager
everything on this.
NARUTO: Next time, Fake Out!
Shikamaru's Comeback.
[theme music]