[theme music]
NARRATOR: Unforgivable
A total lack of respect.
-So what happened?
It's like a typhoon hit it.
-Yeah.
-Run!
Run for your lives!
-Hey, you there.
What's going on?
Tell me, what are
you running from?
-If you're smart,
you'll run too!
There's a monster up there!
-A monster?
-Now, just calm down.
What kind of monster?
What do you mean?
-A snake!
A huge snake!
It crushed the castle
without even trying.
Well, I'm out of here.
-Wait!
How big a snake?
Hey, our village was
attacked by one too.
Wait!
Don't go.
I know something
about big snakes!
-Naruto, come on.
This could be the same snake.
I'd like a closer
look at this monster.
-You're going to destroy
the Leaf Village?
-Well, what do you say?
-Lady Tsunade!
Don't trust them.
Do not listen to
their sweet words.
Think of your
brother and my uncle.
They wouldn't have
wanted any part of this.
This isn't what they lived for.
It would be a betrayal of them.
A betrayal of yourself.
Have you forgotten
all your dreams?
I know it's not easy.
I know how tempting
it must seem to you.
But wake up, Lady Tsunade!
Open your eyes!
-Shut up, Shizune!
-Don't decide now, but
we'll expect your answer
within the week.
Keep in mind, if
your answer is yes,
this Jutsu requires
two human sacrifices.
It will be your job to
take care of that part.
-What are we doing?
I say we kill them
both here and now.
Come on, Lady Tsunade,
what are we waiting for?
Together we can--
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER):
Lady Tsunade.
-Huh?
-It's true, I may be a
little weak right now.
However, (CHUKLING)
our good friend here
has her own weaknesses
too, doesn't she?
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER):
Of course, he's
one of the Sannin like
Lady Tsunade, so he knows.
-I see you haven't
lost it yet, have you?
Your fear of blood.
KABUTO (VOICEOVER): Hemophobia.
-Come, it's time we
were going, Kabuto.
I look forward to your
decision, Tsunade.
I'm sure it will
be the right one.
[anxious breathing]
-Looks like we're too late.
-Did the snake do this too?
-Let's go, Naruto.
-Uh?
-We're not going to
find Tsunade here.
-Not again, I was hoping
you'd forgotten about her.
MALE SPEAKER:
Welcome, come on in.
-Hey, you, another
round over here.
-It's late.
We should be going,
don't you think?
-Ah.
-Lady Tsunade.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): This
is getting ridiculous.
How many places are
going to drag me to?
I'm starting to think this
old lady doesn't even exist.
-Hm.
Well, in the meantime, we'll
get a bite to eat in here.
-Hey!
What are you talking about?
It's a tavern!
-Yeah, so what?
-You trying to be
a influence on me?
Hello!
I'm underage.
-You idiot, nobody is making
you do anything, all right.
Just have a snack and stay
out of the grownups way.
-If we're just looking to eat--
MALE SPEAKER
(VOICEOVER): Welcome.
-Why don't we just go somewhere
real like a ramen shop.
Why this stinky dump?
-When will you learn?
This is just the
sort of place where
you can pick up information.
Hm?
-Huh?
-Tsunade!
-Jiraiya?
What the-- why are you here?
-Finally, I've been
looking everywhere for you.
Oh, should have known
you'd be in here.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
That is Tsunade?
An old lady, right, pervy sage.
I should have known.
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER):
I can't believe it.
To have met two of the other
Sannin in the same day.
MALE SPEAKER: Here
you go, enjoy.
-It's like a reunion.
All y'all's faces coming
back at the same time.
-You mean Orochimaru.
So what happened?
-Oh, nothing very much.
We said hello, that's about it.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): It
she really a great healer
or did me make that part up too?
-Well, then, why have
you been looking for me?
-I'll cut right to the chase.
Tsunade, in it's
wisdom, the village
has come to the decision to
name you as the fifth hokage.
MALE SPEAKER
(VOICEOVER): Hey, can we
get some service around here?
MALE SPEAKER
(VOICEOVER): All right.
All right.
Coming!
[coughing]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Fifth hokage?
Where did that come from?
What the heck's going on here?
-You heard about
the third hokage.
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER):
The third hokage.
So it's true.
-It was Orochimaru's
doing, right?
I heard about it.
In fact, he told myself.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Orochimaru's doing?
-Hold on a second.
You're saying he's the one
who killed the old man?
Who is this Orochimaru guy?
-He's one of the Sannin, like
Tsunade here and yours truly.
-But then why?
The Sannin are all from
the Leaf Village, right?
Why'd he do it?
-Who's this brat
you've got with you?
-(CHUCKLING) This
is Naruto Uzumaki.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): This
kid is the Nine-Tailed?
-OK, wait a second!
I haven't finished yet.
There's something about
this I'm not getting.
So this guy, you
know he's the one who
murdered the hokage, what
have you done about it?
He's a Sannin and
he's one of you guys.
Why's he still walking around?
Why haven't you caught him?
And, oh yeah, what's
the deal about her
being the fifth hokage?
-Naruto, sit down and shut up.
-Absolutley not.
-Sit down.
Hm.
[chuckle] I'll
say it once again.
I Leaf Village has
made its decision.
They have chosen you
to be the fifth hokage.
So what's your answer?
Do you accept it, Tsunade?
-This time around, I'm going
to grind the Hidden Leaf
Village into dust.
I'm offering to bring
your dear little brother
and your beloved back to life.
-Well, I'm waiting.
What do you say?
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER):
Lady Tsunade.
-Ah.
I don't understand any of this.
-Impossible.
I decline.
-You know, it's kind of funny.
That rings a bell.
I remember you saying those very
words the first and only time
I ever asked you out.
-Ahh!
Would somebody tell
me what's going on?
What the heck are we doing here?
You said we were going to
bring her back to the village
to cure [inaudible]
Kakashi sensei.
You pull this stuff
about making her hokage,
then she goes and refuses it.
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER):
No, she couldn't really
be thinking of accepting
Orochimaru's offer.
-Ah!
-Don't worry, Naruto.
She knows can't refuse.
There can be no one else.
There was no one who contributed
more to the Leaf's victory
in the great war.
She combines unrivaled
skills as a warrior
with the ability to heal others.
What's more, she is the
granddaughter of the very first
hokage, so in heritage
and abilities,
she is the clear and only
choice to be the fifth hokage.
And once she accepts her
destiny, which she will,
then she'll have to come
back with us to the village
and there heal your friends.
You see, it's all been
very carefully thought out
by the highest councils
of the village.
No offense, but
it's not something
an underage genin is
expected to understand.
-You're slipping, Jiraiya.
This apprentice isn't at
all like your last one.
He's a fool with a big mouth.
Funny looking too.
-Oh, yeah?
-Well, to be fair,
it'd be hard for anyone
to measure up to that standard.
The fourth hokage
showed all the signs
of becoming the greatest
ninja in generations,
brimming with talent
and natural ability.
Brilliant, popular,
and to top it off,
nearly as handsome
as his teacher.
-Oh, sure, but that didn't
save him from dying young.
Throwing his life away all
for the sake of the village.
Money's one thing,
a life's another.
To risk your life
against all the odds,
that's a sucker's bet.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
A sucker's bet?
-My grandfather
and his successor,
they were also willing to
die to defend the village.
Well, their both dead all
right, and the village
is no safer than it ever was.
-Sounds to me, you've
changed Tsunade.
I don't know what's happened
to make you like this,
but to say such things out loud?
-Don't forget, I'm not
as young as I look.
The years have taught
me a great deal.
Sarutobi sensei too, he
should have known better.
What did he expect trying
to be a hero at his age?
Hm.
Ha, playing at
hokage, count me out.
It's a fool's game.
-Let me go.
Stop it.
Let me--
-That's enough.
People are looking.
[grunting] Man, let me go!
-Lady Tsunade.
I'm not going to
let her sit there
and make fun of the old man.
No way!
I don't care if she is a lady!
I'll knock that cynical
sneer off her face.
-Are you challenging me?
You've got guts,
if nothing else.
Let's take this outside, kid.
-No, no.
-Ah.
-One of the legendary
Sannin taking
on a snotty nosed gening?
I ought to be ashamed of myself.
Who you calling snotty?
-Oh, stop trying to show off.
-You see this, one finger.
It's all I'm going to
need to take you down.
-Please, don't.
-Well?
What are you waiting for, kid?
-Don't ever under estimate me!
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER):
Lady Tsunade!
-A flick to the forehead?
I'll show her.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Whoa, she's good.
-Hey, kid.
One question before
you pass out.
Tell me, what makes you
so touchy about hokage?
-It's because unlike
you, that's my goal.
Just watch.
Some day I'll be hokage.
Remember this, to be
hokage, that is my dream.
-That boy.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
She let her guard down.
There's no way I can
take her head on.
Now's the time to
use that Jutsu.
Focus.
-Hm.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): What?
-Wait!
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER):
That Jutsu, it's--
[theme music]
-It's been a long time since
we've sat down together,
hasn't it?
-Not nearly long
enough, if you ask me.
-I was just thinking you're even
prettier than you used to be.
-Well, you're not.
I'm still not
interested, you old goat.
-Like women my age are
my cup of tea, anyway.
-You say something?
-No, just reminiscing
about the old days.
The old, old days.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Next time, Inheritance,
the Necklace of Death.
[theme music]