-Master Jiraiya,
I believe in you.
I'm putting all my trust in you.
-The Summoning Jutsu:
Wisdom of the Toad Sage!
-Well, well.
Look at this.
Don't you ever sleep at all?
-Why are you here?
What do you want?
-I was planning on attacking
you while you slept.
If I fight and defeat you
now, then in the next round
I can battle the one I
really want to face, Sasuke.
I already know all
about your sand attack.
I wonder which is faster,
your sand, or my sound.
-When the moon is full.
-Hmm?
-When the moon is
full its blood boils.
-What in the world are you?
-Amazing.
So that's Garra's
true form then, is it?
-Listen.
Is this OK?
He was a sound ninja.
-Yes, it's fine.
He's long since
served his purpose.
-But I thought he was
a guinea pig, intended
to test the power
of that kid, Sasuke.
-What?
Is Kabuto in league
with the sand ninja?
-That's true, or it was.
It isn't necessary anymore.
See the thing is, I was
ordered to seize Sasuke
when he was in the
hospital, but I, well I
failed in that mission.
-Wait, what?
-That's right.
You over-estimate me.
-Are you looking to take me on?
You smart-alecky little brat.
I'll teach you to mess
around with grownups.
-Come on, give me a break.
Don't be so arrogant.
The cards are clearly
in my favor here.
Yes, that's right.
They've discovered that I'm
an agent of the sound village.
-Wait a minute.
If they know who you are
and if people find out
that you're having a secret
meeting here with me,
then the plan to
destroy the leaf village
will be completely ruined.
I thought you were
Orochimaru's right hand man.
But after being
revealed to them,
you just nonchalantly come
here and meet with me?
You're a fool.
-Well, to be exact,
they didn't really
discover what my true
identity was on their own.
I let them find out.
Yes.
I wanted to see just how far
the hidden leaf village would
go when they
discovered the truth.
And even after
they did, I knew it
wouldn't be too late
to seize Sasuke.
-It's a plan that was originally
posed by the sound village
so, if you guys are
going to fail then
we'll have to back
off immediately.
The sand won't make a move
until the last moment.
This is the will
of the Kazekage.
-This can't be!
-Very well.
This is the plan that
you are to carry out.
-OK.
-And remember, make
sure you tell them
about this plan as
soon as possible.
-Yes, I know.
-All right, then I'll be going.
-To think our ally
the sand village
has a secret pact with
the sound village.
I must tell Oro Kagay.
-One more thing.
I'll take care of
our little spy.
-No, wait.
I will handle this.
As a gesture of faith
in our allegiance,
the least we sand ninja can
do is lend a helping hand.
Besides, it's just one
little spy, it'll be easy.
-Well, well.
What do we have here?
If it isn't the exam proctor.
What in the world
do you think you're
doing, coming here all alone?
-Seems I have no
choice but to fight.
-Leaf style crescent moon dance.
-I can't free my sword.
-Impressive.
Leaf style crescent
moon dance, and being
able to master it
at such a young age.
As I expected, your village
is full of talented ninja.
Your talent with
a sword is superb.
Of course, stopping a
physical sword is easy.
However, a wind sword
is a different story.
No one can stop it.
-Oh, wow!
-Knock it off.
-We're truly in
paradise now Naruto.
-You are so creepy.
-Hi Master Jiraiya , shouldn't
you pay attention to me now?
I'm just desperate for
someone to train me,
and you're the only one who
can do it, super hunky sensei.
Pretty please, Master Jiraiya?
-So you finally came
out of hiding huh?
I've been waiting for you.
No fair.
Hey are you just making
fun of me Naruto?
-Listen, there's nothing
fun about this situation.
-Hey, I'm getting
kind of hungry.
-Me too, let's get
back to the hotel.
-Oh great, now they're
leaving, darn it.
All right Naruto, I guess I'll
teach you a technique now.
-Well it's about
time and you better
not be kidding around here.
-OK, do you remember what
we talked about yesterday?
You know, that stuff about
the two types of chakra ?
-Huh, we talked yesterday?
-Very funny.
Remember you said
something about having
different chakra,
one blue and one red?
-Oh yeah, so what about it?
-You said that when you
exerted enormous strength,
you felt red chakra?
-Yeah, that's right.
I don't know how
else to describe it.
-All right, try building up
that red chakra, right now.
-Right now?
Well, I guess if you say so.
OK, I'll give it a try.
-Well, did it work?
-No, it's not right.
It's the same chakra as always.
-Oh man, you really have
absolute zero talent,
don't you kid?
-Hey, don't go acting
like you're so great.
And besides, I can't
help it, I mean,
I don't even understand those
two types of Chakra myself,
all right?
-Just keep trying.
-Fine, I will.
-Hmm, so he doesn't
understand it huh.
Naruto probably
still hasn't realized
that his red chakra is really
the nine tail foxes chakra.
Judging by his story, it seems
that the excitement caused
by quite danger, and
also a strong emotion,
are the keys to summoning
the nine tail fox chakra.
-It's just no good.
I'm only getting the usual,
every day chakra here.
Hey, hold on a second.
Maybe I don't even need
to summon the red chakra.
I mean, what in
the world does it
have to do with the
technique that you're
going to teach me anyway?
-Listen boy.
For the technique I'm
going to teach you
the chakra you've
used until now is
nowhere near powerful enough.
If you want to
use this technique
you'll have to be able
to pull out all the stops
and tap into the other chakra
that's been dormant within you.
Summoning it up at
a moment's notice.
-Yeah, that sounds really
cool and exciting, but how do
you even know that I really
have that chakra inside of me?
-Ho, ho, that's just
what I wanted to do hear.
Actually it's
because I am a sage.
-Talk about giving an answer
without giving an answer.
-Anyway, the special
chakra that only you have
will become your
greatest weapon.
I am sure of it.
-Greatest weapon, really?
-Yes.
Not using that is
like wasting treasure.
Look, there's no need to
blindly follow the same training
regiment as everyone
else, right?
Everyone has various
strengths and weaknesses.
You have your own style.
Your training until now involved
maintaining and releasing
a set amount of chakra.
In other words, it
was training you
to control the flow of chakra
so that you wouldn't use it
all up once and get exhausted.
You have a lot of stamina.
You should use your power
instead of doing cheap tricks.
You have two types of chakra,
and don't exhaust easily.
So you should learn to release
the largest amount of chakra
you can, and then train
yourself so you can increase
the total amount of
chakra you can use.
Once you do that, a whole world
of Jutsu will open up to you.
-Seriously?
Like what could I do?
-Well, for example,
the summoning
Jutsu that I'm
going to teach you.
Ah, there, yes that's perfect.
-Summoning?
-That's right.
It is a teleport
technique in which
you sign a contract in blood
with all kinds of living
creatures and then
summon them whenever
you like with ninjutsu,
your ninja art.
-Oh, yeah!
That sounds awesome!
Teach me quick.
Come on, right now.
Let's get going already.
-OK, just relax.
Before we begin,
you're going to need
to use up all your
usual chakra so just
your red chakra remains.
-All right!
Leave it to me.
-So, he already knows
the shadow clone Jutsu.
-Yeah, and I have
a good idea how
I can use it to get rid of my
normal chakra really quickly,
just watch.
-Well, look at that.
And I thought just one of
you was trouble enough.
-Listen up!
All of us are going to have
one great big battle royale.
The last one left standing
will be the strongest me.
We're going to determine
the me among me, get it?
-Yeah!
-Ah, now I see.
That's a pretty clever idea
considering he's so dumb.
-All right, let's do this!
-Uh, this isn't
as fun as watching
those ladies, that's for sure.
Ah!
Oh no!
-Well, it looks like the
finale of this battle
is finally close at hand.
-Nicely done.
-Well, sure enough, just like
I thought I'm the strongest me.
-It seems that at
long last, you finally
used up almost all
your usual chakra.
Now I can teach
you the technique.
-Yes, oh man I've been
waiting for this all day.
-I couldn't tell.
All right, first I'm going
to show you how it's done.
Now watch carefully.
-Whoa, that is totally awesome.
That may be the
coolest thing ever.
-Go ahead.
Open that scroll and
take a look inside.
It's a contract with the
summoning toads that's
been handed down from
earlier generations of ninja.
Just sign your name
in your own blood
and stamp the fingerprints
of one hand in blood
beneath your signature.
Find the place where you
want to summon the creature.
Then build up chakra
and press down
the hand you used
on the contract.
That seal is Eno, E,
Tori, Tsaru, Hitsugi.
-Here goes.
Naruto.
Uzu.
Maki.
OK, I'm all done, right?
What's next?
-After burning off
your regular chakra
it should be easier to
release your red chakra now.
So give it a try.
-Quit bugging me, I already am.
OK.
Eno.
E. Tori.
Tsaru.
Hitsugi.
Ninja Art summoning jitsu.
-A tadpole?
Sure enough this kid has
no talent whatsoever.
-Hayate, what in the
world happened to you?
(MUSIC PLAYING)
-Oh, I should've known.
I go all by myself to visit
Sasuke at the hospital
but little Ms. Eno pig
has to show up too.
And what does she think
she's doing, picking out
that one they call
the flower of love?
That's so lame.
Me, I'm going to choose
this daffodil for Sasuke
in hopes that he'll
get better soon.
Next time, a
feeling of yearning,
a flower full of hope.
This is it!
I just know it.