[theme music]
-Shino, can we
take a break maybe?
We've been walking
since the sun came up.
I'm exhausted.
-If you have enough
energy to keep
groaning about
how tired you are,
it seems to me you
can't be that tired.
-Give me a break.
Just my luck to get stuck
having to do a mission alone
with Shino.
Huh?
Hey, old lady, are we getting
close to Motoyoshi Village.
-Is it Motoyoshi Village
you're headed to?
-That's right.
-Well, then, it's just
up ahead over that rise.
-Really?
What a relief.
-But be warned, you
must be very careful.
-Motoyoshi is a place
where even the dead laugh.
If you start laughing
too, you're finished.
-There it is, Naruto.
Motoyoshi Village.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Right then we
had no idea of the nightmare
we were getting into.
We hadn't even been told
what the mission was.
I suppose that
should have given us
a clue that things were
about to get scary.
[bell ding]
-Huh?
-Greetings.
I am Fuga Kagatsu.
-Shino Aburame.
And I'm Naruto Uzumaki.
-Shall we get right
down to business?
That is the final will of
Tobei Kagetsu, my dear father.
-A will, huh?
-In the event of my death,
my eldest son, Futa,
shall inherit the entire
Kagetsu family estate.
TSUNADE: Tomorrow
in Motoyoshi Village
there will be a funeral
for Tobie Kagetsu, the head
of a wealthy land
holding family.
I need you two to be there.
-A security detail, eh?
Why on earth would
you pick Naruto?
-What's that suppose to mean?
-I certainly wouldn't
want his goofy face
turning up at my funeral.
-Goofy what?
-I couldn't agree more.
Unfortunately ,
I have no choice.
No one else is free,
so it has to be Naruto.
But you're in charge
of the mission, Shino.
As you'll find out,
there are reasons
that you are especially
well-qualified.
This mission has some
rather unusual requirements.
You'll understand when
you read the will.
-However, if my son
Futa, the chief mourner,
should laugh at my funeral,
he forfeits all his rights
and the estate will be divided
among the other members
of the family.
-If he laughs at the funeral?
That's weird.
-The mountains my
family owns are
rich in valuable
medicinal herbs.
If I inherited the
estate, I'll live well
for the rest of my life.
But crack one laugh at my
father's funeral and I'm out.
The others in my family, I
know they'll do everything
in their power to make me
laugh at the funeral tomorrow.
I don't think I have
the strength to resist.
Luckily, for me, there's
a loophole in the will.
It says right there that I'm
allowed to find a substitute
to take my place
as chief mourner,
so that's what I asked the Leaf
Village to send me, a stand in.
Someone guaranteed not to laugh.
-Now, I see why this is a
perfect mission for him.
Don't worry, Mister,
Shino never laughs.
-Excellent.
Then I leave it to you.
-Understood.
-Futa, dinner is ready.
-This is Mai.
She is my youngest sister.
She lived with my
father here in his home.
She looked after him and
was with him at the end.
Mai, this is Shino and Naruto.
-It's nice to meet you.
-I'm starving, let's eat.
-Wait.
Let me taste it first.
-What do you mean?
Are you suggesting
that my relatives
would go so far as
to poison my food?
-Well, better safe than sorry.
-I suppose you're right.
-But if it is poisoned,
what about you?
-The parasitic insects within
me will break down any poisons
before it can cause
any serious damage.
-The, uh, parasitic insects?
-Well?
[chuckle]
-I guess it's all right.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Did Shino just laugh?
-Well, he seems to
be in good spirits.
I guess that means the
food is all right then.
-No, don't eat it.
The way Shino's
laughing his head off,
there's something
definitely wrong.
-The food has some kind
of laughing drug in it.
-Who the heck
prepared this food?
-I did, but the backdoor
right next to the kitchen
is never locked.
Someone could have
come in at any time.
-That anyone in the
family would do this.
That my own flesh and blood
would try to poison me.
-Whatever the drug is,
it's affecting my insects.
It's no use.
They can't break it down.
-Well, then, what
are we going to do
about the funeral tomorrow?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
OK, this is officially
starting to freak me out now!
-Naruto, there's no time
to contact the Leaf Village
before the funeral tomorrow.
You'll have to do it.
You'll have to take my place
as a substitute mourner.
-No way.
-Well, Naruto, It's up to you.
But to be honest, I wonder if
you are the man for the job.
-Yeah, well, to be
honest, I'm kind
of wondering the same thing.
[laughing]
SHINO: Oh, please,
enough already.
How can I get any sleep?
-Ah, Tsukiko,
you're here already?
-Well, of course,
what did you think?
I'd be late for my
own father's funeral?
-Uh, who's the kid?
-I'm not feeling
very well, so I asked
Naruto to stand in
as chief mourner.
-Nice to meet you.
-Yes, I'm just
staying long enough
to say hello to everyone,
and then he'll take over.
-I see.
But wasn't that a
curious will Father left?
To think you lose everything
if the chief mourner laughs.
Good luck, young man.
-That's Tsukiko, the
oldest of my sisters.
She married into a rich
family from the next village.
But that's not enough for her.
She wants my father's
estate more than anyone.
-Little squirt.
This will be easy.
-So many greedy people.
You can see it in their eyes.
What's this?
-The priest has arrived.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Did you have
to find the silliest looking
monk on the planet?
-I don't know
where he came from.
That's not the one I met before.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Don't laugh.
Don't laugh.
[laughter]
-Very well then, let us begin.
-What on earth was that?
-The wind maybe.
-Young man, did I hear you
start to laugh just now?
-Who me?
Laugh at a funeral, no way.
-Mai, you heard him, didn't you?
-Ah, all I could hear was
that bucket falling over
or whatever it was.
-Oh, well.
TSUKIKO (VOICEOVER):
No need to worry.
The ceremony is just
beginning, plenty of time.
And my only obstacle is
this idiotic looking boy.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
I lucked out.
Huh?
Way to go, Shino.
Thanks.
-Oh, that was too
close for comfort.
[speaking japanese]
-You make come up
now one at a time.
-All right, I'll go first.
Ah!
ALL: Laugh Laugh.
Laugh.
-It's no use.
He's not laughing.
Let me see if I can't
push him over the edge.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Don't laugh.
It's not funny.
Not funny.
MOURNER (VOICEOVER): Kid
thinks he's tough, but I've got
a trick that never fails.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Suck it up, Naruto.
Whatever this
joker's got in mind,
you can't laugh no matter what.
-Ha, do it, Kiasu.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Go on,
hit me with your best shot.
Can't make me laugh.
ALL: Laugh.
Laugh.
-Achoo!
Sorry, hay fever.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): No.
No.
ALL: Laugh.
Laugh. laugh.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
That's right.
Hold it in.
You can do it.
ALL: Laugh.
Laugh.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
You can't laugh.
You cannot laugh,
whatever you do.
TSUKIKO (VOICEOVER):
He's a harder nut
to crack then I
would have thought,
but how much longer
can he hold out?
before thus funeral is
over, I will make him laugh.
-It's that old woman.
-Motoyoshi is a place
where even the dead laugh.
If you start laughing
too, you're finished.
-What's she doing
lurking around here?
-Who's there?
Oh, it's you, Mai.
[singing]
-This will do the trick.
Put a drop of this in everyone's
tea and it's all over.
-Yes, but--
-Take it, Mai.
It will work.
Don't worry.
[laughing]
-Huh?
-Not so fast.
-Whom might you be?
-It's Shino.
-I heard everything.
TSUKIKO (VOICEOVER):
What's wrong with him?
Why doesn't he laugh?
The estate is slipping
through my fingers.
-All right then, as
substitute chief mourner,
it is my duty and honor to
thank you all for coming.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Mission accomplished.
-Ah, thank heavens.
I thought it would never end.
Once the priest leaves,
the funeral's over.
-Just a moment?
-Huh?
-If you wouldn't
mind, my husband
would like to thank you as well.
Go ahead, Darling.
-Thanks for the great funeral.
-Oh no.
What is he doing?
-That was the
bestest funeral ever.
It made me want to die
so I could have one too.
So sad.
So moving.
I can't believe that
idiot would stoop to this.
Be strong, Naruto.
Don't let them break you.
It's almost over.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
It's not working.
Think of something else.
Something sad.
Something not funny at all.
Wrong!
Not Pervy Sage.
TSUKIKO (VOICEOVER): Yes.
He's almost there.
-I can't stop crying.
I'm melting.
Melting.
-Oh, that's all right, Darling.
Don't worry, you haven't
another one right here.
-Oh, no.
-We've got him.
Hm?
Huh?
Father?
-This is impossible.
Father's alive?
-Stop it.
Brothers and
sisters don't fight.
Papa doesn't like
it when we fight.
-Get out of here.
My joke was funny.
-You get out.
My joke was funnier.
-Who are those kids?
What's going on?
-Yeah, well, how come
my joke made dad laugh?
-He was laughing at my joke.
-Cut it out!
It's wrong to fight.
-Ha, Mai is right.
Fighting is wrong.
Listen to your little sister.
Futa.
Tsukiko.
-Futa.
-You mean, they're
supposed to be--
-Yes, of course.
They're us when we were kids.
-Ha, fighting very wrong.
Don't make me scratch this
gong. 'Cuz when I hear it gong,
I have to sing a song.
When I hear a gong or
bing, a silly song I sing.
It doesn't mean a thing,
this silly song I song.
The cat took all it's gold.
The fox is really old.
The queen was polishing
the anvils of the king.
Fundle dingle dong,
won't you sing along.
You cannot get it wrong
'cuz it's just a silly song.
-Yes, I remember it so well.
Our father used to make us
laugh with those idiotic songs
of his.
-I'd almost forgotten.
It seems like such
a long time ago.
-Yes, yes.
This is what I wanted to see.
ALL: Huh?
What?
-It's Father.
-But then, who is that?
-At last.
I've stopped laughing.
-Shino.
-Forgive me for having
put you all through this.
I came up with
this little scheme
and Mai helped me pull it off.
I knew the only way I could
bring you all together
is to stage my funeral.
-Is that really you, Father?
You're alive and well?
-But why?
I don't understand.
-To remind you of what we used
to be like before our lands
made us rich.
We were poor then, but how
loudly we used to laugh.
Once we learned how
valuable the herbs were
that grew on our mountains,
everything changed.
There was no more
laughter, only cries
of money, money, more money.
None of us ever even really
smiled again after that.
I wanted to remind the family
of what we'd forgotten.
What's important.
I wanted to see a smile
on our faces again.
I knew if I wrote
that ridiculous will,
everyone would go crazy
trying to make Futa laugh.
Then, perhaps, the
forced laughter
would turn into real
laughter, real joy.
Happiness has nothing
to do with wealth.
It's about being a family,
loving and caring and laughing.
-I remember, Father.
-Oh.
-I want the laughter
back in my life.
-You're right.
Quite frankly, it
will be a relief
not to live at the mercy
of money all the time.
-This I've got to see.
Money is all you
ever cared about.
-Well, I;m singing a
different tune now.
How does it go again?
Ding dong ding or something.
NARUTO: Is that
what I think it is?
SHINO: The laughing drug.
-It's still experimental.
I knew if Futa could pick
a substitute chief mourner
to take his place,
he'd find someone
who's almost
incapable of laughing,
and that would be the
perfect person to test it on.
If there'd been no laughter by
the time the funeral was almost
over, I was going to put
this in everyone's tea
as a last resort.
But then--
-What's the point of
chemically induced laughter.
Laughter that doesn't
come from the heart
isn't laughter at all.
It's the sound of
someone in agony.
Like I am now.
-So technically, did we
accomplish our mission?
-I believe we did.
I suspect the hokage knew what
the real mission was all along.
-Say, while you were
posing as the old man,
did you really
come up with that?
I mean, seriously.
All that dongity ding, the
bongity bing stuff was yours?
Ya!
-Not a word.
It never happened.
Understand?
-Right, never happened.
Got it.
-Good.
-Shino, man, you
really are a joy
to work with, you know that?
[theme music]
-I need you in
the Land of Greens
for some important escort duty.
NARUTO: Important?
It's a lousy team rank mission.
TSUNADE: Listen you.
Their chief has been very
good to me so watch your step.
NARUTO: Ah, I can do
this mission in my sleep.
TSUNADE: Well, don't, you've
done enough like that already.
Oh, and there's one more thing.
NARUTO: What?
TSUNADE: Something
you must not forget
to take with you,
no matter what.
NARUTO: Next time,
"Open for Business,
The Leaf Moving Service."