[theme music]
CHOJI (VOICEOVER): Shikamaru.
He's always believed in me.
SHIKAMARU: More than me,
or Neji, or any of us
here, Choji's got strength.
-Here I come, fatso!
-Huh?
Don't you call me that!
-Partial Expansion Jutsu!
Arm!
Partial Expansion Jutsu!
Leg!
Arm!
-Don't mess with me, scum!
-How about this?
-What the--
-Super Expansion Jutsu!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Goodbye old friend.
I'll always believe in you.
-Shikamaru.
I did it.
What?
-I don't believe I have
to go to the second state
for an opponent as
weak as this one.
Slamming Palm!
-Huh?
What the-- He changed his form!
-I'm afraid it's
all over for you.
In second state, I'm invincible.
I can dish out 10 times as
much power as I could before.
CHOJI (VOICEOVER):
It hurts to move.
I didn't know the side
effects of the curry pill
would be so intense.
-You better listen
to me, because I'm
about to teach you
an important lesson.
This is what happens
to weaklings!
You're pathetic.
You'd be better off playing
ninja with your friends.
BOY: OK, everyone!
Raise your hand if you
want to play ninja!
[excited chatter]
-Wait for me!
KIDS: Rock, paper, scissors!
-Go hide!
-One, two, three, four--
-Hey!
I'm coming too!
Hold on a sec!
-98, 99, 100!
-Hey.
-What are you doing?
Get out of here.
-Ow!
-Ha ha, we gotcha!
-Give up quietly.
The game's over for both of you.
-Great.
-We caught them, so we win.
-I'm so sick of this.
Whatever team Choji's on
loses every single time.
-Sorry.
-Ha.
-Now that I'm in
my second state,
I'm gonna need a lot
more chakra, which
means I'm going to
have to take whatever
you have left inside you.
All right, kiddo.
Let's get this over with.
You don't have very
much left, do you?
Empty already?
You weakling.
I'm still hungry!
I said I'm still hungry!
Huh?
Oh, of course.
Fatso only left one chip.
Well, I guess I'll
take what I can get.
How does it feel to be a pawn?
To be sacrificed by
your so-called friends?
Left here for dead?
A pitiful fatso,
the odd man out.
BOY: You can't play
ninja with us anymore.
-But why can't I?
-Because whenever you
play with us, we lose.
-Yeah, you're way too slow.
-You know, guys, without him,
the teams aren't gonna be even.
It'd be lame.
Like if you played a game of
Shogi with one piece missing.
-But if you have one piece
that's totally useless,
it's the same thing.
-Yeah, what he said.
-It's our team and we don't
mind having one less person,
so let's just play.
-Well, if it's OK with
you, I guess it's fine.
-OK then, it's settled.
-We're so gonna win this time.
-Yeah!
Where should we hide?
BOY: What do you think?
-At least chunky's not playing.
Here's the plan.
You guys go left.
-All right, yeah, I'll
go hide in the alley.
-And they said the whole
Akimichi clan is fat and slow.
Then everybody laughed at me.
-Did they really?
Let me tell you something, son.
None of those boys have
as kind a heart as you do.
-Hm?
-And someday, you'll have
a group of real friends
who see that quality inside
you and respect you for it.
You'll find friends
who believe in you,
who trust you with their lives.
Cherish those friends, Choji.
CHOJI: You think someone
like me could really
have friends like that?
-Rest in peace, scum.
But you're not the only
loser I'm gonna destroy.
After I'm finished
here with you,
I'm gonna hunt down your
heartless friends that
sacrificed you for their
own good and crush them too.
-It's for Choji.
He promised us he'd catch up.
You better catch
up with us, Choji.
You hear me?
-Yeah!
-Trust me.
He will bear that guy.
And after he does,
he'll come and find us.
-No doubt about it.
If anyone can defeat
him, it's Choji.
-Well, as long as we've stopped.
-Good idea.
-All right, everyone.
Let's get Sasuke back
before Choji catches up.
-Huh?
-Hey, wait for me!
-All right!
Here we come!
-Jirobo's late.
He should have
gotten here by now.
-Well, you know how enormous
his appetite can be.
He's probably squeezing out
every last bit of chakra.
-Man, I wish I could be
in his shoes right now.
-Oh, sorry.
Looks like I finished the bag.
Well, punk.
It's getting late, and I've
got some people to meet.
Looks like it's about
time to say your goodbyes.
CHOJI (VOICEOVER): I've still
got the chili pepper pill left,
but if I-- if I
swallow it, I'll die.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
No matter what, don't you
die on me, Choji.
We've always stuck together,
ever since the day we met.
Hm?
Hm.
Huh?
Oh, it's you.
-Hm?
-Oh, yeah.
You were with those kids.
Weren't you playing
ninja with them?
-Heh.
They were a drag, so I quit.
-Really?
-By the way, you're kind of
sitting on my special spot.
-Your special spot?
-Yeah.
On a nice day like
this, I always
come out here and
lie on my back,
and just stare at
the clouds, you know?
-You came to look at clouds?
-That's right.
So, can I sit?
-Oh, sure.
-This is such an awesome spot.
The sky looks amazing.
-You're right.
-Hey.
-What?
-The clouds are pretty
cool from down here.
Wanna lie back
and watch with me?
-Uh.
Yeah, thanks!
Hey.
You know, I brought
some snacks with me.
You want to share them?
SHIKAMARU: That'd be great.
Hey, thanks.
Eating chips and
watching clouds.
Man, this is the best.
-Yep.
-By the way, my
name's Shikamaru.
I'm from the Nara clan.
What about you?
What's your name?
-It's Choji.
My name is Choji, and I'm
from the Akimichi clan.
-Choji, huh?
I got a feeling that you
and me'll be friends.
-Yeah, me too.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
We've always stuck together,
and there's no way
that's gonna end now.
Choji.
CHOJI (VOICEOVER):
Shikamaru-- I'm sorry.
I'm not gonna catch up.
-It's over.
Say your prayers.
CHOJI (VOICEOVER): No.
I have to stop him.
Even if it means I
die, I've got to win.
-There's nothing you
can do to stop me!
Crushing Palm!
Huh?
Wh-- What is that?
Doesn't matter.
Slamming Boulder!
-Don't even try.
Because now, I'm a hundred
times stronger than before.
People hold grudges
when you take
something important from them.
Like, for instance, their food!
That strike I gave
you was for eating
the last bite of
my favorite snack!
JIROBO (VOICEOVER): Impossible!
This punk has so much chakra,
his body's actually changed.
-And this next attack
is for calling me lames,
like pawn, and fatso, and loser.
I can handle being picked
on, but what you've done
is unforgivable!
-When you've got an idiot for a
leader, the whole team suffers.
Know what I mean?
Tell you what.
You don't want to keep working
under this glum-faced little
shadow lover.
I'll just kill you now, and
put you out of your misery.
-He was my best friend,
and you insulted him!
How dare you.
You can steal my very last
bite of my very best food,
you can mock me all you want,
but when you insult my best
friend, I will obliterate you!
All of my chakra
to my left hand.
This last attack is
worth my whole life!
-Wait!
No!
Please don't do it!
[shout]
-I did it.
A guy like me-- I beat him.
My friends-- Huh?
CHOZA (VOICEOVER): Let me
tell you something, son.
None of those boys have
as kind a heart as you do.
And someday you'll have
a group of real friends
who see that quality inside
you and respect you for it.
You'll find friends
who believe in you,
who trust you with their lives.
Cherish those friends, Choji.
[sniffling]
-Hurry it up, slowpoke.
Naruto wrote that.
We're all waiting for you.
Kiba.
And Shikamaru.
-Ino!
-Shika!
-Cho!
Even for a bag of
potato chips, I
refuse to let anyone
have the last bite!
-Choji and I have been on the
same team for a long time.
We work well together, so
asking him's a no brainer.
-Dad, you were right.
I made some really
great friends.
Huh?
[groan]
-What's the matter?
SHIKAMARU: It's nothin'.
[theme music]
-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Yah!
-Fang Over Fang!
-Arf!
Arf!
-Byakugan!
-The darn spider.
He got me, Naruto,
Kiba, and Neji.
But our plan isn't working.
-And if we take much longer,
we're gonna lose Sasuke!
-If we're going to
continue our mission,
there's only one way to do it.
NARUTO: Next time,
Your Opponent Is Me!
[theme music]