[theme music]
[diabolical laughter]
[gasps]
-It can't be!
[diabolical laughter]
-I can tell when you're
bluffing, my dear.
And right now, you're
already finished!
[clink]
[fast breathing]
-[chuckling] Poor little thing.
Look at her, trembling
like a newborn pup.
All right, Kabuto.
Get rid of her, but try
not to let her suffer.
-Right.
[footsteps]
SAKURA: Sasuke!
I'll do anything
for you, Sasuke!
So, please!
I'm begging you!
Don't walk away!
-You haven't changed.
You're still annoying.
-Don't leave me!
-Sakura.
Thank you for everything.
[thump]
-Sasuke.
Wait!
-Hmm?
Yes, my dear?
You had something to say?
-Hold on a minute!
[chuckles]
-Sasuke.
Where is he?
You couldn't have-- you couldn't
have taken his body already!
-No need to hide it
any longer, I suppose.
It's fine, Kabuto.
Go ahead and tell her.
[footsteps]
[door creaking shut]
-Unfortunately, Sasuke was
a little late getting here,
and Lord Orochimaru
wasn't able to wait.
He had to make do
with another vessel.
-So, Sasuke's all
right, then, isn't he?
And he's somewhere
in this building!
-Lord Orochimaru gave
Uchiha the curse mark
to prepare him to be ready for
my lord's next incarnation.
The problem is, not
everyone can bear
the burden of the curse mark.
[crunching]
-Nngh!
-Impossible!
There's no way that
Sasuke could be--
-I'm afraid so.
Sasuke couldn't handle the curse
mark and now he's a memory.
-You're lying!
I don't believe you.
It has to be a lie!
-[sighing] Oh, come now.
What on Earth have
I to gain by lying?
I mean, in another minute
here, you'll be dead.
Since you're in such a hurry
to see him, let me help you.
You can spend eternity
together in the afterlife.
[chuckling]
-Sasuke.
-Sakura!
[kring]
-Nngh.
-Sakura, don't believe a
word out of this guy's mouth.
Nngh.
He's full of it!
-Naruto!
-Well, what do you
know about that!
I just figured you'd
drowned by now, Naruto.
-Whenever I make a promise,
I don't ever give up!
That's my ninja way, pal!
And until we get Sasuke
back, nothing on Earth
is gonna stop me!
-Hmm.
Interesting.
[shing]
[thunking]
-Sakura, you find
a place to hide.
[shing]
-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
[poof]
-Hey, four eyes!
[laughing] Hey, over here!
I mean here!
What are you looking at?
I'm right over here.
[interposing voices]
-Hmm?
Keh!
[shing]
[grunting]
-Huh?
Nngh!
--[laughing] Looks like
you're all out of kunai!
I hope you're ready, 'cause I'm
gonna wipe the floor with you!
[roaring]
[kring]
[grunting]
-These clones are
really irritating!
Fire Style, Mystic
Flames Dance Jutsu!
[whoosh]
CLONES: Ahhh!
[popping]
-[chuckling] Huh?
[buzzing]
[gasps]
-Too little, too late!
Rasengan!
Aaugh!
[roars]
[yells]
[thudding]
-Nngh!
[labored breathing]
[pop]
-Naruto!
[footsteps]
-If you and Orochimaru
are here, then Sasuke
is probably here somewhere, too.
We want the truth.
Now!
[chuckles]
[gasps]
-What-- what the
heck is going on?
What did you do?
I can't move anymore!
-Heh.
Take a good look at yourself.
Notice anything funny?
--[gasping] What
have you done to me?
-Those threads wrapped around
you are made of chakra.
-Made of chakra?
-When you came in
for your big finish,
I was able to weave
them around your body.
Now, look carefully.
See where those threads lead to?
[gasps]
-That's right.
These chakra threads are wrapped
up in the chambers of my heart.
What's more, Naruto, the
threat is weaving its way
into your body as well.
Into your heart.
All of the internal organs
that keep you functioning.
[gasps]
[heart beating]
-Listen.
You can hear it, can't you?
Our heart rates
are synchronizing.
[inhaling] In a moment,
they will beat as one.
-[gasping] Are you crazy?
-Naruto!
-Nngh!
-Mmm.
No use struggling.
Those threads are made
up of pure chakra.
Nothing you do can break them.
[gasps]
-There.
Now our hearts are
totally in sync.
The chakra in these threads has
linked my circulatory system
directly to your own.
Your heart's entirely
under my control.
NARUTO: Ugh!
It's no use.
Even though it's mine.
-If my heart should be
faster, then your heart
will beat right along with it.
And of course you realize when
my heartbeat comes to an end,
so, too, does yours.
[gasps]
-Don't!
What's the point?
If you stop your heart,
then you'll die, too!
-Yes, I'll die.
But then, it hardly matters now.
I've already promised my
body to Lord Orochimaru
to use at his disposal.
Aaugh!
[loud heartbeats]
[gasps]
-What-- what exactly are
you planning on doing?
-Heh.
Now all I have to do is squeeze.
Then I'll die and so will you.
And then I'll die.
And so will you.
Let's go.
You can come with me.
[squish]
-Aaugh!
-Naruto!
-So, how's it feel?
Having your heart crushed
from inside your own chest?
Don't worry, you'll be out
of your misery soon enough.
[squish]
-Aaugh!
[shing]
-That's enough!
-Don't be such a fool!
If you take me out, then
Naruto goes with me.
-I have a better idea.
Let's just do this!
Nngh!
[splat]
-You're wasting your time.
The thread is spun from chakra.
It can't be severed.
-Aaugh!
--[chuckling] Even lady
Tsunade, with all her strength,
would be powerless to break it.
-Nngh!
What do I do?
Naruto is suffering
right in front of me
and I'm helpless to stop it!
-Don't you worry, Sakura.
I don't care what happens.
Nothing's gonna stop
me, not 'til I've
delivered on my promise!
-This ridiculous
bravado ends here!
Time to leave this mortal coil.
Then you can finally
see your beloved Sasuke.
[squish]
-Aaugh!
[heart beating faster]
-Nnngh!
-Aaugh!
-Naruto!
-Sakura!
-Sasame!
-Sakura, take this tag.
Wrap your kunai in it.
[buzz]
-Augh!
[slash]
-Aaugh!
[thud]
-Naruto!
Naruto?
Hey.
Are you OK?
Naruto!
It can't be!
No, please!
You can't!
[crying] Naruto!
[heart beating]
-Huh?
-Oh yeah!
Nothin' gets the
heart crankin' like
the touch of a beautiful woman.
-Jerk!
[clang]
-I can't believe I
wasted my tears on you!
-Sorry, Sakura.
-Man, you really are
hopeless, aren't you?
[laughs]
-So, wait.
Sasame-- What are
you doing here?
-Oh, well, I was just--
-I'm just glad she
showed up when she did,
otherwise I wouldn't be here.
-You can say that again.
-Huh?
What do you guys mean?
-That pit coming Gamakichi
and I were caught in
started filling up with water.
[water rushing]
-Guh!
OK, I think this is the lid!
[grunting] Come on!
When the water
reached the top, I
pushed against the ceiling
as hard as I could,
but it wouldn't budge.
SASAME: Master Jiraiya told
me to head for the place
where he met up with Hanzaki.
[gasping] But I was so
worried about Arashi,
I just had to come.
[splash]
-[gasping] Is that you, Naruto?
-Hey, thanks a lot, doll.
-Tha-- that frog
just spoke to me!
-Now that I think about it,
I guess it was kind of silly
trying to open that thing
just by pushing on it.
-Ugh.
But my kunai wasn't cutting
those threads at all.
So how come it worked after
I wrapped your tag around it?
-Because the chakra thread
is one of the Fuma Clan's
most guarded ninja techniques.
-The Fuma Clan's?
-Oh, that explains it!
So wait a minute, who
the heck is this guy?
[crumbling]
-Huh?
Hmm.
SASAME AND SAKURA: [gasping]
-Well, what do you know?
It was you again.
-Master Kagaro.
She's a Fuma jounin.
-What is it?
What's wrong?
-Hey, Sasame.
It's all right.
Don't be frightened.
Lord Orochimaru has simple
given me a second life.
-Are you kidding?
That snake's playing
you for a fool!
-Where are they hiding Sasuke?
-Yeah, and what about
Sasame's cousin, huh?
Where are they keeping Arashi?
-Lord Orochimaru is our savior.
The honorable Fuma
Clan has fallen,
but he will lift us up again.
Higher than all other shinobi.
-Are you still
spouting that trash?
Enough, already!
Tell Sasame where her cousin is!
[chuckles]
-Huh?
-Over there?
Is that where they are?
-You and your cousin, Sasame.
You were always so close to
one another, weren't you?
[heart beats]
-It would be better if
you didn't see him now.
[gasps]
[heard beats]
[heart beats slow]
-[gasping] Master Kagero.
-Well, Sasame.
What you want to do?
-You can wait here, if you want.
-I have to see him.
I don't care what awaits
me beyond that door!
I came to find Arashi and
that's what I'm going to do!
-Mmhmm!
I like your guts, girly!
-Right!
We forge on together, then!
-Yeah!
Let's do it.
MALE SPEAKER: Sasame.
-There could be some
sort of trap here.
-Just leave it to me.
[door creaks open]
[footsteps]
-Orochimaru!
-It's good of you
to come, Sasame.
-Where's my cousin?
-[gasping] Arashi!
Arashi!
What's wrong, Arashi?
-You're mistaken.
I'm not the Arashi you knew.
[squishing]
[bursting]
-Ahh!
[roaring]
-What the heck is
going on around here?
-The bodies and the skills
of the Fuma Clan's strongest
jounin have merged
and I have been
reborn as the ultimate shinobi!
Now let me show you the
most powerful ninjutsu
you've ever seen, Sasame!
-Arashi!
What have you done to yourself?
-Orochimaru, you lousy snake!
I won't forgive him for
this, no matter what!
[theme music]
SAKURA: I'm sorry.
Forgive me, Naruto.
I haven't been a
help you at all.
The only thing I do
is weigh you down.
I haven't changed one bit.
But Naruto, Sasame, I've
learned so much from you both.
That's why I want to change
the kind of person I am.
This time, this time it's
my turn to give it my all.
Next time, "Sakura's
Determination!"
[theme music]