[theme music]
-Sarutobi, let me
remove the blade.
A fitting end for
one who had mastered
the way of the shinobi.
-My arms feel as
if they are fire.
-No, Orochimaru!
-Our mission has failed.
Release the barrier.
Take me back.
-Right!
Release.
-Look, the barrier!
-It's gone.
Where's Lord Hokage?
-Let's go.
Stop them.
-Ninja art, spiderweb net.
-Watch out.
A chakra web.
And we flew right into it.
-Kakashi, they are pulling out.
We should go after them.
-Wait, Guy.
I'm not so sure.
-That's right.
Let's not be too hasty.
If we rush in, we might
get snared in their traps.
-What are you suggesting,
then, that we simply
stand here and let the swine
escape, after what they've
done to our village?
That's not the Leaf shinobi way.
-So, you propose that we
do nothing, eh Kabuto?
-Well, aren't you
the clever one.
Time to call it a day.
Are you going to run
away from me again?
-That would be too obvious.
Why should I show
my hand when it's
so much more fun
keeping you in the dark?
That eye of yours can't
see everything, can it?
Unlike the Uchiha clan, you
haven't mastered it yet.
Oh well.
-Temari.
-Kankuro!
-I'll leave her with you.
-Wait, what do I?
Oh.
GAARA (VOICEOVER): What could
it be that makes him so strong?
I will not disappear.
I will not cease to exist.
I won't!
-What are you doing?
I told you not to talk to him.
-Let's get out of here.
-Watch out, it's him again.
Why don't you just go away?
Go away, you, you freak!
-Freak!
Why don't you die!
-He's a monster.
Don't even look at him.
-I told you to
stay away from him.
-Go away.
-It's all a distant
memory now. "Why
do I exist," I used
to asked myself.
-But I knew that
something else had
been taken from me--
something even more important.
And that is when
I truly despaired.
My purpose, in all the world,
there was no one who needed me.
I was unnecessary.
-No, stay away!
-It's almost
unbearable, isn't it?
The feeling of being all alone.
I know that feeling.
I've been there, in that
dark and lonely place.
But now there are others-- other
people who mean a lot to me.
I care more about
them than I do myself.
And I won't let
anyone hurt them.
That's why I won't ever give up.
I will stop you, even
if I have to kill you.
-Why?
Why would you do this
for anyone but yourself?
-Because they saved
me from myself.
They rescued my
from my loneliness.
There were the first to
accept me for who I am.
They are my friends.
-Well, love is
the heart's desire
to serve someone who's precious
to you, to watch over them,
like my sister
did for you Gaara.
GAARA (VOICEOVER):
Love, is that the thing
that makes him so strong?
-Naruto, that's enough.
Look, Sakura's going
to be all right.
The sand crumbled away.
She's free.
This guy's chakra
is all used up.
-That's a relief.
-That's enough.
It's over.
-But Gaara.
TEMARI (VOICEOVER): I
never thought I'd see this.
He's had it.
All right, Gaara.
GAARA (VOICEOVER): Who
knows, Naruto Uzumaki?
Perhaps even I, some day.
Temari.
Kankuro, I'm sorry.
-Don't worry about it.
-It's raining.
-Even the heavens weep.
-We are gathered here
to remember and honor
not only the third Hokage,
but all those who sacrificed
themselves in this battle so
that our village would survive.
(VOICEOVER) So
it's come to pass.
In the end, all we
could do was watch.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Why
did it have to happen?
Why did someone so
good have to die?
Why?
-[weeping]
-It's hard to believe
it's been a year already.
Your instructors tell
me you're among the most
playful of their students,
always full of fun.
You're very brave.
It's hard to hide
sadness behind laughter.
-What makes you think
I'm sad about anything?
It's a noble thing to die
in the line of duty, right?
My parents gave their lives to
protect this place from the fox
demon and the son of heroes.
How can I be sad when
they died that way?
I'm not even sad because they
went and left me all alone.
If I cry, it's
because I'm proud.
-It's all right, Haruka.
I know that somewhere
inside of you, there's
a boy curled up
in a ball of pain.
But remember this,
you are not alone.
Inside every ninja of
the Hidden Leaf Village
burns the will of fire.
-The will of fire?
-It's what gives us the
strength to defend our village.
It's the unbreakable bond
that ties us all together.
It's what makes us a family.
I wonder, do you have it
yet, young as you are?
-I think so.
-[weeping]
-Are those for Hayate?
Better make it quick.
The Hokage's funeral
has already begun.
-And you, Kakashi?
Paying respects to Obito?
Instead of constantly inventing
new excuses for being late,
why don't you simply
come here earlier.
-I did.
I've been here since dawn.
This place makes me think of the
mistakes I've made in the past.
And I've made so many of them.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
It's a shinobi rule.
Never show your feeling.
Keep your mind focused on
your mission, no matter what.
No matter how much
you're hurting inside,
you can't shed a tear.
Iruka sensei, why do they do it?
Why do people risk their
lives for other people?
-Well, when someone
passes away, it's the end.
His past and future, all
the dreams he once had,
they disappear along with him.
This is true even if he
died honorably in battle,
as so many have, as Hayate did.
All the ties that
bind him to the living
are severed-- all but one, the
most important of all, people.
Parents, siblings,
friends, lovers,
the people who were
important to him.
And these people,
the ones left behind,
are joined together
in a great circle
by their shared memories
of him-- a circle
of friendship, trust,
and sacrifice that
grows larger and
stronger as time passes.
It's hard to explain it.
We remain in the
circle together.
We have no choice.
It's important to us.
-So we do it because we have to.
I get it.
Sort of.
Still, I'm sad he's gone.
-Think how sad it would be
if he'd died for nothing.
But he left us
something priceless.
Don't worry.
You'll understand
one of these days.
-Hey, give me some credit.
That much I get.
-The rain.
It's stopped.
-By Iruka sensei.
See you later.
-All right.
(VOICEOVER) Do you see it, Lord
Hokage, the [? will ?] of fire
is stronger than ever.
The sparks you left behind
have kindled the flame
among the young leaves
of the next generation.
A mighty flame, Lord Hokage.
It will burn brightly.
And it will shine its
light upon our village
and keep it warm and safe
for many years to come.
And some day, out of that new
flame will come a new Hokage.
-Well, it survived.
But barely.
The damage is extensive.
-Not long ago, he was at
the height of its glory.
Look at him now.
-You sound almost sad.
Don't tell me you still have
feelings for your old home?
-No, none.
[theme music]
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
The ritual is over
and all is covered
in a somber mist.
And silence.
From out of the mist,
a shadow emerges.
And from out of the
shadow, a sharpened fang.
It rips the years away and
awakens childhood memories
of disappointment, anger,
and a fateful decision.
The wheel of destiny
begins to turn.
Next time, Return
of the Morning Mist.