[theme music]
-Naruto.
-Hm?
LEE: There was a distress
call from the training room.
What in the world
happened out here?
-Bad news, guys.
The star was stolen.
It was a ninja, and he flew
off using chakra somehow.
-You actually saw this?
-Yeah, but shinobi can't fly.
Not that I've ever heard.
-Byakugan.
He's too far out.
I lost him.
But Naruto was correct.
-Using chakra to
take to the air?
That is a formidable shinobi.
-Wow.
So it was true.
-Of course, it was true.
What are you saying?
You didn't believe me?
-Pretty much.
-Wha?
Geez.
Thanks for the vote
of confidence, Tenten.
-So the star that their
village was founded on,
this says it's
actually a meteorite?
-That's right.
TSUNADE: It dates back
to the first Hoshikage
who established the village.
He discovered that by training
in close proximity to the star,
his chakra was strengthened.
Ever since then, they've
held a unique position
amongst the hidden villages.
-Yes, but our records show that
particular form of training
has been suspended
for 10 years now.
-After the Third
Hoshikage came to power,
he chose to put an end to it.
But then a year ago,
he passed away, sadly,
and the village lifted the ban.
-It's curious, isn't it?
I wonder what moved
him to forbid it.
-Hard To say.
Only the Village Hidden in
the Stars is privy to that.
Although, there have been
a few rumors on the wind.
-What do you mean?
-Well, details are
spotty, but most
of the ninja who underwent
the training died from it.
Whatever this thing
is, we do know
it forcibly strengthens chakra.
It's likely that gift comes with
adverse effects to the body.
-What?
Someone made off with the star?
-Yes.
There were people training
there when it happened,
but the enemy knocked them
out with some sort of jutsu.
-That's pathetic!
-You wouldn't say that
if you'd seen the chakra
this guy was throwing around!
-Was he truly that
impressive a foe then?
-Yeah.
He was forming wings and
beasts out of chakra.
I'd never seen anything like it.
-Is this true, Sumaru?
-Yes.
Ninja Art Kujaku.
No question about it.
-That's a jutsu unique to the
Village Hidden in the Stars,
right?
-Yeah.
and only those who master
the full star training--
-Sumaru!
-Tenten, this village has a
right to their own secrets.
You should know better.
Especially in regards to a jutsu
that is part of their heritage.
-I beg your pardon.
-Please, my lord.
Just give me the order.
Responsibility for the theft of
the star rests with me alone.
-No.
Our mission was to
protect it for you,
and we let it slip
through our fingers.
We are to share in the blame.
We will retrieve the star.
You may rest assured.
-Very well.
We shall leave the search to
shinobi of the Hidden Leaf.
Sumaru, you keep an eye on
all of your injured brethren.
-But they're outsiders.
What do they know of our ways?
-That's an order.
-Hey.
Are those friends
of yours who got
knocked out going
to be all right?
-Don't worry about it, OK?
You're outsiders.
It's none of your concern.
Now quit acting
like we're friends.
-That guy's a real
piece of work.
-Neji, I know you're trying
to go by the books and all,
but we weren't even there.
-She's right.
And we do not have any leads.
-Actually, we do.
-Huh?
-Then none of you
picked up on it?
Their leader, Akahoshi, is
clearly hiding something.
-Hiding?
What are you talking about?
-Come to think of it, when
Sumaru said the word Kujaku,
Akahoshi got pretty uppity.
-Well, where there is
smoke, there is fire.
An inside job then?
-You're moving too
fast for me, guys.
What's going on?
-I'm going to look
around the village,
and see if I can't find
us a trail to follow.
Tenten, I want you
and Lee on Akahoshi.
Keep an eye on him.
-Right.
Very well, then.
-Just leave it to us.
-Wait a second!
What the heck does that
leave for me to do?
-Oh.
Well, uh-- why don't you
tail Sumaru for awhile?
-You got it!
I'll be on Sumaru
like fleas on a dog!
I'll meet up with you later!
-Same as ever, huh?
-Patience has never
been his strong suit.
No question.
Natsuhiboshi, why
are you so red?
Because I had a sad
dream last night.
My eyes are red from the tears
I shed, swollen as I cry.
Natsuhiboshi, why've
you lost your way?
I'm searching for a
child who's gone afar.
He can't be found
though I search all day.
My sad dreams come once more.
NARUTO: Hey!
Sumaru!
What're you doing way out here?
-Just passing some time waiting
for the stars to come out.
-Star?
Yeah kidding, huh?
The night sky sure
is clear around here.
Take a look at that red one.
Pretty isn't it?
-Natsuhiboshi.
Never alone, the star
on high watches over me.
-What's that?
Hey, hold on a second.
Wait up.
Where you going?
I want to go pay
your friends a visit.
Here.
Check it out.
I brought along some of
the Hidden Leaf's world
famous chestnut bean jelly.
-Look.
Whatever.
You'll find them at
the training hall.
-Man.
That guy's about as
warm as an iceberg.
What gives?
You telling me
there's no one here?
Hope this isn't a bad time.
Where is everybody?
Hey.
You awake over there?
What the?
[groaning]
-Hokuto, knock it off.
Trust me. it's all right.
I can tell.
He's not an enemy.
-Mizura.
-You little!
-Ow.
My butt.
-You're a girl?
-That's right.
Who're you?
-I'm Naruto Uzumaki, a
ninja of the Hidden Leaf.
And I'm here to keep an eye on
this precious star of yours,
OK?
-Wait.
You mean?
I'm so sorry.
Forgive me.
-Ah, don't sweat it.
I just dropped by for a visit.
Uh-- where'd that jelly go?
Do you see it?
Hey!
There it is right there!
-Oh no.
-There's no doubt about it.
-So the shinobi who made
off with the star, are
you're saying it was really?
-How could they even be alive?
-We don't stand a chance.
-They were the last
to ever complete
the full training of the star.
Which means that--
-We're no matter which
with our level of jutsu.
-I wouldn't worry.
If they really are
the culprit, don't
forget we already possess
their Achilles Heel.
-I suppose so.
-That's right.
What are we waiting for it.
Let's go round 'em up.
-Hold on.
First things first.
We need to distract these
annoying little flies.
-I'm Hokuto.
Please, forgive me
for being so rash,
but I didn't
recognize your chakra.
I'm sorry.
-Now that's good.
Go on.
Dig in.
The food's not gonna eat itself.
-OK.
Wow.
That is good.
You weren't kidding.
-I know, right?
Hey. uh-- what gives?
Where did all the
others run off to?
-It's OK.
The thief just put us to sleep.
We didn't really get
hurt or anything.
-No fooling.
[coughing]
-You OK?
I really owe you for
saving my butt back there.
[coughing]
-Are you gonna be all right?
-I'm fine.
I just need a little rest.
-Mizura's health has
been worsening ever
since he began his training.
-Hokuto, you shouldn't
talk about the star
in front of outsiders!
[coughing]
-Mizura, hold on.
I'm really sorry.
I wasn't thinking.
That's all.
-Outsider?
You guys are pretty
cold around here.
Especially that Sumaru kid.
-I'm sorry, but there's a reason
Sumaru acts the way he does.
-Really?
-It happened.
It happened about 10 years ago.
Sumaru's parents were
guarding over the star
when they were killed by ninja
from another village seeking
to steal it.
That's why he's so--
-Right.
I get it.
That explains an awful lot.
So, where is Sumaru?
And there were others.
How come it's you two here?
-They're gone.
They said they we're
going after the star.
[door slams]
-Huh?
All right.
Well, bye.
-All right.
Here they come.
Let us go.
We should just
face them head on.
-You ding-dong.
-Tenten.
-We're on a surveillance
mission here.
-I have never been one for
skulking around in the shadows.
-Shh!
Will you shut your trap?
You're gonna blow our cover.
Leave the Shadowing
Ninjutsu to me.
You just trying to keep quiet.
-But Tenten--
-That's the mission.
-I understand.
-Let's go.
-Creeping, creeping.
-We're cool.
They haven't noticed us.
-Tenten, are you
sure this does not
go against the way of the ninja?
-Quit your
complaining, will you?
LEE: Creeping, creeping.
TENTEN: Will you
stop saying that?
LEE: This is not like any
ninjutsu I have ever seen.
-Have they spotted us?
-Not sure.
[heartbeating]
-It would appear that we
have escaped their attention.
-OK.
Let's stay on 'em then.
Great.
They turned to the right.
-Roger that.
-They vanished.
-So they gave us the slip.
-I don't get it.
Did they see us?
Hold on.
We're not your enemy.
-That is right.
We are here on a mission
from the Hidden Leaf Village.
-Well, a couple of
Leaf shinobi, huh?
-What're you trailing us for?
Don't you people have a
thief to catch somewhere?
LEE: That may be so, but there's
always the distinct possibility
that the two of you are
enemies in disguise.
-Heh.
You've got a lot of nerve.
-We didn't mean to be rude.
It's just that we
don't have any leads.
And we wanna see the star
back where it belonged so--
-So you thought you'd
tag after us for a while.
Is that the idea?
-Pfeh.
Sounds like a waste of time.
-Yeah.
Thanks anyway.
But we can get to
star back ourselves.
If you really wanna
do us a favor,
then stay the heck
out of our way.
-Don't have to be
so mean about it.
-I fear Neji may
have been right.
They do seem to be hiding
something in this village.
-Sure do.
-Everyone, join hands.
All right now.
Start looking for the same
star chakra that we all carry.
There you are.
These threads are
made of chakra.
They can't be severed.
Give us the star.
You may as well have
robbed us our life's blood.
-Hm?
-Neji.
Thank goodness.
Have you seen Sumaru?
-I thought I told you
to keep an eye on him.
-Yeah.
I know.
You did.
But the thing is, he took off
with a bunch of the others
to go out looking for the star!
-Is that so?
-Hey.
Are you listening to me?
What's up?
Something wrong?
-There's a massive amount of
chakra at the Valley of Death.
-Looks like he's back, huh?
-Hurry.
-You got it.
-Give-- give it back.
The star, it's ours.
You've no right to it.
[chuckling]
NARUTO: Hold it!
Chew on this!
-Ninja Art Kujaku.
NARUTO: Whoa!
Whoa!
You're not going anywhere!
Don't even think about it!
-Farewell.
-What is he doing?
That is it!
-Wait.
-Hey.
Let go of me, will you?
-Calm yourself.
That canyon is full
of poisonous gas.
-OK.
Maybe you've got a point.
-Without that mask, he would
have been dead in seconds.
-Darn it.
We almost had him.
-So that's our thief, huh?
-You got it.
100%.
NEJI: But why go so far as
to take Sumaru with him?
He already had the star,
-Someone tried to
steal it ten years ago.
This might be connected somehow.
Sumaru's parents
were guarding it,
and managed to fend
off the attack.
Only, they didn't make it.
-What?
[theme music]
NEJI: We need to search the
outskirts of the village again.
LEE: Leave it to me.
I have a new strategy
I have been working on.
TENTEN: Strategy?
LEE: Your Shadowing Ninjutsu
was not that reliable.
TENTEN: Excuse me?
NEJI: That's enough, you two.
Get going.
LEE: Right.
TENTEN: So, what's this
plan of yours anyway?
NARUTO: Yeah.
Let's hear it.
NEJI: Naruto, wait.
NARUTO: What is it?
Next time-- Hidden Jutsu.
The Price of the
Ninja Art Kujaku.
[theme music]