[music playing]
[explosion]
-Huh?
-The operation has begun.
[music playing]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Zero Hour!
The Destruction of the
Hidden Leaf Village Begins!
-Lord Hokage!
-Leave it to me!
-Lord Kazekage, what is this?
-Lord Hokage.
-Gaara!
-Squad one, above.
Squad two, below.
Protect the nobles.
You will not interfere!
[music playing]
-Lord Hokage, you must flee.
Escape now.
[music playing]
-Finally, it's my time.
-We've all been
waiting for this.
I was so frustrated
hiding in that disguise.
-You're all sweaty, too.
So gross.
-Come on.
We're all friends here, right?
THIRD HOKAGE
(VOICEOVER): Some ninja.
-Righto.
Let's go.
We have to back up Lord Hokage.
Be aware of traps.
-Yes, sir!
-Do it.
-Right.
Ninja art-- four
flames formation.
-A barrier.
We have to figure out a way
past this without dying.
But how?
-Lord Kazekage.
KAKASHI: That's a
barrier ninjutsu.
They outwitted the
ANBU black ops,
and the ANBU are
supposed to be the best.
-Why are you here?
Lord Hokage's in danger!
-What a nuisance.
-An enemy masquerading
as ANBU black ops.
So he was using genjutsu.
KAKASHI: Yes,
there's no mistake.
-I never.
The Sand Village has
betrayed the Leaf Village?
-The treaty between
our villages was simply
a trick to make you
let down your guard.
This petty little
battle game ends now.
From this point on, the
course of history will change.
-What are you saying?
That you're going
to start a war?
-That's right.
-Armed conflict
resolves nothing.
We should seek a resolution
through negotiation.
There's still time,
Lord Kazekage.
You can reconsider.
-Perhaps the fear of death
makes one more cowardly
with age, Sarutobi Sensei.
-You.
-Just my luck to have lookout
duty on a day like today.
What I really want is to
watch the chunin exam.
-Oh, stop.
The chunin exam takes
place twice a year.
You'll have plenty of chances.
-Yeah, but this year that
kid from the Uchiha clan
is taking part, isn't he?
I just hate to miss seeing that.
Well, my life will
be incomplete now.
[explosion]
-What's that?
-Now it's time.
Begin!
The summoning has succeeded.
-What in the?
-Notify Lord Hokage right away.
-You're not getting
into this village.
-Dispatch reinforcements!
-Yes, sir!
-The sand ninja.
-What's going on here?
TEMARI: Stop it, Gaara!
-I must kill him!
-There's no point in
continuing this fight.
-That's right.
Don't forget our mission.
-Out of my way.
-What are you three doing now?
Can't you see the
operation's already underway?
-What is going on?
Tell me!
-Gaara!
-What's wrong?
-His wound's worse
than I thought.
And his chakra's almost
completely drained away.
-Wait.
What about using that--
-It's impossible right now.
-You fool.
It's all because you
tried to transform
before the signal was given.
-So what do we do now?
We need Gaara for this.
-Isn't Gaara here yet?
-Gaara's the trump card of the
Village Hidden in the Sand.
We have to get him to play
his part, no matter what.
All right.
For now, you two take Gaara
and tend to his wounds.
As soon as his chakra
has been restored,
the operation will continue.
-You got it.
-And you, Sensei?
-I'm going to take
care of these guys.
-Do you really think that things
will go according to your plan?
-I'll make sure that they do.
Go!
-Yes, right.
[music playing]
-And is the host of
this party Orochimaru?
-Don't know.
And don't care.
Now let's heat things up, huh?
[music playing]
-Sasuke, I'm sorry, but the
chunin exam ends here for you.
You've already
achieved chunin level.
You're a Leaf Village
shinobi, so put your training
to good use.
-In other words, I'm supposed
to take down Gaara, right?
Our match continues?
-Just be careful.
It's the real thing
now, not a match.
-What I must do is the same.
-Not so fast!
-Sasuke.
FOURTH KAZEKAGE:
Well, well, well.
We had intended
to capture Sasuke
while Gaara was causing trouble.
But I suppose not everything
goes as planned, does it?
-I see.
So that was the plan.
Then the Hidden Leaf Village
and Sasuke were your targets.
Is that correct?
-Ha.
Do you really think that the
Leaf Village is so important?
Now, if Gaara returns,
I'll be able to show
you something very interesting.
Very interesting indeed.
But anyway, you're
stubborness and incompetence
have allowed me to
outmaneuver you.
I've defeated you.
-Hmph.
Nothing is decided
until the very end.
I taught you that
years ago, didn't I?
Orochimaru.
I knew, or at least
thought, this day
would eventually arrive.
However, you're not going
to defeat me that easily.
-I told you, didn't I?
You should have picked the
Fifth Hokage before now.
Because, Third Hokage,
right here, right now,
you are going to die.
IRUKA (VOICEOVER):
Well, I wonder
how the chunin exams are going?
I wonder if Naruto's
match is over yet?
The first match was
with Moegi, right?
Oh, I hope that Naruto
found some way to win.
-No, wait.
That's not right.
I mustn't play favorites.
Every student is equally
dear to their teacher
and I must root for them all.
Oh.
IRUKA (VOICEOVER):
I can't help it.
I still want Naruto to win.
-Are you worried about Naruto?
-Yes, of course I am.
-I thought so.
-But shouldn't you be-- I told
you to run ten laps, didn't I?
-Yeah, but we finished
that a long time ago.
-While you were
daydreaming, Sensei.
-Look, there's no way you
can teach a real class when
you're in this state.
So what do you say we just
call it quits for today.
-What?
Yeah, well, nice try.
No, the class will continue.
-Hey, look.
What's that smoke?
-Hmm?
It's coming from the
direction of the arena.
-Huh?
Do you guys see something
over there, too?
-I wonder what's going on today?
-Orochimaru.
-What should we do?
Should we send in
reinforcements?
-No.
It's risky to act when we
don't know the whole situation.
And if Orochimaru's behind
all this, even more so.
-Is Orochimaru-- I mean, is
he really that dangerous?
-Originally, he was the
Third Hokage's student.
-So why in the world did he
become a rogue ninja, then?
-Long ago, back when the
Fourth Hokage was decided,
Orochimaru apparently put forth
his own name for consideration.
But his request was denied.
Soon after, he severed all ties
with the Hidden Leaf Village.
He most likely holds a
grudge against the Third
Hokage because of that.
-He seeks revenge?
-I believe so.
When I was just a child, I saw
him one time, and I-- I had one
thought-- that he
didn't seem human to me.
That he was just some creature
that had taken on a human form.
It was frightening.
Simply frightening.
-Sir, I have a report.
Giant boas have appeared near
the eastern gate of the Leaf
Village, and with them,
a hundred sand ninja.
They've infiltrated
our village and are
battling our shinobi who
are patrolling there.
-The sand?
-Leave behind squads one and two
and head to the gate right now.
-Yes, sir!
[music playing]
-This is as far as
you're going to get.
-Quite a lot of them, huh?
-We've been careless.
And now even Lord Hokage-- huh?
Kakashi, look there,
inside the barrier.
-Huh?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): What is it?
-Orochimaru.
-Orochimaru!
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Why is he here?
Don't tell me he's
after Sasuke again.
-Hey, Sasuke!
What?
He's-- he's gone.
-Sakura, just stay there while
I trim the enemy's numbers
down to size.
[music playing]
-Nicely done.
But I'm worried
about Lord Hokage.
-Leave that to the
ANBU black ops.
We have enought to handle here.
Besides, Lord Hokage isn't
just some pushover, you know.
-Yeah, but--
-Just remember, Guy,
he is the Hokage.
He can handle it.
-Are you actually crying
because you're so happy?
Or is it that inside your
heart there is sorrow?
A feeling of
unhappiness you can't
shake as you contemplate
killing your old teacher?
-Not at all.
I was feeling so sleepy.
But now it seems
I'm finally awake.
-Yes, that's exactly
what I was thinking.
And I was also thinking that you
aren't the kind of person who
would hold a grudge.
So it seems that you have
neither a goal nor a motive.
-Huh.
I guess-- well, I guess that
I do kind of have a goal.
Let me see if I can explain it.
I find it very interesting
to watch things in motion.
I get no pleasure when
the world is still,
like a windmill
that isn't turning.
I suppose some might
find it beautiful,
even if it's immobile.
But to me, such a
thing is truly boring.
So now I want to put
things in motion myself.
The first step is
crushing the Leaf Village.
-Hmph.
I see you haven't
changed at all.
[music playing]
-Sakura, it was
worth teaching you
genjutsu during survival
training for the genin exam.
You truly do have
a talent for it.
-Huh?
-Release the genjutsu and
wake Naruto and Shikamaru.
Naruto will be delighted he'll
be getting a mission after such
a long time.
-What kind of mission?
-You'll have to be
careful on this one.
It's the first A-rank assignment
since the Land of the Waves.
[music playing]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Yeah!
I've been waiting for
this for a long time!
Finally, an A-ranked mission!
Listen, Sakura and Shikamaru,
as long as I'm with you guys,
this'll be easy.
I'm so good I'm
practically a superhero.
Just keep watching me and you'll
see how good a ninja can be.
Next time-- Village in
Distress-- A New A-Ranked
Mission.
Let's get busy!