[music playing]
[theme music]
[seagulls squawking]
[waves lapping]
[groaning]
-I think I overdid
it with my Sharingan.
-Waking up, huh?
Are you all right?
-I've been better.
It'll be a week before
I can move normally.
-See, it's better if you
don't move, so just lie down.
[groaning]
-Right.
-Look, the Sensei's
coming around.
-Listen, Sensei, your Sharingan
is amazing and everything,
but if it puts that
much strain on you,
maybe it's not worth it.
-Sorry.
[grunt]
-Well, you did take down one
of the most powerful ninja
assassins, so we'll
be safe for a while.
-Right, but you know that boy
with the mask, what about him?
-He's from the
elite tracking unit
of the village
hidden in the mist.
Those masks are only worn
by the most elite Shinobi.
[loud squawking]
-What exactly do they do?
The Anbu Black Ops, also
known as The Inferno Squad,
destroy all traces of
a rogue ninja's corpse.
The Shinobi's body contains
many secrets-- ninjutsu,
chakra, special medicines
used on his body.
These are the secrets
of his village.
If his enemies find them, his
people will be in grave danger.
For instance, if I were to
die at the hands of an enemy,
he would try to
analyze my Sharingan.
In the worst case,
my entire jutsu
could be stolen and used
against our home village.
It is the sacred duty
of the Shinobi trackers
to prevent this, to keep
the village secrets safe.
If a ninja betrays his
village, the trackers
hunt him down, eliminate
him, and obliterate
every trace of his existence.
That's their specialty.
-First, I'll cut the bandage
and drain some of the blood.
[gasp]
-That's enough.
I'll do it.
-So, you've already
come back to life.
[groaning]
-Damn it.
You're brutal, Haku.
-You're the one
who's brutal, Zabuza.
If you keep pulling
them out like that,
you really will be finished.
[clinking]
-How long are you planning
to wear that phony mask?
Take it off.
-I have good memories
of this mask.
And it was quite useful
for tricking that ninja.
If I hadn't intervened,
you'd be dead now.
That much is certain.
-Putting me in a temporary
death state is fine,
but not through the
pressure points in my neck.
Cruel as usual.
I think you enjoy it.
-It was the only sure way.
And I wouldn't want to
mark up your flawless body.
You'd complain about
that even more.
The neck is more vulnerable.
There's no layer of muscle,
so I could go straight
into the pressure points.
[groaning]
-There's no point
trying to move.
You'll be numb for a week.
Although, if you're
as stubborn as usual,
you'll probably be
moving in half the time.
-You're so innocent.
And you're clever
at the same time.
Rare combination.
That's why I keep you around.
[laughing]
-I'm still a kid.
What else would you expect?
The mist is cleared.
[grunting]
-Next time, will you all right?
-Next time, I'll see right
through his Sharingan.
NARUTO: The Forest of Chakra.
-What is this?
If Zabuza is finished,
why do I feel this way?
Something's wrong.
It's like I missed something.
-Hey, are you OK?
Sensei.
-Hm?
Oh, yeah.
To finish what I was
saying, tracker ninja
deal with the body
immediately, on the spot,
so there's no room for error.
-Is that really important?
-Think about it.
Do you remember what that
tracker did with Zabuza's body?
SAKURA: We don't
know what he did.
I mean, I guess he
took it away somewhere.
KAKASHI: Exactly.
But why?
He should have worked on
Zabuza right there, as
quickly as possible.
Think of the weapons he
used for the takedown.
Do you remember what they were?
-Throwing needles.
No way.
-Exactly.
None of it adds up.
-Huh.
-What are you all
yammering about?
You demolished that assassin.
-Here's the truth.
Zabazu's still alive.
[screaming]
[gasp]
-But we saw his body.
Believe it.
-Kakashi Sensei, you
checked him yourself.
You said that his heart stopped.
-His heart did stop.
But, that was just a temporary
state to simulate death.
The weapons that tracker
used are called senbon.
They can pierce
deeply but rarely
kill unless they hit a vital
organ, not in the neck.
They're modified from needles
used for medical treatments,
like acupuncture.
Trackers are trained to know
every detail of the human body.
Causing the heart
to stop temporarily
while keeping the body alive
is an easy matter for them.
First, he carried
Zabuza's body away,
even though it's much
heavier than he is.
Second, he used senbon,
which have a precise effect
but are rarely fatal.
From these two factors,
we can conclude
that the tracker wasn't
trying to destroy Zabuza.
He was trying to save him.
-Come on, you're over-thinking
this, aren't you?
-Encountering suspicion,
the ninja prepares quickly.
Hesitation leads to disaster.
Every Shinobi knows this saying.
-Ahhh.
[laughing]
-He's actually pleased
to hear Zabuza's alive.
Now Naruto's got
another shot at him.
-Sensei, you said, prepare
quickly, but how can
we do that when you
can barely move?
[laughing]
-Huh?
-I can still train you.
-Hold on.
A little last minute
training won't make us
strong enough to fight Zabuza.
You could barely defeat him
even with your Sharingan.
We have to be
reasonable about this.
[clash]
-Yeah, trying to get us killed?
Jah.
-Sakura, why was I
able to stop Zabuza?
Because, you all helped me.
You've grown.
Naruto,
-Huh?
-You've grown the most.
[nervous laughter]
-[thinking to herself] He
does seem stronger and more
confident, but--
-So you noticed, Kakashi Sensei.
Now things are
going to get better.
Believe it.
-I don't believe it.
And nothing's going to be good.
-Huh?
-Who are you?
-Arg.
Inari, where have you been?
-Welcome back, Grandpa.
-Inari, that was very rude.
These ninja helped your grandpa
and brought him here safely.
-It's OK.
It's OK.
I'm rude to them, too.
[laughing]
[drum beating]
-Mom, don't you see, these
people are going to die.
Gato and his men will come back
and find them and wipe them
out.
-What did you say, brat?
-Listen up.
You know what a super ninja is?
Well that's me,
only a lot better.
I'm going to be Okage.
-This Gato or Blato or
whatever he's called
is no match for a
real hero like me.
-Ha.
There's no such thing as a hero.
You're just full
of stupid ideas.
-What'd you say?
-Naruto, calm down.
-If you want to stay
alive, you should go back
where you came from.
[footsteps walking away]
-Inari, wait.
Where are you going?
-To look out at the ocean.
I want to be alone.
-Grr, grr, grrr.
-Sorry about that.
-Grr.
Ahh.
-Who does that brat think he is?
I'm going to put him
in his place right now.
[seagulls cawing]
[crying]
-Huh?
He's crying?
[crying]
-No, Daddy, no.
-All right.
Training starts now.
-Right.
First , we will begin
with a review of chakra,
the ninja's basic
source of power.
Understanding
chakra is essential.
-We know that.
-He's right.
A long time ago we learned
about-- uh, cattra.
-Chakra.
-Daa.
-Go ahead, Sakura.
-All right, Naruto.
I'll explain it simply
so you can understand it.
Chakra is the elemental life
energy a ninja uses in jutsu.
It's the source
of all his power.
Now, this energy has two
forms, physical energy
which exists in all the cells
in the entire body, all working
together and spiritual energy,
the primal source of power
which is intensified through
training and experience.
As you see, these
two types of chakra
must be drawn out
and brought together
in order to perform jutsu.
Notice the interplay between
physical and spiritual power.
That's the key.
Finally, hand signs focus
and unleash the chakra.
-Right on all points.
Iruka Sensei really did have
some excellent students.
-Ha.
-What's the big deal with all
these complicated explanations?
The whole point is to
learn the jutsu, isn't it?
-Naruto is right for once.
We're already using chakra
energy in our jutsu.
-No.
You have not
mastered this power.
You've barely scratched
the surface of it.
-What do you mean?
-Calm down and listen.
It's just like Sakura said.
You have to draw on physical
and spiritual energies
and then combine
them within yourself.
But how do you do that?
Each jutsu requires
different types
of chakra in
different proportions.
You must select and combine
them in exactly the right way.
Up to now, you've just
guessed at the proportions,
hoping they'd come out right.
Even if you produce
a lot of chakra,
unless you can balance and
control it, it's all worthless.
The jutsu won't work at all
or it'll just be a joke.
You waste so much
energy that way.
Then you're out of chakra
and you can't fight at all.
You're just a target.
-So how do we change that?
-Train so hard that
controlling your chakra
become second nature.
To achieve this goal
you must be ready to put
your life on the line.
-What do we have to do?
-[chuckling] Climb a tree.
-Climb a tree?
-That's right.
But there's just one rule.
No hands.
-What?
You're kidding.
-Am I?
Let's see.
[gasp]
-He's climbing.
-Straight up.
And he's only using his feet.
-Well, you get the idea.
Focus the chakra toward
the soles of your feet
and use it to
connect to the tree.
This is one way to apply
the power of chakra.
-Wait a minute.
That's a nice trick, but
how does it help us fight
-It's the only way to fight him,
Sakura.
That's the entire
goal of this training.
First, you'll learn to draw
a precise amount of chakra
to a precise point in your body.
This is difficult, even
for advanced ninja.
This type of climbing
requires a subtle mix
of physical and
spiritual energy.
And the bottoms of the feet
are the most difficult points
to focus chakra.
Are you getting the picture?
If you can master this, you'll
be able to master any jutsu.
Well, theoretically.
The second point is to learn
to maintain your chakra levels.
When a ninja is
focused in battle,
it's even harder to
control and maintain
his chakra levels,
a deadly mistake.
To avoid this,
maintaining chakra
must become second
nature, effortless.
Well, I can talk
about this all day
but that won't advance
your skills, will it?
You need to apply the power
of chakra through training.
[gasp]
Use the Kunai knife
to mark the tree
at the highest point you can
climb without using your hands.
Then, try to get past that mark
the next time and the next.
At first, you'll need
to run at the tree
so your momentum can take
you as highest as possible
until you used to it.
Ready?
-I'm more than ready.
This is going to be
no sweat all the way.
Believe it.
Remember what you
said, Sensei, I'm
the one who's grown the most.
-You're definitely the
one who talks the most.
Now get focused and do it.
-[thinking to himself]
Well, he did say that.
OK, first I need to draw the
chakra to bottom of my feet.
I got it.
Charge.
[grunting]
-[thinking to himself] This
is harder than I thought.
The balance has to be perfect.
If the chakra's too
strong, it smashes the tree
and pushes you off.
-Ahh.
-But if it's not
strong enough, you just
tumble back down, like Naruto.
[grunting]
-That's about what I expected
from Sasuke and Naruto.
-Hey, this is fun.
-Sakura.
[laughing]
-Well, looks like the
female member of the squad
has the most advanced
chakra control.
Well done, Sakura.
[laughing]
-Yeah, way to go, Sakura.
I always knew you were awesome.
Believe it.
-[thinking to himself] It does
sort of tick me off, though.
-[thinking to himself] Whatever.
-[thinking to herself] I thought
Sasuke would be impressed.
Now he's mad at me.
Why is it always like that?
-Well, not only does
Sakura understand chakra,
she can control and
maintain it as well.
We spoke about someone becoming
Hokage one day, didn't we?
Seems Sakura's got the
best chance of that,
wouldn't you say?
And as for the
great Uchiha clan,
but maybe they're not
so great after all.
-[thinking to herself]
Shut up, Sensei.
You talk too much.
Sasuke is going to hate me now.
-All right.
I think they're motivated.
Of course, Naruto and Sasuke
both have far more chakra
within.
If this training works,
their mastery of chakra
will become a valuable asset.
-All right.
First, I'll match Sasuke.
Then I'm going all
the way to the top.
Believe it.
-What a waste of time.
They don't know what
they're up against.
Mmm.
[grunting]
[door opening and then closing]
Samjonin, the unbeatable
ninja just got beat.
Limping back home like
some pathetic has been.
[chuckling] Demon
of the hidden mist.
[laughing] More like
coward of the hidden mist.
-Drawing swords?
-Hang on a minute.
All right.
Let's hear what you have
to say about this fiasco.
And don't play possum.
I know you can talk.
-Keep your filthy
hands off of him.
-Ahh, you're going to break it.
[clash of swords]
-That's impossible.
No one can move that fast.
-Don't push me.
I'm in a really foul mood.
-Arrg.
[clatter of swords]
-One chance.
That's it.
If you fail this time,
I'll cut you off.
And there'll be no one
left to cover for you.
Let's go.
[footsteps ]
[door opening and closing]
-Haku, that wasn't necessary.
-Perhaps.
But it's too early
to take out Gato.
He's still our best cover.
Think about it.
The murders will
draw their attention.
Then they'd be after us again.
We need restraint.
-[sighing] You're right.
-Ah.
Uh.
Ahh.
Huh.
[heavy breathing]
-[thinking to herself]
I'm totally worn out.
How can they just
keep going like that?
-Ow.
Ow.
Ah.
-[thinking to herself] Naruto
isn't making any progress
at all.
Knowing him, any
minute now, he'll
give up and throw a tantrum.
There he goes.
He's so predictable,
it's embarrassing.
Hm?
-Hey, you're good at this.
How about some advice?
-Uhh.
-But please don't
tell Sasuke I asked.
Please, please.
-He's catching on.
From now on, he'll get
stronger and stronger.
How strong?
After all, Naruto possess
more chakra than Sasuke.
In fact, the amount
of chakra he possesses
is greater than my own.
[music]
Cultivate your hunger
before you idealize.
Motivate your anger to
make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain,
never coming down.
Break into the contents,
never falling down.
My knee is still shaking,
like I was twelve,
Sneaking out of the
classroom, by the back door.
A man railed at me twice
though, but I didn't care.
Waiting is wasting
for people like me.
Don't try to live so wise.
Don't cry because
you're so right.
Don't dry with fakes or fears
Because you will hate
yourself in the end.
Don't try to live so wise.
Don't cry because
you're so right.
Don't dry with fakes or fears
Because you will hate
yourself in the end.
Don't try to live so wise.
Don't cry because
you're so right.
Don't dry--
-That boy, Inari.
He's always off by
himself, crying, always
looking out at the ocean,
tears running down his face,
always alone.
What's all that
crying going to do?
I mean, how can
that help anything?
And what made him
so sad, anyway?
Next time-- The Land
Where A Hero Once Lived.
Watch me get even stronger.
Believe it.