[theme music]
[laughter]
-Ye, you will be set free.
And before that, I will
grant you one wish.
Don't worry, your
strength of spirit
was one of the main
reasons I chose you.
And I'd be foolish to
let it go to waste.
Your residual aura
will live on in me.
Well, then, I thank
you for your body.
[scream]
-So it's done.
And now it will be a few years
before he can transfer again.
But next time--
-It's as you say-- my damaged
body is of no use to him
as a vessel for the
Transference Jutsu.
That was my purpose,
and it's gone.
What is there left to
give my existing meaning?
I see now what I must do.
I was not meant
to be the vessel.
I was meant to find the vessel
and bring it safely here.
Even at the cost of my life.
That is the only way I can repay
Lord Orochimaru for my failure.
The only way to give my
worthless existence some value.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Miscalculation!
A New Enemy Appears!
-He's fast.
-Arf!
-Akamaru!
Once you've set the
bombs, get moving!
-Arf!
-Huh?
Oh, no!
-All right.
-He fell for it!
-Akamaru!
Nice work, buddy!
-Arf!
-Don't you mess with me!
Arf!
-Akamaru!
No!
-That's the last time
you'll bark at me, you mutt!
-Arf!
-You won't get away.
-Hang on!
[shout]
-Kiba!
Akamaru!
-I can't see them!
[scream]
-Damn!
-Dammit!
What's happening?
Where are they?
[shout]
-You're mine now!
-Kiba and Akamaru
are still gone!
-And we've got another
one to deal with.
There's no other way.
I'll have to take
care of this one.
You take the coffin and
carry on with the mission.
-Shikamaru--
SHIKAMARU: Just get going.
-Huh?
-What?
What are you doing here?
-Sorry, Naruto.
It looks like I miscalculated.
-Kimimaro.
-You were taking
too long, Tayuya.
And what of our comrades?
What happened to
our other three men?
This from the former members
of the Sound Ninja Five.
-Huh?
-Why have you come back here?
Your body is-- by now,
your body should be--
-My body is too devastated
to move on its own anymore.
I used the power of my mind.
-No way.
Now you're cheating death?
-I understand much more now.
The strength of my life
force has intensified
since escaping the
prison of human flesh.
I've had a taste of Lord
Orochimaru's magnificent dream.
-Orochimaru!
-This vessel is an
important part of his dream.
It has the flesh that
Lord Orochimaru desires.
-But you have taken too
much time retrieving it.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
Another freak to deal with.
He doesn't seem like
an ordinary opponent.
We need to buy time and
sort out the situation.
It'd be dumb to confront
him without knowing--
-Hey, jerk!
-Huh?
-I've had just about
enough of this nonsense
you're yakking about!
-Naruto!
-I'm taking Sasuke back now!
-Hey, wait a second!
-Tayuya, I could end your your
life right now if I wished to.
The reason I've
decided to spare you
is because you have a duty
that you must complete.
And my duty is to deliver
that coffin to Lord Orochimaru
intact.
-But I thought you said
it was too late for that.
-You weren't listening.
I told you that's the body that
Lord Orochimaru desires more
than anything else.
-It's his next vessel, isn't it?
-Exactly, Tayuya.
And delivering it to
him is the only thing
that I can do to please him.
As for those two pieces of
garbage, I leave them to you.
-He's taking Sasuke!
Not again!
I gotta go get him!
-Just calm down, Naruto.
-How can I calm down?
We're losing him!
He's gonna take
Sasuke away from us!
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
Naruto's right.
Our mission is to find
Sasuke and bring him back
to the Leaf Village.
We've got to choose the path
that's best for the mission.
And if we don't, we'll fail.
-You rodents.
I'm gonna end this in a flash.
-Naruto, listen to me.
-Hm?
-I've got a plan, but you've
got to follow it exactly.
-Hmph.
His only good move is
that Shadow Clone Jutsu.
Classic close range moron.
And that one's a mid
range combat type.
Traps his enemies
with the shadow jutsu.
Thinks he's a pretty
sharp platoon leader, huh?
-All right, you got it?
-Yeah.
-Well, let's get on
with it, you wimps.
-It's two on one.
We've got the advantage.
If we gang up on her,
we've got a good shot.
What you say, Naruto?
-Let's get her!
-Ha!
It doesn't matter how
many of you there are,
you're still a pair
of worthless morons!
-Don't be cocky.
We've got teamwork on our side.
-We'll show you!
-Bring it on!
-Now, Naruto!
-I'm gonna punch
your lights out!
Ha, she fell for it.
This plan is working!
I'll see you around!
-What the-- That whole
thing was a trick!
Teamwork my foot, you dirty,
conniving little weasels!
Nice try.
-You sure talk a
pretty big game,
but you fell for the
oldest trick in the book.
-You fool.
You got some nerve
-Oh well.
At least I bought enough time
for my friend to get away.
Hey, remember this.
A person's jutsu
isn't his only weapon.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Shikamaru.
I'm counting on you.
Just hand in here, Sasuke.
-That poor boy.
It's amazing that he could
still move with that body.
Kabuto.
I don't know what kind
of order you gave him,
but it seems a bit
cruel, if you ask me.
-Oh, not at all.
I gave him no order.
I don't really like to
force people to do things
against their will, my lord.
He acted on his own volition.
He did it all for you.
Out of reverence.
-Kabuto.
You are quite a hateful,
nasty person, aren't you?
-Lord Orochimaru, Kimimaro
was the perfect match.
He existed solely for you.
His thoughts were steeped in
eternal darkness, as yours are.
Yet he sanctified you.
He deified and worshiped you.
Moreover, he came
from the shinobi clan
with the strongest
and most ideal bodies.
He had a genuine Kekkei Genkai.
Well, that is,
until just recently.
-Yes.
When I think about having
lost such a specimen,
I still can't accept it.
I can't get him out of my head.
The man best suited
for my spirit,
the body I wanted the most.
Kimimaro.
-And if he hadn't been
stricken with illness,
the assassination of the Hokage
would've gone much smoother.
-The seal is set!
-My-- my arms.
-There you have it.
Your arms are
useless to you now.
And without those arms, you will
never form another hand sign.
Ninjutsu is forever
out of your reach.
Your loathsome dream of
crushing this village dies here!
Your foolishness is
unparallelled, Orochimaru.
My one regret is that I
couldn't take you with me.
Farewell, disciple.
May we meet again
in the next world.
-They're not here yet.
Still no sign of Sasuke.
-We wouldn't have needed to
go through such an ordeal.
But in this world,
all too often, things
don't work out quite
as we want them to.
KABUTO (VOICEOVER): It's
only a matter of time
now, Lord Orochimaru.
KIMIMARO (VOICEOVER):
When Tayuya comes back,
I'll have to kill her.
-Hold it right there!
Hey.
-Let's see.
How shall I destroy you?
Interesting.
Those eyes.
It seems this one possesses
an unusual chakra.
-Tell me what Orochimaru
is planning to do!
And why the heck's he
trying to get Sasuke so bad?
-Lord Orochimaru has already
acquired the immortality jutsu,
but a vast amount
of time is required
to obtain every jutsu
and everything he
wants from this world.
-So what?
What does that have
to do with Sasuke?
-Just because he is immortal
doesn't mean his body
can maintain itself forever.
So before his flesh
decays, a strong, new body
must be made into a
vessel for his soul.
-Are you saying that he's
gonna use Sasuke's body?
-That's right.
Precisely.
-No.
Not Sasuke.
I won't let you do it!
-You idiot.
You really think sending
that little shrimp will
stop anything?
Besides, just think
about what's happened
to your team up to this point.
You probably had to sacrifice
one member each time
you faced an obstacle just
so you could keep moving.
I mean, what the heck is so
special about this Sasuke guy
anyway?
How many are you gonna
lose just to save this one
insignificant shinobi?
You're pretty dumb for a leader.
-You got a point there.
You see, this mission
we're on is my first one
as platoon leader, and
it's pretty nerve-wracking
to see your comrades
whittles down like this.
To be honest, I don't know
if the decisions I made
were the right ones.
As platoon leader, I'm
responsible for the safety
of my men.
You would think I'd value the
lives of my four teammates
over the life of one guy
who's been taken prisoner.
It's a dangerous mission,
and if I decided to scrap it,
I'd have been
playing by the book.
-Of course.
Then why didn't you scrap it?
-It's kind of funny.
The world doesn't seem to play
by book very often, does it?
Besides, there isn't a
single person in my platoon
who would ever stop fighting
and abandon a friend who
had been captured by the enemy.
Not even if it meant
sacrificing all of their lives.
That goes for me, too.
Frankly, I'm a lazy,
cloud watching oaf,
who's not really cut
out to be a leader
or bark out orders at anyone.
But, there is one
thing I do pretty darn
well for my teammates.
And that's believing in them.
Listen.
I don't look at what I've
done as sacrificing my men.
In fact, I don't even believe
that any of them are dead.
Don't insult my
friends, or you'll pay.
-[inaudible]!
-Summoning Jutsu!
-That's not good.
Oh, well.
-I'll play a little
melody of death for you.
You shouldn't insult me or
my friends either, you worm!
-Oh.
-There's no way you're
gonna take Sasuke!
-How amusing.
[theme music]
KIBA: What am I supposed to do?
Even when they're in their
normal state, they're tough.
But when their chakras
increase to enormous levels--
[barking]
-No.
I can't!
I can't use it here.
Not yet.
I may have no choice.
The way this is going,
we're not gonna--
[barking]
-You're right, Akamaru.
We have to do it!
NARUTO: Next time, Roar and
Howl, The Ultimate Tag Team!
[roar]
[theme music]