[music playing]
-All right.
Moving on to the next match.
-This year's rookies
look like they
could be quite a challenge.
-Yeah!
It's here!
It's here at last!
The moment I've
been waiting for.
Finally I get a chance
to show what I've got.
-Look at that.
It's us against the kid.
Hey Akamaru, I think you
and I just won the lottery.
NARRATOR (VOICEOVER):
It's your moment, Naruto.
Go on, show us.
Show us how much you've grown.
-It's my time to shine.
NARUTO UZUMAKI:
Akamaru unleashed.
Who's top dog now?
-Now the seventh match, Naruto
Uzumaki and Kiba Inuzuka.
-I've been waiting
forever for this.
Sorry, Kiba.
Don't take it personally
if I blow you away.
-That's just what
I was going to say.
Only not so politely.
Right, Akamaru?
-Oh, yeah?
Well, talking is easy.
Let's see what you've got to
say at the end of the match.
-Little squirt.
-Wait a second.
Are you kidding me?
What's the puppy doing here?
He's just going
to get in the way.
-Deal with it.
I never go into battle
without Akamaru.
-Come on, isn't that against
the rules or something?
-No.
Like Shino's bugs,
they are a part of him.
He is within the rules.
-Whatever.
Fine with me.
I do my best work
with a handicap.
-We'll just see about that.
Akamaru, you stay right here
and leave all this to me.
I've got it.
-Go on, Naruto!
You can't lose to this jerk.
-The moment is finally here.
(VOICEOVER) Sorry,
Kakashi, but your boy
doesn't stand a
chance against Kiba.
Not a chance.
(VOICEOVER) Kiba is on my team.
I should be rooting
for him, but I really
want to support Naruto.
Kiba wouldn't like
it, but even so--
(VOICEOVER) Naruto.
-Oh, man.
Kiba is so lucky.
(VOICEOVER) I wonder how much
stronger he's gotten since he
became a Genin?
INSTRUCTOR: Today we'll work
on your transformation Jutsu.
Let's see you transform
into Lord Hokage.
(VOICEOVER) Because if he's
anything like he used to be--
-Transform!
-Hey, what's going on?
I was having such a nice nap.
-Just kidding.
Just kidding.
You didn't think that
was for real, did you?
-That's enough, Naruto.
It's your third
year at the academy.
Now straighten up.
-How pathetic.
Who the heck is that kid?
-I'm glad we switched
to this class.
That guy is hysterical.
-Yeah.
He sure keeps things
interesting, doesn't he?
-Mr. Popularity.
-Try it again, and
no fooling around.
-Transform!
-Incredible.
Are you serious?
[laughing]
-Is this kid for real?
You've been here
three years and can't
do a decent transformation?
What a joke.
-I don't have to
pretend to be hokage.
You just wait.
Someday I'm going to
be hokage for real.
Then you'll be sorry.
-Yeah right.
On what planet?
-Look, I feel sorry for you.
So I'm going to finish
you off with one shot, K?
-Yeah?
Is that right?
Man, you're even
dumber than you look
if you think you can beat me.
-You sure talk tough for
such a little squirt.
-When you're ready,
you can begin.
-Ninja art of beast
mimicry all force jutsu.
-Here I come.
-This little guy is going
to be out for a while.
You can call the match.
-Thought as much.
-Yeah.
I thought Kiba might be too
much for him, but that was fast.
-Oh, Naruto.
That was embarrassing.
-See?
Told you.
-What was that?
-I blinked and it was over.
That kid is pitiful.
(VOICEOVER) Naruto!
(VOICEOVER) So that's it.
-And my future dream is
to be the greatest hokage.
Then the whole village
will stop disrespecting me
and start treating me like I'm
somebody-- somebody important.
(VOICEOVER) I always
made fun of his boasting.
I thought he was crazy.
NARUTO UZUMAKI: So this
is what a Jonin is.
A true elite ninja.
I've got to get away.
If I don't, seriously,
he'll annihilate me.
-You're not hurt, are you?
Scaredy-cat.
Unless you have what it
takes to prove me wrong.
-How do you like this?
-Stupid fool.
You don't know
what you're doing!
-I may not know the
password, but there's
no way you're the Sasuke I know.
Let's see you try it!
-What?
No way.
-I was wrong about him.
-Hey, kid.
You're not hurt, are you?
You scaredy-cat.
No way.
I never go back on my word.
That's the way of the ninja.
(VOICEOVER) Come on, Naruto.
Show them what you got.
Don't ever-- don't
ever underestimate me!
-Yeah!
-The kid's come a long way.
-Naruto!
-Atta boy, Naruto!
-Yeah, yeah.
More tough talk.
Look at yourself in a mirror.
You're a mess.
-I just wanted to
see what you've got.
Frankly, you hit
like an old lady.
You have a better
chance of winning this
if you send that puppy
in to fight for you.
-You're going to regret that.
Come on, Akamaru.
-Smoke grenades?
-Take this!
-This sucks.
I can't see a thing.
Gotta get out of this
smoke-- and fast!
-He fell for it.
-What the?
-Darn.
The best part, and I
can't see anything.
-Yeah!
This fight is over.
Good doggy.
Way to--
Hey Akamaru, what are you doing?
What are you doing?
-Surprise!
Gotcha!
-You used a
transformation jutsu!
You little-- get off!
Let go of me!
-You smell even
worse than the dog.
-What did you do with him?
Where is he?
-He's right here.
-How did you-- OK.
-Woah.
Is that really Naruto?
Who would've thought that Naruto
would be a match for Kiba?
-To balance a transformation
jutsu and a clone
jutsu at the same
time-- there's no way
he should be able to do that.
-He's got his jutsu down.
There's no doubt about it.
-Well, well.
Kid's better than I thought.
(VOICEOVER) He's certainly
an interesting one.
It's not every day
you see a Shinobi who
would bite his opponent.
-Wasn't that amazing?
Amazing!
-That was amazing, Naruto!
-What do you know?
Gotten a little stronger, I see.
But not nearly strong enough.
Because now I'm getting serious.
-Oh?
Well, good.
I was hoping you
would, because I
want to seriously knock you out.
-He's gone to a
higher level just
during the course of this match.
That boy never
ceases to amaze me.
(VOICEOVER) Can this really
be the same little goof ball?
-I don't know what
happened, but this
ain't the Naruto
we used to know.
(VOICEOVER) Whatever
training method Kakashi used,
it sure worked.
(VOICEOVER) But still--
-Huh?
(VOICEOVER) He's
about to find out
that Kiba and Akamaru
have tricks of their own.
-Naruto, if I were you,
I'd let Akamaru go.
-What the heck happened?
What was that thing you fed him?
How come all his
fur just turned red?
-Are you sure you want to
stick around to find out?
(VOICEOVER) Food pills.
(VOICEOVER) That's it.
Kiba is going in for the kill.
-Let's go, Akamaru!
Beast mimicry!
-Man beast clones!
-He's got a crazy look in
his eyes all of the sudden.
Hey, wait a second,
he took something!
No fair!
That's cheating!
He ought to be disqualified!
-Food pills.
They're just another tool.
They're allowed.
-You're no help at all!
-I don't get it.
What was that stuff he ate?
-Those are food pills.
-They're what?
-It's something the
military developed.
An energy booster
that's so powerful
that troops who take it can
fight for three days and nights
without a break.
But after extended
battling, it can
result in high levels of anxiety
and almost total exhaustion.
Right now, Kiba and
Akamaru's Chakra
is at least doubled in strength.
-Let's finish this.
Now!
On all fours!
Jutsu!
-Naruto!
-It's bad news for Naruto.
Kiba already fights
like a wild beast.
His chakra is intense enough
even without enhancement.
The idea of these pills doubling
the strength of his chakra--
well, they're the
perfect weapon for Kiba.
(VOICEOVER) Oh no!
Naruto!
-They've got me off balance.
Can't counter attack.
All I can do is try
and keep on my feet
and stay out of their way.
-Now I got you!
Man beast ultimate taijutsu!
Bang over bang!
-I told you it was
going to get serious.
-I will-- I will be hokage.
I will.
-And how are you
going to do that?
By lying flat on your face?
I got news for you.
I'm going to be hokage.
[laughs]
Come on.
Do you really believe a
weakling like you can be hokage?
You must be weak in the head.
[laughs]
(VOICEOVER) No.
You're wrong, Kiba.
Weak?
That's one thing Naruto isn't.
-Someday you'll see.
I'll be Lord Hokage!
I'll show you.
All of you.
(VOICEOVER) Unlike me,
unlike the rest of the world,
Naruto always
believed in himself.
It was amazing to see
how difficult everything
was for him.
But he never gave up.
Always alone, no
one watching him.
No one helping him.
No one cared what
happened to him.
-There.
You see him?
-It's that boy.
I heard he's the
only one who failed.
-Well, it serves him right.
-Just imagine what would
happen if he became a ninja?
I mean, he's the boy who--
-Shh.
We're not allowed
to talk about that.
(VOICEOVER) No
one respected him.
No one even acknowledged him.
-Shadow clone jutsu!
(VOICEOVER) But now--
now everyone is watching.
-On your feet, Naruto!
(VOICEOVER) Everyone
is acknowledging him.
-Sorry, but you can
forget about being hokage,
because I'm the top
dog around here.
[music playing]
NARUTO UZUMAKI: This guy Kiba
is either desperate or dumb.
He's hitting me with
all his jutsu at once.
A ninja has gotta be
careful about that.
You never know when your jutsu
might come back to haunt you.
The tables have turned.
He's kicked me around
pretty good so far.
Now I'm going to give it
back to him in spades.
Next time, surprise attack.
Naruto's secret weapon.
Look out, Kiba.
Have I got a surprise for you!