[theme song in Japanese]
-Aah.
-Uhhh.
-Dammit, Naruto.
- "Zero Motivation:
The Guy with Cloud Envy."
[crowd booing]
-They don't care
about this match.
I'm just the warm up
for the main event.
All they care about
is watching Sasuke.
Listen to them, the jerks.
Well, if that's the way
they're going to be,
maybe I won't give
them a match at all.
Why knock myself out for them?
-What is it?
You planning on giving up, too?
-And to top it off, my
opponent's a girl, again.
-Well, he never was
very driven, but this?
-Come on, come on.
Get up and fight.
Get it together Shikamaru.
You going to get going
sometime this year?
-Well, if you will move, I will.
-Hey, I didn't
start the match yet.
I forgot.
This girl's a spunky one.
I hate spunky.
-Aah.
-What?
Huh?
-It really doesn't make
a whole lot of difference
to me whether I ever
become a Chuunin or not,
but I guess maybe
I shouldn't let
myself get beaten by a female.
So let's do it.
-Aaagh.
Huh?
He's quick when it
comes to running away.
-I know it's not very classy
for a guy to clobber a girl,
but whoever said I was classy?
-Nice try, but I know
what the game is.
-Shadow Possession Jutsu!
-He's trying to lure me to
the shadow of that tree.
I'm not falling for that.
-So why do I always
have to fight girls?
It sucks, man.
-Go for it, Shikamaru.
Use a super, awesome
technique on her,
and take that bitch down.
-Yo, this seat taken?
-I thought you were
in the hospital.
Your stomach's OK now?
-Um-hmm.
What's up?
I thought Sasuke's match
was supposed to be next.
-Shhhh.
-Hmm?
-Oh, I'm sure Sasuke's fine.
He'll be here any minute now.
Man, you'd think her
puppy died or something.
-Hmm.
Never expected to see
Shikamaru the final.
Weird.
-What do you mean?
Come on.
Shikamaru may not have
as much fighting spirit
as some other people.
And OK, his technique
is pretty lousy,
but he's strong at strategy.
So strong, in fact,
that without him, we
might not have gotten through
the preliminary round.
-Huh?
Maybe.
-Once more, you
should have seen how
he threw himself into the arena.
I'm telling you, Choji, he
seems unusually aggressive.
I think he's going to show
us his passionate side today.
Yeah, go Shikamaru.
-Ah, sometimes I wish I was
a cloud just floating along,
going wherever the
breeze takes me.
That's my style.
I'm just not into putting
effort in this stuff.
The only reason I
became a Ninja was
so I could do whatever I wanted.
Gees, who knew it
would be so much work?
-Get your butt in gear.
Let's go, Shikamaru.
-Oh, well, a guy's gotta
do what a guys' gotta do.
-What's he thinking
behind that stupid grin?
Is he mocking me?
Ninja Art.
[inaudible]
-Aaah.
-Remember, this is how
she beat me in our fights.
Nothing I threw at
her could get past it.
-Now I get it.
Almost got me.
Aren't you clever with
that Shadow Possession
Jutsu of yours,
you can manipulate
any shadow you're in.
The Wall Shadow for instance.
But there's a
limit, isn't there?
No matter how thin you stretch
it, it will only reach so far.
Isn't that right?
-You got me.
-And now, I know just
where that limit is.
Even using the Wall Shadow, his
Jutsu can only reach to here.
15 meters, 32 centimeters.
That's the range of his attack.
If I can just stay outside
this line, he can't touch me.
-She's measured his range.
This plays right
to her strength.
She's better at long
range attacks anyway.
This match is as good as over.
-Huh?
-What's that?
A hand sign?
-No, he's not
making a hand sign.
It's something
more like a habit.
-A habit?
-That kid, he's like an old man.
He likes to take things slowly.
I mean, really slowly.
That's why he's so good at
games like, Go and Shogi.
He's always challenging
me to a match.
Whenever he gets
stuck in a move,
he does that thing
with his hands.
-What does it mean?
-He's working on a strategy.
-Huh?
All the times we've played,
I've never beaten him.
-Well, that's fine, but
this is a real fight, not
some game of shogi.
-Strategy on a game board is
no different from strategy
on the field of battle, and
all great generals know that.
Shikamaru has got the mind of a
great general, just you watch.
-You could have fooled me.
Don't forget, I
saw the test scores
when we grouped the Genin.
His were no better than
Naruto's, maybe worse.
-He says the act of putting
pencil to paper is a drag.
It's too much work for him.
He'd rather take a nap
than a written exam.
-He would, huh?
-I didn't say he wasn't lazy.
But he was so good
at strategy games,
I had him take an IQ test.
Of course, I had to
deceive him into thinking
it was just another game.
-Well, what happened?
-Hmm, as I suspected, his score
was almost off the charts,
beyond genius.
The kid has an IQ of over 200.
-200?
-He's done thinking.
Now it begins.
-So you have some
fighting spirit after all.
Aaaagh.
No use in hiding.
-Are you sure he's
even got a strategy?
-I hope so.
-Look at that.
He can't get anywhere near her.
Go, Shikamaru, do something.
-Don't waste your breath.
He'll give up soon.
This is way too
much work for him.
-What are you talking about?
No way he's going to give up.
At least, I don't think
he's going to give up.
[sound of munching]
-Hmm, it's good.
[breathing heavy]
-You can't hide forever.
Come out, coward!
Oh, oh.
Forget it.
As long as I stay on this side
of the line, he can't touch me.
What the-- It's still coming.
-You're pretty
quick on your toes.
-Now I see what
you've been up to.
You weren't just
hiding, you we're
killing time, waiting
for the sun to get lower,
and the shadow of that
wall to get longer.
The longer the shadows, the
farther your range is, right?
-Damn, he almost got her.
-How is Shikamaru going
to use his shadow anyway?
I mean, what's he going to do?
He's in the shadow
of the arena already.
-Unbelievable You
really don't know
anything about Shikamaru's
capable of, do you?
He can use anything.
He can even make
shadows within shadows.
-Shadows within shadows?
-All right.
If I just calculate
the height of the sun
and measuring the
distance he's gained
from his previous attack, I
can still keep out of range.
No problem.
Hmph.
-Temari, over your head.
-Hmm.
-What is that?
Oh, Oh, no.
-I've got you now.
-He made a parachute
out of his jacket
to create another shadow.
Clever move.
Now I not only have to
worry about the shadows
on the ground, I
have to keep an eye
on this thing above my head,
and it extends his range
indefinitely.
Huh, guess I've been
underestimating this slacker
clown.
His Shadow Possessions Jutsu
is a lot more dangerous
than I thought.
-She learns fast.
I'll give her that.
-Good, but not good enough.
-She thinks in the
same way he does.
She's a strategist, too.
The longer this match takes,
the lower the sun gets.
The longer the shadows,
the farther his range.
Time to finish this.
If I create a diversion
with the Clone Jutsu--
-Huh?
-Aaaah.
Yeah, that'll work.
Now Clone Jutsu.
What?
-Aah.
-Oh.
-Huh?
-Hmm?
-My body, it's frozen.
It took a while, but my Shadow
Possession finally worked.
-No.
-How the hell did he do that?
-Amazing.
He was thinking three
moves ahead all along.
-As I said, that's
Shikamaru's strength.
-Impossible.
How could he have caught
me with his shadow?
He couldn't reach this far.
-Look behind you.
I'll let you.
-Out of the hole.
How?
-Don't you recognize that hole?
It's where Naruto
popped out of the ground
and knocked Neji for a loop.
The hole in front of you is
where he went into the ground.
The two are connected.
-Now I see.
I never thought of the
shadows underground.
-That was your mistake.
-Like I said, he's
thinking three moves ahead.
First, he gets her
to retreat behind
the line she thinks is the
limit of his shadow attack.
Then just when she's
starting to feel safe,
he surprises her by
extending his range,
forcing her to fall back again.
All the time making
her think it's
her idea, when actually
he's maneuvering her
closer and closer to
that hole behind her.
And then, she's caught.
Heh.
That's how you play the game.
-I don't believe this.
The whole time I thought
I was keeping out
of range of his
Shadow Jutsu when
I was a really
walking right into it.
Amazing.
This slacker clown
outsmarted me.
-The next move is checkmate.
-He's got control of my body.
I'm helpless.
-Look at everybody.
A minute ago they were
throwing things at him.
-Well, who would
have ever thought
the guy would turn
out to be a ringer.
-Yeah, he did it.
He pulled off an upset.
-You got her.
Way to go.
-Checkmate.
-The hell with it.
I give up.
-Huh?
-He what?
You've gotta be kidding me.
-Loser.
-See, I told you he'd give up.
Looks like I know Shikamaru a
little bit better than you do,
huh?
-What?
What did you say?
-I used up all my chakra on
that Shadow Possession Jutsu.
I'm good for about another
10 seconds and that's it.
Bummer, and here I'd already
planned out the next 200 moves
in my head.
But my chakra's running low.
Anyway, if I was
doing this thing,
it would just mean more work.
This guy is something else.
-The winner is Temari.
[theme song in Japanese]
[crowd cheering]
-Whoa, just look at this crowd.
They are hot.
-Well, it's the match everyone's
been waiting for, isn't it?
I'm even a little jazzed myself.
-What?
Did you say
something, Shikamaru?
-I said it's the big match.
It's Sasuke.
That's why everyone's
going crazy.
-I can't hear you.
The crowd's making
too much noise.
-Forget it.
-Next time, "Dancing
Leaf, Squirming Sand."
I can't wait to see this
one, even if I'm not in it.