[theme music]
LEE (VOICEOVER):
What is that form?
-Is that the best you can do
with your ultimate defense?
Is that all?
I'm very disappointed.
Hm?
I see.
An armor-like shell of sand.
-He is not your only opponent!
I am here, as well!
[scream]
LEE (VOICEOVER):
That might have been
the end, if Gaara
had not intervened.
My body is still too weak.
I am only a burden
to him like this.
-I'm tired of that sand.
Very well, Gaara.
You first.
LEE (VOICEOVER): His spine!
How is it possible?
-Clematis Dance.
First, the bud.
[shout] Then the flower.
This bone is my strongest.
It will bore right through
you, defenses and all.
(VOICEOVER) I don't
have much time.
-Ultimate Defense!
Shukaku's Shield!
OROCHIMARU: Kabuto, how much
longer can Kimimaro last,
do you think?
-Oh, he should be
good for a while yet.
I did everything for him
that I possibly could.
Of course, I'd be more
confident of his treatment
if I hadn't been
working in the dark.
I would have preferred
more information.
His medical history, or
the bloodlines of his clan.
But that was a dead end.
There are no bloodlines.
The Kaguya clan is
gone, except for him.
Whatever they were exists
only in Kimimaro now.
They must have been
mad, to provoke
a war with the Village
hidden in the Mist.
A war they could never win.
The price of their madness
was their own destruction.
OROCHIMARU: The Kaguya clan were
a people who thrived on war.
It was only in the midst
of battle and slaughter
that they felt at peace.
But times change.
There was no longer
a place in the world
for such senseless
savagery and bloodshed.
The world was becoming
more civilized.
And so this last
mad act, pretending
that brute force could defeat
an organized power like the Mist
Village, it was nothing
less than mass suicide.
KABUTO: And yet you
were able to save one
from oblivion, the youngest and
most gifted of all the Kaguya.
OROCHIMARU: Yes.
His powers were so great
that his own clan feared him.
So much so that they kept
him imprisoned and isolated
for nearly all his young life.
-Such a waste it would
have been to let him die.
OROCHIMARU: Exactly.
To have lost that rare
Kekkai Genkai of his.
Imagine, to possess a bone
structure of such density
that it's an almost
impervious defense.
And even better, of
such adaptability
that in offense, it becomes a
weapon of extraordinary power.
LEE (VOICEOVER): No chance.
I have fought Gaara, and I
know that sand shield well.
It may give, but
it does not break.
And this is in a
more advanced form.
There is no way you
will ever break through.
-It's so strong.
-I took the hardest minerals
in the soil I gathered,
and then I fused them with
the sand using my chakra.
Tell me, that's a
very unusual jutsu.
It's a Kekkai Genkai, right?
-It belonged to the Kaguya.
But now it belongs
to me, and me alone.
-You're the last
of your clan, eh?
Then your clan perishes today.
-That might very
well be the case.
My body has weakened.
It may not last much longer.
However, I will still live on.
Because I am not alone.
The earth.
Its curse mark.
With this, I become a part
of you, Lord Orochimaru?
-Come, see the truth of
the world through my eyes,
Kimimaro.
It all could be
ours, yours and mine.
Will you come?
-Yes.
-Excellent.
I knew that I
could count on you.
You're my ideal vessel.
That mark is a gift from me.
I do hope you like it.
-You obey me, or you die.
Which do you prefer?
-How about neither one!
[clashing]
[groaning]
-Pathetic.
Is that the best
you four can do?
Now then, I'll ask
you once again.
Which do you prefer?
Very well.
We are now the Sound Ninja Five.
-You're not alone, you say?
-That's right.
My existence has been subsumed
into Lord Orochimaru's
ambition.
That means a part
of me will survive
in Lord Orochimaru's heart.
Forever.
-Orochimaru's
brainwashed you well.
You sad little pawn.
(VOICEOVER) I've had to
put a lot into this battle.
Almost out of chakra.
I must make this last bit count!
-It is amazing he
still has chakra!
-I underestimated him.
-I will bury you 200 meters
below the surface of the Earth,
under pressure so
great you won't
be able to move a
finger, imprisoned
there 'til the end of time.
-You did it!
This time I am certain of it.
KIMIMARO: Dance.
Bracken Dance.
-Ah!
-This is getting tiresome.
-It's true.
The more you want something,
the harder it is to wait for it.
-Kabuto.
Do not speak to me as if
you were explaining things
to a child.
-I'm sorry.
My Lord, however
long it takes, you
have nothing to worry about.
Nothing.
They have no one who
can beat Kimimaro.
Just try and be
a little patient.
That's all.
-Thank you, Gaara.
you see it in these powers of
yours are truly remarkable.
-Not really.
I'm merely able to make
the sand do my bidding.
It's second nature to me now.
-Lord Orochimaru, I am
sorry I've failed you.
Please forgive me, my lord.
-The end of the Leaf.
Finally.
-Third Hokage.
I'm going to teach
you a lesson, old man.
-I'm sorry.
I was delayed.
[cough]
-What's the matter?
Something wrong?
-No.
Nothing at all.
[groan]
-There's no one who
can stop us now.
Even the Kazekage of the
Sand Village falls before us.
-Of course.
Like lambs to the slaughter.
I have you to thank for
this victory, Kimimaro.
[coughing]
-Kimimaro!
-What is it, boy?
Are you unable to go on?
-Please forgive me,
Lord Orochimaru.
(VOICEOVER) My damanged
body is of no use to him.
That was my purpose,
and it's gone.
KABUTO: How are you
feeling, Kimimaro?
The attack on the
Leaf Village didn't
go quite as well as we'd
hoped, but the Sound Ninja Four
have gone to retrieve
a new vessel.
So Lord Orochimaru will soon
have a new ideal vessel.
GAARA (VOICEOVER): Orochimaru's
brainwashed you well.
You said little pawn.
-You're wrong!
You don't understand!
-Maybe, just maybe, there
is no purpose in life.
But if you linger a while
longer in this world,
you might discover
something of value in it.
Like how you
discovered that flower.
Or how I discovered
you one fateful night.
[laughter]
-The earth.
Its curse mark.
With this, I become a part
of you, Lord Orochimaru?
-Come, see the
truth of the world
through by eyes, Kimimaro.
It all could be
ours, yours and mine.
Will you come?
-I will see the
truth of this world!
Lod Orochimaru will show me!
-A tenacious opponent,
but this time it's over.
We won't be seeing him
again in this life.
-Yes.
Good.
-My strength is gone.
We must descend.
KIMIMARO: I am not his pawn!
He is the one-- the only one
who ever gave my life meaning!
But how could the likes of
you ever understand that?
-He is dead.
-Can it be?
Kimimaro?
-No matter.
He's of no further use to me.
All that matters now is
that Sasuke is coming,
and of his own free will.
Just as I foretold.
-It was sheer luck.
I should've been killed.
-No.
It was not meant to be.
My sensei has often
said to me, a good ninja
always makes his own luck.
-That meddlesome mother hen.
-Guy-sensei is
nothing of the sort!
Yes, he stepped in, but
only that once, and only
because I was not
yet strong enough.
I am very grateful to you
for having saved my life.
But I warn you, I will not
abide anyone speaking ill
of my sensei!
-So you're another one, eh?
-Hm?
-You have someone in your
life whom you honor and revere
so much that every
hurt inflicted on them
is inflicted on you as well.
And the closer they are to
you, the greater the pain.
-I will live on.
I am not alone.
A part of me will live on
in Lord Orochimaru's heart
forever.
He is the one!
The only one who
gave my life meaning!
How could you ever
understand that?
-To feel so strongly
for someone,
you would fight for them.
And die for them.
You and Naruto Uzumaki
have that in common.
However.
What if this person you
honor and would even
die for is not a
virtuous person?
-Impossible!
Such a person would-- would be
unworthy of honor or respect.
-No.
Perhaps the companionship
of even an evil person
is preferable to loneliness.
-Sasuke!
[theme music]
-What's wrong with you, Sasuke?
Are you nuts?
You keep talking about
achieving your goal.
What about Orochimaru's goal?
All he wants to do is put you
on like a new suit of clothes!
Is that what you want?
To become his slave?
Well I'm not gonna
let you, you hear?
I'm warning you, if you
won't listen to reason,
I'll take you back by force!
I don't want to, but-- Oh,
what am I talking about?
It'll be a pleasure!
Next time, A Cry On Deaf Ears!
[theme music]