[theme music]
[singing in Japanese]
[drum sound]
SASUKE: Sasuke, I'm at point B.
SAKURA: Sakura, I'm at point C.
NARUTO: Naruto, I'm at
point A, believe it.
KAKASHI: Go slow, Naruto.
OK, Squad 7.
Hmm?
The target has moved.
Follow it.
[leaves rustling]
-Over there.
-What's your distance
from the target?
-Five meters.
I'm ready, just give the signal.
-I'm ready, too.
-So am I.
-OK, now!
[screams]
-I got him, I got him.
KAKASHI: Can you verify
ribbon, right ear?
[screams]
-Affirmative, we
got a positive ID.
-Right, lost pet Torah captured.
Mission accomplished.
NARUTO: Can't we get a
better mission than this?
I hate cats!
[feedback]
A dangerous mission, journey
to the Land of Waves.
-Oh, my poor little Torah.
Mommy was so worried about her
naughty little fuzzykins, yes.
[meowing]
-Stupid cat.
That kitty deserves to
be squashed. [laughs]
-No wonder he ran away.
-Fuzzykins, ooh, you're my baby.
I'm so happy.
-Now, then, for Squad
7's next mission,
we have several available tasks.
Huh?
Among them,
babysitting the chief
counselor's three-year-old,
helping his wife to do
the shopping, digging
up potatoes, and--
-No!
I want to go on a real
mission, something
challenging and exciting,
not this little kid stuff!
Come on, old man!
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
He's got a point.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
But he's such a pain.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): [sighs]
I knew this was coming.
-How dare you?
You're just a brand-new
Genin with no experience.
Like everyone else, you
start with simple missions
to develop your skills
and prove yourself.
-Are you serious?
Babysitting is not a mission.
It's just a stupid-- [shout]
-Will you put a lid on it?
OLD MAN: Naruto--
-[screams]
OLD MAN: It seems
you do not understand
the tasks you have been given.
Listen, many different
kinds of requests
come into our village
every day, from babysitting
to assassinations.
These requests are carefully
recorded, analyzed, then ranked
A, B, C, or D, depending
on their difficulty.
We ninja are also ranked
by ability-- Hokage
at the top, Jonin, Chunin,
and Genin at the bottom.
At the highest level,
we select the missions
and assign them to ninja who
have the appropriate skill
and experience.
And if the mission
is successful,
we receive a fee that supports
our village and our work.
Since you are untried Genin,
just starting down the Shinobi
path, you are given D-level
assignments, of course.
Hmm?
-So I had this tonkotsu
ramen yesterday,
and I'm thinking
miso ramen today.
-Silence!
-Oh, sorry.
--[screams] You always lecture
me like you're my grandfather
or something.
But I'm not the
little brat who used
to pull pranks all the time.
I'm a ninja now, and I
want a ninja mission.
Hmmm!
[drums and japanese chanting]
-Hmm, I'm going to
hear about this later.
[laughter]
OLD MAN: Naruto wants
us to know that he's not
a brat-- he's a former brat,
and he wants a mission.
So be it.
-Huh?
-Since you are so
determined, I'm
going to give you
a C-ranked mission.
You'll be bodyguards
on a journey.
-Really?
Yes!
Who?
Are we guarding a princess?
Or some [inaudible] counselor?
-Don't be so impatient.
I will bring him in now.
Send in our visitor.
[drums and chanting in Japanese ]
-Hmm?
-What the-?
A bunch of little
snot-nosed kids?
-Huh?
-And you, the little one with
the idiotic look on your face.
You really expect me to
believe you're a ninja?
--[laughs] Who's the little one
with the idiotic look on his--?
Oh, huh?
[electronic sounds]
-Uh, hmm.
I'll demolish you.
Let me get my hands on
him, I'll destroy him!
-You can't demolish
the client, Naruto.
It doesn't work that way.
--[sighs] I am Tazuna, a
master bridge builder,
and I must return to my country.
I'm building a bridge there
that will change our world,
and I expect you to
get me there safely,
even if it means
giving up your life.
[whip]
[screaming]
[whooshing]
[crashing]
-Yeah!
All right!
-What are you getting so
excited about, Naruto?
-This is the first time
I ever left the village.
I'm a traveler now, believe it.
-Hey, am I supposed to
trust my life to this runt?
He's a joke.
--[laughs] He's with
me, and I'm a Jonin,
so you don't need to worry.
TAZUNA (VOICEOVER):
This runt, he's a joke.
(VOICEOVER) Why'd we have to
get this old geezer to guard?
I'm going to cut him
down to size right now.
-Hey.
Never insult a ninja.
It's a big mistake.
And I'm one of the
greatest ninja ever!
Someday I'm going to be a
Hokage and you'll look up to me!
My name's Naruto Uzumaki!
Remember it!
[whooshing]
-Hokage are powerful and wise.
You are puny and brainless.
The day you become Hokage,
I'll sprout wings and fly.
-Ah!
Shut up!
I'm willing to do
anything to become Hokage,
no matter what it takes!
And when I do,
everyone will have
to admit that I'm the
top ninja, including you!
-Heh.
You can become
Hokage 10 times over,
and to me, you'll still
be nobody, a loser.
-Ah!
I'm going to make you
pay for that right now!
-I told you, you're supposed
to protect the client,
not attack him.
-Give me one shot at him!
Let me go!
I'll show you!
That's right, I'm
talking to you!
[birds chirping]
SAKURA: Say, Mr. Tazuna?
-What is it?
-Your country is the
Land of Waves, right?
-Yeah.
What of it?
-Kakashi sensei, there are
ninja in that country, too,
aren't there?
-No, there are no ninja
in the Land of Waves.
But in other countries,
there are hidden villages,
each with their own different
customs and cultures,
where ninja reside.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
To the people
of this continent, the existence
of Shinobi villages means
strength, military strength.
In other words, that's how they
protect themselves and maintain
the balance of power with
neighboring countries.
The ninja villages are not
controlled by any government.
They're independent,
and have equal status.
Now, a small island
like the Land of Waves
has natural protection
from the sea,
so there's no need
for a ninja village.
The five ancient lands that
possess Shinobi villages
are the Lands of Fire, Water,
Lightning, Wind, and Earth.
They each occupy
vast territories.
Together they are known as the
five great Shinobi nations.
The Land of Fire has the
Village Hidden in the Leaves;
the Land of Water, the
Village Hidden in the Mist;
the Land of Lightning, the
Village Hidden in the Clouds;
the Land of Wind, the
Village Hidden in the Sand;
and the Land of Earth, the
Village Hidden in the Stones.
Only the leaders of
these hidden villages
are permitted the name
Kage, which means "shadow."
Hokage, Mizukage, Raikage,
Kazekage, Tsuchikage-- these
are the leaders,
the five shadows
that reign over
thousands of ninja.
--[gasps] Then Lord
Hokage's really important!
(VOICEOVER) Hmm.
Is that old man really
such a big deal?
I'm not buying it.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I got
him with my senjutsu.
He can't be that great.
Believe it.
Hmm.
-Hey.
-Huh?
-Uh--
-You all just doubted
Lord Hokage, didn't you?
That's what you were thinking.
-Uh--
-Um--
-No.
-Well, anyway, there
are no ninja battles
in a C-ranked mission,
so you can relax.
-And we're not going to run
into any foreign enemy ninja
or anything like that.
[laughing]
KAKASHI: Not likely.
[birds chirping]
[footsteps on bridge]
-What?
[grunts]
-Huh?
-What?
-[grunts] Do it!
[crash]
-[screams]
-Ka- Kakashi sensei!
[groans]
[laughter]
MAN: Now it's your turn.
[groans]
[whooshing]
-I can't get loose.
-Ahh, ahh, aah, aah.
[fighting sounds]
Ahh!
[grunts]
-[shout]
-[grunts]
-[grunts] I've got to stop them.
I've got to stop them!
Stay behind me.
[crashing]
[groans]
-Ahh.
Ahh!
-Hi.
-[gasp]
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Kakashi sensei, he's alive!
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
Huh, show-off.
-Huh?
But he was-- what?
Kakashi sensei used
the replacement jutsu.
-Naruto, sorry I didn't
help you right away.
I didn't mean for
you to get hurt.
I just didn't think you'd
freeze up like that.
--[groans] They
saved me after all.
-Good job, Sasuke, very smooth.
You too, Sakura.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
I was useless!
And Sasuke was so
cool, like he'd
done this a thousand times.
Didn't he feel scared at all?
He looked so calm, not a scratch
on him, and I was so lame.
He had to come up and save me!
Ugh!
Why can't I keep up with them?
-Hey.
-Yeah?
-You're not hurt, are ya?
Scaredy-cat.
-[growls] Arrgh!
Sasuke!
-Naruto, stand still.
These ninja have
poison in their claws.
We need to take it
out of you quickly.
-Ahh!
Ahh!
KAKASHI: You have to open
the wound and remove it.
It's in your blood,
so don't move around.
That spreads the poison.
By the way, Mr. Tazuna,
-[grunts] Yeah, what?
-We need to talk.
They're Chunin from the
Village Hidden in the Mist.
Their specialty is
relentless attack.
They keep fighting, no
matter what the sacrifice.
-How did you know
about our ambush?
-A puddle on a clear day, when
it hasn't rained in weeks?
-In that case, why'd you
leave it for the Genin
to do the fighting?
-I could have taken
them out quickly.
But then I'd have
learned nothing.
I had to know who their target
was, and what they were after.
TAZUNA: Hmm?
What are you getting at?
-This.
I wanted to know if they were
after us, ninja attacking
ninja, or if they were after
you, the master bridge builder.
When you put in
your request, you
asked for standard protection
from robbers and highway men.
You didn't say there were ninja
looking for you, hunting you
down.
If we knew this, it would be
a B-rank mission or higher.
Our task was simply to get
you to your destination
and protect you while you
finished building your bridge.
If we knew we'd be fielding
attacks from enemy ninja,
we would have staffed
differently and charged
for the cost of a B mission.
Apparently you have your
reasons, but lying to us
is not acceptable.
We are now beyond the
scope of this mission.
-We are Genin.
This is too advanced for
our level of training.
We should go back.
And I really think we need
to treat Naruto's wound
and get the poison out
as soon as possible.
Back in our village, we
can take him to a doctor.
-Hmm.
-Ahh, huh?
-Naruto's hand could
become a problem.
I guess we should go
back to the village.
-Arrrgh!
[grunts]
[gasps]
NARUTO: Why am I so different?
Why am I always-- [groan]
-Naruto!
Stop that!
What are you doing?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
I worked so hard
to get here, pushing
myself until it hurt,
training alone for hours,
anything to get stronger,
to reach my dream.
I will never back down again
and let someone else rescue me.
I will never run away.
And I will not lose to Sasuke.
Upon this wound, I make
this pledge, believe it.
Bridge builder, I'll
complete this mission
and protect you with
this kunai knife.
Don't worry, I'll be fine.
-Naruto, that was
really cool how
you took the poison out and all.
But if you lose any more
blood, you're going to die.
-[sighing and moaning]
-Good idea to stop the
bleeding now, seriously.
-Not, not, not!
No, no, no!
I'm too young for it
to all end like this.
No, no, no!
-Show me your hand.
-No, no, help, no!
No, no!
-Naruto, you've got a
self-abusive personality.
It's called masochism.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): The wound,
it's already starting to heal.
-Um, um--
-Hmm?
-You have a really
serious look on your face.
You're scaring me.
Am I OK?
-Uh, yeah, you should be fine.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
This healing power,
is it from the nine-tailed fox?
[animal sounds]
-You failed.
You failed?
What is this, amateur night?
I put out big money for you!
I thought you were supposed
to be hotshot assassins.
-Stop whining.
-[grunts] [moans]
-This time, I'll go personally.
And this sword will be the
last thing he ever sees.
--[clears throat]
You sure about that?
Apparently Tazuna has a
high-level ninja guarding him.
And since your first
attempt failed,
they'll be expecting you back.
They'll be waiting, watching.
It'll take someone with
very advanced skills.
-Who do you think
you're dealing with?
I am Zabuza Momochi, the
Demon of the Hidden Mist.
[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
We finally land
ashore in the Land of Waves.
The ninja they send
after us now will
be stronger and
deadlier than before.
Fine.
I'm going to show
them what I can do!
And Sasuke's not going
to show me up, either.
I'll protect the old
man, no matter what.
Oh, wow!
That's who they sent after us?
He's huge!
And his sword is gigantic!
Next time, the
Assassin of the Mist.
No backing down, this time
I'm going all the way!