[theme music]
-Where is he?
Where's the needle
attack coming at us from?
Are they clones?
We've got to find the real one.
Which one is it?
-Look into every nerve
as hard as you like.
You will never learn the secret.
-Oh, yeah?
Shadow clone jutsu!
-No!
Don't!
[yelling]
-These mirrors only
reflect my image,
allowing me to transport
myself at light speed.
Through my eyes, you appear
to be moving in slow motion.
-I knew it.
-It's a blood mark
trait, Kikegenkai.
[man laughing]
-Kikegenkai?
What is it?
-It's my Sharingan.
He inherited it.
-But that means--
-Yes.
Even I can't copy that jutsu.
There's no way to destroy it.
And no way to stop him.
-I couldn't break through.
So what?
He's not going to stop me.
I'm not giving up.
And I'm not going to die
here because I have a dream.
And no one's going to
take it away from me.
Someday, I'll be
respected in my village.
That's my dream, to be
the greatest Hukage.
-Dreams.
The bridge will
be the battlefield
where our dreams collide.
Now, I must fight for my dream,
just as you fight for yours.
Please do not blame me.
I fight for someone
who is precious to me.
I live for him.
And I face death for
him, so that his dream
may become reality.
That is my dream.
And for the sake of
that dream, if I must,
I will act as a shinobi
and take your lives.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): "Zero
Visibility-- The Sharingan
Shatters."
-Sasuke.
Naruto.
Take this guy out!
You can do it.
-Don't, Sakura.
Don't push them.
-Huh?
-Even if they
somehow found a way
to overcome the mirror
jutsu, they still
couldn't defeat this ninja.
-Uh.
How can you be so sure?
-They have the desire to win.
But they don't have
the instinct to kill.
That boy is a whole other breed.
He lives for pain.
He thrives on it.
-Exactly.
Your village has
become complacent.
Your trainees never learn the
most important lesson of all,
to kill the feelings
in their own hearts.
To crush an opponent
mercilessly.
To destroy with no
emotion or regret.
-Uh.
But then, Sensei, what
are we going to do?
Please tell us.
-I could make a break to
save Naruto and Sasuke,
but he'd slay the
bridge builder.
If I use shadow clones-- nah.
He'd just match them
with water clones.
I'd be wasting chakra.
So I have no choice.
It's me or Zabuza, here and now.
I'll have to do
this the hard way.
-The Sharingan.
-Sharingan.
-You're no fun Kakashi,
using the same old trick.
-Huh?
-Sensai, no!
-If it's just an old
trick, why did you stop me?
-Let your opponent see
your jutsu too many times,
and he'll find a way
to use it against you.
-Then, count yourself lucky.
You're the only man alive
who's seen my Sharingan twice.
Show's over.
There won't be a third time.
-Even if you didn't
see me, you'd
have no chance against Haku.
-Oh.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Is that possible?
That boy in the mask is
stronger than Kakashi Sensai?
-When I found him, he
was just a street kid.
But I trained him in the most
advanced ninja techniques.
ZABUZA (VOICEOVER): I taught
him everything I know.
Plus, he had special abilities
that he refined on his own.
The boy developed quickly.
Soon, he could face the most
powerful enemy, out-numbered,
in total darkness.
It didn't matter.
He could strike with
perfect accuracy.
He cared nothing for his own
life or the lives of others.
He'd become a unique
fighting machine, a shinobi.
In the end, his power
surpassed even mine.
His bloodline trait,
the Kikegenkai,
cannot be defeated by anyone.
I've created a tool
that can destroy
anything that stands in my way.
Unlike the useless punks
who follow you around.
-I didn't get do him.
Then, I'll try it again.
As many times as it takes.
Shadow clone jutsu!
-Naruto!
Don't!
[yelling and fighting]
[grunting]
[yelling and fighting continues]
-How is he doing that?
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
It was barely there.
But I saw it.
I could see the trails
and follow his moves.
-One more time.
Shadow clone jutsu!
[yelling]
-Don't you see
that it's useless?
[yelling continues]
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
I can see his speed.
But that doesn't
mean I can match it.
The water, it's being repelled.
What if I try something else.
Not water but-- yes.
Now, it's my move.
-You think those Genin
punks together can be Haku?
He's the ultimate, a
battle tool of destruction.
-Are you finished bragging?
You're starting to put me sleep.
Let's finish this.
Now.
-Fine.
But there's one more
thing you should know.
A little more
bragging, as you say.
-Hm?
-Did you really think our last
battle was just win or lose?
That took your attacks
like some rank Genin?
[grunting and coughing]
[yelling]
-He's finished.
-Haku was there, hiding,
watching every move you made.
Studying your Sharingan.
Haku can see a jutsu once
and immediately devise
a lethal counterattack.
It's one of his gifts.
-Oh.
-I've been waiting to
see the look on your face
when you realize you're
Sharingan has become worthless.
-Huh?
-You once said the same
jutsu won't work on me twice.
Well, now, I'm telling you that.
-Huh?
-Ninja art.
Hidden misjutsu.
-Uh.
-Ninja art.
Hidden misjutsu.
-Uh.
This is it.
TAZUNA (VOICEOVER):
What's going on?
The mist is so thick.
Visibility is zero.
-Sensai.
-Sakura, stay with Tazuna.
-Oh.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): I have
to be strong and believe
in Sasuke, Naruto,
and Kakashi Sensai.
And I have my job to do
no matter what it takes.
-Hm?
Oh, Sakura.
-Follow my lead, Mr. Tazuna.
And whatever
happens, stay close.
-All right.
I'll stay right behind you.
-I know you need me, Zabuza.
I'll finish them off quickly.
-Shadow clone jutsu!
[yelling]
SHADOW CLONE (VOICEOVER):
He just won't give up.
What?
Fireball jutsu?
[yelling and fighting]
SHADOW CLONE
(VOICEOVER): It shouldn't
be taking this long
to defeat them.
[yelling and fighting]
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
Got him that time.
I'm starting to get the timing.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): It's
the hidden mist jutsu.
But this mist is too
thick even for Zabuza.
How can he fight in it?
-Very skillful, as I'd
expect from Kakashi,
the Sharingan warrior.
-His eyes are closed.
-But next time
you see me will be
the last time you see anything.
Without your Sharingan,
you're nothing.
-What?
-You wanted me to
believe you could
see through anything,
even through time.
[yelling]
-How?
Can you see into the future?
-Yes.
This is your last battle.
Ever.
But your prediction was wrong.
I'm still alive.
So you're a fraud, Kakashi.
You can't read the future.
And you can't read me.
The Sharingan is
just a cheap trick
that makes you seem more
powerful than you are.
I know now your Sharingan as two
separate elements, the piercing
eye which sees every
detail and the hypnotic
eye which mesmerized
your opponent.
Employing these abilities you
can execute multiple jutsu
in quick succession
to make it seem
like you could see the future.
First, with the
piercing eye, you
copy my movements instantly.
This replication of movement
makes me doubt my own thoughts.
Once I was shaken, you
infiltrated my mind,
waiting for this
slightest flutter
to anticipate my actions,
seeking out any hints
to my next move.
All you're doing is
copying me like a monkey.
You can beat me
with cheap tricks.
I'll crush you.
When I'm finished
with you, you'll
never open that
monkey mouth again.
You time it precisely,
waiting for the right moment.
-What is that?
-The instant my mind
because unfocused,
you create a new illusion.
With your hypnotic
eye, you induce
me to make hand signs while
you are making the same signs.
So you seem to be copying
me when actually you're
controlling my movements.
-Water-style.
Giant vortex jutsu.
-Impossible.
Now, that I know this.
A very simple plan
can defeat you.
First, neutralize your piercing
eye with zero visibility mist.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): The mist
is slowing my reaction time.
-Next, neutralize your hypnotic
eye by keeping my own eyes
closed.
You can't bore into my mind if
you can't look into my eyes.
-Brilliant, except
with your eyes closed,
you can't see me either.
-Have you forgotten
who I am, Kakashi?
I'm the demon of
the hidden mist,
master of the silent kill.
I can take you our
by sound alone.
SHADOW CLONE (VOICEOVER):
He read my movements,
but that's not possible.
-I was so close, but I
couldn't quite get to him.
-Naruto, can you do it again?
-Huh?
Of course.
Nothing can stop me.
Believe it.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): He
doesn't want to show it,
but he's exhausted.
The shadow clone jutsu
uses up so much chakra.
But thanks to him,
I figured it out.
I know how to break through.
SHADOW CLONE (VOICEOVER):
The human eye cannot track
my movements.
It must have been a coincidence.
-Naruto, run for it!
Get out of here and
attack from the outside.
Hurry!
-Uh.
All right.
You got it.
-You cannot escape.
-You think you can keep me here?
Forget it.
-That's it.
Fire-style.
Fireball jutsu!
-I couldn't get passed him.
-That was good, Naruto.
-Huh?
One more time?
-Yeah.
Let's do it.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): There must
be a limit to his chakra, too.
I can feel him slowing down.
SHADOW CLONE (VOICEOVER):
No more games.
I need to stop this now.
This time you'll stay down.
-Sasuke!
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): An enemy
you can't see and can't hear.
It's been a long time since
I faced anyone this tough.
And Sasuke and Naruto, I don't
know if they can hold out.
Stay calm.
Think.
Where will he strike?
The bridge builder.
-Too late.
[screaming]
[music playing]
NARUTO: Why did it
turn out this way?
How could this have happened?
I never asked for
your protection.
I didn't need you
to do what you did.
I hated you.
Yet, you sacrificed
your life for mine.
I'll never forgive you.
Next time, "The Broken Seal."