[theme music]
-Kiba!
-Naruto.
-Kiba, you OK?
-Yeah.
-Was it another genjutsu attack?
-None of us, including Akamaru,
is safe from Yakumo's genjutsu.
Her power attacks
complex nervous systems,
anything with a cerebrum.
Everyone, move
away from the door.
Parasitic insects.
-Please, sensei, just
tell me the truth.
If you don't, I'll
have to end your life.
-It was my decision
and my decision
alone to seal your
genjutsu away.
The Third Hokage
wasn't involved.
Go ahead and release
all your resentment.
But remember, the only one
you should feel hatred toward
is me.
-You're just trying to
trick me, aren't you?
I heard you and the
Third Hokage talking
about how you were going
to destroy the Kurama clan.
-Yakumo, it's not true.
-Don't lie!
My mother and father
were too strong to let
themselves die in
some house fire.
No, someone murdered them.
What's that?
[insects buzzing]
-Shino.
-Get away!
No.
Wh- what's going on?
-Shadow clone jutsu.
Listen up, I'm
counting on you guys.
-Right.
-OK, Whenever you're
ready, just-- [punches]
-All righty.
And away we go! Charge!
-Naruto, please be safe.
-Naruto.
-Oh, Kurenai Sensei.
You're fading away.
You did this to her,
didn't you Yakumo?
-Of course I did.
She was plotting to
eliminate my family.
This is just punishment.
-What are you talking about?
Yakumo, you must've
misunderstood or something.
Old Man Unkai told me
everything about what
happened between you
and Kurenai Sensei.
He told me that--
-Stop it, Naruto.
-No, I'm saying it.
Sure, Kurenai Sensei
sealed your powers,
but only 'cause she cared about
you and wanted to protect you.
-What are you talking about?
-You think you're the only
one who's been suffering?
Knowing your secret, not being
able to tell the truth all
this time, Kurenai Sensei
suffered just as much as you.
-Please, Naruto.
-What do you mean by the truth?
-Gai Sensei, there you are.
-Kiba, what happened
to the others?
-Shino and Hinata are
standing watch in the hallway,
but Yakumo's genjutsu
created another dimension,
and Naruto and Kurenai
Sensei are inside.
-Huh?
What are you talking about?
-I think I can explain.
-With your injuries,
you should take it easy.
-No, I must tell you
everything if you
have any hope of stopping her.
No one worried about Yakumo's
well being as much as Kurenai
has.
She tried so hard
to convince her,
pleading with Yakumo to forget
her dream and end her training.
UNKAI (VOICEOVER): Yakumo
was completely dispirited.
Obviously, Lord Murakumo was
concerned about his daughter.
But then one day, the
unexpected happened.
Their family residence
burned to the ground
while Yakumo stood
dazed watching
the whole thing happen.
That's when I first saw it.
A strange figure
appeared in the flames,
a horrible monstrous
demon smiling back at me.
But when I learned
what the beast was,
I became frozen with terror.
-The secret, what is it?
-Um, Sensei, what the
hell is going on with her?
-This is bad.
Yakumo, just forget about it.
It's nothing.
Don't try and remember.
-Hold on.
I think something's
coming back to me,
deep in the back of my mind.
But what is it?
I can't remember.
-It's all being revealed.
Naruto, you have to stop it.
Naruto!
-What the heck is
this thing anyway?
Damn it, let go of me.
-Father, mother, all
I want is to live up
to the expectations
of our family.
So why does everyone
always get in my way?
I only want to master genjutsu.
Is that so wrong?
-Everyone has a path in life
that they're meant to follow.
Maybe your path is just
different from what
you thought.
-He's right.
Dear, there's no need to force
yourself to become a shinobi.
-No, don't try to cheer me up.
You try to comfort
me with kind words,
but I see right through it.
Everyone's disappointed in me.
How can I live my life with the
burden of knowing in my heart
that I failed my family?
-Yakumo, what are you doing?
-Uroko, get out of here.
-Yakumo!
-I remember now.
-Yakumo.
-It was-- it was me.
The thing inside me destroyed
my mother and father that day.
My own hidden genjutsu
killed my parents.
-You're wrong, Yakumo.
That thing wasn't you.
You and that monster are
two different beings.
-I wish you were
right, but the truth
is, that thing lives
inside my heart.
Thank you, Sensei, for
everything you tried.
Farewell, Sensei.
-Don't do it!
-No, stop!
-What?
The painting saved her life?
-We wanted to find out
what caused the tragedy,
so we ordered a complete
medical examination of Yakumo.
UNKAI (VOICEOVER): They
arrived at the conclusion
that the creature which
appeared at the fire
came from Yakumo's
deep subconscious.
In other words, it was a
manifestation of her id.
-An id monster?
-I immediately went to the Third
Hokage and asked for guidance.
Ultimately, the girl was unable
to endure the expectations
that the village placed on
her, and soon her subconscious
cracked under the pressure.
To protect itself, it
released her pent up fury.
Sir, we do not think Yakumo's
id monster is finished.
It will keep going until the
whole Kurama clan is decimated,
and then the entire
Hidden Leaf village.
-I understand the
risk, but I refuse
to authorize any violence.
Yakumo isn't even aware that
this evil power exists inside
of her, and this village
does not take innocent life.
-But Lord Hokage, once her
subconscious completely
awakens, there will be
nothing we can do to stop it.
-In that case, we'll just have
to work with Yakumo until she
can control the
power by herself.
And if that's not
possible, then we'll
have to seal her genjutsu.
-How can we?
-It's slightly different, but
there has been one precedent.
In a similar situation, the
spirit of the nine-tailed fox
was sealed away inside
the body of a newborn.
-That's absurd.
There isn't a ninja
alive strong enough
to seal the immense power
that Yakumo possesses.
-Actually, there
might be one person
I know who fits the bill.
However, the mission
will be brutal.
I pray this person
can teach the girl
to control what is inside her.
If we are forced
to seal her powers,
we will erase all
the good Yakumo could
have achieved in her life.
This person will have to
weather Yakumo's resentment
and bear the weight of ending
the lineage of the Kurama
clan's powers.
-Then the Third Hokage
lowered his head and wept.
-The one who accepted the
Hokage's mission was--
-That's right, Kurenai.
-Of course.
So that's what
Kurenai Sensei was
talking about this whole time.
Darn it, I had no idea she
was going through all that.
-[bark]
-I knew that Kurenai had
decided to seal Yakumo's powers,
but this is the first I've heard
about the danger the girl's
subconscious caused.
-Yes.
When the Third Hokage
died, so did the secret.
At this point, only
Kurenai and the Kurama clan
know the whole story.
-Kurenai Sensei
risked everything
to keep it a secret,
even her reputation.
-We've got to go rescue her.
-[bark]
-They're going to
need your help.
-But I--
-It's all right.
I can handle
everything out here.
-Gai Sensei.
-You're worried about Naruto
and the others, right?
So go help 'em.
-Right.
-That's it then.
It's up to them now.
What is it?
-I felt something
strange in there.
I don't know, but it somehow
seemed different from the way
it felt before.
[insects buzzing]
-My insects are acting strange.
-What's going on
in the other room?
Have you heard anything yet?
Are they OK?
-[barking]
-Oh, no.
I'm sensing
something new forming
on the other side, an
incredibly powerful chakra.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Naruto.
-Why, why do you
do this yourself
when you are not to blame?
-Huh?
-The ones who must
be crushed are
those who imposed such a heavy
burden on your psyche, those
who tried to get rid
of me just as you
are reaching your
full potential.
-Who are you?
-I merely crept into a fracture
in one corner of your mind,
and there I was nurtured.
My name is Id.
-So, she's finally awake.
-Kurenai Sensei, you
know what that thing is?
-Yes, it happened
soon after I was
made Yakumo's
personal instructor.
KURENAI (VOICEOVER): I was
having doubts about just how
potent her genjutsu was, so I
explored deep into her psyche.
That's when I saw it.
The sight of that
terrible figure
sent shivers down my spine.
I couldn't move.
You see, the Third Hokage didn't
order me to eliminate Yakumo.
I was to kill the
monster within her.
-That's what this thing is?
-This ghastly specter, it's more
powerful than it was back then.
Even so, I'd die before I
let that thing get loose
in our village.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): She'd die?
Wait, so that's why
she quit squad eight.
This mission is more
important than anything.
-I absorb all your
pain into my body,
and now I'll settle
the score for good.
-No way!
Not on my watch.
-You're in my way.
-Naruto!
-I may not know what
the heck you are,
but Kiba, Shino, and Hinata are
out there waiting right now,
and I'm making sure they
get their sensei back.
-Naruto.
-Shadow clone jutsu!
My jutsu doesn't activate
in this dimension.
-You are a thorn in my side, so
you will be the first I erase.
-Be careful.
Yakumo, you're the only one who
has any hope of defeating it.
Please listen to me.
Every single one of
us has a fanged beast
hidden within the
depths of our mind.
It lies there waiting in the
dark reaches a person's soul,
and it appears at
our lowest moments.
It doesn't matter how
strong you think you are.
When the beast comes, it
is impossible to control.
You can end up hurting those
who are closest to you.
But If the monster
can be tamed, reigned
in with the strength
of your will,
it can become a
magnificent power
and can even make
your dreams reality.
Now, you must fight it.
Obliterate the monster that
the depths of your own mind
created.
-I don't know how.
-Yakumo, you are the only
one who can finish this.
-Time to go, little boy.
[? -help beat ?] the
darkness in my mind.
-Now die.
-But why?
I did my best to serve you.
I only wanted
what's best for you.
-Kurenai Sensei.
It sure is great to
see all of you again.
-Kurenai Sensei.
-You were incredible Yakumo.
You overcame the darkness
in your own soul.
-Oh, Sensei.
-Don't you worry.
You did great.
Huh?
Wow.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
In her heart,
she knew exactly who was trying
to save her the whole time.
She just had to realize it.
-Sensei!
-Kurenai Sensei.
-Hey, don't freak out.
Everything's fine now.
Kurenai Sensei, you
are going to go back
to being everyone's
teacher, aren't ya?
-I sure am.
That was my final mission
from the Third Hokage,
and now it's done.
-See?
-Sensei!
-Well that's great, isn't it?
Things'll go back to normal.
-Yup, looks that way.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Naruto?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
And I will, too.
[theme music]
-This isn't funny.
Why do we have to wear ourselves
out just 'cause of this guy?
-Yeah, we're supposed to
protect this national treasure,
but he keeps getting in our way.
-Plus he blames everyone.
He uses people as shields.
-He doesn't care if a
shinobi dies in a mission.
-I can't take this guy anymore.
-Me too.
If I have to I'll use--
-Rasengan.
-Fang over fang.
-We are gonna beat
up our client!
-Next time, "The Weight
of the Prized Artifact."
[theme music]