[music playing]
[theme music]
THEME SONG: Yeah.
Come on.
Oooh, oooh.
[singing in japanese]
[chanting in foreign language]
-Listen kid.
You sure you want me to take
your pictures like that?
-Just do it.
Come on already.
Come on.
-Ehhh.
Don't blame me later.
Say cheese.
KONAHAMARU: My
name is Konahamaru.
[laughter]
[groan]
-At first, you know,
I couldn't figure out
exactly how to do it.
It too me like three hours
to work it out and stuff.
But finally I got it.
Like an art project on
my face, only cooler.
-Take it again.
-Huh?
No way.
-We can't accept this photo.
-Yeah?
Well, I'm not doing it again.
Ahhhh.
Transform.
-Pretty please Lord Hokage.
-Huh?
Ahhh.
[crash]
-Uh, uh.
-That's the sexy jutsu you say?
Very tricky.
Much too tricky.
Don't do it again.
-Heh heh heh.
-And where is your
headband Naruto?
You're supposed
to be wearing it.
-I'm not putting it on
until the orientation.
I don't want to mess it up.
-So you want your headband nice.
But your photo, which is
supposed to identify you
makes you look like a clown.
It's for ninja
training and missions,
which is the key to your future.
Look at this picture.
You can't even tell who it is.
-Well, fine.
How am I supposed to know all
this complicated stuff anyway?
[chime]
-Hmm?
-Ah?
-Old man.
I challenge you.
-Ahh.
-I'm going to defeat you
and become the Fifth Hokage.
-Wahhh.
-Ohhh.
-My grandson.
Another headache.
-Uhh.
-Ohhh.
Something tripped me.
-Uh.
Uh.
Are you okay honorable grandson?
And by the way, there's nothing
here for you to triple on.
It's pretty flat.
-Ah.
Who is this shrimp?
-Mm-hmm.
-Ha.
It's that kid.
Humph.
The nine-tailed fox.
Of course.
He's the worst kind
of trouble maker.
-Alright.
You're the one who
tripped me aren't you?
-Ahhh.
You tripped your own feet dork.
-Hey you.
Take your hands off
of him right now.
He's the honorable grandson
of the honorable third Hokage.
-Huh?
-That's stopping him.
Just like all the rest.
Ha!
Now that he knows who I am, he
won't dare lay a finger on me.
What's the matter huh?
I thought you were going
to hit me tough guy.
Afraid because the Third
Hokage is my grandfather?
-I don't care if he's
your grandmother.
So believe it.
-Ah.
This guy's different.
-Ha, uh, uh.
-This is not looking good.
-Listen carefully.
You a the honorable grandson
of the honorable third Hokage.
You cannot let riff raff like
this draw you into a fight even
though he deserves it.
You see he's far beneath you.
mustn't stoop to his level.
As your elite ninja
trainer, I am never wrong,
which means I'm always right.
I'm far above the other
trainers so heed my every word.
Your goal is to become
the next Hokage.
And I can teach you
the best way to do it.
Indeed.
Due to my great skill, I can
take you quickly and easily
to the top.
But you must always
stay close to me.
You understand me?
Right honorable grandson?
[zaps]
-Where did he go now?
-I think he followed Naruto.
But I have no idea
where they're going.
-He's with Naruto?
That's a disaster.
Honorable grandson.
-Ahhhh.
How did he grow up
to be like that?
My grandson's quite determined.
That was his 20th
sneak attack today.
And if he starts running
around with Naruto,
he's sure to get even worse.
Naruto wouldn't teach him
anything really bad, would he?
-Huh?
[swoosh]
-Hmmm.
[boing]
-Mm-hmm.
[squealing whistle]
-Ohhh.
I know that you're following
me so just give it up.
[twang]
That's so obvious.
It's pathetic.
[giggle]
-Saw through my disguise huh?
The rumors about you are true.
You're good.
[squealing whistle]
-Alright.
I'll be your apprentice.
And you'll be my trainer.
-Huh?
-And afterward,
you've got to show me
how to do that sexy jutsu thing
you did on Grandpa Hokage.
-This is some kind
of joke isn't it?
-No.
I need a new trainer.
Please boss.
-Huh?
Boss?
-Yeah.
You're the boss.
Boss.
-Well, how can I refuse?
Listen, you want to
be a master ninja?
Then believe it.
You got to learn to
control your catra.
-Your catra?
[sound effect bubble] A cat?
[meow]
-I said, your catra.
-Boss, I uh-- think you're
talking about your chakra.
-Don't question me.
Real ninjas say catra.
-Really?
I didn't know that.
That's cool.
-Hmmm.
He believes anything I say.
Listen, I'll explain
what chakra is.
-Chakra is the
elemental life energy
that is used to perform jutsu.
-Huh?
-The ninja arts
combine physical energy
from each cell in the body
with mystical energy, which
is intensified from
training and experience.
When these two chakra
mix, special hand signs
allow the ninja to
focus this combined
energy for advanced jutsu.
-Know it all.
You were just reading
that whole thing.
Yo.
You can blab all you want about
how to do ninja techniques.
But it really comes
down to one thing.
-What is it?
-Just plain hard work and guts.
-That's two things.
But OK.
I'm with you.
-Alright.
I'm going to throw some really
big challenges at you now.
Are you ready?
-I'm ready boss.
-Good.
Then let's do it.
Show me a transformation.
-Huh?
-Believe it.
Show me what you can do.
And I'll take you
to the next level.
-Oh, right, sure.
But um--what do
I transform into?
-Uh, hmmmm.
Hmmm.
[squealing boing]
-There.
Yeah, right.
You can transform into her.
-No problem.
Here I go boss.
[twang]
-Transform.
Well, do I look like her?
-Uh-- the clothes
kind of look like her.
[boing]
-That looks like me?
Now, now, honorable
grandson, next time
you transform into me,
make me a little cuter OK?
Ta.
-She's scary.
[boing]
-Ahhh.
You did it.
Why am I the one that
gets whacked around?
Alright.
Next, we do some research
on female beauty.
-Female beauty.
Right boss.
[snoring]
[piano trill]
[laughter]
-This is not a library Naruto.
-Ahh.
-Oh.
[stick slap]
NARUTO: Slight setback.
Heh heh.
Now, this is the last stop.
So give it everything
you've got, OK?
-Everything.
Right boss.
-Transform.
Mmmmm.
GIRLS SCREAMING: Naruto.
You again?
Stay out of the
girl's locker room.
-Why do they only whack me?
-Sorry.
-Huh?
-It's because I'm the
grandson of old Hokage.
-Hey, don't worry about it.
-Huh?
-I prepared you.
So now you're ready to
learn the sexy jutsu.
Believe it.
You're just going
to need to practice.
-Practice.
Alright boss.
-Now the trick is to get all
the curves in the right places.
You ready?
-I'm ready boss.
Transform.
[pow]
[chime]
-What do you think?
-No go.
You've got to make her skinnier.
HONORABLE GRANDSON: Skinnier.
Right boss.
NARUTO: Ayee.
HONORABLE GRANDSON: How's that?
NARUTO: No.
No.
Curvier.
HONORABLE GRANDSON: Curvier.
Right boss.
How's this?
NARUTO: Ahhh.
NINJA TRAINER: Naruto.
What has he done with
the honorable grandson?
Ahmmm.
What's his evil plan?
Where did they go?
I'm a chunin, the
highest ninja level.
And I'm an elite trainer
of future Hokage.
Any parasite that leaches onto
my student will be squashed.
[birds]
[slurp]
-So what's up with
this obsession
you've got with
your grandfather?
My grandfather
named me Konahamaru
after the ancient
name of the village.
So it should be
easy to remember.
But no one calls me that name.
Not one person in
the whole village.
That's because when they look
at me, they don't really see me.
All they see is the honorable
grandson of the Lord Hokage.
No one knows who I am.
I can't stand it anymore.
It's like I'm visible.
Like I don't exist.
I hate that.
That's the reason.
I've got to become a Hokage
now so people know who I am.
-Get real.
You think people are going
to accept a squirt like you?
-Huh?
-A kid can't just turn into
a Hokage after a day or two.
-What?
-It's not that simple.
You keep saying Hokage, Hokage.
To really be a Hokage, you
know what you'll have to do?
-What?
What is it?
[chant]
-You're going to have
to beat me in battle.
[chanting]
NINJA TRAINER: Lord Hokage.
I've been looking for you.
-For what purpose?
IRUKA: It's about Naruto.
Did he resubmit
his ninja ID photo?
-Mmmm.
IRUKA: You know, I gave him
a big lecture the other night
at the ramen shop.
But he's still
beaming because he
became a genin, a ninja trainee.
He thinks that'll change
things, that people
will stop looking
down on him now.
-I fear his dream
may not come true.
People don't change that easily.
-Huh?
-The nine-tailed
fox is within him.
Not everyone knows
that of course.
Only those who fought the beast
12 years ago know the truth.
I decreed that no one
could speak about this.
Even those who whispered
it were punished severely.
So the children of
today know nothing
about Naruto's connection to the
beast that ravaged our village
and nearly destroyed us all.
As long as the children
are unaware of this,
Naruto has some hope
of being accepted.
That was the wish
of the Fourth Hokage
before he sacrificed
himself to save us.
He asked that when
Naruto grew up,
he should be regarded as a hero.
-A hero?
-The Fourth Hokage
defeated the fox
by sealing it's spirit in a
newborn baby whose umbilical
cord has just been cut.
By containing the fox
spirit within his tiny body,
Naruto saved the village.
That's why he's a hero.
Unfortunately, many
of the villagers
don't understand this.
People are driven by fear.
Many think the beast could
take over Naruto's body.
Some think he is the beast now.
And their children feel
their fear and hatred.
And they turn against
Naruto as well.
Do you know what the ancients
said about such things Iruka?
IRUKA: What's that Sir?
-When the people reject
someone very existence,
and then look at that person,
their eyes become cold.
Cold as an ice storm
in the deepest winter.
[swoosh]
NINJA TRAINER: I found you.
NARUTO: Huh?
NINJA TRAINER: Hmm.
The nine-tailed fox.
-That icy stare.
They all look at me that way.
Uhhh.
[swoosh]
NINJA TRAINER: So
honorable grandson.
Time to go home.
KONAHAMARU: No way.
I'm learning how to
beat my grandfather
so I can get the title.
Hokage.
Now don't get in my way.
NINJA TRAINER: A Hokage is
more than just a fighter.
He must move virtue,
honor, wisdom.
And he must be skilled
at a thousand jutsu.
You don't even know one jutsu.
KONAHAMARU: Mmmm.
Transform!
[swoosh]
[pow]
-Hi there.
Like my jutsu?
-Ahhhhhh.
-Hey.
He's not defeated.
NINJA TRAINER: What--
what-- what kind
of scandalous technique is that?
Such tasteless vulgarity
can never influence me.
I am far above it.
KONAHAMARU: Unnnnn.
NINJA TRAINER:
Honorable grandson.
Stop this.
Right now.
Ahh.
Naruto's turning you
into a delinquent.
Only my special
training can put you
on the fast track to
becoming a Hokage.
KONAHAMARU: Just leave me alone.
NARUTO: Batlle call jutsu.
KONAHAMARU: Huh?
[swoosh]
KONAHAMARU: Whoa.
This is unreal.
-Humph.
I'm not impressed.
I'm a jounin, an
elite ninja warrior.
I'm not some
lightweight like Mizuki.
Watch how a real ninja
defeats an upstart.
KONAHAMARU: Come on boss.
[swoosh]
-Transform, Transform.
Transform.
[boing]
-Oh.
Oh.
NINJA TRAINER: Ah ah.
Ahhhh.
[thud]
-Gotcha with my harem jutsu.
-He's combined shadow cloning
with his own invention,
the sexy jutsu.
What a foolish ninja technique.
And he could probably
get me with it too.
Ahhhhh.
KONAHAMARU: Oh man.
I couldn't even beat that
snobby trainer of mine.
I want to be Hokage so bad.
But I keep messing up.
Why can't I do it?
-You really think
it's that easy?
-Huh?
-To be a Hokage, you have to
be the greatest of all ninja.
You have to prove yourself
so everyone believes in you.
Look at me.
I've been through a lot already.
I've been ignored,
pushed away, and treated
like I had the
plague or something.
And after all that, I found
one person who believes in me.
To find that one person, I
had to get knocked down a lot.
So you better make
sure that you're ready.
KONAHAMARU: For what?
-For lots of sweat
and tears while
you're learning to be a ninja.
[wind blowing]
-Ha, by the way, there is no
easy way to becoming Hokage.
Believe it.
If you really want
to be a Hokage,
you're going to have
to defeat me in battle.
-Ha.
Who do you think you
are anyway giving me
a big lecture like that?
That's it.
I'm not going to your
apprentice anymore.
From now on we're rivals.
Heh heh.
-Heh heh.
Well, I can't be
your trainer anyway.
Because tomorrow, I start
my advanced ninja studies.
But I accept your challenge.
And someday, we'll fight for
the title of Lord Hokage.
So let's both look forward
to that day Konahamaru.
-At last, he's
finally started down
the path to becoming
a true ninja.
[theme music]
THEME SONG: Cultivate your
hunger before you idealize.
Motivate your anger to
make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain,
never coming down.
Break in to the contents,
never falling down.
My knee is still
shaking like I was 12,
sneaking out the
classroom by the backdoor.
A man railed at me
twice, but I didn't care.
Waiting is wasting
for people like me.
Don't try to live so wise.
Don't cry, because
you're so right.
Don't dry with fakes or fears,
because you will hate yourself
in the end.
Don't try to live so wise.
Don't cry, because
you're so right.
Don't dry with fakes or fears,
because you will hate yourself
in the end.
Don't try to live so wise.
Don't cry, because
you're so right.
Don't dry with fakes--
-Not Sasuke.
I can't stand him.
Why do I have to
be in his group?
-Sakura keeps calling his name.
Sasuke.
-She won't even look at me.
Uhhh.
Hey I know.
I'll play a trick on him.
And fake him out.
Hey, Sasuke, let's
see how cool Sakura
thinks you are after that.
Next time.
Sasuke and Sakura,
friends or foes?
[giggle]