[theme music]
-I depend on no one.
I will do this on my own.
-Hold on.
I'm coming with you.
Like it or not, I made
a promise to Hinata
that I'm going to protect you.
-To Hinata?
-She got pretty badly
injured fighting
that second ninja
who was after you.
-She what?
But I was sure that
you and the rest
have decided that protecting
me wasn't part of your mission.
If that's true, why
are you doing this?
-It's just the way we are.
We don't like it when see
somebody getting a raw deal,
even if that somebody
is maybe not, well,
the nicest person in the world.
But that's not important.
There's a narrow
canyon up ahead.
And we've got to get through it.
The village is on
the other side.
And hopefully, they
won't follow us there.
Come on, let's go!
-Uhh.
-You were so close.
But you'll never reach
that village now.
I'm afraid your
journey ends here.
-How-- how does he do that?
He's floating in air!
-That's right.
And this is just the beginning.
My jutsu is beyond
anything you can imagine.
For example-- heeyah!
-Huh, aah!
-Naruto!
-Yeah, I'm all right.
Don't worry.
But what-- what the heck
was that he hit me with?
-You have other things to
worry about now-- like, what's
to become of those friends
of yours I'm holding hostage.
-Your-- what?
-Huh!
-Don't worry.
I'll let your friends live
if you just step aside
and let me have the girl.
-Hinata and Choji?
-Well then, what's
it going to be, kid?
-Naruto, would you abandon
me, like everybody else?
-You hear that?
What the princess
is really saying
is that you should stay
with her and abandon
your friends to die.
Not a very noble
attitude, perhaps.
But I have to admit, it's
just what I would say.
-Why am I not surprised?
-I have no use for people who
no longer serve a purpose-- be
they friends,
family, or whatever.
In fact, that's
something I should
thank you and your friends for.
-Thank us?
What do you mean?
-For eliminating those
weaklings, Jiga and Ruiga.
You saved me the
troublesome task
of having to get
rid of them myself.
-You what?
-It wouldn't have been
long before they'd
have started whining,
brother, when are you
going to give us a
share of our spoils?
Hah, three feudal
lords is two too many.
-You'd do that to
your own brothers?
-What does it matter
that they're my brothers?
Like I said, if someone's
of no use to me,
I have no use for them.
Now, stand aside and
let me have the girl.
-No way.
-Ha-ha!
-Naruto?
-A guy who'd betray
his own brothers?
What makes you think
someone like that would ever
keep his end of
the bargain anyway?
-Well, there you have a point.
Rrrh!
-Stop, Naruto!
You don't know
what his jutsu is!
-Well, there's only
one way to find out.
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
-Hah!
[clanging]
-Huh?
Aah!
Uhh.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
What's going on?
It's like he's got an
invisible shield around him.
-Agh!
-Naruto!
-I certainly hope you've got
something else up your sleeve
because that pitiful little
ninjutsu will never work.
-[grunts]
-Hey, wait a second.
What did he just do?
Is that--
-It looks like ice.
-Hah, you see I'm able to gather
the water vapor in the air
and instantly transform it
into an impervious wall of ice.
-That's it!
He was attacking me with ice.
No wonder it was invisible.
It's hard to defend against
something you can't see!
-Ha-ha!
If you were impressed
by that, just wait.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I've got a
bad feeling something's coming.
I can sense it.
It's already started.
But what is it?
And where is it coming from?
-So do you want to know the
weather forecast for today?
-The weather forecast?
-I'd say sunny with
scattered clouds.
Perfect conditions for dying.
-Uh, something's going on.
Uh.
What the-- watch out!
-[chuckles]
-Ugh!
Aah!
What's he doing?
-Naruto, it's some kind of lens.
-A lens, huh?
RENGA: Ha-ha!
Exactly.
But turning the ice crystal
into a magnifying lens,
I can focus the sun's
rays into a deadly beam.
Not the most precise weapon, but
brutally effective, as you'll
soon find out.
Once I'm in full control
of the Land of Greens,
I'll use this jutsu to destroy
all the neighboring lands.
-Run!
-It's no use.
No matter where you
run, I can see you.
-[panting]
[both gasp]
-Found you.
[snorts]
-Uhh.
Oh.
-Ugh.
-Naruto, why do you protect me?
-I don't know.
Just call me crazy.
-Naruto.
-Aagh!
[gasping]
-[gasping]
-Listen.
-Huh?
-While I draw his fire,
you run for your life, OK?
-Hm.
-Hm, you think you
can escape my jutsu
with a little trick like that?
-Huh!
-Uhm?
-I see.
Does this mean you're
giving up the princess?
-If you think I'd ever hand
her over to you, you're crazy!
-Think of your friends.
If you ever want to see them
alive again, all you have to do
is walk away and go quietly
back to your own village.
-I swore to defend
her, no matter what!
I gave Hinata my word!
-Really?
So merely to keep a
promise to a friend,
you're going to fight a
battle you can't possibly win?
-Hrrh!
-[laughs]
You're just another
soft-hearted little fool,
like the late lord of
the Land of Greens.
HARUNA (VOICEOVER):
Oh, my father.
-[laughs]
You're just another
soft-hearted little fool,
like the late lord of
the Land of Greens.
HARUNA (VOICEOVER):
Oh, my father.
-There was only one
thing he cared about
as we stole his land from him.
You should have heard him
beg, "Only one thing I
ask, spare my people.
Spare them!"
-I don't care what
happens to me.
But spare my people.
I beg of you.
We're only small,
weak land surrounded
by powerful neighbors.
We can only survive by
being strong and united.
The life of every citizen of the
Land of Greens, young or old,
is precious.
Not a single life can be wasted.
Whatever you do, for
the sake of this land,
you must be good to my people.
-But sadly for him, they're
not his people anymore.
They are mine.
-That's it!
-Wha--
-Now, I see!
That's why this land has
been at peace all this time.
-What do I care whether
it's been peaceful or not?
To me, it's only a stepping
stone to greater things.
And why don't you
ask his daughter
how peaceful her life has
been the last 10 years?
-[gasps]
-What the heck are
you talking about?
-Her father gave
her up as a hostage.
-Our neighbors were too strong.
The pressures they put
on us were too great.
Our land was on the
verge of collapse.
There was rioting,
treachery, corruption.
They demanded a hostage.
And so I made the
dreadful decision
to send them my daughter,
the light of my life.
Is it possible Haruna
could ever forgive me?
Can any father ever
be forgiven who
would sacrifice
his own child, even
if he thought it was
only to save his people?
-I don't know.
You'll have to ask her when next
you see her in the afterlife!
-[gasps]
HARUNA (VOICEOVER):
Father, murdered!
-[laughs]
What a sentimental fool!
-You're wrong!
He was a wise man!
-Naruto.
-Hah!
There are just two kinds
of people in the world--
the ones who use others
and the fools who get used!
As for me, I will gladly
use anyone to get where I
what I want to go.
-No way!
Not this time, mister!
-Oh, no?
Haah!
-Aargh!
Ugh!
He's too strong.
Huh?
Ugh!
-Now, die!
-Aah!
[coughs]
Ugh.
HARUNA (VOICEOVER): Naruto.
-What's wrong, kid?
You don't seem quite as spunky.
-It'll never happen.
You're not the one.
-Huh?
-It was Haruna's father who kept
this place safe and peaceful.
-Huh?
-There's only one person who
can be lord of this land.
Only one person has the right.
And that's Haruna, no one else!
-No, stop!
-What are you doing?
Get out of here
while you still can!
-It's me you want.
To succeed, you have to
eliminate me, not Naruto.
Forget him.
He has nothing to do with it!
-I see there's a
soft-hearted streak that
runs in your family.
You and your father
will have a great deal
to discuss when you're
reunited in the hereafter.
-Uhm.
-Oh, if looks could kill.
-I've had it with this guy!
-And I have more than
had it with you, kid.
-Don't call me "kid."
My name's Naruto Uzumaki!
And I made a promise
to someone-- a promise
to protect the Land of
Greens from jerks like you!
-Naruto!
Uh!
-There, there.
-Hrrh!
-What?
-Rrh!
-Aargh!
-Oh!
-What have you done?
Uhh.
Ugh.
It's too late.
You may have beaten
me, but I've left
the Land of Greens devastated.
And without a leader, it will
soon fall to its neighbors.
WOMAN: Sorry, I don't think so.
-Huh?
Shizune?
-It's such a drag
cleaning up after you.
-Shikamaru!
But, uh, what are
you doing here?
It's not like I
needed your help.
-Oh, you didn't, huh?
How come you're
looking so beat up?
-What do you mean?
I tripped, that's all.
GIRL: Naruto!
-Huh?
-[laughs]
Hinata, Choji, Yurinojo!
And you guys are all right!
-Yes, thanks to all of your
comrades from the Leaf Village.
-Wait a minute.
I still don't get it.
How come you guys are here?
-We received word that
there might be trouble here.
So Lady Tsunade sent
us to offer assistance.
She's fond of the
Land of Greens.
The lord of this place was
very generous to her once.
-My father?
-Unfortunately, by the time
we arrived, your father--
your father was already, uh--
-I understand.
How can I thank you?
-So close.
I was finally lord of the land.
-But wait.
Won't the Land of Greens be
attacked by its neighbors now?
-They wouldn't dare.
We've let them all know
that the rightful leader
of the Land of Greens is
alive and well-- you, Princess
Haruna.
-So, at least,
that's one thing you
won't have to worry
about, Haruna.
Huh?
Haruna?
-[heaving]
-Go ahead.
I don't blame you for
wanting your revenge.
I would do the same thing.
-Huh?
-Aah!
-[shrieks]
Huh?
-I won't do it.
I'm not like you.
[sobs]
-Haruna.
-Forgive me, Kikunojo.
-Princess Haruna.
-He can see everything
from way up here.
You can be sure
he'll be watching
over the Land of
Greens from now on.
-Well, Lady Haruna, we'd
better be on our way.
-Thank you, Naruto,
Choji, Hinata.
-Please, Shizune, I'd like
to ask a favor, if I may.
-Of course, what is it?
-I'm not sure I'm ready
to assume my father's
role as protector of this land.
I'd be much more
confident if I had
the help of the Leaf Village.
-Our help?
-Yes.
Will you let Naruto
stay with me?
-Huh?
-Please, Naruto--
-Haruna?
---won't you help me restore the
Land of Greens to what it once
was?
[crunching]
-[snickers]
Uh, well--
-Uhh.
-I'm honored.
But I'm afraid I can't.
You see, I'm needed at home.
I've got a lot of
responsibilities, too.
A lot of people
depend on me to keep
training and making
myself stronger.
And I depend on
them to do the same.
My friends and me--
we need each other.
-Well then, I can't
take you away from them.
All right, I'll do my best.
And one thing that will help me
follow in my father's footsteps
is if you'll promise to always
be my friend, too, Naruto.
Will you do that?
-[chuckles]
Sure, you've got my word.
-Hm.
Thank you, Naruto!
-Farewell, everyone!
-So long!
-Don't worry, we'll
come back someday!
-Goodbye!
-See you then!
[music playing]
INO: Aah!
He's looking this way!
-Of course, he is.
That's the whole point!
INO: No way!
I can't.
It's impossible.
Oh, no!
He's coming this way!
NARUTO: That's a
good thing, isn't it?
Now, come on, relax.
Just think of the mission!
-No way!
Are you crazy?
He's-- he's-- [shrieks]
NARUTO: Come on, he's not.
INO: Well--
NARUTO: If it was
easy, it wouldn't
be much of mission, would it?
Next time, "Ino Screams!
Chubby Paradise!"
[music playing]