[music playing]
[music - Hound Dog, "Rocks"]
NEJI: Hey you.
Over here.
What's your name?
-I'm not obliged to answer.
-What's that?
TENTEN (VOICEOVER):
[giggles] Cute.
-Heh.
So that's the bunch of
misfits that Kakashi and Guy
have been going on about.
I guess they passed
their first test,
getting their
applications through.
-Right.
It looks like the exams
are gonna be fun this year.
-Yeah, for us, but
maybe not for them.
SAKURA: Hey, Sasuke!
Naruto!
Come on, let's go.
-All right.
Don't pull me, Sakura.
NEJI (VOICEOVER): Sasuke,
of the Uchiha clan.
-He's pretty bold.
You gonna challenge him?
-Hm.
-[chuckles]
Lee, what are waiting for?
We're supposed to check in.
-I will catch up
with you in a minute.
You do not need to wait for me.
I just want to check something.
-What's that about?
-I have no idea.
ROCK LEE: Hey you,
with the attitude.
Hold on.
ALL THREE: Huh?
Right
-Oh!
[gasp]
-What do you want?
-I want to fight, right
here and right now.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Chunin Challenge:
Rock Lee versus Sasuke.
-You want to fight
me here and now, huh?
ROCK LEE: Yes.
My name is Rock Lee.
You said it was common
currency for a challenger
to give his own
name first, right?
Sasuke Uchiha?
-Hm.
So you know me.
I challenge you.
Everyone is always talking
about the Uchiha clan
and how great they are.
I want to see if it is true.
I figure you will be
a good test for me.
And also--
-Aaah!
-Oh, Sakura!
I love you!
--[screams] Those
eyebrows can't be real.
Nooooo!
Your hairstyle is horrible, too.
And those I are so bushy!
You're such a weirdo!
-You are an angel,
sent from heaven.
-Yaaaahahhhh!
Whoa!
-That was a good move, but
let us see you dodge this.
Mwah, mwah, mwah!
[screams]
[clang]
[panting]
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
That was too close.
-Hey!
Keep your creepy little
valentines to yourself!
I was dodging for my life there!
-You do not have to be
so negative, Sakura.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): He
wants to fight Sasuke?
Arggh!
It's always Sasuke!
-You've heard of
the Uchiha Clan,
yet you're challenging me?
You must be even more
psycho than you look,
if that's possible.
You want to know
more about my clan,
then I'll teach
you-- the hard way.
-Bring it on.
ROCK LEE (VOICEOVER): Excellent.
A match-up against
the number-one rookie.
I will draw him out and get
him to reveal his technique,
and I will prove myself
to you, Guy Sensei.
NARUTO: Hold it!
-Uh?
-I get him first.
This weirdo is mine.
-Go for it.
-Naruto.
-What?
It'll take me two
minutes to have
this guy begging for mercy.
-No thank you.
Right now the only one I
want to fight is Uchiha.
-Yeah?
Well, I've got news for you!
Sasuke can't compare to me!
Believe it!
Yaahhh!
Aaaaahhh!
Uhhh-- gaahhh!
-Leaf Whirlwind!
-Aaaaahhhh!
Gaaahhh.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Whoa!
He's better than he looks.
-Just accept it.
You have no chance against me.
Your skills are inferior.
You see, Sasuke.
[moans]
-Out of all the top Leaf
Genin, I am the best.
Fight me and I will
prove it to you.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
He stopped my kick.
That's some chakra
he's got on his arm.
-Hmm.
This'll be fun.
Let's do it.
[gasp]
-There's no time, Sasuke.
We've got to register
by three o'clock.
That's less than half an hour.
-Relax.
This'll all be over
in five seconds.
ROCK LEE (VOICEOVER):
Here he comes.
Forgive me, Guy Sensei.
I know it is forbidden, but
I may have to break the rules
and use that jutsu!
-Unh!
-Leaf Hurricane!
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): I'm
not moving fast enough.
I've got to block him.
What?
-Aaaah!
-Sasuke!
-Unh!
-[grunts] What's going on?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
He had his guard up,
and Lee went right through it.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): He's using
some technique to get to me.
But what is it?
A ninjutsu or a genjutsu?
ROCK LEE (VOICEOVER):
As I expected,
he is coming back for more.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): Hm.
OK, this is good.
Got him right where I want him.
Now's my chance.
-I've been waiting
to try this out.
[gasp]
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Could it be?
Is it-- the Sharingan!
When did he learn to-- his eyes!
It's in both of them.
ROCK LEE (VOICEOVER): So
that is the Sharingan.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): You never
know what Sasuke'll do next.
He's amazing!
If it's like Kakashi
Sensei's Sharingan,
he'll be able to read this
guy's jutsu and nail him!
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
Genjutsu or ninjutsu--
whatever magic he's
using, I'll see it now.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Sasuke's
getting stronger every day!
Just what'd you'd
expect from an Uchiha.
Sasuke could never lose to
a guy like this. no way!
-Aaaugh!
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): What?
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): Nngh!
He got around my guard.
But how?
What kind of jutsu is that?
-You see, my technique is
not ninjutsu or genjutsu.
-Mmmnh!
Aah!
[gasp] Sasuke!
-Unnhhhh!
ROCK LEE: You get it now?
I am using taijutsu.
That means no tricks, Sasuke.
It is just straight
martial arts, nothing more.
-Why, you--
-I know your technique.
Forget it.
It will not work, not on me.
I know you can see through
your opponent's jutsu.
That Sharingan gives you the
ability to read his chakra
and decipher his hand
signs and movements.
You can guess what
he's going to do almost
before he knows himself.
The problem is taijutsu
is a little bit different.
-Right.
So what's your point?
-I do not try to hide
or disguise my moves.
I do not have to.
Even if you can read them,
you still cannot stop them.
You are too slow.
Your eyes may be quick enough
to stay one step ahead of me,
but if your body cannot keep
up, what good does it do you?
-Rrrrrah!
-You know what?
Here is what I believe.
There are two different
kinds of ninja--
those like you were
born with talent
and do not have to work
at it, and those like me,
the ones who have to train
every day of our lives!
Fact is, your
Sharingan is the worst
match for my extreme taijutsu!
Here is what I mean.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
I have to stop him!
-Aaaaaiii-yah!
-Dancing Leaf Shadow.
-Good eye.
Now I will prove my point.
That hard work beats
out natural talent.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
What's his next move?
-You're finished.
Huh?
[thwack]
[gasp]
-This is bad.
-All right, that's enough!
Lee?
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
What-- what now?
-Sasuke!
[thud]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): He
totally beat Sasuke!
Something happened
while I was knocked out!
What'd he do?
[grunts with pain]
-Are you OK?
Sasuke!
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
He's really shaken up.
He didn't even take
the fall right.
-You-- you were watching
us the whole time?
-Of course.
That last technique
is forbidden.
You know that.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): He's
talking to a turtle,
and it's talking back.
-I am sorry.
I did not mean to--
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Now he's
apologizing to a turtle.
Wait a minute-- could
that be his sensei?
-Aaaah!
I was not planning to
use a forbidden jutsu.
It was just-- I was in
the middle of the fight,
and I mean, you understand.
NARUTO: I'm right!
It really his sensei!
-Huh?
-Hm?
NARUTO: Hey, you guys!
-What, Naruto?
-That weird thing he's
talking to is a turtle, right?
-Obviously!
What'd you think it is?
-OK then, so maybe it means
that turtles can be sensei too.
-How would I know if
they can be sensei too?
-You're a disgrace!
-Mmm!
-You think you'll
get away with a bunch
of lame excuses like that?
A shinobi never
reveals his techniques
unless it's
absolutely necessary.
It's such a basic rule,
you should know it by now!
-Forgive me, sir.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): How
could I lose to that freak?
[growls angrily]
-Are you prepared to take the
punishment for your actions?
-I-- yes, sir.
-All right, then.
Please come out, Guy Sensei!
-Hey!
What's shakin'?
How you doing, everybody?
Life treating you good?
-Aaaahh!
Aaaahhh!
NARUTO: He's got the
biggest eyebrows yet!
They're almost alive!
-Hi, lady.
SAKURA: Too weird!
I that's where Lee gets it from.
Same soup bowl haircut
and even bushier eyebrows!
-Hey!
Do not insult Guy Sensei!
He is one of the greatest
men in the entire world!
-Well, excuse me for not
noticing his greatness!
I was too busy
watching him crawl out
from underneath a turtle!
-He did not crawl out!
-Give it a rest, Lee.
-Huh?
Hm.
Yes, sir.
-Now for your punishment.
Yaaahhh!
You little fool!
-Aaaaahhh!
Aaaahhh!
-I'm sorry Lee, but
it's for your own good.
-Sen-- Sensei--
-(TEARFULLY) Oh, Lee.
-(TEARFULLY) Oh-- oh,
Sensei, I am so sorry!
-All right.
It's over.
You don't need to say any more.
-Sensei!
[both weeping]
-Lee!
-Gahhh!
-Uggghh!
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): How could
I lose to someone that lame?
-It's OK.
It's OK.
It's only a phase.
ROCK LEE: I am sorry, Sensei.
-Huh?
Actually, it's kind
of sweet, the way
they're all huggy and stuff.
-Huh?
You've got to be kidding!
They're both totally crazy!
-You're just caught in between.
You're too old to be called a
boy and not yet quite a man.
-You are so good
to me, Guy Sensei.
-Now take off!
I want you to give me 100 laps
around the practice field.
Show me what you got!
-Yes, sir!
No problem.
-Run into the setting sun.
Run and suffer!
But don't mess up your hair.
Let us go!
-Right!
-Hey, wait a minute!
We're not finished here.
You guys can't just
take off like that.
-And what about
the Chunin Exams?
There's no time
for fooling around.
-Ohh.
Uh-- oh, right, I
forgot about that.
[clears throat]
Lee, you not only
disobeyed the rule
against fighting,
but you've disrupted
the Chunin Exams.
I think that warrants a
slightly more severe punishment,
don't you?
-Yes, sir.
-Let's say 500 laps!
How does that sound?
-Outstanding, sir.
-They're insane.
-Probably.
But never mind them-- what's the
deal with that turtle, anyway?
-Vo: Hm.
This must be Kakashi's squad.
I'll check 'em out.
-Aaah!
No!
He's looking at us!
MIGHT GUY: Tell me,
how is Kakashi Sensei?
SASUKE: Do you know him?
-Do I know Kakashi?
[chuckles] Well,
people say he and I
are archrivals for all eternity.
BOTH: There's just no way!
-How dare you?
If Guy Sensei says
it is true, then--
-Let it slide, Lee.
A ninja's actions always
speak louder than words.
-Hm?
Uh?
MIGHT GUY: My record is 50
wins and 49 losses-- which
is one better than
his, by the way.
[gasp]
-What?
NARUTO: Aaah?
You're kidding!
How'd he beat Kakashi?
-The fact is I'm
stronger than Kakashi.
And faster.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): His
speed is incredible.
He's definitely
faster than Kakashi.
Is he even human?
-You see?
Guy Sensei is the best there is.
-I'm sorry for the
trouble Lee caused you.
Look into my eyes and
accept my sincere apology.
Also notice my handsome
manly features.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): He claims
he's better than Kakashi.
Could that be true?
Argh!
I don't think he's
making this up.
-Lee, you should accompany
these fine young ninjin
to the classroom, right now.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Huh?
His hands!
-Remember, give it your best.
Lee, farewell.
-Yes, sir.
-Whoa!
-Hey, Sasuke.
Actually, I have not been
totally honest with you.
I said I wanted
to test my skills,
and that is true enough.
But you are not really the one
I wanted to test them against.
I lied to you when we
were fighting before.
I told you I'm am
the best genin here,
but there is another top
ninja, someone on my own team.
I came here to defeat him.
You were just practice.
Now you are a target.
I will crush you.
There you have it.
Consider yourself warned.
-Oh, Sasuke.
-Nyah.
How about that?
Looks like the Uchihas
aren't as great
as everybody thinks they are.
-Naruto!
-Just shut up!
Next time I'll drive
him to his knees!
-Yeah, right.
Who just got his butt kicked?
-Stop it!
What are you saying?
Just cut it out, Naruto!
[growls]
-You saw his hands, didn't you?
When he took off the tape?
I bet old Bushy-Brow has
been training till he drops,
day in and day out.
He trains harder than you.
That's all I'm saying.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Sasuke.
-Fine.
Hmph.
-Hm?
-This thing's starting
to get interesting.
The Chunin Exams-- can't
wait to see what's next.
-Right!
-Let's get started.
Naruto!
Sakura!
-Yeahhh!
[music - Akeboshi, "Wind"]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Whoa!
All these guys are here
for the Chunin Exams?
Kiba, Shino, Hinata,
Shikamaru, and Choji?
Poor guys.
It's a shame I've got to
make them all look bad.
But hey, after I ace the test
and become chunin, and then
Hokage, I'll make it up
to them by-- eh, letting
'em boil my ramen or something.
Next time, Genin Takedown.
All nine rookies face off!
I don't want to get
cocky, but it's hard
not to be when you're the best.
Believe it!