[theme music]
-Stop it.
OK.
Let's see how you like it.
Hey.
-Nice.
-Pervy Sage.
Hello?
Are you going to watch me
try this jutsu again or not?
-Can't you see I'm
busy with my research?
Do it yourself.
-OK.
I will.
And this time I'm
going to summon
a frog the size of a house.
Summoning jutsu.
Huh?
-So how did it go?
Did you get a frog to appear?
-Wait.
Give it a second.
I think it's still growing.
-Listen, if you're not going
to take this seriously,
then I'm through with you.
Do you understand me?
-I am serious.
You're the one who's staring
at the girls, you old goat.
-Stop fooling around and
focus on your chakras
as if your life depended on it.
NARUTO: What do you
think I'm doing?
Sasuke.
SAKURA'S MOM: Hey,
come on, Sakura.
Are you still asleep?
When are you going to come
down here and help me?
-I wasn't sleeping.
I'm busy.
SAKURA'S MOM: I see.
Well, when won't you be busy?
-Later.
I can't believe it.
I can't.
A feeling of yearning.
A flower full of hope.
Some of you may not yet
have heard the news.
The body of Hayate Gekko
was found near Kikyo Castle.
-What?
Hayate?
-He's-- he's dead?
-Unbelievable.
-This has to be
Orochimaru's doing.
-As likely as that
may seem, let's
not jump to conclusions yet.
We think Hayate was on the
trail of a Sound Village
spy named Kabuto.
No doubt Orochimaru
is up to something.
But we don't know for sure.
-Well, I say cancel the Chunin
Exams and go after Orochimaru.
-No, I think not.
He revealed himself to
Anko and sent a warning
not to cancel the exams.
You see, these exams have
brought together ninja
from every allied nation.
-What do you think it means?
-There are two things
we know about him.
That he bears an abiding
grudge against our Hidden Leaf
Village.
And that his power is great.
Perhaps great enough to
crush a village on his own.
Certainly great enough
that any village
would prefer to have
him on their side
rather than against them.
-Impossible.
No village in the alliance would
betray another and join forces
with that fiend.
-Well, the alliance
treaty is only
as binding as any
verbal agreement.
As we found out during
the last great ninja war.
-In any case, until we're
able to find out more,
this is all just
idle speculation.
-We've dispatched ANBU
black ops to every village
to collect information.
We would be fools
to act too hastily.
That might be just what
our enemy is aiming for.
-And besides, I have complete
trust in every one of you.
When and if the
time comes, we will
gather the strength of
the Hidden Leaf Village
and fight if we must.
-Was I wrong?
-Don't you even think of
telling them about this mark.
-Should I have stopped
him by force if I had to?
What?
No visitors?
NURSE: I'm afraid not.
Sorry.
-But why?
He's not in critical
condition or something is he?
Why can't he have any visitors?
NURSE: I'm sorry.
I'm afraid I really don't
have any more information.
-Well, standing here worrying
isn't going to do any good.
That's right.
I should bring flowers.
Let's see now.
Oh, no.
-Oh, Sakura, you poor thing.
It's sad when a girl has
to buy flowers for herself.
-I'm not.
I'm uh-- not that it's
any of your business.
I didn't expect to find
you minding the shop.
I'll make this quick.
-Taking a planter
to the hospital
is like saying you expect the
person to be there forever.
Some cut flowers might
be a better idea.
-Hospital?
What do you mean?
-Don't play dumb with me.
You're going there to
visit Sasuke, aren't you?
Hey, mom, I'm going
out for a while.
-Wait.
What are you doing?
-Get real.
If you think I'm going to
let you be the first one
to get in to see Sasuke,
you are so wrong.
-Miss Ino-Pig,
always butting in.
-I think I'll bring
him one red rose.
It's the flower of love.
-Ha.
How lame can you get?
Me, I'm going to bring
him a single daffodil.
A noble flower that bravely
endures the long months
of winter then blossoms
forth as a sign of spring.
Just like you will soon
blossom again, Sasuke.
-What are you, a
botanist all of a sudden?
-I warned you.
I will not lose out to you.
-Whatever.
So are you going to
pay for that daffodil?
-I should get two.
-Two?
Why?
Are you trying to impress him?
-One for him and
another for Lee.
CHOJI: Waiter, more.
Ten orders of short ribs.
SHIKAMARU: Man, you could
put me off of food for good.
Just watching her makes me sick.
-So, did you order
the short ribs?
-Ah, finally.
This is all mine Shikamaru.
Don't try stealing any.
-Don't worry.
I wasn't planning on it.
-Oh, this is good.
INO: What the heck
are you guys doing?
-Ino?
Sakura.
-Shikamaru, shouldn't
you be training
for the final exam instead of
sitting around pigging out?
-I have been training.
Every day all day.
[? hasem ?] was a
goddamned slave driver.
-And it's not only Shikamaru.
Choji's joined us
for training as well.
-What?
So you're going for
it after all, huh?
-Mm-hm.
Yeah.
And in return I get all
the barbecue I can eat.
-Well, that would explain it.
-Oh, man.
I wish I'd never signed up
for this stupid final exam.
-I don't want to hear it.
There are plenty
of people who would
give their right arm
to be a part of it.
-Yeah, your sensei's right.
-And besides, from
everything I've heard,
Guy and Kurenai's teams are
training their butts off.
-Yeah?
Well, what about it?
-After coming this
far, you don't
want them making you
look bad, do you?
-Man, this is such a drag.
-I can't keep this up.
No human being could.
-Think I've used too
much of my chakra.
-Oh, Neji, are you all right?
NARUTO: Summoning jutsu.
-Again with the tadpoles.
This is ridiculous.
We're not getting anywhere.
-Look, can't you see it?
This one's bigger
than that last one.
PURVY SAGE: Who cares?
It's still a tadpole.
NURSE: So you're here
to see Sasuke Uchiha?
Please keep in mind that
he's still very weak.
He needs his rest.
You'll have to keep
your visit short.
Five minutes, that's
all I can give you.
-All right.
NURSE: Sasuke?
May I come in?
You have a couple of
pretty visitors here.
Oh.
-Sasuke?
-All of his clothes are gone.
This is terrible.
He's in no condition to be
walking around on his own.
Doctor, doctor.
-Oh, Sasuke.
-Did he?
-At some point he will come
to me in search of power.
-Oh, Sasuke, where
have you gone?
-Why is this so much
harder than it used to be?
Must be getting out of shape.
Time's almost up.
Open.
Huh?
-What's up?
-So you finally showed up.
-Oh, man.
-Well, we'll keep on searching
for him here in the hospital.
But in the meantime,
if you see him,
please contact us immediately.
Will you?
-Yes, of course.
-Now, you wanted to see
Rock Lee as well, right?
INO AND SAKURA: Yes.
-He's in no better
condition than Sasuke so
don't expect to have
a very long visit.
NURSE: Lee, can we come in?
You have a couple of
pretty visitors here.
Oh, no.
Not Lee, too.
Lee?
-Weird.
-Huh?
Look.
-Lee.
-Come on, Sakura.
SAKURA: Right.
-200 push ups.
That was the deal.
If you cannot finish them,
it is 100 leg squats.
So come on, here we go.
190.
-Lee, you shouldn't
be out of bed.
Stop it.
What do you think you're doing?
-191.
-Lee.
-Keep away from me.
Please.
I've got to finish my training.
-I should get two.
INO: Two?
Why?
Are you trying to impress him?
-One for him and
another for Lee.
-Sakura?
Speaking of Lee, you heard the
news about him, didn't you?
-Huh?
What news is that?
-His injuries were bad.
Really bad.
It means that
he'll never-- well,
his days as a ninja are over.
-195.
196.
197.
198.
Do not count me out.
I am not through yet.
-You're right.
All the effort is pointless if
you don't believe in yourself.
-199.
Just one more.
One more.
-Lee.
-Oh, no.
-I'll get some orderlies
out here with a stretcher.
Stay with him until I get back.
-We will, ma'am.
-Why?
Why, Ino?
-Huh?
-What is it that
makes boys like that?
They're always pushing
things too far.
-Why ask me?
I'm not a boy.
-Right.
Sorry.
-Human boulder.
-Shadow position, jutsu.
No way.
Haven't got enough chakra.
-What's wrong, Shikamaru?
Don't tell me you've
run out of gas.
-This is such a drag.
-All right, Choji.
Same thing again.
-Someone was here.
-What a waste of a
perfectly good rose.
-Yeah.
My daffodil, too.
-What a bore.
It's obvious our friends
in the swimming suits
aren't coming back so how
about we call it a day.
Huh, Naruto?
-But you're supposed
to be training me.
Come on, please?
One more time, OK?
-I'm tired.
And I'm hungry.
That's enough.
We've been out here half a day.
-But you haven't done anything.
-You little squirt.
You should be grateful I'm
even hanging out with you.
-Yikes.
Man, this old coot's touchy.
OK.
Wait, I know what you need.
Sexy jutsu.
-Wait.
That's it?
That wasn't very long.
-Hey, I've already got
that jutsu down, OK?
It's the summoning
jutsu I want to work on.
-OK.
OK.
Go ahead.
Give it another shot.
-Right.
Here we go.
Summoning jutsu.
Victory.
-Hopeless.
Why do I waste my time with you?
-What?
Are you blind?
-Huh?
-You see?
This one's got legs.
-Great.
Now just give it two arms and a
brain and maybe I can train it.
-Why do you have
to be so negative?
You gotta admit, at least
I'm making progress.
[theme music]
-Ichiraku's ramen
is as good as ever.
Hey, Purvy Sage, this
is my kind of training.
-That's right kid.
Eat up.
I want you to enjoy this
meal as if it were your last.
-Huh?
PURVY SAGE: Oh, nothing.
So anything else you want?
NARUTO: Well, I wouldn't
mind another bowl of ramen.
PURVY SAGE: Just name it.
Anything at all.
You deserve it.
NARUTO: Next time.
Live or die.
Risk it all to win it all.
Wait, did he say something
about this being my last meal?
[theme music]