[music playing]
-It's time to begin.
I am Ibiki Morino, your proctor.
And from this moment,
your worst enemy.
First, you candidates from the
village hidden in the sound,
knock it off.
Who told you you could fight?
You want to be failed
before we've even begun?
-Sorry.
It's our first time.
Guess we're a little jumpy, sir.
-I'll say this
once, so listen up.
There will be no combat
between candidates.
No attacking each other without
the permission of your proctor.
And even then, the use of fatal
force is strictly prohibited.
Anyone who even thinks
of messing with me
will be disqualified
immediately.
Got it?
-No fatal force?
That's no fun.
-Now, if we're
ready, we'll proceed
to the first stage
of the Chunin exam.
Hand over your paperwork.
In return, You'll each
be given a number.
This number determines
where you will sit.
We'll start the written
test once you're all seated.
-The what?
Did he say written?
No!
Not a written test!
No way!
NARUTO UZUMAKI:
Start your engines.
The Chunin exam begins.
-I don't even know where
the others are sitting.
I'm all alone.
This is already a disaster.
-Tough luck for Naruto.
Written exams are definitely
not his strong point.
-Naruto?
-Oh.
Where'd you come from, Hinata?
I didn't see you.
-I wanted to say good
luck and everything.
-Thanks.
Whoa, that's weird.
I didn't even notice her.
Even when she's there,
it's like she's not there.
-Everyone, eyes front.
There are a few rules
you need to be aware of.
And I won't answer
any questions.
So you better pay attention
the first time around.
-No questions?
What kind of rules are these?
-All right.
Rule number one is this.
The written part of the exam is
conducted on a point reduction
system.
Contrary to what some
of you may be used to,
you'll all begin the test with
a perfect score of 10 points.
One point will be deducted
for each answer you get wrong.
So if you miss three, your
final score will be seven.
-And if I miss 10, my
final score will be zero.
-Rule number two.
Teams will pass or fail based
on the total scores of all three members.
-What?
Wait a second.
You're saying we all
get scored as a team?
-Silence!
I have my reasons, so
shut up and listen.
-Reasons?
-Rule number three.
The sentinels you see
positioned around the room
are there to watch you carefully
for any signs of cheating.
And for every
incident they spot,
they will subtract two points
from the culprit's score.
-What?
-Be warned Their eyes
are extremely sharp.
And if they catch
you five times,
you'll be dismissed before
the tests are even scored.
-Sheesh.
They make it so
there's all sorts
of ways you can lose points.
-Anyone fool enough to be
caught cheating by the sentinels
doesn't deserve to be here.
-I've got my eye on you, guys.
-If you want to be
considered Shinobi,
then show us what exceptional
Shinobi you can be.
-OK, OK, relax.
I know I'll do all right.
And Sasuke should be fine.
So even if Naruto gets a
zero, if we do well enough,
we should survive this.
-One more thing.
If any candidate should get
a zero and fail the test,
then the entire team fails.
-What'd he say?
-They're gonna kill me.
-Naruto?
-The final question won't be
given out until 15 minutes
before the end of
the testing period.
You'll have one hour total.
Begin!
-OK.
Focus, Sakura, focus.
This is where you
show your stuff.
Just don't blow it, Naruto.
Get at least one of them right.
-Oh, man.
This doesn't look good.
He's just sitting there.
He's going to choke.
-What am I worried about?
It's just a test.
I've done a lot harder things.
Believe it.
All I've got to do is just
relax and take my time.
Just read through
all the questions
and find the ones I have
a chance of answering.
No pressure.
OK.
Number one.
Oh, I see.
I've got to decipher a code.
OK.
Forget that one.
What's next?
-Line B in the diagram
indicates the trajectory
of a Shuriken thrown at
Enemy C by Ninja A seated
atop a tree seven meters tall.
Describe and formulate
the trajectory required
if C were positioned at
points D, E, and F. Also
predict the farthest possible
range of the Shuriken
and explain how you
arrived at your answer.
-These are integrated
problems based
on principles of
uncertainty and requiring
complex mechanical
energy analysis.
Incredibly advanced stuff.
Naruto doesn't have a hope
in hell of solving these.
In fact, there can't be more
than a handful of people
here besides me who
even understand it.
-OK, skip that one.
Next.
-Each problem is more
difficult than the one before.
-Well, that's interesting.
I can't begin to understand a
single one of these problems.
-Forget it.
This is hopeless.
What am I going to do?
What'll I do?
-I need a high score if
we're going to have a chance.
This is so hard.
I'm almost tempted to--
no, I can't do that.
It's almost like they're
trying to get us to cheat.
I just hope Naruto and
Sasuke don't fall for it.
No they wouldn't.
No way.
Not even Naruto is that
much of a dumb bell.
Right?
-OK, don't panic.
Don't panic.
There's only one thing to do.
I just have to cheat
and not get caught.
Yeah, right.
And risk getting thrown
out of my [inaudible]?
I can't do that.
-It's strange.
They make more of a
fuss about cheating
than they do about
the test itself.
These sentinels
watching our every move,
trying to catch one of--
somebody just got nailed.
That's another thing.
Why only a two-point deduction?
Doesn't make sense.
Ordinarily, if someone's
caught cheating even once,
that's grounds for
dismissal right there.
-Anyone fool enough
to let himself
be caught cheating
by the sentinels
doesn't deserve to be here.
Show us what exceptional
Shinobi you can be.
-So that's it.
Yeah.
That's gotta be it.
This is about more
than the written exam.
The real aim is not
to test our knowledge,
but our ability to
gather information.
Yeah.
That explains everything.
The eagle-eyed
sentinels everywhere,
these incredibly
difficult questions,
the fact that only
two points are
deducted from each
incident of cheating.
Very clever.
A ninja must see
through deception.
He's not actually
forbidding us from cheating,
he's expecting us to.
He's daring us to try and
cheat and not get caught.
Only exceptional Shinobi
could get away with it
under these circumstances.
And that's just what
he's looking for.
I wonder how many
of the others have
realized that's what
test is all about?
Come on, Naruto.
You can figure it out.
Use your head before
it's too late.
Use your head.
-This is bad.
This is bad.
-OK.
So if the real test
here is finding a way
to steal the answers
without getting caught,
the next question is to figure
out who's got all the answers.
Looks like Gaara's
figured it out.
OK, Crow.
I'm counting on you.
Good boy.
Yeah, that'll do it.
OK.
Now for number four.
-Judging from the rhythm, the
duration, and the frequency
of the strokes-- yes, I see.
Well, show me.
Eight, of course.
-Lee, when you can see
it, adjust your head band.
-Tick, tick, tick.
Oh, man, they couldn't
have a digital clock?
Time's running out.
That does it.
I've got no choice.
I've got to cheat.
Hang on, I can't do that.
What if I get caught?
What are Sakura and
Sasuke going to think?
On the other hand, if I
don't get any of these right,
I'm sunk, and I take
them down with me.
Either way, I'm dead meat.
-Naruto.
-If you want, I could--
I could show you my test.
-Say what?
She'd let me look at her test?
Why would she want to do that?
Unless, of course, it's
some kind of trick.
Yeah.
I bet that's-- no.
What am I thinking?
No way.
Hinata's not like that.
But she could have been
forced into tricking me
by Kiba and the others.
I wouldn't put it past them.
-Hey, Hinata, can I
ask you something?
Why would you want to
show me your answers?
-Why?
Well, just because--
well, you see,
it's just-- it's because I
don't want you to have to leave.
Well, it'd be nice if we
could all stick together.
I mean, the nine of us,
being rookies and all.
-That makes sense, I suppose.
I thought you were trying
to pull a fast one there.
Sorry.
This is my lucky day.
I mean, what are the
chances of sitting
next to someone who wants
you to cheat off of her?
Whoa, how did they know?
I hadn't even done anything yet.
-What the?
What was that all about?
-Five strikes and you're out.
You just failed the test.
-What?
It can't be.
-You and your teammates will
leave the room immediately.
-Candidate number 23, fail.
Number 27 and 43, failed.
-It's not fair!
I didn't do anything!
-No.
No way!
Who says I cheated five times?
Where's your proof?
How can you keep
track of all of us?
You got the wrong guy.
How do you know I wasn't just--
-Sorry, pal.
We were chosen for this duty
because we don't make mistakes
like that.
You can't even blink
without us seeing it.
We're the best of the best.
And you, my friend, are history.
Now get out.
And take your
teammates with you.
-Psst, Naruto.
Go ahead, look.
-Huh?
Thank you.
I appreciate it, but no.
Hey, I'm an ace ninja.
I don't need to
cheat to pass this.
-Well, OK.
But are you sure?
-Yeah.
Besides, if I got
caught or anything,
I wouldn't want you
getting into trouble.
-He cares!
Yes, you're right.
Stupid idea.
I'm sorry.
-Nah, forget about it.
Yeah, right.
I ought to have
my head examined.
When the heck did
I get so noble?
-Sharingan!
I'll try imitating the
movements of his pen.
Bingo.
I hit the jackpot with this guy.
-Look at her.
She's cranking
through this thing.
OK, Sakura, I
concede that you've
got a brain behind that
oversized forehead of yours.
Now I think I'll put
it to work for me.
You ought to be flattered, girl.
I don't hit just anyone with
my my Mind Transfer Jutsu.
-So, Ino's got her
Jutsu working, I see.
About time.
Way to go, putting that
brainiac to work for us.
-Thanks, Sakura, for
letting me hang out
in your soul for a bit.
Even if it is a little
cramped in here.
Now I've got to memorize
these answers quick
so I can pass them on
to Chogi and Shikamaru.
-Number 59, you fail.
Numbers 33 and nine, fail.
-That's the 13th
team to be dismissed.
-Number 41, fail.
-Numbers 35 and 62, fail.
-Hey, no way!
-Look at this one.
Cool as a cucumber.
Stays focused as if
nothing was happening.
Not bad for a novice.
-The opening of the third eye.
Invisibly linked
to the optic nerve.
-Ow.
Damn!
Something in my eye.
-Excuse me.
-What is it?
-Gotta use the can.
Sorry.
-We go with you to make sure
you're not up to anything.
-That's perfectly
understandable.
-Security is pretty
tight around here.
But these sentinels
aren't quite as eagle-eyed
as everybody thinks.
After all, they
haven't even noticed
that there's one more sentinel
than there used to be.
Right, Crow?
-Only 20 minutes left
and I haven't done squat.
I'm so busted.
Unless-- in five
minutes, they'll
give out the tenth question.
So that's what it comes down to.
Everything's riding on that.
Believe it!
[music playing]
-It's hopeless!
I'll never be a Chunin!
My teammates are
going to kill me!
I'll be the oldest living Genin.
What made me think I could
answer the final problem?
This is bad.
I should have cheated
when I had the chance.
NAURTO UZUKAMI: Next
time, the tenth question.