[theme music]
NARUTO: Assassin of
the Moonlight Night.
This, this guy.
Sasuke?
PAKKUN (VOICEOVER): Looks
like we were too late.
-Those two.
-What are you doing here?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): He's
losing control again,
just like before.
Sasuke, hold on.
(VOICEOVER) Kakashi
sensei said that bruise
was nothing to worry about!
-Hey, uh, Sakura.
Earth to Sakura.
-What do you want?
-This guy over here,
who the hell is he?
-His outward appearance
may be different,
but he's the one
you know as Gara.
-My father used
Ninjutsu to ensure
I'd be the strongest of
Shinobi, infusing my unborn self
with a sand spirit.
And as a result, I
destroyed the life
of a woman who gave birth to me.
I was born a monster.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): This is
what he was talking about.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
He did this to Sasuke.
-Hey, little girl.
-Hmm?
-I guess now would be
the time to tell you
I'm not the fighting type.
-I can see that
by looking at you!
(VOICEOVER) In any case,
we have to get out of here
and get Sasuke back
to Kakashi sensei.
-What do you want?
SAKURA: Sasuke.
-So, it looks like you're
good for two bursts-- that's
about your limit.
A third would be impossible.
And remember this, if you try to
force a jutsu, not only will it
not work, but the
attempt can drain
your chakra to absolute zero.
Worst case scenario-- you die.
Even if the worst
doesn't happen,
nothing good can come of
it, trust me-- especially
in your case.
-Because of the curse?
-If you let your hate
consume you, and rely
on the power of
that of curse mark,
your development
will end right here.
If that happens, you
will never beat Itachi.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): I have
to get this under control.
-Sasuke.
-So, it's you.
You're the one I
didn't kill that day.
I live solely for myself.
I love only myself.
As long as there are still
people to kill in this world,
I will never disappear.
-Guys, get up, we
have to go now!
-Die, Sasuke Uchiha!
-Sakura, no!
-Move it!
-[groan]
-Sakura!
-That girl must be out of
her mind facing Gaara now.
-Damn it, damn!
What are we supposed to do now?
We're screwed!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I don't
know if I can handle this guy.
GARA (VOICEOVER): Now
let me feel alive!
Why can't I?
-No Gara, you can't do this!
-It doesn't matter what I do.
The sand just gets in the way.
-Gaara?
-Yashamaru.
As a member of the
Medical Corps, our leader,
Lord Kazekaje.
Has asked that I
see to your safety
and well being personally.
Please, Gaara, it hurts
me to see you do that.
Although I suppose that the
sand would protect you anyway.
-Yashamaru, sorry.
-What, this?
Don't worry.
It's a barely more
than a scratch.
-The wound you
got, does it hurt?
-Yes, a little bit.
But it'll heal in no time.
-Yashamaru?
-What's the matter?
-What does pain feel like?
-Hmm?
-You see, I've never
actually been injured before.
And I was wondering
what it was like.
-Hmm, how can I put it?
It's very difficult, or maybe
upsetting is what I mean.
It's like when someone
is struck, or cut,
it's a feeling that's
very hard to take.
When you're hurt, you
don't feel normal.
I'm not explaining it very well.
Basically, it's a
situation you want
to avoid if at all possible.
-Yashamaru?
-Yes.
-Do you not like me, Yashamaru?
Like the others?
-Everyone goes
through their lives
hurting others and being hurt.
But it's not so easy for
us to hate one another.
--Thanks a lot, Yashamaru.
That helped.
I think I kind of
understand what pain is now.
-I see.
Huh?
-I think I might be hurting
too, just like everyone else.
I'm always in pain.
I know I'm not bleeding.
But lately I've felt
a lot of pain here.
-Wound your body,
and the blood will
flow, following fast
on the heels of pain.
But as time passes, the
pain eventually fades away.
With the help of medicine,
it can heal even faster.
But even more dangerous is
a wound dealt to the heart
because there's nothing that
has more trouble healing.
-A wound to the heart?
-Wounds to the
heart are a little
different from
wounds to the flesh.
Unlike an injury
to the body, there
is no medicine
for wounded heart.
And sometimes it never heals.
But don't worry.
There is one thing that
can mend a broken heart.
But it's a very
complicated remedy.
It can only be administered
to you by another person.
-So then what am
I supposed to do?
There's one thing that can
heal the heart-- only one.
It's love, Gaara.
-Love?
-You've got it.
But how am I supposed
to get rid of it?
What is it I have to do
to get rid of this pain?
-Don't you know, Gaara?
It has already
been given to you.
Love is a heart's desire to
serve someone precious to you,
to watch over them,
to care for them--
like my sister did for you.
There's no question that my
older sister always loved you.
Shukaku, the Sand
Spirit, is living
soul bent towards
the purpose of war.
The sand automatically
rushes to protect you,
just like the love of a mother.
I believe your mother's
will is carried
in every grain of that sand.
My sister, even after death,
wants more than anything
to protect you.
-Yashamaru?
-What is it, Gaara?
-Thank you for all of your help.
You know, for
stopping me before.
-You're very welcome.
After all, you're special Gaara.
I hold you very dear to me.
-(VOICEOVER) Can you understand
the pain that I feel?
GAARA (VOICEOVER):
It tastes like iron.
[groaning in pain]
-[groaning in pain]
[screaming]
-Ha!
Ha!
Twang!
21!
[inaudible] Yeah!
Kakashi, how did you take down?
-22.
-Looks like I win
another round, old buddy.
That last one l knocked
off was my 23rd.
-Yeah, yeah, all right.
-I love that too cool for
school attitude of yours.
That's why you're
my number one rival.
-Let's go.
-All right.
-[groaning in pain]
-Hey, Yashamaru, I
have a favor to ask.
-What is it?
-I need some of your medicine.
Sorry about earlier.
I know it must have hurt.
I brought you some
medicine, if you want.
-Get out here, freak!
--[drunken singing] What the,
watch where you're going,
little brat?
You're-- you're that kid!
GAARA (VOICEOVER): Again?
-Get out of here, freak.
GAARA (VOICEOVER): Those eyes.
-You're that kid.
-Why, why?
-Hey, look, [scream].
-What's going on?
-It's Gaara!
-Hey this guy is dead!
GAARA (VOICEOVER): Father.
I was right.
No one wants me.
Why, why do I have
to be such a freak?
What am I?
-Only one thing cures a wounded
heart, and that's love, Gaara.
-[weeping] Yashamaru?
GAARA (VOICEOVER): What?
Why?
Why me?
Why is it always me?
Who are you?
What do you want?
-You did well, Gaara.
You did very well.
-Yashamaru!
[screams]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Those eyes.
-What's the matter.
Aren't you about to
make a run for it?
-Sasuke.
Naruto.
-Who are these two?
Who are they to you?
-Who are they to me?
They are my friends,
is who they are.
You trying laying so
much as another finger
on the two of them, and
I will pulverise you.
-[scream]
-What's the matter?
Weren't you going
to pulverise me?
Well, come on then.
[inaudible]
[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I
know what kind of strength
this guy possesses.
And I know he sees
me as nothing more
than some brainless weakling.
But still, what's this feeling
that's boiling up inside me.
I'm not sure.
All I do know is
that I'm not going
to lose to this
guy, no matter what!
Next time, Light versus
Dark, The Two Faces of Gaara.