[theme music]
HINATA: "Blaze Away, Byakugan!
This is My Ninja Way!"
-Kiba.
-Naruto.
Well, this is bad.
-Ha, ha, ha.
What's the matter?
Something wrong?
Don't you want to
become larvae food?
-Really bad.
[laughing]
-You honestly
expect that to work?
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
Focus my chakra.
Byakugan.
It's no good.
I can't break free in time.
Naruto.
-Not a chance, pal.
There's no way I'm giving up.
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
That's right.
I know that no matter
what the situation
is, Naruto would never give up.
He doesn't quit.
-So did you take care of them?
-What a bunch of idiots,
provoking her like that.
JIBACHI: Look at them,
trapped in beeswax.
Bees makes sticky wax.
Aren't you supposed to
be an insect handler,
and you didn't know that?
-Yeah, what gives?
Aren't you some
sort of bug expert?
SUZUMEBACHI: So what
about the bikochu?
KUROBACHI: Nothing so far.
We fanned out and
canvassed the area,
but we haven't found it yet.
-Maybe these kids are
carrying it with them.
-Even they wouldn't
be that stupid.
-I guess that means--
-We'll have to squeeze
the information out
of one of our new friends.
-None of us would ever tell you.
SHINO: I'll tell you.
-Shino.
-On one condition.
You give us Hinata.
SUZUMEBACHI: Ridiculous.
Trying to bargain with us?
JIBACHI: [laughs]
Maybe you don't
understand the
position you're in.
SHINO: There is no
way you will ever
find the bikochu on your own.
And I believe your
pressed for time.
Perhaps, you don't
understand your position.
JIBACHI: What should we do?
SUZUMEBACHI: At this rate
the bikochu will hatch
and then it'll be useless.
KUROBACHI: If that happens,
our mission is a failure.
-Yes, but if we can get rid of
even one of the Aburame clan.
-Hinata.
-Are you worried?
-Of course, I am.
-She's strong, you know.
Hinata, much stronger
than you think.
-All right then, we
agree to your offer.
-We want to see
our friend first.
-Huh?
-Ah.
SUZUMEBACHI: What happened?
-That brat.
She's gone, but the wax
cocoon she was trapped in
isn't there either.
The current.
It might have swept her
toward the waterfall.
SUZUMEBACHI: Jibachi.
JIBACHI: This isn't my fault.
I warned her.
I said not to move one
inch or she would die.
-How could you?
What have you done?
What did you do to Hinata?
If she gets hurt, I swear I'll--
-You little twerp.
Shut up.
Your friend's probably at the
bottom of the river by now
anyway.
-How dare you?
-Aw, he's so upset.
The brat must be his girlfriend.
-You monster.
When I get my hands on
you, you'll be sorry.
-You're joking, right?
What could you possibly do
to me all wrapped up like?
-You can forget our deal.
Without Hinata, we'll never
tell you where the bikochu is.
-The girl's death might not
have been part of our plan,
but it's not a complete loss.
In fact, it may be a good thing.
Because you see now we
get to avenge our clan
and take your lives.
Members of the
Hidden Leaf Village
have always been the enemies
of our Hidden Stone Village.
Killing you would be natural.
What's it going to be?
Do you want us to kill you?
Or perhaps, you'd rather
tell me where the bikochu is
and end this game?
If you talk, we may
spare your lives.
-Fine, you win.
NARUTO: Shino, don't you
dare tell them anything.
They can't do anything
to us because I'm
going to tear them
limb from limb.
-Keep your mouth shut, you brat!
Ah!
-Jibachi.
-No!
-Just shut up.
I'm going to get this kid.
-Paper bomb!
JIBACHI: She's--
-Wait, she's alive?
-But how?
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
That was really close,
but I didn't give up, did I?
Just like Naruto.
-No way.
No one can escape
from the beeswax.
-These are no ordinary genin.
-Ow.
-Don't worry.
I can handle it.
-Hinata.
HINATA (VOICEOVER): I've never
used it in an actual fight.
But I'm going to
have to use it here.
-Bee bomb jutsu!
-1,000 stingers jutsu.
-Ninja [inaudible] honey jutsu.
HINATA (VOICEOVER): Naruto.
Naruto, watch me.
-Protective eight
trigrams 64 palms!
-No freaking way.
That jutsu.
Hinata can really do that?
-The Hinata that you
know is from long ago.
-What are you talking about?
-It's been a while
since the Chunin exam.
You've learned many
new jutsu since then.
While in that time, Hinata
has been developing as well.
She's been training
especially hard.
-Yahoo!
Go for it, Akamaru.
-It's nice.
You three.
You all have something special
you enjoy and you're good at.
SHINO: You should find
something like that.
-Yeah, I guess you're right.
-By the way, what's up?
You wanted to tell
me something, right?
-Yeah.
I wanted you to help me train.
SHINO: Hinata was so concerned
about her purpose as a ninja.
She wanted to be able to
offer something unique.
-Hinata!
Hey, maybe we should slow d--
-Don't go easy on me.
If you really want to help
me get better at this,
then come at me full force.
-OK.
SHINO: After months
of harsh training,
Hinata discovered her own style
and her own special jutsu.
What you're seeing is the
result of that training.
[cracking]
-Huh?
Huh?
How'd you--
-I'll let you in
on a little secret.
Angering the queen bee,
getting caught in that wax,
it was all part of my plan.
-What?
-With my chakra depleted
and my weakened state,
it was the only thing I could do
to survive and protect myself.
Besides, what do you
think I was doing
while we were all wrapped up?
Just sitting there?
No, I was directing my bugs.
Turns out, this wax is
actually quite weak.
-All right.
-Because of her hard training,
Hinata's chakra control
has improved dramatically.
And you just saw the jutsu
she's created and perfected,
protective eight
trigram 64 palms.
Hinata took her
superior flexibility
and combined it with
fine-toothed chakra control
to fend off attacks from
all directions at once.
It's the ultimate defense jutsu.
But it's different
from Neji's technique.
It's Hinata's own jutsu.
She pushed herself hard, and
it finally paid off for her.
Through it all, she wanted to
win the respect of her father,
the respect of her
fellow shinobi,
and especially the
respect of you, Naruto.
-None of our jutsus
are having any affect.
-How is she doing that?
-That girl is unreal.
How did they get out?
JIBACHI: And when?
-Summoning jutsu.
Get rid of them Queen Bee.
-Ah!
-No, Hinata.
Shino.
SHINO: Wait.
Have faith in her.
HINATA (VOICEOVER): With chakra.
It must be chakra.
Stronger.
Bigger.
More nimble.
Focus.
Focus!
-No.
-Hinata.
I got you.
-Naruto.
I--
-You're amazing.
That was an awesome jutsu.
You did it.
You totally saved us.
-Naruto.
SHINO: Let's move.
It'll be dawn soon.
NEJI: Right.
NARUTO: OK.
-Wow, it's becoming a pupa.
-Now, all we got to do is
make it smell Sasuke's scent
the moment it hatches, and
then our mission is complete.
-Yeah.
Sasuke, I'm coming, pal.
-Fool.
So it was in the tree.
I don't understand.
My bees would have
found it there easily.
-How are you even alive?
-We hid it in a cage coated
with a secret Aburame
family insect repellent.
-What?
No.
-The repellent kept your
bees at a safe distance.
As long as you were
using bees to search,
you had no chance of finding it.
-I should have known.
Your clan always
stands in our way.
As long as your
family exists, mine
will be destined for
failure and ruin.
No more.
I must avenge the
people of my clan.
I can't let you succeed, even
if it kills me and the bikochu.
-Shadow clone jutsu.
The beetle is our last chance.
It's our only hope of
getting our friend back.
That's why you can't stop us.
-Shut up!
Rasengan!
-Hey, look.
She's hatching.
-All right.
Huh?
-You just had the
headband a second ago.
-Quick.
Search for it, everyone.
-Byakugan.
Naruto.
-Huh?
-Over there.
-Aw, man, you must
have sent it flying
when you used your Rasengan.
-Get it.
-What's it look like I'm doing?
Come on.
Gotta reach it.
-She's going to hatch.
[grunting]
-Ah!
-I got it.
Hurry, make it sniff
this so I can-- Wah!
Aw, no way.
That smell doesn't count.
Come on, sniff
Sasuke's headband.
SHINO: It's over.
-Hey, get back here.
-Ah.
-So you failed the mission
because you did what?
You're gonna pay for this.
-I didn't do it on purpose.
I swear.
-Where did he go?
Hey, isn't that-- it is.
That's a bikochu.
Naruto!
Hi-ya!
-Come on, can't you
forgive me, Sakura?
-No.
I'll never forgive you for this.
-Don't kill me.
It's not my fault.
I swear it's a natural function.
-Ha, so the mission failed.
-It seems they succeeded
at finding the bikochu,
but couldn't train it to track
the scent of Sasuke Uchiha.
-I see.
Hinata must feel so
terrible right now.
After all, the whole
strategy was her idea
from the beginning.
-Actually, I don't think
she's feeling too bad.
-Hm?
-Well, Hinata, I heard that
your mission was a failure.
-Yes, it was a complete failure.
But that only means I only
train more and work even harder
next time.
-Oh, I see.
Well, good luck.
HINATA (VOICEOVER): Focus.
Focus.
[theme music]
NARUTO: Huh?
Why you sending me on
such an easy mission?
TSUNADE: I don't
want to hear it.
You're the one who picked up
this client in the first place.
NARUTO: That's
not a good reason.
Besides, I'm busy
with important stuff.
TSUNADE: Enough.
Do it or I'll send you
back to the Academy.
NARUTO: Hey, that's no fair.
TSUNADE: No arguments.
Neji, Tenten, Lee, Naruto,
I'm sending the four of you
on a brand new mission.
NARUTO: Next time, "Funeral
March of the Living."