[theme music]
[singing in japanese]
GAARA: Are you shocked
by my true form?
Come out, come
out, Sasuke Uchiha.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Sasuke's
decision, pushed to the edge!
-So there you are.
-Guess again.
-Here, you can have them back.
Only a clone.
-This guy's a freak.
What's wrong, Sasuke Uchiha?
Why do you run and hide?
Why don't you attack?
[screaming in pain] Why
do you always run away?
-Yeah, good kick.
-Yeah, it's to me.
-No, it's to me.
-Yeah, get it.
-Come on, you can do it.
Get it.
-That was awesome.
-Pass it, pass it.
-Get in there, come on.
-Here we go man.
-Here we go, come
on, we're real close.
-Look, look, he's open
you've got a chance.
Come on, come on,
shoot it, come on.
-Corner shot!
-Oh man now what do we do?
I don't know any
wall-climbing jutsu, do you?
Huh?
It's him.
-Here.
-It's that Gaara.
He's really creepy.
Run!
-Hurry!
-Let's get out of here!
-No, wait, don't run away.
-Help me!
-Something's got a hold of me.
GAARA (VOICEOVER): Please, I
don't want to be alone anymore.
-Ah, let me go!
GAARA (VOICEOVER): Never again.
-Stop it, please!
-No, Gaara, you can't do this.
-Yashamaru.
I won't let you get away.
You can't escape, do you hear?
Sasuke Uchiha.
[laughing manically]
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
This is unreal.
His strength is off the charts.
-What's wrong?
You're not afraid
of me, are you?
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
If this comes down
to physical strength, forget it.
-Yes, that's it.
You fear me.
Don't you, Uchiha?
You live in fear
every day I'm alive!
Never forget-- you are my prey.
-Hold on.
Why me?
Why are you so fixated on me?
-I see in your eyes you
know what loneliness is.
True loneliness.
You understand that it
is the most painful form
of suffering that
there is in the world.
As I said before, we
have the same eyes--
eyes with a hunger for power,
full of hate-- the same as me.
Eyes that seek revenge against
those who made you so lonely.
Eyes that burn to
see them all dead.
It's all in your eyes.
-OK, hang on a minute here.
So you're the one called Gaara.
Seems you can read a
lot in Sasuke's eyes.
Be careful-- you may
not be able to read him
as well as you think.
If there's something you wanted
say before the final rounds,
go ahead and spit it out.
When we finally
fight, it won't be
to advance to the
next stage, but solely
for survival-- one seeking
to destroy the other.
Only the last one
standing will feel
the full value of his existence.
-You're not talking
about a match.
You're talking about some kind
of grudge bout to the death.
It's crazy.
-Uchiha, in the depths of your
soul-- it's what you want,
too, isn't it?
You want to confirm the value
of your existence, don't you?
To know if you are truly as
powerful as you think you are.
Whose existence is
stronger-- yours, or the ones
facing you with
murder in his eyes?
What's wrong?
Sasuke Uchiha?
Are you really so afraid of me?
Has all your hatred
and sense of purpose
dwindled down to
this-- abject fear?
Is this the existence you
live now-- that of a coward?
Come out and fight me.
Show me that I'm wrong.
Prove that your existence
is stronger than mine.
You'll never know
unless you fight the.
You'll never feel it!
Attack!
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): He
killed everyone but me.
I was the only one
allowed to live.
For what reason?
I know the reason.
He had to leave one
alive to spare himself
the guilt of having
exterminated an entire clan.
By sparing me, Itachi chose me
to be the avenger of the clan.
He chose me to be
the one to kill him.
-Good.
Now we're going to have
some fun, Sasuke Uchiha!
-With one blow,
I'll finish this.
Hurry up and die, you
withered old buzzard.
Put yourself out of your misery.
-I told you before,
we will both die here.
Fool!
-You'll never do it.
Let it go!
-No, I will not
let go until I've
pulled your wretched
soul from your body.
Not much time--
-[scream]
-Gaara!
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
Looks like it worked.
-[laughing]
-I see.
So that's what it is.
-Amazing.
After all Uchiha
has been through,
he was still able to
counter Gaara's attack.
-Now it's clear
to me exactly why
I've been looking forward
to this, this pain.
What a thrill it will be
to crush such as opponent
capable of wounding me so badly.
Such a victory will make me feel
what it is to be truly alive!
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): No one
has ever wounded Gaara--
and he's done it twice.
He's a freak of
nature, like Gaara.
But this one is a freak
in fiber of his body.
For all Gaara's
strength, it's only
his right arm that's
been transformed.
-There's more, so much more.
-What the--
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): What
the hell is this guy?
How many of these things are
going to grow out of him?
He's even faster.
Only by predicting his moves
do I have any chance of dying.
Without my [inaudible]
I'd be dead already.
Use my Chidori, Fire
style, fireball Jutsu!
-[laugh]
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): It
didn't even slow him down.
This level of Jutsu is useless.
-You're finished.
-It's Chidori, or nothing.
-So, looks like you're
good for two bursts.
That's about your limit.
At this stage of your
chakra development,
you've only got two shots
of Chidori in you per day.
And you weren't
using your Sharingan,
which you would be
in an actual battle.
Sharingon and Chidor are a
potent combination, but costly.
Using them simultaneously burns
up a lot of chakra, and fast.
Don't sweat it.
I'm actually very impressed.
Even for me,
Chidori is a killer.
If I had to use the lightning
blade four times in one day,
I'd be running on empty.
What would happen if I tried
to use it more than twice?
-Well, for one thing,
it wouldn't work.
But remember this-- if you try
to force a Jutsu, not only will
it not work, but the
attempt can drain
your chakra to absolute zero.
Worst case scenario, you die.
Even if the worst
doesn't happen,
nothing good can come of it.
Trust me-- especially
in your case.
-Is that it?
That was the best
demonstration you
could make of the value
of your existence?
That's just pathetic, truly.
Your hatred.
It's weak.
You are far too
soft and forgiving.
The greater the hunger for
revenge, the greater, the hate.
And it's the power of hate that
gives you the strength to kill.
Your hate is weaker
than mine, far weaker.
-Shut up.
-You know what that
means, don't you?
-Just shut up.
-It means you can't win.
You are weaker than I am.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
There's a reason
Itachi let me live, a reason
he chose me to be the one
to track him down and kill him.
I am an avenger!
-[groaning]
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
The curse mark again.
Can't move my body!
-Sasuke!
[theme music]
GAARA (VOICEOVER): Tell me,
Yashamaru, what is pain?
I've never been injured,
so I don't know.
But now, I'm wondering if
this is pain, this feeling.
Am I injured?
I'm not bleeding but there's
a strange feeling here
in my chest, pulsing, like
something bad wants to get out.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next time,
Assassin of the Moonlit Night.