[music playing]
-If qualities of
heaven are your desire,
acquire wisdom to
take your mind higher.
If earthly qualities are what
you lack, train your body
and prepare to attack.
When heaven and earth
are open together,
the perilous path will
become righteous forever.
This something is the secret way
that guides us from this place
today.
-This what?
Or is that a secret, too?
-Anyway, it's about the scrolls.
I think we're supposed to open
and read the heaven and earth
scrolls now.
-OK, here goes nothing.
What?
What does this mean?
-A man, a person?
-Oh, no.
This is a summoning Jutsu.
Naruto, Sakura, quick!
Get rid of the scrolls!
What?
It's you?
-Hey.
Long time no see, huh?
NARUTO UZUMAKI:
Surviving the cut.
The rookie nine together again.
-Iruka Sensei?
-Looks like you've gone
through a lot in this test.
-Hey, wait, what's the deal
with the surprise entrance?
Why are you appearing
with a summoning?
-At the end of the
second exam, we Chunin
are supposed to welcome
the test takers back.
And well, it was
just good luck that I
got to be the one given
the important task of being
the messenger for you guys.
-The messenger?
-And you made it
just in time, too.
And now-- congratulations.
You passed the second exam.
To celebrate your
passing, I would
love to treat you all to
some Ichiraku Ramen, but--
-Ramen?
Seriously?
That's so cool.
-Wait!
I'm not done.
-So cool.
-Let go.
Hey, Naruto.
-Yeah!
Ramen would be awesome!
Especially after all
the bugs and plants
we've had to eat for
the past two days.
So great.
I'm going to eat every
noodle ever made!
-Where does he get
all of his energy?
-Yeah!
-Shut up!
-All right.
Well, I can see you're still
as hyperactive as ever, Naruto.
-Now I see.
So then if we had
looked at the scrolls
in the middle of the
exam-- what would
you have done to
us, Iruka Sensei?
-As usual, Sasuke, you're
as sharp as a tack.
You have figured out the secret.
Part of this exam was
to test how well you
could see a difficult
mission all the way through.
Simply put, you knew
that opening the scrolls
was against the rules
of your mission.
And if you had
tried to open one--
-What?
What would have happened?
-If a scroll was
opened, we were ordered
to knock out whoever opened it.
Some ninja found that
out the hard way.
-It's a good thing you didn't
open up yours, huh Naruto?
-I owe you one.
Thanks a million, Kabuto.
-That was a close one.
-Oh yeah, Sensei.
-Yeah?
-What does that writing
on the wall mean?
The parchment the
letters are written on
is kind of eaten away, so
it's difficult to read it.
We can't understand it.
-Oh, please.
Look, we passed, didn't we?
That stuff doesn't matter now.
-Well, actually, explaining that
is another one of the duties
that I've been sent
here to take care of.
-What, seriously?
-That's right.
It's serious business.
Give it a good read.
They're instructions Lord
Hokage recorded as principles
that Chunin should follow.
-They're instructions?
-Yes.
Heaven stands for your mind
and Earth for your body.
If qualities of heaven
are your desire,
acquire wisdom to
take your mind higher.
Get it?
-Huh-uh.
-All right, I'll explain.
In other words, if your weakness
lies in your intellect--
Naruto-- then you have
to make doubly sure
that you work hard to learn
all the information and skills
that you need to prepare
for your missions.
-OK, I get your point.
-And you.
If earthly qualities you
lack, train your body,
prepare to attack.
So if your weakness lies
in your physical strength,
Sakura, then you
have to make sure
that you work on your physical
conditioning every single day
so it improves all the time.
When heaven and Earth
are open together,
the perilous path will
become righteous forever.
Meaning, if your mind and body
are working together as one,
then even a very dangerous
mission can become an easy one.
-So what about that spot
with the missing letter?
-Well, that part is meant
for all of you to fill in.
Do you see that
symbol on the scroll?
It's the character for person,
a reference to you Chunin.
You see, these five
days or survival
were to test your
abilities as Chunin
and to see if you would
be any good at it.
And I got to say, you guys
really didn't magnificently.
A Chunin is a leader, a guide.
It's a Chunin's responsibility
to be aware of the strengths
and weaknesses of those
serving under him,
and to know what skills
in training those ninja
are going to need in order
to succeed on the mission.
You did an excellent
job on this mission,
and I want you to remember these
instructions on your next one.
Well, that's it.
That was everything I was
supposed to say to you.
-Got it.
-One more thing.
For the third exam,
don't push it too far.
Especially you, Naruto.
-Iruka Sensei, when
I got this head band,
I stopped being a student.
So you need to worry
about me at all.
Not anymore.
I mean, this head
band has proved
that I am a full-fledged
ninja, right?
You gave it to me.
I may still be hyper,
but I'm not a kid.
Like you just said, I got
through the second Chunin exam.
And you watch.
I'm going to pass the
third one for sure.
Right now I'm a ninja, too.
-Naruto, you're right.
I'm sorry about that.
Look, I know their
strengths and weaknesses
better than anyone else does.
Whatever the
result, I want to be
the one who breaks
the news to them.
-Fine.
If you're that hung
up on it, then I'll
just leave that
team in your hands.
But I would have
thought you'd have
a little more confidence
in them, you know?
-Thank you, Anko.
-Wait.
Those guys are Kakashi
students, aren't they?
Listen, if Kakashi's
got faith in them,
then I wouldn't count
them out just yet, Iruka.
-Iruka needs to hear this.
He needs to realize that they're
not his students anymore.
They're mine.
And that's the simple truth.
-[laughs]
-It seems to me now that the
one who truly understands
the strengths and weaknesses
of these young ninja
best might very well
be you, Kakashi.
-How is it?
Does the curse mark
still cause you pain?
-No, not really.
Thanks to you, it's much better.
-That's good.
But we better get
back to business.
This Orochimaru is one of the
Sanni, the legendary three
ninja, isn't he?
He's supposed to be so
incredibly powerful that not
even the Anbu Black Ops
Unit could bring him down.
And I'd heard a
rumor that he died,
but I guess that wasn't true.
-Why did he come to this
village now, anyway?
-He's a very promising prospect.
He's inherited the sublime
abilities of the Uchiha clan.
-That kid.
-He's after Sasuke, right?
-Anko, we've confirmed
that 21 ninja
have finished the second exam.
And as for the third exam,
according to the rules,
we'll have to hold a
round of preliminaries
first-- the first
time in five years.
-Now, for the time
being, we'll just
continue with the
exams as planned.
But I also want to keep an
eye on his movements, as well.
-Yes.
-First of all, congratulations
on finishing the second exam.
There were 78 ninja
who took that exam.
Frankly, I'm surprised
that even 21 passed.
I knew that less than
half would make it,
but I really thought the number
would be in the single digits.
-I'm really hungry.
-What a drag.
There's so many left.
This is such a pain.
-Sasuke and his team
have passed, too.
-Well, of course they did.
After all the trouble we went
through to keep them safe,
they've better have passed.
-I see your team didn't
do too bad, Kakashi.
They must have
gotten real lucky.
Of course, with my team
still around, your team
is doomed to failure.
After all, what matters on
the next test is ability,
and we've you far out-classed.
Well, I guess that
part of growing up
is learning to deal with
heartbreak, huh Kakashi?
-Did you say something?
-All right, Kakashi,
you win this round.
Boy, that drives me nuts
when you act so cool.
There's no way I'm going to
let you get the best of me.
-So that's Guy Sensei's
old rival, huh?
Well, if I had to judge
them on looks alone,
I'd say Guy Sensei would lose.
-Guy Sensei is just the
coolest teacher ever.
I mean, he is so cool, he
practically glows with cool.
You watch, Guy Sensei.
Some day, I'll make
you proud of me.
-I do not want to see tears from
anyone close to me ever again.
That is why I'm never going
to lose again, Guy Sensei.
Never!
As expected, all
the best are here.
Sasuke Uchiha, huh?
I'll get you back for what
you did to me, Sasuke,
no matter what it takes.
-I can't believe it.
Only seven teams
out of 26 are left.
-Sure enough, not a
scratch on me, Gaara.
-Akamaru is acting strange.
-Those Sand Village ninja.
-Naruto passed, too.
Thank goodness.
-Hey, look.
All of the Leaf Village
rookies are here, too.
-Woah, everybody's here.
Old Man Hokage, Iruka
Sensei, and even Bushy Brow.
It looks like absolutely
nobody got left out this time.
-I don't have a very
good feeling about this.
-It's hard to believe that
there are so many left
after the second test.
And so many of them are rookies.
So that's why they fought
so hard to recommend them.
-All right, now pay attention.
Lord Hokage is going to
explain the third exam to you.
You better listen
carefully, maggots.
Lord Hokage, they're all yours.
-First, before I tell you
what the third exam entails,
I want to explain something
about the test itself.
Listen closely now.
It's something that all
of you need to understand.
I'm going to tell you the
true purpose of these exams.
-True purpose?
-Why do you suppose
our country holds
these exams in conjunction
with our allies?
To raise the ability
levels of the Shinobi
and increase friendship between
allied nations, to be sure.
But it's important that you
understand its true meaning.
The exams are, so to speak--
-So to speak?
-They're a representation of the
battle between allied nations.
-And what's that
supposed to mean?
-Now, if we look at our
history, all the countries
that we're currently allied with
were once neighboring nations
that continuously fought
with each other for power.
In order to avoid destroying
each other's military strength
meaninglessly, those
nations picked champions
to do battle on behalf
of their countries
at a mutually selected location.
That was how the Chunin
selection exams originally
began.
-Well, that's great.
But why do we have to go
through these exams, then?
I mean, it's not
like we're doing
this to pick Chunin to go fight.
-Well, actually,
there is no question
that part of the
point of these exams
is to select Shinobi
worthy of Chunin.
That's just not the whole story.
These exams also
allow for a place
where Shinobi can carry
the pride of their nation
on their backs, and
fight against other ninja
for their very lives.
-The pride of their nation?
-Many leaders and
people of prominence
from various
countries are invited
to attend this exam
as guests, and also
possibly to seek Shinobi
to work for them.
This exam will determine the
course of your ninja work
from here on out.
And more importantly, those
rulers will watch your battles
and take note of the strengths
that each ninja and each nation
is developing.
If there is a gap in power
between the countries,
the strong nations are
inundated with job requests
for their ninja.
And conversely, the request to
countries that are deemed weak
decline.
Therefore, the
stronger our nation
is, the better our
position when it
comes to negotiating with
neighboring countries.
So it's important
to show how much
military strength
our village has.
-OK, but even so,
why is it necessary
for us to risk our lives?
-The country's strength
is the village's strength.
The village's strength is
the Shinobi's strength.
And the true strength
of the Shinobi
is only achieved
when it's pushed
to its limits, such as in
a life and death battle.
This exam is a chance
for each nation
to display the strength
of its Shinobi,
and hence, the strength
of the nation itself.
It's because this is an exam
where your life is on the line
that it has meaning.
And it's for this very
reason and for the strength
of the nation that
your forerunners
fought in this exam.
It's truly a dream
worth striving for.
-But then why did you use the
expression "friendship" before?
-But you've only remembered
half of what I said.
You also mustn't have the wrong
idea of the exam's meaning.
This is a custom
in which balance
is preserved by
fighting and dying.
In the world of the
Shinobi, that is friendship.
The third exam is
a fight for life
with the pride of your village
and your own dreams at stake.
-Well, he sure convinced me.
-Any test is fine.
Just tell me what the details
of the exam are already.
I can handle anything
you throw at me.
-Very well then.
Now listen closely.
I'm going to tell you
exactly what you will all
be doing on the third exam.
-Lord Hokage, before you do,
please allow me, Hayate Gekko,
appointed as proctor of the
third exam, to speak first.
-So be it.
-It's nice to meet you all.
There's something I
would like all of you
to do before the third exam.
[music playing]
-So what's the deal?
Now suddenly we have to
go through preliminaries
before the third exam?
Just great.
And what about Sasuke?
There is definitely
something wrong with him.
I wish he would just drop out.
He's in no condition to fight.
That's it.
I don't care what he says.
I'm going to tell the teachers
about that bruise he has.
Next time, narrowing the field,
sudden death elimination.
I'm scared of what might
happen to all of us.