[theme music]
-All right.
We're almost at the
Leaf village now.
Is everyone here?
-Yes sir.
-Hey, wait a minute.
One of us isn't.
-Hm?
-Who's missing?
-Who do you think?
It's Idate.
-That kid's getting to
be a pain in the neck.
-What now?
Do we wait?
-Don't have much choice, do we?
Huh?
What in the world?
-You're from the Wasabi family
of the Land of Tea, right?
-Who the heck wants to know?
-One thing you
should know up front.
A bunch of clodhoppers like
you are no match for a ninja.
No need to worry.
I'll let you live this time.
But if you're smart, you'll
forget all about the race
at the Great Todoroki Shrine.
[groaning]
-He's gone.
Got to get to the village and
at least deliver this message.
-OK, let's do it!
Whatever the mission is,
I'm psyched and ready to go!
-Hmph.
-Hm?
-But where's Kakashi-sensei?
-Man, some teacher.
He's always the last one here.
TSUNADE: Kakashi
won't be here at all.
-Huh?
-Grandma Tsunade.
What's up?
-Stop calling me that, will you?
-Uh, Lady Hokage.
What's this about
Kakashi-sensei not coming?
-You know our forces
are stretched thin.
All of our Jonin are already
busy on other missions,
including Kakashi.
You three will just have to
handle this one on your own.
It's a B rank escort mission.
Someone important.
-Important?
Really?
-Of course, it could develop
into an A rank mission
if you run into trouble.
-So, who do we escort?
-I don't know.
-Hold on.
What do you mean you don't know?
-Every four years, our
neighbor, the Land of Tea,
holds a dedication ceremony
at the Great Todoroki Shrine,
and each time we're asked
to escort a runner who
will participate in the race
that's part of the ceremonies.
This year, the messengers
who were bringing the request
were attacked before
they could get here.
-Who attacked them?
-I'm sorry, but I'm still not
following this story very well.
-Well, don't worry
about that now.
When you meet Boss
Jirocho, he'll
fill you in on everything.
-When we meet Boss Jirocho?
Ah!
That gambler guy we met.
-That's everything I know.
Now, no wasting time.
They're expecting you
in the Land of Tea
by the end of the
day, so get moving.
-Got it.
-Right.
-Don't worry.
You can count on us!
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER):I hope so.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Misson!
Help an Old Friend
in the Land of Tea!
Hey, Sakura.
you hungry at all?
-A little bit, maybe.
-Hey!
Good idea!
Lunch break!
And look, what a coincidence.
There just happens to be
a tea house right there.
-Wait, Naruto!
-So you're back.
-Aoi Rokusho at your service.
-Seems we wasted your
time and trouble.
That fool Jirocho doesn't
know when to give up.
-The Wasabi family still intends
to take part in the race?
-Exactly.
What's more, they've even
hired ninja bodyguards
to protect their runner.
-Well then.
If we can't scare
them off, we'll
just have to destroy
them at the race itself.
-What will you be having?
-Some sweet bean soup!
-I'll have the
dumplings, please.
And you, Sasuke?
-Just rice.
Very good.
I'll be back in a moment.
-Leaf village ninja.
-I just hope we get
some fighting in!
-Don't you dare go
making trouble, Naruto.
Not this time.
NARUTO: I won't.
-Just sitting
around in the shade,
sucking down sweet bean soup.
A ninja's life is pretty cushy.
-What'd you say?
-I guess you don't get much
action in the Leaf village,
judging by how out
of shape you look.
-That does it!
-Hey.
Where'd you come from, sweetie?
I didn't see you sitting here.
I didn't mean you, of course.
-Thank you.
-Hello there.
I'm Idate Morino.
So, uh, what do they call you?
-You gonna punch him
in the nose, Sakura,
or do you want me to?
-Sakura, huh?
That's a beautiful name.
Well then.
Since fate has
brought us together,
isn't it time we talked
about our future?
-I'm not sure
that-- What future?
-Oh, you know,
the part where you
give up this ridiculous ninja
business and run away with me.
-Hey!
Quit hitting on her or I'm
gonna start hitting on you!
-Don't worry.
I was just kidding around.
But the rest of
it, that's no joke.
If there's one thing I
can't stand, it's a ninja.
You better go on back
where you came from,
or there'll be trouble.
I'm warning you.
-Yeah?
Well why wait?
Bring it on, tough guy!
-Calm down, Naruto.
-She's right.
Just ignore the punk.
We don't have the time.
-Get our of here, Sasuke!
After what this guy said,
don't you have any ninja pride?
You can ignore it if you want.
I'm gonna flatten it!
Huh?
-He disappeared.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): No way.
How did I miss that?
-Gah!
I hate that.
He gets in his little
dig and then runs away!
-Here you go.
Thank you for waiting.
-Ah phooey.
-I'll take these
whenever you're ready.
-Huh?
What's this?
Why two bills?
-Yours and your young
friend that just left.
He said you'd be paying for him.
-I knew it.
I know I should've flattened
him when I had the chance!
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): His
footsteps are already faint.
That kid's quick.
-That's it!
He's crossed the line,
making fools of us!
I'm gonna catch
that stupid jerk!
-We've gotta go, ma'am, thanks.
I've left the
money on the table!
-Come again.
These young people today.
Always in such a hurry.
-I don't know what this
kid's training has been,
but he's incredibly fast.
-Who could he be?
-Who cares?
He's toast when I
catch up with him.
-Ha.
Before they can
even get started,
I'm gonna be miles away.
All the speed in the
world won't help me
if I don't watch
where I'm going.
NARUTO: Ha!
Serves you right.
-Huh?
-You've got a lot of nerve.
Did you think you'd
get away with it?
-I'm sorry!
NARUTO: Huh?
-I couldn't pay the bill.
All my money had been stolen.
And then you guys came.
I shouldn't have done it, but
I didn't know what else to do.
-Oh, you're kidding?
All of your money?
-Well, why didn't you just
say that in the first place?
Huh?
-Huh?
-What's this thing?
-Hands off!
This belongs to me.
-What are you doing?
-On your mark--
-Huh?
-Get set.
Go!
-Huh?
Leg weights?
-Give it up, idiots!
You'll never catch me!
-There!
He's off and running again!
-We'll see about that!
-This kid's asking for it.
-Is this guy for real?
-I told you he's fast.
-What's goin' on?
He's getting further
away every second.
-There's just no way.
We'll never catch him.
He's out of our league.
-OK.
But if I ever see that
stupid jerk again, watch out.
-Welcome, and thank
you all for coming.
-I bid you greetings and
offer you my services.
I have come from
the Village Hidden
in the Leaves, which is
also the place of my birth.
I was raised on
ramen and hard work,
and given the family
name of Uzumaki.
But I'm known to everyone--
-As the knucklehead.
-As the knucklehead!
Very funny!
-You haven't changed
at all, I see.
-Yeah, well you haven't
changed much either, big guy.
-Watch it, Naruto.
[laughter]
-No, it's all right.
The boy has spirit.
I like that.
Now that we're done with
the greetings, maybe
we should get down to it.
The Fifth Hokage
told us you would
explain what you want us to do.
-All right, then.
You know about the
dedication ceremonies held
at the great Todoroki Shrine
every four years, don't you?
-Oh, well, uh-- not really.
-Go on.
Have a seat.
It all started long ago.
The legend goes that
in ancient times,
there came a terrible storm.
In desperation, the people
dedicated the Ryuko jewels
to the great Todoroki Shrine.
It worked.
The storm subsided,
and now the ceremony's
repeated every four years.
At first it was just a
re-dedication of the jewels.
Then it became a
festival, and a race,
with the winner of the race
being hailed as a great hero.
But, in recent years, what
once was a friendly race
has taken on a more
troubling aspect.
For generations,
Port Degarashi has
been divided between two
families-- the Wasabi
and the Wagarashi, two rival
gambling organizations.
Both families wanted
control of the town,
which naturally led to disputes.
These disputes became
increasingly violent,
sometimes resulting
in all out battles.
The rest of the townspeople
were caught in a crossfire.
Many were injured, or worse.
Finally, in an effort to
end the cycle of violence,
our district leader
called on both sides
to get together and
come to an agreement.
Henceforth, control
of the town would
be decided not by street
brawls, but by a competition.
-What sort of
competition, exactly?
-The race run every four years
at the great Todoroki Shrine
dedication ceremony.
Four years ago the
Wadarashi beat us soundly
by hiring a ninja,
and we found out
they've done the
same thing this year.
That's why we sent messengers
to you, seeking your help.
It was our way of leveling
the playing field.
But before they could reach the
village, they were attacked.
Ambushed.
I beg you, please lend
our family your strength.
If we lose again, it
means the Wagarashi
will control this town
for four more years.
-Not going to happen.
I'm on the job.
-So who are we supposed
to escort, anyway?
-Excellent.
That means you'll take the job.
-Yes, boss?
You wanted me?
Huh?
-Huh?
[groan]
-So you already know each other.
That makes everything easier.
-I wouldn't be so sure.
-Boss Jirocho is a
big man around here.
He shouldn't have
to bow and scrape
to a bunch of shinobi wannabes.
-He can bow and
scrape all he wants.
There's no way I'm gonna escort
a lousy cheapskate like you
anywhere, anyway.
-Fine.
Believe me, if I
wanted an escort,
it certainly wouldn't
be some snot-nosed run
who barely comes
up to my kneecaps.
-Whoa, who you calling a
runt, you ignorant hick?
I'm Naruto Uzumaki.
I'm a ninja.
Not only that, I'm
gonna be Hokage someday.
-Ha.
Hokage.
Big deal.
-It's a lot better
than being the boss
of a bunch of crooked gamblers!
-Hey, squirt, my boss is a great
leader, so watch what you say!
-He's a great leader, huh?
Would he sacrifice his
life for his village
like the Hokage would?
That's a leader!
-Are you kidding me?
He'd sacrifice his life,
his heart, his soul,
and the souls of his children's
children for all eternity!
-That's nothing!
The Hokage would do all
of that stuff and more,
and do it twice a day!
-You'd think this
was a tourist resort.
These prices are outrageous.
-I know what you're thinking.
Too expensive?
-Oh, no--
-Believe me, I don't like
having to charge that much.
But the Wagarashi
family sets the price.
[crashing]
-I'm sorry.
I'm sorry!
-What's wrong with you?
When we want
something, we take it.
You got it?
You wouldn't even
be in business if it
weren't for the Wagarashi.
-I know, I know!
It's just, to take it
without paying me for it--
-You're really not
getting this, are you?
Yo.
-Right.
-No.
No, please!
-OK, then.
Let me make it
easy to understand.
-What the-- who are you?
-Why don't you and your
friends take a hike?
-Get him out of here!
Those are the Wagarashi's men.
-Don't worry.
MAN: You asked for it, punk!
[beating]
-Huh?
-Ain't actin' so tough
now, are ya, kid?
-That ought to teach ya a thing
or two, you little pipsqueak.
Don't mess with us, or next
time you won't get off so easy.
[screaming]
-Young man.
Thank you, whoever you are.
-Just look at those men run.
Now, if only the Wasabi
family can win the race,
we'll be through
with them for good.
-Hey, Sasuke?
-Yeah.
-It's only-- of
all the people you
could choose, why did
it have to be them?
-Tell me when you're
finished sulking.
-I'm not sulking.
It's just that--
-Idate, the Wasabi family
has complete faith in you.
And I have faith in you.
Isn't it time you had a
little faith in yourself?
Idate, I'm asking you
to run for the family.
Begging you.
-I will, sir.
Yes.
(VOICEOVER) Even if
it costs me my life.
[cheering]
-Whoa.
I had no idea it
was such a big deal.
So what kind of
race is it, anyway?
-You know, the kind with
a start and a finish.
Listen carefully,
and I'll explain.
The starting point is here
in the harbor of Degarashi.
From here, the runners
head for Modoroki Shrine.
That's the midpoint.
NARUTO: They run over water?
SAKURA: Uh, no, Naruto.
The first leg of the
race is done by boat.
See?
Anway, the runners pick
up the Ryoko jewels
from the Modoroki
Shrine, and the first one
that gets them to the
great Todoroki Shrine wins.
That's it as far as the
some basic rules go,
but other than that,
just about anything goes.
Shortcuts, dirty
tricks, anythig.
-That's why hiring ninja
to help you out is OK, too.
-OK, so where are the
ninja the other side hired?
-They're keeping a low
profile, but they're around.
So watch your step.
OK, Naruto?
-Yeah, yeah.
-I don't care what you guys
do, but whatever happens,
just stay away from me.
-Say what?
-I've got a race to run.
I don't want you in my way.
-In your way?
-Hey, hey, come on!
Can't we all just work together?
-No way.
Not with him!
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Off to a good start.
This could be a long race.
ANNOUNCER: Attention, attention!
The Great Todoroki Shrine
Race is about to begin!
Running for the
Wasabi, Idate Morino!
[cheering]
SASUKE: Idate Morino?
ANNOUNCER: Running for the
Wagarashi family, Fukusuke
Hikyakuya!
-Yeah!
[cheering]
ANNOUNCER: Runners,
take your marks!
[heartbeats]
-Go!
-Guess that means we
better get going too!
What the--
-Heh.
-What's that idiot doing?
-Idate, where are you going?
-Hey!
You're going the wrong way!
-What's he doing?
-Have you gone crazy, or what?
[theme music]
NARUTO: Where's this bozo going?
Where's he's going?
He's moving at incredible speed.
NARUTO: The race has
barely even started
and his opponent is
already on the boat!
SAKURA: This is bad.
Put it in gear, Naruto.
We've gotta catch him!
-I don't think I
ever have that great!
Man, if this
weren't our mission,
I'd just let the fool go.
But OK, let's do it!
SAKURA: Right!
NARUTO: Next time,
The Race is On!
Trouble on the High Seas!