[theme music]
[yelling]
-So to fight the master, I must
first fight the puppets, huh?
Very well.
Ahh!
Haha, you think a
wall of wood can
block my path into
a glorious tomorrow?
With the power of youth,
I have the strength
to break through any barrier.
I can overcome anything
with hot blooded effort.
With eyes on tomorrow, I strike!
Forget about tomorrow,
what about today?
This is no ordinary barrier.
The wood must be infused
and reinforced with chakra.
GENSHO: Guy Sensei.
-Hmm?
Is that Yagura?
Are you all right?
-Haha.
I'm fine, but I'm not Yagura.
I am the eldest of the
Brothers Ryudoin, Gensho.
-I'm the second
brother, Rokkaku.
-And I'm the youngest, Jako.
-Ryodoin.
Hmm.
That name is vaguely familiar.
-What?
You don't remember?
-Perhaps you remember our
father, Agira Ryudoin,
a mighty warrior who fell
victim to the cowardly tactics
of the Leaf Village ninja.
You prevented him from
fulfilling his missions
and he eventually
died of despair.
-Our father's hatred of you
lasted until the very end.
Your name was on his lips
as he lay on his death bed.
He told us to seek
out Guy of the Leaf
and do battle with him.
-On the very day he
died, we his sons
vowed never to rest
until we had vengeance.
-We've been waiting for the
chance to even the score,
to make you pay for
what you did to him.
-Ah, yes.
Of course, Agira.
Yes, I remember
that battle well.
A heroic struggle.
Your father was the most
noble and worthy opponent.
What a splendid fight it was.
I shall feature it
prominently when
I write my eight-volume
history of Might Guy's most
memorable battles.
A clash of warriors, each
following his ninja way.
It was an honorable
battle between equals.
I'm sure your
father would agree,
so let's just stop this nonsense
before someone gets hurt,
shall we?
-Fool.
We won't stop until we do to
you what you did to our father.
-Yah!
Yes, Sakura.
I know you have been out
there watching for a while.
-Lady Tsunade wanted
me to come and make
sure you didn't
overdo it, that's all.
-What is it?
What are you hiding?
-Hiding?
What do you mean?
Nothing!
-You do not have a
gift for lying, Sakura.
-Huh?
-Vengeance will be ours.
Now die!
-All right, you guys.
Break it up!
You're the phony
Yagura, aren't you?
What are you up to, trying
to infiltrate our village?
-Hmm.
Byakugan!
They have Guy Sensei in there.
They've infused the
walls of that structure
with their chakra.
-Not for long.
-Ahh!
-Hang in there,
Bushier Brows Sensei.
Don't worry, we're coming!
Ah.
What is this?
Ha.
You really think you can
stop us with these overgrown
chopsticks?
You've got to be kidding!
-Naruto, wait!
-Wooden training dummies.
-Oh, I know.
Are these guys controlling
them like puppets?
-I can't believe they could
control them all at once.
I don't care how good they are.
-Yes, I agree.
It's hard to believe they
have that much power.
Byakugan.
That explains it.
-Huh?
-Each of these
things is animated
and it's movements generated by
a seal on the back of its head.
-So that's not a puppet
master jutsu at all.
-No.
They have a basic set
of repetitive movements.
And they can't
anticipate our moves.
-So if we can remove those
seals, that should stop them.
-No sweat, piece of cake.
OK, blockhead.
Time for me to return the favor.
Multi-shadow Clone Jutsu!
Here we go!
Ha.
The bigger they are,
the harder they fall.
I gotcha!
TENTEN: Oh, heck, this is easy.
-Are you fool enough to think
that's the extent of our jutsu?
Ninja art, wooden dummy,
manipulation jutsu!
[rattling]
-Ahh!
Careful, guys.
Some of them have more
moves than the others do.
-Neji!
[grunting]
-Uzumaki!
[shouts]
-Stay back!
-It seems like some
of these dummies
are controlled by a puppet
master jutsu, doesn't it?
-Lee.
-Bushy Brow?
-Leaf Hurricane!
-Lee!
-How the heck did you
know we were way up here?
-When Sakura told me that
Guy Sensei was headed
to the land of
mountain streams, I
guessed at once he
would take this route
through the mountains.
But where is Guy Sensei now?
-Over there, inside that thing.
-What now?
-Are they running away?
-What the?
What the heck's going on?
Looks like some
kind of fortress.
-Let me handle this.
Guy Sensei is my
mentor and teacher.
I would gladly give
my life to save him.
-Bushy Brow, what about
that leg of yours?
It hasn't healed yet.
-I am going in.
-Wait, you can't just--
-You think you can stop me?
I warn you, I feel
very powerful today.
-Least we can do is help.
-I sense a weak
spot in the chakra
at the center of that structure.
Head for that.
-But be careful.
It could be a trap.
-Maybe so.
Very well then.
Let us fall into it willingly.
[wood breaking]
-Dynamic Entry!
Whoa!
It does appear that I've
been lured into a trap.
Be that as it may, I
will see it through.
-Rokkaku, Jaco, leave
everything to me.
I will handle this.
-All right.
It's revenge we want.
Be sure you make the dog pay.
-Oh yes, he'll pay.
Wooden dummy, possess,
transfer, repossessed, jutsu.
[door slams]
-There are more of these
wooden dummies in here?
GENSHO: Your teacher has
filled your head with lies.
-Whose voice is that?
Yagura?
GENSHO: It's a lie
that passion and effort
can overcome anything.
A lie, and you're a
fool to believe it.
-Nobody called
Guy Sensei a liar.
I dare you to come out of
hiding and say that, you coward.
GENSHO: Why should
I, when I can easily
prove my point with these
wooden dummies I've created?
-I have vowed to
rescue Guy Sensei.
Neither you or
any wooden dummies
are going to change that.
GENSHO: You'd be funny
if you weren't so sad.
-Ahh!
That was the leaf hurricane.
Is it possible that
from the one time
I used it against Yagura he
was able to copy and master it
so quickly?
Very well.
Leaf Super Hurricane!
Could Yagura really
be doing this?
If he has already developed his
offensive and defensive skills
to such a level, he truly
is a natural genius.
-There was extraordinary
force behind that kick.
This is not the young trainee
I watched in the practice saw.
In fact, there is
only one person
I can think of who could
unleash such power.
-They're fighting each other
without even knowing it.
How father would
have enjoyed this.
-Yes, a battle to the death
between teacher and student.
-It's perfect.
And even if they discover
the true identity
of their opponent--
-They have to fight on,
even against their will,
until one or the
other is defeated.
That is the secret of
my very special jutsu.
-Ahh!
-My leg cannot take
much more of this.
I have no choice.
There is only one
move left to me.
Forgive me, Guy Sensei.
I know I promised you,
but I must, for your sake.
-The Lotus.
Could it be the wooden
dummy is really Lee?
-Dancing Leaf Shadow!
-The Lotus hit back followed
by multiple severe Leaf
Hurricanes.
Magnificent.
In fact, too magnificent.
Only Guy Sensei is
capable of such a thing.
-Such ability.
If it were anyone
but me, that Lotus
would have ended the
match right there.
But end it must.
And it will end badly,
too, unless, of course.
It's the only chance we've got.
[tapping]
-That's tapping is Morse code.
What is he trying to say?
We have been tricked into--
-Committing
ourselves to a battle
that will only end when one
of us destroys the other.
-So it was Guy Sensei I
was fighting all this time.
-We can only free ourselves
if we attack each other
with such speed and force that
these wooden figures will not
be able to duplicate it.
-I fear it means I must lead
you to the very brink of death
once again?
[tapping]
-Guy Sensei, if I did it only
to protect the most important
person in the world to me--
-Will you forgive me
for breaking my word
and using that technique?
The most important
person in the world?
You mean to say that
I-- I am that person?
Do you mean it?
Oh Lee, of all the times,
why pick now to make me cry?
Listen Lee, I will never
forget the solemn vow I made.
-If by chance, Lee, you
should happen to die,
I will die at your side.
Guy Sensei?
Thank you, Guy Sensei.
-Now is the time.
-We must follow our ninja way.
GUY AND LEE: And follow
it all the way to the end.
-Third Gate of Life, open!
-Fourth Gate of Pain, open!
-Ahh!
-No, not yet!
-Ah!
-Brother, what is it?
-They're too fast.
They're both moving too fast!
At this rate, the wooden dummies
will shatter into pieces.
-Fifth Gate of Closing!
-Open!
-They're too fast to see.
I can't even hear them anymore.
-That's it.
Bring every ounce of
your hot-blooded chakra
to bear on your opponent.
-I will!
-Ahh!
[panting]
[wood cracking]
-The fortress is--
-Falling apart.
[crash]
-If it was revenge
you sought, you
should have fought me like
a warrior, man to man.
Your father, though
out-numbered and the only one
of his squad still standing,
refused to surrender.
All he had left to fight with
was his kung fu and his honor.
Out of respect for
your father's courage,
I accepted his challenge and
met him in single combat.
And when the battle
was finally over,
he was content with
the outcome and said
only that he would
like to fight again.
Whether you believe what I
say or not, that's how it was.
-Perhaps we misunderstood.
Perhaps he told us
we should fight Guy
not in the hopes of defeating
him, but to learn from him.
-So then we-- we've been
wrong all this time?
-Your father taught me
something very important
during our glorious battle.
He taught me that being
born with natural talent
is not the greatest gift.
The truly lucky ones are those
with an unwavering belief
in themselves and the passion to
keep striving to the very end.
-Now that's a
student/teacher relationship.
SAKURA: Naruto!
-Hey Sakura, good to see ya!
You can help us carry Bushy
Brow back to the village!
-You bet.
That's why we brought
the stretcher.
-No, no, forget about me.
Take care of Yagura first.
I mean, what is his
real name, anyway?
Who is he?
-Lee, Lee!
There'll be plenty of time
to explain everything later.
Now hush, and let them
take you to the hospital.
-Yes, Guy Sensei.
-That's a good student/teacher
relationship all right.
Why can't I have a
teacher like that?
Hmm.
[music]
-What's up, Kiba?
KIBA: Sheesh, what makes
you think I would know?
NARUTO: I'm only asking.
NEJI: Quiet, you two.
TENTEN: Yeah, we're about to
get some important orders.
NARUTO: OK.
TENTEN: Troji, come on.
Can't you eat later?
TROJI: Sure, when?
TENTEN: That's not the point!
NARUTO: I am so fired up!
TENTEN: You are so loud.
NEJI: I think everyone's here.
-All right then.
I'll explain the next mission.
NARUTO: Next time.
ALL: Crisis, the
Hidden Leaf 11 Gather!
[music]