[music playing]
[theme music]
-(VOICEOVER) I feel
like I can't breathe.
One shallow breath, one
tiny movement of the eye
is enough to draw his attack.
It's suffocating.
If it goes on like
this, I'll go insane.
The clash of two Jonin
intent to attack.
I've never felt
anything so chilling.
It's as if my own life
is being choked off.
No.
I can't take it.
I'd rather--
KAKASHI: Sasuke!
[gasping]
Calm down.
I'll protect you with
my life-- all of you.
I will not allow
my comrades to die!
Trust me.
[gasping]
ZABUZA: I wouldn't be so sure.
It's over.
-Don't move.
[screaming]
[music playing]
[water spilling]
-Sensei!
Behind you!
-Huh?
[grunting]
[laughing]
-The water clone
jutsu-- it can't be.
-Don't move.
Now it's over.
NARUTO: "The Oath of Pain."
[wind howling]
-You're finished.
-Huh?
(HAPPILY) All right!
[laughing]
-Huh?
-Finished?
You really don't get it, do you?
Your technique is nothing
but a crass imitation.
I'll never be defeated by a
mere copycat ninja like you.
[grunting]
[laughing]
You are full of
surprises, though.
You'd already copied
my water clone jutsu
when you made your
little speech.
-I'll protect you with
my life-- all of you.
ZABUZA: Very
skillfully executed.
You made your clone say those
words to draw my attention
while you hid in the mist
waiting for me to make my move.
Nice try, but I'm not
that easy to fool.
-Hey!
That one's a clone, too!
[crashing]
[grunting]
-Now!
Huh? [inaudible] spikes--
trying to slow me down.
Hmph.
Foolish.
-Sensei!
-Huh?
I can't believe
Kakashi Sensei got
kicked through
the air like that.
-He has great
physical skill, too.
-(VOICEOVER) This
isn't normal water.
It's dense-- heavy.
-Ah, fool.
Water prison jutsu!
-No!
-Escaping into the
water-- bad mistake.
[laughing]
-This prison is made of water,
but it's stronger than steel.
It's hard to fight
when you can't move.
So much for the great Kakashi.
I'll finish you off later.
But first, your little friends
will have to be eliminated.
Water clone jutsu!
[groaning]
-(VOICEOVER) He's even more
skilled than I thought.
[gasping]
[laughing]
ZABUZA: You think wearing a
headband makes you a ninja.
When you've hoovered between
life and death so many times
it doesn't faze you, then
you may be called a ninja.
When you've become so
deadly, your profile
is entered in my
bingo book, then
you may have earned
the title ninja.
But to call up starts
like you ninja is a joke.
-He disappeared again.
[gasping]
[grunting]
-You're just brats.
[gasping]
-Naruto!
[grunting]
-Listen!
Get the bridge builder and run!
You can't win this fight!
He's using all his power
to keep me in this prison.
So he can only fight you
with his water clone.
But the clone can't go
far from his real body.
If you get away from
him, he can't follow.
Now run!
-(VOICEOVER) Run away?
Not an option.
That became unthinkable
the moment you got caught.
No matter how fast we
run or how far we go,
he'll track us down
and wipe us out.
If we try amagni
defense formation,
he can get around
it in an instant.
In the end, if we're on
our own, we're finished.
Our only chance of
survival is to rescue you.
We've got to do it.
[yelling]
[grunting]
-(YELLING) Now!
-Too easy.
[groaning]
-Sasuke!
No!
-He got Sasuke!
[gasping]
(VOICEOVER) So this is what a
Jonin is-- a true elite ninja.
I-- I've got to get away.
If I don't-- seriously,
he'll annihilate me!
[yelling]
[gasping]
[groaning]
Upon this wound, I
make this pledge.
Believe it.
I will never back down again
and let someone else rescue me!
I will never run away.
-(SARCASTICALLY) You're
not hurt, are you?
Scaredy-cat.
-(VOICEOVER) And I will
not lose to Sasuke!
[groaning]
-I-- I-- I want to
try on your headband.
Come on, please?
-Uh-- oh, this?
No way.
You can only wear
the leaf headband
when you graduate from the
Academy and become a ninja.
Naruto, come over
here for a minute.
I've got something special
I want to give you.
Congratulations You graduate.
-That's what happens.
An enemy takes a hostage, and
you have an impossible choice.
On every mission, your
life is on the line.
You pass.
-I'm not the little
brat who used
to pull pranks all the time!
I'm a ninja now, and I
want a ninja mission!
To be the greatest Hokage--
then the whole village
will stop disrespecting
me and start
treating me like I'm
somebody-- somebody important.
(VOICEOVER) That's right.
I'm a ninja now.
Believe it.
I swore an oath of pain.
I won't run away!
[screaming]
-Huh?
Naruto, no!
-(SCREAMING) Ugh!
Naruto!
What in the world are you doing?
[laughing]
-Fool.
[screaming]
[groaning]
-(ANGRILY) What are you thinking
charging at him by yourself?
Even Sasuke couldn't get to him!
We're only Genin!
We can't defeat a Jonin!
What did you think you'd
accomplish by that?
[gasping]
[groaning]
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
The headband?
That's what he wanted?
[gasping]
-Hey, you, the freak
with no eyebrows--
[music playing]
Put this in your bingo book--
the ninja that will become
Hokage of the Village
Hidden in the Leaves--
[panting]
He never backs down!
His name's Naruto Uzumaki.
-Naruto.
-(VOICEOVER) Huh.
I thought he was all talk,
but this kid's got guts.
-All right, Sasuke, listen up.
Can you hear me?
-Yeah, I hear you.
-I've got a plan.
-(VOICEOVER) Hmph.
Now he's got a plan?
This guy.
So you're finally thinking
about teamwork, huh?
-(VOICEOVER) Why do
I have this feeling?
Naruto's so determined.
-All right.
Now, guys, let's go wild!
OK.
Ready?
Let's bring this guy down.
[laughing]
ZABUZA: Big words for
such a little man.
You think your plan's going
to keep you in the game?
-(VOICEOVER) Ugh.
This isn't good.
What are you doing?
I told you to run!
This fight was over the
moment I got caught.
Now, take off!
Your mission is not to
prove how brave you are.
It's to save the bridge builder.
Stay on mission!
-Huh.
Bridge builder.
[groaning]
-Well, I-- I guess this
all happened because of me.
Because of my desire to live.
But I won't let that
stand in your way now.
Forget about me, and
do what you have to do.
Go ahead and fight
to save your sensei.
-Hmph.
All right.
You hear that?
-Yeah.
Believe it.
You ready?
[laughing]
-You really haven't
learned anything, have you?
Still playing your little
game-- pretending to be ninja.
When I was your age,
this hand had already
crushed many opponents.
[gasping]
-Zabuza.
The demon.
-Oh.
So I was in your book, too, huh?
-Long ago, in the Village
Hidden in the Mist-- also known
as Blood Mist Village-- before
a student could become a ninja,
there was one final test.
-Hm.
Do you know about
the graduation exam?
-What graduation exam?
[laughing]
What's the big deal anyway?
We had graduation tests, too.
[laughing]
-Did you have to kill the
other students to pass?
-Huh?
ZABUZA: Imagine young ninja like
you-- eating together, training
together-- and then
comes the final exam.
Only they changed the
rules-- kill or be killed.
You can't stop while your
opponent still breathes.
He was your friend--
shared your dreams.
Now, it's him or you.
-That's so cruel.
-10 years ago in the
Village Hidden in the Mist
the graduation exam changed.
One year before, a dark evil had
filled the school with terror.
-What's he saying?
What evil?
What kind of change?
What caused the terror?
KAKASHI: Without
pause or hesitation,
a young boy who was not even
a ninja approached the class
and took down over
100 other students.
[groaning]
-It-- it felt so-- good!
[gasping]
[groaning]
[grunting]
[yelling]
-Sasuke!
[groaning]
[gasping]
[grunting]
[laughing]
-You're nothing.
-Stop right there!
Shadow clone jutsu!
-Oh.
Shadow clones.
And there's quite a few of them.
[music playing]
-Here we go.
[groaning]
[crashing]
[gasping]
-His skills are too advanced.
He's too powerful.
There's no way to defeat him.
-I'm not giving up!
I've still got this!
Sasuke!
[yelling]
[grunting]
-(VOICEOVER) So
that was your plan?
Not bad, Naruto!
-Huh?
[clanging sound]
-Demon wind shuriken--
windmill of shadows!
[gasping]
[groaning]
-A shuriken?
You'll never touch me with that.
[grunting]
-Hm?
So, you pass the clone
and aim for my real body.
Smart.
But not smart enough.
Huh?
A second shuriken in
the shadow of the first.
The shadow shuriken jutsu.
-(VOICEOVER) The second
shuriken's on target,
and he can't catch this one.
-I told you a shuriken
can't touch me!
[gasping]
-(VOICEOVER) He dodged it!
-Hm.
[gasping]
-(SURPRISED) What?
-Eat this!
[yelling]
[theme music]
NARUTO: Yeah, I did it!
The plan worked!
A ninja must see
through deception,
but Zabuza had no
clue what I was up to.
I totally fooled him!
You saw it!
The Hidden Leaf fighting
style of Naruto Uzumaki!
Believe it!
Al right, Sensei,
we got you free.
Now the rest is up to you.
Next time-- "Kakashi--
Sharingan Warrior."
Don't miss my first big victory!