[theme music]
-For crying out loud.
-Sakura?
-How far have we walked?
That tower is not
getting any closer.
-Now that you mention it,
I was thinking that too.
It's weird.
-Maybe not.
It would seem
we've been spotted.
Somebody's playing
games with us.
Look.
Ring a bell?
-Huh?
Oh, man.
No way!
It can't be!
Hey, what's the big idea?
-What's going on?
-Kenjitsu.
That's what it looks like,
and we feel for it completely.
We were so concerned with
not being seen by anyone,
we didn't see we were
walking around in circles.
-What's their game?
-They're probably trying to
wear us down and then strike
when we're frustrated
and physically exhausted.
-You mean like we are right now?
-Right.
They'll be coming soon.
-Well, Naruto.
You wanted a fight.
-Four against 40, just
the way I like it.
Clone versus clone.
Mine are better than yours.
-What are they?
-Clones, from the look of it.
And a whole lot of them.
-Like cornered rats.
-Oh yeah?
Cornered rats, are we?
-Well, whatever they are,
they sure can't take a punch.
That's showing them!
Way to go!
-Hm?
-What are they?
-I just touched him
and he turned to mush.
-What's really going on here?
Sharingan!
-Naruto, watch out!
-Sasuke!
-Down!
-What's going on?
Can't move my body.
-Are you all right?
-It's obvious this
thing is real enough.
No illusion here.
-Surrender your scroll!
Surrender your scroll!
-The fact that Kabuto
is wounded and bleeding
means that these things
are real shadow clones!
But man, shadow
clones are supposed
to vanish when you
give them a good shot.
These things don't!
So what the heck
are we dealing with?
Some kind of Kenjitsu?
-Surrender your scrolls.
-Come and get it!
-It's no use!
Save it!
You'll only be
fighting illusions.
It's Genjutsu, all right.
-Illusions?
But how?
That gash on Kabuto's
arm is real enough.
-That's true.
But still, Sasuke is right.
Could be the real enemy is in
hiding somewhere in the woods
nearby, launching real attacks
from behind a smokescreen
of illusions and coordinating
their movements with them
so that we're fooled into
thinking these Genjutsu
Shinobi are the
ones attacking us.
-Lucky guess.
-Well, wherever they are,
what are we going to do,
just stand here?
Let's go find these clowns
and take care of them!
-Hold on, Naruto.
They'd like nothing
better than for us
to go searching blindly through
the forest while they sit back
and take us out one by one.
We'd be making their
job easy for them.
I know this kind of attack.
The kind who use it
do so because they're
weak in Taijutsu and afraid
of close, hand-to-hand combat,
according to my data.
We have no choice.
All we can do is hold our ground
and fend off their attacks.
-OK, fine.
Whatever.
Let's just do it.
-How long do you think
they can hold out?
-The night is young.
[laughs]
-Man, how long is
this going to go on?
-OK.
This isn't going to work.
-No.
It's pointless.
You'll only waste your Chakra.
By trying to fight these, you'll
be doing just what they want.
-If we were to eliminate all
of the illusions, whoever
is casting them wouldn't be able
to hurl kunai at us without us
being able to see
where they're hiding.
I'll show them two
can play at this game.
Shadow clone Jutsu!
-Shadow clones!
-Back for more, huh?
OK!
-Sasuke, shouldn't we help him?
-Jerk.
He's given us no choice.
We've got to now.
-Well then?
-You're right.
He's going to need us.
So that's that.
We fight.
-Come on, Sakura.
-Right!
-I'm just warming up.
-Sun's coming up.
Time to move in for the kill.
-I think you're right.
We've crushed their spirits.
Now all that's left
is their bodies.
Lucky us.
You!
I know you.
You're the one who cut
me on the shoulder!
That really messed
me up, you know.
Oh, well.
Now I can finally pay
you back-- with interest.
[laughs]
-Well, well.
Now who's the cornered rat?
-Works like a charm, Naruto.
-What?
It can't be.
If they're over there,
then who are they?
-Confused?
Sorry, but it was
the only way to get
you guys to come out of hiding.
-How?
Don't tell me that, little brat.
It's not possible.
-The shadow clones were
only the first part of it.
My real trick was
coming up with clones
for the rest of my squad.
-While our doubles did all the
fighting and took the beating,
we were safe and sound waiting
for you to show yourself.
What do you think, guys?
I think our little plan worked.
Naruto, take a break.
You've used up too
much of your Chakra.
Don't worry.
I've got them.
-After all the work
I've done, there's
no way I'm going to
stand back and let you
guys have all the fun.
-Woah.
Is this the same Naruto?
What happened?
When did he get this good?
-This kid shouldn't even be
able to move, let alone this.
-Naruto?
-His Chakra is
incredibly resilient.
To be able to pull off a
multiple shadow clone Jutsu,
and then to transform
three of them
into clones of his companions,
and to still come out fighting.
And all this on the 5th day.
If he ever truly
masters his Chakra,
this kid will be unstoppable.
-Not bad.
But that doesn't mean it's over.
We're still feeling lucky.
And besides, time is
running out for all of us.
So we'll just have to take
the gloves off and show you
our Ninjutsu.
Ninja heart!
Falcon jutsu!
-Shadow clones?
-Those are real clones.
Don't waste your
strength, bone head.
Let them make the first move.
-If these are clones,
then the real ones
are in there with them.
All I've got to do is
smash my way through
until I find the
ones that squeal!
-No!
Don't be an idiot.
Listen to me.
-Get off my back, will you?
Just stay out of it.
I can handle this.
-No, Naruto!
Come back!
-Not again.
-Just like before.
The stabbing pain in my neck
when I try my Sharingan.
Maybe I've used too
much of my Chakra.
-So that one's a clone.
Two!
That one, too.
-Naruto, stop!
-Could it be they're all fake?
Or could it be Ganjutsu again?
-I've got to try.
Use the last of my Chakra.
Sharingan!
-Sasuke!
The mark again.
Sasuke, please, stop
using your Sharingan.
Don't do it.
-You should never give
your enemy an opening.
-Hey, are you OK?
Now you're going to get it.
-Forget it, Naruto.
-Huh?
-You can swing at
those guys all day.
You're just wasting
your time on them.
The real ones aren't there.
-What are you talking about?
That last attack didn't
come from any clone.
Of course the real
ones are here.
They've gotta be here.
If they're not, then
where the heck are they?
-Use your head.
If I knew the answer to that,
we wouldn't be in this fix.
-I'm exhausted.
Can't do the Shadow
Clone Jutusu anymore.
-Looks like they've reached
the end of their rope.
Oh, well.
It was fun while it lasted.
-That's it.
They hide using Earth
Style and attack
while we're focused
on their clones.
-Kabuto!
-Like you said, never give
your enemy an opening.
Good advice.
-Thank you, Naruto.
You saved my neck.
-Way to go, Naruto.
-It was nothing.
-That mark on your
neck, what is it?
A bruise?
-It's nothing.
-Hey, guys!
Here it is!
Just what we needed,
a heaven scroll.
-Good for you.
-There's something
about this guy.
Something I don't like.
-There you are, Kabuto.
You're late.
-Sorry about that.
I got a little sidetracked.
-Yeah, and are we glad you did.
After all, it was
only thank to you
that we got both the scrolls.
-Not really.
You did most of it on your own.
Especially you, Naruto.
Very impressive.
Well, this is the door
that we go through.
So long, and good
luck to us both.
-Right.
-A good harvest?
-Yes.
Even better than expected.
I learned a lot about him
during the second exam.
And I recorded all
the data on this.
You want it?
-Of course.
So tell me, what did you think?
-Your curiosity is truly
insatiable, Lord Orochimaru.
-As a sound village spy,
you see things others don't.
Your opinion is
of interest to me.
-Oh, it doesn't really
matter, does it?
Whatever I think, you're
the one who decides.
Isn't that always the way?
-You're a cagey one,
aren't you, Kabuto?
I like that.
Good work.
-What's the deal?
There's nobody here.
-It's OK, Sakura.
I can manage.
-Sure.
-What a drag.
I was enjoying that.
-Huh?
I don't get it.
What happens now?
-Hold on a second.
Just look at that.
-Great.
What is it?
-If qualities of
heaven are your desire,
acquire wisdom to
take your mind higher.
If earthly qualities are what
you lack, train your body
and prepare to attack.
When heaven and earth
are open together,
the perilous path will
become righteous forever.
This something is the secret way
that guides us from this place
today.
-This what?
Or is that a secret, too?
-It's like there's
a word missing here.
Anyway, it's about the scrolls.
I think we're supposed to open
and read the heaven and earth
scrolls now.
-OK.
Here goes nothing.
[music playing]
-Hey, what's the big idea?
What are all these
guys still doing here?
Hinata and her team of goof
balls, Rock Lee and his squad,
and even those other weirdos.
Oh, well.
Just means they'll be that much
more bummed when I leave them
all in the dust.
Because I am going
to beat Hokage.
Next time, surviving the cut.
The rookie nine together again.