[theme music]
[owl hoot]
[crickets]
-Tomorrow.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
The Final Rounds- Rush
to the Battle Arena.
-So what's up?
It's been awhile
since you've come in.
[chuckles]
-I was kind of in the hospital.
-The hospital?
-Don't worry.
I'm fine now.
Never felt better
as a matter of fact.
-Well, that's good.
Ayame.
-Huh?
Oh.
Here you go.
-Uh?
[giggles]
NARUTO: Um, Mr. Chef?
-Just eat it.
The final competition
is tomorrow, right?
-Uh, [giggles] Oh, all right.
Thanks guys!
[laughing]
-Well, at least with
a daughter at home
it's not so bad on the wallet.
Most of my money turns into
food and then vanishes.
-Quit complaining.
You're not the only
one who's got problems.
-Hm?
-Look, I understand.
Daughters are a real drag.
-Yeah.
Man, there are
times when I really
have no idea how
to deal with her.
-I know what you mean.
We dads have it rough.
-Humph and you're telling
me to quit complaining.
Hey, Mister, one
more order here.
These two pages,
everything on them.
-Welcome.
-Aha!
Reinforcements are here.
Come on in.
Order something.
[sigh]
-Hey dad, come on.
Can we go home already?
-What?
Listen, don't be a drag.
You're supposed to be living
it up at this festival.
-Yeah right.
Some festival.
It's a total drag.
-You idiot.
Since ancient--
[enjoying his drink] times
the final competition has
always been like a festival.
-I'm in that final
competition tomorrow.
Oh man, I don't have
time to babysit you.
-Huh?
You're in it?
What?
Seriously?
-Never mind.
Just forget it.
-So tomorrow he'll--
-Yeah.
-Tomorrow is a full moon.
[ticking clock]
[birds chirping]
[breathing heavily]
-Incredible.
You don't have a scratch on you.
It's perfect.
Right Neji?
-Why don't we call it a warm up?
Let's get going all right.
[alarm buzzing]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): So much for
getting a good night's sleep.
Stupid nerves.
And right off the bat,
in the first match,
I have to go up against him.
-But these chakra
points, they're
undetectable even
to my Sharingan eye.
-I have on my team the man who
is probably the strongest genin
ever to come out of the
Hidden Leaf Village.
That man.
Neji Hyuga.
[echoes]
[drums]
[wind]
-At last it begins.
-Neji Hyuga's in the
first match right?
Oh yeah.
That guy's the number one
rookie from last year.
There's just no way we
can miss that match.
-Neji Hyuga.
[laughs]
-Yeah, but now I'm
able to summon a toad.
It'll be OK for sure.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
But all of those guys
looked like nasty competitors.
-Huh?
Hinata?
[gasps]
-Oh, Naruto!
So why are you here?
The final competition?
-Hm.
I just-- It's nothing.
I came to check out
this training field.
This is actually the place
where I became a genin, so--
-Oh, but why are you here?
-Uh, nothing.
No real reason.
It doesn't matter anyway.
-Oh.
Guess you're right.
Sorry.
-Say, Hinata, Neji, he's
a cousin of yours right?
-Yeah.
-So is he really strong?
-Mm.
[sighs]
-Great.
-But, I mean, you still
might be able to win Naruto.
[nervous laughing]
-Yeah.
I'm strong too after all.
[nervous laughing]
[sighs]
-I know you can win Naruto.
-Huh?
-Remember that time
when you cheered for me.
I felt like-- like I was able
to become stronger than ever
before.
-Go Hinata!
You can do it!
-When the preliminaries
ended I was finally
able to like myself a little.
[whimpering]
-I never go back on my
word, because that too
is my nindo, my ninja way.
And you can't take it from me.
To anybody else it might look
like absolutely nothing's
changed about me,
but I feel different,
like I'm a better person now.
And I've been thinking that it
was all thanks to you Naruto.
-Hinata.
You really-- Do you really
believe that's true?
I may look strong to
you, but all I ever do
is mess things up.
I act tough because
I'm so frustrated.
But underneath it all I just
feel like I'm a huge failure.
-No, that's not true!
-Hm?
-Even when you messed up
you were always a-- um,
how can I say this?
A proud failure from
my point of view.
-Huh?
-When I look at you,
you just fill me
with such-- such admiration.
I'm not saying that
you're perfect.
I mean, no one is.
But when you do
make a mistake you
have the guts to pick
yourself up and keep trying.
I think that courage,
to keep going no matter,
is what real strength is.
I just think you're an
incredibly strong person
Naruto.
-Thanks Hinata.
I needed that.
Even though I'm completely
used to being the underdog,
I get this time I was just
really feeling the strain.
I was really down, which
isn't like me at all.
But I feel 100% better now.
-I'm glad you do.
-All right.
I'm off to the match!
Thanks again.
Hinata.
-Huh?
-I kind of thought
you were-- um--
-What?
What?
-Gloomy, timid,
always terrified,
and basically completely weird.
[gong]
-Oh.
-But you know what?
I actually like people like you.
People like you
[echoes] Oh yeah.
Don't forget to come
watch me wipe up
the floor with Neji in
the final competition.
[fireworks]
-Huh?
Oh no.
I gotta get going, and fast.
Oh man!
I'm going to be late.
See you later Hinata!
-Hey, Hinata.
Sorry I'm so late.
Aw well.
Shino's match isn't
til later anyway.
Hey, what's with you?
[footsteps]
-Hm?
What?
What is it?
[fireworks]
-Oh, it's starting.
NARUTO: Move!
Move!
Look out!
Get out of the way!
I'm in a hurry!
Oh man, it's still so far away.
There's no way I'll
make it in time.
-Hey, Naruto!
NARUTO: Konohamaru?
-My friend needs help.
Check it out.
See?
-Konohamaru, what are
you talking about?
What are you up to?
-No time to explain.
Just come on.
Well, actually I
guess there is time.
There's a great
shortcut up here that
goes straight to the arena!
-There is?
Awesome!
Thank you Konohamaru!
-It's said that those who
control the secret path
control time.
-Whatever that means.
But still, you're
awesome Konohamaru.
-As I recall, there's a hole
in the wall around here.
Ah, here it is.
Doh!
NARUTO: What?
What's the matter?
-The shortcut got a
little longer I guess.
-Gah!
That's great.
I'm almost out of time now.
-No wait.
There's another way.
-No!
I can't take anymore chances.
I'm already late.
-He-he, he-he.
This is a sure thing.
It's a secret, but
there's an awesome path
that can get you to the
arena in an instant.
I swear!
-What?
All right!
Nice one Konohamaru.
Really?
This hole is a shortcut.
-Yeah, it's a straight
shot to the arena.
I told you this
one's a sure thing.
-Straight shot huh?
OK.
Let's do this.
-Right!
[screaming]
-Konohamaru, what's
going on here?
-Don't worry.
It's OK.
We're almost to the
final competition arena.
See, there's the
exit right there!
[laughing]
-Huh?
[mumbling]
[splash]
-Hot, hot, hot,
hot, hot, hot, hot!
-Now, just hold on.
This isn't my fault.
It's a mistake.
-What have you done Konohamaru?
And why did we
come out of a tree?
And now we're even further
away than we were before.
-Just wait.
I swear that tunnel
used to come out right
at the final competition arena.
There has to be another way.
Let's see.
Uh, oh!
And there it is!
-Huh?
-Just ride this guy here,
and you'll get to the arena
before you even know it.
-Seriously?
A bull?
-Not just any bull.
The feudal lords'
bulls aren't just
like ordinary, everyday cows.
They're like super bulls!
Once these bulls
start running even
race horses grow deathly afraid.
They know there's no way they
can beat a feudal lord's bull.
Yep, that's one awesome animal.
[grumbling]
-Naruto, if you leave
everything up to this bull
you're going to be at
the arena in no time.
-I'm counting on you bull.
OK.
Let's go!
[moo]
[grunts and groans]
-Ouch.
[moaning]
-Huh?
[trumpets]
[countdown timer beeps]
[countdown timer -go]
-Oh no!
[moo]
-Whoa, whoa.
Nice bull.
-Naruto, good luck
in your fight!
[moo]
NARUTO: Whoa, stay back.
Come on.
Easy.
[panting]
-Look at this.
We're missing quite
a few people here.
-What's going on?
Where is everyone?
This is about to get started.
-Yeah, what's going on?
Sasuke and even Naruto
are nowhere to be seen.
[stampeding bulls]
-Ah!
Why does this
always happen to me?
-Huh?
Whoa!
[panting]
-This is not good!
Wait.
That's it.
Shadow Clone jutsu.
All right guys, scatter all
these stampeding bulls for me.
-Yeah!
[moo]
[panting]
[screaming]
-Hey, what happened?
Why did you guys come back?
You were supposed to get
rid of all those bulls.
-We tried, but more
of them showed up.
We couldn't escape.
-Great.
That was pointless.
All right, just run!
[screaming]
-Hm?
What's that?
-Naruto Uzumaki?
-It's up to you guys now.
[shouting and clamouring]
-Stop.
It's too late to enter.
[moo]
[screaming]
[crowd gasps]
-He sure knows how to make
an entrance, the idiot.
-Naruto!
-Yeah, but he's totally
late, of course.
[grunting]
-Oh man, what a drag.
[groaning]
-Ah!
Guys, run!
You won't believe
this, but there's
a huge herd of stampeding
bulls coming this way?
-What?
Yeah, you're right.
I don't believe it.
-I'm serious.
There mus be a million of
them coming right this way.
Hm?
Hey, wait.
Where's Sasuke?
-I'm fighting Dosu,
but he's missing too.
-Hey, knock it off.
Quit your fidgeting you two.
Stand up straight and
present yourself proudly
to the spectators.
-Huh?
[crowd cheers]
-You guys are the heroes
of this final competition.
[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
All right, Hinata.
You want to watch me fight?
Then watch me defeat
this big jerk.
He thinks that a
person's destiny
can't be changed, that one's
fate is decided at birth.
Give me a break.
People can definitely change,
and by defeating this guy
I'm going to prove that.
Next time, Byakugan
vs. Shadow Clone Jutsu.
Believe it!
I'm going to win,
no matter what!
[theme music]