[music playing]
[singing in Japanese]
[tick tock]
IBIKI MORINO: Now
that we've weeded out
most of the hopeless
cases, 15 minutes to go.
Time for the main event.
All right, listen up.
Here's the 10th
and final question.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Here we go.
Everything's riding on this one.
Believe it.
NARUTO: The Tenth
Question, All or Nothing.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): Man,
this guy is full of himself.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): This is it.
The final obstacle.
TEMARI (VOICEOVER):
Hurry up, Kankuro.
What good is your
cheat sheet going
to be if you miss
the 10th question?
-But before I give
you the question
there are some more rules
that you need to be aware of.
-Huh?
-Ah, made it just in time.
I hope you found your trip
to the bathroom enlightening.
-He's seen through
the crow's disguise.
He's on to us.
-Well, take your seat.
These rules are
unique to question 10.
Listen carefully and try not
to let them frighten you.
-It's quiet without
the rookies around.
I almost miss 'em.
-Don't worry.
Chances are they'll be back
again sooner than you think.
-Why's that?
-I heard that their first
examiner this year is Ibiki.
So, already their chances
of passing look iffy.
Great, sticking them with
that sadist right off the bat.
-What sadist?
[laughs]
-I forgot you're a
new Jonin, Kurenai.
Otherwise, you wouldn't
have to ask that.
-So I'm ignorant.
Who he is?
-He's what you might
call a specialist.
-Oh yeah?
In what?
-Interrogation.
Torture.
Oh, of course, he won't
be using physical torture
during the test
He won't need to.
That's not really
his thing, anyway.
He works on people's
minds, not their bodies.
He's famous for it.
Everyone knows about the
head of the Anbu Torture
and Interrogation Corps for
the Hidden Leaf Village.
Ibiki Morino.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): If
even the rules are scary,
[gulps]
What's the question like?
-Very well then.
Rule number one.
Each of you is
free to choose not
to be given the final question.
It's your decision.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): Say what?
We're free to chose?
-Whoa.
So what's the catch?
Let's say we decide we
don't want to do it.
What happens then?
-If you choose not to
take the 10th question,
regardless of your
answers to the other nine,
you'll get a zero.
In other words, you fail.
And that means, of course, both
your teammates fail as well.
[panicked whispering]
-Not so fast.
You didn't let me finish.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): More rules?
Enough already.
-If you do accept the question
but answer it incorrectly,
you will not only
fail, you will be
barred from taking the
Chunin exam ever again!
KIBA: Hey, that's bull, man!
That's ridiculous.
What kind of bogus rule is that?
There's lots of people here
who've taken the test before.
[quack]
[laughs]
-I guess you're just unlucky.
I wasn't making the rules
before, but I am now.
Of course, if you don't want
to take it, you don't have to.
If you're not feeling confident,
then by all means, skip it.
You can come back and
try again next year.
[laughs]
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Thanks a lot.
So if any one of us chooses to
skip it, then all three of us
fail.
Forget it!
That's not going to happen.
But the other hand,
you only get one shot.
Screw up and you'll
never get another chance.
Either way, it stinks.
This is so unfair.
Why couldn't they just
give us a normal test?
-Now then, if you're ready.
The 10th and final question.
Those who don't want to
take it, raise your hand.
Your number will be recorded
and then you're free to go.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): What
could the question be?
What if it's easy?
What if it's not?
If I get it wrong, I'll be a
Genin for the rest of my life,
the way things are going.
But I can't just skip
it, then we all fail.
I can't do that to the others.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Well, I'm OK.
He's not getting
me to chicken out.
No way I'm raising my hand.
Oh, but what about Naruto?
He doesn't stand a chance.
Go on, Naruto, put your hand up.
It's OK.
Don't worry about us.
There's always next year.
Just think of yourself.
-I'm out.
That's it.
I'm out.
I just can't do it.
I'm sorry.
IBIKI MORINO: Number 50.
Fail!
Number 130.
Number 110.
That means you're out too.
-Gennai, Inaho, I'm sorry guys.
I'm sorry.
-That's it.
I quit.
-Me too, sir.
I'm out.
-I'm out.
-Me too.
-I'm so gone.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Go on, Naruto.
Why don't you raise your hand?
Naruto.
-Someday, I'm going
to be a Hokage
and you'll look up to me.
My name's Naruto Uzumaki.
Remember it!
Ah!
Shut up!
I'm willing to do
anything to become Hokage
no matter what it takes!
To be the greatest Hokage.
Then the whole village
will stop disrespecting me
and start treating me like I'm
somebody, somebody important.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Hokage, Hokage.
He has a one track mind.
That dream's all he's got.
It would kill him to have
it taken away forever.
But he's too stubborn
to raise his hand.
I can't let you do it
to yourself, Naruto.
ASUMA: You see, this guy, Ibiki,
he's a master of interrogation
because he understands
how the human mind works.
He knows just where to probe
to uncover your weaknesses.
The thing is he's
so good at his job,
he doesn't use physical torture.
He doesn't need to.
He just messes up your head
so bad, you torture yourself.
-Don't underestimate me!
I don't quit and don't run.
You can act tough all you want.
Your guys aren't
going to scare me off.
No way!
I don't care if I do
get stuck as a Genin
for the rest of my life.
I'll still be Hokage someday.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): He's
completely clueless,
but he's still going for it.
The kid's got guts,
I'll give him that.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Way to
go, you crazy little fool.
-This decision is one that
could change your life.
If for any reason you
would rather quit,
now's your last chance.
-No way.
I never go back on my word.
That's the way of the ninja.
IBIKI (VOICEOVER): Remarkable.
That little outburst has given
the others some backbone.
He's inspired them into staying.
78 left.
More than I expected.
But I don't see anyone wavering.
I think that's it.
Well, then, I admire your
determination, if nothing else.
For those of you
remaining there's
only one thing left to do.
And that's for me to
tell you that you've all
passed the first exam.
-Huh?
-Hold on!
What just happened?
What do you mean we passed?
Where's the 10th question?
[laughs]
-There never was one.
Not a written one, at least.
Actually your
decision to stay was
the answer to the 10th question.
-Huh?
Wait a second.
So the other nine
questions you gave
us were just a waste of time.
Is that what you're saying?
-No, no, not at all.
Quite the opposite.
The first nine questions had an
important overriding purpose--
to test your ability to
surreptitiously gather
strategic intelligence under
the most adverse circumstances.
-Oh, well that
clears up everything.
-Let me explain.
You see, my objective
was to test you
not only as individuals,
but as a team,
and on how well you function
as a part of that team.
That's why the test was
scored on a team basis,
so you'd know that everything
you did, or failed to do,
would directly affect
your teammates.
I wanted to see how you'd
handle the pressure.
-Mmm-hmm.
Yeah, I figured it was
something like that.
That's why I kept my cool.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Yeah, right.
[giggles]
-The first nine questions
on the test were difficult.
In fact, as you
may have realized,
too difficult for any Genin
to be expected to solve.
I imagine that
most of you quickly
came to that
conclusion, that you'd
have to cheat if you had
any chance of passing.
The fact is the test was
designed to encourage cheating.
It almost demanded it.
Of course, it would have
done you little good
unless you had someone to
cheat from so I disguised
two Chunin who already
knew the answers
and had them sit in with you.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Ah!
The answers were right in
front of me the whole time!
-What is that kid's problem?
-I don't know.
-Hahaha.
Oh, come on, I wasn't
fooled for a second.
You had to be a complete
fool to not to see.
Isn't that right, Hinata?
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): Incredible.
So all the time he never knew.
-Those who were
caught at it failed.
Better not to cheat
then to cheat clumsily.
Information.
It can be the most
valuable weapon in battle.
How well you gather
intelligence can
determine whether a mission's
a failure or a success.
They'll be times you'll have
to risk your life to get it.
-Man, what a mess.
Scars and puncture
wounds, burn marks.
What he must have endured.
-Of course, you
must always consider
the source of your information.
Intelligence gathered
from an enemy
is not necessarily accurate.
Always bear this in mind.
Disinformation can be worse
than no information at all.
It can lead to the
death of comrades
or the loss of a village.
That's why I put
you in the position
where you had to gather
accurate intelligence.
Cheat in order to survive.
And that's why those who
weren't good enough at it
were weeded out,
leaving the rest of you.
-OK, but I'm still not
getting what the 10th question
thing is all about.
-You're not?
The 10th question was the
main point of the whole exam.
Surely, you see that.
-Sure.
But explain it anyway.
-As I said before, the
goal was to test you
not only as individuals
but as part of a squad.
The final question gave you
two choices, both difficult.
You could choose to play it
safe and skip the question,
though it meant that both
you and your teammates
would be failed.
Or you could try and answer it,
knowing if you got it wrong,
you would lose your chance
of ever being Chunin.
It was a no-win situation.
But just the sort Chunin have
to face almost every day.
For example, let me give
you a hypothetical mission.
To steal a document from
an enemy stronghold.
You have no idea how
many ninja the enemy has
or how heavily armed they are.
Furthermore, you have reason to
believe that the enemy expects
you, that you might very well
be walking blindly into a trap.
Now do you have the
option of taking
a pass on this insane
mission or say my comrades
and I would rather live
to fight another day?
Can you choose to avoid danger?
No.
There will be many
missions that will
seem almost suicidal
if you think about it.
But you do not think about it.
You think only of the
goal, and of achieving it
through courage and discipline.
These are the qualities required
of a Chunin squad leader.
Those who choose the
safer of two paths,
those whose
determination falters
in the face of adversity, those
who would put their comrades
lives in jeopardy by
worrying about their own,
those who would
save their own necks
at the price of sacred
honor will never
be able to call themselves
Chunin at least as long time
as I'm here.
As for the rest of you,
you have successfully
answered the 10
questions I put to you.
You have earned the right to
continue on to the next step.
You have passed
through the first gate.
I hereby declare this part
of the Chunin selection
exam completed.
There's nothing left, but
to wish you all good luck.
-All right!
We did it!
That's one down!
Yeah!
Woohoo!
IBIKI (VOICEOVER): He's
a funny one, that kid.
[crash]
-Is this part of the test?
IBIKI (VOICEOVER):
Jumped the gun as usual.
ANKO: Heads up, boys and girls.
This is no time
to be celebrating.
I'll be your next
proctor, Anko Mitarashi.
You ready for the second test?
Good!
Then, let's go.
Follow me!
-You're early again.
[faint laughter]
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Great.
Screaming nutcase.
She reminds me of Naruto.
-How many are there?
Ibiki, you let all
these guys pass?
Your test was too easy.
You must be getting soft.
-Or it could be a stronger
crop of candidates this year.
-Hmm.
They sure don't look it.
Trust me, before I'm done
with them, more than half
will be eliminated.
-Huh?
More than half?
Really?
-This is going to be a fun.
All right, you maggots
have had it easy so far,
but things are going
to be different
starting first thing
in the morning.
I'll let your squad leaders
know where you're to meet me.
Dismissed.
[laughter]
-I just passed a
candidate who didn't
answer a single question.
Naruto Uzumaki.
He's a funny one, all right.
-Whoa, nice place.
What is it?
-This is the location for
the second phase of the exam.
It's the 44th Battle
Training Zone.
But we call it the
Forest of Death.
-Forest of Death?
[music playing]
NARUTO: I passed the first
exam and I didn't even
break a sweat.
I'm one step closer to being
Hokage and I've got momentum.
Nothing can stop me now.
Hey!
What are these guys doing here?
This is the Chunin exams, not
some nursery school field trip.
Next time.
Special Report.
Live from the Forest of Death.
OK, so maybe it won't
be easy as I thought.