[theme music]
[eerie groaning]
[growl]
-Huh?
Sorry about that.
Ah, for the love
of-- you didn't?
I guess not.
I could still use
a shower though.
I really worked
up a sweat today.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): "The
Legend from the Hidden Leaf,
the Onbaa."
-Nothing beats hard
work and elbow grease.
Huh?
[barking]
-What's up?
Why all the barking?
-He says you kind
of reek, Naruto.
You been skipping
bath time lately?
-Hey, you watch it, bub.
I'm not in the mood, OK?
-Seriously, you stink.
-Oh, right I forgot
about that eagle.
Oh hey, Sakura.
-Well, well.
Hey there lazy bones.
I heard you haven't
got a mission.
-It's not like I'm
just lounging around.
-No kidding, you've really
been going at it, huh?
You ripped your pants.
-Huh?
Where?
Oh, you're right.
I didn't even notice.
-Ah, hopeless as ever.
You can bring them by later.
I'll stitch them up for you.
-Like, for real?
You mean it?
I can't believe how kind
you're being to me, Sakura.
That may be the
nicest thing you've
offered to do for me
my whole entire life.
-All right, all right.
Don't get carried away.
Naruto!
-Wait!
I don't understand.
What did I do?
-You just put your
hands on me, didn't you?
-Of course not.
I wouldn't do that.
-And what about those grubby
little paws sticking out
of your pockets, huh?
Wait.
What the--
-Huh?
Ah.
-Check your back.
-Ah!
What the heck is that thing?
-Onbaa.
Onbaa.
-What did that eagle eat?
-There's some kind of creature
on your back, you idiot.
-What is it?
Some kind of caterpillar?
-Get it off.
Get it off.
Nah, it's not a bug.
It's a little animal.
It doesn't want to let go.
-Onbaa.
Onbaa.
-Ah, why does this happen to me?
-Hm.
I don't suppose any
of you have ever
been told the
legend of the Onbaa?
-Onbaa?
It's not ringing any bells.
-You're familiar with
it, aren't you Shizune?
-Sorry.
How old a story are
we talking about here?
Something out of folklore?
-Well, that's what
I always figured.
A long time ago, when I
was still a little girl,
I was told of a legend, the
tale of a dangerous bearlike
creature known as
an Onbaa living
in the mountains
near our village.
Then one day, that
little idiot, Jiraiya,
pledged to spend him summer
break studying the creature
and headed off into
the woods like a loon.
-The Pervy Sage did?
-Yep.
-What are you, deranged?
You don't seriously believe
there's an Onbaa out there,
do you?
-Well, we'll just see,
won't we, once I've
completed my investigation.
-Whatever.
Even if there was
an Onbaa out there,
it wouldn't want
anything to do with you.
-What do you know, you
billboard of a female?
-I'm not a billboard, you jerk.
And there's no such
thing as a stupid Onbaa.
-Yeah?
You want to bet on it?
-Sure thing, pipsqueak.
-I'm betting on
Jiraiya this time.
-OK, guys.
I'm off to wrestle me an Onbaa.
-So did Pervy Sage ever
find one of them or not?
-He returned to the
village three days later
and said he'd won
through a ring out move.
The little liar.
Aw, there it is.
-What am I looking at?
That's the worst
handwriting I've ever seen.
-Oh, like you're one
to talk, you dummy.
-Let's see now.
Onbaa big, about nine feet tall.
When these frightening
beasts get angry,
no one can match them, but
I beat one at wrestling.
Are you kidding me?
Onbaa children are
carried piggyback.
This is how they are raised.
Ah!
-I thought his little
chronicle was hogwash
ripped from the
pages of the legend.
Although, seeing is
believing, I guess.
-That's great and
all, but can we
get back to my problem
for a second here?
He's stuck to my back like glue.
-Oh, right.
Well, let's see,
according to legend,
the Onbaa offspring
consider the first thing
they see as their
mother, and will
cling to that creature's
back exclusively.
They supposedly ride around
in this unusual fashion
until they've reached
full maturity.
But before that
fateful day arrives,
the two are never separated.
-I guess you're just going
to have to wait for it
to grow up, Naruto.
-Oh, yeah, that's
an awesome idea.
What the heck am I gonna
do when this thing is
a nine foot tall behemoth?
-Ah.
-Oh, that's great you guys.
Thanks a lot for the support.
-Relax, it's just a legend.
I'm sure you'll be fine.
-I don't find that
very reassuring.
-Onbaa.
Onbaa.
-Hang in there, Naruto.
-We'll be on the
sidelines cheering for ya.
-Well, feel free to come
join me on the field!
What are you doing?
-I will not be out done.
-This isn't a weight, you know.
Spill it, Hinata.
What's up?
-Uh, well, it's just I
heard this weird rumor.
-Really?
How weird?
-People are saying, well,
you have a baby with you.
-Oh, you mean this guy?
-Onbaa.
Onbaa.
-Oh.
-Huh?
Hinata.
Hey, are you OK?
Hinata, speak to me.
-Onbaa.
-Ah
-What the-- Hinata!
-Onbaa.
-You don't like it?
What are ya, a gourmet?
[running water]
-Ah!
I get the feeling
I'll be spending
a lot of time in the tub.
-Onbaa.
Onbaa.
-You know, we don't
allow pets in here, son.
I'm sorry.
The health department is
pretty strict about it.
-I missed out on dinner because
of the little fuzz bucket.
Just this once, OK?
-He sure is a cute little
fella, I'll give you that.
-Yeah.
You got a name for
your friend there.
-Onbaa.
Onbaa.
-That's about all he says, I
guess we should go with that.
-Onbaa, huh?
-He looks like he's
eyeballing your soup.
-Huh?
-Onbaa.
-One side of fishcake, old man.
-Coming up.
[growling]
-Ever since Onbaa
latched onto my back,
I get all the cushiest
jobs in the village.
Seems like a good deal to me.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): He's
bigger now, and so quickly.
This is bad.
-All right, Naruto,
your current mission
is to get rid of the
mountain bandits holed up
in the Yamabuki Pass.
-What?
All of them?
Come on, grandma, you're only
trying to get rid of Onbaa
now that he's getting
bigger, right?
-No, of course, not.
It's just I been keeping
an eye on you lately.
I'm impressed with the
amount of growth I've seen.
-OK, so who am I going away?
TSUNADE: No, no, no, I think a
solo recon will be sufficient.
This is what you were
talking about, after all.
-You want him out of here, I
see the writing on the wall.
-Onbaa.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): It's
all in fate's hands now.
-Come on, let's
get back to work.
-Gee, Mister, thanks a lot.
Na- Na- Naruto.
Naruto.
Boy, Onbaa, I sure am having
a blast hanging out with you.
Forget that old
stick in the mud,
if grandma thinks she can
split us up now, she's crazy.
I'll wipe the floor
with those bandits
so we can finish up the mission
and return to the Hidden Leaf
Village with our
heads held high.
Does that sound like a plan?
-Onbaa.
-All right, you
bandits, open up!
-Who are you, you little snot?
-Yeah, kid.
-What are you doing here?
-You're looking at
Naruto Uzumaki and Onbaa.
You jerks ready?
-Say what?
-Kill him!
-Shadow clone jutsu.
-Onbaa.
-Onbaa!
That may have just been
a clone, but anyone
who lays a hand on Onbaa
is gonna answer to me.
How bout it?
You had enough yet?
-Onbaa.
-Thanks, buddy.
That was a close call.
Onbaa, you really
saved me there.
I owe you one.
-Onbaa.
-Now, let's get
back to the village.
Wait till they here how you did.
Onbaa, I don't care
what anyone says,
there's no way you're a
threat to the Hidden Leaf.
You and I will be
like Kiba and Akamaru.
The Naruto Onbaa duo,
joined at the hip.
What the heck was that?
-Onbaa.
-Hey, don't you worry, buddy.
I'll take care of you.
Onbaa, is that thing
Is that your mother chasing us?
Why she so mad?
Ah, I didn't steal him, I swear!
Hey, come on, say
something, will ya?
-Onbaa.
-Are you crazy?
What are you doing?
You've got the wrong idea.
Onbaa, this is your mother.
Give her a hug or
something and quick.
You don't understand!
Ah!
-Onbaa.
Onbaa.
-Onbaa?
-Aw.
-Onbaa.
Onbaa.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
All right, I've
had just about enough of this.
I mean, if you're a
mother, you should
have taken better
care of your kids.
-Look, lady, you
don't have to worry.
I'm giving Onbaa
back to you, OK?
Huh?
Why am I so light?
Onbaa, you got so
big all of a sudden.
Hey, uh, come on, talk to me.
What's wrong?
This can't be happening.
Wait a minute,
Onbaa, it's me, OK?
Just take it easy.
I mean, you and I are
like two peas in a pod.
Come on, Onbaa,
you can remember.
Look, it's your old
pal, Naruto Uzumaki.
He gave you all the fishcake.
Fishcake, your favorite.
That stuff that
looked like this.
You see?
Ring any bells for ya?
Come on, buddy, it's me, Naruto.
Don't you remember
riding on my back?
We went everywhere together.
[growl]
-I guess this is it.
Huh?
-Onbaa.
-I don't know about
you, but I'm bushed.
Comfy.
I could lie here forever.
Best piggyback
ride I've ever had.
Onbaa.
So long, Onbaa!
Enjoy your new life
with your mother, OK?
Okie dokie.
You should see the
look on your face.
-The Onbaa are no longer
a legend, are you happy?
They're mating like rabbits in
the woods outside the village,
and the eagles are scooping
them up and dropping them here.
-Onbaa.
-Naruto, how do you get
rid of these things?
Tell me.
-Hard to say, there was a
bit of wrestling involved.
Maybe you should try that?
-Don't screw with me.
The village will be
buried at this rate.
-Onbaa.
Onbaa.
TSUNADE: Spill it, Naruto!
NARUTO: Don't look at me.
[theme music]
NARUTO: Me and Shino
had to go settle
a dispute over some
dead guy's will.
On the way there,
this creepy old lady
appeared on the road and
muttered, even the dead laugh
in Motoyoshi Village.
We had no idea what we were
getting ourselves into.
The stuff we saw there, it makes
my blood run cold just talking
about it.
Next time, "Laughing Shino."
I can't even go to the
bathroom alone at night.