THEME SONG: [singing japanese]
-The melody is a Ninjutsu?
-That's right!
I had so much power, my whole
body was coursing with chakra!
That's one heck of a tune!
-That's an unusual jutsu.
Shizune, have we identified the
one who assailed the villagers?
-No, ma'am.
We're still working on it.
-Menma, I have actually heard
of a power similar to your own.
-Huh?
-Wait.
Is that true, Grandma?
-I'm fairly certain the
Land of Rice Paddies
dabbles in music-based jutsu.
-Wait.
You mean the Land
of Rice Paddies?
-Oh!
You know, now that I think about
it, the mountain stream where
Naruto found Menma was
over in that region.
-Really?
Please, I beg of you.
You must allow me
to return there.
Please!
-Menma, intruding on their
land without a good cause--
-Ha!
I'd say we got plenty of cause.
After all, we might
just find the key
that finally unlocks
his memories over there.
So I second that request.
-Hmph.
Very well, then.
-All right, Grandma!
I knew you wouldn't let us down.
-Thank you so much.
Huh.
-Hee!
-Well, we're off.
We'll be out on the
road for a little bit.
-Business as usual.
Well, at least those
pickled bamboo shoots
will be ready for you
when you get back.
-Save me a big old bowl, OK?
Later!
-You guys didn't have
to come, you know.
We would've been fine.
-It's not like we had a choice.
We're on job here.
-We were told to accompany you.
That is the mission.
-Hmm.
-So it's all settled.
Come on, Menma.
The Land of Rice Paddies
is waiting for us.
-Right.
-Naruto.
-Uh huh.
-I'd like a word with you.
-Hmm?
All right, then, Grandma.
What's up?
-If you call yourself a shinobi,
you should already know.
-What?
-I'm talking about Menma.
If that kid turns
out to be a member--
-I vouch for him.
He's OK, all right?
-I know he's not a bad person.
But can you be 100%
sure he isn't a spy?
-Where are you're going
with all this, Grandma?
-This is the Land of Rice
Paddies, the home to the Hidden
Sound Village.
Have you forgotten
about Orochimaru?
-Orochimaru.
Yeah, I know.
I haven't forgotten.
-Menma's jutsu is strikingly
similar to that of the opponent
Shikamaru fought when
Sasuke was taken.
We can't afford to ignore
the possibility he's
affiliated with
the Hidden Sound.
If he were to
remember something,
and the village was in
danger because of it--
-There's no way
Menma is an enemy.
I'd stake my life on it.
-You don't want to get
left behind, do you?
-I'll be up ahead.
[sighing]
-Are you hurt?
-No, thanks to you.
-You were going a
little too fast there.
-We'll take a rest here.
[sighing]
-Come on, spill it.
What's eating you?
-Who on earth is
this boy, Naruto?
-Well, how the
heck should I know?
That's why we're on
this mission, isn't it?
-I was moving at full speed
when that happened back there,
and losing my footing
was no accident, either.
-Huh?
-Not only could
he match my speed,
but he was swift
enough to catch me.
He shouldn't be as
quick as we are.
-What if he turns those
powers of us against us?
-Wha-- hey, hold
on a second, here.
Menma isn't our enemy.
He risked his life
to save a baby.
All this guy does
all day is help
people, morning,
noon, and night, OK?
Sounding good over here.
-Thanks.
And by the way, I never thanked
you for fixing this, did I?
-Please.
Don't even worry about it.
-Hey.
Not another breath, do you hear?
I'm warning you.
-Neji, what the
heck are you doing?
-Quiet, Naruto.
-(ANGRILY) Come again?
-Neji's right, Naruto.
That could have been some
kind of signal to the enemy.
-A signal?
-We still haven't
caught that guy
who was sneaking
around the village.
That was the whole reason Lady
Tsunade approved this mission.
Whoever this creep is,
if he's following Menma,
we can be pretty certain
he's somewhere nearby.
-You're kidding.
-Though he hasn't yet
revealed his presence to us,
our mission is to
accompany Naruto, find out
who this person is, and then
capture him, plain and simple.
And I'm sorry, but at this
point, I don't trust you.
-That's all right.
It's only natural
you feel this way.
And now that you
mention it, I don't even
know what kind of person I am.
What would I do if it turned
out I was a terrible person?
What kind of person would
you want to be, Naruto?
You know, if you were reborn.
-Where's this coming from?
-I was just wondering.
-Hmm.
Don't know.
I never really thought about it.
-I gotcha.
-Wait a sec.
What are you asking that for?
-Uh, it's nothing.
-What's the matter?
-What am I smelling?
[sniffing]
-Hey, you're right.
It smells like
something's burning.
-Over there!
-Let's go.
-Well, here's what
we were smelling.
I wonder what happened here.
[groaning]
-You doing OK?
-Oh.
Uh, it's nothing.
-Don't move, or I'll fire.
-(ANGRILY) What the heck
is your problem, pal?
-You another bunch of
their underlings, then?
-Whose?
-If you're part of their
brood, you'll die here.
-I don't even know who the
heck you're talking about.
-If you're not one of
them, then prove it.
-We're shinobi of
the Leaf Village.
That's not proof enough?
-The Leaf Village?
-See?
Right up here.
-Well, so you are.
What business does the
Leaf have in these parts?
-None, really.
We just happened to be
passing through this area.
-As you can see, there
isn't anything left here.
If you don't need
anything, then beat it.
I can't guarantee your safety.
-Well, what's it got
to be like that for?
He's the one going
picking fights.
Once we taken a
breather for a while,
how about we get
out here and start
looking for Menma's memories?
-Uh, right.
-What is it?
Did you remember something?
-No.
-You may as well come out.
-Well, hello there.
-Yeah.
You guys are ninja, aren't you?
I overheard you
talking back there.
-No kidding.
I don't want to brag or
nothing, but it just so
happens you're talking to Naruto
Uzumaki of the Hidden Leaf
Village.
-Oh, really?
Um, sorry.
I didn't know.
-So why did you follow us?
-I had a favor to ask you.
That was actually my
brother you were talking to.
-Your brother?
-That jerk from earlier?
-Our village is in great danger.
We need someone to
help us save it.
-Someone to save your village?
-What do you mean?
-We were once the Land
of Rice Paddies' border.
However, so much
trouble has originated
in this corner of the
country that our village
and the surrounding areas
have all been demilitarized.
-So, wait.
You're talking about--
-It probably has to
do with Orochimaru.
Because of the
Sound's involvement,
the whole region
has been punished.
-But at least there
can't be disputes
over territory anymore.
Isn't that a good thing?
-You'd thing.
-But that isn't
the case, though.
There's a small mine
out past the village
that produces a little gold.
Once people realized it was out
of the Land of Rice Paddies'
jurisdiction, the bandits came.
No matter how many times we
pleaded with the feudal lord,
he would always insist that
the nation's treaties couldn't
be broken.
-Then the village-- it was
attacked by bandits, right?
-They actually just took
off a little while ago
when a big storm hit the area.
But there's no question
they'll be back.
I beg you, please
save our village.
You guys could handle them.
I'm sure of it.
-Right.
You can count us in!
-I'm sorry.
We'd like to assist
you here, but we can't.
-Are you kidding?
How come we can't help them out?
-We're in the middle
of a mission, Naruto.
Without a direct order from the
village, our hands are tied.
-Yeah, but--
-Besides, we don't even know
when they're coming back.
It's not like we can just
wait around here forever.
-That's great.
-All right, then.
-Ran, what are you
and Fuki doing here?
-Nan!
-Stay away from these guys.
There's no such thing
as a good ninja.
-You sure about that?
-I'm just speaking the truth.
Rumor is the guys who
attacked the village were
rogue ninjas from
the Hidden Sound.
-Huh?
You mean those
bandits are ninja?
-Come on.
Follow me.
Take a look.
-Are these--
-One third of the villagers
were killed in that last attack,
and half of the survivors have
abandoned their homes and fled.
-The rest of you
should evacuate, too.
-And go where?
Our ancestors lived here.
My people have been
cultivating this land for ages.
Why should we have
to go anywhere?
They brandish a sword, and we're
supposed to just cower in fear?
What would you have us do?
Flee the rest of our lives?
-Please, big brother.
You have to stop yelling.
You'll frighten Fuki.
-Forgive me.
I shouldn't have
shouted, I know.
This child's parents were
cut down in the raid,
and she hasn't spoken a
word since their death.
There's nowhere for
us to run, anyway.
Now, why don't you
disappear already?
We have no choice.
Come on.
We better get moving.
-I'm not going anywhere.
-Huh?
-If these people
are in trouble, I
want to try to
help them if I can.
-Menma, are you nuts?
You don't even
know what you'd be
up against with these bandits.
If you really want
to help, then we
should go back to the Hokage.
-We have no idea when
their next attack will be.
We don't have time to
return to the Leaf Village.
-Well, if you're
staying, so am I.
-Forget it.
It's beyond the
scope of our mission.
-It's not.
For some reason, I feel I
might remember something
in this place.
-Stop messing around
here, all right?
You expect us to believe that?
An hour ago, you couldn't
remember a thing.
-We don't have a choice, do we?
You heard the man.
We'll find answers here.
Besides, he just wants
to help these people.
You can't fault him
for that, really.
-Thanks, Naruto.
-Come on, Menma.
Let's go.
-Right.
-Naruto, wait a minute!
-We'll figure out a way to
deal with these bandits.
You guys just start heading
for the Leaf Village, OK?
-So what do we do here, Neji?
-We let them go.
It's highly unlikely the
villagers will accept them,
anyway.
-You do have a point.
-Looks like the other
side of the village
made it out unscathed.
-How are the two of us
going to protect this place?
-Well, we can build a wall along
this creek, and once it's up,
the water will act as a moat.
Then we can put up a
single makeshift bridge,
leaving only one way in.
-I get it.
-I don't really know how
effective this whole thing's
going to be, but it's
definitely worth a shot, right?
-Got it!
[straining]
-What are you doing here?
I thought I told
you two to get lost.
-Forget it.
We're not leaving, pal.
Get used to it.
-What did you say?
-We're trying to help.
All we want to do is
protect the village.
-Nobody asked you to do that.
This is our problem.
-Yeah, look, that's
great and all,
but you're not going to
put a stop to these guys
by skulking around and hiding.
-All right.
Let's prop it up.
-OK.
[grunting]
-Come on.
What do those two think they're
going to do on their own?
-OK.
I'm ready for you.
Let her rip.
-OK.
-Huh?
-Tenten!
You're still here?
-You know, a thank you'd
be nice once in awhile.
-Thank you, Tenten.
That was close.
-Now, come on.
Get a good grip on it this time.
-Oh.
Right.
[grunting]
-Oh.
Hey again.
For me?
That's nice of ya.
-Hi there.
We brought this, too.
I came to help.
-Thanks.
[music playing]
-Hmm.
-Gotcha!
[? ninjutsu! ?]
Just like before!
Neji, wait up.
-Catching him is within the
parameters of our mission,
is it not?
-Yeah.
But this guy's no joke.
Nuts!
That guy knows how
to make an exit.
Uh!
-Naruto!
The sound waves.
They're amplifying
the chakra in my body.
-With this jutsu backing me
up, that jerk is going down!
-This is for everyone.
Die!
-Meddling little fool!
-Menma, no!
You all right?
Talk to me!
-To the village.
Hurry.
-Menma, hang in there.
-Boiling water and alcohol.
-Right away.
-Are you going to
operate on him?
-I may not look it, but I have
had some medical training.
-We'll get you
through this, Menma.
Don't worry.
-What's wrong?
-There is no way in hell
I'm going to treat this guy.
-But why?
What's the matter?
-That mark.
He's in league with the people
who attacked this village.
THEME SONG: [singing japanese]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Menma
isn't a member of some gang.
I know it, OK?
You have to believe me.
This guy was willing
to throw his life away,
all to save a little kid.
He only lives to help people.
He worked his butt off for this
village, and no one even asked.
You don't know the
whole story here.
Now, please, you've
got to save him!
Next time, "A Past
To Be Erased."
THEME SONG: [singing japanese]