[theme music]
[grunts in pain]
-You're nothing.
-Stop right there!
Shadow clone jutsu!
-Oh, shadow clones.
And there's quite a few of them.
-Here we go.
[crashing sound]
-[yells]
-His skills are too advanced.
He's too powerful.
There' no way to defeat him.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
I'm not giving up.
I've still got this.
NARUTO: Sasuke!
-[yells] So that was your plan.
Not bad, Naruto.
-Huh?
-Demon wind shuriken,
windmill of shadows.
-[gasps]
-A shuriken?
You'll never touch me with that.
-[grunts]
-Hmm?
So you passed the clone
and aimed for my real body.
Smart.
But not smart enough.
Huh?
A second shuriken in
the shadow of the first.
The shadow shuriken jutsu.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): The
second shuriken's on target.
And he can't catch this one.
-I told you a shuriken
can't touch me.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
He dodged it!
-Hmm.
-[gasps]
-What?
-Eat this!
Kakashi, Sharingan Warrior.
-[grunts] Huh?
[grunts] [growls]
-[gasps]
-[growls]
-I'll destroy you.
[bell ringing sound]
-[grunts]
-[gasps]
-Kakashi Sensei.
KAKASHI: Naruto, that
was an excellent plan.
You've really
grown, haven't you?
--[laughs] I knew I couldn't
beat him with my shadow clones.
That was just to distract him.
While he fought the clones,
I turned into the demon wind
shuriken.
He didn't know what to do.
Believe it.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I
used one of the clones
to transform into the shuriken.
When I threw it to Sasuke, it
looked like a real shuriken.
NARUTO: Sasuke!
-[yells]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Sasuke could
tell it was me in a second.
He spun around so
no one could see
and pulled out his own shurken.
Now there were two shuriken.
One was real.
One was me.
-Demon wind shuriken,
windmill of shadows.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I hid in
the shadow of the real shuriken.
And my target was
the real Zabuza.
-Of course, I knew that I
couldn't fight Zabuza myself.
That wasn't in the game plan.
I just wanted to get in there
and breakup his water prison.
I didn't know his clone
would be wrecked too.
That was a bonus.
Believe it.
-Don't brag.
You just lucked out.
-The whole thing
was just a fluke.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): You
can call it a fluke,
but their teamwork was flawless.
They knew what to do without
even talking about it.
Most of the time, they act
like they hate each other.
And yet, they're a perfect team.
-I got distracted and lost
my grip on the water prison.
-Don't flatter yourself.
You weren't distracted.
You were forced to let go.
-Huh.
-Hmm.
-[chuckles]
-Your technique
worked on me once.
But it won't work again.
So what's it going to be?
-Sakura, you know what to do.
-[grunts]
-Huh?
-[grunting and groaning]
-[grunts]
-[gasps]
-The Sharingan.
-[speaking Japanese]
-(TOGETHER) [speaking Japanese]
-Tori!
Water style.
Water dragon jutsu.
-[yells]
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
Wow, so many hand signs.
And he mirrored them all
perfectly, instantly.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
What are they doing?
Is that a ninjutsu?
-[grunting]
ZABUZA (VOICEOVER):
Something isn't right.
-(TOGETHER) [speaking Japanese]
ZABUZA (VOICEOVER):
The Sharingan
can comprehend and replicate
the enemy's technique.
However--
-Tori!
Water style.
Water dragon jutsu.
ZABUZA (VOICEOVER): --both
jutsu occurred simultaneously.
Could he?
-[grunting]
ZABUZA (VOICEOVER): Could it be?
-[gasps]
-Huh.
Huh.
-He's not just following.
He moves the same
way at the same time.
-How's he doing that?
How, Sasuke?
ZABUZA (VOICEOVER):
My movements.
It's as if-- it's as
if he knows what I'm--
-Going to do next?
ZABUZA (VOICEOVER): What?
Is he reading my mind as well?
He looks at me with that eye.
-It makes you
furious, doesn't it?
-Huh.
All you're doing is
copying me like a monkey.
-(TOGETHER) You can't
beat me with cheap tricks.
I'll crush you.
-When I finish with
you, you'll never
open that monkey mouth again.
ZABUZA (VOICEOVER):
What is that?
It's me.
But how?
Is it his illusion jutsu?
-Water style.
Giant vortex jutsu.
-What?
Impossible!
[yells]
ZABUZA (VOICEOVER): I was
just about to create a vortex,
but he created one first.
[yells]
ZABUZA (VOICEOVER): He copies my
jutsu before I can even do it.
I can't keep up!
-[gasps]
-[coughs] [groans] [yells]
-You're finished.
ZABUZA: How?
Can you see into the future?
-Yes.
This is your last battle ever.
-[grunts]
-[gasps]
-[chuckles] You were right.
It was his last battle.
-Ah!
[growls]
-[gasps]
-No vital signs.
-Thank you.
I've been tracking
Zabuza for a long time,
waiting for this chance
to finally take him down.
-By your mask, I see
that you're a tracker
ninja from the Village
Hidden in the Mist.
-Impressive.
You're well informed.
-A tracker!
-Naruto, you don't
even know what that is.
You missed the lesson
on it, as usual.
Tracker ninja have
a special role.
Try coming to class some time.
SAKURA: When a rogue ninja
breaks away from his village,
he carries all kinds
of secrets with him,
the secrets of his people.
Trackers are specially trained
to hunt down these ninja
and eliminate them.
That way, the secrets of
their people remain secrets.
-That's correct.
I'm a member of
the elite tracking
unit of the Village
Hidden in the Mist.
It was my duty to stop Zabuza.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
From his size and voice,
he must be the
same age as Naruto.
Yet, he's an elite assassin?
He's no ordinary
kid, but what is he?
-[growls]
-What is this?
Who do you think you are?
Did you hear me?
-Easy, Naruto.
He's not our enemy.
-Huh?
That's not the point.
Did you see what he
did, just like that?
Zabuza was huge and powerful
like some kind of monster.
And this kid, who's
no bigger than me,
he brought down Zabuza with
one move like it was nothing.
I mean, what does that make us?
We're just fumbling around.
We don't know anything.
How can I accept that?
-Well, even if you
don't accept it,
still it did happen, Naruto.
In this world, there are
kids who are younger than you
and yet stronger than me.
-[grumbles]
-Your struggle is over for now.
I must deal with the remains.
There are many
secrets in this body.
They must not be allowed to
get into the wrong hands.
Please excuse me.
Farewell.
-He disappeared.
-Hmm.
He's gone, Naruto.
Let it go.
--[growls] What
are we doing here?
We're nothing!
I can't believe it!
-Naruto.
-As ninja, the things we
encounter are never easy.
Save you're anger
for the next enemy.
We haven't completed
our mission yet.
We still have to get
the bridge builder
to his bridge.
--[laughs] Sorry I caused
all this trouble for ya.
But you can rest at my house
when we get to the village.
-All right.
Let's get a move on.
-(TOGETHER) [gasps]
-[gasps]
-What?
What happened?
-Kakashi Sensei.
Kakashi Sensei!
[Music: Akeboshi, "Wind"]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
What do we do?
Kakashi Sensei is out cold.
And Gato's men are sure
to come looking for us.
How are we going to
fight them by ourselves?
We've got to train
to get stronger?
How's climbing trees
going to help us?
Well, if Kakashi Sensei
says it will work.
Next time, the Forest of Chakra.
I'll be kicking butt again.
Believe it.