[theme music]
SASUKE: Fire style,
Fireball-Jutsu!
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): How did he--
-What jutsu is that?
Blast.
Chidori, One Thousand Birds.
-I'll win no matter what!
-I'm not finished with you yet!
-Stop it!
NARUTO: Bitter Rivals
and Broken Bonds.
-What a peaceful little village.
Can't say much for
their security, though.
-Ha!
This village really ought
to be taught a lesson.
We could just stroll right in
there, and wipe them all out.
-Don't even start Sakon.
-That's right.
We're not here to
wipe anybody out.
-Aw, what's wrong
tubby, you scared?
Why don't you do us all a
favor, and go back to bed?
-All right, Tayuya.
Everybody, just calm down.
We all know what our
mission is, right?
We're here as an escort
for a very special guest.
-Stop, no!
-Damn!
-Can't stop.
-No!
-Kakashi-sensei.
-Naruto, was that
what I think it was?
[two crashes]
-What do you two think
you're doing, up here?
That was a little intense
for just a sparring match,
wasn't it?
What's wrong with you two?
-[grunting in pain]
No doubt about it, that
jutsu, it was the Rasengan.
But Naruto mastering that
jutsu, how is it impossible?
When were you thinking?
We really going to
kill him, Sasuke?
You've really got to watch this
sense of superiority you have.
That Chidori, it
was not the size
you'd aim at a comrade
from the leaf village.
When are you finally
going to grow up, Sasuke?
Did meeting up with
Itachi cause this?
-Sasuke.
SASUKE: Damn it!
Naruto, how far have you--
-[crying]
Kakashi-Sensei.
-Well, so much for teamwork.
I'm assuming it was you who
taught him that technique.
You don't think, maybe
he's a little young
to be handling that jutsu?
After all, he could
have killed Sasuke.
I know you want to protect
him from the Akatske,
but still to entrust him
with a jutsu like that.
-Aren't you a fine one to
talk, teaching the Chidori
to someone like Sasuke.
I knew he was a
hothead, but I never
imagined he'd be
willing to use a jutsu
that powerful against a
comrade from his own village.
Obviously, there's bad
blood between them.
But where in the world
does it come from?
-It's nothing we
haven't seen before.
-Meaning what?
-Oh come on, when
you think about it,
their relationship isn't
much different than the one
you had with Orochimaru
-Hm, I see.
-To Naruto, Sasuke is a comrade
and a rival at the same time.
In fact, it's the
competition between them
that keeps him going.
That's why he won't
stand for it when
Sasuke tries to belittle him.
He's been dogging Sasuke's
steps every inch of the way,
since their first
days at the academy.
-You're not hurt,
are you, scaredy-cat?
-Sasuke!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I'm
not gonna lose out to you.
-As far as Naruto is
concerned, what you and I think
doesn't matter.
There's only one person whose
approval he really cares about,
Sasuke.
On the other hand,
it's hard for Sasuke
to watch Naruto's
strength and skills
develop at such an
astonishing rate.
He's come along so
fast, Sasuke must
feel like he's standing still.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
You scaredy-cat,
Multi Shadowclone Jutsu!
Summoning Jutsu!
Naruto has something
powerful driving him on,
and so does Sasuke.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): I'm
going to restore my clan
and destroy a certain person.
-You mean revenge.
His hatred of Itachi may
be driving him on too fast.
-Sasuke can't acknowledge
Naruto's abilities.
He's afraid that if he
does acknowledge them,
he somehow diminishes his own.
It can be hard work
maintaining a rivalry.
-Well, it's not a
very healthy rivalry.
It's time I give
somebody a talking to.
-Right, I'll leave
Naruto to you, then.
Well, I have a mission, and then
there's that Chidori business.
Sakura, it'll be all right.
Don't you worry.
We'll soon have them back
to their old selves again.
Cheer up, OK?
I'll see you soon.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Thanks Kakashi-Sensei.
SAKURA: What is it Naruto?
-Listen Sakura,
this is between us.
Stay out of it.
-You're still too weak.
You don't have enough hate.
And you know something?
You never will.
SASUKE: What have I been doing?
What's it all been for?
SAKON: [laughs] I like
that look in his eyes.
All right then, shall we?
SASUKE: What's this all about?
-Sorry, but I knew you
wouldn't want to sit still
for a lecture, so, I figured
I had to pin you down.
-The one with him is Kakashi.
I've heard about him.
SASUKE: [scoffs]
-Let it go.
You've got to forget
about revenge.
-What?
-Believe me, in
this work, I've met
a lot of guys who
feel the way you do.
Trust me, for those who
follow the path of revenge it
never ends well.
You'll only tear yourself
apart, and even if you succeed,
and you get revenge,
what will you have then?
Nothing, emptiness.
-Shut up.
What makes you think you
know anything about it?
It's easy for you to talk.
You have no idea.
-Easy.
Just try to calm down.
-Maybe if I was to kill the most
important people in your life,
everyone who's ever meant
anything, maybe then I'd
listen to you.
Because maybe then you'd
have some idea how I feel.
KAKASHI: Hmm, it's an
interesting theory,
but I'm afraid you're little
late to put it to the test.
Every one you're talking
about has already been killed.
I've been around longer
than you have kid,
and I've seen my
share of troubles.
You're not the
only one who knows
what it's like to lose somebody.
So, it looks like neither of us
has led a charmed life exactly,
have we?
Still, we're not
all that bad off.
At least you and I
have been lucky enough
to find new comrades
to help fill the void.
Anyway, I do know how you feel.
With the Chidori,
you've been granted
a gift of awesome power.
It's not a power to be
used against your comrades,
or to seek vengeance.
I think, in your heart of
hearts, you know what it's for.
OK, end of lecture.
You decide whether what I'm
saying hits the mark, or not.
KIDOMARU: Could
make things trickier
with that shinobi
hanging around.
We better hold off, for a bit.
-Well, if you're
so scared of him,
why don't I just
go in by myself.
He doesn't look
that tough to me.
-I'm with you.
I bet the two of us could
tear that leaf shinobi apart.
-Did I sound like
I wanted your help?
Butt out bird brain.
-Man, it's no wonder you
never had a boyfriend.
You're such a--
-Shut it fatso.
BOTH: I want some more.
-Let's go back.
-All right.
We both made it, we climbed
all the way up to the top.
What's wrong Sakura?
-Look, there's something I need
to talk to you about Naruto,
so if you still want that
date you've always wanted--
-What do I do?
What do I do?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
It's that curse mark
that Orochimaru put on
him during tuning exams.
Kakashi-Sensei said he'd taken
care of it, but I wonder--
Lord Orochimaru, did you
really send all four of them?
Was that necessary?
-I hadn't the heart
to refuse them.
They all were so eager
to meet this Sasuke
I've spoken so highly of.
They wanted to
test his strength.
-It's not a very fair test.
In his condition, he's no
match for all four of them.
--[laughs] And that's why he'll
come to me seeking greater
power, just as I've
always said he would.
-OK, who are you?
Out with hit.
-We're the Sound Ninja Four.
I'm Kidomaru of the East Gate.
-And I'm Sakon of the West Gate.
-I am Jirobo of the South Gate.
-And I'm Tayuya
of the North Gate.
-Before we go another
round, I should warn you.
You might want to
think about it.
I'm in a really bad mood.
[theme music]
NARUTO: We're on a date!
Hey, maybe after dinner
we can sit in the park
and hold hands or--
SAKURA: That's not what I
wanted to talk to you about.
NARUTO: If it's
about Kakashi-Sensei,
I don't know what
his problem was.
We were only having a
friendly little fight.
If he hadn't butt in we--
SAKURA: If he hadn't
butt in, one of you
might have been killed.
I really don't feel
good about this.
NARUTO: What, our date?
SAKURA: [groans]
NARUTO: Next time, An
Invitation from the Sound.
SAKURA: It can't
go on like this.
[theme music]