[theme music]
[shout]
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER):
Unbelievable.
I never expected the
Fourth Hokage's jutsu.
Still, it's not
like the real thing.
Not coming from
this little Genin.
[grumbling]
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER): Hm.
Tsunade's as strong
as ever, I see.
I remember the time
she gave me a shot that
sent me flying 100 meters
in the opposite direction.
Ouch.
Ah-- he shouldn't even
try to take her own.
-Naruto, are you all right?
-Jiraiya!
Are you the one who taught
this little kid the Rasengan?
-Rasengan?
-Well, of course I did.
I'm his teacher, aren't I?
What of it?
-You and the Fourth
Hokage are the only ones
who can use that jutsu.
What's the point of
teaching it to someone
who can never master it?
You old fool!
Giving him false
hopes like that.
Filling his head
with stupid ideas.
Making him think he could
actually be Hokage some day.
-I'll show you who's stupid!
Just wait!
Give me just three days, and
I'll have that jutsu down flat!
-Ha.
Watch what you say, kid.
I might just told you to it.
-Heh.
-I said it, and I never
go back on my word.
That's my nindo-- my ninja way!
-Oi.
-Well then, care to
make a bet on it?
-A bet?
-I'll give you one week.
If you can master that jutsu
by then, I'll admit I'm wrong,
and that you're worthy
of becoming Hokage.
I'll even throw in my necklace.
-Lady Tsunade, no!
No, you don't really mean that.
-Ah, you can keep it.
I'm not really into jewelry.
JIAIYA: You numbskull.
That necklace belonged to
the first Hokage himself.
There are only two
like it in the world.
Why, that little thing is
worth three gold mines,
and the mountains on top of 'em.
-Lady, you've got
yourself a bet.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER): It's
always money with this kid.
-All right.
However, if you don't
master it in a week,
you lose and admit I was right.
And I get the money in froggy.
-Not Gama!
Wait a second!
-Lady Tsunade,
what are you doing?
How could you gamble
with the necklace?
-He hasn't a chance of winning.
Let's go, Shizune.
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER): No
matter how bad things
got, she's never bet
the necklace before.
-Don't decide now, but
we'll expect your answer
within the week.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Inheritence,
The Necklace of Death!
[knocking]
-What the-- who could that be at
this time of night? [knocking]
OK, OK.
I'm coming, already.
Hold your-
-I know it's awfully late.
I'm sorry, but I
must talk to you.
-I want to get a
good night's sleep,
'cause I'm going
to start training
first thing in the morning.
-That's just it.
Before you get
into this, there's
something you must know
about the necklace.
And also about Lady Tsunade.
-Ha!
I couldn't care less
about crazy old bat.
-Don't say that!
She's not the type of
person you think she is.
What right have you-- you
don't know anything about her!
Please forgive me.
I didn't mean to shout.
Lady Tsunade wasn't
always like that.
She used to be so kind,
dedicated to the village,
but she's changed.
But ever since that day--
-Huh?
What day's that?
Talk, already.
Since what day?
-The day she lost all she had.
Dreams, hopes.
Everything.
She had nothing left after
that, except the necklace,
and all of its memories.
Please understand,
that necklace is
more precious than life for her.
It's not simply a
piece of jewelry
to be gambled away
on a silly bet.
-Look, a bet's a bet.
Anyway, it was her
idea, not mine.
-You'll be sorry
if you think it's
something you'll be able
to wear like a trophy.
This is not just any necklace.
It won't accept anyone
else wearing it.
Only on Lady Tsunade
does it remain safe.
When anyone else
puts it on, they die.
-Nawaki, I can't
believe you're 12.
Happy birthday.
-Huh?
Just because you're
my sister, you
don't have to give me presents.
I'm not a little kid
anymore, you know that?
-Oh, yeah?
You're still a kid, as
far as I'm concerned.
Anyway, whether you or
not, go ahead and open it.
I think you're definitely
going to like it.
-Sister, is this
what I think it is?
-Yep.
It belonged to our grandfather,
necklace of the First Hokage.
-I love you!
-I thought it made more
sense for you to have it.
I know you've had your eye
on it for a long time now.
Take good care of it.
-Oh, I will.
And not just the necklace.
This entire village meant
a lot to our grandfather.
And I'm going to be
good care of all of it.
-Nawaki.
-After all, I'm the
grandson of the Hokage
who built the Village
Hidden in the Leaves.
-Remember, like you
always say, a man
never goes back on his work.
-Right.
And I give my word, I'll follow
our grandfather's footsteps
and be just like him.
To be Hokage.
That is my dream.
-Nawaki, take off your headband.
Just for a sec.
-Huh?
-Go on, take it off.
I have one more present
I want to give you.
A magic charm, to make
your dream come true.
-No.
It's best if you
don't look, Tsunade.
-What difference can it make?
The condition the body's
in, she won't even
be able to recognize
her little brother.
JIRAIYA: Silence, Orochimaru!
-This is what happens in war.
Shinobi are just left on
the battlefield to die.
There are no doctors or
healers to help them.
It's too bad the
boy was so reckless.
As if he thought he
were invulnerable.
And the day after receiving
such a lovely gift, too.
NAWAKI (VOICEOVER): Oh, I will,
and not just the necklace.
This entire village meant
a lot to our grandfather,
and I'm going to take
good care of all of it.
TSUNADE: Therefore, I'm making
this proposal for any four
ninja squad that we
send into harm's way.
If we make one
member of each squad
a trained medical
specialist, it will not only
increase their
survival rate, but will
improve the chances of their
mission being a success.
I say we need to establish
a teaching facility to train
selected ninja in the healing
arts, and we need to do it now.
At once!
We've lost too many
shinobi already.
-Ah.
Yes, there is much sense
in what you say, Tsunade,
but at present we have no
one with enough expertise
in such things, and we're
in the midst of a great war.
Such an undertaking would
require time and resources,
and our enemies won't
sit back and wait for us.
-So we do nothing?
We go on, throwing
their lives away?
-I agree.
I say she's right.
If we can learn to save future
generations of shinobi, then
those who've died,
perhaps this way,
their deaths will have meaning.
-Wait!
Thanks for that.
-There's no need to thank me.
What you said was right.
I was thinking,
it's getting late.
Would you like me
to see you home?
-Oh.
But don't you--
isn't your house?
-Mm-hm.
The other way.
-Don't bother.
Really.
-Oh, it's no bother.
I wanted to talk to you, anyway.
Besides I love this walk
and all its memories.
It's the way I used to go
to pick my little sister up
at the Academy.
-Used to?
-Yes.
That night a year ago, when
the village was attacked,
my sister was killed.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER):
So him, too.
We're the same.
Tomorrow's another mission
into enemy territory.
-Whoever said it
was a shinobi's duty
to watch his comrades
die one by one?
-I know.
-We're beset by death.
It's all around us.
I'd give my life to bring some
order to this war torn world.
I love this village, and the
people in it with all my heart.
I want to protect them.
I want to lead them in building
a better world than this.
It's been my dream ever
since my sister died.
It's all that's kept me going.
To be Hokage.
that is my dream.
-Dan.
Take this.
I want you to have it.
Hang on, Dan!
You'll be all right.
-Tsunade-- I don't
want to die yet.
There are so many
things left to do.
[groan]
-Don't try to talk!
-He's all torn up inside.
No one can help him now.
Not even one of the Sannin.
-But it can't be.
I can't die here.
Not this way.
Not yet.
-Don't worry, Dan.
I've stopped the bleeding.
Just save your strength.
You're going to be all right.
-Thank goodness.
That's a relief.
-Wait, Hang on!
No!
Don't leave me!
Come back, Dan!
Don't go.
Please don't go.
Don't leave me.
Don't go.
Don't go!
-That's enough!
He's dead!
-No!
[crying]
-So you see, Naruto?
That was the day.
It changed her.
She's been in
torment ever since.
Where are you go?
-Out.
I need to start training.
MAN: Welcome.
Come in!
JIRAIYA: Funny finding you here.
-What the hell do you want?
-Don't be that way.
You know you're glad to see me.
-Master Jiraiya.
-Shizune, would you mind
leaving the two of us
alone for a while?
It's been years since
we've sat down together.
Bring me the house
special over here.
And a drink.
MAN: Yes, sir.
Coming up.
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER):
Thank you, Master Jiraiya.
-Here you go.
Ah, perfect.
Just the thing.
I have to say, I never
imagined that you'd still
have that necklace
after all these years.
I just assumed you
would've gambled it
away long before now.
Guess it's all you have
to remember them by.
Is he on your mind?
-What do you mean?
-Naruto, of course.
-Not much.
-I don't know.
Taking on a young kid
like that as an opponent.
He'll never be able to
master that jutsu in a week,
and you know it.
It's not much of a bet.
Why so glum, anyway?
-Who's glum?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
-When are you meeting
Orochimaru again?
I can see it in Shizune's face.
I don't know what sort of
deal he may have offered you,
but think carefully
before accepting it.
Very carefully.
Remember the Hokage
that have come before,
and all they've accomplished
for the Leaf village.
It's only thanks to
them that the village
has survived, even prospered,
through troubled times.
This was their dream,
and they were all
willing to gamble
everything to achieve it.
Even their lives.
Betray that dream, and you
make all their sacrifices
meaningless.
Why am I saying this?
Could you do such a thing?
If I thought you could, I would
stop you right here and now.
-It has nothing to
do with me anymore.
-A person who feels nothing at
the death of those close to him
is no different than a butcher.
But you're not like that.
There was no one who
cared more for the village
or felt its pain more deeply.
I remember the day.
-OK, that's enough
with the lecture!
That dumb kid.
Why did you have
to bring him here?
-To be Hokage.
That is my dream!
-They're a lot alike.
They must be almost
the same age.
-It's not just that.
NAWAKI (VOICEOVER):
To be Hokage!
That is my dream.
-You're always so reckless.
You want to kill yourself?
You're still just a genin, so
if there's ever a real battle,
you get out of there, fast.
-Are you crazy?
I'm never gonna run away!
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): They're
more alike than you know.
-There's no way.
I'm totally out of gas.
Just gotta try it
again tomorrow.
JIRAIYA: Ugh.
My head.
What a night.
Ugh.
That Tsunade always
was a bad influence.
Huh?
Naruto never came in.
Must've been training all night.
Hmph.
Little fool.
-So.
Do we have a deal?
-I'm offering to bring
your dear little brother
and your beloved back to life,
with a forbidden jutsu that I
have developed.
Come now.
Don't you want to see
them again, dear Tsunade?
TSUNADE: What do
you plan on doing,
once you arms have
been restored to you?
-This time around, I'm going
to grind the Hidden Leaf
village into dust.
-My lady, think of your brother.
Think of my uncle!
It would be a betrayal of them.
A betrayal of yourself.
Have you forgotten
all your dreams?
-I'll cut to the chase.
Tsunade.
In all its wisdom, the village
has come to the decision
to name you as the Fifth Hokage.
[theme music]
-Oh, no!
What have I done?
How could I fall asleep
today of all days?
This is the day that
the bet comes to!
I've gotta put up or
shut up, and I'm not
even close to nailing the
Fourth Hokage's jutsu!
What's the Pervy
Sage gonna think?
Oh well.
I'll just have to play it be
ear and hope for a lucky break.
That's what gambling's
all about, isn't it?
Next time, A Dubious
Offer, Tsunade's Choice!