[theme music]
[crickets chirping]
[swish of sword]
[screaming]
[laughter]
-Monju.
-Right.
[buzzing]
[clang]
[explosion]
[laughter]
[crying]
-Eh?
Great.
Now we gotta deal with a kid.
-I'll handle it.
-He's all yours, Gantetsu.
[crying]
[gasp]
-(SHOUTING) All right!
Let's do this!
Let's torch the
mansion and get out.
We don't wanna
leave any evidence.
[crying]
[bell ringing]
CHILD: I'm gonna get you!
-I tagged you!
Now you're it.
-Yeah.
-You'll never catch me.
I'm too fast!
-Over here!
-Come on!
You can't catch us.
SHIZUNE: Lady Tsunade?
-Hm?
-There's another request here.
-You're kidding.
I thought I dealt
with all of them.
-Sorry.
-Fine.
Whatever.
-It's the last one.
So if you just concentrate,
it shouldn't take long.
-Let's do it then.
[yawn] It's hard to do anything
when it's hot like this.
So what do they want?
-Well the police have
requested our assistance.
They need to
transfer a prisoner.
-So why do they want our help?
They should be able
to handle that.
-Actually, it's a
little more complicated.
Take a look at this.
-Interesting.
You're right.
This could get tricky.
-The Jonin have all been
assigned to S-level missions,
so they're unavailable.
And 9/10 of the Chunin
and Genin are away
from the village on
different assignments.
-All right then.
Who does that leave?
-Let's see here.
Uh well--
NARUTO: All right!
Time for multi-shadow
clone jutsu!
[boom]
-Argh!
-Let's go, Bushybrow!
[shouting]
[gulp]
-I am coming for you, Naruto!
Argh!
Plead for a day!
-You asked for it.
Here's another serving
of shadow clone jutsu.
Argh!
-That is nothing.
[panting]
-Wasn't bad.
-Not bad yourself.
-Naruto!
Lee, where are you?
-Argh!
[punch]
[gasp]
[groaning]
-What the heck-- What'd
you guys do to each other?
-Sakura!
SAKURA: Would you stop moving?
-Take it easy.
It wouldn't kill you to
be a little more gentle.
-Oh shut up.
If you weren't so reckless,
this never would have happened.
-Sorry.
I do not mean to argue,
but you are mistaken.
Using 100 shadow clones
is an excellent tool
for sharpening one's
taijutsu skills.
Not to mention the fact that
this kind of friendly training
is an excellent opportunity for
Naruto to sharpen his skills as
well, thus killing two
birds with one stone.
-I was just gonna say that.
-Call it what you want,
but all you were doing
was beating on each other.
-Of course we were.
Guys always do that
when we get together.
-You got that right.
[laughter]
-Fine, whatever.
We don't have time to sit
around here arguing about it.
Lady Tsunade wants to see us.
-What'd we do wrong this time?
-Why us?
-Ninja drop outs?
LADY TSUNADE: That's right.
It's a group of ninja who've
chosen to leave their villages
and give up the
life of a shinobi
to go live in the wild
with others like them.
They're a band of
savage thieves who
use their skills to
steal what they want.
-You're serious?
They actually use their shinobi
abilities to commit crimes?
-Unforgivable.
-One of their members
was captured yesterday
in the Ogi Mountain pass
in the Land of Forests.
This particular guy is wanted
in just about every village
you can think of.
He was wandering through the
woods when he was captured.
His name is Gantetsu.
-He doesn't look like
much of a ninja to me.
-We're hoping Gantetsu
has information
that will help us wipe
out the ninja dropouts.
So he's being transferred
to the capital
city of the Land of
Forests to be interrogated.
We're assuming
the ninja dropouts
will try to rescue him
somewhere along the way.
The police are taking
every precaution
and have assigned a
full escort to assure
he makes it to the capital.
But since the
opponents are ninja,
they've asked me to assign
several of our own ninja
to ensure the success
of this mission.
So then, that's why
you're all here.
-This is awesome!
We'll show those guys what the
Hidden Leaf ninja are made of.
-That's right.
-Those guys will
not stand a chance.
-Good then.
Naruto Uzumaki, Sakura
Haruno, Rock Lee.
The three of you are
assigned to the mission
of guarding the Gantetsu convoy.
-Yes ma'am.
-You can count on us!
-There it is.
That must be it.
-Whoa.
They're gonna
transport him in this?
NARUTO: They have no choice.
The only way to get to the
capital of the Land of Forests
is up this river.
-Hey you guys. Look.
-That must be--
SUZUME: The ninja
dropout, Gantetsu.
-Huh?
-Are you the Hidden
Leaf shinobi?
-Yes.
Uh, who are you?
-I'm Suzume, from the
correctional facility.
I'm the one in charge
of this convoy.
-I'm Naruto Uzumaki.
This is Rock Lee, but you can
just call him "Bushybrow."
And this is Sakura Haruno.
-Hmm.
No disrespect, but you
look kind of young.
Are you sure you're
really ninja?
-Of course we are.
-Yup.
I know we look young, but we've
all been on dozens of missions.
We are definitely
full-fledged ninja.
-When the time comes, you
will see just how good we are.
-Leave everything to us.
-I expect the security
team I've assembled
to be able to handle
the situation.
But if that's not
enough, I'll be
counting on you and
your ninja skills.
SAKURA: Yes sir.
-These are the men
that I've placed
in charge of the
prisoner's security.
-They're all dressed
exactly alike.
-You're right.
Those guys sure don't
have much style.
-Naruto!
That's rude!
-Ah.
Captain Todoroki.
-Yes chief?
What can I do for you?
-These three ninja here will
be joining us, as backup.
-The name's Naruto Uzumaki.
-Sakura Haruno.
-And my name is Rock Lee.
-But chief, we discussed this.
I told you we already
have enough security.
-It's out of my hands.
The orders came down from above.
-If you want to help,
stay out of our way.
My men and I will
guard Gantetsu.
I swear by the
power of my sword.
-Oh yeah?
Well that sword is nothing.
I could snap it in two
without even trying!
I could do it with one hand!
-With just one finger.
-Would you guys
knock it off already?
Please excuse them.
-If you get seasick, try
not to throw up on deck.
-We'll see you on board.
-Yes, sir.
Thank you.
-(THINKING) Gantetsu.
All right.
Let's lower the
prisoner into the hole.
[creaking]
-Right there!
Bring her down!
Incoming!
And there.
[boat whistle]
-Wow!
This is great!
-This is ridiculous.
They won't even let us see the
guy we're supposed to guard.
-They treat us like pests
who are in their way.
-Yeah.
Well if those ninja dropout
guys would just attack,
then we could show them
how amazing we really are.
-Don't say things like that.
We're better off if the ninja
dropouts never show up at all.
It's our mission to get
Gantetsu safely to the capital.
Not to show how amazing we are.
-Yeah, I know.
But still, I'm bored.
How am I gonna keep
myself occupied?
-Just deal with it.
It's part of the mission.
-It may be part of the mission,
but I agree with Naruto.
-You're right.
I'm getting bored myself.
[sigh]
[snap]
-Well, dig in.
I still can't get over
them treating us like this.
Who do they think we are?
-Though I have to admit
this stuff is good.
-It's not bad at all.
-Still, it makes me so mad.
Seriously, why did they even ask
us to come on this stupid trip anyway?
Ahh.
Well I don't care what they say.
I'm gonna go stand guard.
-But Officer Todoroki's
gonna get mad at you.
-A ninja's got his pride.
[growl]
-Naruto!
-Are you sure?
-This guy even looks
like a criminal.
Huh?
(THINKING) Todoroki.
What the heck is he doing here?
TODOROKI: Akio!
No!
Mother! Father!
[groaning] Akio!
Akio!
[sreaming]
[panting]
-That's it.
(THINKING) Akio.
I will finally avenge you.
-What the heck are you doing?
Stop it.
Are you outta your mind?
What were you gonna do just now?
[laughter]
-Ninja arc.
Crimson mud.
[grunt]
[crashing]
[laughter]
[waves crashing]
-What is the matter, Sakura?
Something wrong?
-Take a look over there.
Strange.
None of the maps I looked at
showed a fork in the river.
TODOROKI: You.
What are you doing here?
-What I'm doing here
isn't important right now.
The question is,
what were you getting
ready to do to Gantetsu?
-What are you inferring?
-It looked like
you were planning
to use your sword on him.
-Me?
That's ridiculous.
It's my mission to see that this
man reaches the capitol safely.
And that's what I'm doing.
-That's good.
Because no matter
what this guy's done,
he still needs to be
interrogated and given
a fair trial before
anything else.
-Brat.
Like you know what he deserves!
This guy doesn't need
to be interrogated.
He did everything they said.
[gasp]
-Oh he did it.
He's the one.
A lot of innocent people
died because of him.
Even kids.
He showed no mercy at all!
SAKURA: The
current's too strong.
At this rate,
we'll be pulled in!
-What should we do?
-Ninja art.
Link and Slide.
[creaking]
[groaning]
[screaming]
-What the heck?
-That's impossible.
-What?
No!
We've been sliced in half!
-Naruto!
-Over here!
NARUTO: Huh?
TODOROKI: You.
The ninja dropouts.
They're here.
-It's about time.
-Gantetsu.
-What have we got here?
Don't move.
You better tell me
who you are right now.
-I'm Shura Sanjuro.
Head of the ninja dropouts.
-You scum.
-Just hand him over.
Gantetsu is with us.
-Sorry, but that's
not gonna happen.
[laughter]
[growling]
[theme music]
SAKURA: Lee, are you all right?
LEE: Yes.
Although I am not
quite sure how.
What happened back there?
SAKURA: I don't know.
There was a huge crash,
and the next thing I knew,
the ship was sliced in half!
LEE: Then the first
thing we need to do
is make sure everyone
on board is all right.
SAKURA: Well--
LEE: What is wrong, Sakura?
SAKURA: I already checked,
and three of them are missing.
Gantetsu, Captain
Todoroki, and Naruto!
LEE: Oh no!
NATURO: Next time, the
Bewildering Forest!
[theme music]