[theme music]
-I'll get you out.
Just hang on a little longer.
-Hey.
And just what do you
think you're doing?
-And one and two, one and two,
and one and two, one and-- I'm
sure they'll be all right.
They're clever and strong.
They'll bring
Karashi back safely.
Sure they will.
No need to worry.
One, two.
-That must be the place, huh?
The Katabami gold mine.
You know, instead of just
rescuing Rokusuke and Karashi,
I say we finish off this
Kurosuki gang once and for all.
-Let's not get
carried away, Naruto.
-OK, so what's the
plan then, genius?
-Remember what Guy-sensei said.
That worries me.
-What about it?
That the boss of
the gang might be
one of the Seven Ninja
Swordsman of the Mist?
If you ask me, that just
makes it more interesting.
-I don't know, we
can't really be sure
that Guy-sensei was
right about that anyway.
-What are you talking about?
Guy-sensei is always right.
-First things first.
We need to investigate.
-Well, let's go!
[snickering]
-Sir Raiga.
We caught one of
the three villagers
who tried to run away.
-Well done.
-Seems they thought
they'd run and get help
from the ninja of the
neighboring village.
-Dog.
Where did you run to?
-Please.
-Back off, rookie.
-Yes sir.
-Why, Rokusuke?
After all we've done to
establish a good relationship
with you people.
I thought we were
all friends here.
-Oh, we are.
I mean--
-It breaks my heart you
think so little of us
that you'd leave us like
that, without a word.
I tru and remember
the way things were.
The good times.
-Please, sir!
I'm sorry!
It won't happen again!
-Ah.
I have it!
I know what we'll do.
We'll arrange to have a funeral.
Yours.
-Please, forgive me!
I don't know what
I was thinking.
No, please!
It won't happen again!
I promise.
I promise!
-What's wrong?
Don't you like funerals?
-Oh please!
Not mine!
I'm not ready to die!
-Personally, I find
funerals very comforting.
People can be so cruel.
They spend most of
their living things
being unkind to one another,
betraying each other,
envying and hating each other.
There's nothing like a funeral
to bring people together.
To make them forget
their differences
and remember the good times.
People are at their
best at funerals.
Don't you think?
-No!
No, you can't be!
Please!
Let me go!
-Oh, no you don't.
-No, you can't!
Let me go!
-All right.
What do you say?
Shall we have a nice,
big funeral for Rokusuke?
MEN: Yeah!
-Keep it moving.
Keep it moving.
You there!
Faster!
-Is that stuff gold?
Doesn't look like much.
LEE: The gold is just
a part of the ore.
It must be melted and refined,
and the mercury and impurities
removed.
-Sounds like a lot of work.
-Don't worry.
You don't have to understand it.
-What do you think
you're doing, old man?
Get up!
-On your feet.
Or do we tell the boss it's
time for another funeral?
-No.
Please.
-Poor guy.
Ugh.
OK, that does it!
Now I'm mad!
-Relax, Naruto.
We're going to finish
our reconnaissance
before we make a move.
-Yeah.
Hold your horses.
Neji's right.
-Great idea.
Let's just set here and
watch him drive that old man
into the ground.
-Right.
You just leave this to me.
-Lee!
What are you doing?
-That's right.
Pick them up.
Every one of them.
-Huh?
-Way to go, Lee!
-You are all right.
Fear not.
-Are you crazy?
Dear heaven, what have you done?
-Here.
You must be thirsty.
NARUTO: Hey!
What's that all about?
-You've got to do to me,
just what you did to them.
Hurry!
Beat me!
Hit me!
Knock me to the ground!
-You feeling OK?
-If you won't, then
I'll do it myself.
-No, stop that.
-What the heck's wrong with you?
-Don't you see?
If I'm not injured, they'll
think I was behind it,
and that means they'll
give me a funeral.
-That gong.
What does it mean?
-Is it some kind of alarm?
-No.
It's summoning
everyone to a funeral.
-A funeral?
-That's right.
If any of us displeases
Raiga, the leader of the clan,
then as punishment,
he arranges a funeral
in which the guilty
person is buried alive.
-He what?
Buries them alive?
That's the worst
thing I've ever heard!
-Then Raiga gets very sad.
He bows his head and
weeps over the coffin
as if he's lost a dear friend.
-Sounds like we're dealing
with a real nutjob here.
-That gong.
Whose funeral are
they ringing it for?
It can't be yours,
can it, old man?
-No.
I heard they caught
Rokusuke this morning.
It must be his.
-Rokusuke?
-I remember the first
day I met Rokusuke.
It's a happy memory.
-Is it?
That's nice.
-Yes.
I still see the smile
on his simple face
when he learned we were
taking over the gold mine.
When we told him the days
of cruel taxes were over.
How happy he was.
Almost dancing for joy.
That's how I'll
always remember him.
I like funerals.
They're so nostalgic.
-Will you have a nice
funeral for me, too?
-Don't talk nonsense.
There will be no
funeral for you--
because you're not going to die.
Besides, I don't need
a funeral to remind me
of the good times we've shared.
You've always been a good boy.
-Raiga.
-Hm?
-They're coming.
They'll be here very soon now.
-Good.
I'm curious to see who
he found to rescue him.
-OK, what are we waiting for?
Let's save this guy.
What do you say, Neji?
-All right.
Byakuran!
It's all right.
He's still alive.
We'll draw the guards
away, and then get him out.
-OK.
We hit him fast,
and we hit him hard.
-All right.
Time to begin.
[banging]
-Please!
Let me out of here!
Let me out!
[laughter]
-We're under attack!
[shout]
-Get ready!
-Tenten!
Take care of those
two on the right.
-I got 'em!
-Gentle Fist!
-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Uzumaki Barrage!
Someone ought to bury you now.
-Watch out.
-Huh?
-There are three more of them.
-Do not forget that handsome
devil, Rock Lee of the Leaf.
I've found the last one.
-No!
No!
-Is it really you?
-What is it?
Who is this guy?
-He is-- this is Karashi.
-He's the one Grandma
Sansho told us about?
-This guy's Karashi?
-Karashi, is it true
what Grandma Sansho said?
You chose to join
the Kurosuki clan?
-Well, so what if I did?
What of it?
-What of it?
-Sure I did.
Their leader is a great man.
He took the entire gold mine
back from those evil men,
and he liberated
this whole village.
-And one, and two, and one
and two, and one and two,
and one and two.
-Excuse me.
Grandma?
-Unbelievable!
Are you really that greedy?
Shame on you.
Those people are out there
risking their lives for us.
And all you can think
about is your stomach.
Well, you'll just have
to wait, you hear?
-That's not it.
I don't mind
waiting, it's just--
I think something's burning.
-Huh?
-Oh!
No, no!
You're right, I burned it.
Never done that before.
NARUTO: How can
you do this to her?
That poor old woman
worries about you all day
long while she stands
there cooking that curry.
You ungrateful little--
-Wait, Naruto.
Perhaps it would be
better if I handle it.
Karashi, that was more
than just a delicious
curry you used to make.
It literally saved my life.
You have a gift.
You would give that up
to join these people,
who do not even care
about human life?
How can you?
-What did I ever
get for sweating
over that stupid pot all day?
Nothing.
Joining the Kurosuki, I became
part of something bigger.
Something powerful and feared.
I'm important now.
Not some nobody
stuck in the kitchen
of a stinking little curry shop.
-I've had it with this guy.
He's never going to
listen to reason!
Huh?
-Lee.
-Karashi.
Not only did you bring
me back from the brink
of death with your
curry, but you taught me
a lesson I have never forgotten.
You taught me that if you
put your heart and soul
into something,
anything can happen.
You can change the world.
I learned that even someone
like me could accomplish
great things if I
tried hard enough.
That was your gift.
You say you want to be more
powerful and respected?
You were a better man then.
-Karashi.
-I've never seen
anyone work so hard.
-I see.
So you want to help this
young man as well, eh?
-Turn back, Karashi.
You must turn away from
this path you have taken.
Be the man you once were.
-You're right.
I've been a fool.
Forgive me.
-Good.
Glad to have you back on board.
[banging]
ROKUSUKE: Please, someone
get me out of here!
It's dark!
NARUTO: Oh, man!
It's Rokusuke.
The poor guy, we
forgot all about him!
-It's-- it's yu.
-That's all.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
-Forgive me.
But when I thought of
my friend buried alive,
I had to try to help.
I couldn't just stand
by and do nothing.
-Yeah.
I know exactly how you feel.
-Neji.
What is it?
-What is this feeling?
This sudden sense of danger?
-What's wrong, Neji?
What is it?
-We're being watched.
I think it's Raiga.
NARUTO: Where?
NEJI: From the
top of that cliff.
NARUTO: Good.
Let's go get him.
-Karashi, you stay here
and look after Rokusuke.
-All right.
-Wait.
There's no one here.
-Are you sure about that?
What's goin' on?
-An impenetrable mist.
[laughter]
-Ninja Art, Hidden Mist Justsu.
-Here it is.
The Hidden Mist Jutsu is the
trademark of the Mist Village
nina.
-The Seven Ninja
Swordsmen of the Mist.
Guy-sensei was right.
-Fine.
I just wish I could
see something.
-Neji, try employing
your Byakugan.
-Don't you think
I've been trying?
No use.
I can't see a thing.
-Incredible.
So, even the all-seeing
Byakugan is blind in this mist?
This jutsu is very powerful.
-You really can't see anything?
-I've never heard of any jutsu
stronger than the Byakugan.
-Well, Ranmaru,
what do you think?
RANMARU: It's amazing.
One of them has
eyes with the power
to actually see
the chakra network.
He must possess
the Kekkai Genkai.
-You mean he can see us?
-No, don't worry.
My powers are still
greater than his.
So, what will you do?
-I carry the burden of all the
hopes and fears of everybody
who works in the
Katabami gold mine.
The people depend on
me to keep the village
safe from intruders.
-Will you arrange a funeral?
-For them?
They're strangers to me.
A funeral for them would
summon no happy memories.
No.
I'll simply kill them.
-Behold.
Ninja Art, Lightning Fang!
-Now what's going on?
-Lightning Fang,
Strike them down!
How was that, Ranmaru?
-Wonderful, Raiga.
[laughter]
[theme music]
NARUTO: Naruto Uzumaki Barrage!
What the--
ROCK LEE: Leaf Hurricane!
TENTEN: I've got you!
NEJI: This is impossible.
NARUTO: He's vanished!
ROCK LEE: Where is the enemy?
TENTEN: What enemy?
There is no enemy,
-Neji, you sure you got
that Byakugan working right?
NEJI: Quiet, Naruto.
Of course it's working.
He's here somewhere.
He must be.
I can see his chakra.
NARUTO: Next time, The
Enemy of the Byakugan!
[theme music]