[music playing]
-It's your destiny
to lose to me.
And that's it.
-Oh, yeah?
Well, we won't know that
until you beat me, will we?
[panting]
-OK.
So your father was
killed a long time ago,
and I know it wasn't fair and
maybe you're upset about that,
I understand.
But that's got nothing
to do with destiny.
If you think I'm buying
that, you're wrong.
-You will never understand.
-It's over.
Hm.
You're a failure.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): A
Failure's True Power
NARUTO: Wait, don't
walk away from me.
I'm not done yet.
I don't quit, and I
don't go back on my word.
That's my nindo, my ninja way.
-I never go back on my word.
Because that, too, is
my nindo, my ninja way.
-I've heard those words before.
All this destiny crap, well,
if you really believe it,
why are you the
one walking away?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Naruto.
-You impudant little brat!
Why waste my breath
explaining it to you?
We are all given a
destiny at birth,
and it's pointless
to fight against it.
HIZASHI: Neji, my son,
the Hyuga bloodline trait
flows stronger in you than in
any other member of our clan.
I should have been born
a few moments earlier
and made you part of
the main household.
-You don't know what it's like
to be branded with a mark that
sets you apart, a market
that can never be wiped away.
[crying]
-Oh yeah.
I know what that's like.
Well, big deal.
Who cares?
-You worthless little--
-Man, you think
you've got troubles.
I've got news for
you Neji, you're
not the only special
one around here.
Did you ever think
that Hinata might
be suffering as much as you are.
it's not her fault that her
father was born ahead of yours,
but you resent her for it.
You disrespect her
even when she's
trying so hard to
improve herself.
All she wanted was your respect.
That's what she was fighting
for even though it almost
killed her.
And what was that
all about anyway?
I thought it was your destiny
to serve the main household, not
to neat it to a bloody pulp.
After all you said about how
you can't fight your destiny,
you don't really believe
in it either, do you?
AKAMARU (VOICEOVER): Her color
is coming back to her face.
He did it!
Woah, these Anbu BlackOps,
they are really good.
-She'll be all right now.
She just needs rest.
[coughing]
-I have blocked all 64
of your chakra points.
How are you planning
to keep fighting
when you can't use any of
your chakra against me?
It's fitting that you
sympathize with Hinata
because you're about
to share her fate.
-Oh really?
You think that Byakugan
of yours sees everything.
You know everyone's
weakness, right?
-That's right.
But if you think you're the
one who can prove me wrong,
well, be my guest.
-You got it.
I'm going to show you
you're wrong about a lot
of things starting right now.
Yeah, easier said than done.
It doesn't feel like I
have any chakra at all.
I haven't felt so totally
drained since that time
in training with the Pervy Sage.
-Haven't you ever felt the
presence of a different chakra?
You have two types of chakra,
but you must use up all of one
before you can assess the
other and, thus, increase
the total amount of
chakra you can use.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): That's it!
I can use the
Nine-Tailed Fox's chakra.
[growling]
OK you stinking fox, if you're
there, give me your strength!
[heart beating]
NEJI: Proctor, this has
gone on long enough.
I suggest you stop the match.
If he's foolish enough
to continue to fight,
I will not be responsible
for what happens to him.
-Fine.
NARUTO: Hm.
-It's pointless, I told you.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I can do it.
I won't lose.
I vow to win.
-Why bother?
You have no chakra to use.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I can do it.
Oh yeah, don't forget
to watch me wipe off
the floor with Neji in
the final competition.
Uh!
ROCK LEE (VOICEOVER): A
loser beating the genius
through sheer willpower.
Now, would not that make
for an exciting match?
Of course, if you ended up
fighting him that is fine too.
-Why fight a hopeless battle
trying to defy your destiny?
-Cause people
called me a failure.
I'll prove them wrong.
NEJI (VOICEOVER): What?
It can't be.
Where is that
chakra coming from?
It's-- it's not possible!
What-- what is he?
HIZASHI (VOICEOVER): Impossible.
That chakra.
-This can't be happening.
No way!
-But how?
All of his chakra
points were blocked.
HOKAGE (VOICEOVER): No question.
It's the chakra of
the Nine-Tailed Fox.
But when did this boy learn
how to harness it's strength?
-Here it goes.
NEJI (VOICEOVER): Incredible!
Twisting energy.
What kind of chakra is that?
Or is it even chakra at all?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Amazing!
This is even more power
than I felt before.
I like it!
NEJI: Rotation!
Take this.
What?
He's faster than before.
What's going on here?
-OK you.
So I hear you like
close combat, huh?
NEJI (VOICEOVER): You
thought you could be Hokage?
It's absurd, never.
Open your eyes.
Of all the shinobi
in all the world,
think how few ever
become Hokage.
They were born,
destined to be Hokage.
It's not something you become
merely by trying to become it.
They were chosen by destiny.
Each person is given his
own path to follow up,
and he must follow it,
obediently, to the end.
-It may be the Hyuga way
to cave in to destiny.
It's not mine!
if you think it's futile
to fight, then don't.
Just stand there and take it!
NEJI (VOICEOVER): Quickly!
Must use my rotation.
-I'll change the way
of the Hyuga clan
after I become Hokage.
[explosion]
SHINOBI (VOICEOVER): Man, that's
some chakra that kid's got.
Never seen anything like it.
No way that Hyuga
kid could have--
-But, which one's Naruto?
-Don't ask me.
I don't even know what
happened just now.
-Huh?
[gasp]
[sigh]
[panting]
TENTEN (VOICEOVER): That'S
the secret of Neji's rotation
technique, it not only
blocks any attack,
but it turns the energy of
an opponent's own chakra
against him.
And Naruto went right into it.
There's not a genin
alive who can beat Neji.
But still, I've got to
hand it to you, Naruto,
you came closer than
anyone ever has.
NEJI: Sorry, but
this is reality.
You're a failure.
This match is over.
[explosion]
[screaming]
-(PAINFULLY) I can't move.
SHINOBI (VOICEOVER): He
used his clone as bate
and waited for his
chance to get Neji.
Even when he was getting
pounded into the ground,
he never stopped
planning his next move.
He never lost his faith
in his ability to win.
Naruto knows instinctively
that believing in yourself
can give you the power
to change your destiny.
And on top of that, he's
got one hell of a left hook.
-I should have guessed you'd
use that shadow clone jutsu.
It's your specialty after all.
I was careless.
-For the record, I failed the
graduation exam three times
because there was this one jutsu
that was always on the exam.
And it tripped me up every time.
It was the one jutsu that
I just couldn't master.
My clones were pathetic.
That's right.
I flunked the shadow
clone jutsu every time.
So don't come whining to
me with this density stuff.
And stop trying to tell me
you can't change what you are.
You can do it, too.
Cause, after all, unlike
me, you're not a failure.
SHINOBI: The winner
is Naruto Uzumaki.
[cheering]
[music playing]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Woohoo!
I won!
Yes, thank you.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
(ANNOYED) Naruto.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): What is it?
You want an autograph
or something?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): No, shut up.
Do you always have
to be such a jerk?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
What's wrong, Sakura?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): It's Sasuke.
He's still not here.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Oh, typical.
I almost get killed, and all
she can think about is him.
Next time, Hit It or Quit It.
The Final Rounds
Get Complicated.
Ah, to hell with Sasuke!
I won!
[music playing]