[theme music]
-I'm here, Sasuke.
OROCHIMARU: Aaargh!
[heaves]
My arms!
-Lord Orochimaru, are you OK?
Quick, your medicine!
-Aargh!
-[gasping]
-[sighs]
I just got back.
Now, I have to clean the room.
Please be sure to take
your medicine, will you?
-That medicine will do
nothing for me, you simpleton!
-But I made it
specifically for you.
It should ease your
pain, at least, a little.
-This burning in
my arms, I never
imagined the suffering
would be great.
-It was Sarutobi after
all, the Third Hokage.
This was his final curse.
-Enough of your prattling.
Tell me, have you
found the one I seek?
-Yes.
The trail led to a place
called Tanzaku Town.
-Tanzaku Town.
[grunts]
I see.
-Lest you forget, your opponent
is one of the legendary Sannin.
This isn't going to be easy.
-[snickers]
The best medicines
are always bitter.
-Hm?
-Take a look.
It's the same mark.
I don't get it.
How is this supposed to help?
-You're the kind of
kid who got yelled
at in the academy for lack
of concentration, aren't you?
-I don't see what that
has to do with this.
-Look at this piece of paper.
-Hm?
I've seen it.
-All right.
Now, if you will,
give it a second look.
-Huh?
What am I looking at?
-Well, I don't think it's
going to help a whole lot if I
explain too much right away.
But the first time you
looked at this paper,
your eyes just glanced at
the whole thing, am I right?
-Probably.
-And what about the
second time you looked?
Most likely, the
point in the middle?
-Huh?
-Any time that a person's eyes
gaze on a blank sheet of paper,
they don't focus where to look.
The eyes just wander the page.
But if you put even a dot on
it, the mind is drawn there.
You're then concentrating
on a single point.
And with that focus comes
spiritual stability,
letting you tap into
unimaginable power.
-Hm.
-When you finally broke open
the hole in the rubber ball,
I'm sure you must have
been trying desperately
to gather up the
chakra you needed
in the palm of your hand.
-Uh, yeah, that's right!
JIRAIYA: When you concentrate,
you draw out power.
But without some sort of target,
concentration can be difficult;
hence, that mark.
Now, listen, Naruto.
From now on, when you're storing
up power in your right hand,
make sure that you
concentrate only on that mark.
-Concentrate.
All right!
I guess I can handle that!
"Focal Point, the
Mark of the Leaf"!
[grunts]
Concentrate!
[hiss]
Uhh.
I don't think that's
going to cut it.
It has to pop!
Concentrate!
-Hi there.
I was hoping you could
help me with something.
[snoring]
-Dang it!
Haa, hrm.
Concentrate.
[inhales loudly]
Haah.
Concentrate!
[hiss]
[panting]
It's no use.
I thought I knew what
concentration was.
-[sighs]
-[grunts]
Aargh!
Curse you, Sarutobi!
[grunts]
Aargh!
[gasping]
[wheezing]
-All right, then.
I got to go back and scrounge
up some more information.
-What?
Come on, you just got here!
-Sorry, kid.
But I don't have
any time to waste.
-Hey!
That's it?
Not even a soulful
little game of catch
between a pupil and his master?
Urrh!
You lousy ball!
-Hm?
-[gasps]
-[laughs]
Strike!
Ptchoo.
There you go, kid.
Game over.
[guffaws]
See you around, sport.
-Humph.
Who needs that Pervy Sage?
I'll just dig in and
work this out on my own.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER): There's
no other way, Naruto.
This training,
you must do alone.
You can attain the level of
the Fourth Hokage someday,
but you must grab
it on your own.
-Hm, nope.
Never laid eyes on her.
-I see.
Sorry to have been any trouble.
MAN: I know who
you're talking about.
-Hm?
-And I can tell you where
she is right now, too.
-How about a drink, friend?
-Heh, that's all right, thanks.
I made out like a bandit not too
long ago, thanks to the lady.
-Yes, you are indeed
the legendary sucker!
-Hm, she lost again, did she?
Lovely.
-Her losses were
really piling up,
so she went looking for
a change of scenery.
-Where to?
-Tanzaku Town-- Tsunade,
legendary Sannin,
is somewhere within those walls.
-Will these arms can,
at last, be restored?
-She may be good
medicine, but she'll
leave you with more than just
a bitter taste in your mouth.
-Not to worry.
-7, 7, 7, 7, 7, 7, 7, 7, 7, 7.
-Uh!
-Jackpot!
MAN (ON PA SYSTEM):
Congratulations
to our lucky customer.
Machine number 44
just caught the fever!
Don't stop now, keep
that luck coming!
-And to every life, a
little luck must fall.
Isn't that right, my lady?
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER):
I got three 7s?
MAN: Holy smokes, lady!
-Yeah, not a bad haul.
-Wish I had that kind of luck.
CROWD: Oh!
Ho-ho!
MAN: She did it again!
-All right!
Looks like the fever's raging!
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): I
never hit it this big.
I'm getting a bad feeling here.
-I have a little knowledge
of Lady Tsunade myself.
I was a member of the
medical corps after all.
She was the first
to propose what's
now a very common
practice for each squad
to have a medical
specialist included.
Simple but brilliant.
It was a landmark idea.
What becomes of a squad on
the battlefield with no one
to administer emergency
medical treatment?
The answer is clearer
than a fire in the night.
OROCHIMARU: Hah, countless
years on the battlefield
have simply taught them how to
cope with the ravages of war.
All those who were sacrificed
led to the method you speak of.
And one only truly grasps
the value of something
once it has been
taken away from you.
This revolutionary idea enacted
by one of the legendary Sannin,
hailed for her medical prowess,
spawned in that sacrifice.
-It's no good.
I have to concentrate
even harder.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Concentrate.
Concentrate.
Concentrate on one point only.
-Strike!
Strike!
-[guffaws]
-Strike!
How can I concentrate with
that stupid perv's face popping
into my head?
-Ahchoo!
Well, what do you know?
Some gal out there must
be talking about me.
Jiraiya, how do you do it?
-Lady Tsunade,
wait up, will you?
What's the matter?
For you to win this much
is, well, a miracle.
But you don't look
happy in the least.
-This town--
-Huh?
-Something's not right here.
Hurry up, we're leaving.
-Wha-- but this is
a tourist resort.
We should take our time,
go see the historic castle.
-Well, look fast, so
we can get out of here.
-But, Lady Tsunade!
-Uhh. [groans]
-Lord Orochimaru.
-Let's get this
business over with.
Even if we need to get
a little more forceful.
-I've got to do it.
Ow!
Ouch!
I can't even build up chakra.
It hurts so much!
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER): I think
he's almost at his limit.
-[sighs]
[pants]
I just need a little more
time to rest, that's all.
Uh.
BOY: Hey!
We're still in class here!
[laughs]
SENSEI: You foolish runts!
[grunts]
You guys don't
have a single ounce
of concentration
between the four of you!
You are all far from the path
to becoming excellent shinobi!
-Sorry, but I wasn't made
to sit still at a desk.
Right, Akamaru?
[dog barks]
-[yawns]
Man, I'm hungry.
-Sensei, is this
lecture almost done?
-Why, you-- you, you,
you little-- from now
on, you guys are
staying after school
to work on your concentration!
BOYS: [moaning]
Hm?
Huh?
-[chuckles]
-What's this for?
-You're about to take
up a custom passed down
through generations of
the Hidden Leaf Village
for sharpening the mind.
By concentrating all your energy
on the leaf on your foreheads,
you will learn to
build up your chakra.
It is an ancient wisdom.
By focusing on that single
leaf, nothing can distract you.
-Hm?
-He who hones his concentration
is truly a great ninja.
This is the origin of the
leaf symbol that we wear.
-Quit pulling our leg.
-You sure you didn't
just make that story up
to get us to work harder?
-No, I'm not making it up!
It was all true!
-Anyway, you can't
become a great ninja
just by polishing
your concentration.
-Besides, everyone knows if you
want to be an awesome ninja,
you got to be strong!
-He does have a point.
-Stuff like this?
Pfff!
-Aaah!
NARUTO: Catch you later, Sensei!
[boys laugh]
-Now, you boys, wait a minute!
-As if!
-No time, sorry!
-Hey!
You ungrateful little misfits!
-This is the same thing.
[sighs]
I should have paid
more attention
to what Iruka Sensei
was telling us.
I'm so stupid.
Well, I guess there's no use
crying over spilled milk.
All right, here we go.
I'm doing this, no matter what!
Concentrate,
concentrate, concentrate.
SHIZUNE: Wow!
Tanzaku Castle sure does
have a commanding presence.
Oh, they didn't designate it a
cultural landmark for nothing,
I suppose.
TSUNADE: Stop
lollygagging around.
We have to get out of this town.
-But, uh, don't you want
to get a better peek at it?
It doesn't cost anything
to look, you know?
Hm?
Lady Tsunade?
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): What
is this chill I'm feeling?
[whooshing]
-This is it!
Haaah!
Hrrh!
Hrrrh!
[blast]
Aagh!
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER): This
kid is something else.
The chakra was so dense,
it burned his palm.
Hah, one surprise after another.
-Heh, what do you know?
It finally popped.
-Well done.
It looks like you've
mastered the second step.
-Come on, then.
Let me hear the third one.
-That'll have to wait for now.
It's time for us to
meet up with Tsunade.
-Isn't that--
-Orochimaru!
-[snickers]
I finally found you.
[music playing]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I can't
concentrate on my training
while we're walking.
Give me a minute.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
You halfwit!
If we don't hustle here,
we're going to lose her.
And anyway, kid, I'm running
out of patience with you.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Where are we headed?
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
If she's in this town,
we'll need a higher
vantage point to look from.
So we're climbing up the castle.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Castle?
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
It's over there.
Can't you see it?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Which
way is "over there"?
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
I'm telling you-- huh?
Wha-- what in the world?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next
time, "An Impossible Choice,
the Pain Within
Tsunade's Heart."
[music playing]