[theme song]
-For the fifth match, Tenten.
Temari, get ready.
TENTEN (VOICEOVER):
I'm so ready.
After watching that last
match, I'm fired up.
MAN: So this is another
genin from the Sand Village.
-Come on, Tenten.
You can do it.
-This should be
interesting to watch.
-Show her who is best.
-Begin.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Killer
Kunoichi and a Shaky Shikamaru.
-Huh?
-All right, Tenten.
Keep her guessing.
-Go for it.
You've got the power of youth.
-Come on, Tenten.
Send that girl back to her
village on a stretcher.
We're right behind you
all the way, Tenten.
-Let's hear it.
Two, four, six, eight,
who do we appreciate?
-Woo.
-Tenten, Tenten!
-Ugh, how'd I get stuck
in the cheering section?
[cheering]
-[yawn].
-Tenten is carefully
determining her distance,
just what I'd expect from her.
She's well positioned
to attack or defend.
-What are you waiting for?
I did say to begin.
-Ha, guess she's waiting
for me to make a move.
Big mistake, because
that first move
I make will be the
last one you see.
Come on, I don't want this mat
ch to be over too quickly, so
why don't you go first?
Come on, girl.
Show me what you got.
-Well, OK.
If you insist.
Remember, you asked for it.
I missed her!
There's just no way.
-What was that, a
warm-up exercise?
Or maybe you're a little nervous
and its affected your aim.
Is that it?
Rats, I was hoping I'd
at least work up a sweat.
But forget that idea if
this is the best you've got.
-What is going on?
How could she have missed?
It is incredible.
-It's impossible.
Tenten's aim is perfect.
She always hits her mark.
-Not this time she didn't.
-She never misses.
There must have been
something that made her miss.
-Huh?
-You know, you can
always count on Temari
to put on a good show.
-Uh, big deal.
-Man, this is embarrassing.
-Huh?
-The Sand Village wins again.
-What are you talking about?
The match just started.
-It's over.
-Give me a break.
What makes you so smart?
Why don't you explain it
to me so I can understand?
-Uh, skip it.
If you can't see it, I'm not
going to waste my breath.
-It's obvious like he
said, this one's over.
-Ah, I don't get it.
I really don't understand
these guys at all.
TENTEN (VOICEOVER):
OK, stay calm.
don't let her get to you.
One, two, three.
She must have
dodged them somehow.
But if I try a
different approach--
TEMARI (VOICEOVER): Ha-ha-ha.
Look at her measuring
her distance.
Here comes her big move.
TENTEN (VOICEOVER):
So that's her secret,
that fan she carries.
OK.
All right, try this on for size.
No way.
she stopped everything I threw.
What has she got in
that fan of hers?
-Ha-ha, take a look.
This is the first moon.
There are two more.
When you see all three
moons you'll know,
you've lost the match.
-Tenten, do not play
your opponent's game.
Maintain focus.
TENTEN (VOICEOVER): I know, Lee.
I know.
Well, I was planning to
save this for the finals,
not waste it on a
preliminary round,
but it may be now or never.
-Ha.
-She's using that already?
-What's with the two scrolls?
What is she planning
on doing with them?
-Ha.
It won't work, whatever it is.
-Rising twin dragons.
-Ha.
It doesn't matter how
many you throw at me.
It's all the same.
Moon number two!
-I'm not done!
Ha.
Ha, I've got her now.
-Moon number three.
TENTEN (VOICEOVER): Huh?
Where did she go?
She-- she's gone.
TEMARI: Over here.
TENTEN (VOICEOVER): What?
-Now it's my turn.
Wind Scythe Jutsu!
-Tenten!
-Temari's chakra is
controlling the vertex.
-Huh?
-She fought well,
but she'll never
escape from that whirlwind.
It's over.
-[cough].
-Whoa, that girl's
really ruthless.
-Oh, Tenten.
-Wasn't much of a match.
Kind of boring.
-To be able to stop every one
of Tenten's attacks like that.
-I still cannot believe it.
-It was impressive all right.
Scary.
-Yep, it's another win
for the Sand Village,
just like you said it would be.
-Well, of course.
That's why I said it.
-Well, looks like
we're guaranteed
a clean sweep in this round.
-Hm.
-This Sand team is
clearly one to be feared.
-The winner of the
fifth match, Temari.
-Wait a second.
-Hm?
-Ugh.
-Hey, nice catch.
-What is wrong with you?
She may have lost,
but that is no way
to treat an opponent
who has done her best.
TEMARI: Oh, beat it.
And take that sack
of garbage with you.
-No, Lee!
Lee!
-Leaf Hurricane!
-Not even close.
You know what?
You're as dumb as you look.
-What did you say?
-Lee, stop.
-But Guy sensei.
-Temari, forgot them.
The match is over,
so get up here.
You won.
Why are you wasting your
time with that pathetic loser
and his ridiculous mentor?
-What?
-Just calm down, Lee.
A word of warning.
You Sand villagers have no
idea what Lee is capable of.
Remember, he still
hasn't fought yet.
So I'd be careful if I were you.
-That kid's crazy picking
a fight with them.
Those Sand Village
guys are trouble.
They're the last people
I'd want to go up against.
-They do look almost unbeatable.
SAKURA: Don't worry, Naruto.
I'm sure you could take them.
-Sakura?
What, you're all right?
I never thought you'd
be back so soon.
-I'm fine, but never mind me.
It's you you should
be thinking about.
-Huh?
Me?
I don't have any injuries.
I haven't even fought yet.
-What I meant was you don't
want to disgrace yourself
after you worked so
hard to get here.
Think of what Sasuke will say.
-Oh.
Oh, right.
-Stay sharp.
Oh, thanks, by the way.
-No, Sakura, don't.
You worked so hard
to get here, Sakura.
Don't disgrace yourself now by
losing to that lame Ino girl.
SAKURA: If you hadn't
called out when you did,
who knows what
would have happened?
If it hadn't been for you,
I might not still be here.
-Yeah, that's probably true.
-Oh, you little--
-Here we go.
Let it be me.
Please, let it be me.
-No, it's my turn.
My turn.
-Grr.
-Guess it's me.
-Shikamaru, come on.
You can do it.
You can win this no problem.
-OK, OK.
-All you got to do is tell
yourself, I cannot lose.
Right?
CHOJI (VOICEOVER): Man, when did
she get so darn enthusiastic?
-Remember, he
manipulates shadows.
Watch the shadows.
-Ha.
You think I'd ever fall for
a stupid jutsu like that?
-Yeah, OK.
Here we go, Shikamaru.
Make that little girl cry.
-Oh man, this is such a drag.
I mean, give me a break.
I've got to fight a girl?
-Yeah, you just keep
thinking that way, little ma.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): I knew
what these guys were capable
of from the time we
met them in the forest
during the second exam.
Problem is, I didn't
get a look at her jutsu.
And to make things
worse, she saw mine.
MAN: Ready?
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): Oh, well.
MAN: Sixth match.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
Nothing I can do.
MAN: Shikamaru and Kin.
Begin.
-It's all I've got.
KIN: You're not trying that
stupid shadow thing again, are
you?
-Shut your mouth!
Ninja art, Shadow
Possession Jutsu.
-Is that all you know?
If that's the only
trick you've got,
this is going to be
easier than I thought.
-Bells?
Oh, please.
Not that old trick.
Let me guess.
Next, you'll throw senbon
with bells and senbon
without bells at the same time.
I'll react to the
bells and while I'm
focused on dodging
them, I won't notice
the silent needles coming at me.
Am I right?
Good luck.
-You sure talk a lot, don't you?
-Now I know to be careful to
dodge all the senbon, not just
the ones with the bells.
[bells ringing]
What?
Where?
[bells ringing]
Threads?
Oh, man.
-Too late.
-Ah.
-Shikamaru.
-Well, that didn't take long.
-Hold on, don't be so sure.
He's not beaten yet.
-Huh?
-One inch higher and that
would have been a fatal hit.
OK, now I get a turn.
-Sorry, that was your turn.
-What the-- what's going on?
Ugh.
-You see, you don't ever ask
for whom the bells tolls,
because it tolls for thee.
This bell sends off a
peculiar sound vibration
that travels to the
outer and inner ear,
then directly to the brain.
First comes paralysis, and soon
you'll start hallucinating.
-Uh.
-It won't work.
You can't block the sound out
once it's inside your head.
It's useless.
-I can't tell which one
of them is the real one.
-You can't move
your arms or legs.
And even if you could, you
wouldn't know which one of us
to throw your shadow at.
Face it, you're
cooked, little man.
I'm going to cook you nice
and slow over a hot fire.
-You think it's that easy, huh?
Ah.
-That was three.
Next time, I'll throw five.
Each time, a couple
more till you end up
looking like a hedgehog.
-Stop playing games,
why don't you?
KIN: Hm?
-If you're so tough,
get it over with.
Stop wasting my time.
-I'm sorry.
So you're not a fan of my
slow and painful method, huh?
[bells ringing]
Fine, suit yourself.
We'll do it the quick
way then, and painful.
Wh-- what's wrong?
Can't move my arm.
-Huh.
-It looks like my lame shadow
jutsu was a success after all.
-But you haven't
thrown any shadows.
No way, I made sure of it.
-Ha.
You really still don't see it?
-What do you mean?
SHIKAMARU: Look at that
thread you're holding.
Don't you find it a little
strange that it would even
cast a shadow at this height?
Of course you didn't notice it
because you were concentrating
on other things,
like killing me.
-The shadow spreading out around
me and I didn't see it coming.
-Right.
I stretched my shadow out
along the line of that thread
and followed it
all the way back.
Now I'm attached to you.
-And now, so we mirror
each other's movements.
So what?
A cute trick, but what
do you gain by it?
-Man, you're annoying.
Shut up and watch.
Hm.
-You must be insane.
If you throw that
shuriken at me,
you'll just be
attacking yourself.
-Makes it kind of
interesting, doesn't it?
-You wouldn't.
You couldn't.
-Yeah, like a game of chicken.
Let's see who ducks first.
-You're crazy.
Big deal.
I'll do that, too.
-And that's what I
call using your head.
The wise shinobi carefully
scouts the physical layout
of the battlefield
and never loses
sight of his position on it.
That was her problem.
I made sure she was so
busy focusing on me,
she didn't notice the wall
inches behind her head.
So when we both dodge
backwards, kabong!
Now who's hearing bells?
-Winner of the sixth
match, Shikamaru Nara.
-That a boy, Shikamaru.
-Yeah, way to go.
-Come on.
Come on, me next.
Me next, me next, me.
-Even that good-for-nothing
lazy bum won his match.
When am I going to get my turn?
Ugh.
-Now there's only me left.
MAN: All right, moving
on to the next match.
-There's one Sound
Village ninja left.
There's me, you, Naruto,
Choji, Neji, Lee,
and that Sand Village guy.
Just don't put me up against
him, that's all I ask.
-This year's rookies
look like they
could be quite a challenge.
-Yeah, it's here.
It's here at last, the
moment I've been waiting for.
Finally, I get a chance
to show what I've got.
-Look at that, it's
us against the kid.
Hey, Akamaru, I think you
and I just won the lottery.
[bark]
-I am going to die of old
age before I get my turn.
I just want a chance to show
Sakura what I am made of.
She's going to get
tired of waiting.
All I want is a chance.
-Lee.
LEE: Is that too much to ask?
-He's just like Guy used to be.
-Good luck, Naruto.
Do your best.
-You know it, Sakura.
-It's your moment, Naruto.
Go on, show us.
Show us how much you've grown.
-It's my time to shine.
[theme song]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): This
Kiba guy drives me nuts.
Talk, talk, talk, talk, talk.
And that little mutt of his?
Yap, yap, yap.
I don't know which one
of them's more annoying.
But I don't care, talk all
you want, train all you want.
At the end of the day,
you're all going home,
and I'm going to be Hokage.
Did I say believe it?
Believe it.
Next time, Akamaru unleashed.
Who's top dog now?