[theme]
-Release the genjutsu and
wake Naruto and Shikamaru.
We're going to need both
of for this mission.
-What kind of mission?
-Be careful.
It's the first A-rank assignment
since the Land of the Waves,
[scream]
-You release genjutsu
too, you faker.
Why were you pretending to
be asleep this whole time?
-First, track down
Sasuke and stop him.
Then find a safe location,
and await further orders.
-Did something to Sasuke?
-I'll tell you what
happened on the way.
Now let's go.
-So that's what happened.
I get it.
I guess got all impatient.
-Oh, man.
Why did you have to pull
me into this anyway?
This whole thing is such a drag.
-It can't be helped, OK?
It's Kakashi-sensei's order.
-This way!
-How long until we catch up?
-I don't know.
A long time if they keep
moving at this pace,
-Ugh.
Come on.
NARUTO: A Shirker's
Call to Action!
Layabout No More!
[sniffing]
PAKKUN: Come on, you guys.
Hurry it up!
SAKURA: What is it?
NARUTO: Did you see Sasuke?
PAKKUN: No.
There're two squads behind us.
That's eight ninja.
Wait.
No.
There's one more.
That's nine ninja following us.
-What?
-Aw, man.
Come on already.
Give me a break here.
PAKKUN: It looks
like they haven't
discovered our location yet.
We need to lose them.
Hm.
-Argh!
What's the deal?
Why are we stopping?
-Zip it and follow me.
We're going back
over our footprints.
If we pull this
off, our footprints
will seem to disappear.
-Is this really
gonna do anything?
I mean, they'd have to be pretty
lame ninja if this throws them
off the trail.
-It'll help buy us some time.
That's all we need now.
But if our pursuers
get impatient,
succumb to the
thrill of the chase,
and lose sight of our tracks,
I certainly won't complain.
Know what I mean?
SAKURA: Hurry up
SHIKAMARU: We don't
have all day, you know.
-I know.
Quit bugging me!
-Hm?
[sniffing]
PAKKUN: This is not good.
Be prepared for an ambush.
They're definitely
back on our trail.
SHIKAMARU: Great.
They're probably all
chunin or higher.
We'll be wiped our
if they catch us.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Wiped out?
-Listen, guys.
We don't have much choice.
We're gonna have to ambush them.
-An ambush?
That could work.
SAKURA: It would
give us an advantage.
Even if there are twice as many
of them as there are of us,
if we can just catch
them off-guard.
-No.
It's no good.
I'm afraid that those
ninja chasing us
are Orochimaru's henchmen.
My guess is that
they're all jonin level.
-I really thought
that would work.
But I guess it won't.
-Wait.
Hold on.
Why not?
The level of an opponent doesn't
have much to do with an ambush,
does it?
-Wait.
What are you talking about?
-You guys just don't get.
Let me explain.
Yes.
An ambush is a
key battle tactic,
and can be very beneficial.
But for it to work, you
have to meet two conditions.
-Well, what are they?
Tell us and we'll meet them.
-Number one, the ninja on the
run must be completely quiet,
and must find the enemy first.
Number two, they have
to be able to catch
the pursuers off-guard
at a location
where they can do
a lot of damage
quickly, and then conceal
themselves again just quickly.
And it's only under
those two conditions
that an ambush can
truly be effective.
-Hm.
-Now, the first condition
won't be so hard,
since the ninja hound's
nose can find our enemy.
And the second one also
seems to be in our favor,
since we know the
geography of our village
like we know the
backs of our hands.
However, Orochimaru is
a former Leaf ninja,
so on the second condition
we're out of luck.
-We are?
Wait.
Tell me why that is again.
-Our pursuers have studied
the layout of this village,
and I have to
assume that they've
been put through simulated
practices for this mission.
And on top of that,
they're probably
masters of the Pursue Jutsu.
-So they know all the
cards we're holding.
-Well, I don't really know.
I suppose that an ambush
could give us an advantage.
But so many things
are uncertain.
Besides, our enemy
is a special unit
that was specifically
put together just
for this operation.
And what are the four of us?
A fool, a kunoichi with no
particular talent, a mutt,
and me, the shirker who
doesn't even wanna be here.
SHIKAMARU: Look.
Tactics are about clearly
grasping a tough situation
and formulating the best plan.
And right now, only
one plan makes sense.
Just one.
-And that is?
-A diversion that only
looks like it's an ambush.
So one of us is gonna stay
behind, and slow them down.
-One of us will be a decoy.
-That's right.
If one of us can
delay them, they
shouldn't be able to
find the rest of us.
We'll be able to escape.
Of course, the one who acts
as a decoy will probably die.
So, who's going to do it?
We need to the dog
to follow Sasuke.
So that means
-All right, I guess
then I'm gonna have to--
-I'm the only one who can do it.
-Shikamaru!
-Why does it have to be you?
SHIKAMARU: It's better than all
of us being wiped out, right?
Besides, I'm the
only one of us who's
got a chance of pulling
off this decoy act,
and of surviving this attack.
I mean, after all,
Shadow Possession Jutsu
was invented as a delay tactic.
Anyway, I'll catch
up with you later.
Go on.
Get going.
-We're counting
on you, Shikamaru!
Sakura.
SAKURA: When did Shikamaru
become this dedicated?
Be careful, Shikamaru.
-Huh?
Hm.
No matter how much
you try to erase
the signs of your
passage, we'll find you.
[sniffing] Listen.
The enemy's coming up fast.
SAKURA: What?
-I wonder if he's even
trying back there.
-Me.
The shirker who doesn't
even wanna be here.
-No. don't tell me-- Shikamaru--
-Shikamaru will be
just fine, got it?
-Don't tell me that
he just ran away.
-Look.
I said he'd be OK,
and I meant it.
SAKURA: How do you know?
NARUTO: He's lazy,
and he's always
complaining about everything,
but he would never betray us.
-I know he hardly
ever volunteers
to do anything himself, but
if he says he's gonna do it,
then he'll do it,
and that's for sure.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
I wanna believe.
I do, but--
PAKKUN: Pick up
the pace, slackers.
[sigh]
-I can't believe I
managed to get away.
-His footprints are irregular.
Anxiety is probably
increasing his fatigue.
Huh?
SHIKAMARU: Oops.
Sorry.
I was supposed to be the guy
who didn't want to get involved.
But I guess I'm not quite
what you had expected, am I?
You're right about
one thing-- I'm tired.
On everything
else-- you're wrong.
Like our footprints.
This is what I used
to make the pawprints.
-Why he's just a kid.
I can't believe we
got caught by this.
-So this is the Leaf
Shadow Paralysis Jutsu
we've heard about, huh?
SHIKAMARU: Heh.
Yeah.
If you want to call
it by that old name.
But I'm afraid you're
behind the times.
Now it's called Shadow
Possession Jutsu, old man.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): Oh no.
My chakra's still depleted.
I used too much
chakra then, and now I
can't hang on much longer.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven,
eight-- wait a minute.
Eight?
PAKKUN: No there's one more.
That's nine ninja following us.
-Hm?
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
Of course.
The 9th one's role is to
protect against an ambush.
That person stays at
distance behind the others,
a reserve in case
of an enemy attack.
But I know what to do.
This will draw out 9th ninja,
and reveal where he's hiding.
[chuckling]
[panting]
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
There he is.
Oh, man.
The shadow won't reach.
I don't have enough
stamina to use my chakra
to make it go that far.
-It's futile, kid.
I see through your technique.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
So this is it.
-It looks like
you're at your limit.
This Shadow Possession Jutsu
of yours is going to fail soon.
So, prepare yourself.
[sigh]
-All I really wanted was to
be just an average shinobi,
making an average living.
I'd marry a regular girl who's
not super pretty or super ugly,
have two kids, a
girl and then a boy,
retire when my
daughter got married,
and my son became
a successful ninja.
And spend the rest of my days
just playing Shougi or Go.
A nice carefree and
leisurely retirement.
And then I'd die of
old age before my wife.
Yep.
That's the life I wanted.
And yet I ended up
exerting myself.
It's so unlike me.
Even though I wanted to
finish as just a regular guy,
I had to go and get myself
into this sticky situation.
-Huh.
Looks like those ninja
aren't chasing us anymore.
-Awesome!
Shikamaru succeeded.
The delay tactic worked.
-Shikamaru!
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): I'm sorry
I doubted you even a little.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): OK.
We're half done.
Now we can focus on
catching up to Sasuke.
And Shikamaru, survive and
catch up to us no matter what!
You can do it.
-Heh.
Well, as you say, it
appears I'm at my limit.
Hm.
-Hmph.
-Hey.
Come on out.
And when you do,
cut off his head.
-Well, I finally caught
up with you guys.
-Asuma!
How did you?
-You did well, Shikamaru.
-Yeah.
But it was way too much work.
ASUMA (VOICEOVER): Stay
here for now, Shikamaru.
You've earned it.
TEMARI: Hurry!
KANKURO (VOICEOVER): Ugh.
What a pest.
TEMARI (VOICEOVER): We
have even more pursuers?
Two, no, three.
TEMARI: Kankuro,
we've gotta go faster.
KANKURO: OK, OK.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): I
won't let you get away.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Don't be foolish, Sasuke.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Sasuke.
-Now then, shall we begin this?
[theme music]
NARUTO: Agh!
I have no clue what's going on!
Why is the old man
fighting Orochimaru?
And why is Sasuke
going after those guys?
I don't get why we
have to after 'em,
but I guess we have no choice.
Wait up already, Sasuke!
Next time-- An Unrivaled Match.
Hokage Battle Royale!
What in the world is
happening to our village?