[theme music]
-Keep an eye on Akamaru?
What kind of mission is that?
-As I'm sure you know
by now, our village
was infiltrated by an enemy
ninja while you and the others
were away.
-Sure I heard about it.
But I also heard about how
Kiba and his team found the guy
and took care of him, right?
-Yes, they found him.
-Man, Kiba's so lucky.
How come I ever get a
cool mission like that,
knocking some spy's block off?
-That is not what happened.
Before he could be
secured, the intruder
took his own life by
swallowing a poison capsule.
NARUTO: Whoa.
Why'd he do that?
TSUNADE: Perhaps to take
the secret of his mission
to the grave with him.
Our investigation
revealed he was
a shinobi from a distant
village that specializes
in a unique-- and
uniquely unpleasant--
form of battle skill.
-What kind of battle skill?
I mean, what's so
darn special about it?
-You could call it
biological warfare.
-Huh?
Bio-warfare?
-Mm.
They infect their enemies
with a slow-acting pathogen
that gradually takes
over the host's body.
A terrible transformation
takes place.
-OK.
But what's this got to do
with me following Akamaru?
Huh.
You think-- you
think he's got it?
-There's a good chance
he's been infected.
[Akamaru whimpers]
-He doesn't look well, does he?
-No, he doesn't.
I don't think Akamaru's up
for a round of training today.
I think I'll take
the day off, too.
-All right.
[rustling]
[kiba gasps]
[Akamaru whimpering]
-Hey, Shino, call your bugs off!
Shino, what's gotten into you?
Shino!
-Strange.
They suddenly stopped
listening to me.
-Yeah?
Well, you better work on that.
-I'm sorry.
-OK.
Akamaru and I are
going to take a break.
See you later.
-Poor thing.
What do you think
is wrong with him?
Um, Shino?
-I've never seen the insects
attack a comrade before.
[Akamaru whimpers]
-Hmm?
What is it, Akamaru?
-Gah!
I've been spotted!
Whoa, augh!
[thud]
-What are you doing, Naruto?
-Me?
Oh, nothing, nothing.
Just working on my
tree-climbing jutsu.
And, uh, as you can
see, it needs work.
[birds cawing]
-And there's no mistake, sis?
I don't believe it.
-Sorry, but I'm afraid right now
his chances are 50-50 at best.
I haven't been able
to isolate it yet.
But it's in its
blood, whatever it is.
And it's getting worse.
-What if you made a mistake?
You could be wrong, or--
-How long have I
been a vet, Kiba?
You really think I'd
make a mistake like that?
-No.
Of course not.
[Akamaru barks]
-What is it, boy?
-Hey, what are you doing?
Get off of me!
Come on!
-OK, Akamaru.
It's only Naruto.
Let him go, will you?
I said let go.
Akamaru!
-I thought we were
friends, Akamaru.
-Sorry about that.
But what were you doing sneaking
around in our front yard
anyway?
-Sneaking?
No, I was-- I was, uh.
-Whatever.
Come on in.
After all, he is my dog.
The least I can do
is patch you up.
[naruto shrieks]
-It's OK.
But it's not like
you really want
him going around biting
your friends and neighbors.
Are you sure you're
training him enough, Kiba?
-There.
All done.
They're almost as good as new.
-Uh.
-Um.
-You've been sewing
up animals too long.
It looks like those
pants had major surgery.
-Huh?
What are you talking about?
They look fine to me.
KIBA: Sorry, Naruto.
Maybe you can get
Sakura to fix them.
-OK.
KIBA: Well, good night.
-Yeah.
See you around, Miss Hana.
And thanks a lot.
-Akamaru.
-So, my pants got
torn a little bit.
It's not that big a deal, is it?
-[thinking] Hmm.
First this strange business
with Shino's insects,
then Akamaru attacks Naruto,
someone he knows well.
-Lady Tsunade, there's trouble!
They were in the
middle of training
when they were attacked--
suddenly, and without warning.
-There must have been
quite a few of them
to inflict this much damage.
-No.
In fact, there was
only one assailant.
-What?
One person did all this?
-Not exactly, m'lady.
[tsunade gasps]
-It was one animal.
-No doubt about it.
-Kiba, something's happened.
-If you're talking about
that attack on the shinobi
last night, I already
heard about it.
-But, you don't think--
-Yeah, sis.
It's just what we
were both afraid of.
I'm sure of it.
The scent of blood is on him.
-This is the ninja hound
known as "Akamaru," correct?
-Yeah, so what?
What do you think you're
going to do with him?
A warrant?
-Kiba.
Forget it.
There's nothing you can do.
-Kiba Inuzuka, by
order of the Hokage,
your dog Akamaru is to be placed
in the custody of the ANBU
Black Ops.
-Yeah?!
-Kiba.
We have to obey
the Hokage's order
whether we like it or not.
[Akamaru whimpers]
-Darn it!
Akamaru.
-Here.
-OK, sis.
Thanks a lot.
-There's a batch
of vaccine inside
I hadn't finished testing.
Just make sure it gets
to the vet over there.
-Got it.
See you later.
[kiba sighs]
-Naruto?
-Did you really do what
they're saying you did?
You had Akamaru detained?
-He's the one who attacked
the shinobi last night,
all the evidence points to it.
There was no choice.
It had to be done.
The medical corps
is doing everything
they can to find an antidote.
Don't despair-- yet.
-Yet?
And what if they're not
able to find one, huh?
What's going to happen
to Akamaru then?
-In that case, Akamaru
will have to be put down.
-Don't worry.
I'm sure the medical corps
will find an answer soon.
He'll be fine.
-Yeah, right.
-Try looking in on
him again later.
-OK, thanks.
Quiet, boy.
Nobody's going to
take you away from me.
-We just got word that Kiba took
Akamaru out of the hospital.
Lady Tsunade, what
do you want us to do?
-We have to prepare
for the worst.
Have the Special Pursuit Corps
report to me immediately.
-The Special Pursuit Corps?
Hey, don't tell
me you're thinking
about doing something drastic.
Don't just sit there, answer me!
-This is hard for me, too.
-I'm out of here.
[door slams]
-Hey, any sign of them?
-No.
-Kiba!
Kiba!
-Whatever this thing
is, it's getting worse.
Akamaru?
-Where are they?
-They have to be
somewhere nearby.
-I promised I'd protect
you, no matter what.
I promised that you'd
never have to go
through anything
like that ever again.
SHIZUNE: M'lady, the leader
of the Special Pursuit
Corps is here.
-Enter.
-OK.
Come on, come on, Kiba.
Where are you hiding?
-There.
Follow that, I dare you.
[Akamaru growls]
-This vial contains
a serum for Akamaru
that the Medical
Corps came up with,
but it's far from
being a sure thing.
In fact, there's a 50%
chance it'll prove fatal.
There's also a risk
that the side effects
could make Akamaru's condition
even worse than it is now.
And if that should happen, well.
You know what you have to do.
-Lady Tsunade, we
just received word
from the first team of trackers.
They report that they've lost
Kiba and Akamaru's trail.
-M'lady?
[howling]
-What was that?
-Akamaru?
-Kiba, hey!
You OK?
Gah!
[Akamaru growls]
-Whoa, what is that?
What is it?
-It's Akamaru.
Now go.
You think I'm going to let
you take him from me, huh?
-What the heck do you
think you're doing?
I
-Know why you're here.
But you're not
going to touch him!
-You're wrong.
I just came because I
was worried about you.
-You lie!
The Hokage's given you
orders, hasn't she?
-Akamaru will have
to be put down.
-Never going to happen.
I won't let you do
it, you understand?
No one takes Akamaru away!
-Kiba, you're wasting
time fighting with me!
There's some kind of Special
Pursuit Corps on your trail.
That's what you ought
to be worried about.
-What?
-Whoever these special
pursuit hotshots are,
they're going to
be here any second.
And I've got a feeling Akamaru's
going to be in real trouble
when that happens.
So you and I have go to
think of something fast.
Come on, this is no time
for you to be fighting
with the only friend you've got!
[Akamaru roars]
-Stop it, Kiba.
Don't be an idiot!
-Just shut up!
-There.
Akamaru's just up ahead.
[kiba and naruto both gasp]
FEMALE VOICE: Kiba, Naruto.
Just stay out the way.
-No.
That's the Special
Pursuit Corps?
-Sis?
No.
No way.
Hana, come on.
Is this is a joke?
What's that thing?
Are you going to
use that on Akamaru?
-This is a serum that the
Hokage thinks could work.
And yes, I'm going
to use it on him.
-Really?
Do you think that stuff
is going to cure him?
-Perhaps.
Perhaps not.
There's a very
strong possibility
the side effects will
only make him worse.
But it's the only chance
we've got, all right?
But if it doesn't cure
him, we'll have no choice.
Understand?
-No, I can't.
-Snap out of it.
What's wrong with you?
At least we've got a
chance to save him.
That's a lot more
than we had before.
OK, I'm ready to help.
Let's do it!
Multi-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
-All right, Kiba.
If you're not going to
help, do me a favor.
Stay out of the way.
-Come on, Kiba.
-Forget him, Naruto.
You're wasting your time.
Let's go.
-We'll save you, Akamaru.
Don't worry.
-Do not let him move.
Do whatever you can
to pin him down.
-Right.
[hana yells]
-We have no other choice now.
Our only option is terminator.
-Stop!
Stop it now.
Akamaru.
-Kiba?
-Kiba.
-Akamaru.
What's wrong, boy?
Have you forgotten my scent?
We've always been
together, haven't we?
We grew up together.
Akamaru, please.
Somewhere in there,
somewhere, there
has to be a part of
you that remembers.
Show me that you remember.
Akamaru!
[Akamaru roars]
-No!
-Forgive me.
Can you?
I know that I've brought you
nothing but pain and suffering.
I broke my word.
I swore I'd always protect you.
Akamaru?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I wasn't
a better master.
I'm here, here for you, forever.
-Kiba.
No.
-Kiba!
HANA: I don't know if
he would have made it
if the Medical Corps
hadn't arrived so quickly.
TSUNADE: He was fortunate
that Akamaru's attack
missed any vital organs.
By all rights, Kiba
should have been-- well.
It's remarkable, really.
He's a very lucky guy.
-You're wrong.
-Hey, you're awake.
-It was more than luck that
saved me from that attack.
It was him.
Akamaru missed on purpose.
He used the last of his strength
to shift the attack just
enough.
He fought the monster within
him as hard as he could.
And he won.
-Pretty brave, Akamaru.
-He sure is.
Thanks, boy.
[theme music]
-There are many dark legends
in the world, tales of demons
and mysterious monsters
passed down from generation
to generation, the
stuff of nightmares.
What happens when these monsters
become real and step out
of the legends and
into our village?
How well will the
Leaf Ninja do when
they have to face these demons
and confront their own fears?
-Next time, A Legend from
Hidden Leaf: The Onbaa!