[theme song]
-You've got to help me, sensei!
[scream]
-What?
-Ah!
My heart, my heart!
What the?
I can't believe I'm still alive.
-Hey, what are you doing here?
Using a transformation
jutsu, huh?
-Would somebody like to tell
me what just happened in there?
-Just shut up.
If you know what's
good for you you'll
forget about what you just saw.
-Hey!
You're Yakumo, aren't you?
I came out here
because I want to ask
you some questions
about Kurenai-sensei.
Darn it.
Wait a sec.
Is this a hallway
in the academy?
YAKUMO: Sensei, please.
Tell me why you don't
think I'm good enough.
-Kurenai-sensei?
-I want to become a ninja
more than anything in my life.
I just have to become one!
-I already told you,
you should give up.
-I can't!
-Then I'll have to
perform a sealing jutsu.
If I seal your power
you can't keep going.
-Huh?
Hey, Kurenai-sensei!
Why are you being like this?
[loud banging]
[scream]
Oh.
Hey, Sakura.
Um, question-- where am I?
And how the heck did I
wind up lying in bed?
Wait, I know.
Kurenai-sensei got
stabbed, and my heart
was pulled out of my chest.
No, that's not it.
Where's that girl?
You know, Yakumo?
-You don't remember
any of it, do you?
You got caught red-handed
breaking into a safe house
in the mountains, you idiot!
The Anbu black ops got you.
You should be counting
your lucky stars
you're even alive right now.
-Oh, that's right!
But that dream I had-- it
felt like it really happened.
Maybe Yakumo's the
one they're guarding
in that villa, or something.
-What in the world are
you blabbing about?
I'm gonna give you a shot if you
don't start making sense soon.
-I can't just sit
here doing nothing.
-Get back here, Naruto!
The medicine hasn't
worn off yet!
-Hey, sensei!
Open up, will ya?
-Don't waste your time.
She already left.
Hey, since you're
up so early anyway,
what do you say you join me
for an early morning marathon?
-This ain't exactly
the best time.
-Early morning
marathons are great.
All that healthy
marathon sweat purges
impurities that might
build up in your body
over a night of sleep.
-Yeah.
Listen, can you tell me where
Kurenai-sensei ran off to?
-Come to think of it, she didn't
mention paying someone a visit.
Something about a
former student of hers
who was in pretty bad shape.
-She means Yakumo.
-At least join me for my
morning stretch routine.
All that healthy,
stretching sweat
purges impurities
that might build up
in your body over a
long night of sleep.
-Kurenai-sensei, wait up!
Whoa!
Before you go any further, I
just gotta ask you something.
-Naruto.
You'd be smart if you
turned around right now
and left this thing alone.
-Listen to me.
Yesterday I went to see Yakumo.
And maybe this is
somehow related,
but I just had this crazy
dream that seemed so real.
-A dream?
-Yeah.
You were telling me
Yakumo that you'd
use a sealing jutsu on
her unless she gave up
her goal of becoming a ninja.
-Sorry.
I'm in a hurry.
-Huh?
Hey, hold on a sec!
-This is none of your business.
-Sorry.
I'm making it my business.
Something weird's gotta
be going on with you.
Hinata, Kiba and
Shino are freaking out
because you said
you're quitting.
You honestly gonna
look me in the eye
and try to convince me
that Yakumo has nothing
to do with you
quitting squad eight?
-What you experienced earlier
wasn't just a realistic dream.
I did use a sealing
jutsu on her.
I took away my own
student's power.
-I don't get it.
How could you do that?
-It all happened a
little over a year ago.
With my own hands I crushed her
dream of becoming a shinobi.
Up until then I'd been giving
her special one-on-one training
to unlock her hidden genjutsu.
-You're kidding me!
-But I failed her.
I can't be trusted with the
lives of the squad eight ninja.
-But why did you do it?
-This discussion is over.
Now if you'll please
get out of my way.
-Wait, that's it?
But I still have so much to ask!
-I have no choice.
-What the heck is
going on around here?
I can't break free.
Kurenai-sensei!
Now you're just bring cruel!
-We're already surrounded.
Send an alert to the village.
-Sir.
-There they are!
-What the?
-Take this message.
Fly quickly.
You must warn the Hokage.
-Miss Yakumo, we have
orders to take you in.
-Can you believe that guy?
That jerk could have
at least thanked me
for sitting by his
bedside all night long.
Huh?
[scream]
-Can't I take a break?
What about afternoon tea?
-Only after you've taken
care of all these documents.
-What's up with all
this paperwork, anyway?
How'd we get this backed up?
-Because someone doesn't
like to do her work promptly.
-It's a carrier pigeon
with an urgent message!
-What?
It's from the safe
house on Satomi Hill.
Something has
happened to Yakumo!
We've just received
an important alert.
Yakumo, a girl under
Leaf Village protection,
may have been kidnapped.
You will head to the
villa in the Satomi hills.
Your mission is to get Yakumo.
-Hm.
Yakumo Kurama.
As I recall she's the girl
Kurenai was taking care of,
wasn't she?
-Mm.
The only daughter of Murakumo,
the head of the Kurama clan.
-Um, excuse me, but
who's the Kurama clan?
-Right.
You kids probably
don't know about them.
They were once a
distinguished clan
that wielded a lot of
power in the village.
But they've lost
much of their status.
The whole mess
started a year ago.
They lost the leader of
their family, Murakumo,
along with his beloved wife.
And after that the rest of the
clan pretty much fell apart.
-And now the only daughter
of the head of the clan
is kidnapped.
Do you think that
means someone's
trying to steal the Kurama's
secret family jutsu?
-That may be.
-According to records handed
down from the third Hokage
there is a huge power lying
dormant within Yakumo,
one that is extremely dangerous.
-That means if
someone can figure out
how to awaken her powers she
would become a powerful weapon.
And where there's
power to be had
you can bet somebody
will try to get it.
-Ever since the
death of her parents
we've been keeping
Yakumo under lock and key
for her own protection.
-Right.
I'm on the case.
A damsel in distress
is a job for me.
The beautiful green
beast Might Guy
will come to her rescue,
no matter the danger.
-Sakura, you'd
better go with him.
-What?
-Huh?
-Once we have Yakumo
in custody we'll
need someone to look
after her condition.
Preferably someone who's been
trained as a medical ninja.
-Uh-- yes!
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Finally I get
the chance to put
all my training
to use on a real mission.
-Ah!
Ow.
-Are you OK?
Did you trip on a
root or something?
-What in the world?
-Naruto?
-Leave it to Naruto to
fall asleep in the bushes.
-Nice, Akamaru.
HINATA (VOICEOVER): Oh, Naruto.
-Wait a second.
I think he's under a genjutsu.
Release.
-Sakura?
That's salty!
What the heck is on my face?
What's going on?
Did I just fall asleep again?
-Could you please stop babbling.
-Apparently somebody
used genjutsu on you.
-Genjutsu?
The last thing I remember
was chasing Kurenai-sensei
toward that villa
on Satomi Hill.
She wouldn't even
stop and listen to me.
-The villa on Satomi Hill?
Naruto, was Kurenai
travelling there by herself?
-Yeah, probably.
-She has no idea what
she's getting herself into.
Kurenai's in danger.
KURENAI (VOICEOVER):
This doesn't feel right.
Someone's here.
Darn it.
I should have known
better than to come alone.
But now there's no time
to return to the village.
What could they want here?
Yakumo!
-It's trapping me!
-Sorry to tie you up like this,
but we can't have nosy people
like you interfering
with our work.
-Did you really think that
was enough to ensnare me?
-What?
-Sorry, but you're the
one who's getting tied up.
These enemies have genjutsu.
If I'm going to live
I'd better be careful.
What is this presence?
They're both caught in
some sort of genjutsu.
[crying]
-Yakumo?
Yakumo, is that you?
[crying]
Thank goodness you're alive.
-Please help me!
-It'll be all right.
I'm here now.
No matter what
happens, I promise
I'll make sure you're safe.
-Oh, Kurenai-sensei.
Ah.
-Release.
You were hit with
a reverse genjutsu?
-Sir.
I'm sorry.
-Probably a jonin.
In fact it sounds exactly
like Kurenai Yuhi.
Everyone, watch out.
They'll be coming for us.
Leaf Village ninja
are on their way.
-Sir!
They two who went to get
Yakumo haven't returned yet.
MAN (VOICEOVER): Oh well.
Then I guess violence
can't be avoided.
-Forget that you come
from the same clan.
Take out that girl by
any means necessary.
Got it?
-Right!
-Hey, what's the matter, Hinata?
-Did you see something?
-Somebody's attacking
that mountain villa
right this very minute.
There are four out
front and four inside.
-I wonder if two of
the people inside
might be Kurenai and Yakumo.
-Yeah, I bet you're
right about that.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Kurenai-sensei,
what have you gotten
yourself into?
Tell us what's going on!
[theme song]
KURENAI (VOICEOVER):
I'm surprised.
I never would have thought
the enemy would turn out
to be you, of all people.
Whatever your reasons may
be, you're not taking Yakumo.
Don't you see?
The third Hokage entrusted
me with her life.
Even if you are lethal
masters of genjutsu,
I'll use all my powers
to protect this child.
NARUTO: Next time-- Kurenai's
Top Secret Mission--
The Promise With
The Third Hokage!