[theme music]
-All the pieces are in
place and ready to go.
-So, brother.
That's the Land of
Greens you told us about?
-It sure doesn't
look like much, but I
guess it's a stepping stone
to bigger things, huh?
-Half the village officials
have been bought and paid for.
At our signal, the castle will
be overthrown from within.
By day's end, we'll
be feudal lords.
How do you like
the sound of that?
-Feudal lords?
-I like it fine.
TSUNADE: No matter
what combination
I try, the problem
still remains.
Of the ninja that
I have available,
there's no one to take the lead.
-Well, it's only escort duty
for caravan of merchants.
I'm sure they'll be
able to handle it,
no matter who you
end up sending.
-It's not the difficulty
of the mission.
I'm worried about it's
impressing the client.
The Land of Greens hired us
for this one, and you see,
the lord of that land
was very good to me once.
-I remember.
He paid off that gigantic
gambling debt of yours.
I'm not really sure he
was doing you a favor.
-It's just a little place,
but so lovely and peaceful.
I remember a charming
little princess
with two handsome young ninja
bodyguards looking after her.
Foolish boys, always
fighting over me.
Both of them were
dying to marry me.
I wonder if they
still feel the same.
-I wouldn't hold your breath.
-They must be all
grown up by now.
-We'll cross the border soon.
-Take a last look.
It'll be a while.
-Finally!
A real mission!
-Please, Naruto.
Not so fast!
-All this time, I've just
been stuck doing stupid chores
around the village
while everybody else get
to go on missions.
I'm so sick of having to listen
to other peoples adventures.
-Well, I wouldn't
get too excited.
It's only basic escort duty
for some traveling merchants.
-It's OK.
We'll just make up something
like we ran into 1,000 bandits.
Don't worry, we'll have a
story to tell when we get back.
-So he can brag about it.
-There.
It's the guys we're looking for.
Hey!
Hold on!
-Who are you?
We're here to help,
if you're the caravan
from the Land of
Greens, that is.
-Yes we are.
-Well that's perfect.
Me and my buddies here have
been sent to be your escort.
-From where?
-Check it out.
Hidden Leaf village.
-We're here to help out, in
case you run into some bandits.
-Then it's true.
-I'm Naruto Uzumaki, and
this is my friend, Hinata.
-I'm Choji Akimichi.
-Oh, and our, uh, Hokage
gave us one more piece
of identification so you can be
absolutely sure we are who we
s--
-What are you doing, Momiji?
Give that back.
-It's true.
They must be who
they say they are.
Look what this says!
Leaf Village Moving Service!
-What the heck is that?
-That grandma.
She's full of surprises.
-Well, in that case,
my name's Kikusuke,
and this is Yorinoshin,
and this is Shun.
-And I'm Momiji.
We need more pushers.
I'm glad you've come!
-More what?
-You eat a lot, don't you?
I guess that explains why you're
so fa-- --bulously strong!
-Hm.
Want some?
-I admire people who
are really strong.
-Aw, this is nothing, kid.
I've hardly even broken a sweat.
Hang on!
-Look at that show off.
He's gonna be sorry.
-Let's talk and
more effort, you.
We're falling behind schedule.
-Being pack animals isn't
usually part of our job.
And anyway.
How come you're the only one
who doesn't have to push?
-He, uh-- He can't.
Our poor cousin Shun is
not very well, you see?
-Oh.
-Oh, don't worry, cousins.
Nothing he says
could ever offend me.
Good for nothing
weaklings like that boy
are always finding excuses.
-Good for nothing weakling, huh?
Well eat my dust, mister!
-I think you guys may have
pushed yourselves too hard.
-I apologize for Shun's
rudeness back there.
Here.
Have some water.
Huh?
-Mine is empty too.
Are we all out?
-Nope.
Here's some more.
Cold and fresh.
Catch!
-Thanks!
Hey, how'd you find water
in a place like this?
-My grandma taught
me a trick she knows!
-Grandma?
-I'll show you.
You use these.
NARUTO: Huh?
But how?
-It's called dousing.
You just concentrate hard
on what you're looking for,
and they react when you're
getting close to it.
It's a trick we learned
from our ancestor.
-Whoa.
I could use something like that.
I lost some money the other day
and it's been driving me crazy.
-Not as sweet as the
water in the Land
of Greens, but it's water.
-What kind of place is the
land of Greens, anyway?
MAN: It's a small place.
It lies sheltered deep
within the mountains.
Its people live in perfect
harmony with each other
in with the world around them.
It was almost like
a paradise on Earth.
-Was like?
MAN: Oh, I mean--
-What gives?
How come if it's
such a great place
they have to hire
protection from outsiders?
-By taking peace
for granted, they
guaranteed it wouldn't last.
-Huh?
-OK, what's that
supposed to mean?
-Living in peace
and harmony might
sound like a beautiful
thing, but the people
of the Land of Greens
have been living that way
so long that they've
become soft and unprepared.
In times like these,
you'd have to be blind
or a fool not to expect
the worst of others.
-Now, now.
They've done nothing
to do deserve
such disrespectful talk.
Are you forgetting how kind
and hospitable the Lord
of the Land of Greens was?
And we were just passing
through his village.
-Ha.
-He didn't even listen
to the old lady.
That guy's got a serious
attitude problem.
Hey, he's your cousin, right?
Can't you do
something about him?
-Uh, well--
-He's had some tough
times recently.
-Oh, uh, OK.
-Hey!
Careful up there!
Watch your step!
Don't get near the edge!
-Look, Choji.
What's what?
-Naruto!
I
-What's going on?
-Look at that.
-Whoa, smoke.
-That's right where the
Land of Greens is, isn't it?
-I don't like the look of that.
I'm gonna get on over there
and find out what's up.
You guys go ahead.
-Hey.
We don't want everyone else in
the caravan getting worried,
so let's just keep this to
ourselves for right now, OK?
-Right, Our secret.
-Choji, where's Naruto?
-Um, the bathroom.
-I'll let you have
them if you tell me
what it was you saw back there.
-We saw smoke rising.
Lots of black smoke.
-Black smoke rising?
Which direction?
-From the Land of Greens.
-My lord.
Shun, it's finally come.
-According to this,
I'll cross the border
of the Land of Greens
right afte-- Ah!
Man.
Where'd that come from?
There was no one
around a minute ago.
Who's there?
What's the big idea?
MAN: From the looks
of your headband,
you must be one of
the Hidden Leaf.
-So what?
It's a headband, not a target!
What are you attacking
me for, anyway?
Far as I know, I don't
have a gripe against you,
whoever you are!
MAN: The ones we're after
are headed in this direction.
You just happened
to get in the way,
and anyone who gets
in our way dies!
Got him.
-Substitution jutsu.
-Hey, I'm up here!
Man, these two jokers
are pretty good.
-Only two left, so one of
them must be the real one.
What?
-Too bad!
You came so close!
You were only off by one.
Well, so much for them.
I've got to get
back to the others.
Choji, Hinata!
-Well, what did you find out?
-In a word, trouble.
Listen up, everybody.
Let's take a little break, OK?
-What?
-What is he talking about?
-So they were from
the Land of Greends?
-They said that the
ones they were after
were headed in this direction.
-But why?
Why would ninjas want
to attack this group?
It's just a caravan of
traveling merchants.
They're harmless.
And according to them, the Land
of Greens treated them kindly.
-Yeah, well who knows?
Don't look at me.
-So what do we do?
-I say we take them
on, if they're really
dumb enough to
try and attack us.
-That could be dangerous.
What about the chlildren,
and the old ones?
-I forgot about them.
-Hold on.
Why go out of our way
looking for trouble when
it'd be a whole lot
easier to go around it?
-What the heck's that
supposed to mean?
-You ever stop and think?
Maybe we just happen to
be taking the same route
as their real target.
Maybe we're not even the ones
these guys are after, you know?
-Yeah, you're right.
So if we just get off this
road and take a different once,
maybe we can just avoid the
whole problem all together!
Yes!
OK, everyone!
Change of plans!
We're gonna take
another route to avoid
some really vicious
ninja up ahead!
-Some vicious ninja?
-I don't think I would've
put it like that, Naruto.
Now you've got everyone nervous.
-You think?
-Don't worry!
It's not us they're after.
Nevertheless, we think
it would probably best
to try to avoid them.
So we'll take the trail
that cuts off to the side
just ahead.
It may be a little
out of our way,
but better safe than sorry.
-Is that really all
the treasure there is?
What kind of a
feudal lord is this?
-Unfortunately, one too honest
to line his own pockets.
But of course, that all
changes starting right now.
More importantly, has there
been any sign of the young lady?
-Not yet, but those two we sent
out to find her were attacked.
Now at least we know
which way she's headed.
-Just getting the
girl's not enough.
If any of the others
get away, they
might get a hold
of reinforcements
from another land and come back.
If only the sun were
a little stronger,
I could have burned down this
whole mountain with my jutsu.
-Heh, heh, heh.
Leave it to me.
-Excuse me, Lord Renga.
All the local people who
have sworn allegiance to you
have gathered in the main hall.
-Good.
We're very grateful.
Without the help of
turncoats such as yourself,
we never could have carried the
castle's defenses so easily.
-Well, brother, what do you say?
Should we go to the hall and
greet our new supporters?
-Go on.
I'll take care of things here.
-Now, as to the
reward you promised.
-Ah, yes.
Your reward.
Of course.
Go on and help yourself.
Take as much as you like.
-You're so generous, my lord!
-Isn't it funny
how some people are
so gullible and easy to deceive?
-You can say that
again, o wise one.
Our lord was such a fool that
he trusted us to the very end.
-Don't stuff too
much in your pockets,
or you might sink the
ferry carrying you
across the river of oblision.
-Huh?
-You're quite right.
Only a fool would
trust the likes of you.
A fat, greedy weasel who has
already betrayed one master.
-You-- you're
joking, Lord Renga.
No I'm afraid it's no joke.
[shouting]
-So you had me gather all the
others together just so you
could--
-You wanted your reward?
Well, then here it is.
-There, that should do it.
-There can no
longer be any doubt.
They're definitely
coming after us.
-Yes.
-Stay with Lady Haruna.
-Why?
What are you're going to do?
-We can't wait for
them to attack.
There's too many in
the caravan to defend.
If I can find them
first, there's
a chance I can divert them.
Slow them down.
But see, there's three of them.
Rogue ninja with
unknown powerful jutsu.
-I know what they say, but
I'm confident my jutsu will
be more than a match for theirs.
-Very well, then.
Good luck, Hikunojo.
-Thank you, Lady Haruna.
-It's all right.
I've set traps for anyone
who could be following us.
-Yu're always such a
worry wart, Hinata.
I'm sure we won't need need 'em.
-Say, where's Kikusuke?
-Hey, yeah.
What happened to him?
-Oh, uh, there was
something he needed to do.
He'll be back.
-He can't do that.
Just run off and
leave the caravan
any time he wants to-- oh.
I get it.
Something he needed to do.
-What is it?
-Let's just say he had
to take a little break
to go water a tree.
-Naruto.
-I will protect Lady Haruna
with my life if need be.
There you are.
So who are you?
-I'm called Ruiga.
How very bold of you to
come face us on your own.
That clinches it.
She's in that
caravan, isn't she?
-I don't know where
your friends are,
but one rogue
ninja I can handle.
-Heh.
You sure about that?
-Witness the flower ninja
art of the Land of Greens!
Flower Shuriken, Flying
Flower, Falling Foliage!
-Nice try.
-I'm just getting started.
-Huh?
-Flower Ninja Art,
Release Myraid of Flowers!
Ninja Art, Mirror
Flower Water Moon!
-A bouquet of paper bombs, eh?
Clever, but futile.
And now some genjutsu, I see.
Hm?
-And now for the final blow.
Flower Ninja Art Bloom!
Myriad of Flowers!
-Is this were a garden
party, your flower jutsu
would take first prize, but
against me, it's useless.
And now it's my turn!
Try this.
Water Style, Liquid Memory.
[theme music]
NARUTO: Hm.
What exactly is the
Running Ramen strategy?
HINATA: Oh, it's
just another name
for splitting up,
dispersing our forces.
CHOJI: Right!
Giving our enemies more
targets to go after.
NARUTO: What happens
if the ramen spills
while we're running?
HINATA: It's just a metaphor.
NARUTO: Or what if it gets cold?
Maybe it should be the Running
Ramen with Protective Lid
strategy.
HINATA: Whatever
you say, Naruto.
CHOJI: I'm starting to think
you really don't get it, do you?
NARUTO: Next time, Mystery
of the Targeted Merchants!
[theme music]