[theme music]
-Now, Sand Coffin.
I'll handle this.
-No, please.
Just back me up.
I got sand in my mouth!
Will you please let go of me?
-You're not doing anything
in your present state.
I've got this.
-Do not let your guard down.
He uses his bones to attack.
He can launch them like
you saw before, and forces
them to protrude from his body.
He is able to control
them all at will!
-You're Gaara of the Desert.
You wield sand.
Hence the name.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Showdown!
Gaara Versus Kimimaro!
KIMIMARO (VOICEOVER): That
sand is a strong defense,
but he's definitely not
the close combat type.
Getting close will probably
be difficult, though.
Here he comes.
Digital Shrapnel!
LEE (VOICEOVER): Nothing
is waste in his movement.
His level of Taijutsu
is considerable.
-His attacks and
defense are as one.
All achieved with sand.
But the sand which he
can wield is probably
limited to the amount
that fits in that gourd.
Gaara of the Desert.
Rather a foolish
nickname, isn't it?
You're nothing without
that sand of yours.
Why else would you go
through the trouble
of lugging it around?
-Sand Shower.
-What a surprise.
-But as long as I have
it, I can do anything.
The only fool here is you.
If I need more
sand, I can easily
use the Earth to make more.
LEE (VOICEOVER): Of
course, now I see.
All of thie time, he has
been feeding his own sand
into the ground, and
using it to grind up
the stones and the minerals
in the Earth beneath us,
creating new sand.
Gaara of the Desert.
They do not call him
that for nothing.
Amazing.
You did it!
-Almost.
Sand Burial!
When I look at this guy,
it reminds me of him.
Uchiha.
His eyes.
Sasuke had the same
eyes this guy does.
-The same eyes?
GAARA (VOICEOVER):
Seeking to prove
the value of their
own existence.
Eyes like that.
-Sasuke!
Sasuke!
I know you're in here!
Come on!
Answer me!
I don't get it!
What's gotten into you?
[wicked laughter]
KIMIMARO (VOICEOVER): I
don't hate the darkness.
It was in the darkness
that I was raised.
-Why?
It's not fair.
Why am I in a place like this?
Why me?
I don't get it.
What did I do wrong?
Is there really a
god watching over us?
And if God does
exist, how could he
let something like
this happen to me.
Who's there?
-It doesn't matter who.
Get out.
Kimimaro, the time has
come for you to be of use.
Be ready.
For the sake of the Kaguya
clan, you will fight!
KIMIMARO (VOICEOVER): Yes.
Fighting.
That is the only
thing I can do now.
-Im-- Impossible.
-That sure was a
lot of pressure.
If I hadn't grown a membrane
of bone underneath my skin,
I would've been crushed
beyond recognition.
-More bones.
He's a monster.
A freak.
-Well, he certainly
is a nuisance.
-I underestimated you.
But that's the last time
I'll get caught in your sand.
-Sand Tsunami!
LEE (VOICEOVER): Whoa.
So much sand.
He cannot evade or attack.
To think that he could
change the terrain itself.
You-- You did it!
-No.
Not yet.
Giant Sand Burial!
LEE (VOICEOVER):
He is so powerful.
He is even stronger than
when we fought each other.
Well, surely this time--
-Why won't he give up?
-What?
[heartbeart]
KIMIMARO (VOICEOVER):
I'm still alive.
If so, there must
be a reason for it.
MAN: We descend upon the
Village Hidden in the Mist
under the cover of night.
We all feel the sting
of the recent betrayal.
Well, tonight,
they'll see savagery
like they've never known!
Show these scum the ferocity
of our clan, down every last
a man, woman, and child.
-Yeah!
-What are you waiting
for, Kimimaro?
Get going, already.
-I'm not sure what to do.
-What's there to think about?
Go down to the
Village of the Mist
and kill every single
person you come across.
Just follow your instincts.
It'll come to you.
-Are you from the mist village?
-No.
-I-- I see.
Sorry.
-Haku.
-No, it's nothing.
Sorry, Zabuza.
-We don't have time
for daydreaming.
Get a move on.
-Right.
His eyes were the same as
mine, before I met Zabuza.
-Just a moment.
Hasty, aren't you?
Put your dagger away.
I'm not from this village.
What you're seeking is just
below this ridge, child.
Go on.
Have at it.
It seems they've begun.
The Kaguya clan.
What a bunch of idiots.
They understand nothing
other than the sword.
The days are gone when
a horde of savages
could go slaughtering
all in their path.
Brute strength is nothing in the
face of a regimented military.
These fools are
rushing to their death.
-Are we all that is
left of the clan, then?
-That's right.
And it looks like
we're surrounded.
-Their defenses were stronger
than we'd thought they'd be.
-Nothing we can do about it.
Just take out as many of them
as you can before you go.
[laughter]
-Come o Let's show
them a good time!
KIMIMARO (VOICEOVER): What
is it that I fight for?
What am I?
Having none of these answers,
I continued to fight.
-The time has come
for you to be of use.
KIMIMARO (VOICEOVER):
Someone needed me.
That was all that
got my body moving.
That-- and the
obvious, of course.
I had to fight in
order to survive.
[scream]
KIMIMARO (VOICEOVER):
Dawn broke.
And I realized I was the
only one who had survived.
I'm alone.
Again.
I was on my own, wandering
aimlessly from place to place.
This is--
The flower from before.
Why are you blooming
in a place like this?
How come you won't
answer me, huh?
Oh, so you're going to
ignore me too, then?
Who cares, anyway?
It's not like anyone
will see you here.
-That will do.
Maybe, just maybe, there
is no purpose in life.
But if you linger a while
longer in this world,
you might discover
something of value in it.
Like how you
discovered that flower.
Or how I discovered
you one fateful night.
[laughter] Come.
It's time to go.
KIMIMARO (VOICEOVER):
That's what
Lord Orochimaru
said to me that day.
But people are
born for a reason.
That's what I think.
They have something they're
meant to do with their lives.
And I am no different.
I was put on this earth to
protect Lord Orochimaru.
And his ambitions.
-Wait a minute.
What is that?
-Sasuke, come on!
You've gotta come back!
Everyone's worried about you.
[laughter]
-Oh, man.
I can't see anything in here.
The darkness is too thick.
NEJI: Sometimes your eyes
are even better than mine.
-Huh?
-Sasuke is in the darkness now.
-Neji?
-If you stay here too long,
you'll never catch Sasuke.
-Neji!
You're right.
You were right about all of it.
What am I standing
around here here?
Just you wait!
I'm gonna bring
Sasuke home for sure!
If it's the last thing I do!
Sasuke!
GAARA: Sand Coffin!
-What is that form?
[theme music]
LEE: You saved me.
I am in your debt.
To think you could
do such a thing!
-He was persistent, but
this is the end for him.
He's not getting up again.
Brainwashed by Orochimaru.
-I wasn't brainwashed!
My master understands me.
How could you ever understand?
NARUTO: Next time, Vengeful
Strike, The Bracken Dance!
[theme music]