[theme music]
JIRAIYA: At the base of
these mountains here,
we can stop at the
most bustling outpost
in all the Land of Rice Paddies.
NARUTO: Aw, you're just
looking for crazy hot spots
in the name of
research, Pervy Sage.
-Yeah, enough's enough already.
We were barely able to
shake off the bodyguards
from the last place
you dragged us to.
-Mm-hm.
[sigh]
-Listen, you two.
I know what you're saying, but
we don't have a choice here.
This is the only way to find
the Village Hidden in the Sound.
I don't like it any better
than you do, all right?
Still, that's the
predicament we're in.
Sometimes you have to stomach
things you might not like.
And I'm just the man to do it.
OK, let's go!
Come on, you slowpokes.
Quit dragging those feet.
Investigation.
What a chore!
Investigation--
-Peppy, isn't he?
-You can't teach an
old dog new tricks.
MAN: Hey, you!
Get back here!
[drunken singing]
-Watch it!
-Aw, man.
Look at this dump.
It's even worse
than the last one.
-Seriously.
Let's just pass on
through this place
and keep looking for the
Hidden Sound village.
[giggling]
[sigh]
-So, uh--
-Look, I don't have
anymore money, OK?
-Yeah, forget it.
I don't have any
money left, either.
-Here.
I want you guys to go
get some food with that,
and wait in the temple
on the outskirts of town.
Information tends to
gather in places like this,
but I won't corrupt the
eyes of the innocent.
I'll sacrifice myself, and see
what I can dig up around here.
-He sure has a good
heart, doesn't he?
-Gee, Sakura.
You really are
naive, you know that?
-Let's see where I should start.
Hi!
This investigation's
gonna be rough on me!
Let's hope I can handle it!
Ha ha ha ha!
-Let the Pervy
Sage do his thing.
We can have a look
around on our own.
What's up?
Is something wrong, Sakura?
-I don't think Sasuke
is in this land anymore.
-Hey, what are
you talking about?
We can't be sure of
anything until we've
had a good look around.
-Yeah, I know.
NARUTO: We're dealing
with Orochimaru here.
We knew what would be difficult.
But it doesn't matter.
I mean, we're definitely
going to find him, Sakura.
-You're right.
Naruto!
-Hey, you're the
one from before!
-Something's wrong.
I think he's been injured.
-What happened to you?
-Naruto!
-Heh, heh, heh.
Huh?
Substitution, huh?
We let them get away.
[laughter]
-Don't worry.
My beloved little children here
are spinning a trail for us
to follow.
There's no way they
can escape us now.
[laughter]
-Those two were ninja,
from beyond the border.
The fools.
Wandering into our backyard
has sealed their fate.
-A pity.
Anyone skulking
around in this land
could only be looking for
Lord Orochimaru, anyway.
[laughter]
JIRAIYA: Oh, ho!
Oh, man.
Nothing beats the supple
skin of a young woman, huh?
-Some gentleman.
-Huh?
Oh, sorry, sorry.
Hey, by the way,
you ladies haven't
heard any rumors about the
Sound village lately, have you?
-Where's the Sound village?
-Never heard of it.
You must be mixed up, mister.
Aw, come on.
I'll make it worth your while.
-Huh?
-But I told you, I
don't know nothing.
-Yeah, I've never
heard of it either.
WOMAN: I've heard of it.
-Hm?
-One of my regulars knows
all about it, actually.
Coming?
-Mm-hm.
-Aw.
-He lives down at the
end of this alley.
-Uh huh.
Hm?
Here we go.
-Caught like a rat in a trap.
-This guy's just
some mangy old dog.
You said this dodger's
got money on him?
-Sure does.
Saw the cash with
my very own eyes.
-You idiots.
Quit your yapping and
take this guy out already.
-Kay, boss.
You got it.
-You shouldn't have let a woman
lead you by the nose like that.
Now say goodnight!
-Huh?
-Ninja Art, Needle Jizo!
-Bastard.
-Look, fellas, I'm in a bit
of a hurry at the moment.
So what's say we
cut to the chase?
You play nice and
tell me what you
know about the Sound village
and, if you're lucky,
I'll let you walk out of here.
-If you think I'm gonna
play nice with you,
grandpa, then you
must be a fool.
You're a ninja then.
-And if I am?
-Well, now, this is interesting.
We've been reduced
to thievery of late,
but we're actually a
pretty well known clan
of shinobi in these parts.
I could just take your life.
But how about I
hire you instead?
-So you're a ninja, huh?
Then I don't need
to go easy on you.
-I don't think you wanna be
playing the big shot, old man!
-Shut up, you little punk!
A shinobi always endures.
Those who would use the jutsu
they worked so hard to master
for something as
base as thievery
aren't worthy to
be called ninja!
-All right.
Enough is enough.
I tried to cut a
fellow shinobi a break,
and this is the
thanks I get, huh?
Well, now I'm gonna
cleave you in two!
Demon Wind Ninja Blade!
Zabato!
-Rasengan!
-How dare you lay
a hand on the boss?
-This is the end of
the line for you.
-Really?
MAN: Hold on a minute!
-Hm?
-I didn't know I was
dealing with a master!
That jutsu just now-- you must
be a man of limitless ability!
Please, do not consider
me impertinent,
but may I ask of you your name?
-For those who do not know
me, prepare to be enlightened!
Before his manliness, no
female stands a chance.
Felling his foes, yet
falling for the ladies.
He resides within the
Village Hidden in the Leaves!
His name is known
both far and wide!
That's right, soak
it in, gentlemen!
You're gazing on none other than
the legendary master Jiraiya!
-Get on y knees, you idiots,
and beg for your lives
before it's too late!
He'll kill us all!
-Forgive us!
Have mercy, Master Jiraiya.
If we'd known you were one
of the legendary Sanning
of the Leaf Village, we would
never have been so rude.
Have me Please have
mercy on us all!
-Well, well.
My reputation precedes
me wherever I go.
Don't worry, it's fine.
Now, what's the story?
Is it true you have information
about the Hidden Sound Village
you can give me?
-Yes.
We of the Fuma were
one of the many ninja
clans that reside here in
the Land of Rice Paddes.
We all have our own
separate interests,
but the ninja of this land
have always existed in harmony.
Ths is, of course,
until he showed up.
-Who is it you speak of?
-I hesitate to even
speak his name aloud,
but it's Orochimaru, sir!
-It's OK.
You're safe now.
If that wound gets infected with
tetanus, that'll be it for you.
Fortunately, I have
some medicine with me.
Here, let m treat you.
-It's OK.
I don't think they're
coming after us.
Now that we're safe, let's
have a look at that wound.
Hm?
-Naruto, I need to concentrate.
Go wait outside.
-Huh?
What?
Wah!
Well, that's nice.
What'd she do that for?
Fine, then.
Fine, be that way.
Hm.
SAKURA: No peeking!
[scream]
-Don't worry.
I know.
Let's see that injury.
-Big meanie.
She didn't even
give me a warning.
Huh?
Whoa.
Cool.
SAKURA: Naruto!
You can come in!
-Ah!
Why is there a
pretty girl in here?
I-- uh-- Sakura--
I don't get it.
Who is this girl?
-You dope.
This is the ninja
from a moment ago.
-Huh?
Huh?
Come to think of
it-- What'd I do?
-My name is Sasame Fuma.
-So what gives, Sasame?
What were those three
guys chasing you for?
-It's OK.
You can talk to us.
Maybe we can do
something to help you.
-Those three men are responsible
for guarding over Orochimaru.
They're Sound ninja.
-I thought you were in league
with them the other day.
I'm sorry.
-That doesn't matter!
What else do you know?
-Orochimaru is the whole
reason we've come here.
Is there anything
else you can tell us?
-Well, all of this began
when the feudal lord
of the Land of
Rice Paddies tried
to expand his sway over
the neighboring countries.
The Land of Rice Paddies
is a small territory.
We haven't all
that many shinobi.
It was a foolhardy attack.
Our defeat was clear
from the outset.
And the shinobi
clans of this country
who participated
all fell into ruin.
We of Fuma were no exception.
I'm told that of
the survivors, some
decided to abandon
this land, while others
have stooped to common thievery.
Even so, many of us have
struggled on in the shadows,
praying for the day our
clan could be restored.
It was then that an emissary
from the Hidden Sound village
appeared, offering a promise
of the first full scale shinobi
village in this land.
The man from the Sound
village told us--
-My master, Lord Orochimaru,
is collecting jutsu,
and is interested in
those of your clan.
If you are willing to serve
and display enough merit,
you may be given the chance to
serve under the feudal lord.
SASAME: My cousin
Arashi was seen
as our clan's best
hope for revival.
He was chosen as
our representative
and set out for the Hidden
Sound with their emissary.
But--
-And then?
-We just kept waiting for some
sort of message to come from
Arashi, but there's--
-There's still no
word from him, right?
-That snake.
Orochimaru pulled him
into his twisted web!
SAKURA: Naruto.
-Oh!
But, uh, you know,
there's no need to panic!
I mean, your cousin
could be perfectly safe!
We don't know one way or
the other, and uh-- Uh.
-Dumb ass.
SASAME: I'm going
to save Arashi.
I have to!
I don't have any real
strength, and I'm small.
No matter how hard
I tried, I was
nothing but a burden
during training.
But no matter how
many times I faltered,
Arashi was always
there to save me.
Everyone from my village
has already given up,
so I'm gonna find the
Hidden Sound on my own.
-Oh.
And that's why the Sound
ninja were after you.
-Now it's my turn
to save Arashi,
just as he would do for me!
-Sasame.
-I want-- I want to be
there for Arashi now.
-Naruto.
-Oh yeah.
I'm with you.
We have to go to the
Sound village anyway,
to take back Sasuke.
This just means we
have one more person
to bring back with us now.
Don't you worry, Sasame.
I'm gonna get your cousin
back, no matter what!
-Oh, a Spider.
What is this?
Naruto!
-What the heck is going on here?
JIGUMO: Ninja Art, Wind Spiders.
My darling children have spun
threads of the purest silver
and led me right to you.
All three of you together
shall carry our secret
into the depths of Hell!
-He's using a
ventriloquism jutsu,
scattering his voice
in different directions
to mask their
number and location.
-Yeah, I'm on it.
You just take care
of her, Sakura!
Time for Multi
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
OK!
It doesn't matter
where you're hiding!
Bring it on!
-There are a lot of them, but
he's just using a clone jutsu.
No.
Look closely, Jigumo.
The threads are getting tangled.
-They're are tangible?
How could that even be?
Are they shadow clones?
-If so-- Kagero.
-Understood
[shouting]
KAGERO: Born to be born.
Breathing but to live.
One sunrise and one sunset.
Kagero's life, like a
mayfly, lasts a single day.
But pitying one so ephemeral
is, in itself, pitiable.
Know that I am at my greatest
when lying in the deep and dark
of the earth.
Ninja Art, Antlion Jutsu!
[theme music]
NARUTO: Man.
These guys are a real
pain in the you-know-what.
But I'm not gonna be done
in as easy as all that!
I still have to go kick
that Orochimaru jerk's butt,
and bring back Sasuke,
and Sasame's cousin!
I don't care if you
guys are power houses.
I'll wipe the floor
with the lot of you!
So bring it, from
anywhere you want!
Next time, Hear a Betrayal,
and a Fleeting Plea!
[theme music]