[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Oh, man.
What happens now?
[roaring]
-Oh, no.
She's hurt.
I don't like the way
this fight is going.
-I've had to
improvise my training.
Who would've thought that I'd
be more than a match for someone
who had the benefit of the full
and official star training?
What's wrong with
you, Lady Natsuhi?
What happened to all
that awesome power
you showed me the
last time we met?
Are the aftereffects of star
training beginning to wear you
down?
-For what you have done,
you'll never be forgiven!
-Lord Akahoshi.
-Oh, no.
-Huh?
-Be a good boy, son.
-It's an easy mission.
We'll be back
before you know it.
-Kay.
Don't worry.
Mother!
Don't go!
NATSUHI (VOICEOVER): Sumaru.
-Mother, wait!
-Son!
-Sumaru!
-Ha ha ha ha ha!
-Why's Lord Akahoshi
acting this way?
Could it really be true, then?
-Give-- give it back.
The star.
It's ours.
You've no right to it.
-Hold it!
-Farewell.
-What is he doing?
Huh?
-Could it be true that
it was Lord Akahoshi who
knocked us out and
took Sumaru away?
-Anyone who mistreats his
own students in such a way
does not deserve
the name sensei!
-What possible excuse could
you have for doing it?
-It was for the
sake of the village.
To get back the star that
this woman stole from us!
-That doesn't explain why you're
crushing the life out of Sumaru
right now.
-Now just hold on!
That woman is Sumaru's mom!
-My mother?
She's my mother?
-That's right, Sumaru.
She is your mother.
But far more importantly than
that, she is also your enemy.
All that matters is that she
stole the star, and by doing so
risked the destruction of the
village, and everyone in it!
-That isn't true!
She only took it so you
couldn't train with it anymore!
It's the star training
that's risking
the lives of everyone
in the village!
-Fool!
Giving your life for
the sake of your village
is every shinobi's dream!
Sumaru knows that,
and one day he
will become Hoshikage and put
the five great hidden villages
to shame.
Isn't that right?
-Yes.
I will be Hoshikage.
And I will make them all pay!
-Show your foolish
mother just how much
you would sacrifice
to achieve that dream.
-For that, I would give my life.
-No!
-Hey, don't do
anything crazy, Sumaru!
NEJI (VOICEOVER): Something's
controlling his chakra.
-Sumaru's will is not his own!
-I see you guessed it.
Yes, I hold Sumaru's life
in the palm of my hand.
Lady Natsuhi, it's
time to make a choice.
Which will it be?
With you keep the star, or
trade it for your son's life?
-No!
Stop!
-Well, well.
What is it, Lady Natsuhi?
Does this mean you've come to
see the error of your ways?
-Don't give in.
-Very well.
You win, Akahoshi.
-Hmph.
-Excellent.
-Sumaru!
-You did it.
Well done.
How did you get it?
-Actually, Lady Natsuhi
was gracious enough
to give it to me.
-Natsuhi!
Ah!
-No!
That's not fair!
-Sumaru!
-What?
-Sumaru--
SUMARU (VOICEOVER): Is
she-- is she really--
-That was a dirty trick.
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
So, you wanna play rough?
-Leaf Village Shinobi,
are you forgetting
that it was I who hired you?
-And what does that have
to do with anything?
-Wait!
Naruto!
-Hm?
What?
-What are you saying, Neji?
Are you going to
listen to this fiend?
-He's right, Lee.
We fulfilled the mission
we came here to do.
The rest of it is
none of our concern.
-You're saying we just stand by
and let him get away with it?
-You know we can't interfere.
On no account can we
go beyond the scope
of the mission for which
the client hired us.
-Darn it!
-Well, then.
We have the star back, so we'll
overlook everything else that
happened here today.
Follow me, all of you
who would dedicate
your lives to
serving our village.
-But my lord, Sumaru's hurt.
-Leave him there.
He's nothing but the
son of a traitor.
Now get moving.
-Right!
-Sorry, my lord, but I
will not leave Sumaru.
AKAHOSHI: Then
you're a rogue ninja.
-You'll be sorry, Hokuto.
-It's your funeral.
-You jerks!
There it is!
That star's called
the Natsuhiboshi.
-I think most people know
it as the planet Mars.
NARUTO: Whatever.
That's what Sumaru called it.
He told me that star
watches over him
like a guardian spirit.
-Natsuhiboshi.
He gave it the same
name as his mother.
-How poignant.
The ties of love between
a mother and her child.
-Yeah.
[footsteps]
Hm?
Well, how are they doing?
-They're both
resting comfortably,
but she's hurt badly.
She was already weakened
from the effects of the star
training.
Fighting Akahoshi may
have been too much.
Her chakra network is failing.
All I know is, if she tries
that jutsu one more time,
she'll die.
-You positive?
Wait.
Grandma Tsunade!
-I don't know.
-OK, that does it.
Just wait until I get my
hands on that Akahoshi.
I'll knock his block off!
-Naruto.
We can do nothing.
-But he is a most
heinous villain.
-He's even worse than that!
-If we of the Leaf village
were ever to betray a client,
then no other village
would trust us again.
-So you're saying we
should just do nothing?
-Unfortunately,
Neji has a point.
Perhaps we should go home and
ask the Hokage for advice.
-Yes.
And we could give
them better treatment
if we took them to the
Village Hidden in the Leaves.
-All right.
We'll let the matter
rest until then.
-Sumaru!
-Yes, mother?
Mother!
NATSUHI: You're angry,
aren't you, Sumaru?
I don't blame you.
Who wouldn't be angry if his
mother abandoned his village
and left him to be
raised by others?
How often I wished
I'd taken you with me.
But then I kept
telling myself what
a cruel fate that would
be to inflict on you,
wandering the world as a
rogue ninja, like your mother.
A mother whose failing
body could give out
at any time from the cursed
effects of that star training.
-Just stay away from me.
Almost every night for years,
I've had the same dream.
I'm chasing after two figures,
but I can never catch them.
-Sumaru!
-Wait, mother!
-I told myself my
mother wasn't like that.
I know she could
never be so heartless
as to leave me behind.
Not willingly.
She must be dead, like
the Third Hoshikage said.
He told me you had
died in a far off land,
and you'd been
transformed into a star.
The star Natsuhiboshi was you.
-Sumaru.
-Mother.
What you said-- I
wouldn't have cared.
I just wanted you
to take me with you.
-Oh, my son.
-Mother.
I was so lonely.
(SINGING) Natsuhiboshi,
why are you so red?
Because I had a sad
dream last night.
My eyes are red from the tears
I shed, swollen as I cried.
Natsuhobshi, why've
you lost your way?
I'm searching for a
child who's gone afar.
He can't be found,
thought I search all day,
my sad dreams come once more.
-Hey, Sumaru!
Sumaru, wake up!
-Wha-- What?
-What's going on?
Your mom's bed, it's empty.
She's gone.
Do you know where she went?
-Oh no.
-Mother, you didn't.
-That cursed star must be
destroyed once and for all.
I will end my village's
suffering tonight,
even if it costs me my life.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
We gotta stop her!
If Neji's right, and she tries
to use that jutsu of hers--
-You were once the hope and
strength of our village.
I didn't want to
have to destroy you.
But what you demand
in pain and suffering
is too high a price
for our people to pay.
Forgive me.
[whipping]
[snickering]
-Akahoshi.
Ninja Art, Kujaku.
Beast!
Sumaru--
-So, this is the end.
How tragic.
-Mother, no!
-What, Sumaru?
What's happened?
-Is it Lady Natsuhi?
Is she--
SUMARU (VOICEOVER):
my mother is dead.
-From this night
forward, I, Akahoshi,
bear the title of
Fourth Hoshikage,
and I now charge my people
with their first mission.
The traitors Hokuto and Sumaru,
and the Leaf village shinobi
who aid them, we must
consider them our enemies!
Keep watch, and if you
find any of them trying
to enter the village,
strike without mercy!
-Yes, my lord!
-Mother, hear me.
I will make him pay
for your life with his!
-Sumaru!
[theme music]
NARUTO: That rat, Akahoshi!
I'm gonna take him down!
LEE: Not if I get him first.
TENTEN: Hang on, you two.
NARUTO: I'm gonna knock
him into next week.
NEJI: No you won't, Naruto.
Stay out of it.
LEE: That is right!
Leave him to me and
my Hidden Lotus.
TENTEN: That goes
for you too, Lee.
Forget it.
LEE: What?
Do nothing?
NARUTO: Whatever!
I'm going!
LEE: Wait for me!
NEJI: Stop!
Do you want to start a war
with the Hidden Star village?
NARUTO: Next time,
The Star's Radiance!
[theme music]