[theme song]
- [breathing heavily]
I will be Hokage.
I will never lose to
you, or anyone here.
-Dream on, kid.
How can you beat me when
you can't keep up with me?
Uzumaki [inaudible].
-The winner is Naruto Uzumaki.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
I can feel it.
I'm getting stronger!
-Woohoo.
-Yes, Naruto.
That's my teammate.
Way to go!
-Unbelievable.
Who would have thought
he could beat Kiba?
-A major upset.
-Mm-hmm.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Byakugan
Battle: Hinata Grows Bold.
Whoa, this stuff Hinata
gave me works fast.
Here, want to try it, Sakura?
-Hm?
-Only your wounds will
heal that quickly, Naruto.
It's not the ointment.
It's the power of
the nine-tailed fox.
It never ceases to surprise me.
HINATA: Uh, Kiba?
Here.
Here's some healing ointment.
It's for you and Akamaru.
-Huh, Forget About us.
You better start worrying
about yourself, Hinata.
-What do you mean?
-Only six left.
Just you and Choji,
Neji, Lee, and then
there are those two guys from
the Sound and Sand Villages.
Listen to me, be smart.
If they put you in with that
guy from the Sand Village,
you've got to forfeit the match.
Same with Neji.
Be smart and just walk away.
Trust me, he'll be merciless.
He'll destroy you.
-All right, we'll now pick
the names for the next match.
-[gasp]
WOMAN (VOICEOVER): Hinata.
MAN (VOICEOVER): Hm, this should
be an interesting match indeed.
-I never thought
that you and I would
have to face each other, Hinata.
-Nor I, brother.
-What'd she call him?
-Brother!
Those two are
brother and sister?
-They're both descended
from the Hyuga clan, one
of the most ancient
and honorable families
of the Hidden Leaf Village, not
actually brother and sister.
-OK, but they're
related somehow, right?
-Yes.
In the way a branch of the great
tree is related to its trunk.
Technically, they're
more like cousins.
-The trunk of a tree?
-Yes, Hinata belongs to the
family's main household,
directly descended from
the head of the clan.
Well, Neji's family is just
a side branch of the clan.
-Still, they're family.
And now they have
to fight each other.
I feel for them.
It must be hard.
-Yes, but--
-But what?
-It may not be as
hard as it seems.
I have heard that for
many generations now,
there has been some bad blood
between the two families.
-Hm.
And why is that?
-I have never known
the specifics.
But you know about the bloodline
trait to the great ninja clans,
like the Uchya and the
Hyuga, special techniques
and abilities unique
to those families.
The first generation
of the Hyuga clan
made all sorts of
rules and decrees
that favor the main
branch of the family.
It seems some branches of
the family broke these rules.
-Huh?
-Anyway, it is said that because
of that there has been friction
between the branches
of the clan.
-So it's like this
match is a family feud.
-Look, they're about to start.
-All right, you may
begin when ready.
-Before we do this,
a word of advice.
Hinata, listen to me.
Withdraw now.
You know you were never
meant to be a ninja.
You're too kind and gentle.
You seek harmony
and avoid conflict.
You allow yourself to be
easily swayed by others.
Admit it, you have
no confidence.
You feel inferior to
everyone else here.
It would've been better for
you to simply remain a Genin,
but to register for
the Chunine exams,
you need a team of three people.
You never even wanted to
take part in these exams,
but Chino and Kiba
did, and you couldn't
bear to let your
teammates down, could you?
-No, you're wrong.
You're wrong.
I wanted-- I had to find out.
I did it because I wanted
to see if I could change.
WOMAN (VOICEOVER): Hinata.
-Stand up, Hanabi.
-Very well then, I will
take Hinata under my wing.
But are you sure
that's what you want?
She is your first born and
heir to your household.
The life of a Genin can
be dangerous and brief.
-Do what you will.
She's of less worth than her
sister five years her junior.
The Hyuga clan has no
use for such an heir.
If you have nothing more
to say, we have work to do.
Leave us now.
-All right.
Hinata has struggled to
become what she wanted to be.
-Hinata, you are the
pampered offspring
of the Hyuga's main branch.
-What?
-People can't change no
matter how hard they try.
They can't run away
from their true nature.
A failure will
always be a failure.
-[grunting] Listen to this guy.
NEJI (VOICEOVER): People are
judged by their true nature.
It is the way of the world.
That is why we have any an elite
and why there are outcasts.
We can change our
physical appearance,
improve our skills with
training and study,
but ultimately we are judged
by what we cannot change.
What can't be changed
must be endured.
We are who we are, Hinata.
And we must live with it, just
as I must live with the fact
that you were born into
the elite of our clan
while I am from a lesser branch.
I understand these things
because I see the world
clearly with my Byakugan.
Despite your brave
words, what you're really
thinking is that you'd like to
run, run as far away from here
as you can.
-No, you're wrong.
You're wrong about me.
-Byakugan?
-It's the kekkei genkai
or bloodline trait
of the Hyuga, a visual
jutsu like Sharingan.
In fact, they say the
Uchiha clan's Sharingan
was derived from the
Byakugan some time long ago.
But for sheer power of
insight, the Byakugan
is the stronger of the two.
-Byakugan.
My eyes cannot be deceived.
Just one moment ago, in
the slightest of movements,
your gaze drifted toward the
upper-left corner of the room.
I saw at that moment
you were thinking
of your past, your bitter past.
And then, almost
immediately after your gaze
drifted to the lower right.
It was a mere
flicker of the eyes,
but to me it revealed all
of your mental and physical
suffering.
You're seeing your
old self and wondering
if your life has prepared
you for this moment.
You're picturing the
outcome of the battle.
You see yourself losing.
And the way you're
holding your arms
in front of your body like that?
It tells me that you're trying
to build a wall between us,
to keep me at bay.
You want to keep me
from raiding the deepest
recesses of your mind.
And why?
Because everything
I've said is true.
Shall I go on?
-[grunting]
NEJI (VOICEOVER):
That familiar gesture
of putting your
finger to your lips,
I know that it's a desperate
attempt to suppress your rising
panic, made all the more
desperate because you
know it's futile.
It's all futile, Hinata.
You are what you are.
Whether you admit it or
not, you already know.
-That does it.
Who gave you the right to tell
her what she can or can't be?
Go on, Hinata.
Show this guy he's wrong.
-Naruto.
-Hm.
-Hinata, you just going to
stand there and take that?
Do something.
You're driving me crazy.
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
You were right.
NEJI (VOICEOVER):
Annonying, little pest.
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
You were right, Naruto.
Thank you.
NEJI (VOICEOVER): The look
in her eye has changed.
If you don't forfeit the match,
you know what will happen.
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
I won't run away.
-Don't underestimate me.
I don't quit and I--
HINATA (VOICEOVER): Never again.
-No way, I never
go back on my word.
That's the way of the ninja.
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
No more hiding.
Byakugan.
-Huh?
-Defend yourself, my brother.
-[gasp]
-Very well then.
-Of course, it is
the Hyuga style.
That is why their
poses are the same.
-The Hyuga style?
-It is the most effective
type of Taijutsu
found in our village.
I have said it before,
I have on my team
the man who is probably the
strongest Genin ever to come
out of the Hidden Leaf
Village, that man-- Neji Hyuga.
HINATA (VOICEOVER): No.
-Did she get him?
-No way, she hadly touched him.
-Even so, a glancing
blow is enough.
That is what makes the
Hyuga clan the most
formidable of fighters.
-What does?
What are you talking about?
-Their Taijutsu is
a unique one that's
been passed down
for generations.
It's not the kind of
Taijutsu Lee and I employ.
We tend to concentrate on
inflicting external damage.
We use crushing blows to raise
contusions and break limbs,
pounding our enemy.
The Hyuga way is to attack
their opponent's internal organs
and the chakra network through
which the chakra flows.
Their way is more subtle.
Perhaps not as
thrilling to watch,
but it gradually takes effect
with devastating results.
-You see, you can't build
up your internal organs,
no matter how hard you train.
Even the toughest ninja
is vulnerable to this kind
of attack.
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
I can do this.
-She's giving him
all he can handle.
WOMAN (VOICEOVER): Hinata.
-Hinata, way to go.
-They attack the chakra network?
These people are amazing.
-Yeah, you could say that again.
So what is the chakra
network anyway?
-Ugh.
Don't you know anything?
-Here, I will explain it.
It is the complex system
of circulatory canals
that distribute chakra
throughout the body,
similar to a person's
vascular system, the veins
and arteries that carry blood.
-I get it.
Only these veins carry
chakra, not blood?
LEE: Uh, basically.
Furthermore, the chakra network
is so closely interwoven
with all the most
vital internal organs
that they are virtually
one in the same.
Therefore, when the
network is attacked,
these organs suffer
damage as well.
-Wow, Lee.
How'd you ever get
to be so smart?
-Idiot.
How'd you ever
get to be a Genin.
-Ow.
MAN (VOICEOVER): It's no
wonder he's worked up.
He's watching his oldest
competitor and rival, Neji.
-But sensei, how do the know
where to strike their opponent?
I mean, the chakra network is
invisible to the eye, right?
So how do they know exactly
where to land their blows?
-You're forgetting
their Byakugan.
There are few things
invisible to those eyes.
What's more?
When they strike a
blow, it's a little
different from a normal attack.
A small but intense
burst of their own chakra
is released from their hand.
It drills into the
opponent's body,
directly attacking
his chakra network.
-Yeah, get him!
-Did she get him?
[theme song]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Man, is this
the same shy, little wallflower
who always mumbles
when she talks?
Look at her go.
-No matter how many
times she's knocked down,
she gets back on her feet.
She never gives up.
Kind of like you.
-Huh?
-Maybe that's why she's
always looking at you.
Or, could there
be another reason?
-Uh, search me.
Next time, "A
Failure Stands Tall."
Go for it, Hinata.