[music playing]
[theme music]
MAN (VOICEOVER): The Village
Hidden in the Leaves--
many of the world's
greatest ninja
have come from this
secret village.
-(ANGRILY) Naruto!
Come back here!
When I get my hands on you!
MAN (VOICEOVER):
Naruto Uzumaki--
he's the number one
prankster of the village.
He's also determined to become
the greatest ninja of all.
-Give it up, losers!
Transform!
MAN (VOICEOVER):
The sexy jutsu is
one of the unusual
techniques he developed.
-(ANGRILY) Cut
the stupid tricks!
This is your last warning!
MAN (VOICEOVER): But
Naruto had a secret inside
that even he didn't know about.
12 years ago, a nine-tailed fox
nearly destroyed our village.
To save us, the
spirit of the beast
was sealed in the
body of a child.
That child was Naruto.
The adults of the
village shunned him
because they knew he had the
beast spirit inside of him.
-You see him?
It's that boy.
-I heard he's the
only one who failed.
-Hmph.
Well, it serves him right.
-Just imagine what would
happen if he became a ninja.
MAN: Ok.
You can open your eyes now.
Congratulations!
You graduate.
MAN (VOICEOVER):
With my approval,
Naruto finally graduated from
the Academy and became a ninja.
[laughing]
MAN: Say cheese!
MAN (VOICEOVER): At last he was
ready for his first mission.
Ninja missions are carried
out in squads of three.
Naruto's group includes Sasuke
Uchiha of the legendary Uchiha
clan.
Sasuke's superior
skill constantly
frustrates Naruto to no end.
The other member of the
trio is Sakura Haruno,
a Kunoichi-- a female ninja.
Naruto likes Sakura, but she
has a big crush on Sasuke.
To succeed, they'll have
to learn to work as a team.
Their sensei is Kakashi Hatake.
Known as the Copy Ninja, he's
one of the most exceptionally
skilled Jonin in the
Hidden Leaf Village.
The group's first
major mission was
to guard Tazuna,
the master bridge
builder from the Land of Waves.
-(YELLING) Yeah!
All right!
MAN (VOICEOVER):
However, an evil tycoon
named Gato sought the
bridge builder's life
and control of his country.
MAN: Stop whining.
[groaning]
MAN (VOICEOVER): Gato hired an
assassin to eliminate Tazuna.
ZABUZA: This time,
I'll go personally.
And this sword will be the
last thing he ever sees.
MAN (VOICEOVER): Zabuza
Momochi, a rogue ninja
known as the Demon
of the Hidden Mist.
A master of the silent killing
technique, he had many victims.
No one had ever
escaped his soul.
[groaning]
MAN (VOICEOVER):
Naruto and his group
struggled against Zabuza's
punishing attacks.
-(WEAKLY) Hey you, the
freak with no eyebrows--
put this in your bingo book--
the ninja that will become
Hokage of the Village
Hidden in the Leaves--
he never backs down.
His name's Naruto Uzumaki.
[yelling]
-Not smart enough.
A second shuriken in
the shadow of the first.
MAN (VOICEOVER): By disguising
himself as a skuriken,
Naruto turned the tables
on the Demon Assassin.
Kakashi used the Sharingan
eye to copy Zabuza's jutsu
and reflect those techniques
back at his opponent.
[groaning]
-What is that?
It's me.
But how?
Is it his illusion jutsu?
-Water style--
giant vortex jutsu!
-Impossible!
[screaming]
[groaning]
[banging]
[music playing]
-He's finished.
[gasping]
MAN (VOICEOVER): But
the one who dealt
the final blow was a tracker
ninja from the Village
Hidden in the Mist.
-There are many
secrets in this body.
They must not be allowed to
get into the wrong hands.
Please excuse me.
Farewell.
MAN (VOICEOVER):
However, this boy, Haku,
was actually Zabuza's partner.
-Will you be all
right next time?
ZABUZA: Next time, I'll see
right through his [inaudible].
MAN (VOICEOVER): Realizing that
Zabuza must still be alive--
-I got it!
MAN (VOICEOVER): Kakashi
prepared his squad
to face their enemy
by teaching them
special techniques
to control chakra.
[grunting]
MAN (VOICEOVER): One week
later, Kakashi's suspicions
were confirmed.
-His mist.
Sasuke, Sakura, get ready.
-Looks like you've
got a rival, Haku.
-So it seems.
MAN (VOICEOVER):
The time has come.
-Secret jutsu.
Crystal Ice Mirrors.
Now, we'll begin, and I'll show
you what speed really means.
-Take this!
[flying sounds]
[popping sounds]
-Naruto Uzumaki is here!
Yeah, believe it.
[laughing]
"The Number One Hyperactive,
Knucklehead Ninja
Joins the Fight!"
[groaning]
-Ha!
Now that I'm here,
everything will be all right.
-Huh?
-Naruto!
-You know how in
stories, the hero usually
shows up at the last
minute and then kicks butt?
Well, that's what I'm
going to do right now!
Believe it!
-(VOICEOVER) Ugh.
This brat again.
-(VOICEOVER) Shut up, Naruto.
[groaning]
-(VOICEOVER) Ugh.
What an idiot.
If he'd have stayed
hidden, he could
have been so much
more effective.
-(VOICEOVER) That boy--
What are you doing sleeping
way out here in the woods?
[laughing]
-I'm training.
-Impressive.
Are you training for
something dangerous?
-I'm just developing my
skills so I can get stronger.
-All right!
You're history!
Shadow clone jutsu!
-Huh?
-No!
-Naruto!
Move!
[groaning]
[gasping]
-Oh.
-They didn't get him.
-Their weapons cancelled
each other out.
Amazing.
Now, that's what I
call lucky, I think.
-What are you doing, Naruto?
Are you crazy?
-This is a battle,
not a talent show!
Don't let your opponent
see your jutsu.
-Uhh.
KAKASHI: The Shinobi's
art is deception.
Always keep the enemy guessing.
Even when executing
a single jutsu,
one must distract their
opponent's attention--
catch them off balance
and outmaneuver them.
You just turned yourself
into a human target
when you enter a
battle like that.
[screaming]
-(SCREAMING) I'm sorry!
I was just trying
to rescue everybody!
-But there's another
mystery here.
-(VOICEOVER) Him.
-Haku, what are you doing?
-Zabuza, this boy-- let
me fight him my own way.
Please.
-Bring it on!
[music playing]
-Hm.
So you want me to
leave this to you.
Is that it, Haku?
As usual, you're too soft.
-Forgive me.
-(VOICEOVER) Soft?
He's right.
Look at these wounds.
He cut me up with
his needles, yet he
didn't hit a single vital spot.
Why?
Is he just trying
to humiliate me?
-I'm warning you!
One way or another, I'm
going to rip off that mask
and take you apart!
-(VOICEOVER) It's impossible.
Naruto can't match this kid.
I've got to--
-Don't even think about it.
You know the score, Kakashi.
If you go after Haku, I go
after the bridge builder.
[grunting]
-(VOICEOVER) He's got me.
I can't protect Tazuna
and help Naruto and Sasuke
at the same time.
Sakura's feisty, but she
can't fight Zabuza alone.
-Relax, Kakashi.
Sit back and enjoy the show.
Let's see how they
do-- one on one.
-That mask and your bogus story!
You were with Zabuza all along!
You think you can get away
with a stunt like that?
-I'm sorry.
-Huh?
-But as your sensei said,
deceiving your opponent,
catching them off guard-- that
is the art of the Shinobi.
Please don't take it personally.
-(VOICEOVER) And while
you're jabbering,
I'll catch you off guard!
[gasping]
-Sasuke?
-I haven't forgotten about you.
Not for an instant.
-(VOICEOVER) So that's where
Sasuke is-- he's pinned down.
-Some warriors accept
defeat gracefully.
They know when they are beaten.
Others do not.
So be it.
Let us finish our battle
then-- to the death!
-Wha-- hey!
Where are you going?
-It's all right, Naruto.
We'll have our fight next.
[gasping]
[groaning]
-(VOICEOVER) What is he?
-(VOICEOVER) Here he comes.
The real one is over there.
Now--
HAKU: I'm behind you.
-(VOICEOVER) He transported
himself in an instant.
How?
[gasping]
[groaning]
-Sasuke!
(VOICEOVER) What is that?
Sasuke's getting all
ripped up, and I can't even
tell where the attacks
are coming from.
How's he doing that?
[groaning]
-(VOICEOVER) What
kind of jutsu is this?
Could it be he has clones
hiding in the mirrors
all throwing needles
at the same time?
No.
They're too fast for that.
I can't even see where
they're coming from!
And if it was just
a clone jutsu,
then he wouldn't
need the ice mirrors.
Those mirrors are definitely
the key to his attacks,
but what's my next move?
-Sasuke, Naruto, think!
You need to attack
from the outside
and from the inside
at the same time!
-(VOICEOVER) To figure
out how the mirrors work!
-I've got it!
-(VOICEOVER) Yes, it's
all about positioning,
and Naruto and I are in
the perfect position.
If I attack him from
here, and Naruto hits him
from the outside, we can do it.
-Hey!
I snuck in here to save you!
Pretty cool move, huh, Sasuke?
[groaning]
-Naruto, you sneak up on
your enemy, not your ally.
-(ANGRILY) You are
a complete loser!
You're a Shinobi.
Think carefully before you more.
-(ANGRILY) What the
heck's your problem!
You should thank me for
coming in here to help you!
-Naruto, if we're both
inside here-- ugh!
Forget it!
I've had it with your mistakes!
-(ANGRILY) And I've had
it with your attitude!
Believe it!
-(VOICEOVER) Naruto's building
a solid reputation as the most
clueless ninja in history.
The more he helps,
the worst things get.
-That's it.
I'm going to destroy
these mirrors right now.
Fire style.
-Hey!
What attack are you using?
-These mirrors are made of ice.
So how do you destroy ice?
Figure it out. (YELLING)
Fire ball jutsu!
[gasping]
-(YELLING) That didn't
do anything at all!
-You'll need much more heat
than that to melt this ice.
[grunting]
[screaming]
-Where is he?
Where's the needle
attack coming at us from?
Are they clones?
[groaning]
We've got to find the real one!
Which one is it?
-Look into every mirror
as hard as you like.
You will never learn the secret.
-Oh yeah?
Shadow clone jutsu!
-No, don't!
[yelling]
-You've got 100 mirrors, then
100 of me will smash them all.
Then I'll find where
you really are!
[grunting]
[screaming]
-These mirrors only
reflect my image,
allowing me to transport
myself at light speed.
Through my eyes, you appear
to be moving in slow motion.
[groaning]
-I knew it.
It's a bloodline
trait-- Kekkei Genkai.
[laughing]
-Kekkei Genkai?
What is it?
-It's like my Sharingan.
You can't learn it.
It has to be in your blood-- in
your genetic code passed down
from generation to generation
within a single clan.
-But that means--
-Yes.
Even I can't copy that jutsu.
There's no way to destroy
it and no way to stop him.
[groaning]
-I couldn't break through.
-Huh?
-So what?
He's not going to stop me.
[gasping]
I'm not giving up, and I'm
not going to lose here.
Because I have a
dream, and no one's
going to take it away from me.
Some day, I'll be
respected in my village.
That's my dream-- to
be the greatest Hokage!
-Dreams?
[foot steps]
[laughing]
ZABUZA: Pathetic little urchin.
No one wants you, huh?
Before winter ends, you'll
die with nothing-- not even
a dream.
Huh?
-Your eyes are just
like mine, mister.
We're both the same.
-It was not my desire
to be a Shinobi.
It's painful.
I don't want to kill you.
But if you advance, I
will have no choice.
Then I will kill the
kindness in my own heart
and fully embrace
the Shinobi way.
And there will be no
mercy-- no turning back.
This bridge will
be the battlefield
where our dreams collide.
Now I must fight for my dream
just as you fight for yours.
Please do not blame me.
I fight for someone
who is precious to me.
I live for him, and
I face death for him
so that his dream
may become reality.
That is my dream.
And for the sake of
that dream-- if I must,
I will act as a Shinobi
and take your lives.
[theme music]
[music playing]
NARUTO: Crystal
ice mirrors-- wait
til you see how I smash them!
I finally figured out
how to break through.
[laughing]
All right, Sasuke,
we got to get out
of here so we can
help Kakashi Sensei.
I'm getting a bad
feeling about this.
Sensei!
Sakura!
Hold on til we get there!
Next time-- "Zero Visibility--
The Sharingan Shatters."
If I don't pull this
off, we're all done for!