[theme music]
-Blew them to bits.
Blew them to bits
and now they're gone.
And I'm not sad in the least.
I can't hold a funeral
feeling like this.
RANMARU: The four of
them are still alive.
-Impossible.
Not after my Lightning
Fang hit them.
Sorry.
If you say they're alive, there
can't be any doubt about it.
RANMARU: One of
them is troublesome.
NEJI (VOICEOVER):
The enemy was close,
but I couldn't see anything.
It's strange.
I know this is the
Hidden Mist Jutsu,
but my Byakugan should
be able to penetrate it.
-Byakugan.
There's no question this time.
I can see them, a pair, 52
degrees to the southwest.
12 degrees southeast,
another three.
Eight degrees to
the southeast, one.
And 24 degrees to
the northwest, 11.
-Shadow Clone Jutsu.
Let's hit it.
-Leaf [inaudible].
-Impossible.
Why?
-Na-- ru-- to-- Uzumaki Barrage!
I never miss with that attack.
ROCK: Somebody help me, please?
-Huh?
Bushy Brow?
-The-- the enemy
has disappeared.
NEJI (VOICEOVER): It can't be.
Chakra networks running
through illusions?
RANMARU: One is
halfway up the cliff.
Another's at the base.
There's one to the right,
and one to the left.
-We can't hold a funeral,
but I'll take care of them
without leaving
any trace at least.
Thunder Funeral.
Feast of Lightning.
[screaming]
-Warmed over corpses.
We're strong, you and I. No,
it's really you, Ranmaru.
You're the strong one,
and when I'm with you,
your strength is mine.
RANMARU: Wait, they
aren't dead yet.
They're just unconscious.
-Stubborn lot, aren't they?
All right then, if
grilling them won't work,
I'll just dice them up.
[giggling]
-I'll grind their flesh
and bones into dust.
[groaning]
-Huh?
Ranmaru, are you all right?
Hang in there, Ranmaru.
Ranmaru!
RANMARU: I'm OK.
Raiga, this one is
still unconscious.
-What did you say?
Impressive.
RANMARU: He's fighting
solely by muscle memory.
RAIGA: Not a bad face.
It's burning into my heart.
Maybe I'll give him
a funeral after all.
It will bring tears to
my eyes, I'm sure of it.
RANMARU: On your right.
-What's with this guy?
RANMARU: It's hard to read his
movements, but for your sake,
I'll do my best.
-We act together.
RANMARU: Left, right,
head on, jump now.
-You will die.
What?
RANMARU: How can he
posses such skill?
-Bushy Brow's in trouble.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
I don't get it.
Is he still unconscious?
-You guys, where are you?
RANMARU: Raiga, shift position.
-That voice, where
is it coming from?
RANMARU: Raiga!
-Ranmaru!
-What?
-Neji.
-Ranmaru, get off.
-That is so bizarre.
I was just dreaming
that I was in battle.
Ah!
-Ranmaru?
You little--
-All right, pal.
Now you're dealing with me.
-Naruto.
-You filthy little brat.
-Hey, I've got something
I want to ask you.
Word is you're one of the Seven
Ninja Swordsmen from the Hidden
Mist.
-So what if I was?
-You know Zabuza, right?
And a big guy by
the name of Kisame?
-Look, I have nothing but
loathing for those two.
You'll have to forgive me if
I don't feel like reminiscing.
And I'm not too hot on you!
-Well then, I'll just have to
beat the answers out of you!
-A clone?
-What's wrong?
Losing your edge already?
-Wh-- what the?
-Lightning Ball!
-You lousy--
-Well, you're tougher
than you look.
Lightning Ball!
[screaming]
-Mm.
-Seconds, ple-- hm?
[thunder]
-Grandma Sansho?
-Is anything the matter?
-Look yonder.
That's a nasty bit of lightning.
It was flashing
just as ominously
the day Karashi left to find
his fortune in the village.
Oh, gracious me.
That light is like poison.
-No, Naruto.
-Huh?
-Sorry, buddy.
It's going to take
more than that.
-I'm not even going to
remember that smile.
Now die.
[screaming]
-Ranmaru?
Where are you?
-So what do you
think is in this bag?
NEJI (VOICEOVER): Byakugan!
-There's someone in there.
Could it be?
So this dust, it was hiding
the chakra network then?
And it's creating
chakra networks as well.
NEJI: Naruto, use the
Shadow Clone Jutsu.
-But my clones were
useless before.
NEJI: Don't worry.
His eyes are over
here at the moment.
-Ranmaru, I'll be right over,
soon as I finish up here.
-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Bring it on, chump.
-Lightning Ball!
-Your aim is terrible.
You just get lucky before?
-Laugh it up, kid.
I'll just take all of you out.
-Let's go, pal.
[shouting]
-Oh, please.
RAIGA (VOICEOVER): At this
rate, my chakra-- the mist.
The Hidden Mist
Jutsu is fading away.
Better finish this.
-Got it.
You're not going anywhere.
You can run--
RAIGA (VOICEOVER): Ninja
Art Boulder Avalanche.
-Naruto.
[gasp]
-I have to help.
-Ha, did you see that?
NARUTO: Yeah, I saw it.
-Huh?
-Hope you're ready, pal!
RANMARU: Stop!
-Too late now!
[screaming]
-Yikes, I guess that takes
care of that then, huh?
So, Raiga's eyes are
inside that thing?
Hm.
They must be some
pretty big eyeballs.
-Huh?
-You idiot, it's a person.
-So wait a moment, when I
was sleepwalking before then,
was it you I fought?
-No, it wasn't.
It was Raiga and I together.
-Together?
-Always, ever since he found me.
[screaming]
[smashing on door]
-No use feigning sleep.
The hour of your
death has arrived.
Don't move.
The Hidden Mist was infiltrated
by spies from this village.
We've come to smoke
them out and kill them.
Problem is we're not having
any luck finding our targets,
so I've just been
killing people at random.
[moan]
-What's that?
Speak up.
[cough]
-It's all right if you are
the one taking my life.
-Huh?
Me?
What do you mean?
-I saw you, always crying.
-What?
Me, cry?
Deep within your
heart, as you searched
for meaning in your life.
[gasp]
RANMARU: You see, I've
been watching you.
-What are you?
How could you--
RANMARU: I'm the same as you.
Living is painful.
I long to understand
the meaning of my life.
My illness forces me indoors.
Shunned by everyone, all I can
do is peer out at the world
from under this blanket.
But if in my death, you're
able to glean some meaning
behind this thing we
call living, well, then
who am I to stop you?
Go ahead.
RAIGA: You're alone then?
-Mm.
-Come.
From here on out, you
and I shall be as one.
RANMARU (VOICEOVER):
That was the day
I became Raiga's eyes and ears.
And Raiga became
my hands and feet.
The outside world
that we dashed into
was filled with
things that I saw
and heard for the
first time in my life.
It was so much fun.
Wherever and whenever I was with
Raiga, nothing else mattered.
We were never apart.
We were trying to find
the meaning in our lives
by living for each other.
We were convinced we
had found the answer.
That's why if Raiga is gone,
I have no reason to live.
Without him, I have no
purpose in this world,
no cause to exist.
-Is there someone
who's precious to you?
There is only one person
who matters to me.
And I live to protect
and serve him.
That is my purpose.
To show mercy to those who
oppose the one you serve,
to allow his enemies to live
when you go could strike them
down-- this is not compassion.
It is a betrayal of your
life's very purpose.
For what reason
do you exist then?
You're of use to no one.
Your life has no meaning.
It is mere existence.
Day after day of pain and
struggle signifying nothing.
-Yeah?
Well, speak for yourself.
-Are you really that
blind, little one?
I am speaking of myself.
This day has shown that I am
no longer of any use to Zabuza.
-There's no need for me
to be here any longer.
-Look, don't be ridiculous.
You can't talk like that.
-Naruto, kill me.
I'm begging you.
Just put and end to it.
-Huh?
-What are you waiting for?
Go on.
Do it.
Quickly.
-Go on.
Why do you hesitate?
My arms and legs are crippled.
I'm powerless to resist you.
You have a mission to
carry out, don't you?
Well, hurry up and finish it.
-The mission entrusted to us
was to drive the Kurosuke family
out of here.
And with Raiga out of
the way now, he no longer
poses a threat to the village.
-Mm.
-The question at hand is what
to do about the Kurosuke family
now that they have
no leadership.
Take the head off
of a beast, and it's
hard to predict what it will do.
Once that's done, the
mission will be completed.
-Hm, but, uh, what are we
supposed to do about him?
-Do you really think he is
dangerous enough to tie up?
-No, I don't believe so.
-But dangerous to
myself though, maybe.
-Once our mission is over,
we'll come back for you, OK?
-A chakra sealing tag as well?
-Look, we don't
have a choice, Lee.
He's still our enemy, isn't he?
-We have to assume that he
still possesses other jutsu just
to be safe.
[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Rokusuke and the others
have their village back.
Looks like the
mission's complete.
NEJI (VOICEOVER):
Tell that to Lee.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Oh yeah, that's right.
Lee said he was going to
beat some sense into Karashi,
didn't he?
TEN TEN (VOICEOVER): I
wonder if it'll be that easy.
LEE (VOICEOVER): This
could be troublesome.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): What?
I don't want to
hear that from you.
LEE (VOICEOVER): No, I
did not mean Karashi.
I was speaking of this weather.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next time--
The Dark Creeping Clouds.
NEJI (VOICEOVER): I see.
A storm is coming.