[theme music]
Big feast.
-These guys are kind of
throwing me for a loop.
Now, focus, everybody.
Time for decisive action.
Let's do it.
-Kind of itches, huh, Fujin?
FUJIN: Yeah, it itches.
-Huh?
-My punches aren't having any
effect on these two idiots.
-Naruto, this doesn't look good.
NARUTO: One more time.
-Heh, I'm getting that
itchy tickle again.
-You think we got a
rash or something?
-Geez, these guys are tough.
-I'll get you yet.
-Naruto, stop.
-It's hopeless.
-I'm going to wipe those
goofy grins off your faces.
-Goofy, goofy, goofy.
-This is so much fun.
Wee hee!
-They're big, and
they're stupid,
and they're indestructible.
-You just figure
that out, did you?
You've really hit bottom,
Iruka, teaming yourself up
with a snot-nosed kid.
It's sad really.
-Why are you doing this, Mizuki?
Stop this madness, please.
You don't know
what you're doing.
You wouldn't really betray
your comrades again, would you?
-Hmph, comrades.
-That's right-- men and
women of the Leaf Village
who would die for you.
What part of that
don't you understand?
-Comrades, ha.
Hmph, you're as
naive as ever, Iruka.
What I believe in is
power, pure power,
undiluted by sentimental notions
like comrades and loyalty.
-But Mizuki--
-Soon, I'll have that kind of
power, the ultimate power--
Lord Orochimaru's power.
-Huh?
Orochimaru?
-Then your eyes will be opened.
You'll learn how meaningless
a thing like comradeship
is when faced with
power like that.
-Mizuki, before
you lost your way,
you were one of
our finest shinobi.
It's not too late for you to--
-Don't bother.
Save your breath.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Darn it.
They're making mince meat out
of everything I throw at them.
-Iruka, if you really
believe in what you say,
here's your chance to prove it.
This love you have
for your comrades,
let's see how strong it is.
Try and prove me wrong.
Defeat me if you can.
Come on.
-Wait.
-Huh?
-Naruto, forget about these two.
Get after Mizuki.
-Man, I'd to-- OK,
but don't go anywhere.
We'll finish this later.
-Uh hey, look, big
brother, he's gone away.
-They all went
away, didn't they?
-Hey, you think maybe
it's Hide and Go Seek?
-Yeah, that's right.
Hide and Go Seek.
-I guess that means
we're it, huh?
-Hm?
Hey, no fair!
You play Rock Paper
Scissors to decide who's it.
Come on, let's find them.
RAIJIN: Yeah.
-This way, Iruka.
-Faster, Naruto.
-Remember what
happened last time.
-You're not arguing with me,
are you, you ignorant puppy?
If we keep wasting
time like this,
we're going to be
in a lot of trouble.
Huh?
-Now you're it.
-That was a good
one, big brother.
-Thank you.
-Come on, I don't have
time to play games
with these two clowns.
-Hey, bro, this Hide and Go
Seek is making me hungry.
-You and your big stomach.
You're always hungry.
OK, OK, here.
You're not going to go
and hog it all, are you?
-Course not.
Don't worry.
NARUTO: Hey, you two,
the Numbskull Brothers.
-Huh?
-You want a snack?
I'll give you
something to chew on.
-Stop provoking them, Naruto.
We have more important
things to do.
-Yeah, I get it.
Don't worry.
I know what I'm doing.
IRUKA: Mizuki.
Where are you?
MIZUKI: Poor Iruka.
How can you stop me
if you can't find me?
-Mizuki, stop this.
Don't be a fool.
Come on, show yourself.
-Huh?
-Always watch your own back.
That's one of the cardinal
rules for shinobi.
Well done, Iruka.
Excellent.
I see you're not as
dumb as you once were.
IRUKA: Always be aware that
your opponent may be bluffing.
That's another one of the
cardinal rules, isn't it?
-So you think you're
pretty smart, huh?
-What's he doing?
-That kid exploded.
NARUTO: Multi
Shadow Clone Jutsu.
Now let's play Extreme
Hide and Go Seek.
To win, you've got
to find all of us.
-Hear that?
Sounds like fun.
-Yeah, I like this way better.
The other way was too easy.
-So how are we going
to find them all, huh?
-Now I get it.
A decoy strategy.
-Finding them all should keep
those two tied up for a while.
-Good.
Now let's go.
BOTH: Ready or
not, here we come.
[screaming]
-Oh man, they're strong.
They make Grandma Tsunade
look like an old lady.
-Stupidity is a powerful thing.
-Stop this.
Will you come to your senses?
-Will you shut up?
-Why do you have this
insane obsession with power?
-Why?
Because power is everything.
-Don't go down this path.
It's still not too late.
-Hmph, you naive fool.
You really have no idea, do you?
What's the matter?
Why don't you attack?
-We are not enemies, Mizuki.
We are comrades of the Leaf.
-I can't tell you how sick
I am of the word "comrades."
-More than that-- we're kinsmen.
We are from the same village.
We have the will of
fire in our blood.
-Heh, the will of fire.
-Yes, that's right.
Now stop this madness, for
your sake more than anyone's.
-That's it.
Now you're really
starting to annoy me.
IRUKA: Mizuki.
-I was going to finish you off
quickly for old time's sake.
But not now.
I'll give you a taste
of what it feels
like listening to you
by making you suffer
a long, slow, agonizing death.
[laughing]
-Well, Naruto, how long you
planning to stay up here?
It's just a matter of
time before they spot you.
-Hm.
-Oh!
I see ya.
-There.
What did I tell you?
-OK, you want to do it?
Let's do it.
-Ready or not, here we come.
-Shadow Clone Jutsu.
-Hey, brother, didn't
we already play this?
-Yeah, I'm getting
bored of this game.
-Shadow clones again?
That trick's getting
kind of old, isn't it?
-Heh heh, just sit
back and watch.
All right, go!
-Yeah!
-What kind of game is this?
-Ring Around the Roses?
Hey, cut it out.
This is a stupid game.
-I get it.
Very clever, Naruto.
-I'm feeling a little sick.
Are you feeling a little sick?
-Yeah, I'm not feeling so good.
-OK, grab on, everyone.
-Let go already.
-I don't like this game.
-Everything's
ready, so here goes.
Say good bye, you ding-dongs.
IRUKA (VOICEOVER): Focus.
I've got to focus.
-Who are you trying to kid?
You were never a match for me?
-That's right.
I almost forgot.
IRUKA (VOICEOVER): You were
always better at everything,
weren't you?
I was the weak one who
needed special attention.
-It's hard to believe
it's been a year already.
Your instructors tell
me you're among the most
playful of their students,
always full of fun.
You're very brave.
It's hard to hide
sadness behind laughter.
-What makes you think
I'm sad about anything?
It's a noble thing to die
in the line of duty, right?
My parents gave their lives to
protect this place from the fox
demon.
I'm the son of heroes.
How can I be sad when
they died that way?
I'm not even sad because they
went and left me all alone.
If I cry, it's
because I'm proud.
-It's all right, Iruka.
I know that somewhere
inside of you, there's
a boy curled up
in a ball of pain.
But remember this,
you are not alone.
Inside every ninja of
the Hidden Leaf Village
burns the will of fire.
-The will of fire?
-It's what gives us the
strength to defend our village.
It's the unbreakable bond
that ties us all together.
It's what makes us a family.
I wonder, do you have it
yet, young as you are?
-I think so.
-Who is that over there?
-Mizuki?
-What's this all about?
Why were you hiding?
-Well, I had heard
that Iruka's been
feeling pretty down lately.
I was worried so I
thought I'd check on him.
Not just me, everyone's
worried about you, Iruka.
Come on, we're all just
over there goofing off.
Come and join us.
-Go on, my son.
IRUKA: That's the
Mizuki I remember.
The one I idolized.
The one who cared for his
friends more than anything.
That one.
Have you really forgotten
all that, Mizuki?
-Incredible, how
could I have forgotten
what an idiot you are.
-Stop, cut it out, will you?
-Here goes nothing.
-I really don't
feel good at all.
I-- I think I'm gonna-- Oh.
Oh?
-Huh?
-What's going on?
-Brother?
Did you just--
-I did.
I stepped on it.
I squashed it.
Our lunch has been destroyed!
-Our lunch!
[crying]
-OK, so you guys
are hungry, huh?
Well, chew on this.
Here you go.
BOTH: No.
We want our lunch back.
-What the--
-Oh no.
Now he's done it.
-Let me explain it to
you, you pathetic sap.
You thought I was
being nice to you
all that time, when
in fact, I loved
watching you be miserable.
I only wish I could have
made you suffer more.
STUDENT: Hey, Iruka.
-Huh?
-Come on, you want to
play some soccer with us?
What do you say?
We need you.
-Sure.
OK, thanks.
-Poor guy.
Man, what he's been through
would get anybody depressed.
-Yeah, we got to try and do
our best to cheer him up.
MIZUKI (VOICEOVER):
All this fuss.
Why?
All this attention, just
because your parents
were killed by the
Nine-Tailed Fox.
Heh, it served you right.
What?
Even the Hokage?
Why him?
It's not fair.
SARUTOBI: Who Is
that over there?
-Huh?
MIZUKI (VOICEOVER):
All right, I know just
what to do to get in good
with the old man too.
SARUTOBI: What's this all about?
Why were you hiding?
MIZUKI: Well, Iruka's been
feeling pretty down lately.
-That's a lie.
MIZUKI: I don't know which I
felt more-- contempt for you,
or pity.
But I enjoyed them both.
-No, you weren't like that.
I don't believe it.
-That's why I keep telling
you you're as naive as ever.
That kind of naivety
leads to fatal mistakes
on the battlefield, where
all that really matters
is how many of your
enemies you can kill.
If you throw kunai knives
around in a bamboo grove,
you never know where
they'll end up.
I prefer the direct attack.
I'm not falling for that again.
IRUKA (VOICEOVER): He's got the
advantage fighting in a place
like this.
Mizuki.
-Mizuki!
-I told you, it's
a waste of time.
-Calculate the trajectory,
and sometimes you
do know where the kunai
knife will end up.
-That's good.
So you've gotten
serious at last.
Well then, come on.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Where am I?
-Big brother, the little
guy's awake again.
-Oh great.
-It's all because of you
that we lost our lunch.
-You don't think we're gonna
let you live after that.
I'll slug him in the guts.
-I'll punch him in the head.
BOTH: A one, a two--
-A three.
What the--
-Huh?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): What
the heck's going on?
SHIKAMARU: What a drag.
I thought I was going
to get a day off.
-Who-- who's up there?
-Oh, let's skip the names.
It's not like we're going
to be friends, or anything.
-But if you really
want to know, we're
the back up squad
on this mission.
-The Leaf Village's best--
the fearsome threesome.
-Team InoShikaCho!
[theme music]
INO (VOICEOVER): What's
going on with these guys?
They're unbelievably strong.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
Strong enough
to escape my Shadow Possession
Jutsu by brute force.
CHOJI (VOICEOVER): If
this jutsu doesn't work,
we're in big trouble, guys.
INO (VOICEOVER): It just means
we better pick it up a notch,
right?
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): Right.
Ready, everyone?
ALL: Yeah!
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
OK then, here we go.
Time to play our
ace in the hole.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next time--
A New Formation, InoShikaCho!