[theme music]
-I want to show I can be as
fun a ninja as well, even if I
do not have Ninjutsu
or Genjutsu.
I want to prove it
to the whole world.
-All right!
Got a full day of
training ahead.
Ah!
Hey, bushy brow.
How you doin'?
-Naruto.
Good morning.
-Morning.
So, did Grandma Tsunade
check you out already?
-Uh--
-Well, come on,
what did she say?
It's a good thing she came,
'cause you know the village is
in trouble, don'tcha?
We're gonna need
every ninja we've got.
-Yes.
You are right.
-So you'd better get back
up to full fighting strength
as soon as you can,
CHILDREN: Come on, Naruto!
Hurry!
-What is it?
What's wrong?
-It's Konohamaru.
-Huh?
What do you mean?
What's going on?
-He'd blockaded himself.
-Ah?
He's done what?
(VOICEOVER) The Will
of Fire Still Burns.
-That's enough, now.
We don't want to have
to break it down.
KONOHAMARU: Go ahead and try it!
See what happens!
I'm the grandson of
the Third Hokage!
If you go against me, you're
going against my-- my grandpa.
You'll be going
against the Hokage!
-Lady Tsunade has
important work to do,
and she can't do it
until she gets in there.
-Oink.
Oink.
[sneeze]
[coughing]
KONOHAMARU: Pepper smoke bombs.
And you'll get worse
if you try comin' in.
The whole place
is booby trapped!
-Honorable Grandson, even you--
[coughing] [sneeze] there are
some things even you
can't get away with.
Now come out of there.
KONOHAMARU: Shut up and go away!
-Isn't it a little early
for all this racket?
It's giving me a
screaming headache.
-Lady Tsunade--
[oinking]
-Huh?
You two can't handle
one little kid?
-Well--
TSUNADE: Get him out of there.
-But ma'am, he's the
grandson of the Third Hokage.
-What do I care?
I'm the granddaughter
of the First Hokage.
I'm the one you need
to worry about now.
From what I can see,
it might do the brat
some good to be
roughed up a little.
Now get him out of there.
-Right.
NARUTO: Wait!
Don't!
-Naruto?
-Hold on.
Just wait a second.
I don't know exactly
what's going on here,
but don't be too rough
on Konohamaru, huh?
Please, Grandma Tsunade.
-He's a friend of yours, is he?
-Mm-hm.
Don't worry, I can get him out.
Just let me talk to him.
He'll listen to me.
-I want him out of there
by the end of the day.
-End of the day?
But-- Lady Tsundade!
Wait!
-Hello again.
-Oh, hi, Sakura.
Didn't you know that
Sasuke's been discharged?
-I actually came to see Lee.
He should be in
rehabilitation, right?
-He hasn't checked in.
That's funny.
It's not like him to be late.
-No, it certainly isn't.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): The
chances of the operation
being successful
are 50-50 at best.
And if it fails-- he'll die.
-Hey!
Konohamaru!
What are you doing
in there, anyway?
[knocking] Hey, I
know what we can do.
You want to go get some ramen?
How does that sound?
All you can eat, and it's on me!
Steaming hot, with
lots of barbecued pork!
Eggs on top, and
the crunchy things.
Well?
Hey, will you at
least say something?
KONOHAMARU: OK.
Shut up and go away!
-No kid's gonna talk
to me like that!
That does it.
Get out of there, or
I'm gonna drag you out.
KONOHAMARU: Yeah, yeah.
Just try it!
-You little--
-You OK, Naruto?
-Lee.
There you are.
-Huh?
Oh.
Hi, Sakura.
-These are for you.
-For-- for me?
Really?
Thank you very much.
Ah!
Ah-- sorry about that, Sakura.
-No sweat.
-Did you hear?
Sasuke's at home now.
He's recovering
nicely, and they say
he'll be back to his
old self in no time.
All thanks to Lady Tsunade.
-I am glad to hear it.
That is good news for everyone.
-She's everything
they say she is.
You should have her
take a look at you.
I'm sure she could help
you speed up your recovery.
-Ah-- could be.
-Meanwhile, if there's ever
anything I can do to help,
you know you only
have to ask me, OK?
-I appreciate that.
Thank you, Sakura.
-Kay, then.
See you later.
-Look at this place.
Not a single gambling
hall anywhere.
-Well, you don't have
time for that, anyway.
There's an awful lot of
work waiting to be done.
-Nowhere to gamble.
Or get a drink.
What a boring little
dump, the Leaf village is.
It's no fun at all.
Just like the Third Hokage.
-Lady Tsunade!
-I'm exhausted.
I just want to sit down
and have a drink somewhere.
Is that too much to ask?
Huh?
-If that's what you want, if
it's absolutely necessary,
I'll find you a place where you
can have a drink, all right?
-Really?
-Oink?
-But only if you
promise to get to work.
[groan]
-Go ahead.
You wanted a drink, so go on.
Have a drink.
-Look, Shizune, a cup of tea
wasn't exactly what I meant.
-Oh, I know what you
meant, all right.
I think sometimes I know you
better than you know yourself.
-What does that mean?
-Part of you was relieved you
couldn't get into the Hokage's
rooms because it
meant you wouldn't
have to do any work, right?
That's why you
left it to Naruto,
hoping you'd get a day off.
-Hm.
Maybe.
-Anyway, here is the updated
roster of the newest ninja.
You should really go over it.
There have been a lot
of changes in personnel.
You'll need to familiarize
yourself with them.
You have a lot of work to do.
-Hm.
It's all such a bore.
-Look, they have
sweet dumplings.
-You know those
things make me gag.
-Hey, come on, Konohamaru.
Come on out of there
already, will ya?
At least tell me why
you're doing this.
Maybe if I had a
clue, I could help.
-Please, Konohamaru?
-All right, then.
No more Mr. Nice Guy.
I tried to be sympathetic, but
I can see it's not working.
Secret Technique, Sexy Jutsu!
-Konohamaru, won't
you please come out?
don't keep me waiting.
Won't you come out, huh?
Ah-- come on!
Aren't you even gonna
say something, at least?
You want me to freeze
to death out here?
Now I'm angry.
That does it.
Time for Shadow Clone Jutsu!
-OK, Konohamaru.
We're comin' in!
1, 2, 3!
[coughing]
-Shoulda seen that
comin', I guess.
GIRL: Naruto, are you OK?
NARUTO: Yeah.
Except for feelin'
like an idiot.
-You can forget it.
This room belonged
to my grandpa.
No one gets in.
-Hm.
Eight D rank missions,
three C rank missions.
Exactly like Kurenai's own team.
It's not hard to see with the
Third Hokage was thinking.
This squad is a mirror image
of their parents' team.
-I see.
Oh.
Look how well balanced
this squad is.
Each member with his
or her own specialty.
[sigh]
-My neck's getting stiff.
I need some fresh air.
-Success.
Success.
-What are you gonna do now?
-You stubborn
little-- OK, if that's
the way you want
to play it, then
that's the way
we're gonna play it!
KONOHAMARU: This is the
Third Hokage's room.
Nobody uses it except him!
-Hm?
So that's it.
-I'm his grandson.
It's my duty to defend it.
-Hey, you little runt!
This is no time for that!
We're in danger.
It's the village
that needs defending!
-So what?
This stupid village can
burn down for all I care!
-That does it!
You just crossed the line!
Now I've officially had it.
Game's over, kid.
With my new powers, I can
easily blast those doors down.
Though I was hoping
not to have to use 'em.
-Naruto, watch out!
-Ah!
Grandma Tsunade.
Wait.
Be careful!
-Ah!
Huh?
-So here's the
thing, Konohamaru.
The village is in a lot
of trouble right now.
We've got to pull
together, because we're
down to less than
half our strength,
and we've still got
missions to perform.
-Yeah, yeah.
In case you've
forgotten, I'm the one
who told you that, remember?
-Oh, well.
OK.
But you see, the point is we
can't turn down any missions,
because that would just be
telling the world how weak we
are, and bring us
even more trouble.
-Yeah, and Iruka-sensei
already told us that, too.
I got it.
-What is it?
Is it that you don't
like Grandma Tsunade?
-No, no.
That's not it at all.
-Well then, what's it all about?
-Pretty soon, nobody's going
to call me Honorable Grandson
anymore.
I'll just be plain Konohamaru.
-Huh?
What's wrong with
plain Konohamaru?
-You don't get it.
-What do you mean?
I thought you always hated
being called Honorable Grandson.
-Pretty soon, everyone's
going to start
to forget about the old man.
-Huh?
-It won't be long.
They'll forget what
a great ninja he was,
and then they'll just
toss him into the back
of the closet like an old shoe.
Everything's changing so fast.
The village isn't
the same anymore.
-But it's still
the Leaf village.
That much will never change.
And you're crazy to
think that anybody's ever
going to forget
about the old man.
He'll be remembered
long after we're gone!
-They'll forget him.
Just wait.
-I'm saying they won't!
-Well, you're wrong!
-Oh, is that right?
What makes you so smart?
How do you know I'm wrong?
-'Cause you are.
-Argh!
I've had it with you!
You're coming with me!
-Where?
-First we'll go
to Grandma Tsunade
and make her swear an oath that
the Leaf village will never
change.
Then we'll get
everyone in the village
to promise they'll never forget
the old man, no matter what.
That ought to satisfy you, huh?
-Oink.
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER): I
should have never let her out
of my sight for a minute.
-Oink!
-Lead me to her, Tonton!
-Revitalizing the
cellular structure.
Huh.
-Oink.
Oink.
-Ah-ha.
So there you are.
We caught you.
-Shh.
-Lady Tsunade, are
you actually studying?
-Oink!
-Be quiet, will you?
I'm trying to concentrate here.
[scream]
-What did you say?
You've never concentrated
on anything but gambling!
I
-Huh?
That sounded like Shizune.
-Oh, just calm down.
I was thinking about that
medical ninja, Kabuto.
Remember?
-Um, what about him?
-Specifically his body's
ability to create new cells.
If I could apply that
technique to a patient--
-You mean Rock Lee, don't you?
-Even if it only increases
his chances from 50% to 51%,
I think it may be worth a try.
-Lady Tsunade, the
success of that technique
depends so much on
the person doing it.
There's no guarantee that
you'd be able to pull it off.
-Only one way to find out.
I mean, I am the Fifth
Hokage, after all.
-There's no way out
of it, Konohamaru.
I must go.
I am the Third
Hokage, after all.
-If that's what it means
to be Hokage, then quit.
-Everyone in this
village is family to me.
Protecting the family.
That's what it
means to be Hokage.
-Ah-- wait.
Grandpa!
-Just this once.
I'll make an exception.
-Where are we going, Konohamaru?
What's the matter?
Don't you want to
see Grandma Tsunade?
-Nope.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): I mean, I
am the Fifth Hokage, after all.
THIRD HOKAGE
(VOICEOVER): There's
no way out of it, Konohamaru.
I am the Third
Hokage, after all.
-There's no way out of it.
I'm the Honorable
Grandson, after all.
-Huh?
-I mean, I'm Konohamaru
of the Leaf village!
-Hey!
Uh, where are you goin'?
Wait up, Konohamaru!
What the heck's gotten into him?
Hey!
Konohamaru!
-What is it, Lady Tsunade?
-Oh, nothing.
[theme music]
ROCK LEE: From the
very beginning,
Guy-sensei taught me that I
could become a great ninja
through effort, experience,
and the power of youth.
Before I met him, I was lost.
But he showed me a
new path to follow.
A journey of hard work and great
struggle that would take me
to a destination I
had never dreamed of.
He made me believe.
But now--
NARUTO: Next time,
Sensei and Student,
the Bond of the Shinobi.
[theme music]