[theme music]
-Whoa.
I can't believe all
the new buildings
they're putting up around here.
-I heard a lot of the
construction sites
are shorthanded.
There aren't enough
carpenters in the village
to get the work done, so they've
had to hire a bunch of people
from outside the village.
-Even I know about that.
It's old man Genno.
Oh, Naruto.
-You know him?
-Yeah, he's from the land
of sand and he's into ramen.
Sometimes we run into
each other at Ichiraku.
-How about it?
Want to grab some later?
-Oh yeah!
-Here you go.
-Thanks, it looks great.
-Enjoy.
-Ahh, no doubt
about it, Ichiraku
has the best ramen in town.
-Well, I'm glad you think so.
-Could I have some
more water, please?
-Sure.
-Ahh, that hit the spot.
-You're done?
-That one bowl was
enough to fill you up?
-Not really.
I could always eat more ramen.
-Here then, you can finish mine.
-Awesome!
-Naruto.
-Don't worry, they're
always like this.
-The way they act, you'd
think Naruto was his grandson.
-You need to loosen up
a little bit, Sakura.
You've been hanging around too
many crabby people-- Grandma
Tsunade, Shino, Ino,
Kiba, Kakashi Sensei,
you're all crabs.
-We wouldn't be so
crabby towards you
if you weren't such a jerk.
-See, you're doing it again!
That's just what
I'm talking about.
[punch]
-Ow!
-Looks like it's almost
time for me to go.
[chatter]
-Ow!
My head!
Huh?
Looks like the fogs rolling in.
So what?
Like it makes any difference.
-Lady Tsunade, I apologize for
waking you up at this hour,
but it has to do with the
man that the Anbu Black
Ops have been tracking.
-What's going on?
-I'm afraid he's alluded them.
-You mean he got away?
How did he slip through the
fingers of an entire Anbu Black
Ops squad?
What do we know about him?
You must have at least been able
to come up with a name by now.
-We went through the
most recent Bingo Book
and there was no one that
matched his description.
So I looked in an old book,
and I found something.
-Genno?
Could it possibly be
Genno the trapper?
-You think it's him?
-I imagine he must
be pretty old by now.
It's been so many years
since I heard that name,
I figured he just passed away.
I don't know why he'd be hiding
in the Hidden Leaf Village.
-I guess old age catches up
with all of us sooner or later.
I guess I should have expected
as much from Leaf Anbu Black
Ops.
-You need to return what you
took from the foreman's house.
-Why would I be carrying
something like that
around after all this time?
I've had a long, full
life as a shinobi.
And if this is how it
has to end, so be it.
I just wish I'd
lived long enough
to see the end of the Hidden
Leaf Village with my own eyes.
-Paper bombs.
Take cover!
[explosion]
-Huh?
-So then, you think
someone's planning
an attack against the
Hidden Leaf Village, right?
-For now, that's all we've got.
It's the only
possible explanation.
Why else would they
want those plans?
Besides, Genno's last words
would support that theory.
Even with the blueprints,
it should take time
to plan their assault.
But we can't gamble
our lives on that.
We must assume the enemy
could attack us at any time.
I'm going to authorize an
S-level emergency security
alert.
Leave only those necessary
to guard the village
and send every available
man to secure the borders.
Use whatever force
necessary, attack
anyone who attempts
to cross the border.
They must not be allowed
to reach the village.
-Wow, what a beautiful day.
-Naruto.
-Oh, morning, Sakura.
-This assignment
sounds like a drag.
-Nonetheless, I'll be
counting on you to handle it.
That's why I'm
asking you to remain
stationed in the village.
-But in order to
get this job done,
I'm going to need more
men than you've given me.
-We haven't got a
single man to spare,
so you'll just have to make
do with what you've got.
Under the circumstances,
they're the best I can do.
-The best, huh?
-Fog?
It was clear as a bell
when I went to bed.
I wonder where
the fog came from.
-I was wondering the same thing.
Maybe it was just a dream.
Doesn't it seem kind of
deserted around here?
-The place is like a ghost town.
They must all be inside because
of the special security alert.
-What?
Special security alert?
How come nobody
told me about it?
-As a ninja, you should
notice these kinds of things.
-But if we're under a
special security alert,
that means the village is
in a state of emergency.
Why didn't anyone
tell us about it?
-Maybe that's why Lady
Tsunade wants to see us.
[knocking]
-Come in.
-Thank you ma'am.
I brought Naruto like you asked.
-Hey, Shikamaru.
Looks like I'm not the
only one who was left out.
-Left out?
What are you talking about?
-Ha, never mind.
But what did you think about
all that fog last night?
Pretty weird, huh?
-Cut it out.
I told you, you were dreaming.
-There wasn't any
fog last night.
-You see?
I told you so.
-What you saw was a smokescreen.
-What are you talking about?
-I'll explain it all
once everybody gets here.
-Naruto, Sakura, the reason
we took the two of you
off the S-level
emergency security unit
is because we wanted you
to work under Shikamaru
on a special mission.
-What?
-That's right.
We're working together.
First thing you need to do
is gather a few more people.
-Hmm?
-Would you quit pacing
around like that?
Calm down.
-It's already past the time
we were supposed to meet.
-Not quite.
To be accurate, it's
still 20 seconds til.
-Guess he made it.
-What's up?
You guys waiting
for anyone else?
-Can you tell me why you're
always the last to arrive?
-I'm glad we're all here.
We can finally get started.
As I'm sure you're
all aware by now,
the village has been placed
under an S-level emergency
security alert.
You're probably wondering why.
-Last night's
smokescreen, right?
-You guys knew that
was a smokescreen?
-Of course.
My insects made
quite a fuss over it.
-Really?
That's funny, I didn't
notice anything.
-Maybe you should stop
eating and open your eyes!
-I didn't notice it either.
Could it be that I'm
worse than Naruto?
-Lee, do you have any
idea what caused this?
-I know it had something
to do with Anbu Black Ops,
so I did not get involved.
-You're right, the
Anbu were at the scene.
-Just as I thought.
-This is as much as we know.
The Anbu have had a man
under constant surveillance
for the past two weeks.
He had broken into the
construction foreman's house.
Once inside, he found the
chest containing the blueprints
for all the important
structures in the village,
and he stole them.
-Blueprints?
-So what's the big deal?
What can this guy do with a
bunch of stolen blueprints?
-What can he do with them?
Give me a break.
-Oh Naruto.
-In the wrong hands,
the blueprints
for the fort around the
village could prove disastrous.
-How?
-Once the enemy has a detailed
analysis of the structure,
it would be a simple
matter for them
to find the most efficient
way to break into the village.
What if they have the blueprint
to Lady Tsunade's mansion?
With that as their guide,
it would be child's play
to devise an attack on
Lady Tsunade's room.
-And if they were to fall into
the hands of an assassin--
-You're right.
I never knew how
dangerous this could be.
-That smokescreen last
night was something
the suspect used to
cover his get away.
-I see.
-Despite all the
smoke, the Black Ops
were able to corner him
in the eastern forest.
But before they could
get him to say anything--
[explosion]
-Anbu searched the blast site.
They concluded that he
had not been in possession
of the blueprints when
the explosion occurred.
We have to hope
they're not already
in the hands of the enemy,
or the Hidden Leaf Village
could be history.
You can see why Lady Tsunade
ordered the S-level emergency
security alert.
-So what's our mission?
What do we have to do?
-Since he didn't have
them when he died,
our mission is to find out where
the thief hid those blueprints
and recover them.
-It's like finding a
needle in a haystack.
-If we want to find where
the thief hid something,
maybe we should start out
by retracing his steps.
-The thing is, this
guy had a reputation
for setting some pretty
nasty booby traps.
And chances are, we'll
run into some of them
when we're looking
for those blueprints.
-I'd say it's highly probable.
-We understand.
Just give the order
and we'll get started.
-Well then, what
are we waiting for?
-You'll need some
background information.
We checked around
some and found out
that this guy snuck
into the village
a few months back,
posing as a carpenter.
-Wait, this guy is--
-The man's name was Genno.
-No.
No way.
It's impossible.
Old man Genno didn't have
a mean bone in his body.
He's just a sweet old man who
loved the ramen at Ichiraku.
He's not the kind of
person who would do that.
He wouldn't destroy the
Hidden Leaf Village.
-Come on, Naruto.
You thought he was a nice
guy, but it was all an act.
He wanted us to
let our guard down.
So when he got here,
he played the part
of the harmless old
carpenter to avoid suspicion.
-You can't love ramen
that much and be bad.
-No, bad guys like ramen.
They love it.
-Troji, maybe if you try and
talk some sense into him,
he'll listen.
-Though I've got to
admit, I've never
seen a bad person eating
at Ichiraku's ever.
-Told ya.
-That's great.
Thanks for helping
me out, Troji.
-Here's the list of all the
blueprints that were stolen.
I can't tell you
how ashamed I am
for not guarding
these plans properly.
I can never face
Lady Tsunade again.
-Which construction jobs
was Genno involved with?
-None.
He didn't work on any of those.
-But I thought-- didn't you
say that Genno worked for you?
-The structures on
that list involve
the safety of the village.
Outsiders aren't
allowed to work on them.
I always make sure that
outside contractors are only
allowed to work on
residential construction.
-So then you don't think
there's any chance he could
have slipped in and set
traps on these sites?
-We have excellent security.
-Right, but we should
check them just in case.
-Here, Neji.
-I think you're best qualified
to handle this, Hinata.
-Of course.
-I would like to
volunteer to help.
-Me too.
-I know I mentioned
this, but there's still
a chance the enemy hasn't
gotten those plans yet.
He evaded the Anbu Black Ops
for awhile during his escape.
So he could have hidden them.
-And you want us to think like
thieves and figure out where,
right?
-Leave it to us.
-We're going on a treasure hunt,
Akamaru, so do your stuff, boy.
[barking]
-Ino and Sakura, I
want you two to go over
what's left of the
old man's body.
I know it's a long shot, but you
might be able to find a clue.
-Oh, please.
Why do we have to do it?
-Got it.
-Fine, if you think
it'll do any good.
Sakura, you really think
you can handle this?
-All that medical ninja training
will finally come in handy.
I can't be scared of
something like this.
-You may be fine, but
it gives me the creeps.
-Now let's talk.
The carpenter.
I need you to tell me everything
you remember about him.
I want to know where he
came from, who he talked to,
what he did, anything.
-I remember when he first
came to the village.
It was about three months ago.
He came to my place with
a letter of recommendation
from a famous master carpenter
from the land of sand.
I'm sure you're aware that
there's a bit of a construction
boom in the Hidden
Leaf Village right now.
Every local carpenter has
all the work he can handle.
We needed more skilled hands,
so I hired him right away.
He was an adequate
carpenter, nothing special.
I didn't see any reason to
offer him a permanent job.
But like I said, we needed
all the hands we could get.
He took his job seriously.
He always showed up on time
and did whatever he was told.
After he'd been
working here awhile,
I discovered that the letter
of recommendation he'd given me
was a fake.
I don't know if it'll do
any good, but here it is.
-So how did you figure
out it was a fake?
-I've been going
over my records,
and I found another
letter of recommendation
from the same master
carpenter 10 years ago.
Something struck me
as odd, so I decided
to compare the two letters.
And that's when I discovered
that the handwriting didn't
match.
-Do you mind if I look
at the other letter?
-Sure, it's over
here in this cabinet.
That's odd.
Can't seem to find it.
I specifically remember
putting it in here.
-It's all right if
you can't find it.
-Sorry.
To be honest, we
really didn't care
if the letter of
recommendation was fake
or not, as long as he
continued to do good work
and kept his nose
out of trouble.
I realize now that it was
a terrible mistake not
to notify Lady
Tsunade right away.
It never occurred to
me that the old man
could be a shinobi who was
sent here from another country
to steal our plans.
I still can't believe old
man Genno would do something
like that.
Look, are you absolutely
sure he's the one who did it?
-I'm with you.
I can't believe
he did it either.
-Doesn't look like he set
any traps for us in here.
It's clear.
-This is where the
old man lived, huh?
-He was the perfect tenant,
always paid the rent on time.
A nice, quiet gentleman
with good manners.
Of course, once in a
while, he'd come home
after he'd had a drink or two
with his carpenter friends.
But even then, he never
caused any trouble.
-I guess I never really expected
this guy to leave any clues
laying around the
place he lived.
-Found it!
-What did you find?
-A lovely variety
of udon noodles.
He's got sweet,
savory, and super thin.
-We didn't come here
to look for food.
-But usually when
someone lives alone,
they at least stock
up on the essentials
so they can cook something
up when they get hungry.
There's only instant noodles.
-Maybe he didn't like to
cook, so he ate out a lot.
Naruto said that he liked
the ramen at Ichiraku.
That is what you said, right?
-Yeah.
-But if he cooked at home, he
could spend less and eat more.
-We're not talking
about you, Troji.
-The old man really
didn't talk much.
And when he did, it
wasn't about yourself.
-Yeah, I figured as much.
-Oh, yeah, except
for this one time
when he came back from
lunch and went on and on
about this great kid he had made
friends with in the village.
-He probably told
the kid where he
hid the plans before he died.
-Yeah, well, I wouldn't
be too sure about that.
-What are you talking about?
It's the only lead we've got.
So we need to find this
kid and see what he knows.
-I think it would
be a waste of time
for us to look for
this kid, because I
don't think he knows anything.
-What?
How do we know until
we talk to the guy?
-You dummy.
We've already talked to him.
The kid is you.
-Ahh!
He meant me?
-Yeah.
No doubt about it.
-You're Naruto Uzumaki?
-Huh?
-I'm afraid we're going to have
to ask you a few questions.
[music]
TROJI: I wonder what sort
of interrogation Naruto's
going through?
SHIKAMARU: They're
probably using
some regressive hypnosis on him.
TROJI: What the heck is that?
SHIKAMARU: It's a
jutsu where memories
are pulled from
the subconscious.
TROJI: Huh?
You're kidding, right?
Maybe it'll work on Naruto, who
has no sense of memory at all.
NARUTO: Won't be so sure.
SHIKAMARU: Yeah, that's true.
That old man seems to
have been a trickster.
I mean, what are you doing here?
NARUTO: Next time, the Anbu
gives up Naruto's recollection.