[theme music]
-Yah!
As you can see, you failed.
Jiraiya, the Toad Sage falls
victim to no woman's charm.
Rare beauties fall for me.
When you reach stature
I have, the ladies
worship at your awesomeness.
-Ah, don't give me that.
One wink from a
pretty girl, and you
turned into a mountain of mush.
You fell for it like a
ton of bricks, Pervy Sage.
-I really wish you
wouldn't call me
that in front of other people.
-Are you kidding me?
We've got worse
things to worry about
than what these
guys think of you.
Get with it, Pervy Sage.
-Didn't I just ask you
not to call me that?
-Whatever name you go by,
Master Jiraiya, I must say,
you're something of
a disappointment.
A lecherous old man with
the disposition of a child.
It's almost
impossible to believe
that you are one of the
three Legendary Sannin.
-What?
You-- you already
know who he is?
-Uh, don't be fooled
by appearances,
or, you know, anything this
little squirt might say.
-So you somehow
managed to release
the genjutsu we cast on her, eh?
-What kind of coward would
do something like that?
Using his Saimingan
to inflict an illusion
jutsu on an innocent
woman, all in order
to separate Naruto from me.
-T-- to separate us?
But why?
-I know that he's the
one you're really after.
-The Nine-Tailed
spirit inside Naruto--
that's what you're after?
-That explains how Kakashi knew.
Now I understand.
He learned it from you.
You're right.
Naruto is the prize that
the Akatsuki are after.
And we will have him.
-Huh?
Wh-- what's going on?
-No way you're getting Naruto.
-We'll see about that.
-Actually, this is
all very convenient.
I can eliminate you
both at the same time.
SASUKE: Stay out of this.
-Huh?
-The only one who's going
to eliminate him is me.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Hate
Among the Uchihas-- the Last
of the Clan.
Saskue.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
Of course-- revenge.
-Go away.
You don't interest
me at the moment.
-Well, get interested.
-Sasuke, no!
-Damn you lousy--
-No, Naruto.
Don't butt in.
Mind your own business.
I told you before, I've
lived my whole life
for this day, this moment.
This fight is mine!
-Sasuke.
[grunting]
-Not finished.
ITACHI (VOICEOVER):
He can't even
manage to make the hand sign.
-This fight is mine.
-So be it.
-You heard him, old man.
This fight is none
of our business.
Let's let the two
of them sort it out.
-And now finally--
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): How?
All these years,
nothing has changed.
How can it be?
-You show him no mercy.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): What have
I been doing all these years?
Was it-- was it all for this?
-You're still too weak.
You don't have enough hate.
And you know something?
You never will.
[gasping]
-Where am I?
This place, I know it.
[whimpering]
ITACHI (VOICEOVER): Yes.
It's our childhood home.
-Father and mother.
-You're weak, Sasuke.
And 24 hours from now--
SASUKE: Don't.
-You'll be weaker still.
-No!
[screaming]
-Auntie!
Uncle!
ITACHI (VOICEOVER): You're
not even worth killing.
Foolish little brother.
If you wish to kill me one
day, foster your hatred
and despise me.
Surviving in such an
unsightly manner as this.
By all means, flee.
Cling to your wretched life.
[screaming]
-Isn't that heartwarming?
Using Tsukuyomi on
his own brother.
-That does it.
I'm through standing around.
What the-- what's going on?
-Ninja Art Toad Mouth Trap.
You've both just been
swallowed by the Mountain Toad.
Welcome, my friends, to
the belly of the beast.
He has a very sensitive
digestive tract.
Be careful not to upset him.
Not the most glorious
way to die, is it?
It must be humbling
to know that you've
been reduced to toad bait.
He he he.
-Whoa, I'm not
liking this at all.
-Naruto, stay still.
Just remain calm.
Trust in my jutsu.
-Kisame, come.
-Easier said than done.
-It's useless.
The ninja hasn't
been born who can
survive this powerful stomach.
-Don't look now, but there's a
wall of flesh coming after us.
It's too fast.
We won't make it.
It's no use.
-Huh?
Hey, Pervy Sage.
What the heck happened?
They both got away.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
He did the impossible.
He broke through the wall.
-So we just run away again?
We do a lot of that.
-There's no rush for now.
We'll get Naruto when
the time is right.
Besides, I felt it wise
for us to find some place
to rest for awhile and
recharge my powers.
ITACHI (VOICEOVER):
On top of Tsukuyomi,
to have to use
Amaterasu as well--
it was more exhausting
than I thought.
-What is this stuff anyway?
Some kind of black fire?
JIRAIYA: Stay away from it.
-Gyah!
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
How did they do it?
What did they use to escape?
And these black flames--
to burn the Stone Toad when
it has the power to
spit fire itself.
That is strong jutsu indeed.
-There.
Sealing Jutsu.
Fire Seal, now.
All right.
Well, that takes care of
that for the time between.
Now for Sasuke.
-Sasuke.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
What did he do to him?
-Huh?
-Dynamic--
-Guy.
-Entry!
Oh.
[grumbling]
-I guess I was a little
over enthusiastic.
You see, I-- I was
trying to hurry
and I couldn't see very clearly.
Using my headband to peer into
the opening, all I could see
were two sinister
figures so-- I'm
going to put an end
to this right now.
-Do you know what?
If this is your way of
saying sorry, it stinks.
-I'm sorry but it was just
a simple misunderstanding.
-Simple-minded's more like it.
But never mind that now.
We've got to get Sasuke to
the medical corps at once.
GUY: Right.
JIRAIYA: He's badly beaten
up, his arm is broken,
and he's been knocked out
by whatever jutsu that
was that Itachi used on him.
GUY (VOICEOVER): Could it be the
same thing he used on Kakashi?
-Pervy Sage, Sasuke is going to
be all right though, isn't he?
-Physically, yes.
But I am worried about what
may have been done to his mind.
-Enough!
You're dead!
Die!
Yeah
-Enough.
[screaming]
-What the heck.
What did Sasuke ever
do to deserve this?
OK, Pervy Sage, it's
time for a new game
plan starting right now.
I admit I let those
goons scare me a little.
But that's over.
No more running.
After all, it's me
they're after, right?
Well, OK then, it's time I
give them what they want.
-Hmph.
Nice speech, kid.
But I'm afraid you wouldn't
stand a chance against them.
You're not in the same league.
What would have happened if I
hadn't shown up just now, huh?
It took all I had to
get them away from you.
-Is that right?
So what are you suggesting?
That we just do nothing?
Sit here waiting for
them to hit us again?
What kind of strategy is that?
-Just be quiet.
You haven't earned the right.
I'm sorry, Guy.
I wanted to let Sasuke
fight his own fight.
I see now I should
have intervened sooner.
-This is obviously
the same sort of jutsu
that Kakashi was hit with.
We don't know when
he'll come out of it.
-What?
Kakashi-sensei?
-There's nothing worse
than seeing your students
fall in battle.
It's like losing little
pieces of your soul.
What we need is a supreme
medical specialist,
a master of healing
arts, and soon.
-You're right.
And the woman
you're talking about
is the one we've come to find.
-Huh?
The woman?
-You don't mean--
-Wha-- what are you going
to do with all that cash?
-Yes, that's exactly who I mean.
Another of the Legendary Sannin.
The Queen of Slugs and Elixirs.
-Take a good look, Shizune.
The losing streak is over.
Our luck is about to change.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
The Gambling Fool
and Mistress of the Healing
Arts-- Lady Tsunade.
[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): A festival?
Food and games and prizes?
I love festivals.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER): Great.
But hand over your wallet, kid.
I'll take care of it for you.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Say what?
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
The three worst things
for a ninja are money,
gambling, and women.
Without the money, you
won't get into trouble
with the other two.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Oh, come on.
You think everybody's
like you, Pervy Sage?
Well, I'm going to have a good
time, and you can't stop me.
Next time, A New
Training Begins.
I Will Be Strong!
Man, it's like hanging
out with your mother.