[music playing]
[theme music]
[shuddering]
-Hm.
-Go on, Grandma Tsunade.
Don't worry.
You can tell me.
-Hm.
-You know, I have been feeling
kind of out of it lately.
I've been messing up
a lot in my training.
I knew something was wrong
when I couldn't get down
more than five bowls
of Ichiraku ramen.
I've got some kind of awful
incurable disease, don't I?
Go on, let me know the worst.
How much time have I got?
-Oh, shut up.
You're fine.
-Huh?
[screaming]
Hey!
That's Bushy Brow's
medical chart!
-He's overdue for
a full examination.
He's been avoiding it.
-But-- what about, uh--
TSUNADE: You're still
an idiot, that's all.
Go on, get out of here!
[yelling]
-Naruto!
Get your clothes on!
-Sorry!
-Good grief!
-Well, how did it go?
-I'm perfectly healthy.
She says I'm good to go.
-Huh.
Well, bully for you.
NARUTO: What's his problem?
-He's in one of his moods.
NARUTO: Whatever.
Oh, by the way, have you
seen Bushy Brow around?
-No, but I'm pretty sure
where you can find him.
This is where he
usually is these days.
NARUTO: I know it well.
LEE: 2,954.
2,955.
2956.
2957.
2958.
-Whoa, is that for real?
And after those
injuries, we thought
he'd be finished as a ninja.
[screaming]
NARUTO: Bushy Brow!
TENTEN: Lee!
NARUTO: You all right?
[groaning]
-Lee.
-It is nothing.
I am all right.
-You know, Grandma Tsunade says
you skipped your physical exam.
She wants to see you.
-(WEAKLY) Oh.
It must have slipped my mind.
I have been feeling
so much better lately.
That is all.
-You don't look so great.
-What you need is more rest.
That means no more training.
[gasping]
There's cumulative damage
to your chakra network.
You're forgetting
you were injured
so badly that your days as a
ninja might have been over.
LEE: I live by my own rules!
[gasping]
-Your own rules?
-Yes!
And rule number one is to
never forget your goal.
I must work to be the
best ninja I can be.
-Hmph.
[groaning]
-Oh, I give up.
I'll take you off active duty,
but you can keep training.
Just don't overdo it.
-Right!
TSUNADE: Above all,
no hidden lotus.
Understood?
-Right.
NARUTO: Bushy Brow!
How'd it go?
Huh?
What's wrong with you?
Hey!
Uh--
-The results must
have been grim.
Very grim from the looks of it.
-Tenten, what are you saying?
You don't think--
-Well, you saw the
look on his face.
-No!
No!
GUY: Why so down, Lee?
[gasping]
LEE: Guy Sensei.
-I heard the results
of your exam.
You have permission to
keep training, right?
-Yes, sir, but they
told me no lotus.
-I recall a day you were crying.
-Huh?
-You worked hard, Lee.
There's no doubt in my mind
the surgery will be a success.
[gasping]
You have the power to
shape your own destiny.
And on the 1 in 1,000-- no, 1
in a million chance something
should happen to go wrong, I
will die right along with you.
Since the day I
met you, my nindo
has been to train you
to become the most
splendid ninja possible.
That's a promise.
You trusted me then, and
your surgery was successful.
You must trust me now.
[gasping]
If you must forsake
the hidden lotus,
then you'll just have to
work that much harder.
There is nothing you can't
accomplish through hard work.
-Sensei!
Huh?
GUY: You can do it
with your dedication.
-Right!
-We've laid off
training for too long.
Let's begin at once.
To the practice
hall on the double!
-Coming, Sensei.
GUY: If you're not there in
ten seconds, it's 500 push-ups.
LEE: Right!
I was foolish to think I
could make it in ten seconds.
[laughing]
-It's all good.
A little exercise
won't hurt you.
-500.
[groaning]
[panting]
No pain, no gain.
Right, Sensei?
[groaning]
Huh?
Who is that?
GUY: That's Yagura.
He's been here for a week.
A friend of mine
asked me to determine
whether he has the
makings of a ninja.
-His name is Yagura?
He is quite good.
-Yeah.
He has the makings, all right.
He takes everything I teach him
and absorbs it like a sponge.
[gasping]
-You're Rock Lee, aren't you?
-Uh, yes.
-I've heard your skills
are truly remarkable.
Guy Sensei told
me all about you.
-Uh, well, really, I--
[laughing]
-Don't be modest.
-Guy Sensei?
-Huh?
-I'd be grateful if you'd let
your prize pupil train with me.
-Very well.
Begin!
-Huh?
Guy Sensei!
-Well, you wanted to
train, didn't you, Lee?
What a perfect way to
begin by warming up
with your junior partner?
-I guess.
GUY: Now, remember,
he's only a rookie.
So try not to hurt him.
LEE: All right.
NARUTO: What's Bushy
Brow doing working out
in the training hall?
I thought his
condition was grim.
Isn't that what you said?
TENTEN: Yeah.
Grim.
Very grim.
[gasping]
-I'm only just a
novice, and I'm honored
that you're willing to teach me.
-Oh.
Not at all.
I hope you will bear with me.
-Huh?
[guy laughing]
GUY: All right, you two.
I want you to attack your
opponent with everything
you've got, but
always with respect.
And through the
power of youth, you
lay the foundations
of friendship.
Now then, fight!
-(VOICEOVER) He is fast.
-I want you to show me
every secret technique
that you've ever
learned from Might Guy.
[gasping]
[groaning]
LEE (VOICEOVER): Such power.
[yelling]
These are not the
blows of a rookie.
I cannot take much more.
Leaf hurricane!
-(VOICEOVER) The attack from
above disguises the attack from
below.
[thud]
[gasping]
-Incredible.
He defeated the leaf hurricane.
[yelling]
[groaning]
GUY: Stop!
That's enough!
Lee, are you all right?
[yelling]
[gasping]
-Bushy Brow, you OK?
What happened?
What was that?
-It was a cross-block.
Capturing an opponent's kick
between the knee and elbow,
crushing the bone.
It requires perfect timing.
Where in the world did you
learn that move, Yagura?
-I didn't mean to.
It was only a reflex
reaction, that's all.
I'm so sorry, Lee.
Are you all right?
[gasping]
GUY: If Lee hadn't been
wearing his ankle weights,
the bone would have
been shattered.
[groaning]
-Good move, Yagura.
Shall we continue
our training session?
-That's enough for today.
I want the medics to take
a look at that ankle.
-I am fine, Sensei.
[groaning]
-You got to be crazy
even trying this!
Didn't the hospital tell you
you're condition is grim?
Very grim!
-Huh?
-What do you mean grim?
-Well, I mean--
that's what they said.
Right, Tenten?
-Not in those words exactly.
NARUTO: Well,
something like that!
-(VOICEOVER) Even
wearing weights,
he was able to move that fast.
GUY: (LOUDLY) Where
did grim come from?
-Well, fortunately,
the bone's all right
-Thank you.
[groaning]
-So, how soon can
I start training?
[gasping]
-Training?
Are you out of your mind?
You're going to
rest, and that's all.
You're lucky there
wasn't permanent damage
to your Achilles tendon.
[sighing]
NARUTO: Why'd you have to
say his condition was grim?
[slurping]
You made me think he was,
like, dying or something.
-Huh?
TENTEN: OK, OK.
But he looked so gloomy when
he came out of the hospital.
What was I supposed to think?
I just assumed.
-No wonder he's feeling down.
Having to coach some trainee
who's not even in the Academy.
-Lee's coaching a trainee?
-That's right.
Some new guy who's only
been training for a week.
-He's good.
You should have seen
him do this move.
Uh, what was it called?
The uh--
-The cross-block.
And he pulled it off without
even thinking about it.
It's no wonder Lee's
acting so depressed.
-If Lee were the
type to let something
like that get him down, he
would have quit a long time ago.
-Huh?
-All his time at
the Academy, he's
been told he doesn't
have enough talent
to ever master
ninjutsu or genjutsu.
If I were in his place, I would
have given up long before now.
But hard work and perseverance
can mean more than raw talent.
I honestly believe
that if he can just
recover from his injuries,
Lee may surpass us all.
TENTEN: It's true.
NARUTO: Yeah.
TENTEN: But still,
[gasping]
If he pushes too hard, he
could suffer permanent damage.
And no amount of perseverance
will help him then.
-(ANGRILY) Why do you have to
be so negative all the time?
TENTEN: OK, OK, I'm just saying.
NARUTO: Well, cut
it out, will you?
Man, it's like you're the
voice of doom or something.
-Permanent damage?
TENTEN: OK, sorry.
I know as much as
anyone, we have a lot
to be grateful to him for.
-Huh?
Grateful?
-Yeah, very grateful.
GUY: All right.
Today I'm going to teach
you about self-rule.
-You're what?
-You're teaching us self-rule?
-Yes!
Yes!
Me first, Sensei!
Me first!
Whatever it is, I'm
ready to learn it.
[laughing]
Teach me, Sensei!
-As you go through
life, you'll find
that the world is
governed by many rules.
But the most important
rules are the ones
that come from
within-- the rules
that you place on yourself.
GUY: Right.
Today, I'm going to give you
all a very special reward.
-A reward?
-Like what?
GUY: Like this.
[laughing]
[screaming]
Your own set of tights,
just like the ones I use.
Designed for the ultimate in
comfort and ease of movement,
they have outstanding
ventilation and moisture
wicking properties.
One training session
in these, and you're
going to want to wear
them all the time.
Oh yeah.
-Oh!
This is so exciting!
I cannot wait!
Me first, Sensei, me first!
-Those tights were comfortable.
And I looked pretty
cool in them, too.
-Yeah, I bet you did.
[laughing]
NEJI: Yes, it's true.
If Lee weren't here--
[laughing]
-To youth!
-To effort
-And here's to the chicken
that crossed the road.
-But seriously, folks.
[imitating chicken]
TENTEN: I'd sure be sorry
not to have Lee around.
-Yeah, so would I.
TSUNADE: I realize a C-rank
mission is unworthy of you,
but I'm afraid you're
the only one available.
-Leave it to me.
Oh, and if I may be permitted,
I know just the person
I'd like to bring along.
[groaning]
-Yagura!
Do not worry.
We will train agai-- huh?
-Thanks, but I don't really
think that'll be necessary.
You did well considering those
ankle weights, but still.
There's nothing special
I'd want to steal from you.
-Steal from you?
YAGURA: You have no
gift of your own.
You're just a hardworking grunt,
a pale imitation of Guy Sensei.
-A what?
YAGURA: Even Guy Sensei
himself knows that.
He's given up on you.
-(ANGRILY) That is a filthy lie!
Guy Sensei has always said that
his whole purpose as a ninja
is to make sure I become
a fine ninja, too.
[laughing]
-If that's really the case,
then let me ask you this.
Why would he ask me to
accompany him on a mission?
Me.
Not you.
-(QUIETLY) He would never--
[laughing]
YAGURA: Sorry, but hard work is
no substitute for real talent.
[laughing]
-It is a lie!
I tell you!
Guy Sensei would never!
Huh?
No way.
I do not believe it.
[laughing]
[slurping]
[door opening]
SHIZUNE: Lady Tsunade!
-Well?
What is it now?
-Yagura's in the hospital.
He's been badly hurt.
-What the?
What happened?
He was on a mission with Guy.
-No, I'm afraid not, my lady.
Yagura was attacked before
he even reached the building.
-Then that means the trainee
traveling with Guy is--
SHIZUNE: Yes, an impostor.
[groaning]
-Never a moment's peace.
It's one thing after another.
And these are the only
ones left to form a squad.
SHIZUNE: Well, what
do you want me to do?
-Go on!
Mobilize Neji,
Tenten, and Naruto
and send them after Guy
and the phony Yagura.
-Right away.
TSUNADE: And get Sakura.
-Huh?
-Have her watch Lee.
If he learns about this,
he'll forget his injuries
and do something rash.
SHIZUNE: Yes, my lady.
NARUTO: Neji!
Are we sure that Bushier
Brows Sensei went this way?
-He was headed for the
Land of Mountain Streams,
and the most direct route
is through these woods.
TENTEN: There's another
way through the mountains,
but he'd never have taken it.
It's too dangerous.
[laughing]
-Hey!
You still with me, Yagura?
YAGURA: Yes, Sensei, I'm here.
GUY: You see, the trick is
to be sure of your footing
while never slowing down.
YAGURA: Right.
-Lee can do it blindfolded.
He's wonderful at this sort of--
[screaming]
What is it, Yagura?
Oh no.
[grunting]
[crashing]
(YELLING) Yagura!
Where are you?
Yagura?
Can you hear me?
I may have let his raw
talent blind me to the fact
that he's still only a trainee.
Huh?
Yagura, is that you?
What are you doing?
Huh?
Wooden training dummies
for kung fu training.
[grunting]
Ah, how it brings back fond
memories of my fiery youth.
The hours I spent furiously
pummeling dummies just
like these.
It seems like it
was only yesterday.
Still, it's very
curious to find them
way up here in the
middle of nowhere.
I wonder who put them up here
and for what dark purpose.
[grunting]
Hm.
So these wooden dummies
are capable of attack.
Tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk, tsk.
Nice try, but you'll
have to do better
than that, my wooden friend.
You're capable only of repeating
the same pattern of movement,
and your range is
only 3.5 meters,
so if I just stay beyond
that, I'll be safe.
[screaming]
You can walk, my wooden friend?
[groaning]
What the devil?
NARUTO: Neji!
Any sign of them yet?
-No.
Even my Byakugan isn't
finding any trace of them.
-They must be farther ahead
of us than we thought.
[groaning]
-They never would have taken
the mountain route, would they?
[laughing]
-All right.
So you can move.
But you're earth-bound.
You'll never reach me up here.
Oh.
You can jump, my wooden friend?
What a surprise!
[screaming]
Oh, no, you don't!
[yelling]
[laughing]
Huh?
[gasping]
[laughing]
I could use some high
altitude training.
[grunting]
[laughing]
[yelling]
LEE: 6985.
6986.
6987.
6988.
6989.
LEE (VOICEOVER): An injury is
no excuse to stop training.
If I cannot use my legs, then
I will focus on my upper body
strength.
Guy Sensei must have
been disappointed in me
for not trying enough.
He took Yagura with
him on the mission only
to teach me a lesson.
Yes, that must be it!
6996.
6997.
[gasping]
6998.
GUY (VOICEOVER): Their
defenses are rudimentary,
and their movements are
repetitive and predictable.
[grunting]
Or so I thought.
The biggest problem is
there are so many of them.
There seems to be no end.
[groaning]
[clicking sound]
Huh?
What's that sound?
[clicking sound]
What?
[wind blowing]
[theme music]
[music playing]
LEE: Amazing.
This wooden dummy's
power is amazing.
GUY: To be able to
deflect my kicks,
I'm going to need
to go at full power.
LEE: All right.
I will have to use
every ounce of my power.
GUY: Very well.
Come at me with all you got.
LEE: But I have no choice.
GUY AND LEE: I must
follow my ninja way
all the way to the end.
NARUTO: Next time--
"Hot-Blooded Confrontation--
Student Versus Sensei!"
[theme music]