[theme song]
-What is it?
What's wrong?
-You!
Identify yourself!
Now!
-It was you, wasn't it?
You killed him.
-What?
Me?
No.
I know nothing about it.
I swear.
The cursed warrior.
-Hey!
Look at me!
I'm a booger!
It gets boring training alone.
Specially if you're not
really training for anything.
When are we gonna
go after Sasuke,
or something big like that?
-A request from the
Land of Birds, huh?
That's a long way from here.
-Yes.
That was our first
reaction as well.
-An apparition in the
form of a cursed warrior
is terrorizing the people and
giving rise to wicked rumors.
They want us to
go catch a ghost?
-I told the man it was too
far to go on such a wild goose
chase, but he was
incredibly persistent.
-I've been ordered not to
accept no for an answer.
I am begging you to
accept this mission.
Is it because the
money isn't enough?
Is that it?
This is a difficult time
for the Land of Birds.
We had to bankrupt our treasury
to afford even that much.
-It's not a question
of the money.
My problem is with the
nature of the mission itself.
But, now that you mention
it, there's not enough here
to even cover out
travel expenses.
-Then I have no choice.
I must make the
ultimate sacrifice.
-Wait!
No!
-I'll throw in all the
money I have in the world.
Everything I own I
will gladly give up.
Please.
Just say yes.
-Aw.
-Uh-huh.
So you gave in, huh?
-Yeah.
I'm just a big softy.
Problem is, most of
our jonin and chunin
are out on other missions.
I don't know who to
give this one to.
-Ah-- ah-- ah-choo!
-I guess someone must
be talking about you.
-No way.
They're all out on missions.
Anyway, isn't that when
your ears are burning?
Hey, who is that guy?
-Whoever he is, he's been
lurking there for a while.
-How am I supposed
to swallow my ramen
with you staring
at me like that?
If you're hungry, go in
there and order some!
-Who said I'm hungry?
[stomach growling]
-Huh?
[slurping]
-It's good, huh?
Another bowl?
-Yeah.
Please.
-Thanks for coming.
And as long as Naruto's
treating, come back any time.
-Oh, brother.
Oh, no, you weren't
hungry at all, were you?
-I'm sorry.
I, uh-- kind of got carried
away there, didn't I?
I really apprec--
-Eh, that's all right.
Don't worry about it.
I was happy to help out.
So anyway, tell
me about yourself.
What's your name?
I take it you're a stranger
around here, right?
-That's right.
I come from the Land of Birds.
My name's Chishima.
I've traveled here with a
mission for the Leaf Village
ninja.
-I hate to say it,
but it takes money
to get a mission like that.
-I just finished paying for
it out of my own pocket.
That's why I'm totally broke.
-Really?
So I guess this mission
must mean a lot to you.
-It could mean the difference
between life and death
for a very dear friend of mine.
-Life and death, huh?
What sort of trouble
is your friend in?
-Sagi and I have been
close since we were little.
We were raised like brothers.
He's now the lord of
the Land of Birds.
-Whoa!
I'm sitting here with
the brother of a lord?
-No.
You misunderstand.
We grew up together,
and our bond
is as strong as
that of brothers.
But I'm merely his friend.
-Oh.
So I guess he's a real
young feudal lord.
-Huh?
Well, anyway, things have been
very hard for my friend Sagi
recently.
First with the death of his
father, Lord Owashi, and then
his twin sister
died shortly after.
And now the friend I once
knew, always smiling,
always cheerful, has become
like a different person.
He won't show his face in the
village, even when I visit him.
This change in him
worries the others,
because Sagi is the
lord of our land.
I don't care about all that.
I'm worried because
he's my friend.
I would do anything to help
him, to bring him back again.
No matter the cost.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Yeah.
That's just the way
I felt about Sasuke.
The way I still feel.
-Just leave everything to me.
After all, that's what
friends are for, right?
-Right.
-I've seen some dirty
tricks in my time,
but this takes the cake!
-Listen, you.
The least you could
do is knock before you
come barging in here.
-Yeah, yeah.
Never mind that.
What do you mean by taking
every cent the poor guy has
and then refusing to
do his mission for him?
-Huh?
-You oughta be ashamed of
yourself, Grandma Tsunade.
You're a big, fat cheat!
-You want to try that again?
NARUTO: Ow!
Never mind!
Sorry!
-I hope I didn't
get him in trouble.
Poor Naruto.
-I wouldn't worry about him.
He may not seem like
it, but he's solid.
You picked a good one
to have on your side.
-Oh.
Thank you.
-Idiot.
Who said I refused his mission?
-I see.
So you weren't cheating him.
You were waiting for Neji to get
back from the mission he's on.
-That's right, you little jerk.
So, Neji is finishing
a mission with Lee.
Meanwhile, find
Tenten and get ready.
You'll be going out with
Neji as squad leader.
Got it?
-Yeah.
-By the way, did
your friend tell you
the details of the mission?
-Well, no.
Not exactly.
-Their land's being haunted.
-I-- what?
-They call it the
cursed warrior.
A ghost wearing white armor that
appears in the dead of night.
Or so they say.
Huh?
-It's nothing.
I just thought
you said something
about a ghost, that's all.
-I did.
What's wrong?
You scared?
-Course not.
What kind of ninja
would I be if I
was scared by stuff like that?
But come to think
of it, will ninjutsu
even work against a ghost?
-Good question.
-Looks like you'll be the
first to find out, Naruto.
-Thanks a lot.
You know, you could have
said something before
about there being
a ghost involved.
-I didn't mention it?
I thought I did.
-No.
I think I would have
remembered that.
But anyway, it's
just a rumor, right?
Has anyone seen it?
-Well, I've never
seen it myself, but--
-I thought so.
-Then again, my master, Lord
Moso, saw it with his own eyes,
so close he could
feel its breath.
-That close, huh?
-The Land of Birds.
That's a long journey.
-Delicious.
Is it all gone?
-You sure eat a lot
for being so skinny.
-I know.
I'm sorry.
Everyone's always wondering
where I put it all.
-OK, so anyway.
Do your people really believe
in this cursed warrior guy?
-Some think it's the
disembodied spirit
of Sagi's father, Lord Owashi.
-I've never liked that
word, disembodied.
-Well.
Forgetting the ghost
for now, why don't you
tell us more of the
history of your land?
The background?
-All right.
It's called the Land of
Birds because our capital
is built on a lake to which the
birds come when they migrate.
It's always been a green
and peaceful place,
made fertile by the waters from
the lake and the many canals.
The first signs of trouble
came with the sudden death
of our previous
leader, Lord Owashi.
As to who would take
over the leadership
it was between his son, Lord
Sagi, and his most trusted
advisor, Lord Komei.
Lord Komei argued
that Sagi was far too
young to assume
the role, and there
were many who agreed with him.
Nevertheless Lord Sagi
was eventually chosen,
largely because Moso--
our high priest,
and my master-- agreed
to act as regent,
advising Sagi and
helping him to govern.
Then, less than a half
a year later, Lady Toki,
Sagi's twin sister, died
as suddenly as his father.
Since that time
the Sagi I knew has
become a completely
different person.
He's retreated from view,
sees no one, governs the land
from within the
confines of his palace.
And it was about that time
that the white warrior
began appearing in the capital.
Rumors started to spread
about Lord Owashi's death,
that it was not a natural one.
People began to say that
the white warrior was
in fact the spirit of
Lord Owashi come back
to Earth to wreak vengeance on
the traitors who murdered him.
-Vengeance.
Great.
-Huh.
I don't believe for one
second this spirit is real.
-Then what do you--
-It sounds like this High
Priest Moso gained the most
from Lord Owashi's death.
-My master is a good
and virtuous man.
He could never be
involved in this.
-Well, what about
that other guy?
-Exactly.
It's Komei, the advisor,
I'm suspicious of.
He could have assassinated
Lord Owashi to gain power,
and then got angry
when it didn't work.
-It's true.
He's been complaining
bitterly ever
since Lord Sagi was
chosen over him.
I wouldn't put it past
him to have manufactured
the cursed warrior himself, and
then started these evil rumors.
-Yeah, exactly.
Now you're talking.
The ghost isn't any ghost at
all, but this Lord Komei guy.
-So the mystery's solved
just like that, eh?
-We've patrolled the
perimeter again, Lord Komei.
Nothing to report.
-Hm.
Very well, then.
Turn in.
-Thank you, sir.
-Hm?
-OK.
How much farther?
-Not much.
Lord Moso's house
is just up ahead.
-Where is he?
-Which way'd he go?
-Where's he gone?
-There!
-Ah!
-He's here!
-Get him!
-Pull him down from there!
-It's the cursed warrior!
-Whoa!
He vanished!
-My Lord Komei,
are you all right?
-Yes.
I'm fine.
Get ahold of yourself.
[whistling]
-What's that sound?
-The thing can fly?
-Clad all in white, with
a helmet and a halberd
in its hand, wearing the
mask of an evil demon
with eyes of fire.
There can be no doubt about it.
That's the cursed warrior.
-Let's go.
-No offense, but I think
I'll move faster on my own.
Wait right here, OK?
While I find out who
this ghost really is.
-Oh.
OK.
-Where is he now?
-He's right up ahead.
-Byakugan.
I don't see him.
-We know he went in there.
-Yes.
But there's no human
presence in that building.
At least, I don't detect the
presence of a living human.
-Huh?
What the heck does that mean?
No, wait a second.
I don't think I want to know.
-Quiet.
I thought I heard
something just now.
[creaking]
-Hello!
Good job, Neji.
I thought you said
nobody was in there?
-Not quite.
I said no living
body was in there.
-OK, I've officially
had enough of this.
-Weighted chains!
-I don't believe in ghosts,
I don't believe in ghosts,
I don't believe in ghosts.
-No, wait!
Naruto!
-Multi-shadow-clone jutsu!
OK!
Na-- ru-- to!
Uzumaki barrage!
Yeah, that did it!
Now to find out who's
behind this little prank.
Huh?
What?
It's empty.
But that can't be.
Unless-- ahh!
It's a real-- live-- ghost!
[music playing]
-So that's your
friend Lord Sagi, huh?
-Ooh, I didn't get a
very good look at him.
But he's kind of cute, isn't he?
-Shh.
I sense something.
-What is it, Neji?
-Murder.
That ghost isn't the
only one after Lord Sagi.
-What do you mean?
Assassins?
-Perhaps.
And they could be shinobi.
So be on your guard, everyone.
-Right.
-Protect Lord Sagi
no matter what.
Next time-- The
Tactician's Intent!
[music playing]