[theme music]
-Kakashi-sensei.
-We've finished our mission
in the Land of Birds.
We're done here.
-What about Naruto?
We just leave him?
-It's all my fault.
I was team leader.
-Sacrifice is an unavoidable
part of the shinobi way.
Now then, let's get back
to the Leaf Village.
-Do you believe they're
really headed back
to their village, Nagare?
-Could be.
-Hm.
The one in the mask who
joined them later worries me.
-If you want me to
follow them, I will.
-No.
Leave that to me.
Go on and report back.
-Right.
-What do you have to report?
-The two younger ones, along
with the tall one in the mask,
have all been seen
crossing the border.
They appear to be headed back
to the Hidden Leaf Village.
-Very good.
And Lord Sagi's taken
care of their companion,
that persistent little pest
who snuck into the palace.
Very good, indeed.
-They've been there
for a half hour.
What are they doing?
-Oh, yummy, yummy.
-That's mine!
-I won!
-Wait a minute.
Of course.
A substitution.
Think you're clever, eh?
Playing me for a fool?
-My Lord Kome.
It's time.
-A verdict has been
reached, Lord Kome.
Betraying your position
as chief tactician
to our late Lord Owashi, you
conspired in his assassination,
as well as the murder of
his daughter, Lady Toki.
Furthermore, you and
your subordinates
were responsible
for manufacturing
the apparition known as the
Cursed Warrior, your purpose
being to spread panic
among our people,
undermine the
authority of Lord Sagi,
and usurp his role as the feudal
lord of the Land of Birds.
You are a traitor.
Lord Kome, you're commanded
to take your own life!
[gasping]
[laughter]
-So that's it, Moso?
I see it all now.
you've sprung your
trap, haven't you?
-I'm disappointed, Kome!
If you're a warrior, then
at least die like one.
Help him to carry
out his sentence.
-My lord.
KOME (VOICEOVER):
So this is the end.
-What?
What's this?
Is this the Hidden Mist Jutsu?
No, wait.
It's something else.
-Never mind the formalities!
Kill him!
-Yes, sir.
Forgive me, Lord Kome.
-Who's there?
-Who is it?
What the-- what the
devil is going on?
CROWD: The Cursed Warrior!
-The Cursed Warrior, huh?
-Yes.
-Quick.
Don't let him get away.
Right.
-I'm going on ahead.
There's something I
need to check out.
You two stay on
his tail, got it?
-Got it.
-So it's all true, then.
-You are in this together.
-No, wait.
Please!
It's you two-- from
the other night.
NARUTO: I'm on to you,
and your so-called ghost!
-Who's back there?
-The jig is up, Kome.
The Curse Warrior is just
one of your flunkies.
Yeah, what do you think of that?
-That night, I was
trying to find out
the true identity of
the Cursed Warrior, too.
I thought I-- that I might
know who it was, you see.
-So let's find out which.
We can solve this right now.
-Let it go.
-Kakashi-sensei.
Where were you?
-I'll explain later.
Go on ahead.
-What?
-Go on.
You're going with them.
-We are?
-Come on, Tenten.
Let's go.
-OK, I'm coming.
-All right.
You can stop following
me and show yourself.
Fine.
If that's the way
you want to play it.
Summoning Jutsu!
-Hey, Kakashi.
What's up?
-I've got a hidden visitor.
Sniff him out, would you?
-Consider it done.
Hey.
You in there.
Hide and seek is over.
You can come out.
[laughter]
-Even I can't fool a dog's nose.
Very clever.
-So to what do I owe this honor?
-What is this secret tunnel for?
Where's it go?
Where's he leading us?
-They say the feudal
lord built passages
such as this all
over the last land
enable him to secretly
slip out of the palace
and observe the daily
lives of his people.
-Then if this cursed
warrior knows about,
he must have some connection
with the feudal lord.
Right?
-Well, we know one thing.
He's no more of a
ghost than I am.
-Whoever he is, I suspect
he'll reveal himself
when the time is right.
-I always thought
it was customary
for you ninja for hire to
go back to your own village
once your mission is complete.
-That's the idea.
But then, we're not so
sure this one is complete.
There's a few too many
suspicious loose ends.
-You stuck your
nose into something
that's none of your business.
If you'd only crawled on
home like a good little dog,
you would have
lived a lot longer.
-Hey, now.
There's no need to
get personal, here.
-Hm?
Gah!
-Whoa!
-Universal Assimilation Jutsu!
-I wasn't finished!
What happened to him?
-His body's taken on
the physical properties
of the rock.
-You've poked around into
our secrets long enough.
Now you pay!
-This guy's tougher than
he seemed at first bite.
-OK, Pakkun, take off.
I'll handle it from here.
-All righty, then.
Later.
-Assimilation, Rock Tank!
I'll crush you!
A shadow clone?
-Sorry.
Missed.
-Huh?
What are you-- a paper bomb!
-All right.
Don't you think
this is far enough?
-Huh?
-Yeah, you're probably right.
We should be in the clear.
-No-- no way!
Naruto?
-I thought as much.
-Then the Cursed Warrior-- it
wasn't Lord Sagi after all?
I-- I know who you are.
Lord Sagi.
It's you in there, isn't it?
When he made no answer, I
thought for sure I was right.
-You're probably all wondering
what I'm doing in this-- ow!
Tenten, what the
heck was that for?
-Let's just say I don't
like being kept in the dark.
And as for you, Neji, how long
have you known in was Naruto?
-I don't know.
For a while.
-Unbelievable!
I was really worried
about you, you know?
-Remember, we had two shinobi
on our tail at the time.
Careful.
Don't react.
-You're right.
We're being followed.
-We're not going home.
We're going back to
the Land of Birds.
Follow my lead.
-Right.
-Understood, Sensei.
-But I thought we shook them
with that Substitution Jutsu.
-We shook off one of them.
But then, when we went in
pursuit of the Cursed Warrior,
a second shinobi
started following us.
-Wonderful.
So I'm the only one
who didn't know.
And I was actually worried.
-So it was you, young
man, and not Lord Sagi.
-That's right.
-I see.
Then-- then that means
Lord Sagi is safe.
-What's wrong?
Are you OK?
-I'm all right.
Just a bit weak.
You see, Moso was quite
persistent in squeezing
a confession out of me.
-Look at you.
Mister, you've been
beat up pretty good.
Why don't we
continue this inside?
We'll explain
everything, Sagi and me.
-Huh?
NAGARE: Assimilation,
Rock Shower!
We are nomadic shinobi.
With no home of our own, we
wander from village to village,
stealing jutsu and adapting
them for our own purposes.
Some jutsu you might
even recognize.
-Darn it.
What now?
Sharingan!
-Assimilation, Sand Coffin!
-That-- that's Gaara's jutsu!
-Assimilation, Sand Funeral!
Heh, heh, heh.
-Sagi, we've got company.
But first, what's the news
on our friend Chishima?
-Recovering well.
His life is not in danger.
He's sleeping now.
He's being looked after in
special quarters in the palace.
-Well, that's good news.
-Did something
happen to Chishima?
-Who was it?
Who did this to him?
-Kome, forgive me for
our misunderstanding.
-My lord, I'm the one
who seeks forgiveness.
-Chishima.
It was he who risked his life
to make me see the truth.
-I was there.
-Now that you know
everything you do,
we cannot let you survive.
You have trespassed on the
land of the feudal palace,
and the punishment
for that is death!
-You're kidding me.
CHISHIMA: Lord Sagi--
-Chishima!
NARUTO: What happened?
Those are shuriken wounds.
-I'll summon a doctor at once.
-Lord Sagi, you must listen.
Your enemy-- the one who
betrayed you-- is Lord Moso!
-You're sure?
-Yes.
Moso's the one who murdered
Lord Owashi, your father,
and your sister, Lady Toki.
He had his assassins use these
shuriken of the palace guard
to commit the crime.
In order to implicate Lord Kome.
I suspect that Lord Kome had
somehow discovered Moso's plan.
-No!
Chishima!
-Lord Sagi, you must hurry.
You've got to call off
Lord Kome's execution.
-He's right.
There's no time to lose.
-No.
That is something I cannot do.
-What do you mean, you can't?
-It would mean
revealing to Lord Moso
that I know the truth about him.
I wouldn't get my revenge.
-You're saying you'd
sacrifice an innocent guy
for the sake of
your stupid revenge?
-I have no choice.
Besides, Lord Kome is guarded
by an army of soldiers.
We could never save
him by anything
less than starting a civil war.
-Not if I go alone.
I could save Lord
Kome by myself.
So, do you have any
problem with that?
-Lord Sagi--
-Do as you please.
-You guys know the rest of it.
I put on the ghost costume
and snatched him away.
-I played the part
of the Cursed Warrior
in hopes of discovering who
was behind the assassinations.
But I achieved
exactly the opposite.
Instead of finding
the real traitor,
understand, I was used by Moso
as a tool to implicate you.
-For my part, I was sure the
apparition I met in my room
was you, so I went to
the abandoned temple
where witnesses had seen
it coming and going.
At the temple, I encountered
the Cursed Warrior again.
-Yes, but that Cursed
Warrior was not me.
It was most likely something
of Moso's devising.
-Exactly.
Probably one of his henchmen.
It was all part of
the old man's trap.
-Moso.
It's clear that
his fiendish plan
was first to dispose
of me, and then
gain control of
the Land of Birds
by disposing of Lord Sagi.
-All the time
playing the good guy.
I can't wait to get
my hands on him!
-No, Naruto.
You've done well.
However, from this
point on, I act alone.
-But-- What do you mean?
-Understand.
I must settle this myself.
Until I've done this, my heart
is as broken as this watch.
We are both stuck
forever in the past.
[theme music]
-What do you mean
this is something
you've gotta settle yourself?
You think you won't get your
revenge unless you do it alone?
Even if you succeed,
what will you accomplish?
Revenge never solved anything.
It won't bring the
dead back to life.
It won't make you feel better.
You'll just end up being
as bad as your enemy.
Do you think your father and
sister will be proud of you
then?
Next time, When
Time Stands Still.
[theme music]