[music playing]
[theme music]
-Come on!
NARUTO: He's late.
Hm.
SAKURA: Naruto!
Just sit down!
-I don't want to.
How come our teacher's
the only one that's late?
I'm ready to roll.
Believe it.
The other group's already
met their new teachers
and took off on some
adventure or something,
and Iruka Sensei's gone, too.
-We know, OK?
Hey!
What are you doing?
[laughing]
Naruto!
-That's what he gets
for coming late.
Surprise!
-You're asking for trouble.
You know you shouldn't do that.
-Psh!
I love stuff like this.
-Huh.
Our teacher's a
Jonin-- an elite ninja.
You think he'd fall for that?
-Yeah.
Sasuke's right.
You're so clueless, Naruto.
[laughing]
-I got him.
He totally fell for it.
[music playing]
-I'm sorry, Sensei.
I told him not to do it,
but he wouldn't listen.
I'd never do anything like that.
-Perfect shot!
-He actually fell
for that cheap trick.
Is this guy really a Jonin?
-Hmm.
How can I put this?
My first impression
of this group-- you're
a bunch of idiots.
[music playing]
NARUTO: "Pass or
Fail-- Survival Test."
KAKASHI: All right.
Why don't you introduce
yourself one at a time?
SAKURA: Introduce ourselves?
Well, what are we
supposed to say?
-Things you like.
Things you hate.
Dreams for the future.
Hobbies.
Things like that.
-Why don't you tell
us stuff first?
I mean, before we talk,
tell us about you,
so we can see how
it's supposed to work.
-Me?
I'm Kakashi Hatake.
Things I like and
things I hate--
I don't feel like
telling you that.
-Huh?
-My dreams for the future--
never really thought about it.
As for my hobbies-- I
have lots of hobbies.
-That was totally useless.
All he really told
us was his name.
-Uh huh.
-OK, your turn.
You on the right-- you first.
-Believe it.
I'm Naruto Uzumaki.
I like instant Ramen
in a cup, and I really
like the Ramen
Iruka Sensei got me
at the [inaudible] noodle shop.
But I hate the three
minutes you have
to wait after you pour the
water in the Ramen cup.
My hobby is eating
different kinds of Ramen
and comparing them.
And my future dream is to
be the greatest Hokage.
Then the whole village
will stop disrespecting me
and start treating me like I'm
somebody-- somebody important.
-(VOICEOVER) Well, he's grown
up in a very interesting way.
All right.
Next.
-I'm Sakura Haruno.
What I like-- uh-- I mean,
the person I like is--
[giggling]
Uh, my hobby is-- uh--
My dream for the future is--
[squealing]
-And?
What do you hate?
-Naruto!
-(VOICEOVER) Girls her age are
more interested in boys than
in ninja training.
Last one.
[giggling]
-My name is Sasuke Uchiha.
I hate a lot of things,
and I don't particularly
like anything.
[gasping]
What I have is not
a dream because I
will make it a reality.
I'm going to restore my clan
and destroy a certain someone.
-(VOICEOVER) Gee.
Uh, I hope he doesn't mean me.
-(VOICEOVER) Sasuke is so hot.
-(VOICEOVER) Just as I thought.
Good.
You're each unique, and
you have your own ideas.
We'll have our first
mission tomorrow
-(HAPPILY) Uh, what kind of
mission are we going to have?
-It's a task the four
of us will do together.
-What?
What?
-A survival exercise.
-Huh?
Survival exercise?
-I thought we were supposed
to have a real mission, not
more practice.
We already did this
stuff at the Academy.
That's how we got here.
KAKASHI: This is not like
your previous training.
-So, uh-- so, uh, what kind
of training is it then?
[laughing]
-Hey, hold on.
That's a normal question.
What's so funny?
-Well, if I tell you the answer,
you're not going to like it.
-Huh?
-Of the 27 graduates
who just came here,
only nine will actually
be accepted as Genin.
The other 18 will be weeded out
and sent back to the Academy.
In other words, this is a make
it or break it-- pass, fail
test, and the chance that
you'll fail is at least 66%.
See?
Didn't I tell you
you wouldn't like it?
-That's crazy!
We worked hard to get here.
Believe it!
What was that graduation
test for anyway?
KAKASHI: Oh, that.
That was just to
select candidates
who might become Genin-- or not.
-(SURPRISED) What?
KAKASHI: That's how it is.
I decide whether
you pass or fail.
Be at the designated
training spot at 5:00 AM,
and bring your ninja gear.
[groaning]
-(VOICEOVER) Well, I'm not
going to be weeded out.
People are going to
look up to me some day.
I've got to pass this test.
Believe it.
-(VOICEOVER) If I fail, I'll
be separated from Sasuke.
This is a trial of love.
-That's it.
You're dismissed.
Oh, tomorrow you better skip
breakfast, or else you'll puke.
[birds chirping]
-(YAWNING) Morning.
[yawning]
-Morning everyone.
Ready for your first day?
-(ANGRILY) Hey!
You're late!
-Well, a black cat
crossed my path,
so I had to take the long way.
[growling]
Well.
[clearing throat]
Let's get started.
-Huh?
KAKASHI: Here we go.
It's set for noon.
-Huh?
-Your assignment is very simple.
You just have to take
these bells from me.
That's all there is to it.
[bells ringing]
If you can't get them by
noon, you go without lunch.
[naruto screaming]
You'll be tied to
those posts, and you'll
watch while I eat my
lunch in front of you.
-(VOICEOVER) So that's why.
-(VOICEOVER) He told us not to
eat breakfast to make it harder
on us.
Wait a minute!
There's three of us.
How come there's only two bells?
[laughing]
-Well, that way, at least one of
you will end up tied to a post
and ultimately
disqualified for failing
to complete the mission.
That one goes back
to the Academy.
[growling]
Then again, all three of
you could flunk out, too.
You can use any weapons,
including shuriken.
If you're not
prepared to kill me,
you won't be able
to take the bells.
-Those weapons are
too dangerous, Sensei.
[laughing]
-Especially since you couldn't
even dodge that eraser.
-Class clowns are usually
the weakest links.
You can safely ignore them--
lowest scores, losers.
[groaning]
When I say start, you can begin.
[growling]
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): Losers.
Losers.
[groaning]
[gasping]
-Don't be in such a hurry.
I didn't say start yet.
[groaning]
-(VOICEOVER) He's so fast,
I didn't even see it.
-(VOICEOVER) So this is a Jonin.
-But you came at me with the
full intention of destroying
me, so--
[groaning]
How can I say this?
I'm actually starting
to like you guys.
Get ready.
And-- start.
-Iruka, what did you
wish to see me about?
I don't think you
came here merely
to drink tea with me
and chat, did you?
-Naruto's been assigned
to Squad Seven.
The Jonin in charge
of that group--
just how tough a trainer is he?
-Kakashi, you mean.
You are concerned about him?
-I am.
I heard a rumor about
his training methods.
-Hm.
-What's this?
-All the trainees who've
ever been assigned to him--
those who passed and
those who failed.
[gasping]
-May I?
Huh?
Huh.
This-- this is--
KAKASHI: Ninja must know how
to conceal their movements
and hide effectively.
[music playing]
Well, they understand that much.
They've hidden well.
Huh?
-You and me!
Right now!
Fair and square!
Let's go!
-Hm?
-Fool.
-You know, compared
to the others,
you're a little bit weird.
-Oh yeah?
The only thing weird
here is your haircut.
[yelling]
-Shinobi battle
techniques, part one.
Taijutsu-- the physical art.
-Uh!
(VOICEOVER) Taijutsu--
that's hand-to-hand combat!
Then why is he
reaching for a weapon?
-Huh.
-What the?
-What are you waiting for?
Make your move.
-But-- I mean, why are
you reading that book?
-Why?
To find out what happens
in the story, of course.
Don't let it bother you.
With your weak attacks,
it doesn't really
matter if I'm
reading or whatever.
[growling]
-(ANGRILY) I'm
going to crush you!
[yelling]
[groaning]
Now you're mine!
Huh?
-Don't let your enemy get
behind you all the time.
[gasping]
-(VOICEOVER) A hand sign
to focus his chakra.
Is that the sign of the tiger?
That's dangerous!
He could destroy
Naruto with that.
-(VOICEOVER) That hand
sign is for a fire jutsu.
He's not just
toying with Naruto.
He's going to demolish him.
-(YELLING) Naruto!
Get out of there quick!
He's going to destroy you!
-Too late.
[gasping]
Leaf Village,
secret finger jutsu!
-(YELLING) No!
[thumping]
[groaning]
-A thousand years of death!
-That wasn't a hand sign at all.
He just poked him.
-Those two are
just total idiots.
[music playing]
-OK, where was I?
-(VOICEOVER) That must
be against the rules.
He's a Jonin.
We can't possibly
match his strength.
[gurgling]
-(VOICEOVER) I'm not going
to let it end like this.
[groaning]
I'll attack from the water.
Now!
[gasping]
IRUKA: It can't be.
This is even worse
than the rumors.
MAN: Kakashi's test may be a bit
more difficult than the others.
-A bit more difficult?
Not a single student has
ever passed his test.
-That's true.
They all tried,
but not one of them
could live up to
Kakashi's standards.
So they were all eliminated.
[gasping]
-What are you doing now?
You know, you won't get lunch
unless you take a bell by noon.
-(ANGRILY) I know.
I know.
You told us already!
KAKASHI: You look pretty
wobbly for someone
who's going to
surpass the Hokage.
[stomach growling]
-(ANGRILY) You told us
not to eat breakfast!
How can I fight when
I'm starving to death?
[stomach growling]
-(VOICEOVER) Breakfast?
I didn't even have
dinner last night.
Really bad idea to go on a diet.
-So, you caught me off guard.
That's all it was.
Believe it.
I'm so hungry I don't
have any strength.
But I can't let that stop me.
I've got to get one of
those bells no matter what.
I'll find the strength somehow.
Believe it.
I'm going to pass
this test, and I'm not
going back to the Academy.
I will become a ninja!
-Hm.
[laughing]
-(YELLING) You're
overconfident, Sensei.
That's why you weren't ready for
a shadow clone attack-- my best
jutsu.
-(VOICEOVER) Seven Narutos?
What?
They're not images.
They're real.
How could he do that?
-Hm.
[yelling]
It look like the
stories are true.
He can create shadow clones.
-If you ever lay a hand on
my sensei, I'll kill you.
-Show me what you can
do, nine-tail fox!
-(VOICEOVER) Those
aren't just illusions.
They're solid clones.
He's mastered an
extremely advanced jutsu.
-(VOICEOVER) It's
a forbidden skill,
and he defeated Mizuki with it.
Great technique.
But I don't think you can
maintain it for very long.
You talk like you're
the best, Naruto,
but you're still
the worst student.
You can't beat me
with this jutsu.
[bell ringing]
(VOICEOVER) What?
He got me from behind.
Huh?
-Oh.
[laughing]
-Didn't you say don't let
your enemies get behind you?
Good advice, Sensei.
Believe it.
I had one of my clones
come out of the river,
then sneak up behind
you super quiet.
Now, this is for nailing
me in the butt earlier!
-(VOICEOVER) When did
Naruto get so cool?
-(VOICEOVER) A
diversionary tactic , nice.
[yelling]
-You're mine, and
so are those bells!
[groaning]
-Huh?
SAKURA: He's holding himself.
Naruto punched Naruto.
[groaning]
-Ouch!
It's you!
You're Kakashi
Sensei, aren't you?
You transformed into
me using a jutsu!
You are!
You're Kakashi Sensei!
Believe it.
You smell like an old
man, you must be him!
No, you are!
You're Kakashi Sensei!
Hey!
Let's undo the jutsu!
Yeah, that's it!
Believe it.
Then there will just be two of
us, so we'll know who's who.
Should have thought
of that sooner, fool.
You're the jerk.
Why didn't you think of it?
Just undo the jutsu!
Ow.
-(VOICEOVER) Naruto,
you are so not cool.
-(VOICEOVER) He got you
with a replacement jutsu.
Loser.
With this jutsu, you
quickly switch your own body
with an object, so
your enemy thinks
he's attacking you when he's
actually attacking a log
or rock, leaving him
open to a counterattack.
In this case, the Jonin let
himself get caught, then
switched bodies with one
of the Naruto clones.
So Naruto thought
he was nailing him,
but actually he was
just attacking himself.
And that Jonin was
so smooth, he made
Naruto look like a total moron.
[groaning]
-Hm?
A bell?
I must have got to
him with my attack.
He dropped a bell!
[laughing]
[screaming]
Hey!
Let me down!
What is this?
-(VOICEOVER) Of
course it was a trap.
NARUTO: Help!
[groaning]
Somebody!
-(VOICEOVER) That Jonin doesn't
let down his guard even when
he's fighting a
fool like Naruto.
NARUTO: Help!
Come on!
The bell!
[groaning]
[sighing]
-Think before you use a
jutsu, or else your opponent
might use it against you.
[groaning]
Oh, and also, if the bait
is obvious, don't take it.
[groaning]
A ninja must see
through deception.
-(ANGRILY) I get it!
-I'm telling you this
because you don't get it.
You think you get
it, which is not
the same as actually getting it.
Get it?
-(VOICEOVER) This is my chance.
He finally dropped his guard!
-Won't you ever learn?
[yelling]
[gasping]
-He just got
blasted by shuriken!
Are you out of
your mind, Sasuke?
You went too far!
[music playing]
[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Man, at this rate,
there's no way I can
beat Kakashi Sensei.
But if I don't get a
bell, I fail the test,
and that is not an option.
He keeps saying see
through deception,
which I would do if I had any
idea what he was talking about,
but I don't.
So how do I get my hands
on one of those bells?
Next time-- "You Failed!
Kakashi's Final Decision."
It might look bad, but
don't count me out!