[theme music]
-Which way?
How do we get out?
-This way!
I think I can smell the sea!
-Ugh, we're so close!
-No sweat, I'll fire up my
Razen gun and blast us out!
-No way!
You're liable to bring the whole
mountain down on our heads!
-OK, fine.
You got any better ideas?
-Watch out.
Everybody stand back!
-Ah, fresh air!
What a relief!
-Uncle Sensei,
are you all right?
-Let's go.
There's no time to waste.
It's already morning.
-Oh, right!
-The fleet is
sailing into a trap!
-Yeah, we've gotta reach'em
before it's too late!
-Hey!
How about that boat?
-Right!
Get on board.
-Still no word from
the Leaf Ninja?
They were expected to
accompany the fleet into port.
What could've happened to them?
-Yeah
-Captain!
Sir, we just received this!
-Hmm-- Well, well, we were
wrong to have ever doubted them.
They drove the demon of the
ocean out of these waters
last night!
Ohh!
Wonderful!
At last, we know the
fleet will be safe, sir.
-All hands, hoist the
anchor and make sail!
Let's put to sea!
[sounds of seagulls]
-Be sure to steer
clear of the reef!
-Huh?
I don't see a fleet in the
harbor, or any ships at all!
-There's only one
reason they ever
would have left without us.
It's Hamachi.
He laid a trap, and
they fell for it.
-(ON RADIO) Captain Hitone!
-What's the matter?
-There's something down
there-- below the ship.
It's aaaagh!
-The reef!
Hard to port.
-Yes, sir.
-It can't be!
-I said hard to port!
-She's not responding, sir.
-What are you talking about?
Can't watch it.
It's no use.
We're gonna hit.
All hands brace for impact!
-Must be the demon's doing.
-[evil laughter]
-Thank you for
delivering the fleet.
But what's going on here?
Who are you?
And what do you want?
-This fleet and in its cargo.
Hand it over peacefully,
and I'll spare your life.
-You're outta your mind!
-Aaah!
Ugh!
-Ehhh Aaaah!
-It's a monster!
-A demon of the ocean!
-Aaaah!
-Demon illusion, fire jutsu!
-Ah!
What is that?
-It's coming right at us!
[screaming]
[evil laughter]
-Now, finish them off, will you?
-Whoa!
-Ugh!
-I'm the one you
have to face now.
-It's all right!
I've got you.
Hang on!
-Man, that's really low,
even by your standards.
Weirdo.
Glad you showed up.
I've still got a few
questions I want answered.
-Mmm
-Isaribi, what are you doing?
Don't you understand by now?
Keep acting like this, and
you really will be a monster!
-Isaribi, get him!
-I'm the one you've
gotta worry about.
You said Orochimatu left
the research lab weeks ago.
Isn't that right?
Any clue where he's been since?
-I have no idea.
I know he took a young kid with
him, an excellent prospect,
he said.
This kid isn't going to be a
disappointment, like you were.
-Saskarachia.
-You just didn't quite have it.
Guess that's why he
tossed you aside.
Isaribi!
Oh!
Jenaclo jutsu!
Isaribia what do I have to
do so-- so you'll understand.
You're putting people's
lives in jeopardy.
Isaribi, don't you
care about them at all?
-Since you asked, no.
-Huh?
-See, their lives
mean nothing to me.
Yours means nothing to me.
-You know that's a lie!
-Do you think I
care who gets hurt?
Who drowns?
-There's only one
thing I care about,
and that's being returned
to the way I was!
It's about time
somebody woke you up!
Believe me, I know.
I know just how
painful it can be.
But still, that doesn't make
it right to hurt others!
-You saved my life!
Have you forgotten that?
You have a good heart, Isaribi.
You do care!
-Heh, not bad for
a medical ninja.
-So glad you approve.
-You're losing your focus.
That is a mistake!
-Now, I've done it!
-Ha!
Someone was a little
overconfident.
-You're useless!
What the devil's taking so long?
-Hamachi
-He's only a kid.
How hard could it be
to finish him off?
-I'm sorry.
It's just--
-Be quiet!
I'll do it.
-That suits me fine, because
you're the real monster.
It'll be a pleasure
walloping you!
-What did you call me?
A monster?
-Yeah, you hear right!
Anyone who could cause
so much destruction
and laugh it off like it was
nothing-- don't fool yourself!
You're a monster in human skin!
What's so funny, now?
-You've seen right through
me, but no half monster
like Isaribi.
I'm the complete package.
-Huh?
-You wanna see?
-I am the fully-refined model,
perfected for mortal combat.
-Why, you--!
-But Hamachi--
-Out of the way!
I don't have any more
need for a guinea pig.
-Whataya think you're doin'?
Just leave her alone!
-We were planning
to dissect her,
and harvest her organs
for experiments.
But then we took pity on
her, and let her live.
And what did we get for our
trouble, but incompetence
and ingratitude!
What's the matter?
Feeling nervous?
-Grrrrr!
You wish!
Calling you a monster's
giving you too much credit!
Mister, you're so disgusting,
you make pond scum look good!
-Ha!
How impolite.
Come here, and say that!
-You bet I will!
-So long!
-Heh, that all you've got?
-Not even close!
-Multi-jenaclo jutsu!
-It doesn't matter how
many you throw at me!
-What's this?
Done already?
Nah, give it another try.
-Yeah, you'd better believe it!
And until you turn Isaribi back,
I'm gonna keep comin' at ya
again and again, and again!
-Water-style great
cannonball jutsu!
-So whataya say?
Had enough?
Come on, already.
Give it up, kid!
-I already told you-- until
you make Isaribi human again,
I'm never gonna give up!
I'll keep comin' at
you over and over!
-For me?
You'd do that for my sake?
-I'm getting a little
bored of this farce.
Come!
Sea monster!
Sea monster, finish him off!
-Hey!
Hey, whataya--?
-The Sea Monster body
consists entirely of water.
It's almost like a moving
water prison jutsu.
-I've gotta do something.
Haaaa!
Ugh!
Didn't work.
-Of course, not.
Did you really think it would?
Finish them off, Isaribi!
That's right, I'll give
you another chance.
Go on!
Don't you want to
be human again?
What's the matter?
You know I'm the only one
who can turn you back.
Well then, go on, do as I say.
NARUTO: It's no good.
It won't make it right.
Don't do it, Isaribi.
Please don't go there into
that world-- into the darkness.
-Aaaaaah!
Aaaaaah!
-What's happening?
What type of chakra is that?
No, it's not possible!
-Aah!
Aaaah!
-Grrrrr!
No!
There's no way!
I'm not gonna let
you take her there.
Y'got that?
-He's transformed, somehow.
But into what?
Aaaaaaaaaah!
-Naruto!
-That's right, he's
the same as you.
What are you talking
about-- the same as me?
-Yeah, Naruto carries
inside him the spirit
of the nine-tailed fox that
almost destroyed our village.
Ever since he was
a child, people
have treated him like
a monster, and a freak.
That's why he works and fights
twice as hard as anyone.
Every day's a struggle,
just to be accepted
by the world as a human being.
Believe me, I know.
I know just how
painful it can be.
But still, that doesn't make
it right to hurt others!
-What he told me--
it's completely true.
I see what he meant.
-Grrrr!
-No!
Naruto,no!
[gasps]
-You're gonna be sorry!
[theme music]
-All right, I did it!
I summoned the big toad!
-Oh!
-Get ready, you
slimy sack o'guts!
'Cause we've got a
fight on our hands!
-What have you got, you little--
-Aw, what is it?
Don't tell me you're scared!
-Scared?
Of course, not!
-Y'got more important things
to do than save lives?
What's wrong with you?
-Shut up!
It's this salt water,
you knucklehead!
It itches like crazy!
-Oh, sorry.
Next time!
Battle at Sea!
The Power Unleashed!
[theme music]