[theme music]
-Ah?
-Your jutsu's worn off.
Now I am at 100%.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): Blood.
-Lady Tsunade!
-I don't get it.
What's going on?
I'm confused.
Did I miss out on something?
How come Kabuto and Grandma
Tsunade are mixing it up?
-If you want your answer,
just look at his headband.
He serves Orochimaru.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Attack!
Fury of the Rasengan!
-So that's Orochimaru.
-You take four-eyes.
Kay, Shizune?
I can handle our
friend, Orochimaru.
There's just one thing.
I need Tsunade to do
something about my body
before we get started here.
-It may be a while before
the full effects of that drug
completely leave your system.
I'm very sorry, but it can't
be helped, Master Jiraiya.
-What?
You gotta be kidding!
Oh, well.
What can you do, right?
I'll just have to
face him as I am.
Tsunade, use your recovery
ninjitsu and rest.
-What about me?
What should I do?
-Don't do anything.
You just stand guard over
Tsunade with the pig, OK?
-Oink.
-Come on, I want
to fight this guy.
He's gotta pay for what he did.
-Forget about it!
That jerk with the
glasses is right.
You're in over your head.
Our opponent's
one of the Sannin,
like me, and the man who
killed the Third Hokage.
This is an eye for an eye.
I'm the only one who
can fight Orochimaru.
And four-eyes over there could
go toe to toe with Kakashi
if he had to.
-Don't worry.
Not a problem.
Shadow Clone--
-Hold on, Naruto.
Your clones won't work here.
You needn't bother.
There isn't any point.
-What?
-It wouldn't even
be a diversion.
You'd be wasting your chakra.
They're a dangerous pair.
Now, then, how about we
get this thing started?
-Summoning Jutsu!
-What's up?
-What the-- why are you here?
Where the hell's your father?
-Hey, hey!
Long time no see.
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER):
Master Jiraiya
can't build up enough
chakra because of the drug.
[laughter]
-Well, Jiraiya, still
playing the fool, I see.
You always were ridiculous.
But this time you've
outdone yourself.
Clearly our Tsunade has
gotten to you somehow.
-Your jutsu did
require a sacrifice.
Perhaps she was thinking ahead.
Drugging him somehow
to suppress his power.
-To think she would make
a sacrifice of Jiraiya.
Well, just as ruthless as
ever, aren't you, Tsunade?
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER): Well,
how do you like that?
He's already
spotted my weakness.
[laughter]
-You're as big a disgrace
as the day we met.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): That's it!
I'm not going to let that guy
sand there and mock Pervy Sage!
Summoning Jutsu!
OROCHIMARU: That's the
Nine-Tails brat from the Chunin
exam.
I suppose I should have killed
him when I had the opportunity.
For the sake of the
Akatsuki and their goals,
I let the boy slip by.
But the only ones ever capable
of breaking a five pronged seal
were the Third Hokage and
we of the legendary Sannin.
-That may be, but Jiraiya
is training the boy.
-You could be right.
If he's learned to wield
the power of the Nine-Tails,
it's not impossible.
-Wait a minute.
It's--
-But that doesn't
appear to be the case.
-He never had any skill as
a shinobi to begin with.
-What happened?
[sigh]
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER): He's
still got a long way to go.
-Where the heck did I go wrong?
-Hi, everybody.
Hey, friend.
How are ya?
-Hey, Gamatatsu.
Why did you pop out?
Where's the old man?
-Ah.
Gamakichi, what's going on?
This is the first time
anyone's ever summoned me.
I'm finally getting
a chance to shine.
-You dummy.
Get some munchies and go find
a place to hide, will ya?
GAMATATSU: Wait,
they got snacks here?
Gee whiz, this is the coolest.
-Let's begin.
I want you to leave
Jiraiya to me.
The rest are yours to
play with as you will.
-Now, that is a shame.
I'd been hoping
to test my mettle
against one of the Sannin!
-Naruto!
OROCHIMARU: You're dealing
with me, old friend!
-No problem.
Earth Style, Dark Swamp!
Great.
This bog is way too small.
It's not deep
enough to sink 'em.
(VOICEOVER) The drug
hasn't run its course yet.
It's not a total loss, though.
These snakes aren't going
anywhere in this state.
-Ninja Art, Poison Fog!
KABUTO (VOICEOVER): One breath
of this, and I'm a dead man.
-My leg tendons--
-I am not lettin' you
eat me a second time!
-Get ready.
-Ninja Art, Needle Jizo!
Blast-- the jutsu
isn't strong enough.
-Even if we are
both impaired, you
haven't a chance of beating me.
You might as well
give up already.
-What a tragedy.
I had only the utmost
respect for you
as a fellow medical ninja.
-Stay back!
Get away from me!
-Please, get a hold of
yourself, Lady Tsunade.
Else the name of
Sannin, of which
Lord Orochimaru is
counted, weep for shame.
[screaming]
-Can't move.
My body's too heavy.
-Look at you.
They used to call
you the town mad man.
And now you're plodding along
dutifully for the village,
with this brat in tow.
You've really fallen
off, haven't you?
Trust me, I've always
had a good eye for talen.
With that one, all I see
is insipid mediocrity.
-You hit the nail on my head.
What would I want
with the Uchiha kid?
Tell me, where's the fun
in teaching a boy who's
already a genius to begin with?
-How touching.
You're drawn to him because he
reminds you of your old self.
Is that it?
That brat of yours
could never beat
Uchiha, born as he was into
the shinobi art of Sharingan.
Without Sharingan,
poor Naruto hasn't
a chance of srpassing him.
A shinobi's strength
rests upon his ability
to obtain and master all
the jutsu of this world.
The very reason we
are called ninja
is because of the many
ninjutsu arts that we wield.
-Hmph.
You're wrong.
That's not what makes a shinobi.
You never did get it.
A real ninja is one
who endorse, no matter
what gets thrown at him.
-A difference of
opinion, I suppose.
-Let me explain
something to you.
There's only one thing that
matters if you're a shinobi,
and it isn't the number
of jutsu you possess.
All you do need is the
guts to never give up.
-Back off!
That's enough,
already, you traitor!
[shout]
-The guts to never give up.
And the kid has
got that in spades.
-Ah!
KABUTO (VOICEOVER): I don't
know what jutsu you learned,
but you'll need to be
more subtle than that
if you want to hit me.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): It's no use.
I'm not gonna be able
to hit a moving target.
Darn it.
And I still can't hold
in all the chakra yet.
-It looks like you fractioned
the thigh bone in your left leg
during your little
tussle with the serpent.
If it were only the bone,
you could still move.
But it's beyond that now.
I've severed the lateral vastus
muscle in your right leg,
as well.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
What do I do?
This jutsu takes two hands.
If he gets even one
of my arms, it's over!
-What's the matter?
Are you frightened?
Hope you don't feel
like running away.
Naruto, as I remember, you
were nothing but big talk
during that first Chunin exam.
-Don't underestimate me!
I don't quit, and I don't run!
-Don't underestimate me.
I don't run away.
I don't care if I'm a
Genin the rest of my life.
You guys aren't going
to scare me off.
I'll still be Hokage someday.
So, where's all
your big talk now?
-It's because I'm like
you, that's my goal.
Just watch.
Someday I'll be Hokage.
To be Hokage.
That's my dream.
-You're not a kid anymore.
You don't want to shoot
your mouth off like that.
Admit when you're
in over your head.
Sometimes it's
better to run away.
Come, now.
What's the matter?
Why such a look?
If I kill you, you can
kiss your dreams goodbye.
-You're always so reckless.
You want to kill yourself?
You're still a Genin, so if
there's ever a real battle,
you get out of there, fast.
-Are you crazy?
I'm never gonna run away!
KABUTO: Little kids
think life is so easy.
That's why they're always going
on and on about their dreams.
That's why they never give up.
-Jiraiya.
What were you thinking?
You went and taught
this kid the Rasengan?
What's the point of
teaching it to someone
who can never master it?
Giving him false
hopes like that.
Filling his head
with stupid ideas.
Making him think he can
actually be Hokage someday.
[thudding]
-They go chasing after some
stupid dream, and they die.
-Give me just three days, and
I'll have that jutsu down flat!
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER):
Care to make a bet on it?
-That's eno I'm
not gonna run away.
I never go back on my word!
That's my nindo.
My ninja way!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): A bet?
TSUANDE (VOICEOVER):
I'll give you one week.
If you can master that jutsu
by then, I'll admit I'm wrong,
and that you're worthy
of becoming Hokage.
I'll even throw in my necklace.
-You should have stayed
out of this, Naruto.
Why do you-- What are you doing?
-All right, Grandma.
-Still haven't had enough?
-Get ready to pay up on our bet.
That cursed necklace of
yours is about to be mine.
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): Shadow
clones can't help him here.
Enough!
Naruto, you don't
have to protect me!
Stop, already!
-I warned you not
to be stubborn.
Now you die!
You've just thrown it all away!
Dreams don't come
true when you're dead!
-Just get out of
the way, Naruto!
No!
Look out!
-Don't you worry about me.
Until I become Hokage, I
don't care what happens.
I am not going to die!
OK.
Let's see you
dodge me this time.
Here goes!
-He's channeling chakra
again, like before.
No!
This is different!
-Now I see.
He made the clone to
gather up his chakra.
Ingenious.
-Compress the chakra.
Keep it going.
-That's impossible!
-Rasengan!
[scream]
[theme music]
TSUNADE: I have never
forgotten the sacrifices made
to protect the
Hidden Leaf Village,
and keep its people safe.
Each and every Hokage
laid down his life
in service of this dream.
From this day forward, I
put my life on the line.
From this day forward,
I am the Fifth Hokage.
NARUTO: Next time,
The Fifth Hokage!
The Life On the Line!
[theme music]