[music playing]
-Akamaru trembles--
Gaara's cruel strength!
[screaming]
-Huh?
-The grass ninja.
Everybody hide!
[music playing]
-Quick!
Get down!
That ninja-- where
could she be hiding?
-Naruto?
-Ugh.
It's about time the
lazy fool woke up.
[grunts]
-You really are one of a kind.
That's for sure.
And I mean you're the kind
that gets on my nerves.
-Mmhmm.
[groans]
-Oh no!
Sakura!
Sak-- Sakura!
Something happened here.
I mean something serious
happened to your--
to your hair!
-Oh.
That's all.
I just wanted to change my look.
I like it better
long, but when I'm out
in the wilderness like this, and
I'm moving around all the time,
it gets in the way too much.
-Hmm.
So what's your story?
Why are you guys here
in the first place?
What's going on around here?
[sighs]
-Explaining everything to you
is going to be such a pain.
-Everyone just
showed up to help.
-What?
-Sakura's sure putting
on a great face.
-Huh?
-I'll take care of him now, Ino.
-Uh.
OK.
-Come on, Lee!
Pull it together!
Snap out of it already, alright?
[groans]
[music playing]
-Tenten, is that you?
What are you doing here?
-I came to help you
out- what do you think?
-Wha?
Where are those
sound ninja guys?
-Sashin took care of them.
Don't worry about it, Lee.
-Really?
-Just what were you
thinking rushing in there
all by yourself?
Look at you--
you're a total mess.
-Well, Sakura was in trouble,
so I had to do something, right?
-He's gotta be kidding.
He had to know he didn't
stand a chance alone
against all those guys.
-That was pretty darn
stupid, don't you think?
-Well, I guess I cannot
really argue with that.
-Ah ha!
I know you, Bushy Brow!
-(ANGRILY) Hey!
Knock it off!
You better not say
anything bad about Lee!
[yells]
-What in the world happened
while I was asleep?
Everything's gone crazy.
[groans]
-The Naruto is completely
out of the loop.
-So far out of the
loop, he doesn't even
know there is a loop.
He's not going to be the
hero of this little story.
-Lee,
-Huh?
-Thank you.
Because of you, I was able
to stand up for myself,
and I've become a
little stronger.
[whimpers]
-Thank you, Sakura.
But I guess my efforts
alone were not good enough.
-So, Sasuke, you are as
good as your reputation.
Just what you would expect
from the Uchiha clan.
To chase off those
ninja, you must
be very strong-- not like me.
I just got beaten to a pulp.
[music playing]
-What's he talking
about, beaten to a pulp?
Is he serious?
Are those guys
really that strong?
-Sakura, the lotus of the
Leaf Village blooms twice.
-Huh?
[music playing]
-When we meet again I will
have become a stronger ninja,
I promise.
-Uh.
[giggles]
[groans]
-Hey, Sakura, come on over here!
I wanna fix your
hair for you, OK?
-Yeah.
I'd like that.
[cutting sound]
-(ANGRILY) Why, you
sneaky little troll.
Hugging him like that.
Billboard Brow.
-(ANGRILY) Haven't you heard the
expression all's fair in love
and war?
Little Ino pig.
-Sasuke Uchiha.
[wind blowing]
-He's a stronger opponent
than I could have imagined.
[dog whimpering]
-Hey, Akamaru, you OK?
-Is he still shaking?
He's been at it for
half a day already.
-Akamaru.
-I don't blame him--
not after what happened.
It's because of what he saw.
-I know we'll be the ones who
survive this, right Akamaru?
-Of course, it's lucky for
us that the people caught
in that trap had
an earth scroll.
And now we're going to be the
first ones to reach the tower.
-Don't get overconfident.
That's a dangerous
mistake to make.
No matter how small
a bug is, it still
has to guard itself
at all times.
We have to make sure that we
don't encounter any enemies.
That's the only way to be safe.
Yeah, I know that, Shino.
But as usual, you gotta say
it in a weird, vague way.
Bug nerd.
[grunt]
-Yeah.
But Kiba, what Shino said--
he does kind of have a point,
you know?
-Yeah, I know.
Just come on.
-I sure hope that
nothing's happened
to [inaudible] out here.
-Hold on, guys.
We have to stop.
-Why?
-We're being careful not to
counter any enemies, right?
All right, Inara, I
want you to check out
a kilometer ahead
in that direction.
[gulps]
-Here goes.
Byakugan!
Yes.
There's somebody
there, all right.
-It sounds like there
are six people there.
-All right, let's check it out.
[gasp]
-Kiba, what are
you talking about?
We're not going to do that.
-Why not?
The test administrators
said that we
had to get both a heaven
and an earth scroll, right?
But she didn't say we
couldn't take more than that.
If we get more scrolls, there
will be fewer to go around,
and that means other teams will
be cut out of the competition.
[laughs]
-But--
-Look, first we'll
just check it out, OK.
If it looks too dangerous,
we won't battle them.
Now, come on.
Let's go.
[gasps]
-He's the kind of guy that
even the hungriest insects
would avoid.
[dog whimpers]
-What's wrong, Akamaru?
-What happened?
You just stopped
all of a sudden.
-Yeah.
Something just spooked
the little guy.
-What scared him?
-I have no idea.
Akamaru has the
ability to sniff out
the level of an enemy's
chakra, but man, I've
never seen him this
scared by it before.
Whoever those ninja up ahead
are, they aren't normal guys.
[eerie music playing]
-Do you believe the nerve
of these Sand Village ninja
Shigure challenging us head-on?
-Yeah.
They're a bunch of fools.
-What's he thinking?
That guy's way
too little to take
on an opponent who's that big.
[dog whimpers]
[gasp]
-What did Akamaru say?
-That that big guy--
he is big trouble.
-They all look like
they're bad news to me,
like they're really strong.
-Too bad, kids.
You should have picked
your opponents better.
Now you're all going to die.
-I've heard enough out of you.
Let's make this quick.
I don't want to waste
time on this guy.
-We don't even know which
scroll these guys have.
-Hey Gaara, doesn't it make
more sense to follow these punks
and gather information first?
I mean, if they have the
same type of scroll as us,
we're just fighting
an unnecessary battle.
-I don't care.
[grunts]
-They looked at me the wrong
way, so they're going to die.
[gasp]
-This is exactly
why I didn't want
to be stuck in the
forest with him.
[clears throat]
-If you think you can
kill us, then try it.
[music playing]
[zoom]
-Huh?
-And now, ninja art,
Senbon rainstorm!
[wind blowing]
-(SCARED) A
rainstorm of needles!
[groans]
-Up, down, left, right--
no matter where you go,
I can get you.
There's no blind
spot in this jutsu,
and it's deadly accurate.
-Ha!
Child's play.
-Is that all you can do?
-It can't be.
Not one wound.
Impossible.
All right.
[needles flying through air]
-A Senbon rainstorm, huh?
I have an idea-- let's
make it rain blood instead.
[music playing]
[moans]
-Man, his chakra's so powerful.
And that sand.
Do you smell that odor?
It stinks.
-Odor?
-It smells like blood.
-He's created a wall of sand.
-That's right.
It's a defense, and
nothing can get through it.
He carries around all
that sand in the gourd
that he has on his back,
and when he's attacked,
he uses the power of his
chakra to harden the sand.
It's a jutsu that
only Gaara can do,
and somehow it
happens automatically,
independent of his will,
so any attacks against him
are doomed to fail.
-Yeah?
Well, we'll see.
-Just face it.
You guys can't hope
to defeat Gaara.
[snorts]
-Give me a break.
[slam]
-And that punk's a dead man.
-We warned him not
to fight Gaara.
-Saiyan's coffin.
[grunts]
[music playing]
-I can't move.
[gasps]
-Let-- Let me go.
-All I have to do is cover your
big mouth, and you'll be dead.
But that would be too
easy and too boring.
[grunting]
-Sand burial.
[screams]
[grunts]
[gasps]
-There wasn't any pain.
I crushed him with more
force than necessary,
so it was over quickly.
The corpse's bitter,
crimson tears
flow and mingle with
the endless sand,
feeding the chaos within
me, and making me stronger.
[whimpers]
-Just take the scroll.
Go on.
Here.
Just take it.
Please spare us.
[screams]
-Man, this is bad.
We gotta get out of here,
before he finds and kills us.
-We got lucky-- it's
a heaven scroll.
All right.
Now let's head to the tower.
-Just shut up.
-Huh?
-It's not-- it's still
not enough for me.
[music playing]
-Oh no, did he see us?
If he did, we're done for.
-Come on, Gaara.
Let's go.
-What, are you scared?
Coward.
-Huh?
-Look, Gaara, I know this
test is no problem for you,
but it's dangerous
for Temari and me.
One set of scrolls
is good enough--
it's all we need to pass.
-Losers.
Can't tell me what to do.
-All right, that's enough.
Sometimes you have to listen
to what your big brother says.
-It's too bad I don't think of
you as my big brother, at all.
If you get in my
way, I'll kill you.
-Wait.
Just hold on, Gaara.
You don't have to treat
us like we're the enemy.
Look, do it as a favor
for your sister, please?
[gasps]
[sand blowing]
-Oh no.
-(SCARED) Gaara!
-All right.
This time.
[sighs]
-Yeah.
That's why I hate brats.
[dog whimpers]
[heavy breathing]
-Well, I guess now we know
why you were so freaked out.
I just wish you would have
said something sooner.
-No one's here.
-(TRIUMPHANTLY) Ha ha!
We're the first.
-No.
I'm sure that I sent someone
here a little while ago.
-More importantly,
is Akamaru OK?
The poor little guy's been
so scared for so long.
-Come to think of it, what
did Akamaru say before?
-Well, I guess he must have
been saying that that bigger
ninja was in trouble because
that little pipsqueak was
going to kill him.
[gasps]
-Just like I thought,
there's no other place to go.
-We've already
waited half a day--
how much longer are they
going to make us wait?
[eerie music playing]
-Hmm?
[gasps]
-I don't know what that
Sand Village squirt is,
but whatever he is, he's way
too dangerous to mess with.
He's bad news.
-This is turning
into a real mess,
but there's no way we
can cancel the test.
-What do you mean?
-Sorry to interrupt.
-Huh?
What do you want?
We're talking about
something important.
-Uh, I'm sorry,
but it's this tape.
You have to see it.
-What is it?
-OK.
Now, when you watch this, pay
special attention to the time.
[music playing]
-Wha-- but that means--
-That's right, Anko.
This was recorded
from inside the tower.
It's unbelievable.
Those ninja finished only
an hour and 37 minutes
after the test started.
They completely
destroyed the record
for finishing the second test.
-What?
That's impossible.
-It took just 97 minutes.
Nothing like this has
ever happened before.
No one's even come close.
Those ninja from
the Sand Village
are way above genin level.
They beat the record
by four hours.
-I'm afraid it's not just that.
-I don't get it.
What do you mean?
-It's 10 kilometers
from the test entrance
gates to the tower.
And in between are ferocious
animals and poisonous insects,
not to mention the other ninja.
Could they really have
avoided all those things?
Especially the brown-haired
kid in the front.
-What's so special about him?
-You mean you didn't see?
-Interesting.
That is quite a surprise.
-I still don't get it.
What am I supposed
to be seeing here?
-It's what you're not seeing.
Look closely at his body.
-I see it now.
-Not one single scratch.
And I haven't even been able to
spot one little speck of dirt
on his clothing.
-Not even I. No.
None of the Chunin would be
able to make it to the tower
without at least getting a
scratch-- it's impossible.
-He must have some
special ability.
It's been a long
time since we've
had such a promising candidate,
but his eyes are pure evil.
[music playing]
-Next time, I'm going to
look inside that scroll.
-No, you're not.
-What's the harm?
-(ANGRILY) I'll
show you the harm!
-Come on, just one little peek.
-(ANGRILY) What part of
no don't you understand?
No means no!
-Remember what the test
administrator said, loser?
You peek, and we all fail.
-Yeah, but that just makes
me want to peek more.
Next time, The Scroll's
Secret-- No Peeking Allowed.
It's not going to be
easy, but somehow I'm
going to look
inside that scroll.