[theme music]
NARUTO: OK, where is Sasuke?
What have you done with him?
-Heh, I take it you're Naruto.
If I were to tell you the truth,
you wouldn't believe me anyway.
-That's right.
At least not if you
told me he was dead.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Naruto.
-That's right.
Sasuke is alive.
-I promised that I'd
bring Sasuke back,
and I'm the kind of guy who
always keeps his promises.
-Naruto.
-You'll have to
get past me first.
If I were still the
weakling I once was,
I would tell you everything
you want to know.
-Arashi, please.
-Forget it.
The Arashi you used to
know is dead and gone.
What you see now is a fusion
of Ninja Art Cadaver Puppets,
just a lump of unfeeling flesh.
[groaning]
[screaming]
[laughing]
-OK, Sakura.
You look after her while
I take care of this.
-Naruto, no.
You're not really
going to fight him.
-Of course.
I've got to get it
through your head, Sasame.
That's not the sweet, gentle
cousin you used to know.
-Jigumo, attack.
-No!
-Sasame, sorry.
-This way, this way.
Hurry.
-No.
-Sakura, don't do it.
[laughing]
ARASHI: Now, Kamikiri.
Initiate now!
SAKURA: Naruto!
-Now it's your turn.
-Sakura!
ARASHI: Hm.
That was actually close.
I got careless,
let down my guard.
Too bad, Naruto.
You all had your chance for a
sneak attack and you muffed it.
-Naruto?
-All to try and rescue
that worthless dead weight.
-A worthless dead weight?
Naruto, I'm sorry.
NARUTO: Don't let him
get to you, Sakura.
It'll take more than
this to stop me.
This is nothing.
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Let's see the three of you
take on the five of me.
-Kamikiri.
-Naruto.
-Are you all right?
You're badly hurt.
-Sakura, I keep telling you,
it's only a flesh wound.
ARASHI (MOCKINGLY):
Sakura, I keep telling you,
it's only a flesh wound.
[laughing]
-Oh yeah?
You won't be laughing for long.
-You know what?
You're right.
Because this farce
is just about over.
Kamikiri, Jigumo, fuse
your chakra with mine.
Give it all to me.
[groaning]
[arashi chanting]
SASAME: No, how could
Arashi know that?
-Huh?
It's a forbidden
jutsu known only
to the ancient chiefs
of the Fuma Clan.
-Forbidden?
Why?
-Fuma Ninja Art
Spell of the Mandara.
-Naruto.
-OK, what the heck
is this thing?
-It's the end.
-Naruto.
As the chakra cage
shrinks, the person within
is crushed smaller
and smaller until both
are the size of a pebble.
What's more, there's
no way to break free.
Not while I maintain the jutsu
and keep up the pressure.
See?
[screaming]
-Naruto!
[laughing]
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
There's nothing I can do.
There's nothing I'm
capable of doing.
Nothing's changed.
I'm still no use at all.
-No, Arashi.
You can't do this.
No!
-Sasame?
What have you done?
-Sasame!
-Come back, Arashi.
Come back to me.
I know you haven't gone.
You're still in there
somewhere, I know it.
-As I told you before, the
Arashi you used to know
is dead.
[gasp]
-You're there,
Arashi, aren't you?
-Forgive me, Sasame.
All I wanted was the power
to help the Fuma Clan find
its place in the sun once again.
-Yes, I know.
I do understand.
But it's over now.
You can come home.
Come back to the village.
-Never again.
Look at me.
I've become a monster.
-No, that's not true.
-If you knew the agony, Sasame.
End this.
I'm begging you, put
me out of my misery--
[groan]
-What am I saying?
You tried to kill me and
for that you must pay!
-Please, Arashi, stop!
-Pay with your life.
-Sakura.
ARASHI (MOCKINGLY): Sakura.
Watch it or you'll go first.
Is that what you want?
Huh?
-Death's not something
to be afraid of.
Sasame taught me that.
-Oh.
-Worse than death is a
life that helps no one.
I'm not afraid of
giving my life if it
will help someone
who's important to me.
NARUTO: Hold it.
Whatever else happens here,
you're not going to die.
You cannot die.
Got it, Sakura?
-Naruto.
-Oh, please.
What do you think
you can do about it?
It's no use.
You're helpless.
I'll crush you into nothing
like you never existed.
SAKURA: Sasame, no.
-Stop it, Arashi.
Don't do it.
-Sasame, I warn you.
[screaming]
-Naruto.
-Get away from me.
-No.
-Arashi, you're hurt.
-I'm sorry, Sasame.
I never meant to cause
you so much suffering.
-No, no, Arashi.
You're the one that
suffered, not me.
What can I do?
Tell me, tell me, isn't
there anything I can do?
-You've already done it, Sasame.
See?
It's only thanks to you that
I'm finally myself again.
-Naruto.
-Sakura.
Promise me that you won't
ever try that again.
No life should be
thrown away, not
even for the sake
of someone else.
Sakura, watch out!
Huh?
Pervy Sage?
-Sorry if I'm late.
I was held up.
You aren't the only ones
who had their hands full.
-Well, that's typical.
JIRAIYA: Shake a leg, you two.
Come on up.
Let's get back above ground.
Hm?
Huh?
-Is she all right?
-She's fine.
She just fainted, that's all.
ARASHI: Naruto.
Now I can finally tell you
the truth-- the mission
that Orochimaru gave us.
He wanted to make sure
that no one took Sasuke
back to the Hidden Leaf
Village, no matter what.
-Then Sasuke must be--
-That's right.
He's alive.
Sasuke is the vessel
Orochimaru plans to inhabit.
But that can't happen
for three years,
so he has to keep
him safe until then.
-Arashi?
Are you coming?
-Yeah, get up here, hurry.
This place is about to cave in.
[groaning]
-I'm only a puppet
like these two.
This is where I belong now.
-Arashi.
-Let's go.
SASAME: No!
No!
ARASHI (VOICEOVER):
Good bye, Sasame.
And thank you.
HANZAKI: The loss of
Arashi was only part
of the terrible price
that had to be paid.
But the Fuma Clan is
finally free of Orochimaru.
-And free to rebuild
your clan anew.
-And we will.
I know how to begin.
With this-- this life
that I wouldn't even
have without Arashi's help.
We are all grateful
for what you've done.
-It was our pleasure.
-Hanzaki, look after these two.
-I will.
Travel safely, sensei.
-Thank you.
-Good bye.
-Thank you for everything.
Good luck to all of you.
Oh well, look on
the bright side.
We may have failed
to find Sasuke,
but at least we learned
that he's still alive.
What's more, we now
know what Orochimaru
has in store for him.
And that means we
have time on our side.
It seems we have
three years before he
takes over Sasuke's
body as a vessel.
-Right.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Sasame knew
what she had to do for her clan
and she did it.
Once again, I was incapable
of doing anything,
depending on Naruto to
come through as usual.
-Sakura, that was a
great effort back there.
-No, Arashi was right.
I'm just so much dead weight.
I'm useless on my own.
-Are you kidding me?
Seeing you put your
life on the line
like that was the
only thing that
gave me the guts to carry on.
If it hadn't been
for you, I'd have
been crushed to
bits in that thing.
It's only because of you
that we both survived.
-Thanks for that.
-Hey, hey, hey.
Well said.
You've become quite
a sensitive fellow.
-Hey, put me down, Pervy Sage.
What do you think I am?
A sack of garbage?
Come on, knock it off.
-Oops, that's right.
I forgot. [laughing]
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
All I was thinking
of at that moment was
protecting someone I care about.
Maybe that's what
I'm capable of.
-You know, I've been thinking.
-About what?
-Of course, I realize there's
a lot of variables involved--
the size of the squad and
the nature of the mission.
But I think it would be a
good idea if every squad had
at least one member of the
Medical Corps assigned to it.
-You certainly don't
have to convince me.
I wrote a report long ago that
explained how such a move would
greatly increase our rate
of success and survival.
Problem is it takes a long time
to train Medical Corps shinobi.
They need a whole
different set of skills
than fighting shinobi.
Like perfect mastery and
precision of chakra control,
comprehension of a vast amount
of specialized knowledge,
the brains to know how
to apply it, patience.
But of course, the most
important attribute for anyone
who wants to call themselves a
Medical Corps shinobi-- later.
I'm just a little
busy at the moment.
-The most important attribute.
Huh.
-Look at this.
My hands are all
wrapped up in bandages.
How am I going to
hold chopsticks?
I'm going to starve.
Hey, Sakura.
I've got a great idea.
You can sit beside
my bed and feed me.
I'll go like this, K?
Uh, Sakura?
[door opening]
-Huh?
Hey, don't worry, Sakura.
Really, I was only kidding.
SAKURA: Sorry, Naruto.
-Huh?
SAKURA: You may have to
wait for me a little bit.
But next time, I promise
I won't be dead weight.
-Huh?
[knock on door]
TSUNADE: Come in.
-I'm here to make
a request, milady.
-What is it?
-I would like to
be your apprentice.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): Poor thing.
You must really be desperate.
-Sakura Haruno, I'm told
that you have a fine mind,
and that your will is strong.
Very well.
But be warned, I
won't go easy on you.
-Understood.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
That a girl.
Looks like we accomplished
more on this mission
than we thought.
[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): That
lazy old Pervy Sage.
(MOCKING JIRAIYA) You'll
be my only student, Naruto.
I'll make a full-fledged
shinobi out of you.
Yeah right.
So when do we get started?
Meanwhile, Grandma Tsunade's
got Sakura on the fast track.
She's in full training, 24-7.
And what am I doing?
Sitting around,
waiting for Pervy Sage
to get back from
some stupid mission.
Ugh.
I mean, where are
his priorities?
Next time-- The Three Villains
From the Maximum Security
Prison.