[music playing]
-Sensei, please!
You just have to stop
this match right away!
-What?
Relax.
No need to panic.
You know, Sasuke and I
weren't just goofing around.
There's a reason we were
so late getting here.
SASUKE: Late for the
Show, But Ready to Go!
The Ultimate Secret
Technique Is Born!
TEMARI (VOICEOVER):
The third eye.
But that technique--
what's he doing?
Gaara.
GAARA:
[speaking foreign language]
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
Well, that won't work.
Big surprise.
GAARA:
[speaking foreign language]
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): I don't
know what the hell you're up to.
You gonna stay in there forever?
Well, that's fine with me.
Stall all you want.
I can use the time
getting ready for what
I've got in store for you.
-What is it?
Something wrong?
-No.
I must have imagined it.
-Well, get moving!
SAKURA: Sensei?
-Hmm?
-You said there was a
good reason you were late.
What were you doing?
-Hmm.
Well, it's kind of a long story.
-Oh, come on!
Will you please do something?
This is no time for talking!
KAKASHI: You're right,
so shut up and watch.
-Huh?
-Keep your eye on Sasuke.
He's about to surprise you.
[music playing]
BAKI: The little fool!
What does Gaara
think he's doing?
The signal could
come at any moment!
GAARA: Are you ready?
I'm going to open it now.
I'm going to rip it open.
That's how you get it all out.
Everything inside will
come spilling out.
Lots and lots of it.
And I'll give it all to you.
I'm such a good boy, aren't I?
Are you watching, Mother?
Are you ready?
I'm ready.
KANKURO: What's that
lunatic think he's doing?
How long's he going
to stay in that thing?
-I don't know, but he's
not following the plan.
He's no good to us like that.
-Oh, it'll never work.
I say it's time to cut our
losses and get out of here!
-Plan?
-What's your status?
-Everything here is proceeding
according to schedule, sir.
-Hurry up with your
preparations for the summoning.
I want everyone ready to
move at a moment's notice.
-Understood.
-All right, then.
I'll leave you to it.
-Hmm?
But it can't be.
-Yet you wondered
why I always insisted
on training Sasuke myself.
Now you know.
It's because he's like me.
[music playing]
GUY: A physical activation.
I see.
That's what you were
doing all this time.
You were building his speed
up to the level required.
-Exactly.
-It's amazing.
His chakra is actually physical.
How is that even possible?
GUY (VOICEOVER): He's really
mastered that technique
already?
So this is what the
Uchiha are capable of.
-Excellent.
-Wow, I've never seen
him do that before.
-That bizarre noise-- what
sort of technique is it?
GUY: It's a jab?
-A what?
-But this jab is a
jab like no other.
It's the only weapon
in Kakashi's arsenal
he didn't copy
from someone else.
-Huh?
-It's the weapon of
choice for assassinations.
The secret of the jab is
in the speed with which it
is delivered and
the ninja's ability
to focus his chakra at
the point of impact.
Once these two elements,
speed and focus,
have attained a certain
level, the chakra
actually becomes visible and
give off the distinctive sound
that you hear--
like birds chirping.
It is this sound that gives
the technique its name--
Chidori, 1,000 Birds.
-That's impossible.
No one can penetrate
his defenses.
-No way.
-I don't believe it.
-Excellent.
-That technique--
it's Kakashi's.
-Also known as Lightning Blade.
-Why's that?
-It got that name
because Kakashi once
used it to cut a
bold of lightning
in half before it
could touch the ground.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Wow,
cutting lightning in half.
-Yeah, right.
These old guys and
their war stories.
-Woah.
-But whether called Thousand
Birds or Lightning Blade,
it's a technique of
unimaginable power,
requiring almost inhuman
levels of speed and chakra.
But once perfected, it
transforms a ninja's arm
into an indestructible
and invincible sword.
A dangerous technique,
not to be taught lightly.
-Yeah, you're one to talk.
Right, Lee?
-Well, whatever.
I don't understand a word of it.
All I know is it looks awesome!
ROCK LEE (VOICEOVER): I
understand it well enough.
Even with a running
start at top speed,
I would never use a
direct frontal attack
with a jab against my opponent.
Or rather, I could not.
I know that I would be opening
myself to a counterblow,
and I could not trust in
my ability to avoid it.
That requires a
keenness of instinct
that I just do not have.
In short, I envy you, Sasuke.
When we fought, I
told you it was not
enough to be able to
watch and imitate.
Understanding a
technique is useless
if you do not have the physical
ability to pull it off.
I felt so superior.
But now, you have
trained your body
to move at a speed that equals
or even surpasses my own.
And of course, you have
something else-- the Sharingan.
-Now I've got you.
-We're good here.
How about on your end?
-Everything's set.
We're good to go at any time.
-Right.
Be ready to move at the signal.
-It's almost time.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): Huh..
Look at him.
A minute ago, he was
worried that Sasuke
wasn't strong enough.
Now he thinks he's too
strong, and he's jealous.
-Sasuke.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): This is it.
NARUTO: Summoning Jutsu!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I've
worked to make myself stronger
so that I could become
Hokage, so that I
wouldn't lose to anyone.
NARUTO: Hey, Sasuke!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): So that
I wouldn't lose to you.
-Don't lose.
Because I want to
fight you myself.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): But
that was before I knew.
-Got it.
-What is this?
It's so warm and wet.
Mother, what is it?
[screaming]
Blood!
It's my blood!
-Wha-- what's happening?
[screaming]
TEMARI (VOICEOVER): Impossible.
Gaara in pain?
-What's that?
KANKURO (VOICEOVER): Oh, no.
That arm.
-Gaara, you reckless
little fool!
Is that thing taking over again?
-I don't know.
This has never happened before.
I think he's hurt.
KANKURO (VOICEOVER):
Oh, I remember
the first time I
saw it, that thing.
It was awful, horrible.
Oh, man.
Oh, I couldn't eat for a week.
[growling]
-I sense something,
something bad.
-I was right.
He's hurt.
The shell broke before
the change was complete.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
Something's different.
That's not the same look in
his eyes that I saw before.
-Huh?
What's going on?
Everything's getting all fuzzy.
-Kakashi, do you feel it?
-Yeah, a genjutsu.
-Release!
-What the heck?
Uh-oh.
Release!
BAKI (VOICEOVER): Genjutsu.
So Kabuto's already
made his move, huh?
The time must be close.
-It's coming.
Now, shall we begin?
-There's the signal.
[music playing]
-The operation has begun.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Oh,
well, I could use a nap.
Feels good.
Mattress is a little hard.
Hey, who's making all the noise?
Keep it down, would you?
I'm trying to sleep.
I hear voices.
Kakashi sensei?
Sasuke?
Oh, yeah.
Sasuke's match.
I should wake up.
Don't want to miss that.
Next time-- Zero Hour!
The Destruction of the
Hidden Leaf Village Begins!
Wake me up when it gets good.