[theme music]
SAKON (VOICEOVER): You mustn't
lose sight of your purpose.
-Don't leave me!
-Thank you
-Sasuke.
Kotetsu: [yawn] Ugh,
it's four in the morning.
The Fifth Hokage is
a real slave driver.
She forgot these papers,
she should go get them.
Huh?
-What is it?
-Hey wake up.
You're gonna catch a cold
if you sleep out here.
-[mumbling]
-Thank you. [ECHOS
-Sasuke, no!
[crying]
-[snore] [knock] Ugh.
Oh, thank you, boys.
-Huh?
You were fast asleep,
weren't you Lady Hokage?
You made us go fetch these
heavy documents while you just
sit here taking a nap?
-[nervous laugther] No
-Well in any case Lady Hokage,
we have something to report.
-What is it?
What did you say?
Are you sure of that?
-Yes.
-We heard this from
Sakura herself.
There's no reason to
doubt you told us.
HOKAGE (VOICEOVER):
I can't believe it.
He's always making his move.
-In addition to grabbing all
I desire, this time around I'm
going to grind the Hidden
Leaf Village into dust.
HOKAGE (VOICEOVER):
[growl] So that's
what that wretch is after, he's
going for the Uchiha's powers.
Izumo, Kotetsu, there's
somebody that I need to see.
-[yawn]
-Would you hurry up
and eat Shikamaru?
Your dad has an important
mission to get to.
If you just sit there he won't
have time for morning training.
-Yeah, yeah.
-Don't talk, just eat.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
From the second I get up,
it's nag, nag, nag. [doorbell]
-Hmm?
Now who would be visiting
us so early in the morning?
-Hey, dad.
-What is it?
-What on earth
made want to marry
such a crabby woman like mom?
-Hmm.
That's a good question.
Even a crab like your mom
can be gentle sometimes.
She has her moments.
[slurp]
-That's the reason?
SHIKAKU: [slurp] Mhm.
YOSHINO: Shikamaru.
Lady Hokage has sent a
messenger to see you.
-Hmm?
-Late last night Sasuke Uchiha
left the Hidden Leaf Village.
And we are quite certain he's
headed for the Hidden Sound
Village.
-He just left?
How could this happen?
-Simple.
Orochimaru must have
him in his clutches.
-[gasp] What?
Wait, that doesn't
make any sense.
What does Sasuke have to
gain by talking to someone
as depraved as Orochimaru?
-At this point his
motive doesn't matter.
We need to deal with it quickly.
I've decided it's time for you
to carry out your first mission
as a Chuunin, Shikamaru.
-So all I gotta do
is bring Sasuke back?
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): As
long as none of our enemies
are with him, shouldn't
be that big a deal.
-Yes, that's your mission.
But it must be
accomplished without delay.
And you may find it more
dangerous task than you think.
-Huh?
-There's a strong
possibility that Sasuke
is being guarded by
Orochimaru's men.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
Damn, this
is going to be a
real pain in the ass.
What happened to Sasuke anyway?
I used to look up to him, and
now he;s joined up with the bad
guys.
This really stinks.
-Well if we're going to
be facing opposition,
I'm going to need to request
a team composed exclusively
of Jounin and Chuunin.
-I can't honor that request.
-What?
And why not?
-You already know the answer.
As I'm sure you're
aware, most of the Jounin
have been sent out on missions.
Only a handful stayed behind
to defend in case of attack.
Go round up any skilled Genin
you feel are up to the job.
You have 30 minutes
to leave this village.
-This whole thing's a drag,
but I do know the guy,
so I can't just let it go.
Well, that's just the
way it is, I guess.
-Hold on.
There is one person I strongly
recommend you include.
-No way!
You gotta be kidding.
-You just woke up, and
you're already this annoying?
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): Why'd
she want me to bring this guy?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Sasuke, you jerk!
-Hey, hold on a second.
I"ll go get dressed.
-[sigh]
-So, uh, besides
me, have you come up
with any other top
notch guys to ask?
-A few.
Wake up, will ya?
-You said top notch guys, right?
-[sigh] Plan B, I guess.
-Wait, plan B is potato chips?
-They're barbecue flavor.
Feel free to help out.
[munching] Now.
-Aargh!
Even for a bag of
potato chips, I
refuse to let anyone
have the last bite.
-Chouji and I have been on
the same team for a long time.
We work well together, so
asking him's a no-brainer.
-[chuckle]
-I get it, you know him.
But for this kind
of thing, don't you
think your first choice
should be someone like Shino?
-Man, you always have to yell?
-Huh?
-Not on your life!
-Shino can't do it.
He's off on some special mission
with his father right now.
-Hey, wait.
Not them too.
-Yep, they're on the team.
-Aargh!
-Woof, woof.
-I see.
Sound's like an interesting job.
I guess getting up early to walk
the dogs pays off sometimes.
-Hey, Shikamaru, is
there anybody else?
-I wish we had time to
find some more guys,
but we're late already.
If we don't run across
anybody else on our way out
of the village, I
suppose it'll just be us.
-Your surgery, I heard
that it went well.
-It did
-And they said you're
fit to be released?
-I was told I could
resume my training soon.
I have to take it
easy, of course.
-I see.
Yes, I understand.
-Yeah, it's kind
of a drag, but I
figure the more guys
we have the better, so.
LEE (VOICEOVER): Why
now of all times?
-Lee, it's up to you.
You do what you must do.
-Huh?
-Tomorrow I think I will try
climbing these steps by myself.
-Lee.
-I will be fine, you
go on without me.
-It's time to go.
Oh well, at least I got five.
-All right!
come on, let's get going
everybody, follow me!
-Um.
Hey, uh, Naruto,
I'm kind of supposed
to be the platoon leader here.
I know it's a drag but--
-[grunt] You really think you're
the best person to direct this
operation?
You don't seem very reliable me.
-What's up with you
acting like you're
in charge of a sudden Naruto?
I mean, taking orders
from somebody as lazy
as Shikamaru doesn't exactly
thrill me either, but still.
-Woof
-But none of you get to
decide who's the leader here,
because Shikamaru is the only
one of us who's a Chuunin.
That means the
elders of the village
clearly believe he's
got what it takes
to call the shots on this one.
-[moan]
-If that's the case,
then perhaps you
should start coming up
with some sort of a plan.
From what I heard,
Sasuke's gone to the enemy,
and there's a real chance
they could ambush us.
-Well for starters, this
is a rescue operation,
so we'll be in the
position of pursuit.
Which means the
enemy already has
an important advantage over us.
That said, I'm arranging us
in a deployment formation that
can respond to any
assault by the enemy.
If any of you don't
follow my exact orders,
we're all going to die.
-[gasp]
-OK, we'll go with a
single-file strike formation.
As we all know, the
most important position
is the spearhead, so
that's going to be Kiba.
You're upfront.
-[gasp]
-SHIKAMARU: With all the
walks you and Akamaru go on,
you're the most familiar with
the Land of Fire's terrain.
And with that sensitive
nose of yours,
you'll be able to
track Sasuke's scent,
while sniffing out any booby
traps the enemy may have set.
Moreover, because we'll have
two sets of eyes up front,
you and Akamaru will be
more effective in protecting
our single-file line
from an assault.
Second in line will be
yours truly, platoon leader.
From that position, I'll
be able to direct everyone
behind using silent
hand signals.
And because I'm
so close to Kiba,
I'll be in position to
react in any situation.
In the middle, the number
three position is Naruto.
The middle of the line is
the perfect location for you
because you're the most capable
of executing quick moves
either in front of
you, behind you.
You're the cornerstone, and you
have the Shadow Clone Jutsu.
Fourth in line is Chouji.
Chouji, you might
not have any speed,
but your striking
power is the greatest
of the platoon members.
Kiba, myself, and Naruto will
launch a surprise attack,
then you'll swoop in
and finish them off.
You're the second
wave of our assault.
Finally, on the end
will be you, Neji.
Your position is most
difficult, rear lookout.
I want to use your Byakugan
to constantly scan ahead
for weakness in our ranks.
Got it?
Then take a look at this.
This diagram shows exactly
what part of the perimeter
you're responsible for.
Kiba watches the front.
I'm responsible for
a wider forward view.
Naruto's got the left,
Chouji the right,
and Neji, using your Byakugan,
you cover the entire area
to the rear.
All right, now I think I
should familiarize myself
with our arms and weaponry.
I'll need to check out
all of the ninja tools
you each of you plan on
carrying into battle,
that way I'll know what we have.
Are there any questions?
-Uh-uh.
-LEE (VOICEOVER): Even though
he has just assembled this team,
he has already created the best
possible formation for them.
-Since no one has
anything to add,
I saved the most
important thing for last.
For as long as I've
known him, Sasuke and I
haven't exactly
been close buddies.
In fact, I don't really like him
at all. [gasps] All the same,
Sasuke's a ninja belonging
to the Hidden Leaf Village.
He's a comrade, and I'll put my
life on the line to help him.
That's the way of our village.
I know I usually seem like a
pretty lazy guy, but not today.
Because now I'm responsible
for your lives too.
-Wow, I never thought
I'd see Shikamaru
acting like a Chuunin.
Very impressive.
-OK, as soon as we check
our gear, we'll go.
Show me your weapons.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Sasuke would never
let a guy like that
sink his claws into him.
I mean, he's already
a total powerhouse.
It's not he needs that
kind of help, you know.
Don't worry, I guarantee it.
Damnit, why Sasuke?
SHIKAMARU: All right,
let's move out.
SAKURA: Wait!
-Huh?
-Are you all right?
-Lady Hokage told me everything.
Sorry Sakura, I can't
take you on this mission.
I know you tried, but even
you couldn't convince Sasuke,
could you?
-[gasp]
-Now our only option is for
me to find him, and force
him to come back to the village.
I'm sorry, but there's nothing
else you can do for him.
-But that means-- did Sasuke
turn his back on you Sakura?
LEE (VOICEOVER): Sakura.
--[crying] Naruto, this is a
once in a lifetime request.
Just bring him home.
Please bring Sasuke back to me.
I did everything I could.
I tried, but I couldn't stop
him from leaving the village.
At this point.
There's only one person
who can stop him.
Only one who can save him.
Naruto, it's all up to you.
-Well gosh Sakura, you must
really care about Sasuke, huh?
I get it.
I can see that deep down, this
must be really painful for you.
I know you must be suffering.
-Sakura, I want to
ask you something.
-Huh?
-Naruto, what do
you think of him?
-He knows about my feelings, and
he purposely gets in the way.
It's almost like he
enjoys interfering
and making me feel bad.
Despite what he says,
he doesn't understand
one single thing about me.
He's just annoying.
[cries] Naruto,
thank you so much.
-Don't you worry one bit.
I'm going to bring Sasuke back.
I promise that on
my life, Sakura.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
More than anyone
else, you always understood me.
You've always been there
when I needed help.
Naruto.
-Whoa, hold on Naruto.
That's quite a statement.
Are you sure you
should be promising her
that we'll get him?
-Sure.
When I give my word
you can count on it.
That's my ninja way.
Well come on, what're we
waiting for, let's get going.
-All right then.
This little interruption
cost us some time.
Let's get moving.
-Right.
-Did you see Naruto
give you the thumbs
up when he made that promise?
That means he will do it.
I can tell Naruto will succeed.
-Sasuke, I think
this is far enough.
We're already past the
Hidden Leaf Village.
-So what's up?
-Orochimaru gave us
a very important task
to take care of when
we reach this point.
-You going to tell me what
we have to do, or not?
--[chuckles] Before
we go any further,
I'm afraid you must
die just this once.
[theme music]
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
From this position
it's going to be dangerous,
use your five senses.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Roger, got it!
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
We have to find them
before they find us.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
You can count on me!
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
As soon as we locate--
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Yep.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): Are
you even listening to me?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): It
doesn't matter who they are,
I'll beat'em no problem.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
Ugh, why do
I even bother explaining
things to him?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next
time, Sound versus Leaf.
[theme music]