[theme music in Japanese]
-Huh?
-Naruto.
-Yeah, but he's totally
late, of course.
-Hey, wait.
Where's Sasuke?
-I'm fighting Dosu,
but he's missing, too.
-Hey, knock it off.
Quit your fidgeting, you two.
Stand up straight and
present yourself proudly
to the spectators.
-Huh?
[crowd cheering]
-You guys are the heroes
of this final competition.
-No sign of Sasuke yet.
-No, a team of Andu Black
Ops are searching for him,
but so far, they've
found nothing.
He may already be in
Orochimaru's hands,
in which case, of course,
we may never find him.
-I understand.
Aha, you made it.
Welcome, Lord Kazekage.
You must be weary having
come all this way.
-Not at all.
I'm only glad that for
your sake the arena is here
in the Leaf Village.
As strong as you are, I'm
sure a long journey would
have proven difficult
for you at your age.
Isn't it about time you decided
who will succeed you Kazekage?
-Hmm?
[laughing]
You act as if I were
an old man, there's
plenty of life left in me.
No, I plan on staying here
for some time to come.
Now then.
It's time for the
final rounds to begin.
Welcome all, and
our deepest thanks
for coming here to
the Village Hidden
in the Leaves for this
year's Chunin Selection.
We have come to the final
competition between the eight
candidates who made it
through the preliminaries.
We ask that no one leaves
until all the matches have
been completed.
Now everyone enjoy.
-You said eight candidates.
Aren't you missing one?
-Oh, there's one more thing
before we get started.
Look it over.
-Huh?
-There's been a slight
change in the match-ups.
But now it's set,
so everyone take
one last look at who
you'll be facing.
-I thought I was supposed
to fight an extra match.
Hey, so that Dosu
guy dropped out.
-I was planning on attacking
you while you slept.
If I fight and defeat you
now, then in the next round,
I can battle the one I
really want to face, Sasuke.
-What-- what-- what
in the world are you?
Aaagh.
-Uh, question.
Question.
-What is it?
-I was just wondering what
will happen to Sasuke?
I mean, if he doesn't show up?
-Where is Sasuke?
And why did he sneak out
of his hospital room?
But maybe he didn't.
Maybe somebody took him.
-If a candidate is
not here in the arena
at the time his name is
called, he forfeits the match.
-It doesn't make sense.
Sasuke's not the
type to miss this,
even if he had to
drag himself here.
-What is it, Gaara?
Where you going?
-To remind myself I'm alive.
-One more time.
Come on, what's wrong?
Not tired already, are you?
Come on, Sasuke.
-Yaaah!
-No, after all my warnings not
to draw attention to himself.
He wouldn't have killed
Sasuke and [inaudible], too.
Would he?
-All right, listen up.
The terrain's different, but the
rules are the same as before.
That is that there are no rules.
The match continues
until one candidate
acknowledges defeat or dies.
That being said, if I
determine that a match is over,
I can step in and
stop it at any time.
And no arguments permitted.
Understood?
These are the opponents
for the first match.
Naruto Uzumaki, Neji Hyuga.
Those two stay.
The rest of you can go
to the waiting area.
-Byakugan versus
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
-Hey, Hinanta, look,
these seats are free.
-Oh, thanks.
-I think this it's going
to be an interesting match.
-Naruto.
-Hey, Sakura.
-Um-hmm.
-I know that you're worried
about Sasuke, but come on.
Don't be such a lump.
Aren't you going to at
least cheer Naruto on?
-You're right.
-That's more like it.
Not that the poor runt has
a hope in hell against Neji.
-He's not that bad.
-Are you kidding?
Not that bad?
Is that the best you can do?
-Who would have believed
that little squirt would
survive this long?
-Yeah.
He's been one lucky kid
so far, but his luck's
about to run out.
He'll never survive this one.
-Yeah, it's going to be painful.
Going up against one
of the Hyuga clan,
he doesn't have a chance.
-Yeah, I thought
that, too, at first.
And look what happened.
He's out there, and I'm
sitting up here on my butt.
[dog whimpers] Huh?
Yeah, Akamaru, what is it?
[dog whimpers] What
the-- are you sure?
Where?
Up there.
What the hell are the
Anbu Black Ops doing here?
Something's going on.
-You got anything to say to me?
-Only what I told
you the last time.
-Once a failure,
always a failure.
You can't change that.
-Hinata, I give you my word.
I vow to win.
-He as the look.
He's calmer now,
more sure of himself.
So much the better for me.
I can't wait to see the
look of despair on your face
when you learn that your foolish
vow is impossible to keep.
-Are we going to stand
here talking all day?
Let's get going.
Show me what you've got.
-All right.
Now let the first match begin.
-Watch closely, Hanibi.
There's no one in
the Hyuga clan who
has inherited such a
strong Kekkei Genkai.
His is stronger than
your older sister's.
-Stronger than hers?
-Perhaps even
stronger than yours.
-Watch yourself.
This is no pushover
you're up against.
Not want that Byakugan of his.
You don't want to get
too close with this guy.
But does Naruto know that?
-Yaaah.
-You idiot!
A frontal attack
will never work.
-Aaagh.
Aaah.
-Naruto, watch out.
-Hmph-umph.
Aaah.
-Naruto, he can see
your chakra points.
-Hitting one directly
can affect chakra flow,
either halting it
or increasing it
depending on how the attacker
strikes the chakra points.
-Oh, no.
-Hmph.
I missed.
-Almost blew it.
If I get to close he
can turn off my chakra,
and there goes my Jutsu.
I'll have to fight
him from a distance.
-Do you understand now?
You have no way of beating me.
-Heh.
Get real.
I was just checking
you out, that's all.
-Huh?
-OK, now that we're warmed
up, we can get started.
Shadow Clone Jutsu.
-That's using your head, Naruto.
That'll confuse him.
-Well, isn't he something?
-That Shadow Clone Jutsu was
a Jounin-level technique.
Where'd that kid ever pick
up a technique like that?
-This match could be more
interesting than we thought.
-Shadow Clones.
I see.
Quite clever.
He's distributed his
chakra evenly among them,
so that even my Byakugan
can't pick out the real one.
No matter.
You can't hide for long.
-Well, we'll just
see about that.
-If you're coming, then come on.
-It's no use.
No matter how many times
Naruto attacks him,
Neji can win on
his defects alone.
-Hey, don't ever, don't ever,
I mean, never count me out.
-He got him.
-Just wait.
-Not bad.
But let's see you do that again.
Come on.
Aaagh.
Aaah.
This guy, he must have eyes
in the back of his head.
-You thought you
could beat Hokage?
It's absurd.
Never.
These eyes of mine
show me many things.
One thing they've shown
me, people's limitations
are set, fixed,
and unchangeable.
Only a fool wastes
his time trying
to become something
he can never be.
-A fool, huh?
Not this crap again.
Who are you to judge what
a person can or can't be.
-Do you think anyone
can be Hokage?
That all it takes is
a little hard work?
Open your eyes.
Of all the shinobi
in all the world,
think how few ever
become Hokage.
They were born
destined to be Hokage.
It's not something you become
merely by trying to become it.
They were chosen by destiny.
Each person is given
his own path to follow.
And he must follow it
obediently to the end.
There is only one destiny
we all share equally.
Death.
-There's hatred in his eyes.
Hatred for the main
branch of the family.
-Yeah?
So what?
You can think that
way if you want.
People always tell me I just
don't know when to give up.
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
[theme music]
-What's going on?
I hit him with my best shot,
and I'm the one sent flying.
No problem.
I can learn from my mistakes.
OK, I can't beat
him inside, and I
can't beat him from the outside.
So what have I learned?
I can't beat him.
No, that's not right.
Of course, I can beat him.
I've got to beat him.
I made a promise to Hinata.
Next time ultimate
defense, zero blind spot.
Don't count your
chickens bug-eyes,
you ain't seen nothing yet.