-Gaara.
-Kankuro.
-Primary Lotus!
-I'm at the end of my rope.
I can't hold on any longer.
-[laughing]
-You're staring
death in the face.
Shouldn't you be
screaming for mercy?
Huh?
-[laughs]
-Now die!
-You're mine!
-You're gonna die, kid!
Wipe that grin off your face!
-[scream]
-What the--
-Who are you?
-What do you know?
Looks like we're
on the same side.
-Who are you?
-Allies of the Leaf Village.
-We're shinobi.
-Of the Sand.
-Yeah.
Well, careful getting home.
-OK.
-I'll see you next time
you need to be rescued.
Just let me know and I'll
come, you big crybaby.
-You girls are all alike.
You had to get the
last word in, huh?
-[laughing]
-Hmph.
-We owe you for that one.
Time we paid you back!
-What's up, Shikamaru?
What's the matter?
-We're going to
wait here for now.
-Wait here?
Are you out of
your mind, or what?
It's no time to
be taking a break.
-Put a lid on it, Naruto.
-[barking]
-That's right.
Shikamaru's leading
this mission,
not you, you knucklehead.
-Yeah.
Come on.
Get with it.
You have to obey
your leader, Naruto.
-Hmph!
Fine.
Whatever.
-I'm counting on you, Shino.
[theme song]
-What's happening?
Are they still coming?
-Oh, yes.
We made sure that by leaving
tracks, they couldn't miss.
They're hot on our
trail, all right.
It's perfect.
They'll be within range shortly.
There are three of
them, including Gaara.
-As for the other
two, divvy them up
however you like, and take
them on in one to one combat.
Meanwhile, I'll lure Gaara into
the reverse scale position.
-OK, but I get
first crack at them.
-All right.
You're on.
-Hokyo's clever little plan is
a waste of time, if you ask me.
There's only three of them.
No reason I can't take
care of them myself.
Kujaku, double edged sword!
Tempest wind!
-What's going on?
-A wind user.
Just my thing.
-Excellent.
-Not bad, Temari.
-What did you expect?
-Not bad at all.
Not everyone can blow
away my tempest wind.
And look at you.
You're just a kid.
Ha.
-You two go on ahead.
-What?
You're good taking
her on by yourself?
-Are you sure of this?
-No problem.
We're two peas in a pod.
She and I are going to
swap wind jutsu techniques.
Get moving, Gaara.
Save your student.
-You're right.
Thank you.
-Be careful.
-Right.
-You're finished!
-I was about to
say the same thing.
Cyclone scythe jutsu!
-Wind slash!
-What kind of wind?
-My twin swords can twist
the wind in counter currents,
increasing its power.
You've only just begun
to see what I can do!
Having second thoughts?
With these, I need only
a fraction of my chakra.
You have to use all of yours.
How long can it last?
I guess we'll find out.
-Matsuri.
There they are.
-Where am I?
-So, you're awake.
Good.
You'll see the trap unfold
as you lure your teacher
right into it.
-Huh?
Gaara-sensei!
-Dragon eye, fang release!
Dark sword!
-What the heck?
-[laughing] What do you think?
Bet you've never seen
a sword like this one.
-He's just a kid!
Hmph.
I get it.
That sword's made up
of sections connected
by a wire running
through the center of it.
What do you know?
It's like one of
those bamboo snake
puppets I used to scare
people with when I was a kid.
What are you planning to
do with that kids' toy?
I hope you got something better
than that up your sleeve.
Because I'm warning you, little
man, when it comes to puppets,
you're playing with the master!
You go on ahead.
-I can leave him to you?
-Yeah.
Don't worry.
He's not worth your trouble.
I'll catch up with you.
-You got it.
-OK, sonny, I'll play with you.
-I wouldn't be so
confident if I were you.
It could be the last
mistake you ever make.
-Kid, you're going
to get a spanking.
-I'm going to wipe that
makeup right off your face!
-Let's play!
-Gotcha!
What, is that it?
I wasn't expecting
much, but come on.
Huh?
How did he--
-Now are you starting to get it?
This sword is hardly
a child's toy.
I only have to exert
a tiny bit of chakra,
and it amplifies it
tenfold and channels it
into the form of a dragon.
-Gaara, sorry.
This could take
longer than I thought.
-Suiko, this is the spot
to stop and ambush him.
Draw him into the
reverse scale position.
Got it?
-Got it.
[yelling]
[laughing] This is as
far as you go, Gaara.
Unless you go through me.
-If you insist, fine.
-Hey, Shikamaru!
How long are we
supposed to wait?
-Use your head.
You can't just throw
an ambush together.
You've got to set
it up, and it means
doing reconnaissance,
which is what Neji, Shino,
and Hinata are doing
for us right now.
-They're doing what?
-So you found them.
Byakugan!
-I see.
They're just up ahead.
Byakugan!
-Understood.
Three separate battle zones.
-This sack carries the
scent of the female.
As long as you keep
it on you, they'll
find you no matter how
far away you may be.
-OK, guys.
We're counting on you.
-We'll be off, then.
-Be careful.
-That's it.
The news I was waiting for.
-Good!
I was starting to cramp up.
-OK.
What's the word?
-Well, that's a drag.
Things have already
gotten started.
All right, Kiba and Choji
take to the west forest.
Ino and I will take the
hills to the northeast.
Naruto and Lee, take
the northwest forest.
We'll operate in
backup squads of two.
Ready?
Let's begin Operation
Return The Favor.
-Right!
-[bark]
-Finally some action!
-Move out!
-What is it?
-Let's hold up a minute.
If they're really
trying to get away,
why would they stop and
turn on their pursuers?
Take them one by one,
in separate battles.
Unless it's a trap!
-Huh?
-Just to be safe.
-That should do it.
Let's go.
-Right.
-Aww, nowhere left to hide,
and you feel helpless.
Poor thing.
-She can take everything
I throw at her.
I've got no choice.
I have to try it.
-Wind style sea dragon!
-I'm waiting.
Isn't something
supposed to happen?
[laughing] It
looks like the wind
has turned its back on you.
-I wouldn't be so sure.
The wind and I are good friends.
-Then let the battle
begin in earnest!
Wind reversal!
-[screaming]
-Get off!
Get off, you-- ugh!
-What a shame.
The game's over already?
I expected to have
a lot more fun.
-[grunting]
-Hm?
Now that's more like it.
I wonder what kind
of toy this is.
-[groaning]
-Ha!
You're so pathetic.
Is this silly little puppet
the only trick you have?
-Better than that piece
of junk you've got.
-Damn!
The dragon has three heads.
-You're quick, when
you're running away.
-It's no use.
Crow's playing at
a disadvantage when
he's not teaming up
with the black ant.
-Well done, Gaara of the Desert.
Just how much of your chakra
is that sand infused with?
-You really want to know?
Very well, but it's
gonna cost you your life.
Sand coffin!
-It can't be.
-Thank you.
That was very refreshing.
-But how?
How could you break out?
-It's my armor.
It absorbs chakra.
It feeds on it.
-Aww, are we tired?
Well, don't let me wake you.
You can sleep forever!
How did she--
-[groans]
-I almost came too late for
my shadow possession jutsu.
-Playtime's over!
-Oh no.
-What?
-I-it's you guys!
-And who are you?
-Who are you?
-Allies of the Sand.
-We're Shinobi.
-Of the Leaf Village!
-So you better watch out!
They're not here.
-Just up ahead!
-Right!
-Don't worry, guys.
It's a straight up battle.
No sign of chakra surges
anywhere in the valley.
There is no trap.
-Good luck, everyone.
-I've got your back, guys.
-Gaara-sensei.
-Hang on.
We're coming, Gaara.
We owe you one, and
we haven't forgotten!
[theme song]
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): Oh, man.
So that's what these guys
have been after all this time.
Gotta hand it to
them, they're really
using the terrain
to their advantage.
If we don't turn the tables
quick, Gaara's in big trouble.
But they got us pinned down.
What a drag.
Naruto, Lee, I hope you
guys are on the way.
You're the only ones
who can save him!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next time!
Sealed Sand!
The Counterattack!