[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): "Mystery
of the Targeted Merchants."
-Did they really come this way?
-I don't get it.
Why would they
come through here?
If it's like you
said, Choji, they
should be heading in a
completely different direction.
-Well, I only said
that because I
didn't think we were the
ones who were being chased.
-Maybe this isn't the best
time to have an argument.
We should come up with
some sort of strategy.
-Yeah, but you got
to be kidding me.
SHUN: What's happened?
-Huh?
-Are the people you spoke
of before pursuing us now?
In that case, I think we should
form two groups and split up.
-It's hard enough to protect
one group around here.
It would be idiotic to
split ourselves into two.
HINATA: Naruto!
-Hm?
-Sorry about that.
Please tell us your
plan, and we'll listen.
-Here's the idea.
I'll demonstrate.
Let's say there are
10 persimmons here.
-Hey, does it matter
what kind of food it is?
-Uh, no.
-Well, OK.
Then I want it to be ramen.
-But, Naruto, it's hypothetical.
-All right then,
we'll make it ramen.
Let's say someone is after
these 10 bowls of ramen.
And there are three
people to guard the ramen.
So each one of them has to
protect, roughly, three bowls.
-Now way!
If it's ramen, we
should just scarf it
all down before the
bad guys show up.
That would settle
things real good.
-Huh?
-Um, Naruto, but this
ramen is special delivery
for someone very hungry.
We can't just eat it.
-Well, it's not going
to taste very good
if it sits out and gets soggy.
-Let's move on,
if you don't mind?
The people have to
protect 10 bowls of ramen.
So each watches,
roughly, three bowls.
But remember, this ramen
has legs and can run.
-Hold on.
You mean there's
ramen that has legs?
SHUN: Five of the bowls
can run very quickly.
But the other five
bowls move slowly.
-Wow!
This whole ramen thing
is getting kind of crazy.
-I see.
So if we divide ourselves
up into two groups--
-And logically, the pursuers
would target the slower group
first.
-So we only have to assign one
person to defend the faster
half and still have two to
guard the slower-moving group.
-Hm.
Hm.
SHUN: And by taking this
approach, the ones defending
the slower group only have
to defend 2 and 1/2 bowls
each instead of 3.
-Oh.
-I get it.
The quick-moving ramen
represents the younger people.
And the slower
ramen bowls must be
the older people and
children, correct?
-Exactly.
And not only will the likelihood
that the first group escapes
increase, but the burden on
the second group will decrease.
We'll be killing two
birds with one stone.
-Boy, you know, you're a
pretty intelligent fellow.
-But, Shun, won't the elderly
and children be exposed?
-The plan I laid out is
our only logical option.
If we stayed together,
then the whole group
is at risk of annihilation.
Am I right, Yurinoshin?
-I suppose.
-All right then, it's settled.
We'll divide everyone
up into two groups.
-I'm sorry, Gramps.
-Ah, don't worry
about us old folks.
It would be far worse
if something happened
to you, young whippersnappers.
After all, you've got
wives and children at home
to think about.
-Then, I guess, I'll
take the first group.
Bye, Naruto.
See you soon, Choji.
-(TOGETHER) Hm.
-We're counting on you, Hinata.
Naruto and I will
do our best to take
care of anyone following you.
-OK, I'll protect my group.
-Lady Haruna.
-Yurinoshin, keep
your mouth shut.
Don't you remember
what your mission is?
Your only concern
shall be my well-being.
Everything will be
fine when Kikunosuke
defeats our pursuers.
-Well, I guess we
should head on out.
-I just know you're
going to keep us safe.
-Yup.
You got nothing to worry about.
NARUTO: Choji!
-Yeah?
-You should take the
gang and get going.
-What?
-I'm going to double
back real quick and check
things out where
we set those traps.
-But if you turn
around, you're going
to run straight
into the bad guys.
-That's OK by me.
After all, just sitting
around waiting to be attacked
isn't exactly my style.
-Naruto!
-Just go!
I can handle myself.
-That's not what I meant.
It defeats the whole
point of the strategy
if I have to guard
five people alone.
-Hm, the plan is ruined.
-We came down that path, so
the trap should be up ahead,
past that ridge.
I know!
I'll take a short cut.
What the heck?
What happened here?
[splash]
Why is the ground so wet?
[gasps]
Huh?
What kind of wounds are those?
Kikunosuke!
CHOJI (VOICEOVER):
This is not good.
-Hey, Choji, I something wrong?
-Hm?
No, everything's fine.
-OK.
CHOJI (VOICEOVER): I can
sense that whoever is out
there is so cold-blooded.
And they're getting closer.
-Hm, what's that?
-It's raining?
CHOJI (VOICEOVER): Terrific.
The rain's going to blot
out any trace of the enemy.
-Huh?
-This rain is really weird.
-Hm.
Hm.
Everybody gather round!
Stay close to me.
Don't leave my
sight, you got it?
What is this?
It's moving?
Not good.
[zoom]
Oh, great.
What was that?
Everyone, get under that
cart as fast as you can!
-We're already under here.
-That was pretty fast.
NARUTO: Choji!
-Huh?
Naruto!
-Better get down.
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
-Aah!
-Naruto, if you're going
to use paper bombs,
do you think you could give
a guy a little more heads-up?
-That's it.
It looks like they're
gone for the moment.
-Why do you think
they just ran away?
-Isn't the reason
obvious, young one?
You don't shop at the store
that doesn't have what you want.
-What the heck are you saying?
-It's simple.
If a shop sold out
of the item you want,
you would go to
another shop, correct?
-Wait, what you're saying is
whatever these guys are looking
for, they must have realized
it's with the other group!
-What does that mean, Choji?
-Hinata's in danger.
Everyone, we're going
to be moving fast.
Leave everything behind
that you don't need.
-Oh, no, Hinata!
HINATA: All right, everyone.
Let's make camp for the night.
We'll leave our tents here.
It will be far too dangerous
to move in the dark.
-Huh?
-Hey!
-[gasps]
-How's it going, guys?
We finally caught up with you.
-You two aren't
supposed to be here.
What about the plan?
-Just forget about the plan.
The situation is
much different now.
-It seems that one of
the folks in your group
is keeping something from
us, something important.
-Something important?
-And whatever it is,
I'm pretty sure it's
the reason those guys have
been chasing after us.
-But which of the group?
And what could they
possibly be hiding?
-Everything is pointing
to Shun and Yurinoshin.
At least, that's my hunch.
-How dare you!
What are you implying
that we're hiding?
-Don't act all dumb!
They already got Kikunosuke.
We don't have time to
play games anymore.
-They what?
-Not Kikunosuke!
-Don't act all dumb!
They already got Kikunosuke.
We don't have time to
play games anymore.
-They what?
-Not Kikunosuke!
-If you don't know
what's going on,
why did you have him suit
up in full ninja gear,
battle those guys, and
get himself killed, huh?
-I'm under no obligation
to tell you anything.
-Can't you see?
If you don't tell us why
we're being pursued--
---then you're putting
everyone of us here in danger,
including you!
If you don't come
clean, we won't
be able to protect anyone.
We'll have no chance!
-Kikunojo.
[sobs]
-Kikunojo?
-Was that Kikunosuke's
real name?
-It was.
And my name's not Yurinoshin.
It's Yurinojo.
-Hold your tongue, Yurinojo.
-The person standing
here is the only daughter
of the Land of
Greens' feudal lord.
Her name is Lady Haruna.
-Princess?
It's Princess Haruna
of the Land of Greens.
My, just look how
much you've grown.
-No way!
Pri-- princess?
You're saying that he's a she?
-Lady Haruna, what these shinobi
have told you is the truth.
We must not put the
rest of them in danger
by concealing our
secret any longer.
-Tch.
-So what's a princess
doing traveling around
with a bunch of
merchants anyway?
-There was a threat.
We learned of a coup being
planned in the Land of Greens.
-A coup d'etat?
-Our small land may have been
a peaceful and fertile place;
however, it was, by no
means, a prosperous one
before we even realized that
half of our public officials
have been bought off.
-But who would do that?
-They're called the
Janin, three evil ninja
who came to us from
across the sea.
-The Janin?
-Yes.
They're called that because
they are the only ones who
can use a particularly
dangerous ninjutsu.
They have taken
many lives and think
nothing of attacking
innocents if it
furthers their wicked schemes.
The three have complete
disregard for human life.
-But still, why would
they target your home?
-That's something
we just don't know.
But in order to
protect its only heir,
his lordship had
Lady Haruna hide
amongst this group of
merchants that flee the land.
Kikunojo and I were charged
with the safety of the princess.
But we weren't confident
with just the two of us.
We needed more force, which is
why we commissioned you, Leaf
Ninja, under the pretext
of a protection job.
-But why wouldn't you
share this information?
-I couldn't trust you.
My escape is top secret.
If we said anything, word
might have gotten out.
Besides, if you knew,
you'd probably run away.
-You're not looking at somebody
who runs away from trouble.
And if you'd given us the
whole picture from the get-go,
your pal Kikunojo might
still be alive right now.
-I'm not so sure.
If one of you ninja had
gone in Kikunojo's place,
you might have
suffered the same fate.
-Humph.
-We can hold our own, thanks.
You're the one who
had to get old people
and children involved in this.
-What the heck
were you thinking?
Your plan was to use old
ladies and kids as decoys
while you make you getaway?
-That's right.
You have a problem with that?
-Choji, Hinata, I
don't know about you,
but I am really
ticked off right now.
-So what?
If something terrible should
happen to the Land of Greens,
I would be the only
person remaining
in the royal bloodline.
I have to survive.
Even if farmland is
completely destroyed,
I can go back someday
and restore it.
-That's all you care about!
And you would sacrifice innocent
people's lives to get it!
Ugh!
-Ow!
I beg you, please
forgive our princess.
-But why, Yurinojo?
-Have completely
forgotten that you've
been hired to
protect me from harm?
-What, are you nuts?
You think I care about?
-Naruto, please, just wait.
Lady Haruna, that's
indeed my mission.
However, their assignment
isn't the same at all.
These ninja were hired
to protect merchants
from roving bandits.
Saving you isn't what
they signed on for.
-Uh!
-He's right.
We were told this
was a D-rank mission
to guarantee these merchants
had a safe journey.
Protecting a
prominent figurehead,
like you, would
have been classified
A-rank at the very least.
The two missions carry
completely different risks.
-So now, you're just going to
leave me to fend for myself?
-First, you say you don't
trust people like us.
And now, your begging
for us to rescue you?
-I will protect you with
my life, Lady Haruna.
-Shut up, Yurinojo.
Kikunojo was more
skilled than you are.
If he wasn't able to
defeat this opponent,
what makes you think you
have any chance at all?
-It is my fate.
When the time comes, I will do
what I have to, Lady Haruna.
-Uhh.
-Hey, Choji, check this out.
CHOJI: Whoa, awesome!
-Hey, I'm sorry about
what happened before.
I just couldn't hold
myself back anymore.
-Don't be concerned
about my feelings.
However, I sincerely wish you
could forgive Lady Haruna.
The Land of Greens
is a fragile nation.
To make sure her
lineage was safe,
Lady Haruna was taken
to a far-off land
when she was very young--
held hostage there
while she grew up.
-Held hostage?
-For smaller lands in troubled
times, it is a common practice.
Later, when Lady Haruna finally
returned from the other land,
she had completely lost
her trust in people.
Lady Haruna is a victim
of this turbulent world.
-There's a village about
one leap down the mountain
from where we are.
-For their safety, we should
take the elderly and children
there for now.
Just be careful.
-Yeah.
You, too.
-Bye-bye.
-Why are you just getting
rid of them like this?
Without them as decoys, how
do you expect to protect me?
-Are you still
going on about that?
They gave up everything,
all of their possessions
to save your sorry hide!
-Then we should go with them
and hide in the village, too.
-No, we mustn't.
If we venture
anywhere near them,
there's a chance the
group of merchants
could be attacked again.
-He's exactly right.
It's our turn to be
the decoys, so we
can make sure those guys
stay safe and sound.
-Fine.
Do as you like.
-Uhm.
-Hm?
-Hm.
-Hinata, I can help Naruto.
Why don't you go and
rest for a while?
-Yeah, we got things
under control.
-Well, OK then, if
you both insist.
NARUTO: Oh, yeah, here.
Kikunojo was holding
it when I found him.
-Thanks, Naruto.
I appreciate it.
Kikunojo was a master of the
Land of Greens Special Flower
Ninjutsu.
We trained together when
we were little kids.
But I never managed to
beat him, not even once.
Now, it seems that
I'll never again
have the opportunity
to best my friend.
-Not quite.
You still got one more chance.
-Huh?
-If you can defeat the guy
who took down your buddy, then
in a way, you'll be winning
against Kikunojo, too.
-Thanks, Naruto.
Yes, that makes sense.
They're here!
NARUTO: Aside from the fact
that the enemy uses water,
I got no clue what they're
going to come at us with.
-I think I know.
-Power Ninjutsu, Flying
Flower, Falling Foliage!
-Hrm.
What the--
-They changed the kunai's
trajectory in midair?
-Uh-oh!
-The princess is mine.
Nobody home?
He-he.
What do you think I am-- a fool?
-You finally had the guts
to show your face, huh?
-I will avenge Kikunojo.
You can mark my words.
-[chuckles]
Go ahead and give
it your best shot.
-Huh?
[yells]
-You can't get away that easy.
Heh, too bad for you,
you're one person short.
-You're about to find out I
already took care of that!
-Huh?
-He-he, how pathetic.
-I love water.
-Urgh!
-Aagh!
-I believe I'll finish you
off first, little man-- water
style.
Liquid Memory!
-Naruto, no!
-[chuckles]
Now, for the fun.
Rrh.
Summon Ninjutsu!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
What in the hell?
-That must be--
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): --the
jutsu that killed Kikunojo!
-[laughs]
I think we've seen
the last of you.
-Ah!
Aaah!
[music playing]
-Aargh!
What's this huge thing?
I really don't want
to be his dinner!
Listen, I'm not very tasty.
CHOJI: I'm not tasty either.
NARUTO: But there's more
meat on Choji's bones.
CHOJI: Naruto's
a healthier meal!
NARUTO: Just get in for
the sake of your pal!
CHOJI: Me?
Why don't you be
this guy's food?
NARUTO: We don't have
time to argue about this.
CHOJI: You're in it, too!
NARUTO: Aah!
Let's just run as fast as
we can and get out of here!
Next time, "A Limitless
Supply of Ninja Tools"!