[theme music]
NARUTO: Shikamaru!
Ino!
Choji!
-Well, well, well.
It's a drag, but we had to
come on Lady Hokage's orders.
-Grandma Tsunade sent you?
-You're going after Mizuki.
Is that right?
-Huh?
Yeah.
-So, uh, who are
the two big guys?
-They're Fujin and Raijin.
-Fujin and Raijin?
Who are they?
-Well, these guys may be
a little slow upstairs,
but their physical
strength, it's Herculean.
Even more powerful
than the Sannin.
-No way!
-It feels like he
might be right.
It's amazing.
They're able to hold
back my shadow possession
jutsu just by using brute force.
Great.
Looks like we've
gotten ourselves
into another annoying mess.
Naruto, leave
these idiots to us.
You keep going after Mizuki.
-We can handle 'em.
-No problem.
-Fine.
But be careful, OK?
These guys are crazy.
Like a couple of deranged
monsters or something.
-Monsters.
Yeah, I can see that.
Naruto!
Just go!
-All right!
Thanks, you guys!
-We better hurry, Naruto.
-Hey.
Your opponents
are over here now.
-You little [inaudible].
How dare you treat my
brother and I like this?
-There's no way you're
gonna leave here alive!
-Oh yeah?
I wouldn't bet on that.
Choji.
Ino.
Let's hurry up and take
care of these chumps.
-Mm-hm.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
A New Formation!
Ino Shika Cho!
-Mizuki!
Come back!
[wicked laughter]
MIZUKI: Looks like I get to
have a little fun, old friend.
-That way.
Mizuki!
Show yourself!
What?
What's happening?
Some sort of genjutsu.
Release.
First a genjutsu,
then that thing.
He's got some talent.
On top of that, he times
his jutsu superbly.
If I'm not careful, I could
be in a lot of trouble here.
I had no idea he had such
skillful command of high level
jutsu.
Mizuki--
[laughter]
-Nicely done.
You figured out my
puppet wasn't real.
Still, I wonder how long you
can last playing my game, Iruka.
-Where am I?
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
This isn't good.
They're resisting
the Shadow Possession
Jutsu using only
physical strength.
-Shikamaru, let me have a try.
-Choji, don't!
Stop.
Their power is too much for you.
-I'm telling you, I
can hold this guy down!
While I do, take care
of the other one!
-I see.
Fine.
Ino, do it.
-Leave it to me!
Now, Ninja Art!
Mind Transfer Jutsu!
-Hey?
What's that look?
Big brother, what's wrong?
-He's all mine now.
-Gotcha.
All right, there.
Formation Ino
Shika Cho complete.
-Big brother--
what's the matter?
Big Brother!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Iruka-sensei, I'll
be there soon.
Please stay alive.
-What do you think, Iruka?
Like my jutsu?
For being self-taught,
I'm pretty good, aren't I?
IRUKA: I don't understand.
-Hm?
-You have this
astounding ability
to use such high level ninjutsu,
and yet you just waste it.
-There you go, lecturing me.
As always.
So weak.
So naive.
Ha!
Don't start preaching
your morals to me.
You fool!
I have 0 respect for
the likes of you!
In the Leaf village,
I hardened my heart
to carry out my missions.
But did it matter to
you and the others?
No matter how powerful
I became, no matter
how many enemies I took
down, didn't matter!
You people gave me
no respect at all.
Even when I was part of
a team, of my comrades
were all bound by
rules of morality.
-They're trying to get
the secret manuscript.
Back up Mizuki!
-Right.
-Hey.
Are you alright?
-I think so, but I
can't feel my leg.
-What do you think, Mizuki?
-It's no good.
He can't go on.
He's done.
-I see.
All right, then.
Let's withdraw.
Hurry!
-I'm coming.
It's unfortunate, but those who
are no use on the battlefield
only become dead
weight for the rest.
It may just be a minor
injury, but if you
aren't able to get up
and fight, you only
have yourself to blame.
I simply carried out
my mission to the end.
And despite that, you people
in the village, not one of you
showed me the
respect I deserved.
Why not?
Why couldn't one single person
acknowledge my strength?
Why, Iruka?
It's not fair when
you even acknowledge
that Nine-Tailed brat Naruto!
What about me?
-It's still not
too late, Mizuki.
If you pay for your
crimes, you can start anew.
The people of the village,
I promise they'll forgive--
-Don't make me laugh!
What gives you the right to
stand there and lecture me?
You're just the same
as the rest of them.
Treating me like I'm
not as good as you.
-Mizuki--
-That day.
Yes.
Everything began on that day.
[sigh]
-You know, no point
getting nervous like that.
-Mizuki.
-Tomorrow's the big day.
The Ninja Academy's
teacher recruitment exam.
-Yeah.
The suspense is killing me.
I'm so jealous of you.
Your scores are so
high, you'll probably
breeze right through
tomorrow's exam.
-I don't know about that.
Hey, in any case,
let's do our best.
-Yeah.
Oh no!
-Get down!
That was a close one, Iruka.
-Yeah.
Mizuki, thank you.
You saved me.
-Don't worry about it.
Now, let's get going.
-I did it.
I did it!
Mizuki!
MAN: Now, regarding Mizuki--
I say we adopt a wait
and see attitude.
MAN: Yes.
It's a shame, but I agree.
There are still many
questions about his mission
to recover the
secret manuscript,
and well, until
those are cleared up,
he shouldn't progress.
-According to the autopsy of the
fallen man, the cause of death
was suffocation.
And yet, in Mizuki and
the others' report,
they stated his leg injury
wasn't that serious.
-Yes.
I understand.
He's brilliant, but
he must be held back.
-Damn!
You see?
I was just carrying
out the mission
I was assigned to complete.
You've no idea how miserable my
life has been since that day.
Since then, I--
Don't you understand?
You don't know.
You have no idea!
I've been through so much pain,
and you've had it so easy.
Which one of us is
the true shinobi?
Let's find out, shall we?
Come, Iruka.
Come on in.
-Darn it.
-Mizuki, where are you hiding?
You don't have any intention
of changing your evil ways,
do you?
-Don't make me say the
same thing over and over.
-Then I'll bring this to an end.
It's sad, but--
-I could just cry.
You're making me smile, Iruka.
-Talk to me.
What's the matter, big bro?
All right!
You came back to
me, Fujin-- Huh?
What are you-- What?
What did you weaklings
do to my big brother?
-I hijacked his body, moron!
Whoa, what the heck?
-Huh?
-Big brother!
Wake up!
Snap out of it already!
-No.
He's just too strong.
Ino, are you OK?
-Well, I think so.
I feel-- I'm not OK!
My gorgeous face!
No!
-Women.
Give me a break.
[screaming]
-No.
Choji.
Choji!
-Aw, man.
-Are you OK, pal?
-Well, I'm not dead.
-Sorry.
Feels like I fell asleep.
-Hey.
Big brother.
You're all better now.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
Aw, what a drag.
I guess I gotta use this.
K, here we go.
Shadow Strangle Jutsu.
-Big brother.
-How dare you?
-We're getting closer
now, and Mizuki
may have set a trap for us.
Be careful with every step.
-Yeah, I kind of
figured he would.
MIZUKI: It was so enjoyable,
being locked behind bars.
The dank moldiness.
The unrelenting gloom.
Pitch black all year round.
That darkness made me stronger.
It's how I mastered techniques
an ordinary shinobi would never
have learned.
Even in these
shadows, I am still
able to sense your energy.
What's the matter?
Tuckered out already?
Now's not the time to lose
your concentration, Iruka.
This is fun.
I wanna make it last.
Let's take our time.
-All right.
My turn.
-Ino, wait.
If you use your mind
transfer technique,
my Strangle Jutsu is
just gonna hurt you, too.
-Hmph.
If you think are you're
the only one who's
learned a cool new technique,
Shikamaru, you can kiss my ass.
-Huh?
-Ninja Art, Mind
Destruction Jutsu!
-Hey, wha-- What is it?
Hey, Raijin!
Raijin!
What are you doing?
-Nice.
Not a bad move there.
-So glad you like it.
The new Ino collection.
-Almost there.
Ah.
That's it.
That building!
-All right.
Just a few mot steps
and we're there!
MIZUKI: Well, Iruka?
Have your eyes adjusted at all?
For guys like you who live
their lives in the light,
darkness can be a
bit of a problem.
-Come on.
Where is he?
-Hey, Iruka.
What were you saying
before about how
you were going to
bring this to an end?
Oh.
I see.
By bring this to an end, you
were talking about yourself.
[evil laughter]
-Almost.
Give them a little bit more.
-Yeah, Ino.
Hang in there.
-We got these guys.
-No way.
These idiots are so strong.
-Those jerks.
They don't stop.
I don't think I can
hold them back anymore.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): If we
release this jutsu right now,
all our work will
be for nothing.
Come on.
Think about the next move.
[grunting]
-Hang in there.
-Ino.
I've gotta do something.
-Why?
So they can knock you out again?
-Ino.
Just shut up and watch.
Even the chubby guy's got
some skills when he tries.
[scream]
-Here's my Partial
Expansion Jutsu!
Both hands!
[screaming]
-Choji.
-Well, I couldn't just sit back
and let you have all the fun,
could I, Ino?
That's right, suckers.
You're looking at the
number one handsome chubby
ninja in the land.
-You're amazing, Choji!
So cool!
-That's my Choji.
Brand new formation,
Ino Shika Cho complete.
-That's strange.
Mizuki-- I don't
sense his presence.
It's too quiet.
That's not it.
It's even deeper.
[heartbeat]
-Are those footsteps?
No.
They're not.
It sounds different
from footsteps.
Subtler.
Smaller.
More steady.
The sound-- of a paper bomb!
-Was that some kind of bomb?
-What happened in there?
-Iruka-sensei!
Iruka-sensei!
[theme music]
-I can't believe this.
What just happened?
Where's Iruka-sensei?
-His scent ends here.
The only thing we can do
now is search the vicinity.
-This whole place is destroyed.
No!
Iruka-sensei, I hope
you're still alive!
PAKKUN: Shh!
Keep your voice down, Naruto!
I think someone may
be coming this way.
NARUTO: Next time,
Orochimaru's Shadow!
[theme music]