-So, that's the Shukaku.
It's the first time
I've ever seen it.
-Go on.
Get out of here, will ya?
-But-- but Gaara-sensei.
-Get moving.
Gaara's only trying
to keep you safe.
Now get out while you can!
-All right.
-Oh, man.
That what I think it is?
-Yeah.
The transformation's begun.
-This is bad.
-Naruto!
-Hinata.
Sakura.
-Matsuri, you OK?
-Yeah.
But Gaara-sensei needs help.
-OK, I'll let you
look after her.
-What do you think
you're doing, Naruto?
You're badly hurt.
Stay out of it.
-I can't.
-Come on, you won't
last a minute.
At least let me patch you up.
[theme music]
TEMARI: Things are going
to get really ugly.
Really soon.
-I was afraid of that.
Sakura, will you hurry up?
It's not like we've got all
the time in the world, here.
-Right.
Got it.
OK, now hold your hands out.
-OK.
-What in the world's
going on there?
-What do you see?
What is it?
NEJI: Gaara appears
to be transforming
into some sort of half beast.
While his opponent's chakra
is increasing exponentially.
-That one called
himself Seimei, and said
he was the founder of
the Village of Artisans.
He said he'd been reborn
as the ultimate ninja tool.
-A lousy thief is what he is.
He's stealing Gaara's chakra.
-Come to think of it,
the enemy we faced
woere a similar sort of
armor, with the power
to absorb one's chakra.
-Hm.
Armor that feeds on chakra.
We must be very careful.
We can't just rush in.
-Yeah, but we
gotta do something.
-I never imagined I would
be fighting Shukaku himself.
But far from dreading the
battle, I'm delighted.
It will give me the
opportunity to prove that even
his power is no match for
the Village of Artisans'
ultimate ninja tool.
GAARA (VOICEOVER): What c
be that makes him so strong?
-I care more about
them than I do myself.
And I won't let
anyone hurt them.
That's why I won't ever give up.
I will stop you, even
if I have to kill you.
-But why-- why would you do
this for anyone but yourself?
-Because they saved
me from myself.
They rescued me
from my loneliness.
They were the first to
accept me for who I am.
Thy're my.
Friends.
-Well, love is
the heart's desire
to serve someone who
is precious to you.
To watch over them,
like my sister did.
GAARA (VOICEOVER): Love?
Is that the thing that
makes him so strong?
[groan]
-Gaara
-Look!
He's-- he's returning to normal.
-But how?
What happened?
-He stopped it.
He's using all his strength to
fight off the transformation.
-But why?
He'll need every
advantage he can
get if he's going
to beat that guy.
-That may be, but
even so, he's chosen
to depend on his own powers, not
that of the monster within him,
which he knows he can't control.
[laughter]
-So it was too much
for your chakra
to complete the
transformation, eh?
-If I'm to help my friends,
I must do it for myself.
On my own.
-You fool.
You're allowing your
emotions to guide you.
A shinobi must abandon
emotion if he's ever
to obtain ultimate power.
And power-- power is the
only truth in this world.
As you're about to find out.
It's over.
Your time is done, you
freak of the Sand Village.
Mm?
Why so cocky?
You have no more chakra.
In fact, I'm surprised
you have the strength
to hold that grin on your face.
-Yes, my chakra's
almost totally depleted.
But all the time I was
trapped in that cage,
do you think I was just sitting
on my hands doing nothing, huh?
-Meaning?
-Sand Tsunami!
-Ha.
It would appear that you've run
out of sand, as well as chakra.
-I'm Gaara of the Desert.
Wherever there's rock,
wherever there's earth,
I can make more sand.
[shout]
-SEIMEI: Kujaku
Hurricane Formation.
You have that much chakra left?
How unexpected.
On the other hand,
that means there's
that much more I can feed on.
-He's draining the
last of Gaara's chakra.
-Huh?
-Gaara-sensei!
-That does it!
NEJI: Just stay out of it!
-Stay out of it?
What are you talking about?
-Look, you'll only be
getting in the way.
And Gaara is stronger
than you think.
-Hope so.
[laughter]
GAARA: Extreme Tempered
Ultimate Attack, Shukaku's Pike!
-How?
How did you-- no!
It's impossible.
-You wouldn't understand.
You're only a ninja tool.
You turned your
back on being human.
-Ridiculous.
It can't be.
It can't be!
-Giant Sand Burial!
-All right!
-He did it!
Gaara-sensei beat him!
-He sure did!
Hey, Gaara!
-Gaara!
-He's all right.
He's just exhausted from having
to use so much of his chakra.
TEMARI: To think, he was able
to suppress Shukaku and do it
all on his own.
-Yeah.
-I will work hard, and connect
to the people of this village.
Watching Naruto Uzumaki
has brought me clarity.
Until I met him,
my ties to others
brought only pain and sorrow.
But he was always pushing
me to redefine those ties.
I think I finally understand
the suffering and sorrow,
and the joy.
These are feelings I can
share with those around me.
-I guess you finally found
someone who understands you,
didn't you?
-Huh?
What did you say?
-Oh, nothing at all.
-Hm?
-Would you look at that?
We go to all the trouble
of rushing to the rescue,
and it's all over.
-Heh.
It appears that Naruto's
coming along pretty well.
Not that he's not still an
inexperienced knucklehead.
KAKASHI: My, you
are hard to please.
JIRAIYA: You know it.
-Huh?
Gah!
Pervy Sage?
-Ah.
Long time no see, Naruto.
-Don't you give me that long
time no see stuff, old man!
You were supposed to be
supervising my training,
teaching me everything you
know, making me your protege!
What happened to that?
Where have you
been all this time?
-Oh, well, I've had a lot to do.
Been busy with my research.
-Yeah, yeah, spying
on pretty women
for those stupid books of yours.
-Stupid, huh?
Anyway, it just so happens
you're way off base.
I was gathering as
much information
as I could on the Akatsuki.
-Akatsuki?
-Yes.
I have a pretty good
idea what they're up to.
I estimate we have about two
years before they're really
ready to make their move, which
means I have that much time
to try and make a
real ninja out of you.
You ready for some
serious training?
-Heh.
I've been ready for
months, old man.
TEMARI: We owe you one.
SHIKAMARU: Aw, skip it.
We're just returning the favor
that you guys did for us.
Next time you'll owe us one.
-Well, at least this time
you didn't get all choked up.
That's an improvement.
-Sheesh, women.
You always gotta
get the last dig in.
-What about him?
-Huh?
-Oh, you mean Naruto?
He leaves the
village this morning
to begin his training
with Jiraiya.
KANKURO: Jiraiya?
One of the Sannin?
-Yeah.
It's going to be such a drag.
When he gets back,
he'll be stronger
and more obnoxious than ever.
-Goodbye.
-See ya later.
-Yeah.
See ya.
-Will you please tell
Naruto something?
-Huh?
-Tell him that thanks
to him, I finally
understand what Gaara
was trying to tell me.
-Huh?
-Thank him for making me
see the value of real effort
and dedication.
-Terrific.
Another Naruto fan.
-Well, guess that about does it.
TSUNADE: About the mission
to the Village of Artisans.
I've read the report.
Maybe not a perfect 10, but
impressive, nonetheless.
-Thanks, but I need
more experience--
-You bet you do.
And that's why I'm going to be
assigning a lot more missions
to you, to build
up your experience.
So get ready to
really apply yourself.
-Huh?
Forgive me, Lady
Tsunade, but that
sounds like a whole lot of work.
-Phew.
-Uh, Sakura?
You got a minute?
-Huh?
Ino?
What's up?
Something wrong?
-See, it's like this.
I've been wondering about
something for a while now.
It suddenly became clear
to me on our last mission.
I can't do it anymore.
Not like this, anyway.
-Ino.
-I saw how important your
job was to the mission.
The way everyone
depended on you.
I finally realized, I want
to be a medical ninja.
I know the training will be
tough, but I'm a quick study,
and I'll really buckle
down and work hard.
You know I will.
So I'm asking if you'll talk
to Lady Tsunade about it.
Sure.
-Do you mean it?
-But you know what
this means, don't you?
If you really go
through with this,
it means you're my little
protege from now on.
-Huh?
Your little what?
-It's a fancy word for flunky.
Someone you boss around.
Because I'm going
to be your boss.
Yeah.
Boss.
Can you handle it?
Man, I can't wait.
I've always wanted a
little protege of my own.
But I warn you, I'm
gonna work you hard.
-That's what you think!
Just wait, I'm gonna
leave you in the dust!
-If anything will be in the
dust, it'll be your ugly face!
-Yeah, yeah!
You and your big forehead!
-Why me?
It's not fair, you know?
-What are you talking about?
-Why was I the
only one who didn't
get to go on that mission?
-But you were otherwise
engaged, Tenten.
You were with another squad.
-Everyone went except me!
-She seems a little upset.
-It's hard being the only one
who's not part of the team.
-Yeah, and speaking
of which, Naruto's
leaving us to go train.
-Yeah, I heard.
And I heard Jiraiya's
going to be his teacher.
-You heard right.
That little jerk's just
going to get stronger.
-Grr.
-Things will be
different around here.
Quieter.
-Don't ask me why,
but I can't help
feeling just a little bit sad.
ROCK LEE: No!
There is no time to be sad.
If I am to keep up with Naruto,
I must train harder than ever.
100 times harder, if I must.
But I will be ready, when
he comes back to us one day.
-Gotcha!
-Lee's right.
We must use this time wisely.
We must use each other,
learn from each other
in order to get stronger.
That's teamwork.
That's friendship.
-Hear that?
Sounds like we've got our
work cut out for us, Akamaru.
-Arf! Arf!
-I'm ready!
-Lee, are you OK?
-Oh, yeah.
Just swell.
-Right.
That's enough for today, Hinata.
-Huh?
But we didn't--
-It's almost time for
him to be on his way.
We won't be seeing
him again for a while.
IRUKA: Well, well.
You've got quite a
journey ahead of you.
NARUTO: Yup.
-Hey, listen up.
You keep focused out there.
No goofin' off, all right?
-Focus is my middle
name, Sensei.
-All right.
Time to hit the road, Naruto.
-OK!
Thanks for the
ramen, Iruka-sensei.
I'll pay you back.
In fact, when I'm Hokage,
I'll buy you lunch.
IRUKA: When you're--
IRUKA (VOICEOVER):
Good luck, Naruto.
-Just you watch.
-Sometime this
year would be nice.
Let's go!
-Huh?
OK, OK, I'm coming!
Wait up!
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
I'm going to have
to work hard to keep
up with you, Naruto.
But I'll do it.
[theme music]
NARRATOR: It's been two
years since they left.
The day of battle draws near.
The hunters have closed
in on their prey.
Time won't stand still
for one young boy.
The Akatsuki are on the
move, and Orochimaru
is putting the finishing touches
on his forbidden reanimation
jutsu.
The time has come to
regain what was lost.
The boy must do
battle once again.
He must ride the winds
of fate, and endure.
Next time, Homecoming.