[music playing]
[theme music]
-That's Naruto.
What is this power?
And what was that red chakra?
Is he some kind of monster?
I've had enough of this.
What the heck are you?
-I'm your friend.
That's why I'm telling you.
I'm not going to let
the likes of Orochimaru
get a hold of you.
And if you won't
listen to reason,
then I'll break every
bone in your body.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): Fire Style.
Fire Ball Jutsu.
-Now let's go.
Enough is enough.
Snap out of it already.
If you don't come
to your senses,
then I'm just going to have
to break all your bones
and drag you back
to the village.
So get up, Sasuke.
-Just shut up for once.
What the heck do
you know about it?
It's not like you ever had
a family in the first place.
You were on your own
right from the beginning.
What makes you think you
know anything about it, huh?
I'm suffering now,
because I had those ties.
How on earth could you
possibly understand
what it feels like
to lose all that?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): It's true.
I have no idea what it's like
having parents or a brother.
IRUKA: It's my treat today.
Eat as much as you want.
-All right.
Whenever I'm with
Iruka Sensei, I wonder.
-(BOTH) Down the hatch.
-First of all, a ninja's
got to have sustenance.
-Hey, take it easy.
Don't wolf it down so fast.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
I wonder if that's
what it feels like
to have a father.
And when I'm with you--
whatever, you moron.
-What the heck is your
problem, you loser?
-There's no way I'm
going to lose to you.
-Yeah.
Keep talking.
[laughing] Gotcha.
-Just get off me.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
I wonder if this
is what it feels like
to have a brother.
-Why, Naruto?
Why would you go so far for me?
NARUTO: Because this
is the first time
I've ever had a bond like this.
That's why I'll do
anything I can to stop you.
-It's too late, Naruto.
It's just too late.
I can't turn back.
Come, Naruto.
If that's how it is, I'll
just have to sever that bond.
-Severe it just like that, huh.
Then why do you even bother
wearing that headband anymore?
-I'll admit it.
You're definitely strong.
It's because you know the
pain that solitude brings,
just as I do.
It's that very pain that
makes you and I stronger,
Naruto, which means if I
can just break that bond.
I'll be able to achieve
even greater strength.
It's time you and I
had this out as equals.
But you're still not
going to be able to lay
even a single scratch
on my forehead.
I know that hasn't
changed at least.
-Fine.
Guess there's no point
in talking anymore.
Sasuke.
-Enough.
No more words.
From here on out, we
stick to fighting.
Come.
I can see.
His moves that were too fast for
me before, I can see them now.
I can see.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
His moves, they're
totally different from
just a few moments ago.
Not like it matters.
I don't care what his deal is.
I can't afford to lose here.
-It must be the influence
of the Curse Mark again.
With every step, every
subtle shift in his momentum,
the image of his next move
becomes vividly clear.
As long I have
these eyes, I don't
need to expend any chakra.
The Curse Mark would
eat up too much of it.
With vision like
this, I can make out
the image of Naruto's every
move before it happens
and time my attacks accordingly.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
This isn't good.
He's totally reading
my movements.
What do I do?
-Oh there you are?
Are you sure it's this way?
-Yep.
We better pick up the pace.
I'm getting a bad
feeling about this.
NARUTO: Sasuke!
SASUKE: Fire Style!
Dragon Flame Jutsu!
-(HOARSELY) Sasuke.
-It's too late, Naruto.
It's too late now.
Naruto!
[gagging]
-You runt.
You really are weak.
[laughing]
You better be grateful to me and
to your beloved Fourth Hokage,
who sealed me inside
a twerp like you.
-Wha-- What is--
What was that?
I can still read his
movements, but this chakra,
it's-- it's almost like
it has a mind of its own.
Even my eyes can't follow it.
That red aura, that's
no ordinary chakra.
-I know that he's the
one you're really after.
-You're right.
Naruto is the prize that
the Akatsuki are after.
And we will have him.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): I see.
So you have some kind
of special power then.
I think I understand now.
Fire Style.
Fire Ball Jutsu!
That chakra is protecting him.
Calm down.
As long as I keep my
distance, I'll be fine.
What is he?
All I can do is dodge.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): Please
just let me make it in time.
[laughing]
-Oh well, no getting
around it, I guess.
Once I go ahead and let
this power take over, I--
I'm not all that sure
what'll happen to me in end,
but you're not leaving me a
lot of choice here, Naruto.
There's no question
that you're special.
Unfortunately, you're not
quite as special as I am.
[laughing]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Sasuke.
[theme music]
NARUTO: My whole body
hurts, and on top of that,
I've lost all feeling
in my left arm.
It looks like this power isn't
going to last me forever.
But it doesn't matter.
I can't give up.
This next blow will be the last.
Next time, "The End of Tears."
[theme music]