[music playing]
[theme music]
KUNIHISA: Look, daddy.
Look at this marble.
-Hmm?
What about it, son?
KUNIHISA: It's just as pretty
and sparkly as a diamond,
isn't it?
KUNIJIRO: Why so it is.
You're right.
KUNIHISA: But a
diamond's valuable.
And this is totally worthless.
Why is that?
-Uh.
-Life's funny, isn't it daddy?
NARUTO: Impossible celebrity
ninja art money style Jutsu.
What?
You really mean it?
No kidding?
-Will you calm down?
-OK.
Sorry about that.
You're right.
OK.
I'm fine now
-Oink.
-Uh.
--[clearing throat] This
is an important person.
And I could think of no one
better for the job than you.
-At last, I'm
finally going to get
a mission worthy of
my awesome abilities.
It's everything I've dreamed of,
being the escort of a real VIP.
-Will you shut up for
one second and listen?
--[screaming] Right,
sorry, gotcha.
-Do you want to the details
of your mission or not?
Shizune?
-Yes, milady.
TSUNADE: The client's name
is Kunijiro, an old friend.
He started with nothing,
and made himself
into one of the richest and
most successful rare gem dealers
around.
-You're saying this
guy's a friend of yours.
-That's right.
But he is not your assignment.
Your mission is to
look after his only son
and heir, Kunihisa.
-(THINKING) The heir
to a rare gem fortune.
KUNIHISA: Daddy?
-Hmm?
-Are they all real?
-Why of course
they are, Kunihisa.
KUNIHISA: And that, and
that, and that, and that?
KUNIJIRO: Yes, Kuni-wooni.
They're all real.
-I've never seen
so many ninja ever!
-Ah!
Right!
OK, I'm all fired
up and ready to go!
I accept the mission.
And I won't let you down.
I promise.
So when do we get started?
Where is he?
[knocking]
-Huh?
TSUNADE: Come in.
-Ninja!
-Whoa, what are you doing?
-Ninja, ninja, ninja, ninja!
You're a ninja?
-I don't really like the
way you asked that question.
KUNIJIRO: So you're the one.
-Huh?
-You really don't mind if my
little boy tags along with you,
and plays ninja for a day?
Hmm?
Can't tell you
how grateful I am.
-Uh, did you say he wants
to play ninja for a day?
-It's an obsession.
He's wild about
everything ninja.
You should hear him--
ninja, ninja all day long.
[laughing]
-What is this?
I thought I was escorting
an important VIP.
-Well that's your problem.
I never told you it was an
important VIP, now did I?
-What a dirty, rotten trick.
TSUNADE: That's enough, Naruto.
Your mission is to
play ninja for a day.
-What the?
This is so not fair.
-What's more, on
top of that, you
have your regular
missions to perform.
-What's going on, grandma?
Why are you doing this to me?
Why?
I've got to clean the
pond, repair the bridge,
take care of a feral pig.
Oh boy.
-[giggling]
-(THINKING) Now I get to
add babysitting to my list
of deranked missions.
-When do we start playing ninja?
-Watch closely, Kunihisa.
I'll show you a little trick
we ninja know how to do.
-Ah!
[clapping] Awesome,
Naruto, awesome.
--[chuckling] But being a ninja
isn't always fun and games.
So if you want to be
a ninja for a day,
help me clean up this pond.
-OK, I will.
-Oh, but one thing.
This pond is tricky.
If you step in the
wrong spot, you
can get stuck,
and never get out.
So stay on the bank, all right?
KUNIHISA: Oops.
Too late.
-Huh?
-What are we going to do?
-Hey, hi, Naruto!
-[screaming] Are you nuts?
What are you doing in there?
OK, OK, don't move.
Stay right where you are.
I'll come and get you out.
-Don't worry.
I can handle it.
-What do you mean
you can handle it?
-I've got some
ninjutsu of my own.
-Some ninjutsu?
-His father's going to kill us!
His father's going to kill us!
-Ah.
Ah!
Alligator, snapping turtle,
bunny ears, ninja art.
Come and help me!
-Ah!
[shouting]
-See what I mean, Naruto?
What's going on?
What are you guys
doing down there?
I'll have to increase
the power of my ninjutsu.
-Serve them right if I just
left them all here to drown.
So tell me, Kunihisa.
-Huh?
-Who are the big
goons in the suits.
-Never mind them.
They're just some people my
daddy hired to look after me,
and stuff like that,
like if I get in trouble,
or I want something.
-Uh huh.
-Here, want to see an example?
Fetch.
See?
-You have got to be kidding.
-Ugh.
Are you sure it's safe?
NARUTO: Yeah, it's safe.
It's safe.
-Are you positively
sure it's safe?
-I'm standing on it, aren't I?
Come on.
It's OK.
Trust me.
-Cross your heart,
and hope to to die?
-I said it's safe.
Now knock it off
and get out here.
-OK, OK.
But first I'm just
going to make sure.
Ninja art substitution Jutsu!
[laughing]
-Are you satisfied?
Now come on.
Let's go.
-Hmm.
Yeah, but what if my weight's
enough to make it break?
Let's just try a few more.
Ha!
-Whoa.
-I'm still not convinced!
Once more.
Catch!
-Money!
-Huh?
[screaming]
-So it wasn't safe.
[moaning]
-See what you did?
What was that?
-Uh, you should be happy
I wasn't on the bridge
when it broke.
-Why you crazy little--
-Gentlemen, you
deserve a nice big tip.
There you go.
-Hey.
Cut it out, will you?
Stop that.
THUG: That kid's
throwing around money
like it's going out of style.
THUG: Yeah.
And he's only got a
single genny with him.
What do you say?
Wanna make some money?
-Yeah.
-So what's next?
-I have to deal with
a feral pig that's
been bothering some farmers.
-No problem.
I'll get my ninjutsu
ready. [giggling]
-What the heck's that?
That thing's a pig?
-[snarling]
-It's the size of an elephant.
Stay back.
Shadow Call Jutsu!
-Whoa, amazing.
-[roaring]
-Naruto!
OK, piggie.
Now you deal with me!
-No, stay away from that thing.
It's too big.
You don't know
what you're doing!
-Ha!
Here's my cash clone Jutsu.
-Did he say cash clone Jutsu?
-[giggling]
-Huh?
-Listen up, you overgrown ham.
I'm going to see to it that
you never bother anyone again.
Attack!
Give it to him.
Let him have it.
That's the way.
Go on.
Get out of here.
You're not even
good for sausages,
you big fat tub of lard.
-[snarling]
-[gulp]
-[growling]
-Wait, it's all his fault.
He made me.
-Huh?
-He made me do it.
I, I don't even eat pork.
-[snarling]
-Whoa.
Now just hold on.
That's not true.
Ah!
You're going to believe
that kid instead of me?
[screaming]
-You're a brave ninja.
-Why you, you, of
all the selfish,
spoiled, rotten little kids.
-I bed you don't
have a lot of money.
Am I right?
I've found that poor people tend
to lose their tempers a lot.
-Gah!
-Go on, help
yourself, however much
it takes to put you
in a good mood again.
-Get it out of here.
I told you before
to stop doing that.
-Why?
NARUTO: You can't just buy
your way out of everything.
There are times when
money won't work,
when you've got to
do it on your own.
--[sigh] I suppose if I
didn't have any money,
I'd believe that too.
-Man, are you like
this all the time?
How do you even make friends
with an attitude like that?
-How do you think?
It's easy.
-Huh?
So what you're saying is
that you buy your friends?
-Sure.
And when I lose one,
I just buy another.
-But, Kunihisa?
-That's why I didn't want a
ninja from a little village.
You'll never understand.
You're too poor and stupid.
-Wait, Master Kunihisa,
where are you going?
Don't run off.
[stomach growling]
-Hmm.
I guess all that
running made me hungry.
Go find me some lunch, will you?
-But sir, there are no
restaurants around here.
-Fine.
Just a snack, then.
-I'm sorry.
But look around you, sir.
There's nothing here.
-Well, what good are you then?
This is exactly why
I hate the country.
[stomach growling]
-Uh, oh, that stupid Naruto.
[sniffing] What is that?
-Wait, sir, wait.
-Ooh, look, someone's
having fish for lunch.
I'm sure they won't mind.
-Look at the way he
swallowed that bait.
He's as dumb as he is rich.
-Yeah.
-Whoa!
-Huh?
What's going on?
-Man, you are one high
maintenance kid, aren't you?
You don't know
how close you came
to having those
two goons grab you.
-Oh, it was just another
kidnapping attempt, that's all.
-Huh?
Just another wh--
-It happens all the time,
because I'm stinking rich.
-All the time?
How often is that?
-Oh, a lot.
Anyway, do you know where
there's a store around here?
I'm going to need
more to eat than this?
-Listen to you.
You've got it stuck in
your head that money's
going to solve everything.
Well, all right then.
Just watch this.
-Oh, wow.
That was awesome, Naruto.
-Ha, see that, that's something
all the money in the world
can't buy you.
It's something you've
got to earn on your own.
-Not even all the
money in the world?
-Dirty little rat, sneaking up
on us from behind like that.
Next time, I'll wring his neck.
-Hey, take it easy.
We've got to have a plan.
We'll just get clobbered again.
-You got something in mind?
-It's right there
in front of is.
-It is?
-Watch it closely.
Anticipate its movements.
Then try to hit it
right when it reaches
the high point of its jump.
-There!
Aw.
-That's OK.
You were close.
-Let me try one more time, OK?
Don't worry about the knife.
I'll go get it.
-Master Kunihisa,
watch your step.
It's deep.
BODYGUARD: Please
be careful, sir.
KUNIHISA: I know.
I know.
I'm not a child.
Give me a break.
Oh, where did it go?
-I'm sure it's in this area.
-Ah!
--[evil chuckle] Oh, you
don't get off that easy.
-What are my men doing?
-We hired their services
with some of that money
you were throwing around.
-They're not your men anymore.
They're with us now.
-Listen, you guys.
I can pay you more.
Whatever those kidnappers are
paying you, I'll double it.
Uh, what the?
Don't tell me.
-Hmm.
THUG: What's the matter?
You finally run out of cash?
-So what's it going
to be you two?
Gonna come on over to our side?
-Why don't you come and get it?
Cash in advance.
-Ha, you're wasting your time.
They've been with me forever.
They'd never betray
me for a few-- ah!
-Never liked working
for you anyway,
you spoiled little brat.
-You, you guys are
going to be sorry.
-[evil laughter]
-Stop it!
Let me go!
-Shut up, and stop
squirming, kid.
Don't make this any
harder than it has to be.
-Whoa!
-Ah!
[whimpiring]
-Kunihisa, are you OK?
-Naruto, I thought-- I didn't--
-Never mind.
It's OK.
-Hey, you, we'll pay
you double whatever
you're getting for this mission.
Just hand over the brat to us.
What do you say?
-Yeah, and don't worry.
He'll be fine.
It's not like we're
going to hurt him,
or anything, just
hold him for ransom.
So, do we have ourselves a deal?
What's the matter?
That not enough?
Look, we'll triple it.
Take it.
-Naruto?
-Hurry up.
Get on my back.
-OK.
-What, is that still not enough?
Here, look, you can have it all.
Take it.
-You guys just don't get it.
-Huh?
-You'll never learn
that there are
some things in life
you just can't buy.
-Oh yeah?
Get him!
Go on!
-Just keep hanging on
tight, no matter what.
-OK.
-(THINKING) Darn it.
I can't outrun them for
long with him on my back.
-Oh, I can't even
see the bottom.
-Hiya!
Now hurry up.
You go over first, OK?
-What?
Go over?
Whoa. [whimpering]
-There they are!
Get them!
Yeah!
-What are you waiting for,
an engraved invitation?
Hurry up and jump.
-I c-c-can't.
I'm sc-cared, Naruto.
-You'll be fine.
Just go on!
-I can't.
-[evil laughter]
-Stay back.
-Get him.
-Yah!
-Naruto?
[evil laugh, cracking knuckles]
-You're coming
with me, pipsqueak.
-Go on, Kunihisa.
-I'm afraid.
-You can do it.
Stop thinking about it.
You can do it.
--[evil laugh] You're
staying right there.
-Whoa!
-Way to go!
You did it!
-Big brother, are you all right?
-[screaming]
-Hey, are you OK?
-Ow!
[wailing]
-I'll finish off these
guys, and come on over.
You wait there.
-Right.
I'll wait here.
Oh?
Naruto!
Hurry up!
The cliff's collapsing.
-What is this?
You guys planning on
sitting there all day?
Shadow Call Jutsu!
-Whoa!
-(THINKING) What should I do?
-There are times when
money won't work,
when you've got to
do it on your own.
-(THINKING) Do it on my own.
-That's something all the money
in the wold can't buy you.
It's something you've
got to earn on your own.
-(THINKING) I can't
buy this with money.
I gotta do it on my own.
I can do it.
I can do it!
-(THINKING) Looks like I
came up one step short.
-Naruto!
-Kunihisa!
-No!
You can do it.
-We did it!
-All right!
-I can't say it was much fun.
And I'm still scared.
But at least I did it!
--[laughing] Man, you should
see your face right now.
-Yeah, I bet it looks
pretty silly, huh?
-Hey, Kunihisa?
-Yeah?
-Great job.
You saved my life.
-[gasp] [sobbing] Naruto!
-Hey, whoa, watch it!
You're dripping on me.
-I'm sorry.
I can't help it.
-I'm drowning here.
Use a hankie or
something, please?
Well, guess this is goodbye.
KUNIHISA: Next time,
you can come play ninja
for a day at my house.
-You bet.
Got yourself a deal.
-You did a fine job of
looking after my son.
You have my thanks.
-It was nothing. [chuckling]
-Goodbye, milady.
-See you soon.
KUNIHISA: Look, daddy, look.
KUNIJIRO: What is it, son?
KUNIHISA: See how it
sparkles in the sun?
-All that glitters is not gold.
It's just a marble.
It has no value.
KUNIHISA: Not in money, no.
But, daddy?
-Hmm?
-Maybe it has a
different kind of value,
just because it's pretty.
[giggling]
[music playing]
NARUTO: Trecheron, really?
Now that's my kind of mission.
I have my doubts.
You haven't been doing too
well on your missions lately.
NARUTO: Don't worry.
Anyway, we've got a map.
What could go wrong?
With you, plenty.
I'm warning you, Naruto.
NARUTO: Aw, come on.
It'll be a cinch.
If you fail this mission--
NARUTO: Yeah, I know.
I know.
It's back to the
academy for you.
NARUTO: Yeah, yeah I know.
I-- what?
Next time, the
treasure hunt is on.
[music playing]