[theme music]
[wailing]
RAIGA: Why?
He was such a good man.
Truly.
Why did he have
to be taken away?
Sorrow.
Such sorrow.
[sobbing] I remember
a day you showed me
one of your most
prized possessions.
[muffled screaming]
-With a twinkle in
your eye, you told me
how it had once
belonged to your father.
It was a beautiful piece.
A gorgeous pipebox.
No wonder you were
so proud of it.
Yet when I ripped
it from your hands
and smashed it to the ground,
all you did was laugh.
And when we booted you in
the ribs and tossed you in
you only smiled.
It was such a lovely smile.
Beautiful!
-Hold it in, Rokusuke.
They'll be gone in a minute.
This is our chance
to sneak away.
We've only got one shot.
-I know.
But Kanpachi--
-For our people, we
can't just sit idly by.
That village is our only hope.
We've no choice.
-Ah.
Nothing like a good funeral!
I can't wait till the next one.
[sigh]
RANMARU: One, two, three.
Another three have gotten away.
RAIGA: One more funeral
to look forward to.
[screaming]
-Where am I?
-The Hidden Leaf Village.
-Who are you?
-Naruto Uzumaki.
And I'm right in the
middle of some training.
-The Hidden Leaf?
Huh?
Hey, You OK?
Hang in there, buddy.
I gotcha.
Guess I can chalk this up
under training as well.
[grunting]
-I could do better.
ANKO: Lord Chichiasu
of the Land of Swamps
arrived at his destination
without a hitch.
-Good to know.
-Hey!
Tsunade was eating that!
[eating sounds]
-Man, the dumplings in
this village can't be beat.
-Anko, you just
took the last one.
-Mission accomplished, my lady.
I laid the smackdown on the
dastardly pirates of the Kitani
Channel with my
frenzied fists of love!
If they take this opportunity
to start their lives anew,
then the beautiful green
beast of the Leaf Village
will shed a tear!
[laughter]
-You know what I'm saying?
-I have something I want
to put your squad on.
-Huh?
[sigh]
--We're stretched
thin enough as it is.
And yet somehow Naruto
has brought in more work.
-And remember, Guy.
One of our clients
already asked for you
specifically for that
one S-rank mission.
He'll have to set out today if
he wants to make it on time.
-They won't need Guy then.
-The day has finally come.
-Your kids will go.
Alone.
Neji, Tenten, and Lee.
-You won't regret this either.
My students will nail this one.
Believe you me.
-Also Naruto is going with them.
-What's that about?
Listen.
I love those kids more than
anything in this world,
but I'm telling you
that they can handle it!
Why can't they go alone?
-Look.
Just because.
All right?
[door opens and closes]
TSUNADE: Those men
Naruto rescued are here
to request our services.
They came all the way from
the Katabami gold mine,
one of the most abundant mines
in all the Land of Rivers.
But about six
months ago, a bunch
of goons calling themselves
the Kurosuke family
showed up and ran the
magistrate out of town.
They've taken over their
village and apparently are
killing people left and right.
-That is unforgivable.
TSUNADE: Once these men have
regained their strength,
your objective is to escort
them back to the Katabami Mine
And take out this
Kurosuke Family.
A simple mission really.
They're probably just a pack
of money-grubbing hoodlums.
-So what am I doing here?
It sounds like a chimp
could do this mission.
-Who the heck do
you think you are?
-Come on, grandma.
I've got enough on my plate now.
With training and
looking for Sasuke--
-You think you get to call
the shots around here,
you pipsqueak?
You're a genin.
You'll take whatever
mission I give you!
I'll send you back
to the Academy
so fast you head'll spin.
[grumble]
-Neji Hyuga!
-Yes.
-You're team leader!
It'll be good training for you
trying to tame the untameable.
-I'd rather not.
But I'll give it a go.
-I'll be out training
when you need me.
The old bat.
-Naruto.
-Um-- sorry about that.
They have no manners, you know?
[awkward laughing]
-Uh-- wait up, you guys.
[groaning]
-Ow!
-Those lousy little brats!
What the heck do they think
I'm running here anyway?
GUY: Milady, if I may.
-What is it?
-The Kurosuke Family.
What did you say their
boss's name was again?
-Raiga.
-As I thought.
-What do you mean?
-Well, I heard a
rumor about him when
I was in the field one time.
-Huh?
-What kind of rumor?
-Still no sign of
Pervy Sage, and now I'm
stuck with some
lame-ass mission.
Man, this bites!
Hey!
Sakura!
-Naruto.
-What're you doing out here?
Huh?
A bird?
-Yeah.
I found it yesterday and I've
been trying to treat it but--
-Wow.
Sakura, that's amazing!
-But the poor little thing.
It got separated
from its friends.
-Naruto.
Uh-- sorry.
Am I intruding?
-Well, what does it look like?
-No, Lee.
Hold fast.
You must not turn away.
In our youth with must
always seize the moment.
Hey, Sakura.
How are you today?
-I'm great, Lee.
-What do you want already?
-A word with you, actually.
-Huh?
-See you later, Sakura.
-Could have been worse.
Least it wasn't a desk.
-You're hilarious,
you know that?
NARUTO: Say what?
The Kurosuke boss is
one of the Seven Ninja
Swordsmen of the Mist?
-That is right.
Guy-sensei filled me in.
And if he says it,
you know it is true.
-So who are these
sword dudes anyway?
-Naruto!
You said you fought
in the Land of Waves
on one of your missions.
Remember?
Back then.
-Oh yeah!
Zabuza.
And?
-And let us not forget that man
our senseis fought together--
Kisame Hoshigaki.
Word around the village is
you also a run-in with him.
-Oh right.
That guy.
I forgot about him.
-Both men hailed from
the Land of Mist,
and both are former members
of the Seven Ninja Swordsmen
as well.
And Kisame had a partner.
He was not alone.
-Ah.
Yeah.
That Itachi guy.
And?
-Do you not get it yet?
This Raiga, if he is indeed one
of the Seven Ninja Swordsmen,
will probably have some
connection to Itachi
who seems to be in
league with Kisame now.
-Oh.
And?
-And who is Itachi linked to?
-Oh!
I know!
It's Sasuke!
-That is right, Naruto!
That gold mine is
the perfect place
to pick up Sasuke's trail again.
Am I right?
-Yeah.
I don't know.
If Guy told you then--
-Hey!
Do not disparage
my sensei, Naruto.
That info is totally reliable.
110%.
-Mhm.
NEJI: All right.
We keep a close
eye on our friends
here as we head
for Katabami, then
deal with the Kurosuke
Family once we arrive.
LEE: There is a shop that is
very close to that village.
It can be our home base.
-Why do you know about
a shop out there.
-Sorry.
That is a surprise
for the journey.
-We're just waiting on
Naruto then, naturally.
-Well this whole mission is
based on info from Guy-sensei.
Maybe Naruto just didn't buy it.
-That is not true, Tenten.
He will definitely be here.
Naruto knows Guy-sensei's
intel is rock solid.
-Terrific.
-Huh?
-Here I am!
So, we're all here.
Let's hit the road, everybody.
-That's not your call.
-Let's do it!
Hey-- uh-- which way is it?
-Calm down, Rokusuke.
It's gonna be OK.
These shinobi will
save our village.
-Heh heh.
Nothing like a little
post-meal training.
I will no allow myself to lose!
Hiya!
-Well, I'm not losing either.
[laughter]
-How long do you ninja
plan on resting here?
-Huh?
-We need to keep moving if
we want to save Kanpachi.
-Have you gone mad?
Come on.
You know how long he's
been in that coffin.
It's hard but--
-This grogginess-- I remember.
Must be close.
Grogginess?
Are you sleepwalking right now?
-Do not worry.
I ran a marathon here one time.
It was three days and I slept
through the whole thing.
-You're pulling my leg.
-No.
It is true.
Guy-sensei and I
raced one another.
My body aches just
thinking about it.
I am so sleepy.
-Hey, uh-- bushy brow.
Are you sure you're OK?
-Hah.
I almost forgot how thick the
scent of curry is around here.
It is so spicy.
-Curry?
Oh yeah.
-I was right!
It is just up ahead!
The Curry Shop of Life!
LEE: Grandma Sansho!
-Wait.
Is that?
Well, goodness me!
LEE: Long time no see!
-Oh, my, my, my, my!
-I told you I would
return one day!
-So, um-- this is
Lee's shop then?
-Hm.
-That mountain is the
Katabami gold mine.
-Huh?
-Grandma Sansho's curry
saved my life back then.
NARUTO: Huh?
You just mean it's
good though, right?
-No.
It obviously saved my life.
I am in its debt.
This was back in the days when
I had just become a genin.
Guy-sensei had brought
me out to these parts
to introduce a new
training regimen.
-Oh.
Of course.
I remember.
That brings me back.
-Come on, Lee.
Give it your all.
[panting]
-Oh, my.
-Ah, hey.
Grandma Sansho, how'd you do?
-Why, there're back again.
-Huh?
-Those gentlemen are
running in their sleep!
-Karashi, if you had the kind
of energy those boys have,
you'd never lose to those
rotten bullies again.
[footsteps]
-Oh dear.
Me and my big mouth.
-Huh?
GRANDMA: Gracious.
This is the third day.
And they've never
stopped running.
Ah!
One of them's down!
-Easy now.
Easy.
[snoring]
-I wonder if he's hungry.
Yeah Oh.
What a pickle.
He still won't wake up.
Perhaps it needs
a bit more spice.
Karashi.
-I've never seen
anyone work so hard.
-I see.
So you want to help this
young man as well, eh?
[scream]
LEE: This is the
courage of life.
Now, Grandma Sansho
went to all the trouble
of making us this curry.
So let us dig in!
I cannot wait!
Delicious!
This is just so delectable!
Mm!
A myriad of flavors!
The spices are
blended to perfection.
Plus, whatever these little hard
chunks are, they're amazing!
[screaming]
LEE: So good.
Oh, by the way, where's
Karashi right now?
Is he out?
-Oh.
Well, the boy was very
moved by your work ethic
and began attacking life
with quite a new vigor.
So much, in fact, that he left
the shop and set out for town.
I shouldn't have
pushed him so much.
Always telling him to be strong.
I'm going to be a man, he said.
Part of the Kurosuke Family.
-Huh?
-Hm?
-Oh.
Please.
You mustn't worry yourself son.
I'm not blaming you.
-Too late now.
-I am responsible for this.
-Oh.
Dear me.
-Neji!
Request to incorporate
the rescue of Karashi
into our mission.
We will bring him back from
this road of evil he has taken!
NEJI: Very well.
We'll use the shop as
a base of operations,
and start scouting the village.
Then we can come up with a
strategy and make our move.
-Roger.
NEJI: You three had
better stay behind here.
If we face the
Kurosuke Family things
will definitely get dicey.
HACHIDAI: This is terrible!
Rokusuke!
He's-- he's-- he's gone!
-He must have gone
into town alone.
The blasted fool!
-That spells trouble.
Neji, if those guys
find him then--
-Too late trying to map out a
strategy at this point, guys.
-We better get
straight to business.
-Right.
Let us get to business.
NEJI: Let's hurry.
ROKUSUKE (VOICEOVER):
Just hold on, Kanpachi.
I won't abandon you.
RANMARU: Someone is coming.
RAIGA: What a pity.
Seems we'll be holding
yet another funeral.
[theme music]
LEE: You should have
told me that day.
If you put enough care
into your cooking,
even a single serving of curry
can save a person's life.
With enough hard work
and effort nothing
is impossible, even
for someone like me.
I've always believed that.
You were far more admirable
when I first met you, Karashi.
And yet-- Next time--
A Lesson Learned.
The Iron Fist of Love.
[theme music]