[theme music]
-So you guys want to
tell us who you are?
-It appears that they
would rather fight.
TODOROKI (VOICEOVER): No.
I won't be fooled by you.
I won't.
--[panting] [metal noises]
[deep breaths] [yelling]
-Todoroki!
[slicing noise] [gasp]
-Stop it, Todoroki.
This isn't what your
mission's about.
You're supposed to get
him to the capital alive.
-Not this one.
He must pay for what he did.
-What are you talking about?
-Let him live?
No.
Not him!
He slaughtered them all.
My family!
My little brother!
-He did what?
Gantetsu murdered
your whole family?
-Yeah, five years ago.
TODOROKI: I witnessed
it with my own eyes.
[music playing]
-Fire!
-[gasp]
-This is terrible.
-Is anyone still inside?
-[grunt]
-No!
[grunt] Mother!
Father!
-[muffled screaming]
-Akio.
[breaking noises]
-Akio!
[screaming]
-[panting]
[clanking]
-Akio.
[music playing]
MAN: Todoroki,
I've learned who it
was that attacked your family.
TODOROKI: Who was it?
MAN: Bandits called
the Ninja Dropouts.
TODOROKI: Ninja Dropouts?
MAN: They're ruthless,
evil beyond words.
After they've robbed
their victims,
they massacre
everyone in the house.
TODOROKI: But why?
MAN: So that no witnesses
are left behind.
Your parents bodies
were recovered,
but the fire was so fierce
and Akio was so small.
There was no trace of him left.
I'm sorry, but you have to
let your little brother go.
TODOROKI: Impossible.
-[yelling]
TODOROKI: I can't.
I won't.
-Akio.
[yelling]
-The irony of it.
I can finally avenge
my family, make
him pay for what
he's done to us,
except that I must escort
him safely to the capital.
-Todoroki.
-I know where my duty lies.
I know it's my mission.
I should be satisfied that he'll
no doubt be sentenced to death,
but seeing him now
within reach, the calm
expression on his face.
The face of the man who
destroyed my family, who
took the life of
my little brother.
-Hmm?
Your brother?
You lost him?
-Now die Gantetsu.
[yelling]
-No.
-Out of my way!
-Stop it.
-He's a thug.
A monster who's taken the lives
of countless innocent people.
-Like you said, your mission
is to escort Gantetsu
to the capital.
-I don't care about that.
He took my little
brother away from me.
-We can't judge him, even
if he's as bad as you say.
We can't.
It's wrong.
-There's no one around.
Here in the forest,
no one would see.
-Don't even think like that.
-No one would ever need
to know what happened.
-Todoroki, stop.
I'm around.
I'll see.
-No one will ever know.
-Don't do this.
-As long as you keep
your mouth shut.
Better if you weren't
even here at all.
-Now hold on a minute.
What the hell are you thinking?
You've got to calm down.
I am perfectly calm.
One way to be sure.
-Oh here we go again.
Seems like half
the time I end up
fighting the guy I
thought I could trust.
-What are you waiting for?
If a fight is what you
want, come and get it.
-Yeah, enough playing
hide-and-seek.
Are you too scared to come
out and show us your faces?
-Huh?
-They're only children.
-Stop picking on Gantetsu.
-Give Gantetsu back.
-What is this?
-No idea, but
those are not toys.
-Get ready.
-Please, wait just a moment.
-What's your
connection to Gantetsu?
-[yelling]
-Cut it out.
-Let us retreat.
If you will remain
calm, it will be
easier for us to
understand each other.
-Look, you guys aren't
Shinobi, are you?
Because amateurs with
weapons could get hurt.
How are we going to handle this?
-It is a problem.
We do not dare use our full
powers against these children.
-[yelling]
-Right.
Shadow Clone Jutsu.
-Get off!
Let me go.
I need to avenge my
parents and my brother.
-You need to calm down
is what you need to do,
and think this thing through.
-Did you say, your brother?
-Don't be stupid, Gantetsu.
Just stay out of it.
[crashing]
-Gantetsu.
[screaming] [grunting]
-Who are you?
What do you want?
-I can't move.
What is this?
-Save your strength.
Those strands are
stronger than steel.
All the struggling in the
world won't get you out.
-Then who the heck are you?
-Ninja Dropout Monju.
-A Ninja Dropout?
-I've come for Gantetsu,
and now that I have him,
I won't trouble you any further.
By the way, that web will
shrink as it gets warmer out.
First you'll do some suffering,
and then eventually you'll
be cut into tiny pieces.
Take it easy.
-Todoroki!
-Gantetsu!
[music playing]
-I don't want to die,
especially not like this.
[grunting] Our mission
is to do deliver Gantetsu
to the capital.
-You fool.
Just look at our situation.
You and I will both be
dead before we can do that.
-I've got a feeling the
Ninja Dropouts aren't really
friends of Gantetsu's,
which means
Gantetsu was telling the
truth the whole time.
I don't think these guys
are trying to save him.
I think it's just the opposite.
-You should have just
let me finish him
when I had the chance.
-But why was he
calling out your name
when he was being taken away?
-I have no idea.
-It had to be something
important, something
he felt he had to tell you.
-I don't want to
hear any excuses
from an animal like him.
-Based on the way
things have gone so far,
I can't believe Gantetsu's
really that bad.
-You're wrong.
-OK suit yourself.
But there's no way I'm going
to kick the bucket until I've
heard exactly what it was
that he wanted to say.
[yelling]
-You stop this right--
-I am certain we can
work this out, but first
put down those weapons.
-No way.
-Wait, hold on.
Maybe they have a point.
Sorry, we thought you
were Ninja Dropouts.
-We're Hidden Leaf
Village Shinobi.
We're part of the
team that was assigned
to take Gantetsu to the capital.
-Please, you have to
let Gantetsu go free.
-That's not possible.
But Gantetsu is the
one who saved all of us
from the Ninja Dropouts.
-Saved you?
-Just who are you anyway?
-We're all kids who lost our
families to the Ninja Dropouts.
Gantetsu wanted to make sure
at least the children would
be saved, so he rescued every
one of us and brought us here.
-Rescued you?
AKIO: He took in every child
that was orphaned by his gang.
[music playing]
[door opens]
-Gantetsu.
Ninja Dropouts?
-I'm sorry.
-Where am I?
-You'll be safe now.
-Mother?
Where is this?
What happened to my mom?
-You poor thing.
We all know exactly
how you feel.
Please don't think
you're all alone.
We're with you.
We're your new family
now, all of us.
-I'm leaving the Ninja Dropouts.
I can't stand it anymore.
They're not people.
They're animals, so I can't
be a part of it any longer.
-But you know what they'll do
to if you try to leave them.
-What I'll do is rob them--
-Huh?
-And then get myself
arrested by the police.
-But why?
-Because then the
whole gang will do all
they can to free me in order
to get their loot back,
giving the police a
chance to round them up.
-You're the bait
to draw them out.
-So that there will be
no more victims like you,
this is the path I have to take.
-Gantetsu stole
all their treasure,
then brought it back to us.
We came out into the
forest because we
were worried something
had happened to him.
We prayed the Ninja
Dropouts would finally
be caught, however--
-So Gantetsu's making
amends for his past
by destroying the gang
he used to belong to?
-Then we must
address the real evil
in this picture, the bandits
of the Ninja Dropouts.
-They're not the ones we should
be worried about right now.
What's important is
that we rescue Gantetsu.
-If that is the case,
it is most likely
we will find him
by finding Naruto.
You do not have
to worry that he's
been taken by the
Ninja Dropouts.
-OK, then that's the plan.
[music playing]
-This is not good.
[struggling]
-If this goes on
much longer, we'll
just be a couple of dried fish.
Huh?
What's this?
Hey, Todoroki, this stuff gets
looser when it soaks up sweat.
-What's that?
Are you sure?
[grunting]
-Look at that.
You're right.
-Course I'm right.
-Ah!
But why?
-It's venom has no effect on me.
I'm used to it.
[yelling] Here.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): No way.
After what he did, I just
can't believe he's that evil.
-Whatever it takes, I've got to
see Gantetsu again and find out
for sure.
-I agree.
Yes, I need to see him
one more time as well,
and get revenge for
the death of my family.
[grunting]
-We actually did it.
-I wasn't too sure.
-All righty.
So now we're going to go
and rescue Gantetsu, right?
Let's go.
-Oh no.
I'm going to cut him
down like a dead tree.
-Hmm?
[grunt]
-Gantetsu.
-What?
-What in the world is going on?
-What could this be?
-What are you doing, you idiot?
-Gantetsu!
You OK?
-Gantetsu.
-Be careful, little boy.
He's one of them.
-A Ninja Dropout.
-[laughing] Right you are.
Ninja Dropout Monju.
Let Gantetsu go, or
you're going to pay.
-Hmm, you brats need to have
someone explain things to you.
I'll cut you some slack
since you're only kids,
but you should be careful
about giving me orders.
"Give us what we want", that's
been our line, right Gantetsu?
Who the hell are
you kids anyway?
-We are the ones who
will avenge our families.
-Excuse me.
Just lie there and
be quiet, punk.
-I'll get you.
-Monju, let him go.
You don't have to
torture the kid.
-The boy needs to be
taught some manners.
And what did he
mean when he said,
they're avenging
their families, huh?
What's that's about?
-I've had enough of you.
-Ninja Art Mesh Cage.
-And now you must face me.
I did not even make a dent.
-Of course not.
There's nothing that
can penetrate that.
And now I want an
answer, friend.
-You won't get it.
So it's like that?
And what if I do this, hmm?
-[screaming]
-Akio.
All right, I'll talk.
I'll do anything you want me to.
Just stop.
-You should have said
that in the beginning.
-They're our victims,
these children.
They're all from homes
attacked by the Ninja Dropouts.
I rescued them, made them safe.
-You did what?
You rescued witnesses?
You betrayed us?
Did you take our treasure
and give it back?
-That money didn't belong to us.
It belonged to their families.
-Don't talk to me
you dirty traitor!
-Hey, hold it down in there.
Sorry if I kept you waiting, but
Naruto Uzumaki is on the scene.
-Naruto.
-I knew you would
make it in time.
-Oh I wasn't going
to miss the fun.
Just so you know, you're
not taking Gantetsu.
-[panting] It's Gantetsu.
[music playing]
-No.
Is that?
It can't be.
[theme music]
-Is that the Ninja
Dropouts' secret base?
Yes, they were probably
holding Akio in there.
-What a bunch of creeps.
They're going to pay for this.
-How dare they interfere
with a brothers' reunion?
That is unforgivable.
-All right, let's go bushy brow.
-Ready when you are, even
if the enemy are ex-Shinobi.
We're going to pound
them into the dirt,
and definitely get
Todoroki's brother back.
Next time "To Each
His Own Path."
[theme music]