[music playing]
[music - Asian Kung Fu
Generation, "Far Away"]
-Curse Sealing.
-[screams]
KAKASHI: This
Curse Sealing jutsu
is only as strong as you are.
It derives its power from
the strength of your will.
If that will ever
weakens, if you ever
begin to doubt
yourself, the curse
will be unleashed
in all its fury.
Hmf, amazing.
Too tired to even argue.
OROCHIMARU: My,
how you've grown.
To think you've
become strong enough
to perform the
Curse Sealing jutsu.
-You.
Orochimaru.
-Long time no see, Kakashi.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Kakashi
and Orochimaru-- Face-to-Face!
-No offense, Kakashi, but
I didn't come to see you.
My business is with
that boy behind you.
-What do you wanted with Sasuke?
-Hah.
You've acquired something new.
How I envy your good fortune.
[small gasp]
-I don't believe you had
it the last time we met.
Did you?
The gift.
The Sharingan in your left eye.
It's only fair that I should
want it, too, the Uchiha power.
-All right, fool.
You had enough?
Huh?
He's-- there's no way!
[chittering]
-Hey.
What?
-Uh?
-Huh?
-[gasp]
[chittering]
ZAKU (VOICEOVER):
What the-- he's
got bugs coming out of
him, like a human hive!
This guy's a freak show!
-Great.
Now that you've creeped us
all out, what happens next?
Aahh!
[chittering]
-They're a rare species
of parasitic beetle
that attack their prey in
a swarm, eating its chakra.
An army of this size will suck
you dry in less than a minute.
Your only intelligent option
is to forfeit the match.
You can't fight two
opponents at once.
If you use your
good arm against me,
my friends will swarm
you from behind.
Conversely, if you use your
good arm to keep them at bay,
then you'll have me
on your blind side.
Either way, your defeat will
be certain-- and unpleasant.
It's wise to always
have an ace in the hole.
[chittering]
MAN: Hey you!
Come back here!
ZAKU: [panting]
-Where do you think you're
going, you little thief?
-[panting]
-Grab him, somebody!
Catch him before he gets away!
-[panting] Aaah!
Dead end!
Aaah!
[screams]
MAN: There.
You get the message,
you little punk?
That'll teach you
to waste our time.
[whimpering]
OROCHIMARU: You
have potential, boy.
-Huh?
[gasp]
-I saw something in you I
like, a look in your eye.
If you leave this
place and come with me,
I will make you strong, boy.
Follow me.
OROCHIMARU (VOICEOVER):
Come with me,
and I will make you strong.
I will make you strong.
[chittering]
-Be my weapon and
do my bidding, Zaku.
Battle for me, and you
will become strong.
[panting raggedly]
-Rrrraahhhhhh!
[boom]
[panting]
OROCHIMARU (VOICEOVER):
Now don't disappoint me.
ZAKU (VOICEOVER): That's it.
Never again.
Unh!
SASUKE: You seem to be very
proud of these arms of yours,
very attached to them.
-No!
What are you doing?
[screams]
ZAKU (VOICEOVER): That's it.
That's never gonna happen again!
[roars]
-Now you've done it.
Now you've made me mad!
Heh.
Hnnh!
Like you said yourself, always
have an ace in the hole.
Right?
-Huh?
-What the?
I thought his
right arm was shot!
--[low laugh] So it was just a
ploy to make us believe he had
only one good arm.
Clever move.
[roars]
KAKASHI: What's your game?
-This Sound Village that
everyone's curious about?
It's mine.
You see, I created it.
I think you understand
without my saying any more.
-Hmph.
You and your wild-eyed ambition.
-Oh, yes indeed.
As always.
But to play the
game, as you put it,
I need pieces on the chessboard,
willing pawns to do my bidding.
-[roars] I'll blow you away!
-And Sasuke is
one of your pawns?
-Oh, not a pawn.
He's a far more valuable
piece than that.
But as for the
others-- well, you
know how it is in
the game of chess.
Pieces must be sacrificed.
[gasp]
-Aaaaahhhh!
My arms!
What's wrong with them?
Aah!
Wh-what?
-Earlier, while I
was distracting you
with my helpful
advice, I was also
sending some of
my little friends
to plug up those bothersome
wind holes in your hands.
Both hands, just to be sure.
You see, while an ace
in the hole is good--
[gasp]
-Two aces are better.
[roars]
[cries out]
KAKASHI: Stop!
Don't come any closer.
[crackling and zapping]
-I don't care if you are
one of the Sannin, the Three
Shinobi of legend.
I swear, take one more step
towards Sasuke and one of us
will die here!
[laughs]
-Funny, is it?
-Poor Kakashi.
All your noble
efforts, all in vain.
-What?
OROCHIMARU: Do
you really believe
that the seal will hold?
Do you think you can keep him
from what he truly desires?
You know I'm right.
A heart like his, that
hungers for only one thing,
will not be denied, no
matter what obstacles you
put in his path.
He's an Avenger, isn't he?
-You think you can
take advantage of that?
Not Sasuke.
-You cannot stop it.
At some point, he will come
to me, in search of power.
Unless of course you carry
out your threat to kill me.
Now is your chance.
Take it, if you dare.
[breathing shakily]
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): "One
of us will die here."
I must have been out of my mind.
[cries out]
-I'd say this one has had it.
The winner is Shino Aburame.
-Wait.
How did he do that?
Who is he?
Find out.
NEJI (VOICEOVER): Byakugan.
-[gasp] I had no idea.
I thought he must be
using a summoning jutsu
to get all those
insects, but no.
They're actually
living inside of him.
-Living inside of him?
-There's a legend
in the Leaf Village
of a clan of insect tamers.
-Yes, I've heard of
that clan as well.
They say that when a
bug master is born,
he enters into a sacred
pact with the insects.
He allows them to
nest in his body.
In return, they obey
their host's will.
They serve him, answering his
call, fighting his battles
and destroying his enemies.
I've also heard that they
allow the insects to feed
on their chakra as
part of the bargain.
-So this guy is one of them?
One of these bug-tamers? tamers?
DOSU: Well, that
was unfortunate.
-What just happened?
How come his arms
broke down like that?
-At some point
early in the match,
this guy Shino managed to get
his beetles into Zaku's Wind
Cannon and plugged the opening.
As soon as Zaku tried to
use his Slicing Sound Wave,
he was doomed.
With its usual
outlet sealed off,
the energy from the Sound
Wave was trapped in his arm,
expanding, searching
for an exit.
Sooner or later,
something had to give.
In this case, it was Zaku.
I can't pretend we had
anything in common,
except this team
and our mission.
Still, I'll even the
score for you, Zaku.
[low chortle]
KURENAI (VOICEOVER): [sigh] My,
it's getting chilly in here.
-Man, that Shino is good.
Who woulda thunk it
with him being so quiet?
I can't wait to
get my shot at him!
-Whoa, Why thought Shino
was weird before, but now--
-Oh, wow, I, uh--
congratulations, Shino.
-Way to go.
Good work.
SHINO: Hmf.
Just see that you
two do the same.
AKAMARU (VOICEOVER): Grrr.
Yeah?
Who died and made
you team leader, huh?
-Uh, all right, everyone.
Moving right on to
the third match.
-Hnh.
Huh?
-Kakashi-sensei!
-Hi.
-What do you mean, hi?
Is that all you can say?
Wh-what about--
what about Sasuke?
How is he?
-Oh, he's fine.
Sleeping soundly
in the infirmary.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): But
he's been put under guard
by the Anbu Black Ops.
[gasp]
KANKURO (VOICEOVER): Heh.
Finally, my turn.
BAKI (VOICEOVER):
Careful, Kankuro.
You'll underestimate your
opponent one time too many.
GAARA (VOICEOVER): Hmf.
Idiot.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): This guy!
-I'm not like Yoroi.
I don't get careless,
not even against kids.
-Heh.
KANKURO: A piece of advice.
Once I go into my
jutsu, give up quick.
If you do, I promise to
make it short and painless.
-Funny, I was about
to say the same thing.
Though I can't promise
it'll be painless.
-All right, then.
If you're ready, let
the third match begin.
[music - Rythem, "Harmonia"]
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): We're
not little girls anymore,
are we, Ino?
When I think back on those
days, how I used to idolize you?
I wanted to be just like you.
But I'm grown up now, and my
goals are a little higher.
I want to prove I'm
better than you.
And if I can't, I don't
deserve to be here.
Next time: Kunoichi Rumble:
The Rivals Get Serious.
The fun and games are over, Ino!