[theme music]
-All right!
I'm finally gonna get
to do some trainin'.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Come on.
This is the only way
I'm gonna get better.
Can't give up yet.
[barking]
-So what's going on?
It's not like you to stop
by and pick me up like this.
Besides, aren't we all
supposed to meet up
at Kurenai-sensei's place soon?
-Taking some time
to converse once
in a while-- that's a part of
being on a squad, isn't it?
That mission you guys went
on, I'd like to hear about it.
-It was pretty incredible.
But unless you lived
through it, you
wouldn't really understand it.
[barking]
KIBA (VOICEOVER):
I can't let Akamaru
go through something
like that again.
That's why I have to perfect
my jutsu as much as I can.
-Even so, I'd like
to hear the details.
After all, that's what being
on a squad is all about.
-Hey.
You in a bad mood because
you're the only one who
didn't get to go?
-Yeah.
That's gotta be it.
NEJI (VOICEOVER):
I've still a long way
to go 'til I can see his moves.
KIBA: Isn't it a little
early for training?
[barking]
-Neji, let's go ahead
and take a break.
-Yes, sir.
-Come on, Hinata!
-OK!
I'll be right back, father.
-Fine.
[barking]
-You're eating barbecued
meat for breakfast.
-And he just lost
all that weight
when he was resting
in the hospital.
Amazing how fast he
got back to normal.
-Well, with an
appetite like that,
at least we don't have to
worry about his health.
-When I'm finished
with my breakfast,
you're gonna help me
with my training again.
Right, Asuma-sensei?
-Hey, are you an
idiot, or something?
You're supposed to be taking
it easy and recuperating,
you nincompoop!
-Yah!
Ha!
-Oi, slow down.
Come on, let's take
a little break.
-What is the matter, Guy-sensei?
One's youthful energy
must not be wasted!
-Yeah, but your
youthful energy's
running my body into the ground.
-Thank you very much,
and see you again soon.
-All right, kids.
Keep training.
-I'm gonna learn
the Shuriken Jutsu
by the time you come back.
Ha!
-Yeah.
I, uh, I will too.
-Oh, Temari, someday I'm
gonna be a strong kunoichi,
just like you.
-I'm very honored
to hear that, dear.
-Thanks again.
I had to ask you guys
to teach at the Academy
because we're a bit
short-staffed at the moment.
I'm sure you would have
rather gone sightseeing, or--
-No problem.
I helped out 'cause I enjoy it.
-Same here.
Besides, these kids
were the future
of the Leaf's military power.
This was a good opportunity
for us to evaluate them.
-Yeah.
Well, careful getting home.
-OK.
-I'll see you next time
you need to be rescued.
Just let me know, and I'll come.
You big crybaby.
-You girls are all alike.
You had to get the
last word in, huh?
KIBA: Let's kick some
butt today, Akamaru!
[bark]
-All right.
So we're all here?
There's nothing to be
nervous about, Hinata.
-OK.
-Now, everybody stand ready.
HINATA (VOICEOVER): I
have to work harder,
so I can be as strong as Naruto.
-OK!
I'm ready to go!
I just gotta wait for Pervy
Sage to show up, and-- It's him!
Uh-- um-- hm?
Hey, what about my training?
Now, don't look
so mopey, Naruto.
Some important last
minute work came in,
and I have to take care of it.
-It's probably research for some
kind of trashy novel, isn't it?
I wouldn't exactly call that
important work, you know?
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
It's actually
a mission to gather
information about the Akatsuki
organization.
But if I tell Naruto, he might
ask to come along with me.
Tell you what.
I'll make it up to ya.
-What is it?
-Something to help you from
getting too bored while you're
sitting at home alone.
I put together a special
training regimen for you.
-No way!
You did?
-Hey!
Hold on a second!
My own personal super
secret training methods
are inscribed
within that scroll.
You can't just
open it up outside,
where other people might see it.
-I won't!
-Well, you'd better get started.
-I'm gonna use this
scroll to train
like I've never trained before!
Thanks a million for
this, Pervy Sage.
The walls have ears.
Paper doors have eyes.
Pervy Sage's secret
training system!
Huh?
Willpower?
Pervy Sage!
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): You all
built the great Hidden Leaf
Village, and I've been
entrusted with its well being.
No matter what
danger may strike,
it's my duty to
protect this village.
The Hokage sure
has it tough huh?
SHIZUNE: Yes.
You really do.
-That you, Shizune?
Enter.
I'm sorry there's so many
reports to go through.
They've been accumulating
because so many things have
been happening to
the village lately.
-I guess the only
thing I can do is
start at the top of the pile.
Leaf Maximum Security Prison?
Did the name of
the prison change?
-Yes.
It used to be called the Ninja
Prison for Capital Expenses
and Felonies.
Fortunately,
because there's been
a drop in the number of
shinobi committing crimes,
the facility has been
downsized and the name
was changed to
reflect the cutbacks.
It was originally built
to house murderers, those
who committed
treason and the like.
The most hardened criminals.
But there hasn't been much
trouble the last few years,
and the prison's
been quite secure.
[whistle]
-Chow time!
-I gotta get my
hands on some grub.
Right, bro?
-My stomach is growlin'.
I can hardly wait to eat.
-Knock it off.
Fujin Raijin, if
you don't shut up,
you're gonna starve tonight.
Those guys are such a handful.
Keep it moving.
Wait, stop right there.
Looks like you have an injury.
Get that checked out
at the infirmary.
-Yeah.
-OK, who's next?
-Hey, I got a little question.
-Yeah, What?
-Well, look at my itty
bitty little pinky.
Why does it gotta be so
short and weak like it is.
-That's an easy one, Raijin.
If the pinky finger was big and
strong like the others, then
your thumb wouldn't
be special anymore!
-Oh.
Yeah!
Big brother.
Big brother!
-I'm a lizard.
-Raijin, ever since I've known
you, you've been a moron!
-Yeah.
Yeah.
[gurgling]
-We haven't had enough
to eat, have we, Fujin?
-You're right.
-You're out of your cell.
What's the matter now?
What is it this time?
-We're completely starving.
-You gotta give us some grub.
-Uh-oh.
If these guys find out I don't
have anything-- Well, I-- Uh,
it's just, right now--
-Let me see if I understand.
You're saying you have
absolutely nothing to offer us?
-Nothing you can present that
will satisfy Fujin and Raijin
tonight?
-No, we'll find something.
-What do you think?
Tastes good, huh?
-Mm-hm.
-I'll be sure and bring you
something else later tonight.
That ought to hold you
over for now, though.
-OK.
-You all right?
When they have enough
food in their bellies,
those two are pretty calm,
but when they're hungry,
they're impossible to control.
-Yeah.
They even turned against
their own teammates
during a mission over
a meal they wanted,
and then the people who
captured them barely
managed to hold them down.
-Huh?
-Hm?
[sniffing]
-I'm smelling
something delicious.
-Me too.
-That way.
-Food, food, food, food, food,
food, food, food, food, food,
food.
[sigh]
-All this paperwork I have
to go through is so boring.
-Unfortunately, there's still
a lot more to do, Lady Tsunade.
-Huh?
SHIZUNE: That's odd.
It looks like some sort
of formula for a potion.
-What formula is this?
Find any available Jonin
and bring them here at once.
-Really?
-Do it!
-Oh, yes ma'am!
-Tell me.
Is it all to your liking?
I guess that's a yes.
There's plenty more, you know.
-I should've known that
delicious smell was
coming from your
cell, big brother.
-Yeah.
'Cause somehow you
always figure out
how to get the
tastiest food for us.
-It took a lot of
sneaking around,
but it was definitely worth it.
I would feel absolutely
terrible if my brothers
had to go hungry.
-You're the best.
We're lizards.
-You're too funny.
But even so, you
must still be hungry.
What would you say if I could
get even more gourmet food?
-Hm?
What?
Food?
Where?
Give me!
-I know a place where we can
go visit an old friend of mine.
There, you can
taste cuisine that's
even more scrumptious than this.
-An old friend of yours?
Is this the same fella you
told us about a long time ago?
-Yeah.
His name was, uh, O-- O-- O--
-That's right.
Lord Orochimaru.
NARUTO: Pervy Sage
thinks he can just
ditch me in my
training like that!
-Come on.
Don't be so hard on him, Naruto.
There was a mission Master
Jiraiya had to complete.
-Hmph!
-I'm sure that's it.
Lady's Tsunade must've send
Master Jiraiya on a really
important mission that
only he could accomplish.
-Oh, is that right?
So it was grandma
Tsunade's fault, huh?
-Well, there's
nothing we can do now.
Listen.
Ramen noodles are my
treat tonight, OK Naruto?
So just cheer up.
Huh?
-That's it!
I'm gonna go give Grandma
Tsunade a piece of my mind.
Thanks for the free
eats, Iruka-sensei!
-Naruto, wait!
I--
-Hm?
Oh, great.
What is it this time?
-Hm?
What?
The Leaf Maximum
Security Prison?
-The crime occurred
about a year ago.
A Chunin Academy staff
member manipulated Naruto,
and used him to sneak
out the secret scroll.
-According to the final
report, Mizuki acted alone.
He was punished and the
case was closed, wasn't it?
-That's right.
But I'm not sure he
was acting alone.
Evidence has surfaced
that indicates
there may be a mastermind
who orchestrated
the crime from the shadows.
I found this clue in my files.
When he was first locked up at
the maximum security prison,
Mizuki was concealing
this piece of paper.
At the time, the
guards just assumed
it was an innocent doodle.
-Lady Tsunade.
What is it, anyway?
-I'm not certain.
However, the handwriting
resembles a document
that was confiscated at the
location where Orochimaru
was experimenting on humans.
-Wait.
Are you saying Orochimaru
is behind this?
-That possibility does exist.
Think about it.
If a lone, inexperienced Chunin
stole the secret scrolls,
he wouldn't actually be able
to do anything with them.
He lacks the power.
No.
It would only make
sense if Orochimaru
were behind him, commanding
him, pulling the strings.
Asuma, Kurenai, get going
to the maximum security
prison at once.
Find out everything
Mizuki knows.
-Orochimaru.
-Watch yourself.
Something doesn't
seem quite right here.
-It's much too quiet,
even for a jail.
Let's move.
Oh.
How touching.
They've sent a welcoming
party to greet us.
-Yeah!
And we're gonna give you a
big welcome, right, brother?
-You bet.
-Asuma.
Don't tell me those two are--
-It's them.
The famous idiot brothers,
Fujin and Raijin.
-Asuma.
-Hey, if you want
to throw a party,
you guys gotta it
make some more noise.
MIZUKI: Calm down, tough guy.
The welcome party's
only just beginning.
-Being stuck in prison really
changed this guy's personality.
-Get ready, dirt bags.
-Say your prayers, 'cause we're
about to eat you for dessert!
-Yeah.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Orochimaru.
-Asuma-sensei.
Kurenai-sensei.
[theme music]
-Oink.
Oink.
NARUTO: What's the
matter, Tonton?
Oink.
Oink oink oink.
-What in the world happened?
TONTON: Oink.
Oink oink oink.
-Hey.
Come to think of it,
weren't you with Shizune?
TONTON: Oink.
-You're trying to
tell us something's
happened to Shizune, right?
TONTON: Oink!
NARUTO: I don't know what's
going on, but lead the way,
Tonton.
I'm getting a bad
feeling about this.
Next time, Tonton,
I'm Countin' On Ya!
[theme music]