[theme music]
-Inari?
Could you give me a hand here?
Inari?
-I'll be right there!
-This mist-- Sasuke, Sakura.
Get ready.
I knew he was still alive.
He just couldn't
wait for round two.
-Kakashi-sensei, it's
Zabuza, isn't it?
This is his Hidden Mist jutsu.
ZABUZA: Sorry I kept
you waiting, Kakashi.
I see you've still got
those brats with you.
That one's still trembling.
Pitiful.
-I'm trembling with excitement.
-He's all yours, Sasuke.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
I can see it.
-Oh, so you could see they
were water clones, huh?
The brat's improving.
Looks like you've
got a rival, Haku.
-So it seems.
-I really hope I'm not too late.
-Well, well.
So I had it right.
It was all an act.
-An act?
-With a cute little mask.
-Huh?
-Big phony.
Ha.
-So I guess all that about
being a tracker ninja protecting
his village was just
a bunch of bull.
-They look pretty chummy to me.
I'd say they've
been pulling scams
like that for a long time.
-He's got some nerve,
facing us again
after pulling that tricks.
KAKASHI: And hiding
behind a mask.
Who does he think he's fooling?
SAKURA: Speak for
yourself, Sensei.
-That's it.
I'm taking him out.
[gasp]
-Who does he think
he's fooling, hiding
behind that mask like
some sort of clown?
-Sasuke, you're so cool.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
Wait a second.
Didn't I just say that?
She'll never change.
HAKU: He's impressive.
ZABUZA: Hmph.
-Even though they were
just 1/10 the strength
of the original water clone
jutsu, he did destroy them all.
-That move still gave
us the first advantage.
Now use it.
-Right.
-What's this?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Haku's Secret Jutsu,
Crystal Ice Mirrors.
-So you're Tazuna's
daughter, huh?
Too bad.
You'll have to come with us.
Now.
[scream]
-Mother!
-No!
Don't come out here!
Run away!
Hurry!
-Don't move.
-Should we grab this one, too?
-No.
Gato asked for just one hostage.
INARI (VOICEOVER): Hostage.
-All right.
Then let's waste him!
-Wait!
Please don't hurt my son.
I'm begging you.
He's just a boy.
I'll do anything.
Just please don't hurt him.
-Looks like your mom came
through for you, kid.
Lucky.
-What a waste.
I was in the mood
to cut something.
-Give it a rest.
You already drew blood today.
Let's get her out of here.
-I'm sorry, Mom!
I'm sorry!
What could I do?
I'm too weak to protect you.
I'm scared.
I don't wanna die!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Coward!
Listen to yourself,
whining and complaining
like some sorry little victim.
You can whimper all
day for all I care.
You're just a coward!
-My guess is he just
got tired of crying
and decided to do
something about it.
He knows what it means to be
strong-- like your father did.
-If you really care about
something, protect it.
Even if you have to put
your life on the line.
Protect it with both arms.
-Inari.
-Can I-- can-- can I
be that strong, too?
Father.
[laughter]
-We're going to
treat you just fine,
so don't you worry your
pretty little head.
-Come on, keep walking.
INARI: Stop!
-Well, well.
If it ain't the
little tough guy.
-Inari!
-How cute.
You've come to save your mom.
-You'd better get
away from my mom!
-Inari!
No!
-This kid's a little short
on brains, don't you think?
-Take him down.
[shout]
-If you hurt him, I swear I'll--
-Shut up.
Take a nap.
-Inari--
[shout]
ZABUZA (VOICEOVER): So, he can
keep up with Haku's speed, huh?
-Hm?
Sakura, cover Tazuna,
and stay close to me.
Let Sasuke handle this.
-We want the bridge
builder, not you.
If you back down, I
won't have to kill you.
-Save it.
-You're making a mistake.
You won't be able to
keep up with my speed.
I've gained two key advantages.
-Yeah?
What are they?
-First, we're
surrounded by water.
Second, I've blocked
one of your hands,
therefore you only have one
free hand to defend yourself.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): What?
Using one hand?
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): Hand
signs with a single hand?
I've never seen that before.
-Secret Jutsu, 1,000
Needles Of Death.
ZABUZA (VOICEOVER): He
doesn't want to kill the kid?
Does he mean that?
-Sasuke!
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
Remember the training.
Focus.
Summon my chakra at once.
-A substitution jutsu!
-The woman.
She's gone.
NARUTO: Sorry I'm a little late.
-Huh?
Who's that?
-You know, heroes usually
show up at the last minute.
-Naruto, it's you.
-Who else?
Inari, you did great.
-Huh?
-When you charged, they forgot
about your mom for a minute.
That gave me the chance to use
a cool jutsu to get her away
from them.
-Naruto, how did you know these
samurai guys were coming here?
-Uh, in the forest, I found a
boar that had been attacked,
and the trees were
all cut up, too,
like someone had been practicing
with a sword, or something.
The cuts led back toward the
house, so I followed them here.
-That was really smart.
-Blah, blah.
It's one of those puny
ninja brats Tazuna hired.
-Get him.
-Yeah.
-They're coming!
-Try something else!
-I did.
-I want him!
He's mine!
-You did it!
-Yeah!
Believe it!
-Huh?
That was so excellent.
Like a real ninja!
-You twerp.
I am a real ninja.
That's what I've
been telling you.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
Summon my chakra at once.
And direct it to my feet!
HAKU: He vanished.
-You're not as
fast as you think.
From this point on,
you'll be the one
defending against my attacks.
ZABUZA (VOICEOVER):
It's not possible.
No one's faster than Haku.
-Thought you were quicker, huh?
Now, what else are
you wrong about?
-You made a big mistake
insulting these ninja
and calling them brats.
That's just guaranteed to
bring out Sasuke's attitude.
And he's the best young fighter
of the Hidden Leaf Village.
And Sakura here is
our sharpest mind.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Heh, heh, heh!
"Shya!"
Am I bad, or what?
-And last but not
least, our number one
hyperactive knucklehead
ninja is Naruto Uzumaki.
-Achoo!
-They say when you sneeze,
it's cause somebody's
talking about you somewhere.
-You don't believe that, do you?
Hey, by the way,
sorry about yesterday.
-Huh?
-Calling you a coward
was pretty mean, I guess.
Anyway, it's not true, you know?
Cause you are really brave.
[whimpering]
-Hm?
-Darn it!
I promised myself I
wouldn't cry anymore.
You're gonna make fun of me
again and call me a baby--
but I can't stop!
-What are you talking about?
-You're happy.
What's wrong with that?
-Huh?
-When you're happy,
it's okay to cry.
Really, it is.
-Naruto.
-OK!
I can leave you in charge
of things now, right?
-Yeah.
-Good!
Then I'm going
over to the bridge.
It's not easy being a hero.
It's tough.
Believe it!
-Believe it!
[laughter]
-Haku, if we keep
going like this,
we'll be the victims
instead of them.
Get on with it.
-Right.
-What's that?
-I'm sorry it's come to this.
-The air-- so cold.
-Secret Jutsu.
Crystal Ice Mirrors!
-What is that?
How does it work?
-They're mirrors.
But how?
-If you enter this
fight, you fight me.
Your boy has no chance
against that jutsu.
He's finished.
-Now we'll begin.
And I'll show you what
speed really means.
-Sasuke!
-Just try to help him, and
I'll kill the other two
in a heartbeat.
-I'm sorry.
I can't stay with you.
Forgive me.
-I understand.
Go now.
-Sakura--
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Sasuke!
-Take this!
He caught it!
Huh?
Who is it?
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): What a fool.
Such a showoff.
-Number one hyperactive
knucklehead ninja.
-Naruto Uzumaki is here.
Yeah.
Believe it!
[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Naruto Uzumaki is here.
Now everything will be OK.
Since I'm the hero,
I'll just smash
those messed up, weird looking
mirrors, and that'll be-- huh?
Why won't they break?
They're just made of ice.
Why won't they melt?
What the heck's going on?
-Next time, The Number One
Hyperactive Knucklehead Ninja
Joins The Fight.
Will I kick butt again?
Or will I get my butt kicked?
What am I gonna do?