[music playing]
[theme music]
-Guess that storm's
going to be here soon.
-We should hurry back
to the restaurant, then.
-Oh dear.
-(THINKING) That
lightning just now,
it came from over the
Katabami gold mine.
-[whimpering]
Boss, but how?
-No, it can't-- Ranmaru.
Ranmaru, wake up already.
Quit joking around, OK?
It isn't funny.
Hey, Ranmaru.
Tell me.
Tell me what you did to Ranmaru.
-Nothing.
I swear.
It was you.
-Huh?
KARASHI: Ranmaru, he, he
laid his hands on you, boss.
And you came back.
And then he--
-Ranmaru.
-[faint moaning]
-(THINKING) Raiga?
But how?
I can't let him escape.
-Ah!
-[roaring]
-Ha!
-[growling]
-Ah!
-More lightning?
But how?
-[laughing] Sorry.
Too slow!
-[screaming]
-It's you.
You're that little
brat's teammate.
-[panting]
-[growling]
[roaring]
-Ah!
-[whimpering]
-(THINKING) This
wooden staff is safe.
But I still can't
hold it up too high.
-[roaring]
-I've had enough.
Huh?
-[screaming]
-[roaring]
[gasp]
-You're an annoying little gnat.
So buzz off already.
-[screaming]
-[whimpering]
-You know, I'm not
a real smart person.
He's dead.
And I don't know
how it happened.
I don't have the slightest idea.
So who killed him?
Was it you?
-No.
It wasn't me, I swear.
Maybe those guys from
the Leaf Village.
-[gasp] You're right.
If those brats had
never come, then I
could have had Ranmaru
with me forever.
Where are they hiding?
Come on.
You better know where.
Because if you
don't, you're dead.
-Yeah, I know, maybe.
Ah!
[gasping and panting]
[soft nervous laughter]
-Get up, you worm.
And take me where they are.
Get up!
-Yes, boss. [whimpering]
-Don't go yet, Ranmaru.
I haven't given you a funeral.
I swear that soon I'll lay
their corpses at your feet.
[thunder]
-[moaning] [gasp]
Ranmaru.
This child, did he
really sacrifice
himself to save
the likes of Raiga?
-Ra-Raiga.
-Ranmaru!
You're alive!
Hang in there just a
little longer, Ranmaru.
Ranmaru!
[panting]
-The rain finally got here.
-Good thing, now that
we're almost done
-Yep.
-My goodness.
Look Is this.
You kids sure did a lot
of work for this old lady.
KARASHI: Come quick.
-Huh?
-You'll never believe
what happened.
Oh, it was horrible, mom.
-Horrible?
Karashi what are
you talking about?
-It's Tenten.
She--
-[gasps]
-What do you mean?
What happened to her?
-She-- she fell off a cliff.
-What?
What are you talking about?
-We were both running, Tenten
and I. Lee was still busy.
And she told me I
could train with her.
But then, when we
got to Lighting Pass,
a bolt of lightning hit a
tree and knocked i towards us.
And Tenten, Tenten fell
off the cliff, all the way
to the bottom.
-How awful!
Hurry back and
help the poor girl.
-We have to go.
Tenten needs our help.
-Yeah!
-Uh, go on.
And I, I'm going to go
grab the first aid kit.
I'll be right behind you.
I promise.
-Very well.
Naruto, Lee, let's go.
-Right.
-Right!
-Karashi, what are you--
-I'm going to run away.
And so are you, mom.
-What on earth are you
talking about, child?
-It doesn't matter.
I'll explain it all later.
Grab your stuff, and let's go.
-I'll be waiting
at Lighting Pass.
So bring them to me, you worm.
I will have my revenge.
If you don't, the corpses
I lay at Ranmaru's feet
during his funeral will
be you and your mother.
-Mom, we gotta go.
I'm begging you.
-I don't want to.
No sir.
I'm not budging until
anyone else comes back.
-You don't get it.
We're leaving, mom, now!
GRANDMA: Let go of me!
No, Karashi, I won't.
-Would lightning in
some tree really be
enough to send
Tenten over a cliff?
-Huh?
What do you mean?
-I don't know.
Perhaps Karashi's
training didn't stick.
-That is my fault.
-Then what?
-Maybe, maybe it's some
kind of trap again.
LEE: Or someone is
threatening him.
-But we already beat
the Kurosuki family.
-Maybe my eyes were clouded.
NARUTO: No way.
It's him.
[thunder]
-He's burning up.
-Is he still gone?
-Raiga woke up.
Let's worry about you.
-It's all right.
I know I'm going to
be dead soon, anyway.
-I won't let that happen.
You're not getting
off that easy, no way.
The people you and Raiga
killed, they all wanted to live.
But you didn't leave
them that choice.
You decided for them.
Well, you don't get to
decide this time, OK?
You're going to live.
And you're going to
take some responsibility
for all those people
whose lives you cut short.
-[coughing]
-Are you OK?
[wind howling and wood creaking]
-(THINKING) The storm.
We won't be safe here.
I'll take him to
grandma's place.
-Ready to die?
-Raiga.
-He is alive.
You were right.
-Come on, Raiga.
Let's do this thing.
And this time, you're
going down for good.
-[roaring]
-Lee!
-This is it!
What are you doing?
What's going on?
His lightning's way
stronger this time.
[screaming]
-He was using sheer
chakra before.
So there was a limit to
the power he was wielding.
But this time, he's using
real lightning as his source.
If he can draw upon the
power of nature itself,
truly harness it,
there's no stopping him.
-[roaring]
-Get down, now!
[inaudible]
If we can dodge his attacks, and
take the battle right to him--
Naruto!
-One step ahead of you.
Shadow Clone Jutsu.
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
-Excellent work, Naruto.
Gentle fist.
[groaning]
-Negi!
[screaming]
-[chuckling] You brat.
Are you really that dumb?
This isn't extraordinary
chakra I'm blasting you with.
It's actual lightning.
[chuckling] You
really are that dumb.
LEE: Stop it.
How dare you
disrespect an opponent
who fought you with all he had?
-Oh, I remember you.
On second thought, no funeral.
I'll just kill you.
-I'm very angry.
[coughing]
-Karashi, what are you doing?
-I'll explain later.
Please, just come with me.
We have to go, now.
-I'm staying put,
and that's that.
Oh, Tenten.
This stupid son of
mine did what now?
-Ow!
It's not like I had a choice.
If the boss had stayed dead,
I wouldn't have done it.
Look, he's going to
kill us if we stay here.
We have to run away.
-Go if you want, Grandma Sansho.
-What?
-But I'm not running away.
And I'm not giving up.
I will save this child.
-[coughing]
-Well then, I'll stay and feed
the curry of life to this boy.
-Grandma.
-Why not?
My curry certainly did
the trick with Lee.
-[giggling]
-Well, don't blame
me if he gets worse.
-[screaming]
-I hate this kid.
-One and two, and one and two.
One and two, and one and two.
-This is bad, really bad.
-[roaring]
-Ah!
[screaming]
-[sniffing]
-Eat this.
You'll feel a lot better.
Just a bite?
-Oh.
KARASHI: You messed up
on the blend of spices.
-I did what?
Son, are you honestly
telling me you
memorized it, my recipe
for the curry of life?
Karashi.
-Here it is.
One genuine order of our
signature curry of life.
-Here, try this.
Are you so dependent
on Raiga you can't even
eat when you're not with him?
-Why?
Why are you helping me?
-Do I need a reason
to not let you die?
Grandma Sansho and Karashi
put their heart and soul
into making this curry.
They did it to save you.
Don't you feel anything
seeing the two of them
try their best
for you like that?
Because if you don't
feel something,
then you're just a
horrible human being.
People help each other,
whether it's saving their life
or just lending a hand.
If someone needs help, don't
you naturally just step in?
-Well, why don't you go ahead
and try it, just one bite?
-[gasp] [gulping]
-So was it good?
What you're feeling, that's
what it feels like to live.
-[gasp]
-Raiga.
I want him to eat
this curry, too.
-Let's go.
[thunder]
-[screaming]
I'm still standing.
-This kid is unbelievable.
[thunder]
[music playing]
NARUTO: Darn it.
What in the world
happened to my body?
I mean, everywhere I look,
stuff is pitch black.
And I'm all numb.
And I can't move anything.
Whoa.
What's this feeling?
It's warm.
My whole body is burning up.
And there's this taste
bringing energy up
from the bottom of my stomach!
Next time, "Run,
the Curry of Life."
[music playing]