[theme music]
-End of the line.
Now return Matsuri.
-You really think
you've got me cornered?
You might want to reassess that.
The only one
trapped here is you.
-What?
-Byakugan!
Gaara has the final enemy
backed into a dead end canyon.
-Interesting.
The area surrounding the
canyon is pretty calm.
I'm not seeing
any other enemies.
-I wonder if Shikamaru
figured out a solution?
Doubtful.
There's No.
Way of knowing whether
the fight is over.
We can't even rule
out the possibility
that all these battles
were just diversions.
-OK, Lee.
I'm almost done.
I just have to reconnect
two or three more muscles.
INO (VOICEOVER):
Sakura's mastery
of medical ninjutsu is perfect.
But me?
I'm--
-Phew.
That's it.
The treatment's over for now.
You must have been
fighting like a maniac
to end up in such bad shape.
-Sorry.
But you saved my life.
Now I will be forever
in your debt, Sakura.
-I was just doing my job.
No!
You shouldn't get up yet.
As a medical ninja, I forbid
you from doing anymore fighting.
You need your rest.
-No.
Please let me go.
I cannot leave Gaara alone
out there fending for himself.
I must repay the
favor he did for us.
-Gaara, you may very well be
called the ultimate weapon,
but unless I'm mistaken,
you used up all your chakra
in that earlier fight.
-This is all the weapon I need.
GAARA (VOICEOVER): He's right.
I drew on almost all
my chakra infused sand
to beat back his first attack.
Dammit.
-Think what you want, but I'm
still ready to take you on.
Sand or no sound,
I can handle you.
-Hmph.
Somehow a ninja without a
weapon doesn't scare me.
Come, Infinite Kujaku Armor!
-Huh?
[shout]
-Fang Release!
Airborne Dark Sword!
A shinobi fighting
with his bare hands
is no match for a
mighty ninja tool
forged by the
Village of Artisans.
Dragon Eye, Fang
Release, Dark Sword!
Well, well.
Looks like you're
all out of chakra.
I'm told you have a
monster inside of you.
Isn't that so?
Well, it's about time you
unleash that Shukaku of yours.
-Hey, you doing OK?
-Gaara-sensei's in trouble.
-Yeah.
I figured that out.
Listen, find a safe
place somewhere and hdie.
-OK.
This could get ugly.
Even though Sakura treated
him, Gaara's still weak.
-It's the end of the line,
ultimate weapon of the Sand
Village.
GAARA (VOICEOVER): Not good.
-What are you waiting for?
Let loose with the Shukaku!
NARUTO: Hey, you!
Just back off!
And who might you be?
-I'll tell you who I am.
From here on out, I'm the
guy you're fighting with!
-You're getting it my way, boy.
Kujaku Hurricane!
-Dammit!
-Just keep watching,
Leaf Village ninja.
Soon the reign of the
five hidden villages
will be over, and
even more than that,
the time is approaching
when the Village of Artisans
shall complete its
ultimate ninja tool.
And when it does,
there will be no need
for shinobi to
even exist at all.
-You're crazy.
What are you talking about?
-The village of artisans
has proud weapons makers.
For years we've been
making ninja tools
as good as or better than
the five great nations.
In times of war,
however, our village
is always attacked, targeted
for fear our valuable ninja
tools would be used
by the other side.
You ninja of the
five great nations
have forgotten
that our handiwork
is what keeps you in power.
You to take our tools and
repay us with bloodshed.
And despite our
expertise, to survive,
our village has
been forced to bend
to the whims of the so-called
great hidden villages.
However, that era well end
today, and the first to all
will be the Leaf Village.
Fang Release, Dark Sword!
You can't keep
running away forever.
Like a bird of prey,
I'll strike you down!
What?
But how?
MATSURI (VOICEOVER):
Gaara-sensei.
He used the sand to
protect that Leaf ninja.
Wow.
-That sand dome is packed hard
with minerals from the ground.
Your pathetic attacks are
far too weak to break it.
I will defend him, if it
takes everything I've got.
-Gaara-sensei.
-Don't make me laugh!
You, the so-called
ultimate weapon,
would risk your very
existence protecting someone
like this nuisance?
You would use what
little chakra you
have left for the
sake of a friend?
Quite a choice.
And it's one that
will be your downfall!
-Gaara-sensei!
-Now that I've captured
you, the plan is complete.
-Damn him.
-Gaara!
-We've been contacted by someone
from the Village of Artisans.
Apparently we have
enemies there,
a mysterious group known
as the Four Celestials.
They've been doing
some illegal research,
attempting to recreate
their village's
legendary ultimate weapon.
Intelligence tells us the other
villagers discovered the plan
and evacuated for
their own safety.
-I see.
That explains their village
being completely empty.
So this ultimate
weapon, what is it?
-The revival of Seimei, the
founder of their village.
-Seimei?
Are you saying they're actually
trying to raise the dead?
Of course.
That must be why we
found his tomb damaged.
-For our security, we must
stop this ultimate weapon
from being restored
at all costs.
-I understand.
Ma'am.
-Wait.
One more thing.
-Yes?
-I'm sending along someone to
accompany you on the mission.
-Huh?
Who might that be?
-Heh, heh, heh.
At last we will have
your Shukaku chakra.
-What did you say?
-It's what we've been
after this whole time.
Go ahead, Gaara, unleash
the force of Shukaku,
so that I can be
infused with its chakra.
NARUTO: Gaara!
Don't worry, I'm coming!
-Naruto!
GAARA (VOICEOVER):
Matsuri, take this.
-My rope javelin?
GAARA: The optic
nerve is connected.
Third eye, open.
-Hey!
Buddy!
What's the meaning of all this?
What are you up to?
-Don't worry, you'll see.
Long ago, the great founder
of our village, Lord Seimei,
began creating the
ultimate ninja tool.
-You're doing all
this for a weapon?
-And now it will
finally be completed.
Ha!
[groan]
-Gaara!
-Oh mighty Lord
Seimei, may your spirit
come and be joined with my
flesh to complete your revival!
[shout]
[scream]
-What the-- he just vanished.
What?
That guy came back to life.
-I am called Seimei, founder
of the Village of Artisans.
And now, after 100
years of slumber,
I have been awakened as my
village's ultimate tool.
-It's so bright!
What the heck is going on?
[laughter]
-I have waited so long for this.
For my plans to
come to fruition.
Now the Village of
Artisans will rule
over all other shinobi lands.
Oh, I see.
The monster from
the Sand Village
has become the source
of my renewed energy.
-What are you saying?
-It is just as Hogyo predicted.
Lying dormant within
the body of the one
called Gaara of the Desert
is a monster, and once caged,
he will transform
into the beast,
releasing his awesome Shukaku.
My body will be fueled
by the Shukuaku chakra,
and I will obtain
infinite power.
-No way I'm gonna
let that happen!
Get ready, 'cause here I come!
That bastard.
Keep holding on, Gaara.
'Cause I'm going
to break you out.
-What a waste of breath.
Dashing Wind.
-You want some?
-Such a fool.
-Hang on.
I'm getting you out of there!
Come on, come on!
Don't give up, Gaara!
Keep listening to the
sound of my voice!
Come on, answer me!
What's goin' on down there?
Gaara!
[groan]
-Naruto.
-Hey, Shikamaru.
-So what's the word?
-We do not know Naruto
and Gaara's location.
-Neji, Hinata, look ahead and
tell me what the situation is.
-There's a large metal cage in
the middle of an open canyon.
And I sense a massive amount of
chakra being extracted from it.
-All that energy could
mean Gaara's inside.
-Hey, Shikamaru.
-Yeah, what's up?
-You are aware that Gaara
has a terrifying power lying
dormant within his
body, aren't you?
-Yeah, sorta.
I know about it.
-I'm worried about his chakra
being extracted like this.
He might not be able
to contain the power.
Something truly
horrible could happen.
If he loses control, the
Shukaku could be released.
And when it goes berserk, there
would be no way to stop Gaara.
-What a drag.
-I have wasted too
much time on you.
This game was entertaining,
but it ends now.
-Hot, hot, hot,
hot, hot, hot, hot!
I hate this guy.
I'll rescue you, Gaara!
-What a little pest.
You have no chance, so give up.
Now to end this.
Solid Blanks.
[laughter]
-Ah, how I have longed for
this moment to finally arrive.
Wash over me, Shukaku.
Let me drink your power.
I feel the power.
It's absolutely incredible!
[groan]
-Ah?
-Why don't give up, boy?
The power of the
Shukaku is already mine.
Now I declare war on
the five great nations,
and against every single
ninja of those lands who
took advantage of the
Village of Artisans.
They will suffer
the consequences
of the hundred year grudge
held by my proud people.
For they will all be sacrificed
as we seek our revenge.
-You shut your mouth!
-Huh?
-If you think we're
just going to let
you use our own power against
us, you're dead wrong!
I hope you got a good
taste of Gaara's chakra,
'cause you're about
to give it back!
You got that?
-He must be in pain, so
how can that boy continue
to fight despite
all his injuries?
-I'm curious.
Why are you still trying to win?
Why is that monster of
the Sand Village worth
putting your own
life on the line?
-I'll tell ya why.
'Cause Gaara's my friends,
and my friends are important.
-He told me he would
fight to the end for those
who are important to him.
-He's fighting for
someone important.
For his friend.
-Very well, then.
Die for your friend.
-Huh?
-What do you think
you're doing, girl?
-I get it now.
I've figured out
what Gaara-sensei
was trying to teach me.
Maybe weapons took the lives
of my mother and father.
However, you can
also use a weapon
to protect those close to you.
-Utter nonsense.
-You jerk!
-The transformation's begun.
-What's happened to him?
[groan]
-Huh?
Gaara!
[groan]
-Is that you?
[theme music]
SHIKAMARU: Hey, is that--
TEMARI: This is bad.
If Gaara loses
consciousness in that state,
the Shukaku will emerge
and completely take
control of his body.
If that happens, it
won't matter anymore
if you're an enemy or an ally.
Gaara will level everything
and everyone in his path,
and there's nothing
we can do to stop it.
SHIKAMARU: You're
saying all we can
do is sit here, fold
our arms, and watch?
NARUTO: Next time, Departure.
[theme music]