[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
"The Demon in the Snow."
-Gato, I don't understand.
What is all this?
Why are you here?
And who are these thugs
you brought with you?
Hm?
-Well, you see, there's been
a slight change in plan.
According to the new
plan, you die right here
on this bridge, Zabuza.
-What?
-That's right.
You're too expensive.
So I've decided to take
you off the payroll.
Of course, even these thugs I
brought with me cost something.
So if you could manage to
slaughter a few of them
before they take you
down, I'd appreciate it.
Think you can manage that?
Do you, the Ninja of the Mist?
[snickers]
Look at you.
You look about as
demonic as a wet kitten.
[laughter]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): There
are so many of them.
One rogue ninja was bad enough.
-Well, well, Kakashi.
It would seem our
fight is at an end.
Since I am no longer in
Gato's employ, Tazuna's safe.
We have no quarrel.
-Yeah, I suppose you're right.
-That reminds me,
you little punk.
You grabbed me and
nearly broke my arm!
I've been meaning to
repay you for that.
[grunts] Aah!
-[gasp]
-Huh, I only wish he
was alive to feel it.
-Get away!
Get away from him, you scum!
-Hey, stop!
Use your head.
--[grunts] Well, what
about you, Zabuza?
You going to let him do that?
-Be quiet, you fool.
Haku's dead.
What does it matter?
-(ANGRILY) What?
You mean you could just
stand there and watch
him get treated like a dog?
You and Haku were
together for years.
Doesn't that mean anything?
-You don't understand
the way of Shinobi.
I merely used him
just as Gato used me.
-Huh?
-Now, it's over.
His usefulness is at an end.
The loss of his
strength and skill,
yes, that means something to me.
But the boy-- nothing.
-If you mean that, you're an
even bigger rat than I thought.
-OK, that's enough.
Calm down, Naruto.
He's not the enemy.
Not right now.
-Aah!
Shut up!
As far as I'm concerned,
he's enemy number 1!
Why you, [grunts] you
ungrateful-- after everything
he did for you.
Haku lived for you.
-Is there someone who
is precious to you?
-You were the most important
thing in the world to him.
-For me, there is only
one person who matters.
And my purpose is to
protect and serve him.
And that purpose is what
gives me my strength.
-And he meant nothing to you?
Nothing at all?
HAKU (VOICEOVER):
The way of Shinobi
is very difficult for me.
-While he was sacrificing
everything for you,
you never felt anything
at all for him?
HAKU (VOICEOVER): But
I will do anything
to see that his
dream is fulfilled,
even become Shinobi if I must.
-And if I become
stronger, does that
mean I'll become as
cold-hearted as you are?
He threw his life away.
And for what?
For you and your dream!
-I want only to make
his dream come true.
That is my dream.
NARUTO: You never let him
have a dream of his own.
But he didn't care.
-I was happy.
-And you just tossed him
aside like he was nothing.
A broken tool.
Man, that's so wrong.
So wrong!
-You talk too much.
-Huh?
-Your words cut deep--
deeper than any blade.
While he fought you, his
heart was breaking in two.
You see, Haku was always
too soft and too kind.
He felt pain and sorrow.
And now, curse him,
I feel them, too.
And something else, I
feel content that this
is the way it ends.
-Huh?
-Uh, well, cat got your tongue?
Are you so surprised to
discover that I'm human?
Even Shinobi are human.
No matter how hard we try
to escape that simple fact,
we always fail.
Well, at least, I have failed.
Boy!
-Huh?
ZABUZA: Give me your kunai.
-Uhh.
Here.
-Aah!
That's enough of this!
Do it!
Take him down now!
MEN: Yeah!
Yeah!
-He must be out of his mind!
One against all of us,
what's he thinking!
[grunts and groans]
-Aargh!
-Somebody do something!
[yells]
-Hah!
[whimpers]
He-- he's of the devil!
Ugh!
[grunts]
-[gasps]
[coughs]
-You crazy fool.
If you're so eager to join
your friend, go ahead.
But you're not taking me!
Not this time! [wheezes]
-Uh-uh.
I won't be joining Haku.
Where he's gone,
I cannot follow.
[heaving]
-Stay back!
Stay back!
-We wouldn't be welcome
where Haku's gone to.
Hell is where we're going, Gato!
-Uh, huh.
-I can't think of a more fitting
destination for a demon ninja,
can you?
I'm told there are many demons
down there of all shapes
and sizes.
Oh, yes, I should fit right in.
You, on the other hand,
Gato, well, I fear,
you're in for a long and
very painful eternity!
-Agh!
Aah!
-[growls]
[gato screams]
[men gasp]
-[grunting]
Ungh.
Haku.
So this is goodbye at last.
Not once did I ever
thank you, Haku.
Forgive me for that.
Ugh.
-Uhh.
KAKASHI: Don't turn away.
-Huh?
-When you live like a
warrior, this is how it ends.
-[groans]
[heartbeat]
BOY (VOICEOVER): Where am I?
Am I alive?
Or-- Sakura?
[girl sobbing]
BOY (VOICEOVER): Can it be?
It is.
-[sobs]
-Sakura, it's hard to breathe
with you on top of me.
-Sasuke!
[sobs]
-[grunts]
-Tazuna, he's alive!
Alive!
-Ow!
Sakura, that hurts.
-Sasuke!
Sasuke!
TAZUNA (VOICEOVER): So things
turned out right after all.
SAKURA: No, no,
what are you doing?
You shouldn't move.
-How's Naruto?
And what happened to
that guy in the mask?
-Naruto is just fine.
But the-- the one in
the mask, he's dead.
-Dead?
But how?
Did Naruto do it?
-Oh, I-- I came in late.
I'm not sure what happened.
He was protecting Zabuza.
I had faith in you, Sasuke.
I knew you'd pull through.
You're too cool a guy
to stay down for long.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
He never meant to--
from the very beginning.
SAKURA: Naruto!
-Huh?
SAKURA: Over here!
Look, it's Sasuke!
He's all right!
-Uh, huh?
Huh.
[chuckles]
But how?
ZABUZA (VOICEOVER):
While he fought you,
his heart was breaking in two.
You see, Haku was always
too soft and too kind.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I see.
-Well, well, will
wonders never cease?
Amazing.
-Hey, yoo-hoo!
-Huh?
-Don't go getting
too comfortable.
-This party ain't over yet.
Who's going to pay us
now that Gato's gone?
-No way we're going to
leave here empty-handed.
So we'll just have
to hit that village
and see what they've got for us.
MEN: Yeah!
Come on, let's go!
-Not good.
-Come on Kakashi-sensei!
You must have a
jutsu that could take
care of this bunch of losers!
-Not right now.
I used too much of my chakra.
-Get them, boys!
[men yelling]
MAN: There is one little
thing you're forgetting about.
Before you set one
foot in our village,
you'll have to go
through all of us.
VILLAGERS: Yeah!
-Inari!
-[chuckles]
Heroes usually show up at
the last minute, you know?
-They've all come.
The whole village.
[men gasp]
-Huh, no way I'm going to
miss out on all the fun.
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
[men gasp]
-Hm, I might have just enough
chakra left to help you out.
Shadow Clone Jutsu.
Kakashi style!
KAKASHI CLONES: OK,
still want to fight?
-No way!
[men yelling]
-Victory!
VILLAGERS: All right!
[laughing]
We did it!
Hey!
[cheers]
We did it!
-Sounds like it's over.
-Yeah.
-Kakashi?
-Yeah?
-I have a favor to ask.
-What is it?
-Take me to him.
Before I go, I need to
see him one last time.
-Sure.
[weapons clatter]
-Huh?
-Impossible.
-Snowing at this time of year?
ZABUZA (VOICEOVER):
Is it you, Haku?
Are you weeping?
-Thank you, Kakashi.
You were always at my side.
The least I can do is to
be beside you at the end.
[gasping]
I know it cannot be, but I wish
I could go to where you have
gone.
How I wish I could
join you there, Haku.
[sighs]
-He told me, where
he came from, it
was always snowing all the time.
[sniffles]
-Of course, his spirit
was as pure as the snow.
You never know, Zabuza, maybe
you will join him there.
Who's to say?
SAKURA: Is that really
it, Kakashi-sensei?
-Hm?
-Is that the ninja way?
To use and be used
by people like tools?
-Shinobi are all merely tools
in the hands of destiny.
No point in wondering
whether it's right or wrong.
It just is.
It's the same in the Village
Hidden in the Leaves.
-Well, if you ask me if
that's what being a ninja
is all about,
something's out of whack.
Ugh.
Is that why we go through
all this training?
Just to end up like them?
-What is the reason for that?
-[sighs]
Well, it's a question
without an answer.
And that is something
we ninja have
to deal with every day of our
lives, like Zabuza and the kid.
-OK!
ALL: Hm?
-I've just come to a decision.
From now on, I'm finding
my own ninja way.
A way that's straight and
true and without any regrets.
From now on, I'm following
the way of Naruto!
-Uh.
[chuckles]
-We could never have finished
the bridge without you.
I can't tell you how much
we're going to miss you.
-Do be careful.
-Thank you for everything.
-Now, now, don't
get all choked up.
We'll come back and
visit real soon.
-You swear you will?
-Huh?
-Of course.
You know, Inari, it's all
right to cry if you want.
There's nothing wrong with that.
Go for it.
-Who says I want to cry?
Anyway, if there's
nothing wrong with it,
then why don't
you go on and cry?
-(HOARSELY) No, you first.
-[muffled sobbing]
-Forget it!
-Nah, uh.
[boys sobbing]
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Boys can be so pathetic.
TAZUNA: It was all his doing.
That boy made you
stronger, Inari.
And you, in turn, made
the rest of us stronger.
It was thanks to
that boy, we were
able to build a bridge to
a place we've never known,
a place where we
found our courage,
a place to fulfill our dreams.
-Say, speaking of the bridge,
now that it's finished, uh,
shouldn't we name it?
-Yes, of course.
Huh, and I know just the name.
-You do?
What?
TAZUNA: We'll call it
the Great Naruto Bridge.
-[chuckles]
That's a very good name.
-Ha-ha!
As soon as we get
back, I'm going
to let Iruka-sensei fix me
up a whole mess of ramen
to celebrate our
mission accomplished.
Oh, and just wait
till I tell Konohamaru
about all my adventures.
The kid's going to worship me.
-Hey.
-Yeah?
-Not you, Naruto.
Sasuke, when we
get back, you want
to go out and do
something together?
-I don't think so.
Thanks.
-Oh, OK.
-Sakura, I'd do something
with you if you want.
-What?
Hey, that was a
private conversation!
-Uhh, ow!
-You sure about
that name, Tazuna?
TAZUNA: [chuckles]
It's a name that
brought us good luck.
It'll do the same
for the bridge.
I think this bridge will
stand for a long, long time.
Perhaps it will even
be famous one day.
The name Naruto, known
throughout the world.
That would be
something, wouldn't it?
[ship horn blowing]
THEME SONG: Cultivate your
hunger before you idealize.
Motivate your anger,
make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain,
never coming down.
Break into the contents,
never falling down.
My knee is still
shaking, like I was 12.
Sneaking out of the
classroom by the backdoor.
A man railed at me twice,
though, but I didn't care.
Waiting is wasting
for people like me.
Don't try to live so wise.
Don't cry 'cause
you're so right.
Don't try with fakes
or fears 'cause you
will hate yourself in the end.
Don't try to live so wise.
Don't cry 'cause
you're so right.
Don't try with fakes
or fears 'cause you
will hate yourself in the end.
Don't try to live so wise.
Don't cry 'cause
you're so right.
Don't try with fakes--
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Here I am, back
from defeating Zabuza,
ready to really kick butt.
And what do I get?
More training, more
tests, more exams.
How long are they
going to keep us here?
It's like we're in daycare.
Man, don't they
understand there are
a lot of other dangerous
ninja like Zabuza out there?
Next time, a new chapter begins.
"The Chunin Exam."