[music playing]
[theme music]
[waves]
-How is she?
-I'm not really sure.
She collapsed so suddenly.
-I see.
The ship carrying their payment
sets sail in the morning.
We should get back to the inn.
-Wait a minute, Shino, what's
going to happen to Isaribi?
-Who cares what happens to her?
She's the demon of the ocean.
-Yeah, I know, but--
-What exactly went on between
the two of you, anyway?
-What do you mean?
I told you before, didn't I?
That girl totally saved my butt!
[water bubbling]
[water running]
-What happened?
-Uh, I'm very sorry.
It just slipped out of my hand.
-Ah.
-I'll get this
cleaned up right away.
-Anko.
-Yes?
-The work I've been doing here?
The Hokage already
knows about it.
-Understood.
[music playing]
-So you're telling us this
girl Isaribi saved your life?
-That's right.
If she hadn't come when she
did, I wouldn't even be here.
-That may be, but
there's no question
she's in league with
the men who attacked us.
And anyway, our
hands are tied here.
Our mission is to protect
the government's money,
and catch the
demon of the ocean.
-He's right.
I mean all you have
to do is look at her.
She's obviously this demon
thing we're looking for.
-Yeah, sure.
But there's got to be a
reason for all of this.
Maybe if we were to
go after her, then--
-Will you drop it already?
You're not going
to go after her.
You don't even have
a clue where to look.
-Actually, I might.
-Wait, for real?
But how?
-I overheard something.
There's an island
out here that's
at the heart of all those people
being taken away by spirits.
-So where do we find it?
-It's a barren crag where
the demon of the ocean lives,
Demon Island.
-Demon Island?
-Oh, sensei, you're up.
Are you feeling all right?
-Yeah, I am.
But forget about me.
There's something I need to
tell you guys about the demon.
This isn't some sea
creature we're dealing with.
Our demon was made in a lab.
It used to be human.
-Huh?
-What did you say?
[music playing]
-Don't you mess things
up like that again.
-Yes, sir.
[music playing]
-Look!
It's the monster!
-What monster?
-Get out of here.
-You're a bad omen.
-Yeah, take this!
-Hey, it's that girl.
The one who got taken
away by spirits.
-She was the only
one who came back.
-Yeah, steer clear of her.
[music playing]
-It used to be a human?
What are you talking about?
-A good number of people
did mysteriously vanish
in the Land of the
Sea 10 years ago,
but it wasn't
because of any demon.
They were being snatched up
and used as test subjects.
In experiments
conducted by Orochimaru.
-Orochimaru.
So you're telling me he's
mixed up in this somehow?
-I don't understand, though.
Orochimaru?
An experiment?
Where is all this coming from?
-I think I'd better
start at the beginning,
back when he left the village.
More than 10 years
ago, Orochimaru's lust
for knowledge and power
became so insatiable
that he gradually exceeded
the normal limitations
of a shinobi, and
began experimenting
with forbidden jutsu.
-Oh, such a pity.
-Of course this all
became common knowledge
in the Leaf Village.
-After him!
-Don't let that
traitor get away!
-But his missions had taken
him far and wide in this world.
The Hidden Leaf Village
wasn't the only place
he had research
facilities set up.
-And one of those is hidden
on Demon Island, I take it.
-So the people who disappeared?
-Human guinea pigs.
-That psychotic lunatic.
What the heck does
he think people are?
-So what's our next move?
-Isn't it obvious?
We bust into their hideout.
We're going to march right in
and get Isaribi out of there.
-Sounds like a plan.
Let's pay the demon of the
ocean a visit, shall we?
[waves]
-So sensei, how exactly
do you know so much
about this Demon Island, anyway?
-Orochimaru was the
was the Jonin I trained
under back in the day.
What
-Oh!
-Tell me when we get
close to the island.
The pain is getting worse.
-Someone draws near.
-So what do you
think we should do?
-I leave that to you.
-All right.
-Hm.
The arrogance.
He'll get his soon enough.
[waves]
-Oh.
-This way.
-Hurry!
-How's it look, Shino?
-We're good.
-OK.
[footsteps]
-So one of their
ships is on the move?
Well, perfect timing.
Well done.
Sending you back
to Mother Island
really paid off then, huh?
What's the matter?
You look a little pale today.
-Do you think I'll ever
be, be normal again?
I've gathered information
on the ships docked back
at the village, just
like you told me to.
I've pillaged them for you.
So--
-I cannot believe this.
You're not serious, are you?
You're my magnum opus child.
I mean, you're the
prototype for this project.
You know what the deal is.
The data that you're
generating is invaluable.
Besides, your total
cooperation was
one of the conditions
of our agreement.
Look, don't worry.
We'll have all the data
we need pretty soon.
I'll honor my promise.
Just as long as you don't
give me any reason not to,
is that clear?
-Yes.
-Well then, if it
is, why don't you
go and keep our
guests company, dear?
-Very well.
-You really are
cruel, you know that?
-It doesn't look like
anyone's home right now.
-Sh!
-So what do you guys think
they're doing in here?
-Birds?
Or fish?
-Easy.
You're in a tight spot now, huh?
You should never have
messed with Shinobi
from the Hidden Leaf.
You little!
[music playing]
[screaming]
-Everyone OK?
-You bet!
[laughter]
-What a joke.
Don't you people get
tired of saving the day?
-You're the guy from last night.
-I recognize that face.
The Chunin Exams,
if memory serves.
-Yeah, you're right.
He was matched up against
Sasuke, wasn't he?
-You mean the guy
who was with Kabuto?
-You got that right.
Of course that was the
last time I saw him.
It's been awhile now.
-He used a jutsu that siphoned
off his opponent's chakra.
-You were the guy who sucked
up all of Sasuke's strength.
I remember now.
-Well come and
get it, you three.
Let me show you just how
much I've changed since then.
-Fine.
Get ready, pal.
I'm going to put
your lights out.
-Naruto, wait.
-Why?
What is it?
-You go on ahead.
I think I'm better
suited for this.
-Huh?
-His jutsu will be a problem
for your style of close combat.
Besides, we can't all
stick around here.
-All right.
Wipe the floor with him.
-Be careful!
-Not so--
-Parasitic insects, huh?
[gasping]
[door creaking]
[music playing]
-Found him.
[footsteps]
What the?
-Welcome.
Or should I say,
long time, no see.
-What's going on here?
Amachi?
-I have to admit, I'm a little
surprised that you'd return,
after all that
happened back then.
-What are you talking about?
-You mean you don't remember?
-Look, I don't have time
to waste on you, OK?
Where is Orochimaru?
-Orochimaru?
-Cut the act.
He's here now, isn't he?
-So, the curse mark's acting
up, even after he split.
I wouldn't have guessed
that was possible.
Well, you're half right, anyway.
Orochimaru was here.
But that was well over two
weeks ago at this point.
-I don't believe you.
-Believe whatever you want.
It doesn't matter to me.
-So you mean to tell me that
the pain I'm feeling right now
is from him being here
close to a full month ago?
-Just a minute.
-Sensei!
-Hey, glad you could make it.
-Well, well.
You brought Genin.
Look at you, you're
all grown up now, Anko.
-Who is this clown?
-Meet Amachi.
He's a medical ninja who's
teamed up with Orochimaru,
and conducts research here.
His master's not around, though.
This whole rigmarole
is Amachi's doing.
-So he's behind it all.
You and your crazy
experiments are finished, pal!
-Crazy?
This isn't a joke.
I've devoted my entire
life to this research.
-Research, huh?
-Look here.
This girl is capable of adapting
to an aquatic environment.
Combining the ability
to breathe underwater
with advanced
strength and agility.
It's always been my
dream, a ninja corps
for underwater warfare.
And this girl here
is the first step.
-A ninja corps for
underwater warfare?
-That's right.
An unparalleled military
force that can move freely
on both land and sea.
Once I've done it, we'll
spread across the nations
and take complete control
of marine shipping routes.
Astounding, isn't it?
With that kind of strength,
the world will kneel before me,
and Orochimaru will rue the
day he abandoned my work.
But it will be too late!
-These are people
you're talking about.
They're not your tools.
-Oh, that's a shame.
I figured someone
your age would have
grasped the
importance of my work.
Well, no big deal.
You're just another bunch of
brainless guinea pigs, right?
Who cares what you think.
-Oh yeah?
Ha!
-Thank you, Isaribi.
-Come on, out of the way.
-I'm not moving.
-Aw, come on.
Running in circles won't
get you anywhere, kid.
[rumbling]
-No!
-I don't get it.
Why are protecting this moron?
I mean, he's the one
who did this to you.
-I know!
But, but I don't
have a choice now.
He's the only person who can
turn my body back to normal
again.
He promised me that he would.
Here, look.
-What are you?
-Look at me.
People in this world
judge others based solely
on their appearance.
They stay away when they
see me covered in bandages.
Imagine what they'd
do if they saw
a monster covered in scales?
I just want my body back, OK?
I want to be human.
I'll do whatever it
takes to be myself again.
-But you still are human.
It doesn't matter
what you look like.
And yet you're attacking
ships with these guys
and sending them to the bottom.
It's not a face that
makes someone a monster,
it's the choices they
make with their life.
-Just shut up!
Stop it!
-But I didn't--
-I don't want to hear any more.
Just shut up!
Why does everyone have
to be so cruel to me?
-You don't get it.
You see, you and I, you
and I are exactly alike.
-Be quiet!
You're human, aren't you?
You have no idea what
I'm going through.
I, I only wish I was like you.
[crying]
-Now, now, don't cry.
I'll have you back to
normal in no time, Isaribi.
-Watch out!
-That paper bomb was
right on the money.
Thanks for distracting
them, Isaribi.
-Are you OK?
-Take care of it, will you?
-Got it.
-Isaribi, let's go.
-Wait a minute!
It's not too late yet.
Don't go.
-What say we get this
out of the way, everyone.
-Give it up.
It's over, friend.
You're one more guinea pig
for Amachi's collection.
An insect clone?
We both steal chakra
from our opponents,
so this won't be an
easy fight to finish.
[music playing]
-He disappeared?
What's his game?
-Naruto!
-I'm going to squeeze the
life right out of your body!
[music playing]
What is this?
-Mind destruction jutsu success!
-All right.
Nice work, Ino.
-I don't know what
it is you're doing,
but you'd better let go of me.
This isn't fair.
-What are you whining about?
We're Shinobi, pal.
Everything's fair game.
-And you call yourself a ninja?
-Shut up.
-Huh?
What is that?
[rockfall]
-I think the whole
place is coming down.
-They're taking us
out with the building.
-Aw, you gotta be kidding me.
-Hurry, the entrance
is already blocked.
-I always knew somebody
would find this place.
It's a decrepit old
building, but a fine tomb
for the likes of that bunch.
-One of us didn't
make it in time, huh?
-No big deal.
These ships just carry money.
We don't need a lot of brawn.
-Man, there's got to
be a way out of here.
[theme music]
-Shino!
Where's the exit?
-How should I know?
-What do we do?
-A little less whining,
a little more running!
-But I don't see
an exit, anywhere.
-That's because it collapsed.
-What?
-Then we'll be buried alive?
-Looks like we
need my resei gun!
-Calm down.
-What do you mean, I am calm!
-Shut up already!
Just step back and
give me a little room.
-Next time, despair.
A fractured heart.
[music playing]