[music playing]
[theme song]
MAN: More to the right.
That's it.
Steady.
-Well, there it is.
Sheesh.
All this trouble for
a stupid tea cup.
It's crazy.
[sigh] I've got to
deliver this thing?
-More than that.
You've got to protect
it with your life.
This is no ordinary
delivery mission.
That thing-- as
you so nicely put
it-- is a famous
national treasure.
It's called the
Beauty of Nature,
and it's worth the
prince's ransom.
-What?
It is?
-It needs to go to Kale Avenue
where it will be exhibited.
See that it gets there safely.
-OK but what's with
the enormous safe?
How do we carry that?
-Thanks for showing up.
[barking dog]
-Why are you here?
-Lady Tsunade ordered me to come
along as backup just in case
you needed help.
Which knowing you,
you probably will.
You find out anything
more about it?
-Nope.
Not a thing, except that it's
some kind of national treasure.
[chains rattling]
MAN: Hey you, dummy!
-Hmm?
-Me?
-Huh?
-What's wrong with you?
The sign says no trespassing
in nice big letters.
Can't you read?
-Yeah, but we're here on
orders from Lady Tsunade.
We're supposed to escort this
thing wherever it's going.
-Yup.
That's the dealio.
Got the papers right here.
-Oh Yeah?
huh.
-Hey guys watch out!
Hey! it's going to collapse!
[breaking wood]
[shouting]
KIBA: It's coming down.
-(SHOUTING) Buddy,
don't just stand there!
Get out of the way!
-Huh?
Hey, what is wrong with you?
Catch it quick.
[gasp]
-It's your mission
to protect it, right?
So get to work and start
protecting it, ya morons.
-Yeah, but--
MAN: Hurry up already.
Throw your bodies under
it if you have to.
[music playing]
[grunting]
-That's it.
[music playing]
-Eah, ugh.
-Got it.
Whew!
That was close.
-OK.
That's great, but ah-- what are
we supposed to do with this?
-Well, that's your problem.
-Huh?
Man, what a jerk.
[snapping sound]
-Ahh.
[crash]
[shouting]
-Are you really as big a
jerk as I think you are?
-Hey!
In case you hadn't noticed,
we could have been killed.
-So what?
I thought you
ninja were supposed
to risk your lives to
fulfill your mission.
-(ANGRY) Well wait a
second there buddy.
Hold on!
-Don't call me buddy.
I'm the client who hired you.
I'm Shin'emon.
So since you weren't
killed, let's get moving.
-You believe this guy?
[grunt]
SHIN'EMON: Want to
get him Akamaru?
[dog barking]
NARUTO: (ANGRILY) Ooh let me
pound him with my rasengan.
SHIN'EMON: (LAUGHING) Sheesh,
you guys are touchy aren't ya?
Come on, hurry up.
Where's that indomitable
ninja spirit?
-Slow down.
We got a long way to go yet.
-Watch it, or you'll
run out of steam.
-I thought you guys were
supposed to be in good shape.
What a joke.
[music playing]
[rushing water]
-You're not serious.
You got tired and dropped it?
[rushing water]
-OK, so I blew it.
-All Right.
Guess we'll just have
to take the long way
back down to the
river and fish it out.
[dog whimper]
-Huh? Don't look now,
but I don't think
we've got that kind of time.
-Huh?
[music playing]
Oh no.
What are we going to do now?
It'll go over those
falls long before we
can get back down there.
-Try this.
-What do you mean try this?
What's that for?
-For bungee jumping.
[music playing]
-(YELLING) I wasn't ready.
Look at it this way, if you
don't survive at least you're
feedin' the fishes! [laughs]
[music playing]
[boing]
-Ahh
[boing, boing]
-Ahh, it worked!
I got it!
Woah.
Ahhh.
Whew.
Now that's what I
call thinking fast.
-It's not over yet you idiot.
Turn around.
[dog barking]
-Huh?
What is it?
[rushing water]
-Ooh. [screams]
[music playing]
-Ahh.
My precious.
Thank goodness
you're still safe.
-And what about him?
-What are you so
upset about? huh?
Ninja die all the
time don't they?
It's part of your
job description.
NARUTO: (ANGRILY) Yeah?
Well maybe it's time
you tried dying once.
[whimper]
SHIN'EMON: Whoa.
NARUTO: Let me go,
[? shin. ?] Let me at him.
I'm going to rasengan
this jerk into next week.
SHIN'EMON: Easy does it Naruto.
Calm down.
[shouting]
SHIN'EMON: Hey, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Sheesh.
[birds cawing]
[wind blowing]
[grunting]
-Act natural, will ya?
-What are you talking about?
I'm acting perfectly natural.
-Might as well put a sign on it.
MAN: Whoa guys.
Hold on there a minute.
[music playing]
KIBA: Oh, man.
-Are you carrying something
valuable in that little safe?
I'd be careful if I were you.
This is a dangerous place.
-That's right.
You better let us take it.
We'll look after it for you.
-Thanks a lot, but
it's really not-- I--
I mean don't let
the safe fool ya.
It's nothing valuable.
Right?
-No, absolutely not.
There's nothing inside but
a worthless piece of junk.
Right buddy?
Isn't that right?
-Are you guys insane or what?
Don't you realize
that inside here
lies one of the most priceless
work of art ever created
by mortal hands?
Not valuable?
You ignorant clods.
The Beauty of Nature is more
precious than human life
itself.
You don't even deserve to be
on the same planet with it.
-What a piece of work.
Will you tell him to shut up?
-Buddy, ixnay on the eciouspray.
-Buddy?
I'm no buddy of yours.
How dare you call
The Beauty of Nature
a worthless piece of junk?
-So that thing's more
valuable than human life, huh?
-In that case, you'll understand
why we have to take you down.
[gasp]
-Ah, forgive me.
I'd love to stay and chat,
but I really have to be going.
I have a date.
[nervous laughter]
[laughter]
[shouting]
KIBA: Run!
-OK.
Kiba you stay with
buddy here, while I
peel off and try to
draw these clowns away.
-All right.
Move.
-Ahh.
[music playing]
[dog barking]
MALE SPEAKER: Get 'em.
-Oh no.
There's more of them and
they're trying to cut us off.
-Why are you running
away you coward?
I'm supposed to run.
You're supposed to
stand and fight.
[shouting]
-Oh brother, what a jerk.
Go on ahead.
OK Akamaru, play time.
[dog growling]
[boom]
-It Sounds like they're
having another fight in town.
-Yes ma'am.
It sure does sound
like a fight all right.
-(SIGHING) I wish they
wouldn't fight all the time.
-Yes you're right ma'am.
Fighting's very bad.
[slurping soup]
NARUTO: Hey, buddy.
-Huh?
[heavy breathing]
SHIN'EMON: Well it took
you two long enough.
NARUTO: You're
really asking for it.
You know that?
KIBA: That does it.
Fang over fang Akamaru.
[dog barking]
SHIN'EMON: Aah-- hey, joking.
it was just a joke with
the kidding.
[music playing]
[eagle cry]
-[laughs] It's ours.
The thing we've been looking
for just fell right in our
[evil laughter]
[bird song]
[dog growling]
-Someone's here.
-You sure?
[whoosh]
[gasp]
-OK.
Stay here, and keep down.
-Yeah, you got it.
-All right.
Whoever you are, why don't you
come out and show yourself?
[bang]
[coughing]
-Very clever.
Smoke screen.
-Instead of sitting there
admiring them, why don't you
get up there and
fight them? [cries]
-(ANGRILY) Shut
up and stay down.
Let's do it Kiba.
-You're on.
-Sharukan Jutsu.
[explosion]
-All right, let's show
'em what we can do.
[dog growling]
-Long as you can
smell 'em, it doesn't
matter if we can't see 'em.
Let's sniff 'em out boy.
[dog barking]
-OK, OK.
Where are you hiding?
Huh?
[laughter]
[shout]
MALE SPEAKER: The Beauty
of Nature, mine at last.
NARUTO: Where is he?
[dog growling]
KIBA: All right, Akamaru.
Beast mimicry.
Man-beast clones!
(SHOUTING) Fang over fang!
[grunting]
-Do your thing Akamaru.
[dog barking]
KIBA: Dynamic barking!
SHIN'EMON: Yuck.
What the hell was that?
-What is it?
What's the matter?
Huh?
SHIN'EMON: I'm wet.
-OK.
Hang on, I'm coming.
SHIN'EMON: Naruto where are you?
Get over here, and protect
me you idiot! [gasp] Oh.
Finally.
Where have you been?
huh?
[whimpering]
[shouting]
[music playing]
-It's OK now.
Are you all right?
-Naruto?
-Huh?
Ugh.
SHIN'EMON: That dumb
mutt peed all over me.
You guys are gonna pay for this.
-Never mind that,
we've got to get
your national treasure back.
-Can't believe we
let him get it.
Man.
I knew I should have
taken charge of it myself.
What was I thinking?
-We'll be able to track
them by Akamaru's dynamic
marking if they
haven't gone too far.
[dog barking]
-You don't say boy?
So they're still close, huh?
-Then what are we waitin' for?
-We have it.
We finally have it.
[grunting]
[rattling]
-Huh?
-Good job.
You just gave us away.
-I didn't see it.
-I don't know how the
heck they found us,
but they're not
getting it get back.
Let's move!
NARUTO: Hold it right there!
KIBA: (SHOUTING) Give that back!
-Not in this lifetime.
Get him!
-OK.
Leave these three
to Kiba and me.
You go after the leader and try
to keep him from getting away.
-Right.
-Ready Kiba?
-You bet.
-Would you stop already?
[music playing]
-I gotcha now, you lousy thief.
-No, I've got you.
So long.
[shout]
[grunting]
[grunt]
-All right.
Now for the last one.
-Let go of it.
Give it to me.
-No, never. [grunting]
SHIN'EMON: Ugh.
-You ignorant fool.
You'll be lucky if I let you
walk away with your life.
Ahh.
[grunting]
-Give it back.
I'm warning you, give it back.
You can't have it.
[shout]
-Huh?
Ahh.
-You don't get it.
No one understands do they?
I'll be luckily to
walk away with my life?
How many times do
I have to say it?
No human life is as valuable
as The Beauty of Nature.
Not yours, not
mine, not anyone's.
Now do you understand
why I won't give up?
Because it doesn't matter
whether I live or die.
And it never did.
[shout]
[grunt]
-(ANGRILY) Now give it back.
[laughter]
-Hey buddy, you OK?
[grunting]
[laughter]
-There you are.
What's wrong?
Were they too much for you?
-Hardly.
You should talk, you look
like you just got run over.
[evil laughter]
-You!
-Well then.
If I can't have it, no one can.
[grunting]
[gasps]
[crashing sounds]
[evil laughter]
-Now you're all finished!
-He's right.
We're finished if
we don't move fast.
-Come on, let's get out of here.
Run!
-Ahh.
[crashing sounds]
-(SHOUTING) Buddy!
-We still got a chance.
I'll toss it to you and
you can take it to safety.
-What are you talking about?
Don't be an idiot.
Just climb over the rock
and let's get out of here.
-There's no time.
Forget about me.
Just hurry up and take it
while you still have a chance.
-Shut up and get over here.
-(URGENTLY) Hurry!
Dah.
Ugh.
Ahh.
MAN: Move!
[cracking]
[grunting]
-Buddy, you all right?
[whimpering]
-Oh no.
Don't fall.
[grunting]
-(SHOUTING) No!
Don't go after it!
Just crawl back this way
and reach our your hand.
I've got ya.
[music playing]
[grunting]
-Are you nuts?
Towards me you idiot,
and reach out your hand.
-(ANGRY SHOUTING) Do I
have to spell it out again?
Forget about me, and
save The Beauty of Nature
you stupid ninja.
My life doesn't matter.
-Huh?
-He's not gonna listen Naruto.
forget about him.
I say we leave him and
his stinking tea cup,
and get out while we can.
-Go ahead, do what you want.
[gasp]
[shattering noise]
[rumbling]
-It's gone.
Forever.
[cracking noise]
[shout]
-(SHOUTING) Buddy, no!
-He's done for.
[yelling]
[music playing]
-This, is this it?
-Hey, in case you
hadn't noticed,
we could have been killed.
-So what.
I thought you
ninja were supposed
to risk your lives to
fulfill your mission?
So since you weren't
killed, let's get moving.
[music playing]
[grunt]
-Not valuable?
You ignorant clods.
The Beauty of Nature is more
precious than human life
itself.
You don't even deserve to be
on the same planet with it.
-Is this how it ends?
-Huh?
Argh.
Ugh.
-You don't get it?
No one understands do they?
I'll be lucky to walk
away with my life?
How many times do
I have to say it?
No human life is as valuable
as The Beauty of Nature.
Not yours, not
mine, not anyone's.
Now do you understand
why I won't give up?
Because it doesn't matter
whether I live or die
and it never did.
Yah!
-Ahh.
-No.
[music playing]
-I don't want to die.
[grunting]
[gasping]
-Gotcha.
Sorry.
But I still think
there's nothing
more valuable than a human life.
[creaking noise]
[gasp]
[crying]
[plink]
-Nice bungee jump.
[giggle]
[chatter]
-Well then, what do you
two suggest I do now?
-Well, uh--
-I don't know.
It's a shame about
your national treasure.
-What are you gonna do?
Sit around and cry about it?
I didn't think you
ninja were supposed
to give up that easily.
-The priceless treasure
was lost forever.
There's no changing that.
-So I'll just have
to make another one.
-Huh?
-What are you talking about?
What do you mean you'll
just make another one?
[boing]
-Hmm?
-Huh?
-Hey, that's a picture of you.
-Appearing this week famed
Potter and living national
treasure Shin'emon, creator
of The Beauty of Nature.
-Ehh
-Woah.
Wait a minute.
-Huh?
-So the national
treasure was you?
You're the one who
made that thing?
-But I thought you were,
you know, just a client.
-What's wrong?
You never been hired by living
national treasure before?
You got a problem with that?
-No, but it's just kinda--
-Come on, where's that
indomitable ninja spirit?
Cheer up you guys.
You got me here safe and sound.
And as we've all come
to learn, my life
is the greatest treasure of all.
So give yourselves a
big pat on the back.
You did a good job.
For Genin, that is.
Later.
I'm off to make another
priceless irreplaceable
masterpiece.
[laughs]
[music playing]
[theme music]
LADY TSUNADE: Your mission is to
help escort a captured renegade
to the capital.
NARUTO: What do
you mean, renegade?
LADY TSUNADE: He's from a
gang of rogue Shinobi who
no longer owe allegiance
to any master.
MAN: They have betrayed
their own ninja way.
The worst of the worst.
LADY TSUNADE: You all
understand the assignment?
WOMAN: You said a gang.
So chances are, his comrades
will try and free him.
LADY TSUNADE: Exactly.
And that's why I'm sending you.
To make sure they don't succeed.
GROUP: Right.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next time,
"The Enemy-- Ninja Drop-outs."
[theme music]