[theme music]
-Orochimaru.
The Fuma are no
different than us.
They love their clan
just like we do.
To play on people's
feelings like
that-- to take their
feelings of love and pride,
and twist them into
a force for evil.
How low can you get?
Get ready, Orochimaru,
because I'm coming
and I'm going to take you down.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Pure Terror!
The House of Orochimaru.
-I don't get it.
The Pervy Sage got his butt
kicked by Lady Tsunade's
numbing medicine,
so how the heck
did he detect Sasame's
medicine this time around?
-Yeah, for Master Jiraiya,
that was pretty sharp thinking.
-Hey, hey, you both
heard Sasame talking
about how Hanzaki was
a traitor, didn't you?
That's how I figured it out.
By chance, Hanzaki told me
everything I needed to know.
-When Orochimaru first came to
this land, there was much talk.
Many among my people
wanted to use his power
to revive our clan.
Others saw his evil intentions.
We implored the rest not to
join forces with this person.
-Hm.
And that's why you were chased
out of your own village.
-Yes.
It was probably an
order from Orochimaru.
They said we were endangering
our clan and chased us away.
They called us traitors.
-So you see, the moment
that Sasame called Hanzaki
a traitor, I knew she
had gotten mixed up
with a group on
Orochimaru's side.
What are you doing?
-Wait, Pervy Sage.
Let's just calm down here, OK?
-No, I deserve this.
-But Sasame, you only did
this so you could find Arashi,
isn't that right?
-I'm so sorry.
I just thought this would be
the only thing I could do.
-Master Jiraiya,
Sasame just did what
she did because she
wanted to see her cousin.
You've got to forgive her.
-I'm with sakura.
Give her a break.
-The law of the shinobi
cannot be ignored.
[gasp]
-For the things
that she has done,
there must be
severe consequences.
Huh?
-Well then, I guess
you're just going
to have to punish me instead.
I made a promise,
I swore no matter
what, that I'd help Sasame
track down her cousin Arashi.
If I don't keep
my word, then I'll
have violated my ninja way.
-Me too, Master Jiraiya.
-Now take it easy.
I mean, it's not as if I'm
going to eat her alive.
Sasame, my dear, Hanzaki has
been quite worried about you.
He suspected you might
leave your village
to go look for Arashi.
-Huh?
-After you take us to
Orochimaru's hideout,
you'll immediately be sent back
to the inn where Hanzaki is,
and wait there for us to return.
That shall be the
punishment for your actions.
-Master Jiraiya.
-I got to give you more
credit, Pervy Sage.
-Well, Hanzaki did treat me
to a lot of expensive stuff
at the Fuma Tavern, and
to pay him back for it,
he kind of asked me to
look after Sasame for him.
-Huh?!
-We should've known it
was something that sleazy.
-That's the last time
I give you any credit.
-Hey, hey, hey, cut me
some slack, all right?
Adults are allowed to take a
break at a tavern now and then.
-That's the hideout.
-You've done your part.
Leave the rest to us.
-Careful, Sasame, on
your way back to the inn.
-Don't worry, OK?
Like I said, I'm not going to
quit until I bring Arashi back
to you safe and sound.
-Take care of I him.
I'm counting on you.
-Just leave it to me.
You're going to be amazed at
how daring my rescue plan is.
Gyah!
-Can it!
Would you quit yakking about
how great you are, Naruto?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): He's there.
That's where Sasuke is.
JIRAIYA: This appears
to be the only entrance.
SAKURA: If this is an ambush,
we'll be easy pickings.
NARUTO: Well, there's nothing
else we can do but go find out.
JIRAIYA: Let's not be hasty.
Three big rats will
definitely attract attention.
So why don't we
send in a critter
that won't Summoning Jutsu.
-Yo.
-Th-- th-- that's
a talking frog.
NARUTO: Hey, long time no see.
Oh, Sakura, this is Gamakichi.
-Gamakichi?
-See that entryway?
We need you to check it out.
-No problemo.
That's a simple enough task.
Leave it to me.
[squirming]
-I can't help it.
Frogs just really
give me the creeps.
-Hm, there doesn't seem
to be anything fishy.
JIRAIYA: At least there's
no trap at the doorway.
SASAME (VOICEOVER): Arashi.
-So far, I don't see anything
out of the ordinary down here.
-Hm.
-What should we do?
-We have no choice but
to split up into three.
-Hah, my gut's telling
me it's the middle door.
-No, wait.
-What the heck?
-In situations like this,
you can't be too careful.
All right, guess I'm
going through this one.
-What was that?
-Come on, how was that
any different from my gut
instinct, Pervy Sage?
-Well, it's all about technique.
If you haven't found
anything after 30 minutes,
we'll meet back at this spot.
Got it?
-Got it.
-Naruto, Sakura, for your
own safety, the two of you
had better stick together.
Listen up, from this point on,
it's the first circle of hell.
A snake or some demon
might attack you.
Stay on alert and be prepared.
-Right.
-I understand.
-Me and Sakura are
going down the middle.
-And that leaves
this way for me.
-See ya.
Huh, I smell perfume.
[koto plays]
-I'm being invited in.
I suppose it'll be more exciting
if I accept the invitation.
Oh.
-We heard guests would be
arriving from far away.
So Lord Orochimaru
instructed me to provide you
with some entertainment.
-I feel like I'm dealing
with a fox or badger spirit.
-If you're implying that I'm
some sort of fox or badger,
perhaps you want to step
over to this side of the room
and check for yourself to
see if I have a tail or not.
-Well, I clearly picked an
interesting path, didn't I?
How about yours, Naruto?
-Sakura, careful where you step.
There's no telling what sort
of traps there might be.
-Yeah.
-Huh?
-Naruto, what?
Huh?
And you were the one who said
to be careful where you step.
-That trick floor was ingenious
No one could have seen it!
Aw man, what else
is going to happen?
[thumping]
-Sakura!
-Naruto!
It's all my fault.
Naruto, no!
NARUTO: What the heck hit me?
I kind of stuck.
Give me a hand?
-You're alive?
Why'd you scream in
such a misleading way.
I thought you--
-Just help me, will you?
-Ugh, sometimes
you're so annoying.
-Ah, you saved me.
-You're welcome.
I'll take the lead from here.
[scream]
-Thanks, Naruto.
-It's going to be OK.
Just hold on.
-Naruto!
Naruto.
Naruto!
NARUTO: Sakura.
[grunt]
-Naruto, are you all right?
-Don't worry about me.
I'm fine.
You just get out of this trap
hallway as fast as you can.
-But I--
NARUTO: I said go!
I promise I'll be
right behind you.
-Are you sure?
NARUTO (STRAINING):
Oh yeah, I'll
catch up with you in no time.
-You better catch up.
You made me a promise.
[koto playing]
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
Hm, the sake
doesn't taste like it's
been tampered with.
So then what kind of
snare is she setting?
-Right.
You're from the
Sound Village, so you
must be planning to use
some kind of music jutsu.
-I'm afraid this song
isn't only for our guests.
I'm also playing for myself.
-I see.
And what do you play when
you play from the heart?
-I composed this music to
accompany my own funeral.
-Trying to seduce me?
You've underestimated
this Jiraiya-- [groaning]
-Escorting our guest
to the underworld
is my final mission before
I can go there as well.
-A false ceiling?
-I need to hurry up and
get out of this pit.
Shadow Clone Jutsu.
-This is torture.
-You got to be kidding me
-Just give me your hand.
We need to combine our chakra
and create the Rasengan.
-What are you talking about?
We can't stretch our
bodies out any further
than we already have.
-My muscles--
they're cramping up.
-Aw man, I got to
think of something.
[clanging]
-Huh?
What the--
-Water?
What next?
-Woo hoo!
I found dry land.
-Hey, get off of my face.
-Ah, Naruto.
what are you doing here?
-Gamakichi, do you see
any way out of this place?
-Sorry, pal, I don't.
I was flushed down here
just like you were.
-Terrific.
I'm doomed.
-Hey, are you all right?
-I'm drowning,
what do you think?
[gurgling noises]
-Naruto's been a while.
Maybe I should just go back.
[door creak]
KABUTO: It's quite
admirable that you made it
this far, Sakura.
-I know that voice.
Is it Kabuto?
-Isn't it ironic?
You dragged down your
team at the Chunin exam,
but now look at you.
You're the only person from
the Hidden Leaf Village
who is able to make it
this far into our compound.
-I'm not here by myself.
Naruto and Master Jiraiya
will be along any minute now.
Tell me where Sasuke is.
He is all right, isn't he?
-Enough about Sasuke.
If I were you, I'd be more
concerned about Naruto
and Jiraiya's well-being.
Or maybe not.
It may very well
be that those two
are no longer in this world.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
They couldn't--
-There's no way Master
Jiraiya and Naruto
would be taken down that easily.
-Oh, is that so?
Or could it be that you
dragged down Naruto again,
like you always do.
Am I right?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Naruto.
KABUTO: If you're
so worried, why
don't you go and check on him?
Or are you too
afraid of my attack
to come out from
behind that pillar?
Is that it?
Pathetic.
If someone as weak and slow
as you were on my team,
I'd have died dozens
of times by now.
-I can do it.
I can do it!
KABUTO (VOICEOVER):
Substitution jutsu?
-Substitution again?
-I'll show you.
I'm not as weak as you think.
KABUTO: As I thought,
you can't take me.
It's about time I put
an end to this charade.
After all, I can't
keep Lord Orochimaru
waiting much longer
while I play.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Orochimaru?
-There.
When this is all over, one
of us will have both scrolls,
and the other will be dead.
[vomiting]
-No.
I'm a different person now.
I'm stronger.
-Let's see about that.
[laughter]
-It can't be.
-I can tell when you're
bluffing, my dear.
And right now, you're
already finished.
[laughter]
[theme music]
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): I'm scared.
What is this uneasy feeling?
My legs are weak and I don't
have any strength in my body.
I thought I was a different
person now, but I don't know.
Stop it.
Calm down.
If these guys are here, it
means Sasuke must be nearby.
I have to put up a strong fight.
I came here to save Sasuke.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next time--
Two Heartbeats, Kabuto's Trap.