[theme song]
[gasps]
-Naruto, Choji, get 'em, quick!
-Oh, yeah.
Right.
We're on it.
-Um.
-Multi-Shadow Clone jutsu!
[clones yelling]
-Partial Expansion jutsu!
Ah!
Uh, unh, got it, got
it, got it, got it!
-Huh? (THINKING) Where
did that bird go?
No use.
It's long-gone.
-There!
Got two more.
Unh.
Eh!
Ah.
I'll get you!
[screaming and panic]
OK, OK.
Sorry!
Careful.
That's really important.
You think I could play
with that for a sec?
It's OK.
Let go, let go, let go!
[crying]
-Lady Tsunade,
we've got trouble!
-What is it Shizune?
-Those papers
falling from the sky
were actually the stolen plans
we've been looking forward.
Shikamaru and his squad
have been collecting them
from all over the village
and gathering them together.
It appears they've
recovered all of them.
-So what do you think it means?
-Who knows?
-Lady Tsunade, we've just
had word from the forces
that we sent to the border.
-Well, what's the news?
-It seems the troop
movements we detected
were just part of a
training exercise after all.
The Village Hidden
in the Waterfalls
had no intention of invading us.
-They what?
-They finished their
training and the troops
withdrew without incident.
All's quiet on the border.
-So there was no connection
between that and Genno
after all.
Suspend the security alert,
and order everyone back!
All our forces are to
return to the village.
-Right.
-Just what is our
friend Genno up to?
[growling] Ah!
-[whimpers]
-Lady Tsunade!
-(IRATE) Yeah?
What is it now?
-Uh.
The body that the Anbu Black
Ops thought was Genno's--
CHOJI: What?
It's not Genno?
What do you mean, it's not him?
-But wait.
I thought old man
Genno blew himself up
when the Black Ops
had him surrounded.
-Maybe he was ready for that.
Maybe he had someone else's body
ready to switch for his own.
-Yeah.
That's what it's
starting to look like.
It's a similar body type
to Genno's, but there
are distinct differences.
They're still examining it.
-Umh.
-In short, it's
not who we thought.
-So the Anbu were
totally fooled, huh?
-But then, where is the man now?
-After all that, the
old man's still alive?
-Yeah.
And I'd give anything to
know what he was up to.
-Try over there.
Go look under that fallen tree.
-Unh, uh ah.
-So that's it.
Old man Genno had an escape
tunnel waiting for him here
all the time.
-He disguised it well.
We might never have found
it without Neji's byakugan.
-Yeah, and look at this.
He designed the tunnel
so it would slowly
collapse on itself from
the weight of the dirt.
In another day or so,
we would have never
been able to find,
even with the byakugan.
There wouldn't have
been a trace of it.
He went to a lot of trouble
to cover his tracks.
-OK, boy.
See if you can
pick up his trail.
[whimpers]
-Oh.
-Look at that.
The wily old man even
covered up his scent.
-Where could Genno
be now, I wonder?
-From what we know
so far, we have
to assume Genno is still
alive, and possibly
hiding right here
in the village.
-Uh.
-First, he stole the
plans, then staged
an elaborate phony suicide.
He might have been hoping
to draw our attention away
from the village.
All that activity on
the border was a help.
He must have known the Village
Hidden in the Waterfalls
was planning that.
-Uh.
-But remember, we
only suspected him
because of the fake
letter of recommendation.
And it was only by
sheer coincidence
that we discovered the letter.
-Was it a coincidence?
It was convenient that a
real letter of recommendation
was found in the very
house Genno was working at.
A little too convenient,
if you ask me.
-Oh. [gasp]
-All right, then.
What is he really after?
-If we knew that, we wouldn't
be sitting here sweating,
would we, M'lady?
-Shikamaru!
-But one thing we do know.
The number of Shinobi
left in the village
now is pathetically low.
Everybody but the
back-up squad has
been sent away on
a wild goose chase.
And everyone here is looking
for the threat from the outside.
Old man Genno could be
walking the streets right now,
whistling a tune,
and we wouldn't even
know a thing about it.
-So you think he's planning
something here in the village?
-Is that why he scattered
the plans around?
Because he's already
finished setting his trap?
-I think that was just
another diversion.
Another way of keeping us
running around in circles.
-If he did set a trap, we'll
have to find it ourselves.
All our defenses are
already thin enough.
But where do you look?
And where do you even start?
-With the Academy.
-The Academy?
Of all the buildings in
the village, what makes
you think the Academy
is his target?
-Because of all the building
sites Genno worked on,
the Academy is the only one
whose plans were stolen.
-Mm.
Another coincidence?
I don't think so.
-Byakugan!
-Well?
-Uh-uh.
I see nothing unusual is
this part of building.
-Oh.
Well, then, we'll
move onto the next.
-Byakugan!
No.
There's nothing in this room.
-Can't you and
Hinata do some kind
of quick scan of the
whole place at once?
It would save a lot
of time, you know?
-If we just knew what we
were looking for, then maybe.
But since we
haven't a clue, it's
safest to go slow,
one section at a time.
[laughing]
-Gang way.
Coming through.
-Out of the way.
-Coming through!
-Out of the way!
-Huh.
And with these kids around,
it makes it even harder.
-So now do you understand?
That's why you've
all got to clear out.
Everybody go outside
on the double!
-Well, that isn't what
our teacher told us.
He said we're supposed to study
in the classroom all day today.
-That's right.
We're not supposed to leave
the room, no matter what!
-Look, it's just
for a little while.
Your teachers will never know.
They're all away on an
important mission, OK?
Tell you a secret.
When I was your age and Iruka
Sensei wasn't watching me,
I used to sneak out
of class all the time!
-Huh?
You played hooky?
-Juvenile delinquent!
[students all protesting]
-Uh?
Whatever.
Will you just clear out?
-Anyway, if everyone's been
sent on a big important mission
to defend the
village, how come you
guys are still
hanging around here?
-Are you losers or something?
-(IRRITATED) Hey, hang on!
What we're doing is defending
the village, too, OK?
-Naruto, you're just
wasting your time.
I'll handle this.
-You will?
-(YELLING) Expansion jutsu!
-Uh-oh!
Watch out!
[kids yelling in panic]
-I'm going to the
teacher on you!
-(YELLING) Now get of here!
Go on!
-Hey, let's go and work
on our kunai training!
-Good idea!
-I didn't find anything.
It looks all clear up here.
[kids yelling happily]
-Hurry up!
-Let's go!
[laughing]
-Woohoo!
-Huh?
-Hey!
Hey!
Come on.
You guys have all got to
clear out of here right now!
-Naruto.
-Yeah?
-Those kids, the ones running
off toward the practice hall
just now, what do you
think they're up to?
-Don't know.
-I heard him say something
about some kunai training.
-That's right!
Yeah, yeah.
I think I heard
something like that.
-A strange place indeed
for kunai training.
STUDENT: Hurry up!
STUDENT: Do it already.
STUDENT: Just throw it already.
STUDENT: Hello?
STUDENT: Just stop,
let me concentrate!
STUDENT: It's my turn.
STUDENT: Yeah, there you go.
STUDENT: Oh, that
was a nice shot.
-Uh, uh!
-Nice try.
-Wow!
Seriously.
-Look at them.
They're really training.
Remember when we
were at the Academy?
We used to skip class and
hang out here all the time.
It was the last place
the teachers ever thought
of looking for us.
[chuckles] It was great!
I used to read manga
here, or take a nap.
-A nice quiet place
to eat a snack.
-I would not boast about that.
You could learn
something from them.
Look at them, training
hard, even when
the teacher is not watching.
-Unh!
-The picture of
the ideal student.
Uh!
(PASSIONATELY) Such
drive and dedication.
It is inspiring to watch.
I only wish I could
go through training
all over again with them!
-Yeah.
-We must not interrupt them.
Let us be off!
-OK.
-Hey, Naruto.
-Yeah?
What is it?
-That thing didn't used
to be there, did it?
-Huh?
Uh.
-OK.
Watch this.
I'm going to nail it!
-Ah!
-Huh?
-Um-eh!
-Unh, yah!
[all wincing]
-Ow!
-Oh.
-Hey, that one was
right on the target!
-It looks new, like it
was placed here recently.
-You think Genno
might have done it?
-Wait!
I know.
I'll find Neji or Hinata
and they can check it out.
STUDENT: Hey!
Do you mind?
Get out of the way.
-Uh?
-We're trying to practice here!
-Sorry.
Go right ahead, boys.
-OK, I'm next!
NEJI: Byakugan!
That's it!
I found it.
There's a paper
bomb behind here.
-There's a what?
What do you mean?
Where?
-A paper bomb hidden
inside this wall.
-Inside?
But how could-- well, how could
anybody detonate it in there?
-Uh.
There she is.
Thank goodness.
Hey!
Hinata!
SAKURA: Uh?
What is it?
-What's going on?
-Uh.
Hinata, you're the one I want.
-[gasps]
-What the heck's wrong with you?
You idiot!
Saying stuff like
that right now!
-Uh.
-I never knew.
I don't know what to say,
-I need you, Hinata.
-Ah, Naruto, I never knew
you could be so impetuous.
-[growls] Oh.
Never mind.
I'll ask Neji.
See ya!
-Huh?
Oh.
-The paper bomb has a long
thread attached to it.
-A thread?
-Not just any thread.
More than likely, it's
a fuse, allowing someone
to set off the
bomb from far away.
-Well, thread, or
fuse, or whatever
it is, where does it lead to?
NEJI: It goes around the
classroom, then goes outside,
and it ends in
the practice hall.
There's something there.
A log, or a pole.
The booby trap.
That's it!
-Uh.
Neji!
Hurry.
You've got to with me!
-We're in the middle of
something kind of important
here, Naruto!
-There's this weird kind
of log thing standing up
in the practice hall.
We need to come
and check it out!
-It's an explosive device.
-Huh?
STUDENT: Heh!
-Try loosening up your
shoulder before you throw.
-Who asked you?
-Stand aside.
I'll show you how to do it.
NEJI: Does the log
have a target on it?
-Yeah, exactly.
-The center of that
target is the detonator.
-Hyah!
NEJI: If a kunai knife
hits that bullseye,
it will trigger the
detonator and the Academy
will be blown sky-high.
-Oh, so close.
Do not forget to focus.
Focus on the target, boys.
-All right.
I'm going to nail It this time.
Focus, focus.
Here we go!
-Let's hope their aim's
not getting any better!
-I've got it.
Bullseye!
-Bravo!
Well-done!
[metal clinking]
-What the--?
-There must be a
flaw in the blade.
Yes, indeed.
Let that be a lesson to you.
You must take good
care of your weapons.
-Hey!
No fair!
That was a bullseye!
-This way.
It's shorter!
Hurry!
-OK.
I got it now.
This one's going to
be right on the money.
-That is the spirit!
-Ha!
-That one looks good!
There it is.
Bullseye!
-Bushy Brow!
Uh!
-Grab it, Lee!
[loud explosion]
-[gasp]
-What was that?
-Oh.
Did I scare you guys?
My bad.
I dropped one of my ninja tools.
Sorry!
[giggles]
-Unh!
Ah.
-Way to go, Bushy Brow.
Nice stop!
-Hey!
That was a bullseye!
-Why do you guys keep
butting in, anyway?
-(ANGRILY) Quiet you brats!
If you had hit the
bullseye, the whole Academy
would've blown up!
[gasps]
-Oh.
-No.
-Man!
-A triggering device
hidden inside it, huh?
-Cleverly set to be activated
by a direct hit on the target.
-We were just lucky that
none of those little snots
was good enough to hit
it before we got here!
-It's a good thing they
hadn't had any more training.
-We got lucky, that's for sure.
-Hey, you guys!
Who was it that told you to do
your kunai training in here?
You remember?
-Who was it again?
Hey, do you remember?
-No.
But somebody told us we should
do our training in secret
and impress our teacher.
-Training in secret, huh?
-Whoever it was must have
used some kind of genjutsu
to put that thought
in the kids' minds.
-It was Genno, no doubt.
-Unh.
-Hinata, what is it?
-I don't know what
it means, but I
was looking at the
explosive device
and there's more than
one fuse leading to it.
-What?
Are you sure Hinata?
-Uh, yes.
-Huh?
-Byakugan!
She's right.
There's more than one.
There's two, No, three.
-But where do they all lead?
-Somewhere outside the Academy.
Uh.
I can't see clearly
from in here.
-Uh, wait.
I-I'll come, too!
-Byakugan!
HINATA: Neji!
Do you see?
NEJI: Yes.
I see it!
Well, where does it lead?
Wait.
It branches of again over here.
HINATA: Over here, too!
-There's no end to it!
-It can't be!
There's no way!
-(YELLING) Hey!
Did you find anything?
-(YELLING) There are paper
bombs all over the village,
and they're all connected!
-Not just 10 or 20 paper bombs
either, but dozens of them,
hundreds of them.
Too many to count.
[all gasp]
The entire Leaf Village is
a giant nest of paper bombs!
[theme music]
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): So I guess
this means the Academy is safe.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): All right!
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
We're not out the woods yet.
If he finds out we've
discovered his paper bombs,
he may just blow 'em up
before we can get rid of 'em.
-We've got to
evacuate the village!
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): No.
Then he'll know we're onto him.
-So what do we do?
SHINO (VOICEOVER): Act
like everything is normal,
as we quietly defuse the bombs.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): Exactly.
Let's get to work.
-(BOTH) Right!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next
time, "The Powerful Helper".