[theme music]
-Sakura!
It was worth teaching you
genjutsu during survival
training for the genin exam.
You truly do have
a talent for it.
Release the genjutsu, and
wake Naruto and Shikamaru.
Naruto will be delighted.
He'll be getting a mission
after such a long time.
-What kind of mission?
-You'll have to be
careful on this one.
It's the first A-rank assignment
since the Land of the Waves.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): "Village
in Distress-- A new A-ranked
Mission."
-But Sensei, what are you doing?
With this battle going on, why
send us off on some mission?
-Sasuke's chasing Gaara
and the other Sand ninja.
-What?
-Sakura, release the genjutsu.
Wake Naruto and Shikamaru,
and follow Sasuke.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): I feel
uneasy about that weird chakra.
- But then shouldn't we wake
Ino and Choji and go in a group?
-No time.
I suspect that
many Sound and Sand
shinobi may have already
infiltrated this village.
Besides, if you have
more than the four ninja
essential to a squad, it takes
longer to get anything done
and becomes more difficult
to hide from the enemy.
You did learn that in Academy
patrol training, didn't you?
-Of course.
With four squad
members, that means
you'll be coming with us, right?
-No.
I must not leave this place.
Summoning jutsu!
-Huh?
Pakkun here will track
down Sasuke by scent.
-Wait.
Seriously, our fourth
member is a puppy?
-All right.
Listen, little girl.
Don't you dare go around saying
I'm just some cute puppy.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): But
I didn't even say "cute."
-OK, it's time.
Sakura, go release the genjutsu.
[music playing]
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Release.
-Huh?
Hey, what's going on, Sakura?
-Get down!
I'll fill you in later.
Just stay down.
Shikamaru, you were--
this whole time?
-Ahhh!
-You really scammed
[inaudible] you faker!
Why were you pretending to
be asleep this whole time?
-I didn't want to get involved.
Just give me a break.
I couldn't care
less about Sasuke.
-[growling]
-Ah!
-What-- what is all this?
Whoa!
-Behind you!
-[gasp]
-So fast!
-Not just fast.
Powerful.
-Guy Sensei.
Huh?
-Now, I'll explain the mission.
As soon as I do, go
through that opening.
First, track down
Sasuke and stop him.
Then find a safe location
and await further orders.
-Did something happen to Sasuke?
-I'll tell you what
happened on the way.
Now let's go!
-Why me?
What a drag.
-Listen, whiner.
-Huh?
-Look, if this mission
is a success, as a reward
I'll let you touch
my palm, or my pads.
So there's no reason to sulk.
-What?
-Come on.
They're really soft.
-They're-- what?
-No one ever wants to shake.
But my paws are so
soft and supple!
Forget it.
Let's go.
-Ah!
-Are they going to
be OK by themselves?
-Yes, they'll be fine.
Pakkun will protect them.
As long as they
don't go too far.
-I never thought I'd get to
face you in battle again.
-This barrier can only be
broken from the inside.
If Lord Hokage would just take
out one of those Sound ninja,
then we could help.
-OK, let's get this
show on the road.
-Put up a barrier
on the inside, too.
-Right.
-Hah!
-Doesn't look like I'll be
able to get out of this easily.
-Of course it won't be easy.
I know you.
It would be a big bother
if someone came in here
and got in your
way, wouldn't it?
-[laughs]
Ninja Art, Tile Shuriken!
-This is too easy.
Striking Shadow Snake!
With a weak technique like that,
there's no way you can beat me,
Sarutobi Sensei.
Ah!
A substitution.
-Earth Style, Great Mud River!
-Is that all you've got?
-Far from it.
Earth Style, Earth Dragon Bomb!
Fire Dragon Bomb!
-Ahh!
-He combined Fire
and Earth styles.
-Excellent, Lord Hokage.
-Ahhh!
-You can stop your
little act, Orochimaru.
-[laughs] All right, then.
But fair's fair.
It's foolish to
underestimate me.
Did you seriously think
that you could kill me
with such a pitiful jutsu?
-Huh!
Falling back on taunts
since you can't defeat me?
-Oh, don't be angry with me.
Difficult students
are all the more
rewarding to teach,
right, Sarutobi Sensei?
[chatter]
-So lame.
-I can't believe we're
sitting here right now.
-Would you stop
kicking me, dude?
-Come on!
KONOHAMARU (VOICEOVER):
Something weird is going on.
All the teachers
left the students
to study by themselves, and
then there's that smoke.
-It's coming from the
direction of the arena.
-Huh?
Do you guys see something
over there, too?
-I wonder what's going on today.
KONOHAMARU (VOICEOVER): Yeah,
this is definitely weird.
[chatter]
-Busy work.
-I mean seriously,
who wants to do this?
-Come on!
-Right in the middle
of a lesson, and bam,
we're just stuck in
her by ourselves.
And we've been in her so long!
-Yeah.
Iruka Sensei and
the others are late.
Aren't they, Konohamaru?
[chatter]
Hey, Konohamaru?
[wood cracking]
-Oh, come on!
My mom just bought this for me.
-Relax.
I'll loan you my colored pencil.
-I don't want that.
This one is a brand new,
limited edition color.
Aw!
Just great.
[music playing]
KONOHAMARU (VOICEOVER):
That rainbow.
-Naruto and the others must
have gone to stop Sasuke.
-Those brats?
Huh!
No matter how many little
genin go after him,
it won't do any good.
Is this the data on
the kid from before?
Come on!
You give him too much credit.
-Guess again.
Underestimate the
enemy and you will die.
-Oh!
Hm!
-We've gotten information
that several enemy units have
already infiltrated the village.
-Then we have no choice.
We should evacuate the students
to a safe place immediately.
-Yes, but we have
to do so in a way
that doesn't cause
them all to panic.
-Right.
OK, here's what we're
all going to do.
Tell them we're having
an evacuation drill.
[music playing]
-Isn't it about time we
stopped playing around here?
After all, this isn't
an Academy class.
-Huh.
Yes, you do have a point.
-Did you foresee
this, dying this way?
[music playing]
--[laughs] Don't think
I'll go easy on you just
because you're
old and doddering.
-I wouldn't want you to.
Now depending on how
good your jutsu is,
I might send you
back to the Academy.
-At least try to make
this an interesting fight.
-Whoa, so much chakra.
-Yes, so much that
the air itself
has become heavy with it.
I can feel it
bearing down on me.
-Shuriken Shadow Clone Jutsu!
-Summoning Jutsu, Reanimation!
SARUTOBI (VOICEOVER):
That technique!
-First!
-A Summoning jutsu
used as a shield!
And what he summoned is--
-Second!
-I must stop the
third at any cost.
-Third!
-Hah!
OROCHIMARU (VOICEOVER): So
the third one failed, did it?
Oh, well.
No matter.
SARUTOBI (VOICEOVER): It looks
as if I stopped the third one.
Now this is where
it gets difficult.
I can't believe he
summoned those two.
-It can't be!
Those people are--
-What?
They're what?
-Hah!
What are you going to
do now, Sarutobi Sensei?
What can you do?
Hah!
(SARCASTICALLY)
Lord Third Hokage.
IRUKA: OK, everyone,
please move quickly.
-This day just keeps
getting better.
First we're left here alone,
then my favorite colored pencil
breaks, and now this!
-These drills are so annoying.
Even studying all by ourselves
was better than this.
-Konohamaru has been
real quiet, hasn't he?
I wonder what's wrong.
-I know.
Huh.
KONOHAMARU (VOICEOVER): The
whole school has study hall,
and now we're put through
an evacuation drill?
This is just too weird.
-OK, stop and get into line.
KONOHAMARU (VOICEOVER): That
loon on Iruka Sensei's face.
Something's definitely
going on here.
And then, there's that.
-Now listen, everyone.
Don't go running off
on your own, got it?
KONOHAMARU (VOICEOVER):
That rainbow's
been bugging me for
a long time now.
Hm?
Hey, what's that?
Oh, man, what's
that weird rainbow?
-Hmm?
[laughs]
-That's a real unusual one, huh?
-So you like rainbows,
then, to you?
-Um-hum.
You bet.
But I've never seen a rainbow
as pretty as that one before.
-I see, I see.
Did you know, Konohamaru?
-Hm?
-Rainbows are
beautiful, it's true,
but they were once used
to symbolize snakes,
and it's said that they
foretell the arrival of evil.
-A pretty thing like that?
Come on, that's
not true, old man!
-All right, all right.
[laughs]
KONOHAMARU (VOICEOVER): A
rainbow symbolizes snakes.
What in the world
is going on here?
[music playing]
-It's been a very
long time, Saru.
-Oh, it's you.
You've gotten so old, Sarutobi.
-Never in my entire
life did I imagine
I would have to face off against
my brethren in this manner.
What a vile trick.
-This is horrible!
That's Summoning jutsu.
Who in the world are those two?
-Please prepare yourselves.
First Lord Hokage,
Second Lord Hokage.
-Huh?
What?
-That's right.
The one with the black
hair is the First Hokage,
and the one with the
white hair is the Second.
They're considered
the greatest shinobi
our village has ever seen.
I mean, they built the
Hidden Leaf Village.
-A Summoning jutsu.
It seems that he used
the forbidden Reanimation
technique.
How insolent.
-Then Sarutobi, tell me,
does this Summoning jutsu
mean we're being forced
to battle against you?
-Enough with the reminiscing.
It's time that we got started.
-Whenever you live,
there's always war.
-Isn't it great?
-Nothing good can
ever come of this.
You've disrespected the
dead and manipulated time.
NARUTO: Oh, I get it.
So that's what happened.
I guess Sasuke
got all impatient.
-Oh, man!
Why did you have to pull
me into all of this?
I mean, it's such a drag.
-It can't be helped, OK?
It's Kakashi Sensei's order.
-[sniffing] This way!
-Right!
[music playing]
-That brat's mine.
Let's go!
[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Ah!
Those ninja after
us are too fast!
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
They're going to catch us,
and that'll be the end of us.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Then let's
ambush them and get them first.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): Even if
we do, we probably won't win.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Quit being negative!
We got to do something.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): There's
only one thing we can do.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next
time, "A Shirker's Call
To Action-- Layabout No More."
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
All right.
It's not my style, but I
guess we have no choice.