[theme music]
TSUNADE: There has been a
coup in the Land of Greens?
-Yes, it's been confirmed.
The lord of the land
has been overthrown
with the help of some
of his very own people.
-And Naruto's squad?
-Their progress from
their last known position
would bring them to
right about here.
TSUNADE: So they must have
already crossed the border.
-Well, the area's been
declared a demilitarized zone
by the neighboring lands.
And considering the nonmilitary
nature of Naruto's mission,
I'm sure he and the
others are safe.
-Hm, I'm not.
-But why?
What do you mean?
-These separate events
happening at the same time,
you really think
it's a coincidence?
-Are you saying the
mission to escort
the merchants is tied up
with the coup somehow?
-It seems more than likely.
In any case, we can't worry
about Naruto and the others
now.
The Land of Greens
must be recaptured
and the usurpers expelled
as soon as possible.
The longer things are left
like this, the more likely
a full-scaled war
will break out.
-That's true.
-Shizune, summon
every available ninja
and get them ready to move
on the Land of Greens.
-Yes, ma'am.
-OK.
Now, you've made me mad!
-Stubborn little brat!
-Ugh!
-Hah!
You won't get up again.
-Naruto!
-I hate to disappoint you.
-Hey, impressive!
At least, you have some spirit.
But try getting up from this.
Ninja Art Magnet!
Electromagnetic Illusion!
[static noise]
-Naruto!
-Save your breath.
He can't hear you.
My magnetic sand interferes
with the electric impulses
in his brain.
Huh, hear you?
Right now, he can't
even think straight.
Rrrh!
-Ugh!
-And now, this
magnetized cable is
going to take you
down, literally!
Rrgh!
-No!
-[grunts]
-Are you all right?
-Aah!
[gasping]
-Thank goodness.
-Get out of here.
Go on.
-Mm-hm.
I'm not going to leave you.
-Hinata, he's too strong--
more than you can handle.
Huh?
-No way.
I won't let him have you.
-Hinata!
[groans]
-Hah, don't even try.
Just tell me where the girl is.
-Byakugan!
-Now, Electromagnetic Illusion!
-Protective 8
Trigrams, 64 Palms!
-What the-- I thought so.
That's the Byakugan
of the Leaf Village.
Hah, interesting.
The famous Byakugan, huh?
Let's find out how it works.
Can you see your
way out of this?
-Yes!
Hai!
It worked.
-Not even close.
I'm afraid it will
take a lot more
than that level of Taijutsu!
-Huh.
-[chuckles]
-Aah!
-Heh, hopeless.
[groans]
[gasping]
-Disappointing.
I expected more of a challenge.
Now, why don't we end this?
Just tell me where
you've hidden the girl.
Tell me and I may let you live.
The boy, too.
But you better hurry,
he hasn't got long.
-Uh.
-Run, Hinata, while you can.
-Tell me, where is she?
-No.
-Do you actually believe
you can defeat me?
Or is it just that you don't
care about saving the boy?
HINATA (VOICEOVER): If I tell
him what he wants to know,
Naruto will never forgive me.
-Huh!
And if that's that way you want
it, we'll do it the hard way!
I've just magnetized that
rock wall behind you.
I can turn any of these
rocks into a powerful magnet,
so you've nowhere to run.
Hm?
JIGA (VOICEOVER): Very clever.
She diverted them all
by throwing a paper bomb
at the last minute.
Not quite all.
You won't get away.
-[gasping]
-Hinata.
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
Don't worry, Naruto.
I'll come back for you.
I promise.
He's too powerful.
I can never defeat him.
Can I even survive against him?
He's caught up with me already?
What do I do?
Uh, what's this?
Some kind of iron sand?
Oh!
That's what he was doing--
knocking off the iron sand
that his magnetized
body had attracted.
That's why he didn't
attack me right away.
He had to shake off the
magnetic sand from his body.
If he doesn't, he'll
attract the very weapons
he uses against us.
That explains his pattern of
attack-- alternating Ninja Art
Magnet with the
Iron Sand Gejutsu.
It's as if he has to
give himself enough time
to turn his magnetized
body on and off.
Perhaps there is a way
to defeat him after all.
-Enough of this!
Play time's over!
Give up.
Can't you see it's pointless?
-Not while there's still
breath left in my body!
Giving up is not
part of my ninja way!
-It's your funeral!
-Naruto is my friend.
I will never forgive you
for what you did to him!
-You'll join your friend
in the spirit world
after you've told me
where the girl is!
Eeyah!
Now, don't be shy.
Come a little closer!
HINATA (VOICEOVER): Now, Hinata,
you only have one chance.
Make it count!
-Hai!
-Uh!
-Heh, did you think
that same attack
would work at me
better this time?
-Yes, I did.
-Huh?
Hrngh.
-No!
-[gasping]
The only one who's going to
the spirit world are you and I!
-Ugh!
Ugh!
Aargh!
What do you think you're doing?
Get off!
-Argh!
Ugh!
-Little fool, you annoy me.
I've changed my mind.
I'm going to finish you off now.
Huh?
What?
What the devil's going on?
-Just now, I hit one
of your chakra points,
disrupting the flow of
chakra through your body.
And now, your body
is a powerful magnet
that you can't switch off.
-That's why you led me to
this canyon full of iron sand.
Urgh!
Make it stop.
Urrgh, urgh.
-I did it.
Naruto, I-- um, mm.
-I can't move at all.
SPEAKER: Human Boulder!
Yaah!
Naruto.
-[gasping]
Choji.
Uhh.
-You sure you're
all right, Naruto?
-Yeah, I'm sorry, Yurinojo.
-For what?
What happened?
I was attacked by that second
ninja, and I let him beat me.
-What about Hinata
and the princess?
-Hinata!
I got to get going!
-Oh, Naruto, you're in
no shape to go anywhere.
-She's in danger!
-Hold on.
Wait!
-Naruto!
-Hinata!
Aaah!
-Hinata, are you OK?
-Hinata?
Hinata?
-Naruto, you're here.
And Choji?
Yurinojo?
You did this.
You did this all just for me?
-Sure, what did you expect?
What do you think
friends are for?
-Uh, yeah.
-Say, where did Mr.
Magnet Man get off to?
-He won't bother us anymore.
He's buried under the sand.
-He's what?
You mean, you did it?
You really beat him?
-Yeah.
Well, I mean, I
did what I could.
-Man, Hinata, you're amazing!
You saw how well I handled him.
-Uh, you don't know what that
means coming from you, Naruto.
Uh, look, Naruto, it's yours.
-My headband?
But where did you-- ah.
-Our mission is far
from being over.
There is still Princess Haruna.
You must find her
and protect her.
-Don't worry.
I'm going to take care of it.
And I swear to you
by this headband,
I'll make sure nothing
happens to her.
Besides, I can't let you go
around making me look bad.
[chuckles]
-Of course not.
-You guys, stay.
Look after Hinata.
Can you do that?
-Right.
-We'll take care of her, Naruto.
-Well, who would have thought?
Ruiga and Jiga have
both been defeated.
Ha, it saves me the trouble.
But still, there's not a person
alive who can defeat my jutsu.
I sense today is going
to be a sunny day.
-Haruna, are you here?
Huh?
Is that-- it's her!
Haruna!
-[groans]
-Are you OK?
-Hm.
-[sighs]
You had me worried for a second.
-Uhh.
-Aaah!
What are you doing?
It's me!
-What?
Naruto?
-I came to help you.
What was that all about?
-I'm sorry.
-What do you mean running
off all by yourself anyway?
-I'm all alone now.
I can't depend on anyone.
The rest of you are only
here to assure my survival,
nothing else.
As long as I survive, there's
a chance the Land of Greens
can be restored.
That's all that really
matters in the end, isn't it?
I am the rightful heir.
I must reclaim the power
that is rightly mine.
Once I'm lord of
the Land of Greens,
the people will flock to serve
me, their faith restored.
The land will be again
what it once was.
-You think?
I'm not so sure about that.
-Are you saying
the Land of Greens
can never be great again?
-No!
No, that's not what I meant.
But I was thinking if
I lived in your land,
was one of your people, if I was
a ninja, like Yurinojo-- what
I'm trying to say
is I don't think
I'd be able to serve
a lord like you.
-How dare you?
How dare you say that?
What can you possibly
know about it?
You know nothing of
what I've gone through,
living my life as a hostage
ever since I was a child.
Surrounded by strangers,
watched 24 hours a day,
never getting to do what I want!
You have no idea
of the loneliness.
I couldn't take it.
Eventually, I became
very, very ill.
I almost died before my parents
finally let me come home.
Say it.
If you think something's wrong
with that, say it, Naruto.
Could it be wrong
when it was all
for the sake of
the Land of Greens?
Is it wrong for a
mother and father
to send their child away to live
among strangers as a hostage?
Is it, Naruto?
Answer me!
I depend on no one.
I will do this on my own.
-Hold on.
I'm coming with you.
Like it or not, I made
a promise to Hinata.
And I'm going to protect you.
-To Hinata?
-She got pretty badly
injured fighting
that second ninja
who was after you.
-She what?
But I was sure that
you and the rest
have decided that protecting
me wasn't part of your mission.
If that's true, why
are you doing this?
-It's just the way we are.
We don't like it when see
somebody getting a raw deal,
even if that somebody
is maybe not, well,
the nicest person in the world.
But that's not important.
There's a narrow
canyon up ahead.
And we've got to get through it.
The village is on
the other side.
And hopefully, they
won't follow us there.
Come on, let's go!
-Uhh.
-Be careful where you step.
This deer trail hasn't
been used for ages.
They'll never think of
looking for us here.
[crackling]
-Huh?
Huh?
-Sorry to disappoint you.
All that trouble for nothing.
There's nowhere on earth
you can hide from me.
-Urgh.
Ugh.
-Huh?
Choji!
-Needless to say,
resistance is futile.
You may all consider
yourselves my hostages.
Take the three of them
back to the castle at once.
-My lord.
-I wouldn't want any of
you getting hurt now.
I'm about to use
some powerful jutsu.
Hm.
-[panting]
There it is, Haruna.
We're almost there.
Well, what are we
waiting for, then?
Let's go!
-Hm.
Ugh!
-Huh?
What is it?
-I'm OK.
[whistling]
-Uh-oh!
Ngh!
What was that?
MAN: Bravo!
-Huh?
MAN: I must commend you for
anticipating that attack.
-Who's that?
Where are you?
-[laughs]
I'm right up here.
You were so close, but you'll
never reach that village now.
I'm afraid your
journey ends here.
[music playing]
-Oh, man, this guy's really
getting on my nerves!
Going on and on about
his all-powerful jutsu,
bragging about how
invincible he is!
Of course, he does have a point.
I haven't found any way to
get past his offenses yet.
And Haruna's injured,
so she's not much help.
In fact, we're cornered.
Come to think of it, maybe he's
got a reason to brag after all!
Next time, "Forecast Death!
Cloudy with a Chance of Sun."
[music playing]