[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
A Battle of Bugs!
The Deceivers, and the Deceived!
-I don't get it.
What the heck is
going on around here?
Who would want to kidnap
Hinata, and why does anyone even
know we're looking for the
bikochu in the first place?
-I don't really know,
but from the moment
we got here they've been
watching us like hawks.
-Huh?
So wait, you knew
they were there?
-You were the only
one who didn't.
-And you don't think maybe
you should have filled me in?
-Oh, please.
If we'd have told
you, you would have
raised a big stink over it.
Every insect in a square mile
would have buzzed out of here,
including the bikochu.
[bark]
SHINO: If they had tried to
take the bikochu by force,
they'd risk harming the insect.
So they decided to capture
Hinata and offer an exchange.
It was a smart move.
-Huh?
Does anybody else
smell something sweet?
-Yeah, like honey.
-Honeybees.
-Bees?
-Well, that's it, you guys.
Hinata's scent ends here.
-In that case--
-So they waited for a moment
when Hinata would be alone,
then attacked her
with a swarm of bees.
-I've heard in
the Land of Earth,
in the Hidden Stone
Village, there's
a clan of handlers who
specialize in bees.
Word is they're called
the Kamizuru clan.
-Kamizuru?
I've never heard of them.
-Apparently they were thought
to be as skilled as the Aburame
clan in the past.
-But they aren't anymore?
-It was back in my
grandfather's day.
The Shinobi of the
Hidden Stone Village
attempted to invade
the Hidden Leaf.
The Kamizuru clan were
chosen to map out a strategy.
Their plan was to attack with
an immense swarm of bees,
letting the main forces
strike in the chaos.
But the Aburame caught wind of
it, and met them in the forest
to the west.
It was an unprecedented battle
between instect handlers.
And the Aburame prevailed.
With that victory in hand,
the Aburame clan quickly
rose to prominence
in the Leaf Village,
while the Kamizuru
fell to ruin back
in the Village
Hidden in the Stones.
They say that there are
only a few of them left.
-And they're the
ones who came here
looking for the bikochu, huh?
So what do you think
they plan to do with it?
You got any idea?
-Hopefully when
my insects return,
they can shed a little
light on the matter.
HINATA (VOICEOVER): Of course.
I've been captured.
MAN: The Leaf Village is up
against the wall right now.
-With the fiasco at
the Chunin exam--
-Their Hokage assassinated,
and scores of shinobi lost.
Times are about to
change dramatically.
This is what our clan
has been waiting for.
A chance for us to
show our mettle.
But in order to do that--
-Our Tsuchikage's book.
-Yes.
-A wide array read of forbidden
jutsu useful to insect handlers
are said to be within it.
If our clan had had it
when we fought the Aburame,
we wouldn't have
lost that cursed day.
-Maybe, and yet
all of our people
have been searching for it a
great many years to no avail.
You really think we can
find it after all this time?
-That's why we need the bikochu.
This belonged to my grandfather.
He was the original Tsuchikage.
When the bikochu
emerges, it'll seek out
the first scent
it's introduced to.
We should be able to locate the
book of secrets grandfather hid
as he was dying.
This lock of his hair
will lead us right to it.
If we can get our
hands on that book
and aren't afraid to use
it, there's no question.
The village will acknowledge us.
HINATA (VOICEOVER): They're
no different from me.
They just long for recognition.
Naruto.
[buzzing]
-Huh?
What's the story, Shino?
Where have they got Hinata?
-I don't know.
And they probably took out the
rest of the insects I sent too.
-Great.
Guess that's it, then.
We don't have a choice
but to do what they say.
-And after all the trouble
we went to get 'em.
-So, you think we
should desert Hinata?
-Are you crazy?
There's no way
we're gonna do that!
I don't care what happens.
I'm not gonna abandon her!
Anyone who leaves
a comrade is trash!
-Hear, hear.
[bark]
-The problem is,
we're still gonna
need our little friend here
if we wanna find Sasuke.
-Well.
We'll just have to come up with
another way of tracking him
down.
-Yeah, you're right.
But for now, the priority
is rescuing Hinata.
-Although-- I wonder if
that's what Hinata would want.
-Huh?
-This entire plan,
it was her idea.
-What?
But--
-It's true.
I told her about the
existence of the bikochu.
However, the odds of finding
one are extremely low.
Kiba and I thought we should
set our sights on missions
that were sure to
help the village.
We didn't want to go
chasing some long shot.
But Hinata wouldn't give up.
She was adamant.
No matter how remote
our chances of success,
she said we should
move forward with it.
-She-- she really said all that?
-Yeah, I know.
We couldn't believe how
much fight she had in her.
She was so passionate
about it, all Shino
and I could do was agree.
-It's the first time Hinata has
ever volunteered for a mission.
For that reason as well,
I want us to succeed here.
-Yeah.
-But back to our
original question.
How do we rescue her if we
don't even know where she is?
-There is one place where we
know she'll make an appearance.
-Of course!
When we make the trade off.
-That's right!
They'll have to bring
her for the bug!
-Correct.
It's our only chance.
-All right, you guys!
So that's the plan!
We save Hinata and protect
the bikoch, no matter what!
There, you see?
We brought the bikochu.
Now hand over Hinata!
-Set the insect cage down
on that rock right there.
-Hinata!
There's your stupid bug.
Now let her go!
-Not until we've had a look.
-What is this?
You little brats.
You think you can mock
our clan like this?
A goliath beetle?
Are you kidding?
-Shino, now!
-What?
-Parasitic Insects!
-Recovery successful.
-Now, that's what
I'm talking about!
-Naruto!
-OK, I hope you're ready!
-You guys are done here.
Wait a second.
[bark]
-You guys!
She doesn't smell like Hinata.
-Huh?
-Just as I thought.
-What the-- It's only beeswax.
[buzzing]
-Incoming!
-Aw, great!
They're all over the place!
Hey, watch it!
-Sorry, Naruto.
It's these stupid bees!
-I know!
There's too many!
Why are we fighting
these things?
They're just wax!
-You guys!
Don't move!
-This one isn't fake.
And it's carrying
a deadly poison.
It appears there are
real ones in the mix.
-Yeah, but they all
look exactly the same.
-Watch my back for a second.
Wall of Insects Jutsu!
-Wow, that's cool.
WOMAN: Impressive
strength for a Genin.
-Huh?
[laughter]
-But I should expect no
less from the Aburame clan.
Isn't that right?
-The Kamizuru clan.
-So, cat's out of the bag.
-You give Hinata back!
-We had every intention
of returning her--
if you were good little boys
and handed over the bikochu.
Only thing is, it doesn't
look like that was your plan.
-So, what do we do?
-You're an insect handler.
You'd never carry a delicate
creature like the bikochu
into the danger of battle.
So we'll finish you
off right here and now,
and then take our
time afterwards
to search for the bug.
-Wall of Insects Jutsu!
-Heh.
Is that the only
trick she's got?
-Huh?
-Shino!
Paper bombs!
-Huh?
[screaming]
-You asked for it, lady
-1,000 Bee Stingers Jutsu!
-Beetle clones?
-Hmph.
Nothing but two-bit tricks.
-Well?
What's the game plan
gonna be now, Shino?
-Don't you think we should
turn around and head back?
We don't want those
guys to find the spot
where we hid the bikochu.
-Don't worry.
The location will be
safe for the time being.
Right now, all that
matters is finding Hinata.
[whine]
-No question about it.
-In there, huh?
[bark]
NARUTO: Hinata!
Where are you?
-Stay on your toes, everybody.
There's no sign of those guys,
but it could still be a trap.
[barking]
-Is she there?
Hinata-- She's alive!
-Hinata!
Hey, are you OK?
-Don't worry.
We'll have you out
of this in no time.
KIBA: Almost there.
-All right.
That's the last of it.
-Naruto?
Oh, thank you.
-Hinata?
-Huh?
-I-- I-- ah-- What the
heck ya doin', you nut job?
-Out with it.
Who are you?
-Um, Shino?
What are you talking about?
That's Hinata, remember?
-No, it's not.
If it were, she'd have
gone red in the face
and passed out
after hugging you.
-Huh?
Yeah, but-- Akamaru's nose
never would have missed that.
[whine]
-What?
The cent of two
people mixed together?
-If you're not Hinata,
then who are you?
-Naruto, please.
I swear, it's really me.
-If that's true,
show us what you've
tried to stick on
Naruto's back just now.
NARUTO: A paper bomb?
-You were gonna
blow his head off!
[giggle]
-I don't believe it.
I was sure that would work.
-You.
I see.
The one on the hill
was only a clone.
KIBA: She had Hinata's
coat around her.
So that's how she hid her scent.
-Out with it.
What have you done
with our friend?
-So sorry.
Hard to say, really.
-Good.
Looks like the
rest of their clan
followed Suzumebachi
right into our trap.
Your comrades won't
be coming, dear.
Guess they feel the bikochu
is more of value than you are,
so you can forget
about being rescued.
MAN: All right, come on.
We'd better start searching
for the bikochu they've hidden.
There's not much
time until sunrise.
-Right.
I wouldn't bother
trying to escape.
You make even the slightest
move out of the ordinary,
and the bees will
sever the rope.
Right up ahead is
the entrance to
a labyrinthine
underground sewer.
Plunge in there and you'll
be dead in an instant.
We have no desire
to kill anyone.
If you want to live, I
suggest you stay still.
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
I feel so awful.
In the end, I was nothing but
a burden, the same as always.
-You guys are like
a trio of moths,
flying blindly into the fire.
If you're lucky, though,
maybe we'll meet again.
Careful, boys.
This is no ordinary cave.
-Hey!
Come on, you guys, let go!
SHINO: There's nothing
else to grab onto.
Just be patient.
We need to get our bearings.
-There are bee larvae
everywhere you look!
-Bee larvae, huh?
Something's wrong.
They're far too big.
-All you have to
do is tell me where
you've hidden the bikochu.
I get what I want
and you get to live.
NARUTO: Forget it!
Our mission was to
bring back the bikochu,
and that's exactly
what we're gonna do!
-Really?
Willing to die for it?
-Paper bombs.
-Come on, Akamaru!
Fang over Fang!
HINATA (VOICEOVER): That sound!
I see.
They haven't given up yet.
They're still fighting.
This isn't the time for tears.
I can't give up.
This whole mission was my idea.
Byakugan!
There are 13 bees
around the rope.
If I can take them all
down at once, I'll be safe.
But I'm not used to
such small targets.
[explosion]
-Impossible.
How could he--
-I told you.
I just don't know
when to give up.
HINATA (VOICEOVER): Naruto!
Right.
Quitting isn't an option.
I have to concentrate,
control my chakra.
-Fang over Fang!
-How many of these
things are there?
-Kiba.
-Sorry.
I'm coming up empty here.
For some reason, my
body's giving out.
-It can't be.
-The larvae in this hive hunger
for only one kind of food.
Chakra.
-What?
-And as long as
you're down there,
they'll drain every ounce
you have through the walls
around you.
Don't pout.
Why don't you just
tell me the location?
HINATA (VOICEOVER): Now!
4, 5, 6.
10, 11, 12, 13.
Oh, no!
-Summoning Jutsu.
What's your preference?
You want the larvae
coming after you,
or would you rather be
food for the big guy here?
It's your choice, gentlemen.
What'll it be?
[theme music]
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
What do I do?
My body won't move.
I just wanted to help Naruto.
That's the whole reason I
fought for this mission.
I can't end up being
a burden on everyone.
Not again!
No.
I have to calm down,
focus my chakra,
and remember my training.
I don't have any other
choice right now.
Next time, Blaze Away, Byakugan!
This Is My Ninja Way.
[theme music]