[theme music]
-Nicely done.
All of you showed a lot of
determination on this exam.
It wasn't an easy one.
Just one more thing-- I
congratulate you on passing.
-Huh?
-That's right,
you've all passed.
The first stage of your
Chunin Exam is done
and now I pray you succeed
on the next part of the test.
-Yeah!
Believe it!
I passed!
Yeah!
Wooh, wooh, wooh!
Yahoo!
--[chuckling] He's an
interesting one, all right.
Incredible-- to
think that someone
would just pass in a
completely blank test paper.
Yes, that Naruto Uzumaki
sure is an interesting kid.
-The Chunin Exam Stage
Two-- The Forest of Death.
[birds squawking]
-Ugghh.
-This whole place just
completely creeps me out.
--[chuckling] It should-- they
call it the Forest of Death,
and soon enough, you're
going to find out why.
-Hmph!
(MOCKINGLY) "They call
it the Forest of Death,
but soon enough, you're going to
find out why. " Do your worst,
you're not going
to scare me away.
I can handle anything!
-So looks like we've got
ourselves a tough guy.
Are you tough enough
to handle this?
You're not afraid, are you?
-Uh.
U-ugh.
-Tough guys like you
usually leave their blood
all over this forest.
-I was just
returning your knife.
-Why, thank you, Grass ninja.
You know, I really
only recommend
you stand this close
behind me if you
wish to reach a premature end.
-My pardon.
With the sight of
blood and your blade
slicing through
my hair, mhm, I'm
afraid that I just
became a little excited.
I meant you no harm.
-Naruto.
[orochimaru chuckles]
-Likewise.
-(VOICEOVER) Ugh.
I thought this
forest was creepy,
but these guys
are even creepier.
-(VOICEVOER) Hey, I wonder if
I could do that with my tongue.
-Mmm.
I don't know.
-It seems like everyone here
today is quick-tempered;
there must be
something in the air.
[chuckling] This
is going to be fun.
-(VOICEOVER) "Quick-tempered?"
Sheesh, you're the one
who threw the kunai at me.
Now before we begin
this test, I have
something to hand
out to you all.
It's just a standard
consent form.
Before the test,
all of you are going
to have to read over this
form, and then sign it.
-What for?
-Some of you may not
come back from this test,
and I have to get your
consent to that risk.
Otherwise, it would
be my responsibility.
[laughter]
[whispering among the genin]
Now, I'll explain what
you'll be doing on this test.
Here, pass these out.
The first thing
you need to know is
that this test will tax every
one of your survival skills.
-(VOICEOVER)
Survival-- what a drag.
[yawn]
-First, I'll give
you all a description
of the terrain on
the practice field.
The 44th Battle Training Zone
has 44 locked entrance gates.
There are rivers
and a forest inside.
-In the center is a locked
tower, located 10 kilometers
from each gate.
It's in this confined
area that you'll
undergo the Survival Test.
The test consists of
an anything goes battle
to get your hands
on these scrolls.
-Both of them?
ANKO: Yes, you'll be
fighting to get both a Heaven
Scroll and an Earth Scroll.
All together, 26 teams will
be taking part in this test.
So half of those
teams will be going
after the Heaven Scroll
and the other half
will be trying to
get the Earth Scroll.
I'll hand over one kind
of scroll to each team,
and that's what
you'll be vying for.
-OK, so how do we pass the test?
ANKO: Your entire squad must
bring both the Heaven and Earth
scroll to the tower.
-That means at the
very best, half of us
will fail-- more,
if not every team
is able to get both the scrolls.
-No one ever said
it would be easy.
Oh, and one more thing,
the test has a time limit.
You must finish it
within five days.
-Five days out there?
-What are we supposed
to do for food?
-Just look around.
The forest is full
of things to eat,
and there's plenty
to feed all of you.
-Yeah, but that's not all
the forest has plenty of.
There are man-eating beasts
and poisonous plants in there.
-Oh, man!
-Quiet down.
This is why they call
it "survival", you now.
-That means with
these circumstances
there's no way half the
teams will pass the test.
-With the days getting longer,
the nights are getting shorter.
So we will have less time to
sleep and less time to recover.
It is a challenge, indeed.
-Completely
surrounded by enemies,
there won't be time to rest.
We'll have to keep
a constant watch.
-Right.
This test also measures
endurance behind enemy lines.
This is designed to
be a grueling test,
and I'm sure some of you
won't be up to the challenge.
-So um, let's say mid
exam-- can we quit?
-Of course, not.
In the middle of a battle, you
can't say, "Sorry, I quit."
Well, I guess you
could, but it's probably
going to get you killed.
-Oh, just great.
This is going to be a drag.
-There are also some ways
you can get disqualified.
The first is simple-- if
all three members of a team
can't make it to the tower with
both scrolls after five days.
Number two-- if a team loses a
member or if a member becomes
incapacitated and
cannot continue.
But most important, none of
you-- absolutely none of you--
may look at the
contents of the scrolls
until you've reached the tower.
W- what if it just happens
to flap open and you read it?
-Let me put it to you
this way, young man,
you don't want to know.
--Naaa!
ANKO: There are times
when a ninja will
be asked to carry
secret documents.
The scroll rule is to
test your integrity.
OK, we're done.
Each team, take
your consent forms
and exchange them over
there for your scrolls.
After that, each team pick a
gate, and you'll be let inside.
[sigh]
-Oh, and I have one more word
of advice-- just don't die!
-Hmph.
[whispering among the genin]
-(VOICEOVER) I see how it is, we
won't know which team has which
scroll, and we won't know which
of the team members is carrying
a scroll.
Stealing information is really
a matter of life and death.
It's just like Ibiki said.
[whispering among the genin]
-(VOICEOVER) Everyone is
equally determined to pass,
and all of them are my enemies.
-(VOICEOVER) Hm, it looks like
they're starting to understand
what's really
involved in this test.
INO: Well, well,
well, if it isn't
the little future failure.
What's up, billboard brow?
I thought you would have washed
out of the program by now.
Your big forehead alone,
should have gotten you tossed.
-So sad, you're jealous that I'm
spending five days with Sasuke.
And it's clearly
turning you into someone
very petty and ugly.
And you were already ugly .
[laughter]
-Grrr!
-Ugly!
-You are!
-Billboard brow!
-Ugly!
-Billboard forehead!
-Enough!
Give it up, Sakura!
You and I both know you're
too weak to pass this test!
-Yeah, right!
You're the one who's going down!
[groans]
-Hmph!
[trembling]
-I'm glad they
didn't turn on us.
Why are they like
that to each other?
-Pffft!
Who cares?
Like I have time to
worry about that stuff.
-Huh?
What are you doing
all the way out here?
[gasp]
-Oh, Naruto, I um,
I just, nothing--
-(VOICEOVER) That's
Hinata, weird as always.
-I, uh, oh, you're cut.
Here, I have mist--
-Well, anyway, see you later.
-(VOICEOVER) Uh, I guess I'll
just keep it for later then.
-All right, everyone.
We're going to start
handing out scrolls.
-(VOICEOVER) I wonder if any
of them will survive this.
-(VOICEOVER) Ha!
We are so going to win this.
-Listen up.
All the teams have
received their scroll,
so everybody go to your
gate and wait there.
When the gates open,
the test is on!
-Yahoo!
We rock at survival.
There's no way we can lose.
Hinata, you'd better
be strong for this.
-Right.
SHIKAMARU: The test might cost
us our lives-- what a drag.
But since we have
to do it, let's
just go after Naruto first.
-Burrito?
Check.
Potato chips?
Strawberry layered cake?
Yeah, yeah!
-Believe it!
I dare you to
bring it on, ninja.
I'll just send it right
back-- twice as hard!
-Oooh!
Ooh.
-Sia!
That's right!
--[chuckling] The time has
come to carry out our orders
in the open.
-(VOICEOVER) Not only do I
have to deal with the punks
on the other teams,
I'll be with Gaara,
and he might try to kill me.
-We'll target the rookies--
they're easy prey.
-We'll get their scroll
from them in no time.
Anything goes, right?
-Sensei, I will make you proud.
Just watch, soon everyone
will know the name Rock Lee.
[clock ticking]
-All right, heads
up, you maggots!
The second part of
the test has begun!
-You know who we're looking for.
-Yeah, those three brats.
-Hee, hee, hee.
We're all right!
Here we go, guys!
-Ugh.
-OK, first thing we've
got to do is to find it.
Are you ready, Hinata?
-Mhm.
Byakugan!
NEJI: Take it easy, Lee.
The test has only just begun.
-That may be, but still,
whoever our enemies are,
I want to find them
before they find us.
-You hot-blooded fool.
-We have only one target--
stay focused on it.
-Ah!
Are you kidding?
What are you doing?
-I'm just having a snack.
I mean, I've got to keep
my strength up, don't I?
-We haven't even been
out here five minutes!
-Yeah, now come on Choji,
we have a job to do here.
-I can't help it.
I've got to eat-- they're
my favorite flavor.
-You and your snacks.
This is a survival
test, you know.
You should have packed
more kunai and less candy.
[gasp]
-You guys, quick-- hide!
-Ugh.
Huuh!
-(VOICEOVER) Oh, no.
-Huh!
Oh!
[sigh of relief]
-(VOICEOVER) Aw, man, I've got
to deal with five more days
of this?
KIBA: So if the tower
is where everyone's
going to be headed in the end,
I say, we lay a trap near it
and just take the scrolls
off whoever we catch.
-Grrr.
-Well, well, we've got company.
-Hm?
-Ha!
Bunch of fools, just
standing out in the open
like they want to get caught.
-Well, it seems that
they've sensed our presence,
but they're all such lame
ninja that they can't even
pinpoint our location.
Ugh.
-Hey, what's wrong?
What's in your shirt?
-Oh, what is that thing?
-Ah!
Oh!
[screaming]
KIBA: Well, it looks like
the leeches found them.
They sense body temperature
and perspiration
and then in a group, they
swoop down on their prey.
If they suck your blood for
five minutes, it's all over.
These predators are smart.
We've taken advantage of their
instincts to trap our enemies.
-Get off me!
Huh?
[screaming]
-There's one team down.
--[chuckling] Sounds
like the fun has begun.
-Aaaagh!
-That sounded like
someone screaming.
[birds chattering]
-I do not like this place.
-Oh, come on.
It's nothing to be scared of.
It's going to be
a piece of cake.
Excuse me a second, I've
really got to you know--
-Yeah, right!
Get out of here!
What is this, a kennel?
Not in front of me you don't!
Find a bush or something!
NARUTO: Ah.
Mmm.
Ah, yeah.
Wooh!
Ah.
Aw man, that was a lot.
I wrote my whole name.
-You are such a pig!
You're really disgusting
sometimes, you know that?
-Augh!
-Huh?
-Du yaah!
-Sasuke, it wasn't that bad.
Don't you think you're
going a little overboard?
-Yeah, what the heck
was that all about?
Augh!
Ugh!
Ya!
Du ya!
Ugh!
You'd better watch out, Sakura,
I think he's gone crazy!
-Yeah, you wish.
I just struck before you could.
-Sasuke, no!
-All right, then-- bring it on!
Ugh!
Du!
Ya!
Ugh!
-Sasuke, what are you doing?
-Take a good look at him.
-Huh?
-Talk!
What have you done with Naruto?
[gasp]
-What?
What do you mean?
I am Naruto.
-Then where's the
cut on your cheek?
[gasp]
-Huh?
-I guess you didn't
know the real Naruto got
a cut on his face
before this test.
You also have your
shuriken holster
on your left leg,
not your right.
But the real Naruto
is right-handed.
Your transformation skill
is worse than Naruto's.
Tell me who you are!
-All right, you got me.
So what?
I'm still going to
take your scroll.
Now hand it over, or else.
So, which one of you has it?
Hmph!
Fine then, I guess I'll just
have to take you both out!
[theme music]
-That guy's going to
pay for what he did.
I mean, sneaking up on a guy
while he's-- it's just not
right.
Of course, even after
we're done with him,
we've got plenty
to keep us busy.
Vicious ninja, a giant
snake, and five days
of non-stop tension on this
ninja-fighting, scroll-hunting,
leech-filled survival test!
Oh man, I could use a vacation.
-Next time-- Eat or Be
Eaten-- Panic in the Forest.
Wait, what?
That's not cool.
I don't like the
sound of that at all!