[theme music]
-Come on!
[speaking japanese]
-Glad you came, Sakura, for
your sake, and the others.
-Huh?
-Now, you can all formally
register for the Chunin Exam.
-Why?
What do you mean?
-You see, only
groups of three are
allowed to apply for,
and take the exam.
That's the way it's always been.
-But Sensei, you said the
decision to take the exam
was up to the individual.
-That's right.
I did.
-Was that a lie?
-Sort of.
It is an individual decision,
but it affects all of you.
I didn't tell you
before, because I
didn't want the other
guys pressuring you.
-Hmph.
-At the same time,
I didn't want you
feeling obliged to participate,
because of any feelings
you might have for
Sasuke, or Naruto.
I wanted you to come to a
decision of your own free will.
-Wait a minute.
Do you mean if the
others had shown but,
but I decided not
to come with them--
-It would've been
the end of the line.
If you hadn't come
along, I couldn't
have let the others in.
But it's a moot point.
You're all here, and
for the right reasons.
Sakura.
Naruto.
And Sasuke.
I'm proud of you.
I couldn't ask
for a better team.
Good luck.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): We
won't let you down, Sensei!
Believe it!
Genin Takedown!
All Nine Rookies Face Off!
-Wh-- What's this?
-Gee, I guess we're not alone.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Man.
I had no idea there'd
be so much competition.
If being scary-looking
was one of the tests,
they've got me beat!
[gulps]
INO (VOICEOVER): Sasuke,
where have you been?
-Wha?
[giggling]
-Boy, you have no
idea how much I
was hoping you'd show up here.
I've missed those brooding
good looks of yours.
[growls]
-Hey, you porker!
Back off!
He's mine!
-Miss Forehead!
They let you in?
Still got those big frown lines
on your billboard brow, I see.
-Leave my forehead out of it!
[mocking]
[growls]
-Oh, it's you guys.
I knew this was gonna
be a drag, but I
didn't know it was
gonna be this lame.
-So all three stooges are here.
-Hey, you know what, pipsqueak?
Ah, forget it.
You're a waste of time.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Shikamaru Nara.
Always complaining, never
does anything about it.
The laziest kid in the Academy.
[chewing]
Choji Akimichi.
Akimunchi's more like it.
I think he'd eat his
own head if he could.
-Sorry, but Sasuke's all mine.
[mocking]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Ino Yamanaka.
Now she's annoying, and
not just because she's
got the same stupid thing
for Sasuke that Sakura's got.
-Well, what do you know?
It looks like the whole
gang's back together again.
-(NERVOUSLY) Oh.
Hi, Naruto.
-Hmm?
[gasps]
Hinata Hyuga.
She's OK, but I
don't know why she
gets all shy and embarrassed
every time I even, like,
look at her.
It's kind of weird.
Kiba Inuzuka and
his dog, Akamaru.
Forget what I said about Ino.
This guy's the most
annoying of all.
Thinks he's so cool.
Then there's Shino Aburame.
Well, he's just weird.
Kind of a mystery, but
that doesn't mean he
isn't annoying, too.
-You guys, too, huh?
Man.
Everyone's here for
this stupid thing.
KIBA (VOICEOVER): Yep.
Here we all are.
The nine rookies.
This is going to
be fun, at least,
for those of us good
enough to make the cut.
Right, Sasuke?
-Kiba, careful you
don't get overconfident.
-Just wait.
We're going to
blow you guys away.
We've been training like crazy.
-What do you think
we've been doing?
Sitting around picking daisies?
You don't know what
training means!
[gasps]
-Don't mind Kiba.
I'm sure he didn't really
mean anything by it.
-Huh?
[whimpers]
CHOJI (VOICEOVER):
Akamaru's looking plumper.
Juicier.
[growls]
-What do you want?
What's wrong?
-Thought maybe you
hadn't seen it.
-Huh?
-Didn't want you stepping on it.
-Why?
You saving it for lunch?
-Hey, you guys.
You might want to try
keeping it down a little.
I mean, no offense, but you're
the nine rookies, right?
Fresh out of the Academy?
I wouldn't go making a
spectacle of yourselves.
Just cool it.
This isn't a class field trip.
-Well, who asked you?
Who are you?
-I'm Kabuto Yakushi.
But really, look around you.
You've made quite an impression.
[gasping]
See those guys?
They're from the Rain Village.
Very touchy.
They all are.
This exam makes
everyone tense, and you
don't want to rub them
the wrong way right now.
-Uh-uh.
-You can't help it.
I mean, how could you
know how things work?
You're just rookies.
You remind me of
myself a while back.
-Kabuto.
Is that your name?
-Yeah.
-This isn't the first time
you've taken the exam?
No, it's-- my seventh.
-Huh?
KABUTO (VOICEOVER): Well,
they're held twice a year.
So, this will be my fourth year.
-Wow, a veteran.
You must really be
an expert by now.
-Yeah, sort of.
-Cool!
You can give us all
the inside tips.
-Yeah, some expert.
He's never passed.
-Well, seventh time's the charm.
That's what they say, huh?
-So I guess all of those rumors
about the exam being tough
are true.
Oh man, I knew this
was going to be a drag.
-Hang on.
Don't give up hope yet.
Maybe I can help you
kids out a little,
with my Ninja Info Cards.
-What the heck are those?
-It's hard to explain,
but these cards
have been chakra
encoded with everything
I've learned over
the past four years.
I've got more than 200 of them.
So you see, I haven't been
completely wasting my time.
They may not look like
much to the naked eye.
In fact, they appear blank.
Don't want just anyone
seeing this stuff.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
What are you doing?
-You see, I'm using my chakra
to reveal their secrets,
like this, for example.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Awesome!
A map!
INO (VOICEOVER): Of what?
KABUTO (VOICEOVER): It shows
the geographical distribution
of all the candidates who have
come to take the Chunin exam.
What villages they come from,
and how many from each village.
Why do you guys think
they all come here
to take the exam together,
at the same time?
[chewing]
-It's to foster friendship
between nations, of course.
International
brotherhood, and all that.
And it's true enough,
as far as it goes.
-But there's another reason.
-Yeah.
You see, the important
thing is that this way, they
can carefully regulate the
total number of Shinobi
that end up in each
village, thereby
maintaining the
balance of power.
-Oh, yeah.
Balance of power.
-Balance of power.
Big deal, it's all a drag.
-If the balance
isn't maintained,
one nation could wind up
with many more Shinobi
than its neighbors, and it
might be tempted to attack them.
So, they try to
maintain the status quo.
Makes sense, I suppose.
-Hmph.
-Do those cards of
yours have any info
on the other candidates,
individually?
-They might.
You have someone
special in mind?
-I might.
KABUTO (VOICEOVER):
Well, I can't
promise my information
is complete or perfect,
but I've got something
on just about everyone,
including you guys, of course.
So which one is it?
Tell me anything
you know about them.
A description.
Where they're from, whatever.
Anything at all.
-He's Gaara of the desert.
And there's Rock Lee of the
Leaf Village while you're at it.
-Man, that's no fun.
You even know their names.
That makes it easy.
Here they are.
-Show 'em to me.
-Hmm.
Hmm?
Mhmm-hmm.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I haven't
a clue what's going on here.
But I'll act like I do.
-OK.
First up is Rock Lee.
KABUTO (VOICEOVER):
Looks like he's
about a year older
than you guys.
Mission experience, 11
C ranks and 20 D ranks.
His squad leader is Guy.
In the last 12
months, his taijutsu
has radically improved, but his
other skills are pretty shaky.
Last year, he got a lot
of attention as a Genin,
but for some
reason, he chose not
to participate in
the Chunin Exam.
This will be his first time as
a candidate, same as you guys.
His teammates are
Tenten and Neji Hyuga.
-Huh?
Hyuga?
KABUTO (VOICEOVER): OK.
Now for Gaara of the desert.
Mission experience, eight
C ranks, and-- Get this.
One B rank as a Genin.
There's not a lot more
information on this guy.
He was a rookie from
another land, originally,
but there is this.
He survived every mission
without getting a scratch
on him.
-The dude's done a
B rank as a Genin,
and has never even been injured?
-What's the deal with this guy?
KABUTO (VOICEOVER): Leaf, Sand,
Rain, Grass, Waterfall, Sound.
From the looks of
it, they've all
sent exceptionally
skilled candidates
to the exam this time around.
Of course, the hidden
Sound Village is small.
It sprang up recently.
No one knows anything about it.
Those guys are a mystery.
-Well, you get the point.
The competition's going
to be intense this year.
-So it would seem.
It's almost enough to make
you lose your confidence.
-It's a fine time to
start talking like that!
-Do you really think it's
going to be tougher this time?
-Oh, yeah.
In the four years
I've been coming,
I've never seen a
crop of candidates
with as much potential
as this bunch.
[growls]
KABUTO (VOICEOVER): Yep.
We've got our work
cut out for us.
-I can't go along with this.
They may be under your care now,
Kakashi, but I know these kids.
They were my students.
I trained them.
I don't know what you're trying
to prove with this, but--
-You know, he may
be right, Kakashi.
You're putting a lot
of pressure on them.
Why so impatient?
I held my team back for a year,
so they could hone their skills
and mature.
Let them enjoy their
youth a little longer.
-Your concern is touching.
You sure it's not
just because you
know your guys don't stand
a chance against mine?
-All right.
All right, that's enough.
The matter of the rookies'
participation is closed.
Now, as for the other
Genin, I'm ready to consider
your recommendations.
-I know what I'm doing.
You'll see.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): I wish
I was as sure as I sounded.
I wonder how they're doing.
Even the cockiest of 'em
must be a little scared.
[shivering]
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): OK.
So we're just rookies,
and most of these guys
are older and more
experienced than we are.
No big deal.
It's OK to be a little scared.
I can handle it.
But it'd be a whole
lot easier if I
didn't have to watch Naruto tell
falling apart right in front
of me.
I mean, nothing
usually gets to him.
Poor guy.
Maybe I can try to cheer him up.
-Hey.
Don't worry, Naruto.
We'll be fine.
[screams]
-My name is Naruto
Uzumaki, and I'm
gonna beat every one of you.
Believe it!
[chuckles]
-Hey, what's that idiot
trying to do, get us killed?
-I should have known.
He's not smart
enough to be scared.
-Tell your boyfriend to
keep his big fat trap shut!
-Whose boyfriend?
-Oh, I forgot.
You can't get one!
-What'd you say?
-Yeah!
I feel a lot better now.
-Hmm.
That's the same kid
as before, isn't it?
-He yips just like a little dog.
-What a jerk!
-Well, he sure hasn't
lost any of his spunk.
-He has passion.
-I guess you didn't intimidate
him as much as you thought,
huh, Lee?
ZAKU (VOICEOVER): You heard what
he said about the hidden Sound
Village?
He called us little.
A mystery.
DOSU (VOICEOVER): I heard.
-I say, we teach this
guy some manners.
-Yeah.
Time to clear up some
of the mystery for him.
Update his information.
Let him know that if you
insult the Sound Shinobi,
you'd better be ready
for the consequences.
-Uh, can you say that
again a little louder?
Didn't quite catch it.
-You moron.
Are you trying to get everybody
in the place to hate our guts,
or what?
[laughing]
-Naruto, you jackass!
[screaming]
Why'd you have to go and
say something like that?
You obnoxious little--
Oh, hi, everyone.
Don't mind him.
Sometimes he says
these spazzy things.
He doesn't really mean them.
They just kinda come out.
He's got this
condition, you know.
Kind of a psychological thing.
He really should
be on medication.
Now see what you've
done, Naruto?
You've hurt
everybody's feelings.
They think you
don't respect them.
But that isn't
true, is it Naruto?
DOSU (VOICEOVER): You ready?
ZAKU (VOICEOVER): Let's do it.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Would you
just for once in your life
think about what you're doing?
Think about the rest of us!
-Fine.
-Huh?
[gasps]
KABUTO (VOICEOVER):
They're from the village
hidden in the Sound.
[gasps]
NARUTO AND SAKURA
(VOICEOVER): Man, he's fast.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): He's
almost as quick as me.
KABUTO (VOICEOVER): Hmm.
[glasses cracking]
-Oh, I get it.
So it was that kind of attack.
-Hang on, I saw it all.
He dodged the attack.
How did that happen?
-It must have come
closer than it looked.
Look at him acting
like it was nothing.
Real tough guy.
[gasps]
[retching]
-What?
Did he just?
-Kabuto, what's wrong?
What is it?
-Heh.
-Hey, Kabuto.
-Are you OK?
-Yeah.
I'm fine.
-Are you sure?
-Not such a tough guy,
after all, I guess.
Maybe that's why he's
on his seventh try.
ZAKU (VOICEOVER): Write this
on your little card, punk.
The Genin from the
Sound Village will
be Chunin when this is over.
Guaranteed.
[growls]
[grunts]
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
I don't get it.
He saw their attack
in time to avade it.
What made him fall apart?
-Hey, Lee, what was going
on with that attack?
-There was more to
it than just speed.
some kind of trick.
-Hmm.
IBIKI (VOICEOVER): All right,
you baby face degenerates.
Pipe down and listen up.
It's time to begin.
I'm Ibiki Marino, your proctor.
And from this moment,
your worst enemy.
[theme music]
THEME SONG: Cultivate your
hunger before you idealize.
Motivate your anger to
make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain,
never coming down.
Break into the contents,
never falling down.
My knee is still shaking,
like I was twelve.
Sneaking out the classroom
by the back door.
A man railed at me,
though, but I didn't care.
Waiting is wasting,
for people like me.
Don't try to live so wise.
Don't cry, 'cause
you're so right.
Don't dry with fakes or fears.
'Cause you will hate
yourself in the end.
Don't try to live so wise, Don't
cry, 'cause you're so right.
Don't dry with fakes or fears.
'Cause you will hate
yourself in the end.
Don't try to live so wise.
Don't cry, 'cause
you're so right.
Don't dry with--
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Finally,
no more talking the talk.
Now it's time to walk the walk.
Man, not to sound
conceited or anything,
but really, why bother, guys?
It's over!
Hope you brought a
toothbrush, 'cause
you're gonna be picking
my dust out of your teeth.
I mean, not to brag or
anything, but hoo-ee!
Chunin, here I come!
Next time, Start Your Engines.
The Chunin Exam Begins.
I'll be here, locked and loaded.
Believe it!