[theme song]
-OK, let's go!
Eh?
-Let's go?
Are you kidding me?
Quit acting like a stupid
little kid, will ya?
-What the-- why are
you in such a bad mood?
-Well, what do you think?
We're still in the
middle of my training.
You said there were three
steps to learn, right?
Well, I've only
learned two of them.
Now quit holding out on me.
-Relax.
You can work on the third
one while we're walking.
-What?
Are you serious?
Huh?
A balloon?
-Here.
-OK.
So what's the deal?
An ordinary balloon?
-The first step you
learned was rotation.
The second step was power.
The third and final step
for you to master is this.
NARUTO: An Impossible Choice--
The Pain Within Tsunade's
Heart.
Ugh!
What do you mean
by this already?
-It looks like I'm simply
holding an ordinary balloon,
doesn't it?
-What do you mean, looks like?
That is all you're
doing, you pervy weirdo.
-Huh.
Let me try again.
Over on my left this time.
Let's see what's really
happening inside the balloon.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Whoa.
The chakra is spinning
wildly and getting faster.
But it's still perfectly round.
It's almost like--
-Take a look at that.
Like a small typhoon.
-So then what you're
doing in your left hand
is also happening in the
balloon on your right?
-That's right.
What do you think?
Nifty, huh?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Awesome.
He's got all of that
chakra whizzing around.
And the balloon
isn't even moving.
There's more power than
when the rubber ball popped,
and way more spin to it.
-Now listen.
In the third step
you've gotta draw up
100% of what you've
learned so far.
And then maintain it.
In other words, keeping
the power and the rotation
of your chakra at their maximum.
First visualize a thin membrane
just inside the balloon,
then of compressing
the chakra inside it.
-Hey, I think I get it now!
So this stage is
about keeping up
the power and rotation
that I learned,
only this time without
letting them pop open
a delicate balloon!
-Well, you're starting
to get the hang of this.
Good!
-Hm?
So wait.
Hold on a second.
Why exactly am I going
to all this trouble?
-Come here.
I'll show you.
Watch closely.
After the first two steps
of training, you get this.
-Whoa.
-Then, once you've mastered
the third step-- you get this!
If you can keep that small
typhoon the size of your palm,
then the energy will
be unable to disperse.
It'll spin faster and
faster, and its power
will become more
and more compressed.
And its destructive
power will reach its max.
So, there you have it.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Right.
This'll be no sweat.
OK.
This feels right.
Now!
Keep it going-- keep it going--
keep it going-- keep it going!
-There's no cutting
corners here.
Get your power and rotation to
100%, and then maintain them.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
This is crazy.
Unless I can perfectly control
my power it's impossible.
I see now.
This third step-- it's
on a whole other level
compared to the first two.
-I told you, didn't I?
This is an A-rank technique.
It's a highly advanced
ninjutsu, kid.
OK.
That's enough
explaining for today.
You can practice on the road.
-Hey, hold on a minute.
Do we have to rush?
Give me a chance to--
-We've already
wasted enough time
waiting for you to
recover your strength.
There's no guarantee that
Tsunade will stay in this town
much longer.
-Wha-- yeah, but-- but--
-It's not like she's gonna
bump into some old acquaintance
and start reminiscing
over the good old days.
Come on.
Let's go.
-All right.
-It's been quite a long
time, hasn't it, Orochimaru?
-Indeed.
I've been looking
for you everywhere.
-What do you want with
me after all this time?
You feel like kicking around
stories of the old days?
-Actually, I was hoping
to ask you for a favor.
-His heartbeat is racing.
And he's burning up,
by the look of him.
Definitely signs of
prolonged fatigue.
And those arms--
-Lady Tsunade, I'm sure
you've surmised by now.
-Find someone else.
I haven't treated
anyone in years.
-That won't do.
Surely you must realize how
serious these wounds are.
There isn't anyone who can
cure him of his affliction.
Except, of course, for
the legendary sannin
and medical genius,
Lady Tsunade.
Only you can do this.
-Those arms of yours--
that's no ordinary injury.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): A special
sealing jutsu, or something.
-What have you
gotten yourself into?
-Nothing, really.
I was just killing
the Third Hokage.
-Impossible.
Is this true?
-Oh, come now, Tsunade.
Quit shooting me
that dirty look.
Anything that has form
must one day decay.
Even men.
But I don't really need to
tell you that, now do I?
After all, you let the
two most dear to you
march off to their deaths.
KABUTO (VOICEOVER): Let the
two most dear to her die?
I see.
This is a wicked
game he's playing.
-Such a pity.
It really was a terrible
way for them to die.
-Scum.
Needles.
Dipped in poison.
KABUTO (VOICEOVER): She's fast.
-Get out of my way!
-I won't let you!
-Shizune, calm down!
KABUTO (VOICEOVER): This
assistant-- she's powerful.
-Orochimaru.
You were always this twisted,
even when we were kids.
Come on, you know
the type of gal I am.
Don't even kid with me, OK?
Or shall I kill you
where you stand?
KABUTO (VOICEOVER):
She's strong.
And terrifying.
She must be single, no doubt.
-Tsunade's impatient, and
extremely quick to anger.
[pop]
Come on, kid.
We don't have time
for kicking back.
If we don't hurry, who knows
where that wayward woman will
scamper off to next.
-Listen, you pervy sage.
That's no way to talk
to an apprentice who's
working his butt off!
-Oh, zip it.
Just calm down, will you?
Tsunade's the priority here.
-Son of a-- well,
how do you like that?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Pervy
sage came all this way
to find this lady.
She must really be something.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER): I
hope she's still here.
-Please.
We haven't come all
this way to fight.
We're here to negotiate.
-Negotiate?
-That's right.
-Are you trying
to make me laugh?
I've told you once already.
Now get the hell
out of my sight.
-I'm afraid that's
just impossible.
-Get out of here.
-You're the only ones who can
cure Lord Orochimaru's arms.
You know that.
-I'm warning you.
-We're not asking for charity.
We can make a deal here.
-I'll count down from five.
I suggest you leave
before I'm done.
Otherwise I'll have to make you.
-Please, try to remain calm.
This could prove
beneficial for both of us.
-Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
And one.
-I'm offering to bring
your dear little brother
and your beloved back to life.
With a forbidden jutsu
that I have developed.
I can't help but notice
that you haven't chased us
off yet, my old friend.
I suppose it's safe to assume
we have a deal here then?
-Eh, sure.
I know the young lady.
-You're sure?
-Yeah.
Think she said she needed to
win back the money she lost.
Said she was heading over there.
-Rotation and power.
Charge them both
up to the maximum.
And then maintain them.
-Hey, kid.
-Huh?
-How about it, sonny boy?
Wanna throw the dice around?
-Heading over there?
Well, where do you mean?
-Check it out.
If you roll the dice and it
comes up odd, that's han.
And if it's even, then it's cho.
-Look, zip it, pal.
I'm trying to get some
training done here.
Quit bugging me.
-What are you talking about?
This is a gambling house.
Now why don't you ditch
that balloon there?
We'll have more fun with these.
-What, are you kidding?
I have work to do.
I don't have time to be
messing around shooting dice.
-Man, what a boring kid.
-Oh, shut up.
-So, you gonna tell me where?
-Sure, but don't expect it to
be free in a place like this.
-Oh.
-Let's make a deal.
If you win, then the
information will be free.
But if you lose it's going
to cost you a thousand.
-You're on, son!
-So what'll it be?
Han, or cho?
-OK.
Here we go.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER): Hm.
Let's see.
I'm exactly 50 years old.
So--
-Gimme cho!
-Remember, if it's han, I win.
Now then, let's see what we got.
-Oh!
Two and five-- that makes han!
-What the heck's going on?
-There goes my thousand.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
Nice, Naruto.
-What do you know?
Looks like I win, doesn't it?
-Huh?
Ugh.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Aw, man.
I screwed it up again!
-Maintain--
-Well, great.
Where am I supposed to look now?
[pop]
-Well, I'm stumped.
That woman isn't
anywhere to be found.
-Hm?
Huh?
Me?
-Scratch off cards?
-Kids, grown-ups.
Everyone loves the lotto.
Give it a whirl, cutie.
It's fun.
-Uh--
-What about this one, hm?
You'll know right
away if you've won.
-You're cuter when you're
chubby, aren't you, froggy?
Yes you are.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
I can't believe
he won off of just one ticket.
Kid must have a
knack for gambling.
If only he was that
sharp on his jutsu.
Anyhow, I need to focus
on finding Tsunade.
Where could should be?
She couldn't have gotten
far in so short a time.
Well, I guess we better
find some high ground
and take a look around.
If I remember it correctly,
this town surrounds a castle.
If we climb up to the top--
-Hey, Naruto.
Come on.
This way.
-Huh?
All right.
-Come now.
Don't you want to
see them again?
Dear Tsunade.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): Nawaki.
Dan.
-What do you plan on
doing once your arms have
been restored to you?
I you know me.
I've never been one to lie.
So I'll just give you the truth.
How about that?
-Hey, hold on a minute.
Where's this castle
you were talking about?
-It's gone.
-In addition to grabbing all
I desire-- this time around
I'm going to grind the hidden
Leaf Village into just.
[music playing]
-Hey!
Enough already!
I don't care if she's one of the
sannin, a medical specialist,
or the legendary kunoichi!
There's no way I'm gonna accept
this lady's the Fifth Hokage.
It doesn't matter if she is
the best person for the job!
If she says anything against
the Third and Fourth Hokage,
I'll wipe the floor with her.
Next time-- Unforgivable!
A Total Lack of Respect!