[theme music]
-[sighs]
Think before you use a
jutsu, or else your opponent
might use it against you.
NARUTO: Aww.
-Oh, and also, if the bait
is obvious, don't take it.
-[grunts]
-A ninja must see
through deception.
-I get it!
Agh!
-I'm telling you this
because you don't get it.
You think you get
it, which is not
the same as actually getting it.
Get it?
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
This is my chance.
He finally dropped his guard.
-Won't you ever learn?
Ugh!
-[gasps]
-Aah!
He just got blasted
by a shuriken.
Are you out of
your mind, Sasuke?
You went too far!
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
Another substitution jutsu.
And now, he knows
where I'm hiding.
Got to move fast.
I thought he lowered his guard,
but he did that on purpose.
And I fell for it.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
So that's where he is.
[chuckles]
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Sasuke, where did you go?
Don't tell me
Kakashi-sensei found you.
No, he can't capture my Sasuke.
I won't let him.
Whew!
He didn't hear me.
I'm safe.
MALE SPEAKER: (WHISPERS)
Sakura, behind you.
-Huh?
[screams]
-"A ninja must see
through deception."
Yeah, yeah.
How am I supposed to do that?
[grunts]
Well, I'm sure I'm not falling
for any more of his traps!
[grunts]
[chuckles]
Aargh!
I fell for it again!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): "You Failed!
Kakashi's Final Decision."
-Oh, my!
Huh?
Uh, someone there?
Uhh, I think I felt something.
What was it?
Uh, huh?
What's going on?
MALE SPEAKER: Sakura.
-Sasuke!
--[grunts] Sa--
Sakura, huh, help me.
Please help me.
-Uhh.
[whimpers]
[screams]
-I think I overdid
it a bit, but she's
got to learn to see
through these things.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): Hm?
Sounded like Sakura?
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): Shinobi
Battle Skill Number 2,
the Illusion Jutsu.
Sakura studied it in
class, but she still
couldn't see it coming.
-Genjutsu.
It's just simple mind control.
I'm not surprised he
caught Sakura with it.
But I'm not like
Sakura and Naruto.
-Say that after you get one
of these bells, my Sasuke.
[chuckles]
-Eyah!
-There's no point
using normal attacks.
-[grunts]
-A trap!
What?
-Aah!
Harrh!
[grunts]
[chuckles]
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): Hm?
This kid.
-Ugh.
[panting]
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
He's fierce.
Hm.
I won't be able to read
"Make-out Paradise" now.
-Wha-- what happened?
[gasp]
Huh?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Sasuke, I saw him.
He was on the verge of-- no!
Sasuke, no!
You've got to survive, please!
Where are you?
-Hmm, hmm, huh?
Hey, what are those
things down there?
Gaah!
I know what those things are.
Those are boxed lunches.
Uhh, oh.
"A ninja must see
through deception."
Hm.
[giggles]
-Well, you are different
from the other two.
I'll grant you that.
-Humph.
Horse, Tiger Fire Style.
Fireball Jutsu!
-What?
Genin can't do a fire jutsu.
Takes too much chakra.
There's no way.
-[gasp]
Where did he go?
Behind me?
Above?
KAKASHI: Where?
-Huh?
[gasp]
-I'm where you least expect me--
-Aah!
---right under your feet.
Earth Style Headhunter Jutsu.
Can't move, huh?
That was ninjutsu, the
third shinobi battle skill.
You have talent,
and you are right.
You are different
from the others.
But different isn't
always better.
They say "the nail
that sticks up
is the one that
gets hammered down."
-Oh, great!
-[laughing]
Sensei told us that if
we don't get a bell,
then we don't get any lunch.
But if I eat my lunch now, then
there's nothing he could do.
It's chow time!
-Hi there!
-Gaah!
[moans] I was just
joking, Sensei.
-Nice try.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): [grunts]
He's stronger than I am.
I can't get around that.
[rustling]
Huh?
-Uh. [gasp]
[sighs]
Hm?
Huh?
-Sakura?
--[shrieks] Sasuke's just
a head without a body,
and he's talking!
Ugh!
-And that's my partner.
-[groans]
Sasuke.
Huh!
You're OK!
-Hey, cut it out!
Let go!
I've got to get a
bell before lunch.
That doesn't leave much time.
-Sasuke, you're still trying
to get one of those bells?
-A while ago, I touched one.
Next time, I'll get one.
-That is really great.
I can't believe you did that.
You're amazing.
I can't believe it!
He touched one of the bells!
I'll never get my hands
on one of those things,
which means Sasuke
will pass and I won't.
And we'll be separated forever!
No, no, no, no, no!
Uhh, it's almost lunch.
There is not really
enough time left.
So maybe we should just give up,
and then try again next year.
-[grunts]
-Hmm.
-I'm the only one who
can destroy that person.
-What?
Who?
You mean the sensei?
-That day, I was crying.
-When were you crying?
-It was my--
-What?
What happened to you?
-I am an avenger.
That means I must be
stronger than my prey.
I need this training.
There's no time for setbacks.
-Uhh.
-I'm going to restore my clan
and destroy a certain someone.
[alarm clock rings]
Ugh.
I've wasted too much time.
-Sasuke.
[stomach growling]
-Uh-oh, stomach's growling, huh?
That's too bad.
Oh, by the way,
about this exercise?
Well, I've decided I won't send
any of you back to the academy.
-Aah, hah!
-What?
I passed?
All I did was faint
and fall over.
Do you get points for that?
Love wins out!
Cha cha cha!
-Hm.
-Yay!
-Then, then that means
all three of us-- I mean,
all three of us?
-Yes.
All three of you are being
dropped from the program.
Permanently!
-Uh?
-Huh?
-Aah!
MALE SPEAKER: Unbelievable!
Kakashi has never
passed a single student.
He fails all of them.
-Iruka, this group is young.
Even I cannot see if it is good
for them to face the rigors
and dangers of ninja life.
However, Kakashi was correct
about all those he failed.
-Hm.
-Drop us from the program?
That means we can
never become ninja.
You said if we couldn't
take the bells,
we'd be sent back
to the academy.
You can't just change
your mind and kick us out!
Why would you do that?
-Because you don't
think like ninja.
You think like little
kids-- like brats.
-[grunts]
-Haah!
-Sasuke!
-You think it's all about you.
-[grunts]
-Let go of Sasuke!
You can't step on
him like he's a bug!
-You don't know what
it means to be a ninja.
You think it's a game, huh?
-Uhh.
-Oh.
-Why do you think we
put you on squads?
Did you consider that
question for one moment?
-Uh, I don't know what you mean?
-I mean, you never realized
what this exercise is all about.
Not even close.
-What it's about?
-Yes, that's what determines
whether you pass or fail.
-But that's-- I mean, I wanted
to ask you about that from
the beginning.
-Tch.
Use your head.
Three people on a squad.
Why do you think
we would do that?
-Aah!
How are we supposed to know
why you picked three people?
We didn't make the rules.
-It's so basic.
Teamwork!
-It means working together.
Is that what you mean?
-That's what I mean.
It's too late now.
But if all three of
you would come at me,
you might have been
able to take them.
Well, anyway, it's over.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Wait a minute.
-You set it up with three
people but only two bells.
If we worked together and
got the bells, only two of us
could keep them.
And that would lead
to group conflict.
And the squad would break up.
-Exactly.
I purposely pitted you
against each other.
-Hm.
-Huh?
KAKASHI: I wanted to see if
you could overcome that and put
the squad ahead of
yourselves, A Genin should
have a natural
feel for teamwork.
But you-- it never
even crossed your mind.
Sakura, you obsessed
about Sasuke who was gone;
while Naruto was
right in front of you,
and you wouldn't lift
a finger to help him.
-Uhh.
KAKASHI: Naruto, you do
everything on your own.
Everything.
And you Sasuke thought the
others were so far beneath you,
they were worthless.
Arrogance.
Ninja missions are
carried out in squads.
Of course, you need
individual skills.
But teamwork is the
most essential element.
Every shinobi understands this.
When individuals put
themselves above the squad,
this can lead to
failure and death.
For example, Sakura, kill
Naruto now or Sasuke dies.
[both gasp]
That's what happens
on a mission.
-Oh, boy.
That was really scary.
-[sighs]
-The enemy takes a
hostage, and you've
got an impossible choice.
And someone ends up dead.
On every mission, your
life is on the line.
-[grunts]
-Did you look at this stone,
the names engraved on it?
They are all ninja
who are honored
as heroes in our village.
-That's it, that's
it, that's it!
Now, I know!
I've decided I'm going to have
my name engraved on that stone.
I'm not going to live and
die for nothing like a dog.
I'm going to be a hero!
A hero!
-They are a special
kind of hero.
-Huh?
What kind of heroes are they?
Come on, tell us.
Well?
KAKASHI: They're all KIA.
-Ooh.
That sounds real cool.
-It means "killed in action."
They all died.
-Huh?
Uhh.
Oh.
-Hm.
-This is a memorial stone.
The names of my closest
friends are engraved here.
-Oh.
-[grunts]
-All right, I'm going to
give you one more chance.
But I'm going to make
it much harder on you.
You'll have three
hours to get a bell.
Eat lunch now to
build up strength.
But Naruto doesn't get any.
-[grunts]
-It's your punishment
for breaking the rules
and trying to eat by yourself.
And if anyone tries to
feed him, that person
will immediately fail.
-Nyaah.
-Hm.
-I make the rules.
You follow them.
Got it?
-I'm leaving.
-Iruka, listen to me.
-Huh?
-Whether they pass or fail,
you must not blame Kakashi.
-Right.
[stomach growls]
-Huh?
-This is no big deal.
I can go without eating
for days, for weeks.
Believe it!
This is no big deal.
[stomach growls]
No problem.
-Hm.
-Mm.
-Here.
-Huh?
-What?
No, Sasuke, you can't do that.
You heard what the sensei said.
-Kakashi's gone.
We need to get those
bells as a team.
If Naruto's hungry, he'll
be weak and ineffective.
That hurts the team and
jeopardizes the mission.
-Um.
-Sasuke.
[gulps]
Uhh.
-Sakura?
-Hm.
-OK, thanks.
-Don't thank me.
Just hurry up and eat.
-But isn't that your lunch?
-Uh, I'm on a diet.
I mean, I don't eat
at as much as Sasuke.
So, uhh, just take it, Naruto!
-I can't take it because
I can't move my hands.
You've got to feed me.
-Huh?
-Hurry up.
He could come back any minute.
-[grunts] This is one time only.
That's it!
I'll never do this again.
Is that clear?
-Clear as a bell, Sakura.
Ah, hm, mmm.
-[grunts]
-You!
-Aah!
-Ugh.
-You broke the rules.
I hope you're ready
for the punishment.
Any last words?
-[whimpers]
-[whimpers] But you said--
-Yes?
-You said that there
were three of us.
That's what you said!
And that's why Sakura and--
-We're all on this squad.
And we're all in it together.
-Yeah, that's right.
We gave our lunch to him
because the three of us are one!
-Uhh, yeah!
Yeah!
Believe it!
That's right!
-"The three of you are
one," that's your excuse?
Hm.
You pass.
-Huh?
-Haah?
-You pass.
-What do you mean?
How did we pass?
-You're the first squad
that ever succeeded.
The others did exactly what I
said and fell into every trap.
They couldn't think
for themselves.
"A ninja must see
through deception."
In the ninja world, those
who break the rules are scum.
That's true.
But those who abandon their
friends are worse than scum.
-Ah.
-[whimpers]
-Hm.
-He's a-- you know,
he's kind of cool.
-The exercise is over.
Everyone passes.
Squad 7 starts its
first mission tomorrow!
-Yes!
-I did it!
I did it!
Believe it!
I'm a ninja!
Ninja!
-Let's go home.
-Cha!
I did it!
-Aah! [grunts]
I knew they'd do this.
It happens every time.
Believe it!
[grunts]
You guys forgot to untie me!
THEME SONG: Cultivate your
hunger before you idealize.
Motivate your anger to
make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain,
never coming down.
Break into the contents,
never falling down.
My knee is still
shaking, like I was 12.
Sneaking out of the
classroom by the backdoor.
A man railed at me twice,
though, but I didn't care.
Waiting is wasting
for people like me.
Don't try to live so wise.
Don't cry 'cause
you're so right.
Don't try with fakes
or fears 'cause you
will hate yourself in the end.
Don't try to live so wise.
Don't cry 'cause
you're so right.
Don't try with fakes
or fears 'cause you
will hate yourself in the end.
Don't try to live so wise.
Don't cry 'cause
you're so right.
Don't try--
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
What's up with this?
All we're doing are these
boring training missions.
Then finally, we get a
chance at something big,
and it turns out it's just
guarding this old man.
And he says, I'm only a
kid, and calls me a loser.
I won't tell you what
I called him back.
But I did tell him, look,
someday I'll be-- hey,
are you listening to me?
Next time, "A
Dangerous Mission--
Journey to the Land of Waves."
Don't miss me as
a full-on ninja!