[theme music]
-What is this?
You come at me and
that's all you've got?
All that effort and you
couldn't even touch me.
What a joke!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Sakura.
-I don't really know how
much damage I can do.
But it doesn't matter.
I just have to give
it my best shot.
NARUTO: Naruto's Ninja Handbook.
-Shadow Clone jutsu!
Here goes!
Get ready for the
ultimate secret taijutsu!
Naruto Uzumaki Clone Body Slam!
OK!
Let's do it!
Shadow Clone jutsu!
And another!
Take this!
Leaf Village secret taijutsu!
Straight from the teachings
of Kakashi-sensei!
Thousand years of death!
-An enema.
Great.
Huh?
Boom.
Hey.
You OK?
-That was a nice
move the kid pulled.
-Yeah.
So did he get him or not?
-Gaara.
-All of that work and
you only scored one blow?
-Ah, put a sock in it.
-He attacked at the
base of the tail
where the defense is weakest.
He didn't wound me, but the
sand couldn't absorb the impact.
Have I underestimated him?
-Naruto, listen to me.
You have to save Sakura if
it's the last thing you do.
Once you've got her, I want
you to take her and flee
as fast as you can.
It's all up to you.
-Sasuke, you--
-I can hold him here
a little longer.
If it ends here,
it just means this
was as far as I was meant to go.
I lost everything once.
I don't ever want to
have to see that again.
My trusted comrades falling
right in front of me.
-Your comrades?
Sasuke.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): I will
not allow my comrades to die.
That is absolute.
-I get it now.
Of course.
He's no different than I am.
Going through life with
the exact same sadness
and loneliness that
I had to carry.
He fought only for himself,
never relying on anyone.
And because of that I thought
that he possessed strength.
I really did.
-Naruto.
-I don't know.
I guess I should
have known better.
That's not what
real strength is.
If you never fight for
anyone but yourself,
you'll never be strong,
no matter what you do.
-So is there someone
who's precious to you?
Anyone?
The truth is when a person
has something precious
they want to protect
it's only then
that they become
genuinely strong.
You will get strong.
Very strong.
[gasp]
-Haaa!
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
He's releasing
a massive amount of chakra.
How is he doing it?
-No matter what happens, I
swear I'm going to protect you!
[groan]
Multi-Shadow Clone jutsu!
-Nice, kid.
Not too shabby.
-Gee, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to keep
you waiting so long.
So get ready for an original
jutsu straight from my ninja
handbook!
-What the?
How could he have
summoned so many clones?
-You've got to be kidding.
-This is amazing.
I don't believe my eyes.
-Way to go there, blondie.
You're showing a lot of promise.
-How did you do this?
-Sasuke, why don't you
take it easy for a while?
You deserve it.
Just leave the rest
to Naruto Uzumaki.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
What happened to him?
-All right, everyone.
Look out.
Here I go!
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
Unbelievable.
Is that Naruto?
-Let's do this!
Direct from Naruto's
ninja handbook!
Everywhere!
Shuriken!
GAARA (VOICEOVER): My
body hasn't recovered yet.
Have to use the sand to defend.
[shouting]
-Na ru to 2K.
Uzumaki Barrage!
[groaning]
From Naruto's handbook!
GAARA (VOICEOVER): That kid--
-This time I'll use both legs
for a barrage of 4000 kicks!
GAARA (VOICEOVER): Where did
this come from all of a sudden.
-Unbelievable.
Taking on Gaara in
his current form.
Where did that
strength come from?
There's no way.
Not to him!
There's absolutely
no way I'm going
to lose to a guy like him!
-Huh?
-What the?
What is that?
-Huh?
TEMARI (VOICEOVER): So,
he's finally emerged.
The perfect possession.
-So that's it.
The monster inside of him.
-Well, what do you know.
I never thought you would
bring this out of me!
[scream]
-Naruto!
[groan] My body--
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I
used up all my chakra
on all those clones.
Sakura!
-No--
-Inu, tori, saru, hitsuji--
-This is the end for you.
Sand Bur--
-Summoning jutsu!
-Hm.
-It's amazing that he
could summon in that state.
-Sakura!
I swear I'll protect you.
-Naruto Uzumaki.
[chuckling] You really
are good at amusing me.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): Naruto,
how on earth can you do that?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Those hours of practice
are finally paying off.
This'll be a breeze.
-What the?
Not you again.
What is this?
Huh?
Well, will you look at that.
Shukaku the Sand Spirit.
-What do you say?
Will you fight alongside
today, Chief Toad?
-Take a hike.
-Wah?
-Why go out of my way to
mess with a guy like him?
What am I?
An idiot?
-Why?
Are you kidding me?
You already told me you
would make me your henchman,
didn't you?
It's only natural a boss would
want to help out his henchman,
isn't it?
Don't you have
any sense of duty?
-Yeah.
Sure.
I told you I'd make
you my henchman,
but we haven't even sealed the
deal over a cup of sake yet.
-Give me a freaking break!
I'm not even 21 years-old yet!
I can't have any alcohol!
-Ah, come on, pops.
Don't be like that.
Why don't you just settle
down and hear the kid out?
-Huh?
Pops?
-And just what do you think
you're doing here, Gamakichi?
-I had nothing else to do.
I just came to hang out.
-Huh?
Huh?
You're father and son?
-By the way, pops, that
big ugly lug over there
was picking on me before.
-Come again?
-Oh yeah.
And when he did, my friend
here came to my rescue.
He went head to head and toe
to toe with that monster.
I'm telling you, pops.
There's a heck of a lot more
to this kid than meets the eye.
-Is that right?
-OK, kid.
You're hereby accepted
as my henchman.
Sit tight.
I'll show you what
duty is all about.
I'll take him down, but not
before he's paid for what
he's done.
That worthless little flunky!
Hang on tight, small fry!
How do you like that?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Whoa.
Awesome.
[groaning]
CHIEF TOAD (VOICEOVER):
This guy's no joke.
I barely managed to make
that cut he's so heavy.
If I don't end this
quick, the landscape's
going to start
changing around here.
-Hey, Chief, hold on a second.
Don't go over in that direction.
Sakura's still there.
Try and lure him over
this way if you can, OK?
-Sakura?
-It's his little
girlfriend, pop.
Right, kid?
-I have to take him out.
Otherwise, Sakura's
as good as dead.
[chuckle]
-Interesting.
Interesting!
Not bad, Naruto Uzumaki!
[gasp]
TEMARI (VOICEOVER):
This isn't good.
Gaara-- he's really
going to do it.
I have to get out of here.
-What the?
What the heck is that?
-A spiritualist medium.
-To thank you for
entertaining me here
today, I'll show
you the true power
of the manifestation
of the sand.
-The circles under his eyes,
they're signs of insomnia.
Evidence that the medium's
been possessed by the Shukaku.
-Huh?
Insomnia?
-Those possessed by
Shukaku the Sand Spirit
are no longer able to sleep
soundly through the night.
The terror is too great.
If one does sleep, the Shukaku
will eat away at your psyche,
until the person that you
once were ceases to exist.
Since he normally
doesn't get much sleep,
the medium's personality tends
to become quite unstable.
-Great.
-But as long as the
spiritualist medium is awake,
the Shukaku's true
power is held in check.
The only danger is if the
medium finally falls asleep.
-Play possum jutsu.
-He's done it.
-I don't like this
at all, Chief Toad.
What's going to happen?
-If he's set the Play
Possum jutsu in motion,
then the Shukaku
will be unleashed!
[shout]
-I'm finally free!
Here I come, baby!
-So that's the Sand Spirit?
-Man.
That is one funky demon.
-Yeah!
Here we go!
I hope you're ready to die.
Let's do this.
-I'm going to jump.
-Huh?
-Wind Style!
Air Bullet!
-Water Style!
Liquid Bullet!
-Well, this is nice.
I didn't know it
was going to rain.
-What kind of a battle
is this turning into?
-Remember, Chief.
Not in that direction!
Will you shut up?
I know already!
-Air Bullet!
-Liquid Bullet!
-Too bad.
-This is bad, Chief.
There's one more coming.
[groan]
-Yeah!
I did it.
I killed him!
-Now that kind of hurt.
That was an awful lot of chakra
that you blasted me with.
I have to admit.
Hit me with a couple
more of those, even
I won't last much longer.
-Chief, what should we do?
-Well, for starters,
you could wake up
the spiritualist medium,
to release that jutsu.
-How am I supposed to do that?
CHIEF TOAD: Just fire
off a few rounds at him.
Liquid Bullets!
-You missed!
[grunt]
-Now's your chance!
-Hey, Chief, you're going to
have to keep a grip on him
if you want me get a shot in.
[groan]
-My body doesn't have any claws
or horns to dig into the enemy
with.
-Ah!
Then what the heck
are we supposed to do?
-Use the transformation
jutsu to change
into something that
has what we need!
Then again, I'm not particularly
good at transformation.
-Huh?
-Don't worry about it.
You shall act upon my
will and make a handsign.
-What?
-A combined transformation!
-Uh-- OK.
-Conjure up something
with fangs and claws!
-Let's see.
Uh--
-Here we go.
-Hey!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Wait a second!
Fangs and claws, fangs and
claws, fangs and claws.
-Transform!
NARUTO: Transformation jutsu!
-That's the--
[growling]
[theme music]
NARUTO: I don't really care
about your past or even my own.
All that matters are the
people I have to protect.
All right, you
pasty faced creep.
Let's finish this one on one.
I'll wrap this up with one hit.
I'm through messing around.
This blow will be the
last thing you ever feel.
You can count on it!
Next time-- beyond the
limit of darkness and light.
[theme music]