[theme song]
-This training by myself--
I just can't get into it.
Pervy sage.
Where the heck did you
run off to, anyway?
Weren't you supposed to
help me train or something?
Man, I hate this.
Darn it!
Huh?
What's she doing?
Wow.
You're really good.
Huh?
Wait a minute.
There's no rain clouds today.
Huh?
The Hokage's house!
-Come on!
What are you waiting for?
We need water now.
-Yes, ma'am.
Water style.
Marine battle formation jutsu!
-I don't want it on me.
The roof, you idiots!
-Sorry, Lady Tsunade.
-That's good.
Keep it up!
-Yes, ma'am.
It's as I thought.
My worst fears
have come to pass.
-There she is.
Hey!
Wait up, will ya?
-Hold her still.
-You had to go and make trouble.
-We should get her
back right away.
-Right.
-Hey, hold on!
What do you guys
think you're doing?
Get your hands off her!
Anbu.
-Naruto Uzumaki.
You need to leave
this area immediately.
-But what are you
doing with that girl?
What did she do?
-It doesn't concern you.
Now get going.
You're not to breathe a
word of what you saw here.
-Wait a minute!
You need to tell me
what you're doing.
-Don't try to interfere.
-They just vanished.
How weird.
I wonder what that
was all about.
-All these important
documents are soaked.
-We'll have to put
them in the sun to dry.
-I'll take them outside
and get started.
-Thank you.
-Good morning.
-Good morning, Kurenai-sensei.
-Is she in there?
-Yes.
-So you're serious about this?
You really want to resign
as leader of squad eight?
-Yes, ma'am.
-Think carefully about this.
Kiba, Shibo, Hinata--
you're the one
who recommended
they take the chunin
exam despite their
lack of experience.
Don't you care about
what happens to them?
-Despite my commitment
to them I am
responsible for the
current situation,
and therefore must
accept full blame.
-The incident was unfortunate,
but it wasn't your fault.
-You'd never know it
by looking at her,
but if the Anbu black ops were
involved she must be dangerous.
Or maybe something
really bad happened
and she's just mixed
up with it somehow.
[barking]
KIBA: What was that you said?
GIRL: Kiba, calm down.
-What's going on over there?
-Go ahead, Shino.
I dare you to say that again.
-All right.
I said it's pointless.
-I can't believe you would
say something like that.
-Cool it, you guys.
-Naruto.
-Come on.
Take it easy, will ya?
What the heck's going on?
-Kurenai left us swinging in the
wind, that's what's going on.
She just abandoned squad eight.
-Huh?
She wouldn't do
something like that.
-She just called us together
a few minutes ago and told us.
-I have fulfilled my obligation.
I'm sure they'll try to find
another chief jonin to take
my place as soon as possible.
-But you're our sensei.
You can't just
leave us like this.
-We need you.
-The decision's
already been made.
Our relationship
has always been that
of commander and
subordinates, that's all.
Someone will fill my role
and the squad will continue.
It's as simple as that.
-She never gave a reason.
Just walked away.
-She didn't say anything?
And you guys are just
gonna accept that?
-Not a chance!
We're not like
some little insects
that can be pushed around.
So I say we march into
the Hokage's office
and demand to know why Kurenai's
being removed from squad eight.
I say it's our only shot.
-And I say it's pointless.
She said herself that the
Hokage hadn't removed her.
She's the one who made
the decision to step down.
-Yeah?
I don't believe it for a second.
What about you, Hinata?
What do you think?
-Well, it's difficult.
Because even though I want
Kurenai to stay our jonin,
it's just--
-It's just what?
What's the problem?
-Maybe she has her own
reasons for wanting to do this
and we shouldn't get involved.
I think.
-So you're siding with
Shino on this, huh?
-No.
I'm not siding with anyone--
-Come on, guys.
Shut up and stop
fighting already.
You guys just relax
and let me handle this.
-He's not even on this team,
so why should we let him do it?
-Have you got a plan?
-Of course I've got a plan.
Just leave it to me.
She'll be back in charge
of squad eight in no time.
Why do I say I've
got a plan when
I have no idea what I'm doing?
Huh?
It's Kurenai-sensei.
I wonder what she's thinking.
Well, the only
way to find out is
to go up and ask
her face to face.
Uh, sensei?
-Naruto.
-Kiba, Hinata and Shino
told me what happened.
-And?
-And you shouldn't leave
them after everything
you've been through together.
They don't know what they're
gonna do without you.
-You ran up here
to tell me that?
-Well, yeah.
You're their sensei.
They look up to you.
-I don't know exactly
what they told you,
but I can no longer
be their sensei.
I don't deserve to
carry that title now.
-Why don't you?
-I have a message I
want you to deliver.
Tell them that I'm
never coming back.
-Sensei.
What can I do?
It's like she didn't hear
a single word I said.
I guess there's nothing
left to do but go talk
to Grandma Tsunade herself.
-Naruto.
-Oh.
Hey, Sakura.
-What are you doing here?
-I don't know if you heard, but
Kurenai's quitting squad eight.
So I came to see if I could
convince Grandma Tsunade to try
and talk her out of it.
-Don't think you'll
have any luck.
You can try.
-Oh, don't worry.
I know the place where she
keeps her booze hidden.
So all I gotta do is
threaten to tell Shizune
and she'll be putty in my hands.
-But you never know.
She might have had a good reason
for wanting to quit the squad.
-Like what?
Wait a minute.
You know something, don't you?
I can see it in your eyes.
You know something!
-What are you talking about?
I don't know anything.
-Come on, Sakura, tell me.
I know you know.
-No way.
What do you think,
I stand around
with my ear against
a door listening
to important conversations?
-You didn't!
You were eavesdropping
at the door?
-Shh!
Don't talk so loud, you idiot.
Someone'll hear!
-Yakumo?
-Yeah.
I'm pretty sure
that's who she said.
-It's my fault.
I'm the one who allowed Yakumo
to become the way she is.
-I'd say that the only
reason she's done so well
up to this point is because
of your influence on her.
Where is she now?
What's her status?
-A three-man squad consisting
of two medical ninja and one
Anbu black ops member is
keeping a 24-hour watch over her
in a mountain villa just
outside of Satomi Hill.
-The situation's been handled.
Isn't that enough?
-No.
I must be held accountable
for my actions.
-That explains what
was going on earlier.
Sounds just like
those four people.
And what did you say
her name was, again?
I forgot.
-Yakumo.
Right.
Thanks, Sakura.
-Remember, if someone asks,
you didn't hear any of this
from me, OK?
-Yeah, yeah.
Whatever!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): If
that girl I saw is Yakumo
then she might know
something about what's
going on with Kurenai-sensei.
-You're not quite there yet.
-Kurenai Yuhi.
I am requesting this because
you are the most skilled ninja
in the art of genjutsu.
I would like you to take this
young girl under your wing
and give her guidance.
-Who is she?
-Yakumo Kurama.
I'm sure you've heard
about the Kurama clan.
-Yes.
-At one time their
mastery of Genjutsu
was such that it made them a
driving force in the Hidden
Leaf Village, much the
same as the Uchiaha clan.
But in recent years
their influence
has weakened because
of a lack of talent.
As of late they've
been unable to produce
a single jonin-class shinobi.
-So, she comes from
the Kurama clan.
-Correct.
She is the only daughter
of the head of the family.
But unfortunately
she has health issues
which have kept her from
enrolling in the academy.
-You want me to
act as her master
and train her in
the art of genjutsu?
-No.
Yakumo has already begun
to master genjutsu,
and her potential is incredible.
Her family is aware
of this potential
and they've placed onto her
all of their dreams of a return
to power.
-What is it?
She couldn't deal with that?
-I don't want this to
go beyond this room.
-Of course.
-Yakumo's parents, Murakamo
and Uroko, have passed away.
-Easy.
Don't push yourself so hard.
-It's all right.
I'm fine.
Really.
I'm just out of breath.
No need to worry.
-Just relax for a minute.
Let's talk.
You don't have to become
a shinobi, you know.
-Huh?
-You're an intelligent
young woman,
and you need to know that
there are other ways to live.
-No!
I don't care.
I want to be a ninja.
I heard about a
student in the academy
named Rock Lee who can't
use ninjutsu or genjutsu.
So he's working to become a
ninja using only taijutsu.
I may not have much physical
strength, but if he can do it
I don't see why I
can't do it, too.
I could use the power
I have and become
and ninja like you, Kurenai.
-I wish I could help you.
But I'm not a teacher like Guy.
I'm sorry, but training
you is out of the question.
-Nice work!
We'll call it quits for today.
-Thank you, Guy-sensei.
-All right.
Now go clean yourself
up and get some rest.
-Yes, sir.
Right away!
[laughter]
-Lee keeps getting better
and better, doesn't he?
-Is it true?
You're leaving your students
and quitting squad eight?
-I have no choice.
Those assigned to
me have not been
reaching their full potential.
-Come on, that's not true.
Although I admit they're
no match for the members
of my squad, the growth that
they're getting in your group
is still quite impressive.
-If so, it's not because
of what I've done.
It's the results of
their own hard work.
-Listen to yourself.
In the end, what can any
of us really do for them?
You commented on how
Lee was progressing,
but the credit for all
that progress goes to him.
The only thing I've
done is believe in him,
tell him that
anything's possible.
We believe in our students,
no matter what the cost.
I trust him with my life, and
that gives him the strength
to make the right decisions.
Couldn't be easier.
It's a piece of cake.
-You make everything
sound so simple.
I wish I was like you.
I couldn't even do that much.
-Hey, Kurenai.
GUY (VOICEOVER): Just
believe in yourself.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Kurenai and
that girl from this morning.
I wonder how they're connected.
It's definitely
worth checking out.
-That's the villa
on Satomi Hill.
-Sounds like the eastern trap.
-An intruder.
-Someone tripped an alarm?
-Yes.
-Kurenai.
-Your security
detail is excellent.
I've come to visit Yakumo.
-Isn't it a little late.
-Yakumo's in her room,
but she's resting.
-I'll just need a few
minutes alone with her.
Unfortunately it can't
wait until morning.
-Ma'am.
-Don't be too long.
-I'll be out in 10 minutes.
-See that you do.
-All these paintings
are so morbid.
-You've got to help me, sensei.
[scream]
-What?
-Ah!
My heart, my heart!
What the-- I can't
believe I'm still alive.
-Hey, what are you doing here?
Using a transformation
jutsu, huh?
-Would somebody like to tell
me what just happened in there?
-Just shut up.
-If you know what's
good for you,
you'll forget about
what you just saw.
-Hey.
You're Yakumo, aren't you?
I came out here
because I want to ask
you some questions
about Kurenai-sensei.
Darn it.
[theme song]
NARUTO: Why am I sleeping
in a place like this?
SAKURA: That's what
happens when you
break into a
high-security safe house.
NARUTO: Oh, right.
SAKURA: You should be
grateful you're still alive.
The Anbu black ops
are on this case.
NARUTO: The Anbu?
That's right!
I don't have time for this.
SAKURA: Naruto,
where are you going?
NARUTO:Sorry, Sakura.
I have to find Kurenai.
I've got a feeling
she's the only who
knows what's going
on with Yakumo.
SAKURA: What?
Hey, Naruto, wait!
NARUTO: Next time--
Yakumo's Sealed Power!