[music playing]
[singing in Japanese]
[sighs]
IRUKA (VOICEOVER): So
his opponent is Neji.
These final rounds are
nothing like the preliminaries
as Naruto will find out.
If he hasn't already.
-Put on a good show
will you, Naruto?
You know, I've got
a tough job to do
and I'd like to be entertained
while I'm doing it.
ANNOUNCER: Ultimate
Defense: Zero Blind Spot!
[music playing]
[yelling]
-Hey!
[yells]
[grunts]
-This is ridiculous.
We're not even getting
close to this guy.
-You think I can be fooled
with a trick like that?
NEJI (VOICEOVER): Conjure
all the clones you want.
You can't hide from me.
[yells]
[gasps]
NEJI: You're the one keeping
out of range for fear of my
striking your chakra
points like this.
The more the others
attack, the more
you stand out for holding back.
You're the real one, aren't you?
-Naruto.
-The match is over.
-I told you it was pointless.
-No.
Don't give up, Naruto.
[laughs]
-Oh yeah?
And I told you it was a
mistake to count me out.
-But how?
-All right!
Way to go Naruto!
-Naruto.
NEJI: He held one of his
clones back to deceive me,
to lure me into a trap.
NARUTO: You thought I'd
be too much of a chicken
to attack you myself.
Well, think again!
[yells]
-But that--
-Uh?
What the heck was that?
-Did you really think you'd won?
-What happened?
-That punch of Naruto's
should have flattened him.
-But that was--
-Rotation.
TENTEN (VOICEOVER): That's one
of Neji's special defenses.
-We'll see about that!
TENTEN (VOICEOVER): Neji
can see almost 360 degrees
with his Byakugan.
It's pointless.
He can detect any attack
as soon as it's launched.
That's when his
real defense comes
into play, the Eight
Trigrams Palms Rotation.
The moment he senses an attack,
Neji discharges an intense,
focused burst of chakra from
the chakra's points in his body.
Then, by rotating
his body quickly,
he builds up enough energy
to not only block, but repel
his attacker.
Normally, chakra emitted
from chakra points
is difficult to control.
Even jonin can
usually only utilize chakra
from a single body part at a
time, like the hands or feet.
But Neji's mastery of
the Gentle Fist Taijutsu
is so great, that he can emit
chakra from several places,
warding off simultaneous attacks
from multiple directions.
It's an ultimate defense,
even more impenetrable
than Gaara's Shield of Sand.
Nothing can get through it.
-But I thought
only father could.
-It's a secret ninja art.
For generations, reserved
only for the main household
of the Hyuga clan.
But Neji has somehow
discovered it on his own,
incredible as it may seem.
He's come far.
TENTEN (VOICEOVER): No
one should be surprised.
You haven't even begun
to see his full powers.
[grunting]
NEJI: This is the end for you.
You're in range and you can't
escape my Eight Trigrams.
Gentle Fist art.
Eight Trigrams 64 Palms.
-Let's dance.
It can't be.
-Eight Trigrams.
Four palm.
Eight palm.
16 palm.
32 palm.
64 palm.
[screams]
-Have we been surpassed
by this branch family?
-Looks like it's over.
-To think that Hyuga's Kekkei
Genkai would find its purest
form in this child of a
lesser branch of the clan,
a child banished from
the line of succession.
Truly, my brother,
you've been denied
what is rightfully yours.
-I have now struck all
64 of your chakra points.
You're lucky to
still be breathing.
-Act.
Come on!
-Well, must be frustrating to
realize how utterly hopeless
it all was, this
little dream of yours.
You thought you could succeed
through hard work alone.
That's only an illusion.
[coughs]
-Hey, Hinata, what's
wrong, you OK?
-What a fool!
I almost thought he could win.
-Naruto.
-Bushy brow.
Hinata.
No way.
-Huh?
-Come on!
[breathing hard]
-Impossible.
How could he?
-I told you, I just don't
know when to give up.
-It can't be!
[coughs]
-Hey!
Hey!
You're coughing up blood.
-What is it?
-Oh wow.
You must still be
injured from your match.
Hinata, you going
to be all right?
You need some
water or something?
-Let me have a look at her.
-Who are you?
-It's all right.
You can trust me.
-Stop this madness.
You'll only get
more of the same.
I have nothing against
you personally.
-That's touching.
You're going to make me cry.
Anyway, I've got
plenty against you.
-I don't know what you mean.
-You don't?
And here I thought you
were Mr. Know-It-All.
You don't remember what
you did to Hinata, huh?
The way you worked on
her with your mind games,
tearing her down when she
worked so hard to get here.
-Never mind that.
It doesn't concern you.
NARUTO: You mocked
Hinata, calling
her a failure, all that stuff
about the great Hyuga clan,
main household, branch families.
What a bunch of crap!
It doesn't give you the right
to decide who is a failure.
That's what I've
got against you.
-Hey!
What are you?
-Don't worry.
I'm a doctor.
-Very well.
As you are so interested
in it, I'll tell you about.
The Hyuga clan's
heritage of hatred.
For generations, the main
household of our clan
has practiced a secret ninjutsu
known as the cursed mark jutsu.
-Cursed mark jutsu?
-The curse mark is the symbol
of a bird locked in its cage.
It's the mark of those who are
bound to a destiny they cannot
escape.
-Uh.
Is, is that?
That's the curse mark?
-I was four years old when
the leaders of my clan
branded this symbol
on my forehead
with their cursed mark jutsu.
On that same day,
a great celebration
took place in the
Hidden Leaf Village.
After many years of
war, a peace agreement
had at last been reached
with the Land of Lightning
and they had sent the Head
Cloud Ninja to sign the treaty
and join in the celebration.
Everyone was there to
welcome our old enemies.
Every genin and jonin
in the Leaf Village.
Only one clan was
absent, the Hyuga clan.
Because this was
the day on which
the heir to the main
household was to turn three.
It was Lady Hinata's
third birthday.
Her father, Lord Hiashi
Hyuga, is sitting up there.
He and my father, Hizashi,
are twin brothers.
And yet, he entered
into the world first,
so he is head of the
family, the firstborn.
While my father,
his twin brother,
is banished to a lesser
branch of the family.
-So Lady Hinata is
three years old.
Congratulations.
-Thank you.
-She looks nice,
Father, don't you think?
What is it, Father?
What's wrong?
-Oh, it's nothing, my son.
-Hizashi, it's time I
took Neji under my wing.
-Yes.
NEJI: It was then, on the day
the heir to the main household
turned three that the
curse mark was put on me
and I was made a bird in
a cage by my own uncle.
-You and this clan of yours,
what's the point of it all?
Why have a main family
and a branch family?
And this weird curse mark?
What's it mean anyway?
-I can assure you of one thing.
It's not simply for decoration.
-Your kick is still weak.
-Yes.
[screaming]
-Listen, Neji, is your
destiny clear to you?
You live only to
protect Lady Hinata
and to preserve the power
of our clan's main house.
-I understand, Father.
[music playing]
-It's wet.
Hiya!
[screaming]
-Father!
Father, what is it?
-Take your father home.
I'll forgive the fool this
time, but only this time.
See that you never
forget your destiny.
NEJI: You see, this is more
than a mark that we wear.
It is also the
instrument by which
they keep us in our place.
We live with the fear that
they will use this curse mark
to turn our brains to
jelly any time they wish.
Fear, that is what
we live with it.
And we live with it every day.
Only in death are we free of it.
This is how the power of the
Byakugan is kept sealed away.
Only the Hyuga
possess the secret
of this unique form
of Kekkei Genkai.
And of course, there are many
who would steal it from us.
That is why we exist.
It is the purpose of the branch
family to defend that secret
and to serve the keepers of the
secret-- the main household--
obediently and without
question for eternity.
That is our destiny or was
until that dreadful night they
went too far.
When they murdered my father!
One night, someone
entered the main household
and abducted Lady Hinata.
[door opens]
Lord Hiashi quickly
caught and killed the man.
And who was this
intruder, stealing
through the shadows in the
dead of night, wearing a mask
over his face?
It was none other than
the Head Cloud Ninja
of the Land of Lightning,
the man who had just
signed an alliance with us.
It was obvious to
everyone that he
was after the secret
of the Byakugan.
But the Land of
Lightning professed shock
at this willful
murder of their ninja.
They claimed that the Hidden
Leaf Village was in violation
of the treaty and they
demanded recompense.
Things got worse
and worse until it
looked like war
would break out anew.
The Leaf Village wanted above
all things to avoid a war,
so at last they made a deal.
NARUTO: A deal?
NEJI: A life for a life.
The Land of Lightning
demanded the death
of the person who had
slain their ninja.
If there was to be peace,
Lord Hiashi must die.
The Leaf Village
accepted their terms.
HANABI: But Father, then how?
-And so to avert a war a man
was killed, but not Hiashi.
My father, his twin brother,
was killed in his place
in order to protect
the main household.
Only in death was my
father finally free
of this evil curse mark.
They were so much
alike-- twin brothers--
but their destinies
had been determined
long ago when one was born a
few seconds after the other.
And this match is the same.
Your destiny was
decided the moment
I was chosen as your opponent.
[music playing]
-This guy and his magic
fingers or Gentle Fist,
or whatever he calls it.
He knows just which points
to hit to shut off my chakra
and without it I'm helpless.
Feels like that time I
used up all my chakra
when I was training
with the Pervy Sage.
Wait a second, that's it!
Yeah.
I could also squeeze out
a little more chakra.
Next time, a
Failure's True Power.
[music playing]