[theme music]
-OK, who are you?
Out with it.
Before we go another
round, I should warn you,
you might want to
think about it.
I'm in a really bad mood.
[chuckle]
-Stop your prattling,
you little weakling.
Come on, kid.
I'm waiting.
I want to play Do-Re-Mi on those
ribs of yours 'til they crack.
Get ready.
-Hmph.
SAKON (VOICEOVER):
He's got my legs.
-Hm, let's have a
little music, shall we?
Do!
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): What the--
-Re!
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): Where
is he attacking from?
-Hm your bones ring
with a nice low tone.
But when we switch to a
sharper reverberation-- yeah.
I think we'll go with a
mi-fa-so combination now.
Huh?
What?
-I've had enough!
Lions Barrage!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): An
Invitation From the Sound.
SERVER: Here you are.
NARUTO: Down the hatch.
Come on, Sakura, what
are you waiting for?
Dive on in.
The barbecue pork ramen
here is out of this world.
And listen, don't
even worry about it.
All this is on me.
You got that, old man?
-So you're treating
your girl, huh?
Looks like you're starting
to grow up a little, Naruto.
-Huh?
G-- g-- g--?
What are you talking about?
We just came here to
hash some stuff out, OK?
I-- I mean, it's not like
she's my girlfriend or anything
so-- what is it, Sakura?
-I'm sorry, Naruto.
I was spacing out a little.
This looks delicious.
Now then, let's eat.
-Yeah, and you can tell
me all about Sasuke
while we're chowing
down here, OK?
Oh--
[grumble]
NARUTO: Hey, are you, uh--
-So Naruto, I-- I promised
Sasuke not to tell you this,
but-- this is all that
Orochimaru's fault.
-No.
what are you doing?
[screaming]
[gasp]
SAKURA: Kakashi-sensei said
everything would be fine,
and I wish I could believe him,
but when he was fighting with
Gaara--
[groaning]
-And then again today, he had
that same look in his eye.
I don't know what to do.
-Orochimaru, huh?
Yeah, I ran into him
not too long ago.
-You did?
But where?
-When I was off searching
for Grandma Tsunade.
-I'm happy to accommodate you.
-What the devil?
NARUTO: He went up against
Pervy Sage and Grandma Tsunade
at the same time.
He was incredibly powerful.
The guy is bad news.
-This is not good.
-Come on, everything
will be fine.
Sasuke would never
let a guy like that
sink his claws into him.
I mean, he's already
a total powerhouse.
It's not like he needs that
kind of help, you know?
Don't worry.
I guarantee it.
SAKURA: OK.
-What does Lord Orochimaru
even want with this kid?
I don't see what
the big deal is.
Kimimaro would have
been much better.
Ah well, spend all of
your life in a dump
of a village like
this place, and you'll
turn out mediocre at best,
never realizing your strength.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): Why?
All my barrages were solid.
This guy it's like I
never even hit him.
-If you just keep playing ninja
with all of your friends here,
you'll continue to
rot on the vine.
-You're acting like a fool.
You should come with us.
Lord Orochimaru
offers you power.
[grunt]
TAYUYA: He there'd be no point
in our taking you by force.
You have to decide.
SAKON: This is turning
out to be a real pain.
Let's go.
What's it going to be?
Are you in or out?
What do you say, kid?
This runt makes
me wait any longer
and I'm going to
ring his little neck.
SASUKE: Come and try it.
-Ah, the curse mark.
Kind of hurts, doesn't it?
-Come on now.
You didn't think you were Lord
Orochimaru's only pet, did you?
One shouldn't use the curse
mark so recklessly, kid.
Although it doesn't
really look like you've
got much of a handle
on it, do you?
If you unleash it for
too long, the curse
will start to eat
away at your body.
You're in the
early stages of it,
so it shouldn't sink its
teeth into you too quickly.
But once it spreads
through your body,
your former self will be
gone, never again to return.
-In exchange for
the curse's power,
you will be tethered
to Lord Orochimaru.
All semblance of freedom
will be lost to you.
To gain one thing, another
must be left behind.
What is your purpose
is this life?
To stay here in the
backwater village,
hiding with your little friends?
Surely you haven't
forgotten Itachi Uchiha?
-You mustn't lose
sight of your purpose.
Life in this village is little
more than bondage for you.
Sever your ties to
this pathetic place.
If you can do that, there
will be no limit to the power
you can wield.
Remember your purpose.
SERVER: Thanks again.
-Uh, hey, Sakura,
let me walk you home.
-Oh no, that's all right.
-Huh?
What do you mean?
These streets can be
dangerous at night.
-No, they're pretty well-lit.
I'll be OK.
-Uh, Sakura?
-Thank you, Naruto, really.
But I'd kind of like to
be on my own tonight.
-Yeah, sure.
-I'll be fine, OK?
-It's the middle of the night.
What are you hanging
around here for?
-This is the only road
out of the village.
-You should go to bed.
-Why, Sasuke?
Why won't you ever
tell me anything?
Why is it always
silence with you?
You've never shared a
single thing with me.
-Why should I have
to tell you anything?
Just keep your nose
out of my business.
It's none of your concern.
-I know you hate me.
Even in the beginning,
you could never stand me.
Remember?
Back when we made
Genin and we were
assigned to our
three-man squads?
We were alone together for
the first time right here
on this very spot.
You got so mad at me that day.
Think about it.
He just does whatever
comes into his head.
But if you don't have parents
to tell you, how would you know?
He's selfish and bratty.
He's all alone.
-Alone.
Isolated.
-Huh?
-It's not about your
parents scolding you.
You have no idea what
it means to be alone.
-Wh-- why are you saying that?
-Because you're annoying.
-I don't remember that.
-Yeah, sure.
I mean, it so long ago, right?
But still, that's the
day when it all began.
It was the start of you, and me,
and Naruto, and Kakashi-sensei.
The four of us started
going on missions.
It was rough back then.
Every day was such a challenge.
But more than anything,
it was so much fun.
I know about your plan, Sasuke.
I do.
But seeking revenge, that
won't bring anyone happiness,
nobody at all, not
you, and not me.
-I knew it.
I'm not the same as you.
I'm travelling a path the
rest of you can't follow.
I know that the four of
us have worked together.
And for awhile, I thought I
could take that road instead.
But in the end, I've
decided on revenge.
That's always been
my reason for living.
I'll never be like
you and Naruto.
-Don't do this, Sasuke.
You don't have to be alone.
You told me that day how
painful a thing solitude can be.
I understand that pain now.
I have a family and friends,
but if you were gone, Sasuke,
it would be the same thing
for me as being all alone.
-This is a new beginning.
Each of us has a new
path lying before us.
-Sasuke, I'm so in love with
you, I can't even stand it.
If you would only be
with me, I promise
I'd never let you regret it.
Every day will be a joy.
I can give you have happiness.
I'll do anything
for you, Sasuke.
So please, I'm begging
you, don't walk away.
I'll even help get your revenge.
I'll do whatever it takes
to make it happen, I swear.
So stay here with me.
And if you can't, then
take me with you, Sasuke.
-You haven't changed.
You're still annoying.
-Don't leave me!
If you go, I'll scream and--
-Sakura, thank you
for everything.
[whack]
-Sasuke.
SAKON: We've been
waiting for you, Sasuke.
-So what's with the
change in attitude?
-It had already been
decided that the moment you
abandoned the village, you
would become our new leader.
Please forgive the rudeness
we displayed earlier.
-Like I care.
Let's go.
This is the beginning.
[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): What?
Sasuke, that jerk,
what's he thinking?
Man, he's got issues.
What messed his head up
so bad that he'd do this?
I'm not about to let him
do whatever he pleases.
If it comes down to
it, I'll chase him down
to the ends of the earth.
I'll drag him back,
even if I have
to do it by the
scruff of his neck.
Next time-- Formation!
The Sasuke Retrieval Squad!