[theme music]
NARUTO: "Hit It or Quit It-- The
Final Rounds Get Complicated."
-[panting]
-[gasping]
-[sigh]
-You did it!
[applause]
-(VOICEOVER) Wow, that Naruto
kid really knows how to fight.
-[panting] Huh?
[applause and cheering]
-Huh?
-Yeah!
[laughter] Yeah!
-(VOICEOVER) Incredible.
Even after that fight, he
has the energy to run around.
That kid has amazing stamina.
-Yeah!
Yeah, yeah!
-(VOICEOVER) Naruto just
keeps getting stronger.
-Wow, he did it.
He won the fight.
-Mhm.
He's on the track to success.
And he's kind of cute, too.
--[sigh] I hate to admit
it, Naruto, but I envy you.
But watching your
battle has made
me realize that I have
to work really hard, too,
or I'll never get anywhere.
[sigh]
-Ugh.
Naruto defeated Neji?
Oh man, I can't believe it.
And I thought Naruto
was the same as me,
one of the dorky, uncool guys.
-Dorky and uncool?
-Now everyone's
saying that he's going
to make something
big of himself.
Just great.
I doubt I could beat him now.
This is really bad.
I've never felt so depressed.
What a drag.
-He was able to draw upon the
Fox's chakra all by himself.
-Yeah.
Even the people from
the Hidden Leaf Village
seem totally surprised.
-(VOICEOVER) Remarkable.
When did he learn to control the
chakra of the Nine-Tailed Fox
to such a degree?
-Yeah!
Yeah!
-Even a caged bird
was smart enough,
and will be able
to figure out how
to open the door to
its cage with its beak.
The dream of flying and breaking
free is too great to resist.
But this time, you lost.
-Father.
DOCTOR 1: Good news.
No damage to your
internal organs.
DOCTOR 2: It seems like you
used up all your chakra.
-I've got news for you, Neji.
You're not the only
special one around here.
NEJI: Why fight
a hopeless battle
trying to defy your destiny?
-Because you called me a loser.
I'll show you I'm not.
-They were born
destined to be hokage.
-You can think that
way if you want.
-Huh?
Lord Hyuga.
-I'm sorry, but could you
please step out for a moment?
-Well, we're not supposed to.
-It won't take long.
DOCTOR 1: Yes, of course.
--[groans] What do
you want with me?
-You know that day.
Well, I've come to tell you
the truth about what happened.
-What are you saying?
-[panting]
[sobbing]
-That day, I was
fully prepared to die.
-What?
What are you talking about?
That day, my father was
forced to pose as you,
and was murdered for
the sake of the family.
-The truth you seek.
The truth is here
in this scroll.
-Of course.
It's only excuses made for the
convenience of the head family.
-The person you are now
should be able to understand.
-That writing.
MAN (VOICEOVER):
Neji, I'm afraid
that I only have a
little time left.
And I want to use that limited
time to tell you something.
-Tell me something?
MAN (VOICEOVER):
The Head Cloud Ninja
from the Land of Lightning
tried to abduct Hinata.
But Lord Hiashi killed
the would-be kidnapper.
However, the Land of
Lightning refused even
to acknowledge the
abduction attempt,
and instead only made trouble
about the Head Ninja's death.
The demands for retribution
were completely unreasonable.
-It cannot be helped.
With my one life, the
entire village can be saved.
-Just hold on, Hiashi.
Please don't be so hasty.
-Hm.
-The Hyuga family's
kekkei genkai
is one of the most important
strengths of our village.
It's the sworn duty
of the Head Family
to protect it forever,
no matter what.
-Yes, but I must put aside
that duty if keeping it
means involving our
village in a desperate war.
-I understand that,
but that is why--
-Huh?
-Isn't that why we have
branch families after all?
We'll take Hizashi's corpse and
hand it over in place of yours.
Do not worry.
Hizashi fully
understands his duty.
-Yes, but what they're
really after is
the secret that lies
within the Byakugan.
And when Hizashi
passes away, that power
will be sealed forever.
I doubt that the Land of
Lightning will consent to that.
-Hm.
Yes, you may be
right about that.
But there may be
a way around it.
The Land of Lightning's
demand simply
says hand over Hiyashi
Hyuga's dead body.
If we pretend that we're
agreeing to their terms
and hand over Hizashi-- who
looks identical to you-- then
they can't pursue it
any further than that.
-But-- it's not--
-Look, Hiyashi.
Don't concern
yourself with this.
Any of your predecessors
would have done the same
to protect the Hyuga Clan.
Even siblings must
have the courage
to sacrifice each
other when needed.
This must be.
This is the fate of the
Head Family, its destiny.
Those born to the Hyuga Clan
bear the burden of ruling.
-What's wrong, Lord Hiyashi?
You're usually so
confident and determined.
-This is far too important
for me to act recklessly.
It's not that easy.
Ah!
Ugh.
-[gasp]
-Ugh.
-[struggling] Hizashi, no.
You mustn't.
-Please, Hiyashi.
Let me do this.
-But-- but you have Neji.
Why do you choose death?
To save the Head Family?
It makes no sense.
-You must understand.
For a long time, I have
resented the Head Family.
To tell the truth,
even now, I'm bitter.
I'm not doing this
because you're
a part of the Head Family.
I want to die protecting
you because you're
my brother, Hiyashi.
It's the first time
I've felt free enough
to choose my own path, the first
time I've truly had freedom.
I've always only shown
Neji my ugly side.
But this time, it's different.
This time, I've finally
come here to act in the way
that I believe is best.
I ask you, please give
Neji a message for me.
Tell him that I wasn't killed
to protect the Head Family,
but rather to protect my
siblings, family, and village.
And by my own free will, I chose
death, and I chose my freedom.
-You-- you think that choosing
death is the same as choosing
to be free?
-Don't you see, big brother?
I have become free.
I have defied the fate
of the Hyuga family.
I simply wanted to
choose my own destiny.
Goodbye.
LETTER: Forge your
own destiny, Neji.
Your fate is something you
create with your own hands.
-Father.
-This is the truth.
I'm sorry.
-Please, Lord Hiyashi.
Don't bow to me.
-(VOICEOVER) Father, I can't be
sure if a person's destiny is
like a cloud, floating on
a fixed current that it
can't escape, or if people are
able to ride on whatever breeze
they choose.
I don't know.
I don't completely
understand it yet.
And maybe the
destination is the same,
no matter what you choose.
Just when you choose
one course, along
comes someone who's picked a
different path-- one that's
devoted to living
life to its fullest.
There's real strength to be
found in that love of life.
I finally understand that
because of this latest battle.
Now, father, I have
only one goal--
to become stronger so I
won't lose to anyone again.
That's what I feel
my goal is now.
Father, I wish you could
see these birds flying.
They're finding
their freedom too.
[crowd chattering]
-Heh heh heh.
This crowd is
certainly energized.
-That's because it
was a terrific fight.
-Of course.
It's that too.
But--
-Hm?
- --it's also anticipation.
It's likely that the Shinobe
leaders, Feudal Lords,
and other spectators are looking
forward to this next match
more than anything.
By the way, the Uchiha wasn't
at the opening ceremony.
He has arrived
already, hasn't he?
-Uh-- well--
-There's been no
news of Sasuke yet.
And there's the issue
over Orochimaru.
Please, before everyone
starts to make trouble,
disqualify Sasuke.
-Hey, what's going on here?
Hurry up and start
the next match.
-Come on, let's go!
-Some time before night falls.
-Gah.
-I wonder what's going on.
The next match-- Sasuke
should be here by now.
-(VOICEOVER) Sasuke.
-That Sasuke, what in the
world does he think he's doing?
Forfeiting?
A wise man never courts danger,
leading to a wise decision.
-Huh, what are
you talking about?
He's definitely going
to be here, believe it.
-(VOICEOVER) But seriously,
what is he doing?
If he doesn't get here soon,
he's going to be disqualified.
-I have no choice.
Sasuke is disqualified.
-Right.
-Sasuke Uchiha is disqualified?
-Yes, I'm afraid that
this has to be done.
-Ugh, what are we
going to do now?
If he doesn't show up,
our strategy is ruined.
-This is really bad.
-[grunt] Could he have--
-Where are you going, Gara?
-To remind myself
that I'm alive.
-(VOICEOVER) Gara, I
wonder if he did it.
Could he really
have killed Sasuke?
-Sasuke, one more time.
Hm?
-What's wrong?
-It's obvious you're hiding
there, thirsting for blood.
Save me the trouble
and come out.
So, it's you.
-Lord Hokage, I
ask you to consider
waiting a little longer before
disqualifying Sasuke Uchiha.
-I understand your point.
But no matter how excellent a
Shinobi he may be, he's late,
and we can't make
special allowances.
If there's no clear reason
to make all the Shinobi
leaders and Feudal
Lords wait, then there's
no reason not to
disqualify him immediately.
-I see.
Then it's good I do
have a clear reason.
-Huh?
-Including myself, most of
the Shinobi leaders and Feudal
Lords here came
simply because they
want to see the next match.
-Yes, but still--
-He's the only remaining
member of the Uchiha Clan.
And I know that the
Land of Wind especially
is hoping for a bout
between Sasuke and our Gara.
-Lord Hokage.
-(VOICEOVER) There's no
guarantee that Sasuke will
come, but--
Very well, then.
We will make an exception.
We shall postpone
this match and wait.
-Hm.
-But Lord Hokage,
I must protest.
-Inform the proctor right away.
-Yes sir.
-However, it's most
unusual for you
to insist so strongly,
Lord Kazekage.
-To display the full strength
of our village's ninja,
no opponent but
an Uchiha will do.
This is a big chance for Sasuke,
yes, but a big opportunity
for us as well.
[crowd jeering]
-I understand.
Listen everyone.
One of the competitors
from the next battle
has not arrived
yet, so we're going
to postpone this match
briefly and simply jump ahead
to the battle that would
have followed this one.
-Just what in the world
could Sasuke be doing anyway?
-So cool.
That means Sasuke
is still in this.
-[sigh] That's good.
-Hey, that means my battle's
one match closer now.
What a drag!
-Then on to the next battle.
So Shino and Kankuro come down.
-Ugh.
(VOICEOVER) My match
doesn't matter at all now.
Besides, I don't want to reveal
the mechanism of my trained
crow puppet to the enemy before
our plan comes to fruition.
Proctor!
I withdraw.
-Huh?
-(VOICEOVER) What?
-I withdraw, so please
advance to the next match.
[crowd jeering]
-Ugh.
Due to Kankuro's withdrawal,
Shino Aburame wins by default.
[crowd jeering]
-And you are?
-It's my turn, right?
-Well, you're sure an
eager one, aren't you?
Fine, let's start
the next match then.
Hey, you up there.
Come down.
-Oh, come on.
What are you doing moving
these matches up like this.
Why does it have to be my stupid
match that get's pushed up.
Oh man, this is such a drag.
Shikamaru Nara, come on.
-(VOICEOVER) Great.
If it's going to be like
this, maybe I'll withdraw too.
-All right!
Go on, Shikamaru.
You can do it!
-[screaming] Yeah.
Thanks a lot, Naruto.
[theme music]
INO: Go Shikamaru!
SAKURA: Doesn't it
seem strange that he's
fighting in the final round?
-I think it's great!
He's fired up and ready to win.
Go teammate!
SAKURA: But doesn't he look
weird staring at the sky
like that?
INO: I think he looks totally
awesome and ambitious.
All right, Shikamaru!
Stay strong and fight hard!
Next time, "Zero Motivation:
The Guy With Cloud Envy."
SAKURA: Ino, your cheering
is getting kind of scary.
[theme music]