[music playing]
-Waves of pain, they're
coming sooner and sooner.
-Sasuke, listen to me.
You have got to quit.
-Huh?
-You've been like
this ever since you
tangled with Orochimaru.
And it's getting worse.
-Didn't waste any
time, did they?
-I couldn't ask
for anything more.
-You have been chosen for
the first match, Yoroi Akado
and Sasuke Uchiha.
Are there any objections?
-None here.
-No.
-The pain won't go away.
-That curse mark
giving you trouble?
-Don't use your Sharingan.
-So you know about it?
-If that mark on your
neck gets out of control,
your life could be in danger.
-I'm aware of that.
-Just to let you know,
if it gets to that point,
I'll have to step in
and stop the fight.
Good luck.
-Stop the fight?
This thing, it seems to be
responding to my Chakra.
I've got to fight him
without using my Sharingan.
And even my own
Jutsu is off limits.
Maybe I can make him
laugh himself to death.
-The thing is, Sasuke,
Yoroi's unique skills
are going to be
disastrous for you.
-Then if you're ready,
let the match begin.
-[laughs]
-What the-- my Chakra,
what are you doing?
-[laughs]
You're just noticing it now?
-Bushy Brows' jealousy.
-Lions barrage unleashed.
-My Chakra!
You're stealing it from me.
-[laughs]
You finally caught on, huh?
-That's right, Sasuke.
He's draining your Chakra.
Yoroi has an extraordinary
ninja art at his fingertips.
He can absorb an opponent's
spiritual and physical energy
with the palm of his hand.
And once the last
drop of your Chakra
has been drained
from you, Sasuke,
you'll have no other
choice but to rely
on the power of the curse mark.
Go on.
Release that delicious
forbidden power.
Set it free.
It's the only chance you
have of saving yourself.
-Get off!
-So, you've still got
some strength left, huh?
Impressive-- for a guinea pig.
-Woah.
That was close.
-Don't worry, little man.
I'll make it short and sweet.
What's the matter?
Is that really the
best you can do?
-Don't have the speed
to keep away from him,
and don't have a chance
at a close quarters fight.
I need to think
of something fast.
-The great Sasuke Uchiha.
Is that all he's got?
-Come on, Sasuke!
Hey, Sasuke!
Come on, man!
What was that?
And you call yourself an Uchiha?
You're going to let this
goon walk all over you!
Come on, stop messing
around and get it in gear!
-They're all-- wait!
That's it!
-Huh?
-I'll teach you to
turn your back on me.
Big mistake, and your last!
-Is this as far as it goes?
-Huh?
Where did he go?
-That's my move.
-What the?
-Huh?
-OK, I admit it.
I kind of borrowed that move.
But from here on in,
it's all original.
-A Dancing Leaf Shadow!
Now take this!
-No, not again!
He keeps getting
stronger and stronger.
-Don't do it!
Stop, please!
-Come on!
What was that?
And you call yourself an Uchiha!
-Shut up, loser.
Don't write me off yet.
-Is this it?
-No!
I won't let this
thing take over.
No way!
-The curse mark receded!
-Here we go.
-You're no match for me.
-Who's no match for who?
-Come back here!
-I'm not done yet!
Lions Barrage!
-Well, this one's had it.
I'm declaring this match over.
As the winner of this
preliminary round,
Sasuke Uchiha advances
to the finals.
-Way to go!
-Hm, not bad.
Funny.
Before the Lions
Barrage, your technique
was very reminiscent
of Guy's Taijutsu.
You must have used
your Sharingan
to copy it when you fought
with Rock Lee that time.
-You OK?
[laughs]
Hey, Sasuke!
You won, but in
such an uncool way.
You came out looking like
you're the one who got beat up!
-Idiot.
Give me a break, you
little-- oh, well.
-Sasuke, thank goodness.
-I can't wait
until it's my turn.
-Rock Lee.
If I hadn't seen your
moves up close when
we went head to head, this one
would have turned out badly.
Still, I don't think
it's a technique
I want to use very often.
-Amazing.
He only saw me do
it once, and he
was able to copy it perfectly.
-Sharingan!
-So that is your
special ability?
You really are
something, Sasuke.
You just keep getting
stronger all the time.
You make me almost
a little nervous.
-Impressive.
But you can't expect to master
high speed Taijutsu and Lotus
movements just like that.
It takes more than Sharingan.
It takes blood, and
sweat, and brutal training
that whittles at your flesh.
Even so, that last
move of yours-- he
reminds me of you, Kakashi,
when you were young.
-Last year, Neji Hyuga
was the rookie to beat.
This year, it's Sasuke Uchiha.
I wonder when we'll find
out which one's stronger?
[laughs]
-The kid is something else.
To have already developed his
Sharingan to such a level.
And to think, we haven't even
seen his full Uchiha ability
yet.
-I still can't believe it.
The way the curse
mark receded, as
if he's gained control over it.
-Oh, no.
Not again!
-Well, well.
So that's how it's done.
-[laughs]
I knew all the time he'd be OK.
-This could be the end
of the line for us.
Man, I'm hungry.
-Wow.
He was amazing.
-He wasn't anything
that special.
-Magnificent!
-Sasuke Uchiha, maybe
you should come along
to the infirmary, too, and
let us treat your injuries.
-I think you're out of
your league with this one.
-Huh?
-I'll look after him.
-OK, up you go.
You're coming with me.
We've got to seal
that curse mark.
Before the
preliminaries are over?
I want to see who gets
to go on to the finals.
-Forget it.
And don't even think of arguing.
If we leave it any
longer, who knows.
It may be too late.
I've already cut you
enough slack as it is.
Come on.
Let's go.
-Sasuke!
-Huh?
Hey, Sakura.
Maybe I'm just
crazy, but did you
see any weird marks on
Sasuke's neck during the fight?
-You've got to
promise me you won't
tell Naruto about
the curse mark.
-Why?
-There's nothing
he can do about it.
And we're a team.
It doesn't do us any good
if he's worried about me.
-What mark?
I didn't see it.
-Oh, OK.
-OK then.
Let's move right on
to the second match.
-Which sucker is that?
-Step forward, please.
Very good.
Now, if you've both
ready, then we'll begin.
-That's that sound
village Shinobi,
the one who had his
arms broken by Sasuke.
-You seem to be very proud
of these arms of yours,
very attached to them.
-What?
What are you doing?
[screams]
-How's he going to
fight with those arms?
-Do you think Shina
will be all right?
-He's OK.
Don't you worry about him.
-Huh?
-He's the last person here
I'd ever want to take on.
-Candidates ready?
Begin.
-Well, Zaku.
How you pull this one off
will be a sight to see.
-If you fight me, you
won't be able to recover.
Forfeit and withdraw.
-But what do you know,
I've got a little movement
in one of them.
One good arm is more
than enough to beat you!
-You couldn't beat me
using both your arms.
-Yeah, well I've
got news for you!
Try this!
[inaudible]
-OK.
It'll be over quickly.
You ready?
Curse sealing.
There.
Now the next time that
curse mark starts acting up,
the seal should
keep it in check.
But remember, this curse
sealing Jutsu is only
as strong as you are.
It derives its power from
the strength of your will.
If that will ever
weakens, if you ever
begin to doubt
yourself, the curse
will be unleashed
in all its fury.
Amazing.
Too tired to even argue.
-My, how you're grown.
To think you've
become strong enough
to perform the
curse sealing Jutsu.
-You.
-Long time no see, Kakashi.
-Orochimaru.
[music playing]
-Well, this is a nasty surprise.
What snake pit in hell did
you crawl out from, and why?
What do you want with Sasuke?
I don't care if you are one
of the legendary Sannin.
I won't back down, Orochimaru.
If you want him, you'll
have to kill me first!
Next time, Kakashi and
Orochimaru face to face.
I'm going to stop
you here and now!