[music playing]
[theme music]
HAKU: Is this the first
time you have seen a friend
die in battle?
It is the way of the Shinobi.
NARUTO: You'll pay for this.
[angrily] I'm going to kill you.
[groaning]
[grunting]
White Past-- Hidden Ambition.
HAKU: The bloodlust in his eyes.
This is no longer a child.
[yelling]
[gasping]
HAKU: His chakra grows
stronger every second.
I must strike now.
[groaning]
Now.
Impossible.
Those eyes.
[groaning]
NARUTO: Could it be?
The seal has been broken.
No.
It's been loosened,
and a glimmer
of the nine-tailed fox's
chakra has slipped through.
But the seal still holds.
Good.
Then maybe we still
have a chance.
Just maybe.
Zabuza, I don't mean
to spoil your fun.
I know how you like to
stretch these things out.
But how about we put
an end to this now?
Come on, what do you say?
We're both busy people.
ZABUZA: Hm.
Tempting.
I'm curious to
see how you intend
to back up such brave words.
Show me, Kakashi!
HAKU: I can't.
His energy is too strong.
[groaning]
[yelling]
[glass breaking]
HAKU: Zabuza.
I am no match for this boy.
Master.
I have failed.
[grunting]
NARUTO: So that guy in
the woods-- that was you?
HAKU: Why do you not strike?
-Huh?
-Did you not just vow to
avenge your comrade's death
by killing me?
Or was that vow
just empty words?
[grunting]
[yelling]
[groaning]
-And now-- that won't do.
You're still holding back.
If that is all the strength
you can put into it,
you will never keep your vow.
Perhaps he didn't mean as
much to you as you pretend.
[grunting]
Is there anyone who's
important to you?
There is only one person
who matters to me,
and I live to protect
and serve him.
That is my purpose--
to show mercy
to those who oppose
the one you serve--
to allow his enemies to live
when you could strike them
down-- this is not compassion.
It is a betrayal of your
life's very purpose.
For what reason
do you exist then?
You're of use to no one.
Your life has no meaning.
It is mere existence-- day
after day of pain and struggle--
signifying nothing.
-Yeah, well, speak for yourself.
-Are you really that
blind, little one?
I am speaking of myself.
This day has shown that I am
no longer of any use to Zabuza.
-Zabuza.
[angrily]Why that guy anyway?
To devote your life
to a rotten skunk
who doesn't know the
meaning of the word honor.
If he's really the
one person that
matters to you-- man, that's the
sorriest thing I've ever heard.
-There were once others who
mattered to me long ago.
My father and my mother.
I was born in the Land of
Water in a small village where
the snow lies deep
in the winter.
My parents were
farmers and very poor.
Our life was hard,
but we were content.
My parents were good to
each other and kind to me.
Yes, we were happy once.
But then everything changed.
Because of something that
happened long before I
was even born,
everything changed.
-What do you mean?
What was it?
What happened?
-It wasn't my doing.
It is in the blood.
-Blood?
So what was it?
You said something happened
that changed everything!
-It was my father who changed.
He killed my mother,
and he almost killed me.
[gasping]
After years of suffering
the horrors of civil war,
the people of my land
had come to fear and hate
anyone who carried the
Kekkei Genkai in their blood.
NARUTO: Kekkei Genkai?
HAKU: The advanced
bloodline trait of a clan.
It's jutsu and abilities
passed down from generation
to generation.
Because of their
unique abilities,
the clans were used
as mercenaries.
They fought in many battles
and were much feared.
But when the war was
over, they were despised
and shunned by the people who
feared their presence would
only bring more
war and misfortune.
So it was that after
the wars, these clans
went into hiding-- denying
the bloodline trait that
flowed in their
veins, concealing
their unique abilities--
knowing that to be discovered
meant certain death.
If you had searched
that boy's memories,
I'm sure you would have
found it there, too.
The cruelty of people--
their fear of things
they don't understand.
For years, my mother
was successful in hiding
her bloodline trait.
She met and fell in love
with a simple farmer.
And they were married.
And after that,
my mother thought
she would lead a
peaceful, ordinary life
to the end of her days.
[girl laughing]
Mama, look what I can do.
[gasping]
[laughing]
See what I made?
See?
Isn't it beautiful?
HAKU'S MOTHER: No!
You must never!
Do you hear?
Never!
You wicked, wicked child!
-Mama, what is it?
Stop!
Mama!
[slapping]
[crying]
HAKU'S MOTHER: Oh, I'm sorry!
I'm sorry, my darling!
I'm sorry!
[crying]
HAKU: My father had
seen-- and so he
knew our secret-- my
mother's and mine.
[groaning]
[gasping]
[crying]
[foot steps]
HAKU: When at last I was myself
again, I was no longer myself.
My father and mother
were gone, but I
knew that something
else had been
taken from me-- something
even more important.
And that is when
I truly despaired.
-More important than
your mother and father?
What?
-My purpose.
In all the world, there
was no one who needed me.
I was unnecessary.
-(VOICEOVER) Just like me!
-Why is it you're so
determined to be Hokage?
Because you want all eyes in
your village to look on you
and recognize you
as a great ninja.
You see, it is only
through the eyes of others
that our little lives
have any significance.
When there is no one who sees
you or will even look at you,
it's as if you do not exist.
Then Zabuza came along
and looked at me,
and his eyes were not
full of hate or fear.
He did not shun me
for my strangeness.
Indeed, my special powers
were just what he wanted.
He made me necessary again.
ZABUZA: Huh.
Little kid like you with
no one to look after you--
you'll die a beggar's death.
-Hey, you know what?
Your eyes remind me of mine.
ZABUZA: Well, little one,
will you stay here and die?
Or come with me
and be of some use?
Will you serve me and submit
to my will in all things?
[music playing]
Then your special abilities
belong to me from this day
forward.
[music playing]
Let us go then.
-I was happy.
ZABUZA: My time
here is done, Haku.
Tonight, I cast aside
the Land of Water.
One day I will return
and seize this land
and hold it in my hands.
Many things must be done
before that day comes,
and you will help me to do them.
But I warn you-- friendship,
comfort, encouragement--
I do not need these things, nor
should you expect them from me.
-I understand.
I am yours, Zabuza.
I am only an instrument
of your will.
Think of me as a weapon
to be kept at your side
and used as you see fit.
-Well said, child.
[wind blowing]
-I have failed you, Zabuza.
I am like a weapon that
has been broken and is
of no further use.
[gasping]
Naruto.
Kill me.
-Ninja art summoning!
Earth style-- fanged
pursuit jutsu!
ZABUZA: I don't
know why you bother.
Of what use is your jutsu
if you can't even find me?
But I can find you.
Blindly falling into my trap.
You disappoint me, Kakashi.
I think you're right.
It is time to put
an end to this.
[rattling]
Huh?
[growling]
[biting]
[screaming]
[barking]
-That dreadful noise!
What could it be?
-I don't know, and I'm not
sure that I want to find out!
[growling]
-I realized that I couldn't see
you, I'd have to smell you out.
That was a summoning jutsu.
I was calling forth
my ninja hounds.
They can track a scent anywhere.
When you attacked me, I
let you get past my guard.
I wanted you to cut me.
You see, it's the smell
of my blood on your blade
that led them to you.
Surprised?
Looks like I wasn't the
only one who was blind.
Huh.
Falling into my trap.
You disappoint me, Zabuza.
Ah.
The mist is finally clearing.
And you know what I see?
Your death.
ZABUZA: Talk.
Talk.
Do you mean to talk me to death?
KAKASHI: In a way, yes.
Right now, my hounds are
just playing with you.
But one word from me, and
they'll tear you apart.
Poor Zabuza.
See where your
ambitions got you?
You were always
pushing things too far.
[crashing]
It was the failed
Mizukage assassination
and your attempted coup d'etat.
You were forced to flee with
the few followers you had--
your country's tracker
ninja hot on your heels.
You became a rogue ninja whose
name was quickly known even
in the village
hidden in the leaves.
Now, you're crazy enough to want
to go back and try it again.
But for that, you need money.
And to get it,
you stooped so low
as to be the hired thug
of a swine like Gato.
All right, Zabuza, enough talk.
Time to finish it.
But it won't be with
Sharingan-- imitations
of some other ninja's tricks.
No, it's time I introduced
you to my own jutsu.
[sizzling]
-[yelling] Lightning blade!
-Chakra's so strong,
it's visible!
He holds it in his hands!
-I won't allow you
to kill Tazuna.
He's a brave man
with a noble dream.
The bridge he's
building is the hope
of this land and all its people.
You're like a disease.
By attacking one,
you infect all.
And you don't care.
That is not the
way of the Shinobi.
-You're right.
I don't care!
These useless little people
and their petty little dreams.
Why should they matter to me?
I have a dream of my own.
[sizzling]
-But to have a dream, you
need to have a future.
-Huh?
-You don't.
Your future's all
used up, Zabuza.
HAKU: Go on.
Strike.
Kill me.
Why do you hesitate?
[groaning]
[yelling]
-That's the most ridiculous
story I've ever heard!
I mean, he treats
you like a slave.
You're a human being,
not a weapon or a tool.
How can you care about
someone like that?
-For that very reason.
-Huh?
-Does that seem
so strange to you?
-Well, yeah.
A little.
When he found me, I was without
a purpose or reason for living.
Zabuza gave me both.
[music playing]
[laughing]
[gasping]
-But now, my usefulness is over.
The only thing that gave my
life meaning-- it's gone.
I am a broken tool-- a blunted
weapon of no use to anyone.
Go on, Naruto, do it.
For both of our sakes,
do it-- quickly.
[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Look.
It's not as if I like
Haku-- not after what
he did to Sasuke, but to
kill him in cold blood?
What do I do?
What would a Hokage do?
If only I could have
had a straight-up fight
like Kakashi-Sensei and Zabuza.
I mean, hey, I'm just a kid.
How come I always have to
make the tough decisions?
What would the other guys do?
Next time-- The Weapons
Known as Shinobi.