[theme music]
-(LAUGHING) Bit of a
monster yourself, huh?
Maybe you shouldn't
be pointing fingers.
Take this!
Are you kidding?
[growls]
-Aah!
-Ugh!
-Naruto!
-I've got him!
-Well, what do you know?
-Naruto, hang in there!
Naruto!
-Don't worry, I'm still here.
Thanks to you, Isaribi.
-Oh no!
- All of your chakra
is gonna be mine!
-My destruction jutsu!
-Impossible!
-Ah!
-Whew!
Just in time.
-What the--?
-Oh, I get it.
It was you, huh?
-Don't mess with me, kid!
-Get away from me!
-Aah!
-Never turn your
back on the enemy--
the most basic rule of combat.
You cost yourself the battle.
-Thanks, Shino.
You saved me, there.
-That snot-nosed little twerp
hit me with everything he had.
Well, I see Yoroi is
out of the picture.
-(CHUCKLING) Looks like I
caught me a big one, huh?
You weren't planning on
sneaking off, were ya?
[seagulls]
-That's it, sir.
We've seen to all the wounded.
-Right!
Excellent work!
-All that's left is--
-Naruto and the others, right?
-You've been a busy
boy, out there.
You're gonna have a
lot to answer for,
once we get you back to shore.
-This is far from over.
-Oh yeah?
Maybe you need a
little more convincing!
[chuckling] I'm gonna miss
you when you're gone, kid.
-What's that supposed to mean?
Guys, you seeing
what I'm seeing?
--[chuckling] You won't
be able to kill it.
The Sea Monster is immortal!
It draws its life from the
fast waters of the ocean.
You guys don't stand
a ghost of a chance.
-Aw, shut up!
Summoning Kyoto.
All right, Chief,
I'm counting on you.
Now let's flatten
that gob o' goo, OK?
Hey!
We don't have time
to kick back, Chief!
Now are you gonna
clobber that thing, or--
-It's hot!
Hot!
[grunting]
-Trouble follow you around, kid?
Or do you go looking for it?
I got a rash all over my body,
and it itches like crazy!
-Don't come over here, Naruto!
Whoa!
You little nimrod!
I'm gonna tear you
apart limb from limb,
when this mission is over!
-Well, pipsqueak, I hope you've
got a plan, 'cause I'm itching!
-What?
Are you kidding me?
Nobody's tougher than you!
Don't tell me a little salt
water's gonna hold you back!
-Whoa!
-Heh, you're a disgrace, kid.
You can't even control the
creature you summoned up.
-What was that?
-You'd better send
him on his way.
And quick, too, before the
Sea Monster swallows him,
and he shrivels up like a slug.
-Did you just call me a slug?
All right, Naruto, you're
in for a world of hurt
when we're finished.
But I'm gonna lend you a hand.
-Wait, what?
-Don't mess with an amphibian,
lest you suffer his wrath!
-At a boy, Chief!
I knew I could count on ya!
-Hold on tight!
Yea!
What the-- [grunting] Won't
let go of [inaudible] Yes.
-What gives, Chief Toad?
Are you gonna take this?
-Shut your yap, will
ya? [grunts] Ah!
Hm, I'm gonna have
to rethink this.
-Oh brother!
What are we up against, anyway?
-Hmm, I'm not sure--
a bunch of spirits
trapped at the core of a
water elemental, probably.
That's what I'm
thinking, anyway.
-Darn it!
You got any ideas?
I'm coming up blank!
-Well, cutting it's
not gonna work.
It'll just revive itself
with all this sea water.
-Yeah, so what other options
does that leave us then?
-The trick is gonna be getting
to those spirits at its core.
We have to damage them, somehow.
-Damage them?
Well, how do we pull that off?
-Our opponent is
a clump of water.
If we heat things up around
here, maybe he'll evaporate.
-Heh, they haven't got half a
brain between the 2 of them.
They should surrender,
while they can!
I rule this ocean now!
-I'm not impressed!
You ready, Naruto?
-Huh?
Wait!
Ready for what?
-Take it slow.
I've gotta spew some oil!
I hope you know some
fire-style jutsu!
-Fire?
That's not exactly
my specialty, Chief!
-Here we go!
-Aah!
What do I do?
Aah!
-All right, here goes nothing!
-How did they--?
-Oh!
-Boy, look at that!
-Nicely done.
-Naruto
-No!
It can't be!
-We got 'em, Chief!
-Heh, walk in the park.
-That's right, big guy,
you put us together
and we're unstoppable!
I hate to rain on
your parade, but I
think you might be
forgetting something.
-Huh?
I don't follow ya.
-You brought me down right
in the middle of the ocean,
you dum-dum!
Look at this-- my
skin's a catastrophe!
-Please!
These warts have been here
as long as I've known ya!
-Keep pushing me, kid!
You're on thin
enough ice as it is!
Don't make it worse!
-Huh?
N-n-now, wait a second.
Let's just talk about this!
-I'm done talking!
-Aah!
Aah!
-Yuck!
Everything itches!
You deserve a lot worse,
but I'll let you off
with a slap on the
wrist this time,
for all the trouble my
boys have caused you.
-Aah!
-See ya later!
[grunts]
-It won't happen again, Chief.
They'll think that
you burned me alive.
Huh?
[seagulls]
-Well, we dealt with your
sea monster, now you.
You'll be taken to the
Village Hidden in the Leaves
and tried for all the crimes
you've committed out here.
-That's right!
Not to mention the trip to
the moon I got from the Chief!
-Humph!
What's wrong with you, Isaribi?
Take care of these fools now!
-I'm done with you!
-Are you forgetting?
I'm the only person who can
give you back your humanity.
-I don't care!
If I keep this up, I'll
be nothing but a monster,
at heart!
-Hey, I knew you'd
finally come around!
Well said.
--[laughing] You're
neither a human being,
nor fully integrated like I am!
[laughs] The best
you can hope for is
to wander this earth as a freak!
The truth of it is, I never
wasted a moment's thought
as to how I would
reverse your condition.
Like I said before,
the only reason I
kept you around
was to dissect you.
-It can't be.
-You rotten piece of garbage!
How much lower can you get?
Huh?
-That's enough.
Once we get him
back to the village,
he'll be held accountable
for everything he's done.
[laughing]
-Now, I think it's
about time you told me.
Orochimaru-- where
do I find him?
-Do you really think
I know where he is?
The man tossed you aside.
(MOCKINGLY) And yet, you
still search for him.
-You and I are nothing alike!
With my research
on this island, I
would've eventually
surpassed him.
-Oh, really?
-Aah!
[groans]
-Hey!
How come you got to sock him?
-All righty, then,
mission complete.
Let's get going, shall we?
-That ain't fair!
I wanna get one in!
-Give it a rest.
-Your luck, pal!
-This is the place
Amachi was talking
about-- chair Alignment.
This is where my
nightmare began.
There may be fragments
of my memory left here.
[birds chirping]
-Ugh!
[gasping]
-Nyorai Hashimoto,
what have you done?
This pain is--
[evil laugh]
-[groans] [gasping] Ah!
Ah!
[screams]
[organ playing]
-She's still alive.
LORD AKAHOSHI: Mm.
[chuckles] She's a lucky girl.
So out of the 10 we tested, she
was the only one to survive.
One last delicious harvest,
before my departure.
-Departure?
LORD AKAHOSHI: There's no reason
for me to be here, anymore.
But my lord-- the research.
It's all yours.
You can consider
it a parting gift.
As of this point, I've
no further need of it.
-But why?
How could you do this?
I don't get it!
I've looked up to you more
than anyone in the world!
-You simply didn't
measure up, my dear.
I'm afraid you lack
the hunger for power,
the drive, the hatred.
Everything and anything.
Although, you didn't die.
To make it this far, you
can't be totally useless.
Well?
How about it?
Care to accompany me then?
[heart beating]
-Fair enough.
Somewhere, out there, is
the diamond in the rough
that I'm looking for.
[gasps]
-It's all coming back.
-It's so bright!
I wasn't cast aside.
It was my choice,
and mine alone.
-Hey, you guys!
How come Haku is
missing in action?
-There was no sign of
her when I woke up--
just a note saying that
she'd be back in a bit.
-What's her deal?
Can't she sit still
for like, one second?
-There's the pot calling
the kettle black.
-What's that supposed to mean?
-You got a beef with me?
[growling]
-Are you sure?
I can really come with you?
I mean--
-Well, of course, you can!
And don't worry.
She's a little scary, but we've
got a top-notch medical ninja
back in the Hidden Leaf!
-Right.
Lady Tsunade is actually
a medical specialist.
-Yeah!
The whole kage is
simply amazing!
I just know she'll
be able to help.
You can relax, now.
You'll be in good hands with us.
-Thank you, all.
-Hey!
Come on!
-Huh?
-What's the hold-up?
The boat's about to shove off.
-Wha-- when did she--?
-What's the matter with you?
We've just been standing
around waiting for ya!
-Oh, sorry about that.
-Whoa!
Whoa!
We're coming!
-All right!
We're headed back to the
Hidden Leaf Village again!
-Seriously, you've been
spinning like a top from start
to finish on this journey.
Don't you know the
meaning of the word tired?
-OK, what's that
supposed to mean?
-It's a compliment.
You really came through.
-Wait, for real?
Go on-- you're embarrassing me.
[giggling]
-Right.
[laughter]
[seagulls]
[theme music]
-Ha ha ha!
Guarding a VIP has a nice
ring to it, don't ya think?
I finally get a mission that's
up to par with my ability!
Just you wait, Mr. Moneybags!
Once I take on a
mission, I'll go
through fire or water
before I-- What the--?
D-Ranks babysitting?
She pulled a fast one on me!
Next time!
Impossible!
Celebrity Ninja art!
Money-style jutsu.
[theme music]