[theme music]
-I hope that woke you up.
Now you know I'm
not messing around.
We had a bit of an
interruption that day.
But that won't happen this time.
So let me show you the true
power of the Sharingan.
-OK.
I guess that means I can
stop going easy on you.
Come on and fire up
that Sharingan of yours.
I don't want you to
miss a thing when
I hit you with my
Way of the Shinobi.
-Heh.
-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
What good will that do you?
Ten times zero is still zero.
-Gotcha!
[chuckling]
-Thanks to the
Sharingan I knew which
was the real you all the time.
I played along for
old time's sake.
[chuckling]
-But now playtime's over.
Fire Style!
Fireball Jutsu!
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
What did it mean?
That look in my brother's eyes.
That was no ordinary Sharingan.
And ever since, even though
that was a while ago,
there's been something wrong
between him and father.
-Good morning to you, father.
-Ah, yes.
Good morning.
Tell me.
How's everything
going at the Academy.
-Some of the lessons
are a little bit boring.
But I'm always top
of in my class.
UCHIHA: Fire Style!
Fireball Jutsu!
This is the key
jutsu of our clan.
Now I've already shown
you all the handsigns.
The next step is to
build up your chakra
and focus it to a
point in your chest,
and then force it up through
the throat and out the mouth.
Now you try it.
-Right
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
Father's actually
teaching me the jutsu himself.
He's finally giving me a chance
to show that I matter too.
I can't disappoint him.
I can do it!
Fire Style!
Fireball Jutsu!
[sigh]
-Why did I think you
would be like Itachi?
It's too soon.
You're not ready yet.
UCHIHA: A member
of the Uchiha Clan
is not recognized
as full fledged
until they can use
the Fire Style.
[panting]
UCHIHA: the Uchiha
Crest represents
the fan that rouses
the flame of our will.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): Fire Style!
Fireball Jutsu!
-One more time.
SASUKE: Fire Style!
Fireball Jutsu!
Fire Style!
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): OK.
Today for sure.
Fire Style!
Fireball Jutsu!
-Sasuke?
-Huh?
-Hold on a minute.
-What is it?
[laughter]
-What's that for?
-No, no.
Don't go yet.
There.
That should help.
-Hey, mom-- Mhm.
No.
It's nothing.
-You sure?
SASUKE: Fire Style.
Fireball Jutsu!
[sigh] Why did I think
you would be like Itachi.
It's too soon.
You're not ready yet.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): I'll get it.
I'm just getting started.
OK.
Here we go.
SASUKE: Fire Style!
Fireball Jutsu!
Father!
Just once more.
Will you come watch
me one more time?
-I've told you.
It's too soon for you.
I could teach you every day for
a week and it wouldn't help.
-No.
Not teach me.
-Hm?
-Watch me, I'm
saying, I think I've
got the hang of it, father.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
Failure is not an option.
Fire Style!
Fireball Jutsu!
-Now then, that's my boy.
You've done well.
Work hard and you're
bound to soar high
and to bring honor to that
crest you wear on your back.
-I will!
-From now on, walk
your own path.
Not in the footsteps
of your brother.
-Hey, mom?
-Hm?
-I was wondering
about Itachi and me.
What does father
really think of us?
-What on earth
makes you ask that?
-It was something he said the
other day down on the dock.
Father said to
me, that's my boy.
That's something he's
only ever said to Itachi.
So it made me really
happy to hear it.
-Of course.
And I'm glad it did.
-But then I started to wonder.
Now that father and Itachi
aren't getting along,
am I just someone to
replace my older brother?
-Your older brother's your
older brother and you are you.
But your father has always cared
very deeply about both of you.
-He's only thought
of Itachi before now!
-Well, if it's sometimes
seemed that way,
it's only because your father
is a leader of the Uchiha Clan.
He has to make sure
it's kept safe.
-What's that got to do with it?
-Your brother is the firstborn
and he's bigger than you are.
And as the firstborn,
he's going to have
to assume his responsibilities
earlier than you will.
So since it's your father's
job to look after the clan,
it's only natural
he'd want to be
sure Itachi's ready
to take on his role.
But I'll let you in on a secret.
When we're alone
and no one's around,
the only one he
talks about is you.
-He has a hard time showing it.
It's how he is.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): I'll
be as good as he is.
I promise.
-Itachi.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): No matter
what I do, I can't catch up.
-I'm sorry, Sasuke.
Some other time, OK?
-The clan, the clan.
You overestimate
your own abilities
with no idea of the
depth of my own.
And look at you now--
groveling in the dirt.
I've had enough.
There's no hope left
for this pathetic clan.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
That's when it happened.
Ever since that day, it's
like he's not the same.
-Big brother, do you think
you could help me out
with my Shuriken Jutsu
after school today?
-No.
I can't.
I'm busy.
Why don't you go ask
father to help you?
-Aw, come on.
You're way better at the
Shuriken Jutsu than father is.
I mean, even I can see that.
Big brother, why do you always
treat me like such a pest?
-I'm sorry, Sasuke.
Some other time, OK?
I don't have time
for this today.
-You're always doing this to me.
You jab me in the forehead and
then say I'm sorry, Sasuke.
And you never have time.
It's always the same story.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): That's good.
He hasn't changed after all.
But still-- his eyes when he
looked at father that time.
I'm sure that was no
ordinary Sharingan.
I wonder.
-Father?
-Hm.
-About Sharingan, is there
more than one type of it?
-Hm?
What's this?
So you're already thinking
about Sharingan now?
Well, don't.
It's far too soon for you
to be worried about that.
It's not the same
as Fire Style Jutsu.
-But I'll have to know
all about it some day.
After all, I am your son.
-Well, there is a
visual jutsu that's
a level above the Sharingan.
It's called the
Mangekyo Sharingan.
-Mangekyo Sharingan.
-It's an almost legendary jutsu.
In the history of our
clan, only a very few
have been able to master it.
What's more, it said that
it can be called forth only
under very specific
circumstances.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
Specific circumstances.
UCHIHA: From now on,
walk your own path.
Not in the footsteps
of your brother.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): What does
he think of Itachi and me?
The way we are with each other.
-Father?
-Hm?
-Do you know why Itachi
is always so cold to me?
-He's a peculiar
one, your brother.
He's never cared about
being liked or making
friends or any of that.
-But why is that?
-I don't know.
As his father, you'd
think I would have a clue.
But I don't.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
All this time
I've been afraid to talk
about Itachi and me.
But it's OK.
He doesn't mind.
-Got your lunch ready.
It's time to go.
And after you get
home today, I'll
watch you practice your
Shuriken Jutsu, OK?
-It's not practice.
It's called training.
See you later!
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
That's a a relief.
I thought father hates
Itachi for some reason.
But it turns out he's
just confused, like me.
My brother was seven when he
graduated top of his classroom
from the Academy.
He could use the Sharingan
when he was eight.
And he made chunin
when he was only ten.
I've got the same Uchiha
blood in my veins, don't I?
If he can do it, I can do it.
-Is that really all you've got?
Come on.
After all that big
talk, that's it?
That was your Way
of the Shinobi?
You still think we're on
the same team, don't you?
If you're not
convinced yet, I'll
just have to spell
it out for you!
What are you waiting for?
I want to see what the number
one, hyperactive, knucklehead
ninja has got!
[theme music]
NARUTO: Neji was right.
Something's got a hold
of Sasuke and pulled him
into the darkness!
He was playing for keeps
when he hit me just now.
He could have-- Sasuke, does
this mean I'm nothing to you
anymore?
All we've been through, all
the missions we went on,
the friends we've made!
That all means nothing to you?
Next time-- The Secrets
of the Mangekyo Sharingan!
[theme music]