[theme music]
-Huh?
Shizune!
-Lady Tsunade!
What is it?
What's that?
TSUNADE: A security mission
from the Village Hidden
in the Stars.
-Is there something
wrong with that?
-You don't know the Village
Hidden in the Stars,
do you, Shizune?
It's a relatively small place,
but they are proud people
and have caused a lot of
headaches in the past.
-So, are you planning
to accept the job?
-I can't simply
disregard it, can I?
-Why not?
-That village has
something very special.
-Anyway, apparently they
decided to form a three man
squad with Neji as team leader.
-But the Village Hidden in
the Stars is a full on shinobi
village, isn't it?
Why do they need us?
Can't they use their own ninja
to handle security themselves?
-Hm.
Well, sometimes
a smaller village
will strengthen relations by
coordinating with its allies
militarily.
And in this case, their
village is smaller than most.
They probably don't have
enough ninja to protect it.
-Oh.
But why's a place that
tiny being attacked?
-You don't know?
It all started 200
years ago,
when a shooter star hit the village.
-You mean like a star in the
sky, not like a throwing star,
right?
-Yep.
And according to
legend, the star
contains a mysterious power
that can affect chakra.
-What a ridiculous story!
-First off, no way has a
star ever just dropped out
of the sky and his the Earth.
-It happened.
Why do you think the
village has been targeted
by foreign shinobi
several times already?
-Wha-- This isn't
the first time?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Mysterious power, huh?
Sounds like something Orochimaru
would wanna get his hands on.
-OK.
Looks like I'll
be going with him.
-What?
You can't.
The three man squad's
already been chosen.
-Yeah, but I got an
ace up my sleeve.
Hm.
-All right, I'd better take the
lead position from here on out.
We may run into
danger on the way.
-OK, sounds good.
-Heya fellas!
I'm gonna keep going.
See you there!
-Naruto!
Hold on!
No way.
-Um, what is Naruto doing
on this mission anyway?
-No idea.
-Lady Tsunade.
We just received
word that Naruto
has joined up with Neji's team.
-(MUMBLING) Mm.
Yes.
I added him to the
mission last minute.
-Wh-- Why?
-Those four did well at
the Katabami Gold Mine.
Besides, while he's
gone, I can relax.
-You would change the lineup of
an established squad on a whim?
[choking]
-Lady Tsunade!
Is that a rare roasted
chestnut bean jelly
with gold leaf candy?
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER):
Wait a second.
Did Naruto bribe her with that?
-(MUFFLED) Tea!
I need tea!
Now!
-Izura!
-You OK?
-I'm fine.
-I said not to push yourself.
-I know you did,
but I just don't
want to fall behind
the rest of you guys.
-You are supposed
to be training.
-Mizura was in pain,
so we stopped, sir.
-Take him to get
medical attention.
-Yes, sir.
-I'll go too.
-Hokuto can accompany
him there alone.
Sumaru, do not
forget your training.
-All right.
I'm the first one here.
Once I cross this canyon,
I'm in the Land of Bears.
The Village Hidden in
the Stars is close.
Huh?
Eat that!
-Ninja Art, Kujaku.
Protection.
-He blocked my
kunai with chakra.
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
-Destroy!
-Aw man.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): The
chakra's incredible.
-Stop.
But this jerk's an enemy.
He attacked me out of the blue!
-Oh.
You're a Leaf ninja.
-Wait.
You're from the
Hidden Star village?
-I'm Sumaru.
I came to pick up
you and your friends.
-So what's with the arrows?
-Look there, Naruto.
-Huh?
-The border canyon
of the Land of Bears
is eternally filled
with poison gas.
The fog acts as a barrier
against foreign invaders.
-Whoa.
So this was the danger
you warned us about, huh?
-You should be grateful, Naruto.
It looks like Sumaru
truly saved your life.
It is the beginning of
a beautiful friendship
between Leaf and Star.
[laughter]
-Whatever.
I didn't need his help.
-I didn't have to
help you, you know?
I could have just stood there
watching while you perished.
-I'm Akahoshi, and I
serve as deputy Hoshikage
of this village.
-Deputy?
But then--
-The Third Hoshikage passed
on quite suddenly a year ago,
so at present the village finds
itself without a true leader.
-But I thought only leaders
of the five great villages
could be called Kage.
-Yeah.
SUMARU: That makes
no difference.
The people of this village
are inferior to no one.
We may be small, but
someday this village
will rival those of
the five great lands.
And when that day comes,
I will be Hoshikage.
-Be quiet.
Return to your training at once.
-Hey, wait up!
I want to ask you something!
-Naruto!
TENTEN: Where are you going?
There he goes again.
-I'm sorry about our friend.
Please continue, sir.
-Where was I?
Yes.
As you correctly pointed
out, the shinobi of our land
are not qualified
to even have a Kage.
However, we possess a star
that the Kages of the five
great hidden villages covet.
Someday we'll harness
the power of the star,
and our village will at last
be able to seat a sixth Kage.
-So your enemies have been
trying to get that star.
-That's right.
Our scouting team managed to
get some useful intelligence.
-Huh?
Where the heck did
that guy run off to?
Huh?
Hey!
I finally caught up.
What was your name, again?
Omaru?
-No, not Omaru.
Sumaru.
-Oh.
Oops, sorry about that.
But hey, Sumaru is a
pretty interesting name.
-Well, it's derived
from the star cluster
Subaru, or the Pleiades.
In fact, everyone in
our village has a name
that's associated
with a certain star.
After all, this is
where a star fell.
-No kidding.
-What do you want
from me, anyway?
-Who, me?
Ah, nothing in particular.
I just realized I never
thanked you before, you know?
-Don't try to act nice with me.
Foreigners are all the same.
They're all trying
to get to our star.
They think if they
get its power,
they can rise above the
other hidden villages.
-So does that mean
that chakra of yours
is fueled by the power
of the star, too?
I mean, if someone
else had the star,
wouldn't they have the
same chakra as you do?
-No!
The more power you draw from
it, the more hard work and skill
you need to control it.
-Yeah, but--
-And that's what
I'm going to do.
Nothing but hard work.
I will become the Hoshikage.
-Great.
I can't wait to work with ya.
-Huh?
-'Cause I'm gonna become
Hokage of my village, too.
-You know, you're kind of weird.
-You think?
-Intruder!
Guard the star!
-Oh, man, you're right.
The tree trunks all fell outward
from the center of the crater.
-When a star impacts
like this, it's
exactly the pattern
you would expect.
Over there is our training area,
where the star is enshrined.
-Well, let's go.
I'm dying to see it.
-Never.
No one from a foreign land
is allowed beyond this point.
-The star's the
point of the mission.
How are supposed to protect
the thing if we can't even
get close to it?
-You're foreigners.
We can't just leave you
with something so sacred.
-Man, you really are
paranoid, you know that, pal?
I mean, come on.
You hired us for security,
and you still don't trust us?
-Well, I am who I am.
[door closing]
-Huh?
-Who is that?
The star!
-I'll go chase him down.
You check on your friends
in the training building.
We don't have time to hesitate.
-Right.
We'll have to split up.
Hokuto.
-Sumaru.
I'm sorry.
We couldn't protect it.
-Did you really
think you could just
steal something from this
village in broad daylight,
and get away with it?
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
You got no chance
of getting away.
Huh?
-Ninja Art, Kujaku.
-What?
That same chakra?
-Beast.
-Oh, no!
Look out!
We gotta get this guy!
Fire the everywhere,
Shuriken Jutsu!
-It's futile.
-Gotcha.
You're the real target, and
I just found your weakness.
All right, guys,
his physical body
can't move while he's
controlling a jutsu.
Let's get him, with
a clone body slam!
-I can use my chakra
more than one way.
-Huh?
Yah!
That guy can hit hard.
Huh?
-Synthesis.
-Darn it.
-Naruto!
-Huh?
-Wings!
What?
You can fly, too?
-He's gone!
-I almost took him
down, but then--
-It's my fault for
agreeing to let you try.
-What's going on?
That jerk used the exact
same ninja art as you.
Want to tell me what's
really going on?
-That ninja art.
Only a star-trained
ninja could know it.
-You mean that guy was from the
Village Hidden in the Stars?
-I can't be sure.
-Listen to me.
I'm the one who
let him get away,
and I'm gonna be the one who
gets that star back, I swear.
[theme music]
TENTEN: There's something fishy
about the village leader's
attitude.
-Naruto's opponent used
the ninja art Kujaku.
NEJI: Yes.
The attacker is definitely
a shinobi from this village.
NARUTO: But that old guy
didn't mention a traitor.
TENTEN: Looks like there's
some kind of secret.
We need to investigate
the leader.
We should all split up.
NARUTO: All right!
I promise, I will get that
start, no matter what!
Next time, The
Remembered Lullaby!
[theme music]