Morning!?
I'm going to practice.
Bye, see you later.
Okay, bye-bye, Azusa.
Sky high!
No.
The music that I think we should be aiming for...
is NOT this at all!
Yeah but this is the direction that I think we oughta go.
What?!
You're cocky!
Stop it! Stop it you two!
What exactly is going on here?
Well After-school Tea Time may break up, that's what.
Break up?! No way! Why now?
Because everyone seems to be
moving in different directions.
Musically, that is, we're not actually moving, Azu-nyan.
That's nothing but a bunch of bunk!
Face it, Yui, you learn one new chord and
then proceed to forget the previous three.
Yeah well, you fell and showed
your panties to the whole school.
What?! Th-That's irrelevant!
Um you're talking about musical direction?
What's your opinion, Azusa?
Um... Well isn't After-school
Tea Time suppose to be all about
being all bright and bouncy?
Honestly...
That's all just fluff!
I've grown tired of it.
Look who's talking!
When you first came and joined this band,
all you wanted was this so called fluff.
You had the musical sense of an old lady!
Old lady?
You begged me to join, saying I could
just sit around, eat snacks and take it easy.
Um guys, you want to play Old Maid?
Not now, Azusa! We don't have time for that!
We're talking about the survival of the band here!
Azu-nyan.
Yes!?
We'll play a little later.
Don't forget, we let you join us even
though you couldn't play guitar or harmonica!
What do you mean? I can play
harmonica! Oh really? You can?
Then show me!
I can't! I'm sorry, I lied!
You're all crazy, you know that?!
Mugi-chan?
Mugi?
Come to think of it, it's Mugi's fault for
distracting us with all those snacks and teas.
You pig out more than any of use!
Well she brings really good stuff!
Well I'm sorry if it bothers you so much.
Hey don't get sarcastic. Say something, Mio!
Uh okay. I blame Ritsu!
Ah! What did I do?!
Yeah, it's all Ritsu's fault!
This is what you just played.
What are you doing?
You caught me.
We're copying "DEATH DEVIL".
Oh it's so much fun!
Okay can we all stop the play
acting now and get back to practicing?
You really got into it, too, Mio.
Play acting?
Yeah, that's right.
We were pretending to have a big ol'
nasty fight over musical differences.
You know it's standard rocker stuff.
Yeah. I should have guessed what was going on.
Well now that Azusa's arrived...
Oh, wait just a second.
Let's have some tea.
What?!
Alright, now it's time to grade ourselves.
I thought Azu-nyan would get a lot more
startled than she actually did when walked in.
I thought she meant we were gonna grade the music?
Oh! Don't worry, I already fed Tonchan.
Oh, thanks a lot, Senpai.
We weren't that convincing, were we?
Mugi's "You're all crazy!" was a little bit over the top.
I don't mind.
Yeah but we do.
Boy, I had no idea what a total slacker
after-school club this would turn out to be.
Hey watch it, Azusa.
That tea!
You wouldn't have been able to taste it
anywhere else but at this after school club.
It's the pride of the Kotobuki family.
I'm sorry. It's delicious.
Oh! Is that baumkuchen, Mugi?
Let's eat it layer by layer.
Please don't. That's torture.
Mugi! Hurry and open it!
I can't.
for the past years, we've been meeting in this club
room, having tea and cake and sometimes band practice.
All that's left for us now is graduation.
That may be true, but should you really be
kicking back so casually like you're doing?
Sure. I already got into college. Didn't I?
It's a miracle, I mean I
expected Mio and Mugi but...  What?
Huh? What did she just say?
Senpai, what is this?
Cute, huh?
It opened.
What are we gonna toast to?
How about to everyone of us
getting into the college they want?
Okay, let's toast to that.
You too, Azu-nyan.
Um... okay.
Cheers!
Cheers.
Sawa-chan!
I for one am extremely relieved
that you all passed your classes.
I imagine that teaching seniors must be really hard.
Oh my, I just can't believe you're all
graduating already. Where did the time go?
Boy, I wonder how many cups
of tea we all drank in 3 years.
I think a thousand cups, easily.
A thousand cups!?
Well we are After-school Tea Time.
Boy, I guess we really lived up to the name of our band.
All that's left now is for you to
get ready for your big sendoff...
if nobody's held back of course.
Held back?
There's a meeting next week.
It's to determine if you've all met your basic
attendance requirements and other such things.
No kidding! Is that true?!
S-Sawa-chan, w-we were just
doing a DEATH DEVIL impersonation.
The DEATH DEVIL rules!
That was Miss Yamanaka's killer band!
That's right, so what?
A-A-As big sister to our club, please have mercy!
You're my mentor!
That's some serious begging.
Kissing up won't save you.
Oh please, oh please, oh please!
Madam Sawako Yamanaka!
What's wrong?
Worried about not graduating?
No, not really.
This has to belong to Yui.
I guess I'm afraid that we're graduating without
giving Azu-nyan a really good reason to look up to us.
What!?
Now that's not true.
Because the four of us...
Are taller.
And older.
And active.
Is that all we've got?
I know!
Why don't we come up with something
real senior-like for Azu-nyan?
That's perfect!
I'm in! Nice one, Yui!
So what is it we're going to do?
Well I think a thoughtful present might be nice.
Something very Azu-nyan-ish.
There you are.
Wow! This is so exciting.
Just don't say a word to her, okay?
Hello there.
Oh Azu-nyan!
You- You kind of left a trail of garbage to here.
I did it on purpose cause I wanted
to be able to find my way back?
Well I picked it all up.
I'll never find the room now.
Oh don't be silly. Come on, let's get going.
Something that Azusa would like, huh?
Yeah.
A thing or an act or something.
Let me think.
Aw come on, Ui, you're in her
class. Has she said anything?
Like how cool we seem to her or something like that?
Well...
She must have said something.
She told me she wishes you guys
would practice a little harder.
And um, that you would try to keep
the club room just a little bit tidier.
And uh, that would try to stop hugging her so much.
That's it.
What's wrong, Sis?
That's what I figured she'd say.
We probably should be thanking her
for putting up with us all the time.
the only thing Azusa ever really talks
about is the band and the Light Music Club.
You mean it?
Yeah.
Not only that, she decided she
wanted to join the Light Music Club,
after she heard you guys play at that concert.
Did she really say that?
Oh! Why don't you all just hold
yourselves back so you can graduate with her?
No wait! I'm just kidding, Sis! Don't even think about it!
Azu-nyan.
What should we get you?!
Yui!
Good morning, Mugi-chan!
You've got guitar lines on your face.
I slept on Geeta.
It's so cold!
Let me feel your hand, okay?
Guess what?
What?
I wrote some brand new lyrics
last night before I went to bed.
Oh a new song? "Ice Cream Boy" huh?
Yeah, I need Mugi to put some music to it.
Ritsu! Mio-chan!
Good morning!
Same to you!
Mugi-chan's hands are so hot, I'm actually sweating.
Yeah well, Mio's hands are so cold,
it feels like they're frozen solid.
What's that mean?
Did any of you think of a present for Azu-nyan?
Did you?
I fell asleep thinking about it.
So did I. Socks and all!
I take them all off for bed.
Really?! Mio, how very audacious!
I meant my socks!
Good morning. You're here early.
Yeah I know, but I guess I just miss seeing everybody.
That's a good idea.
Morning, Nodoka-chan.
Good morning.
Alright, so let's go book it tomorrow.
Then we'll go shop for bathing suits.
Oh wow! My first trip to Hawaii!
Hey Mugi-chan, did you hear that?
Mika, are you going to Hawaii?
Yeah. For a graduation trip.
Isn't the Light Music Club going anywhere?
Rit-chan!
What's up, Yui?
So what do you guys think?
The volleyball team's taking a graduation trip.
Really?
I think we should, too.
When are you guys going?
The week right before graduation.
When the fares are still cheap.
Well, Rit-chan?!
That's before spring break.
Come on we should do it too.
Hmm...
Nope. We do our thing. They do theirs.
Awww!
Let's not forget that our priority right
now is to think of something to do for Azusa.
Listen up, everyone!
I think it'd be nice if we pulled together
and did something as a class for Ms. Yamanaka.
Any ideas? Oh and we have to keep it a secret, of course.
What do you think would be good?
Something tearful.
Sing the school song for her.
What does Ms. Yamanaka like anyway?
Tht's a good question.
And so guys...
I think we should take a graduation trip!
Didn't we all recently go and
get our passports squared away?
You told us we were all suppose
to think of a present for Azusa.
Hmm well yeah, we'll do that, too.
Yeah. No way!
You're always putting things off
and then we have to scramble to fix it.
What's a little trip, Ms. Stingy?
I interviewed my sister about Azu-nyan yesterday.
Yeah? Well give us your report then.
Well, she told me that...
Wait a sec! What is that?
That's a flying Beast! It's one of
Japan's oldest and most talked ab...
Right. What did your sister say?
Oh, she told me that we should all
just stay in the school for another year.
And that way we could graduate with
Azu-nyan instead leaving her behind.
You mean flunking as a present?
Yes. Flunking!
What's with you guys?
But I'm sensing a lot of panic.
You are?
Plus I though I heard someone say the word "flunking".
Our problems are many and vary.
So where did you hear that, Azusa?
Just now, from you guys when I came in.
You're hearing things, Azu-nyan.
It was just your imagination.
What are you doing that for?
We were discussing where we
might go for a graduation trip.
And there's this city in the
middle of Germany called "Flunken".
What!?
It sounds totally awful.
Let's not go there!
Really? Graduation trip, huh?
Dubai!
What happened to the idea of going to Hawaii?
Let's go to Europe!
How about a hot springs with ping-pong?
How about you Mio?
I don't know.
I think London, becuase of its deep
historic rock n' roll musical roots.
It's home to some great musicians.
Pretty tough decision.
How about you?
Oh. I'm not graduating yet, so I really can't say.
How did we end up talking about a
graduation trip instead of her present?
It sort of just happened.
My bad. My bad.
Don't you want to go on a trip with us, Mio?
Of course I do. I didn't mean that.
Okay, who DOESN'T want to take a graduation trip?
Silence.
Tonchan.
It's settled, then!
Whoa that was quick.
Great! Let's choose where
we're going by ghost leg lottery.
I'm the type that's pretty good at
that sort of thing if I do say so myself.
What type is that?
It's done!
Here you go, Captain Ritsu, it's all yours.
Who, me? Okay then... this one.
All righty. Let's see where it leads us to.
The decision is in!
Europe it is!
Wow that was your choice, Yui.
So where exactly in Europe are we gonna be going?
Yeah Yui, where?
Senpai?  Yes?
Can I take a look at that paper for just a second?
But why? How come?
No reason.
Well...
She's running!
And falling!
Yui!
Yui?
YUUUI!
Rit-chan.
Yui!
I can finally do this. You see, Rit-chan?
That's great! That's great, Yui!
Thanks.
I knew it. this whole thing was rigged.
What!?
Oh drat!
Yui's always so obvious about this stuff.
Hey, you conned us.
Though it was pretty impressive, Yui.
Hey, don't gloat.
It was a simple mistake.
You can stay like that for a while.
Yui.
Okay, let's decide this the right way.
But no one here agrees on where we should go.
Let's take a vote.
Meaningless.
I know! Let's have Tonchan decide!
Stop it already.
Which teacup will Tonchan choose?
It's like a theme park or something in there.
By the way...  What?
The Europe cup looks a lot smaller
than all the rest of the cups in there.
Yeah, that's the penalty for cheating.
Oh I see.
I never thought Tonchan would
shoulder such a big responsibility.
Tonchan's swimming pretty high today.
He doesn't look at all interested in any of the cups.
What a nice day.
Everyone's so bored!
T-T-Tonchan! Look!
He's in front of Europe!
Yeah, but he's touching London.
Does this mean that it's London?
London's in Europe so you should be happy, Yui.
What? Really?
Wow! How far does Europe go anyway?
I feel sorry for the university you're going to.
Mio, we're going to London!
Congratulations, Mio.
YES!
Mio?
Yes, London! Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
Okay, take it easy. Will ya?
Lo-lo-London!
I guess you really wanted to go there, Mio-chan.
We can have afternoon tea there.
You mean they have tea in London?
It's the country of tea.
Really?! Then that's perfect for us!
There's 5 of us, so we should get two rooms.
3 and 2?  Mhm.
You're coming too, aren't you?
Oh no. I shouldn't go, it's your graduation trip.
Did you lose your passport?
No, of course not, but I still have to go to school.
You don't have classes after your finals, right?
Well no. We all get a 5-day break.
Great! So what's the problem then?
But...
We've all gotta go together.
It just wouldn't be right without you, Azu-nyan.
Azusa, don't you want to go?
I do! I'd love to, but wouldn't I just be in the way?
'Course not.
Then... yes. I'll go.
Yeah! It's settled!  Yay!
It's not quite settled yet. I've
got to check with my parents first.
Hello, Mom? It's me Azusa.
Yeah, listen um...
Oh thank you, Mom!
My Mom said that I can go, so...
That's right. London.
5 days. It's our graduation trip.
Uh, hi, Mom...
I'll never ask for anything again!
Mhm, Ritsu's going so you can relax.  Really?!
I think they really need me.
What?
You mean "London" as in the real London?
Well of course the real one. Which London
did you think we'd be going to, Nodoka-chan?
I don't know. I thought it might be
the name of a new shop of some kind.
We're all going to talk to a travel
agent tomorrow so we can book the trip.
That's terrific. You know, I had no idea you
all had such a big interest in going to England.
That's interesting outfit, Yui.
It was Mio who came up with the idea of
going there, but Tonchan decided for us.
A turtle decided?
Yeah to keep it fair, but Tonchan decided
that we're going to London, not to England.
Yui.
I hate to break this to you but...
London is in England.
It's all so sudden.
But I'm going to London.
But why all the books?
Because someone's got to be informed about the city.
Take care of my big Sis, okay?
I will, Ui.
Oh and about your big sister,
I get the distinct feeling that
she's hiding something from me.
Do you know what it is?
I honestly don't think Big Sis is
really capable of hiding anything.
You've got a point.
Welcome.
Are you here for a travel consultation?
Uh... yes.
We want to take a 5-day trip to London.
London 3 nights and 5 days?
3? Is she trying to gyp us?
No, we're going to need 2 travel days.
Ooh.  I knew that.  Yeah.
So you'll be wanting a London only tour?
London only?
I think so.
It's fine. There's lots of things to see there.
Let's ride that!
And then visit a tea shop.
Wow, that looks really delicious!
Yeah.  Hey look at that!
And I wanna see the homes of Jimmy
Page and Jimi Hendrix while we're there.
Great idea.
And David Bowie's, too!
Look, music stores!
Abbey Road!
Pardon?
Perhaps you'll want to choose a free
activity package to add to your trip.
No, I don't think we'll need that.
Oh Yes. Perfect! We'll take it!
Good morning!
Hmm? Miss Music Club.
Isn't it cold?
I gather that the Occult Club isn't on vacation yet?
Yes, we're heading up to the roof to see if
we can make contact with any extraterrestrials.
Oh really? The Light Music
Club is taking a trip to England.
Very nice!
Yeah, it's a graduation trip.
You want anything from there?
Yes, Nessie.
Nessie...
Take a photo of Nessie for us.
Right! You got it!
Leave it to me.
Miss Music Club?
So do you think that maybe we
can fit that into our schedule?
You mean Nessie?
Loch Ness is pretty far away.
And I hear Nessie is just a myth, it doesn't really exist.
So that was an Occult Club gag?
How're we supposed to get something like that?
Don't worry about it, Yui.
Okay!
Alright, any more requests for the trip?
Nope! That's it!
Good. Then I'm going to put together
a doable itinerary for us based on these notes I've taken.
You really don't mind doing that?
No. I kind of like this sort of thing.
Thank you.
Would you like some more tea, Azusa?
Oh no, thank you.
I'm feeling pretty full right now.
You know, whenever Azu-nyan makes
schedules, she always leaves out snack time.
I mean, what happened to the "free" in free activity?
Are you going home?
Yes, aren't any of you leaving?
Sure, I'll go home now!
Once we practice having Enlish style "Afternoon Tea".
I think...!
I think, I'll be having another cup of
tea, first. Here's a small gift for you.
Just a little something for the road.
We'll wash the cups, too.
Okay. Thanks a lot for the gift.
Take care, Azusa.
Include snack time, okay?
Sure. See you tomorrow.
Later Azusa!
Okay.
Alright, now we can get down to business.
What business?
She's still here?!
Hey! What gives?
You gotta go too, Sawa-chan.
Here's your parting gift.
Ohho that's right, you don't
you have a date tonight do you?
No! Not that I know of.
Go get one!
Okay!
We need to get a present for Azu-nyan.
So what do we get her?
We always rely on her for everything.
So we need to show her we're grateful,
and we need to do it in our own very special way.
Any ideas?  A play?
No! No more plays.
Ah! Azu-nyan left "Mud Stain" behind!
Oh no! Oh no!
That's "Mustang".
Yours is "Elizabass", right?
Why don't we just ask Mud Stain?
Mud Stain?
What would Azu-nyan like as a present?
I'm kidding!
Mud Stain!
Mud Stain said, "Song!"
Oh no! Did you hit your head?
It said "Zong"?
Not "zong", "song".
"Gong"?
No! "Song"!
"Tang"?
No, listen, I mean it actually said the word "song" to me!
Aw man! Why didn't I think of that before?
Are you saying that we should give Azusa a song?
Ui said, that Azu-nyan really loves the Light
Music Club and the band and all the music we play.
A brand new song for Azusa?
That's just perfect!
It is. A farewell song to Azu-nyan, it's gonna be so cool!
Yes, very cool.
Alright, so what kind of song?
Well, it has to sound real "senior-ly".
With zing, and a whole lot of bang, and boom!
You know?
What do you mean?
In short, it has to be bigger and more
powerful than anything we've ever done before.
For example what?
Boy, I neary forget Mustang.
Good morning everyone!
Just kidding.
Oh Azu-nyan! When did you...?
I just came back.
For how long?
Now.
Oh! Ooh, right! You came back here to get Mud Stain.
Don't be forgetting him.
Um, sorry.
Well, see ya.
Bye-bye!
You're safe and sound.
Azu-nyan?
Oh, no it's nothing. Nothing at all! Whatever am I doing?
Well see ya!
I don't remember ever seeing those four
looking as serious as they looked today.
Something's fishy.
It's Mugi.
At least she's having fun.
Boy, I'm nervous as all heck.
This could really turn out to be a global song.
Big Sis, could you hold this for me?
It's too full.
Why all the Japanese food?
I thought you'd probably miss it.
Why are you taking your school uniform?
Everyone's bringing theirs.
Oh, okay.
Yui? You might need an English
phrase book to help you get around.
Thanks, mom.
And you're also going to need an outlet converter.
Thanks.
More things you gotta pack.
Alright girls, better hurry off to bed now.
Okay!
Tomorrow, I'm going to London.
I'm jealous.
I'd feel better if you were coming along.
But will you fit?
Just kidding.
Stop that, Big Sis!
See you 5 days!
Take care of youself, Big Sis!
I'm going to get something to drink.
Watch my stuff, okay?
Okay!
Rit-chan! Rit-chan! Good morning, Rit-chan!
Morning!
I thought it might look good in
all the photos we'll be taking.
Both you and Mio.
What?
Azusa, too?
Good morning you guys!
Good morning!
So you brought Mustang along, huh?
Sure did. I wasn't really sure, but I
figured Yui would bring hers along on the trip.
I was right.
Yui and Azusa brought them too.
I want any famous musicians that
we might meet there to sign my bass.
Gotcha. Okay, on to Mugi's station.
Did you bring your drums?
You haven't forgotten anything have you?
Oh! I forgot my passport!
Then I guess we're gonna have to leave you behind.
Hey!
It's hanging from your neck.
Sorry, I just couldn't resist.
Good morning, Mugi-chan!
Good morning!
Aw! No fair! I knew I should've brought my keyboard!
Wow!  It sure is big.
Let's go get some tea.
This is cool!
Let's check in our bags first.
Good idea.
I'm terribly sorry.
We have a very full plane and not much carry on space.
I'm afraid that we'll need you check
your instrument bags along with your luggage.
I'll see you in London, Geeta!
This is awesome! We could use one of these at school.
A people walker.
People mover.
I see your legs!
Are all the boyfriend rumors true?
Can you make it official?
Please, just a word, Ms. Kotobuki!
?Moonwalking? Moonwalking?
I'm so excited.
Look!
Wow.
Ritsu! Ritsu!
Shouldn't we get snacks?
They'll feed us soon after we take off.
You know all about this, Azusa.
That's 'cause I read up.
It's like a dream.
When this plane lands and we get
off, we'll be in London, England.
In a totally different country!
Wow! We're really traveling abroad together.
Yeah or maybe into the future or past!
It's a plane not a time machine.
But time will go backwards.
You scared me!
Here. Eye masks for you.
Thanks, Senpai.  Thanks, Mugi-chan.
Time will go backwards?
We're flying against the Earth's
rotation and across time zones.
Does that really make time go backwards?
Yes.
It's time to put on your seatbelt, Senpai.
If we didn't land and just kept going,
would we travel all the way into the past?
No not that far.
Well then how far would we go?
Look we're taking off.
Taking off already?!
Azu-nyan, we're moving!
Whoa! We're so high! Look at the pretty clouds! Woo-hoo!
Azu-nyan, from here on, no Japanese is allowed.
Okay?
Okay, I understand.
Azu-meow.
Huh?
No Japanese.
Geeze.
Azu-meow? What's kinaishoku in English?
In flight meal.
Beef or chicken?
We're practicing.
Give me, chicken.
Yes! Excellent!
And now me! Okay?
Cheers!  Chicken or beef?
The beef, please.
That's excellent.
Ma'am?  Yes?
Now which would you like? Japanese or western?
Azu-nyan! Azu-nyan!
Hey! I should write lyrics for her song.
Upsy daisy.
What's this?
"Worldwide"?
Did you see anything?
Who, me? No.
Um were you trying to write something special?
I was just thinking about how I should live.
It turns out I've really got a lot to think about.
Oh.
What's going on?
is she really hoping to change the band's
direction and totally remake the sound?
Or is she actually flunking out of school and
worried about what's going to happen to her in the future?
Will she become... Big outlaw rocker Yui?!
Nah!
Azu-nyan, wake up!
We're arriving!
England? Is this really England?
Boy the trip here eemed so quick.
We're jet-setters now! We flew
half way around the world in the air!
Take it easy, Yui.
I can't believe we're really here.
We go through immigration next?
What do we do?
Let me see, usually you're asked
your purpose for coming to the country.
Oh! Our purpose?
Yes. Just say that you came
her on vacation to go sightseeing.
Okay.
Side business!
Side business?
Hello.
Y-Yes sir.
Uh... 4 days.
Yes, I am 17.
Oh I really missed you, my Geeta!
When you think about it, why'd we
bring all of our instruments anyway?
Mio, got your luggage yet?
No.
Really?
Don't worry, it'll come.
I guess, it didn't make it?
But why just my bag?
Do you think they might have lost it?
What'll you do without clean panties? As a lady?
But Mio doesn't wear them, does she?
Yes! She wears no panties!
I said I don't wear socks, not panties!
Look! It's over there!
Hey, yeah.
Someone must have set it aside for her.
Right under her nose.
It's such a relief.
Brrrr!
London is really cold.
London sky!
London taxi!
London English!
All of us in London!
Ahem.
Taxi, taxi!
Hello.
'ello.
In London, I'm pretty sure the custom is,
that you have to open the taxi doors yourself.
Wow.
But there's no handle.
I guess maybe the door is automatic.
Why don't we ask the driver?
The door opens the other way. I knew that.
Put your luggage up here in front.
Thank you.
Where to?
Well um, to the hotel Ibis, please.
Yeah, the Ibis. Where abouts?
He's asking where the hotel is, I think.
Where? Well it's right here in London, of course! Right?
London humor?
London city?
Yes!
I'm facing backwards.
Feels weird.
Are you all right, Yui-senpai?
Sorry, Yui. I closed the door before you were ready.
Don't worry, I'm fine.
Mugi-chan's softness saved me from getting hurt.
I'm glad.
Wow, that was a real surprise.
I think it's the first of many.
Welcome to London.
Facing backwards was a bit uncomfortable for me.
Are you okay, Yui?
No sweat, I'll be fine.
Mind if I sit down a minute?
Sure you're okay?
What about dinner?
Dinner?
I'd like roast beef and yorkshire pudding and ice cream.
Huh?! Oh no!
What's wrong?
They don't seem to have our reservation.
We can't stay here?
We have to sleep outside?
What do we do?
May I see that?
Y-Yes, ma'am!
You booking's actually over at the Ibis at Earl's Court.
Ibis Earl's Court?
Correct. This here is the Ibis London City.
We have a number of locations throughout the London area.
I don't get her accent.
Me neither.
Well I do. They have other hotels in the city.
They do?
Our reservation is for the Ibis hotel
that's located in a place called Earl's Court.
Boy that's a big relief.
Thank you very much.
You're welcome. You have yourselves a lovely day.
Let's see... Earl's Court.
Oh! There it is!
Yeah but, we're way over here.
Should we get another taxi? It's awfully far away.
What so Yui can bounce around again?
Don't worry, I'll face backwards!
I know! Why don't we all just take a bus?
Great idea!
You see one, Mio-senpai?
Nothing that goes directly there.
Too bad.
But it looks like we can get there by one subway.
What's wrong, Azu-nyan?
Um... I'm wearing new shoes and they're a little stiff.
Do your feet hurt?
A little.
Got a blister?
You mean all this time?
No. It just started a little while ago.
Then I think we should go buy you some new ones!
No, you've all got to be really tired!
And you're carrying luggage.
Hey, we should go here.
Where? Where?
Here, they sell rock 'n roll wear and accessories.
Lovely.
Okay, Azusa?
It's so cool!
I need to take a picture with with Geeta.
Yui, I'll hold your stuff for you.
So, how do they fit?
They look like they're pretty comfortable.
They are. I'm okay now.
That's wonderful.
They look really good on you, Azu-nyan.
Look there! Suishi!
It's kaiten sushi.
It spins?
Yes.
Mugi, you've never been to one before?
Then, we should go in.
But why in London?
Because it happens to be here in London.
Alright now, let's just see what you guys can do.
London!
Look at this place.
It's like really, really fancy.
The sushi's moving!
It's so strange.
I've a bad feeling.
What's wrong? Is the airport trauma's back?
It's a little different in here from what I expected.
I imagined ballerina-like
sushi spinning around and around.
Look they have a stage.
'ello.
You're the birds from Japan right-o?
I understoof the word "from". And also "Japan".
Y-Yes!
I'm the govenor of this establishment.
You're the ones who'll be songbirding today, right-o?
Um... Uh... Yes!
Very tall!
Welcome to my sushi bar!
Yes.
Would you stop saying "yes" to everything?
I would but he seems happy to see us.
Shall we to work?
Y-Yes.
Wow, I guess in London, they wear
happi coats whenever they eat sushi.
Kind of like the aprons at a Korean barbecue.
Alright loves, time for you to get cracking.
Geeta!
W-What's happening?
Oh my gosh!
Mugi-chan?
Mugi!
Excuse me, please!
Oh good, Mugi-chan must be explaining to
them that we only came here to eat sushi.
Leave it to Mugi to take care of things like...
...wait a second!
What did you do, Mugi?
There wasn't a keyboard up there.
Okay let me handle this.
Hey you!
I am bucho!
We are okyakusan.
Enso , not happening.
Rit-chan, you're speaking to him in mostly Japanese.
Try again! You can do it.
I love sushi.
London is intense.
Rit-chan, he's still looking at us.
You know, I don't think we're gonna get out of doing this.
Well then, we're just gonna have to do it.
Yeah, you're right. They may
not let us eat here otherwise.
This is an awful lot to go through just to get some sushi.
What'll we play?
Yui? What do you think?
Um I...
um...
"Curry, then Rice"?
At a sushi place?
Yeah, there's rice here.
And he looks like a nice person.
Let's go!
Who is that person?
Please don't leave us behind.
Oh gosh, I'm do sorry. I guess
I just got a little pumped up.
I think we'd better hurry, though.
Oh no, Azu-nyan, you sound
like you're about a halftone off.
Wait I need time to tune up.
Never mind, I'll just tune it to you.
Okay.
One, two, one two three four!
Hello. We're After-school Tea Time!
Hurray! Nice!
Thank you! Arigato gozaimashita!
That was brilliant!
Really blinding!
Right!
Thank you! Thank you all.
But uh what about the sushi?
Thank you! You're brilliant, Love Crisis!
That tall man...
what was it he called us again?
I think he said "Love Crisis".
I'm pretty sure I've heard that name before.
Ritsu isn't that your friend's band?
That's right.
I guess that makes them "Love Crisis
of Japan" since they're not here.
I knew it. Revolving things are always bad.
What's more...
I'm really hungry.
Be quiet.
It's too late for that.
I want sushi.
Please give us some.
I-I don't have the guts to go back in there.
Does everyone have to perform before
they're allowed to eat in this country?
Well we may as well get moving and get to our hotel.
I agree.
What is with this stupid sushi place, anyway?
Ritsu? Mio?
Uh yes?
What a surprise! Are you on vacation?
Yes, we're all sightseeing.
You came together.
Yep, we did!
I think my English is really improving.
But they're speaking Japanese.
Maki?!
Love Crisis Japan!
What are you doing here in England!? I'm so confused!
It's so good to see you!
Hey, what's going on?
We just went in there to try out their sushi
but they told us that we had to perform first.
So we went up there and played but
they didn't feed us. Maybe we stunk.
Really? You are kidding!
We're booked to perform here tonight
to celebrate their big grand opening.
I get it now! They mistook us for Love Crisis!
Mugi-chan, nice deduction.
Remember Ms. Kawakami?
You mean from the music club?
Yeah. She recommended us to these guys for this gig.
It turns out she's good friends with the manager here.
I know it's a small world but what are the odds?
Wow, it's kind of trippy.
Wait, we've got a problem, they
think you guys played the gig already.
Oh man, you're right. We'll go talk to them.
Okay. See ya.
See ya. Bye.
They're so cool.
They are.
Oh boy, we finally, got checked in.
At last, it's just the two of us, right Azu-nyan?
Yeah, it's been a tiring day.
I'm really hungry and I want to take a nice hot bath.
Yes, I know. It was really cold.
What are we gonna do about dinner tonight?
This, huh?
Thank you, Ui!
We'll need to bring her back a really nice present.
Aw look, we're gonna need a microwave for this one.
So what were you guys doing in here before we came over?
Taking photos, of course.
In school uniforms?
Well that's why we brought them, silly.
Whatever makes you happy, Ritsu.
Yeah, well you changed quickly, too, Mio.
Ah, that felt great.
Oh wow, Ui is always so prepared.
That's my little sister.
What's wrong?
It blew fire at me.
Scary!  Yui, you need to use a power converter.
No. I'm way too scared now.
Let's just eat dinner.
Azu-nyan, I flunked my senior year!
Now you and I get to be classmates!
Oh no!
Wait a minute, does that mean
you're not my senpai anymore?
No way. Consider us equals now!
Really?
Mhm.
No formalities?
Nope, we're both the same now!
Stop that, Yui! Please!
What? Just like that?
It just all seems really strange.
It may seem pretty strange to you right
now, but you'd better get used to it.
We're classmates now. We're classmates now.
Huh?
What's this?
Yui's scaring me.
Good night.
What a relief.
There's something that I really want
to see since we're here in England.
Ritsu used it in the school play.
Oh, that grave, right?
Wow! The Occult Club's replica was really accurate.
What passion.
This is a replica, too.
We've walked so much.
Let's rest a bit.
Well there should be a tearoom somewhere near by here.
Afternoon tea! That's the heart
and soul of The Light Music Club!
I can't believe you need a reservation.
It's so big!
It's revolving.
Revolving.
I think we should ride it!
Come on, Mugi-chan! You too Mio-chan?
No, I think I'll just stay here
and keep and eye on everyone's stuff.
You guys go ahead and have fun.
Mio?
Mio-chan.
Aw come on, chicken.
No! I don't want to go on anything that's revolving!
It's okay. We'll all be with you.
Get a grip, Mio-chan.
Nothing revolving!
Wow look at that!
I can see all of London!
Mio-chan's sure enjoying herself.
Yep, you really can't see something
revolve if you're riding on it.
This is awesome!
Where's my camera?
Hey, Mio, I'll hold your stuff for you!
Hey Rit-chan, look over there!
Mugi, would you mind holding this for me, for a minute?
No problem.  Wow this is delicious.
It's so delicious.
See ya later.
G'night!
I think I'll join them.
But you're with me, Azu-nyan.
I'm home!
I'm sorry! Are you all right, Yui?!
But you see... I'm- I'm just not like that!
Not like what?
I was just going to hug and kiss my Geeta.
What?
Forgive me! I had the wrong idea! I'm so sorry!
That's okay. I guess the self-defense
book Ui gave me a few weeks ago came in handy.
Huh? Going to bed already?
I guess you're really tired.
Shall I sing you a lullaby?
I'm so sorry.
All right that's enough. We're not here
to sit around looking at photos all night.
Well then, has anyone come up
with a concept for Azusa's song?
Not a thing yet.
I expected London to inspire a powerful song.
At least an idea for one.
Like ?Big Ben! The London Eye! The Thames River!?
Like that.
Yui, you're just reciting the famous sites in a big voice.
I know, but I just really want to
write the absolute best song ever.
Something that will be remembered forever and will
energize people who hear it long after we're all gone.
Yes, an eternal classic.
Eternal, huh?
What?
I just realized I forgot my room key back in my room.
Can't you just enter from there?
That's strange.
A candy trail can be useful after all.
Alright, goodnight everybody,
I'm going back to Azu-nyan now.
You're dropping your candy, you know.
That's alright, you can have it. Enjoy.
Good night, Yui.
Good night.
She's so scattered.
Who could it be at this hour?
The peep hole's too high!
Put everything away! It's Azusa!
Coming! Welcome!
Evening.
Azusa?
What's up?
Sorry to disturb you.
We got big trouble!
Big trouble! Big trouble!
Calm down, Yui.
Azu-nyan's missing!
She was just here.
But she went back to your room.
She what?
Something is very wrong, Senpai!
She's awake.
Yui-senpai is gone!
Rit-chan, she's really missing!
Big trouble, big trouble!
Big trouble, Azu-nyan!
Azu-nyan's gone missing!
Wait, you're here.
Where'd you go? I was so worried about you!
Um... well...
It's the phone.
Who is it?
Front desk maybe?
At this hour?
Maybe the call's from Japan?
But it's only 6 a.m. in Japan.
Yui's really got the time difference down.
Yes uh, hello?
Yes? Oh yes I understand, of course.
A killer what?!
What do you know? They hung up before I could answer it.
I wonder who it was?
I'm sure if it's really important,
they'll try calling us again.
Yes, that's true.
An eternal song.
Wait a minute, does that mean
you're not my senpai anymore?
Azu-nyan?
Must be dreaming.
Senpai, you really should blink once in a while.
A song for Azu-nyan.
Hello.
Would you stop staring at me?
It's annoying.
Oops, now she's mad.
I just can't think of anything good for a song.
I really have to dump that phrase.
That's lame.
Yui-senpai!
We're leaving in just a few minutes!
Azu-nyan!
Now this is London.
Oh look, they've got Yui's guitar!
Hey, yeah they do!
A song for Azu-nyan. I need something really big.
Big, ?big, very big.?
That's so lame.
A cool song for Azu-nyan.
A song as cool as London itself.
It's Ms. Kawakami.
How's it going? Doing good?
Hey I'm next. Alright?
Maki called me today and told me that
you guys are over there in London, too?
That's right.
Good, then I have a favor to ask.
There's going to be an event introducing
Japanese pop culture over there.
Love Crisis and Black Frill will be performing at it.
Can I ask you guys to perform too?
Wait pop corn?
Perform.
It's tomorrow afternoon.
Will you still be there?
Ah, yeah.
Excellent, I'll email you all the details later.
She's introducing us as an
all-girls' high school music group.
I'm curious.
Does email from Japan have to be sent into the
past in order to get here when its suppose to?
But here in London it's today, and
back home in Japan, it's tomorrow already.
Yeah, but...
What are we going to do?
This is all so sudden.
That means the email we send from
here is being sent into the future!
Yui-senpai, this is really getting
confusing. Could you please be quiet?
Should we refuse?
But I really want to perform.
Don't you?
I'm not sure but this seems like a stroke of luck.
I mean it! It'll be okay! Not like
when we played at that sushi place.
But Yui-senpai that's not what we're worried about.
I want to do it, too!
Okay!
Then let's tell Ms. Kawakami.
Come on, hurry up, Azu-nyan!
Okay!
Press "Send"!
There goes our email into the future!
We're suppose to go home tomorrow.
Oh, yeah that's right.
Will we be able to make the flight?
What time do we need to be there?
We need to be at the airport by 5 o'clock.
According to this the show is at 4.
Then we're okay!
No problem.
Is that a peace sign?
Mhm. Peace. Peace.
Yui-senpai's "no problem" sounds very dangerous to me.
I translated a song into English for tomorrow.
What?  We're singing in English?
For an international audience.
You sure about this?
How did you translate it?
Check it out...
"Gohan wa sugoi yo" is "Rice is super."
Very direct translation.
"Goes with anything" Huh?
The word "Batchiri" just fit!
Yeah but "batchiri" is a Japanese word.
"Mushiro rice is a nice side dish"
"Mushiro" is "not so much A as B" ryme.
I guess technically you're right.
Not so much A "Azu-nyan".
Wait a minute, rice is not so much
a main dish as it is a side dish.
But isn't rice suppose to be a main dish sometimes?
Oh yeah, I guess you're right.
Whatever. Just move on.
I just had a flash! About Azu-nyan's song. What was it?
And it felt like a major discovery, too.
You mean you're not my senpai anymore?
Didn't sleep well, Azu-nyan?
No, I kept having really strange dreams about you all not.
Really? Dreams about me?
Yeah, very, very strange dreams.
I'm not telling, though.
Wait just a second.
What is it, Mugi-chan?
Mugi-chan!
Wait a minute, is that your keyboard?
You all brought your instruments so I just thought...
I really envy the rich.
Now we're a complete band again!
It still looks so huge.
And it's still revolving.
That must be the place.
Where do we go?
Look, they have a yakisoba stand!
How much you want to bet we won't be able to eat any.
Hey, Maki!
Yo, Ritsu!
So what time are you guys going on?
We're going up at 3:30
That's right before we go on.
When does Black Frill go on?
They go on at 4?
But I thought we were suppose to go on at 4?
Mhm that's right.
Rit-chan, did we make a mistake?
No mistake, that's when you're on.
Our band and Black Frill are going to be
performing over there at the indoor stage.
And you guys are gonna be
performing over on the outdoor stage.
Outdoor?
Not here.
But here?
What a great view.
This is great! It'll be like a dream performing here.
I thought we were getting the shaft being
sent outside, but I think this is a lot better.
Hi. After School Tea Time?
Yes?
Could you get your kits set up now, please?
Say what?
He wants for us to set up out instruments.
Are we sure I can plug this in?
Will it spew flames at me?
Well of course it won't, it's
perfectly safe to plug it in. Right Mio?
Oh man, I've got a bad feeling about this.
You too, Senpai?
Do you think I can ask someone before I do it?
Wait, you mean one of the visitors?
Yui, you want me to call one of the show staff?
Just plug the damn thing in!
Geeta!
Owie
Think about it, that guitar
wasn't even made in Japan, was it?
Are you a spirit?
Why're you here?
I'm not a ghost! What's the matter with you?
Why are you in London?
Honeymoon?
I had some free miles to us.
I have to use the miles I racked up
last year from using my credit card,
before they expire and I lose them for good.
Plus, I am the Light Music Club adviser.
When'd you get here?
Yesterday morning.
And returning?
Tonight.
I really envy adults.
You should've told us you were coming here.
I called your hotel the other
night but you guys didn't answer.
Oh, that was you, Sawa-chan.
Oh! And I brought some costumes for the show!
They're Japanese lady ninjas!
"Kunoichi"?!
Wow! Bravo! Bravo!
Please don't do that.
Look. Look!
It's Nodoka!
Ui, too?
And Jun!
No, thanks.
Alright, we're on standby, girls.
Thanks everybody! We had a blast here in London!
It really was the bees knees!
Did I say that that right?
Yui, hurry up, we've got a plane to catch.
Oh!
Now for our last song.
"Rice is a Sidedish"!
One two three four!
After all that... She's singing in Japanese.
She switched to English.
Senpai.
Sky high!
What was with that "sky high" bit all about?
I just got really excited. And that baby was so cute.
I agree with Yui-senpai about the baby but...
You mean the one sitting in front?
I knew we'd be rushing to the airport!
I wanted to end our concert in real style!
Hey taxi!
She's asleep.
She's earned it. She's worked really hard being
our information guide the whole time we've been here.
She must be exhausted.
Is that snow?
Oh wow it is!
You know, I just realized something amazing.
We can just write one of our usual songs for her.
Yeah well it took you long enough.
That's what I've been thinking, too, Yui.
You too, Mugi-chan?
I realized it ages ago.
Nodoka-chan, go ahead and take whatever you like.
There's like 10 years worth here.
She never did get the chance
to have afternoon tea in London.
Aw that's too bad.
Yeah, I know.
But you got to play your music, right?
I wish I could've been there to see it.
It was such a blast.
Your whole class said they
wished they could've been there.
Really?
Yui, I heard you rocked out in London.
Yeah, how was it?
What did you play?
"Rice is a Sidedish"!
"Say what?"
That's right, Ichigo!
I'd really like to hear you guys play one more time.
Any chance that'll happen?
The Jazz Club's doing a graduation concert.
Really?!
Great idea!
We didn't think of that?
Come on let's do it.
Alright! Where?
The club room?
This is great! Think we can make some requests?
A concert in class?
That's right on the last day of school.
You know a final memory of high school.
I did something just like that when I was...
No way! You'll bother all the other
classes with the noise you'll make.
The choir and wind orchestra don't
even perform in their classroom, okay?
What the heck's gotten into you, Sawa-chan?
You can't expect me to keep giving
you special treatment, understand?
It's final!
The answer is no!
We hear you, Sawa-chan.
Good, I'm glad I made my point.
See you tomorrow.
I remember we got in a lot of
trouble for playing in class.
And we played really hard rock,
not like the music those girls play.
Their music is all fluff.
I doubt they could handle the scolding we got.
They'd be crushed.
I have to protect them!
Make sure your corsages are finished by tomorrow.
Okay.
Azusa, lend me some scissors.
Sure. Here you go.
Thank you.
Azusa?
Hm? What?
You do really funny things.
Oh my gosh. No, I didn't do that!
Ui, look what Azusa did!
What did she do?
Geeze, that wasn't me.
Hi!
A live show in the classroom?
Yeah. We'll be doing it in our own classroom so...
the four of us were thinking that it would just...
be the four of us performing.
Absolutely not.
Cause I want to perform too.
What you do?
Yes.
It'll be the last time that I'll be able to perform
with you guys in front of everyone that we know.
Together here at school.
I'm so glad.
Thank you, Azu-nyan!
So when is this big live show going to happen?
It's here. The last day of school.
And I am going to protect those girls!
I think we'll need another row.
On the desks?
Yeah, we'll wipe them off later.
Oh, these guys are cool!
You're early today, Ms. Yamanaka.
Well I- I have a lot to do before school's out.
What's all the sound?
That? Perhaps they're doing construction.
Well that's pretty lively construction if you ask me.
Like heck it is. I knew you had to be up to
something to be here this early in the day!
No, wait!
Live show?
Oh cool! Let's go see!
Okay, this next song will be our last one.
Mornig.
I wish we could do this everyday!
No, please! Wait!
Out of the question.
They'll be done by the time homeroom starts. I promise!
Let go of me!
Could you take a picture and send it to me?
Okay.
Unlike you guys long ago, they're cute and they play well.
Well, all that's left to do is to finish Azu-nyan's song.
All that's left? That's the most important thing.
Oh yeah, I came up with a melody.
Let's hear it.
Mugi, this is amazing.
We just have to put some lyrics to it and it's done.
Yeah.
I can't believe how much time we've
spent with Azu-nyan these past two years.
She's our biggest treasure.
Let's use that.
See you tomorrow.
Bye!  Later.
Dinner's ready!
What?
You've really grown.
Really?
Is it done?
It's all done.
That's great. Just in time.
Yui, you kept this quiet right?
You haven't let on to Azusa?
I haven't said a word. I haven't even told Ui.
You know what?
No. What?
The girls are acting strange.
Something's going on.
Yeah well, they've always been strange.
That's not what I mean.
So  how're they strange?
Whenever I walk in, they suddenly
stop everything they're doing.
That is strange.
When I try to ask them about it,
they look away and change the subject.
They're probably communicating with aliens.
No way.
Or they're eating lots of candy behind
your back and they don't want you to know.
I wouldn't put it past them.
It's like they're hiding something.
Hey, Ui? You don't suppose...
Yui's planning to stay back a year, do you?
No of course not.
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm positive. She's buying tights for graduation.
I see.
I know, maybe she didn't get into a college.
Huh?!  No, she got in.
Then what is it?
Don't worry about it, Azusa-chan.
Even so... we all still met
and you were so wonderful.
There's still something missing with these lyrics.
Big Sis, can I come in?
Yes.
Wait!
Hold on a sec!
Okay, come in.
Big Sis, you'll get guitar lines on your face again.
Oh yeah, thanks.
I hate it when that happens.
So are you ready for tomorrow? It's a big day.
Yup.
It's graduation at last.
Better get to bed.
You, too, Ui.
Ui?
What?
Thank you.
Don't worry, I can graduate on my own.
Right!
Well, good night then.
Good night, Sis.
Oh by the way, Ui?
What, Sis?
Once I'm in college,
we can still get together for tea, right?
Well yeah. Of course we can.
Really? I'm so glad.
Well, good night, Big Sis. Sleep tight.
Good night.
Even so we all still met
a wonderful kitten girl.
Come on! Come on!
Wait up!
Hurry up!
Yui!
It was open!
Hey, Rit-chan?
You think we'll play this well?
I don't think I've ever been this
nervous as I am right now in my life.
Me, too.
My hands are so cold.
They are.
This is nerve-wracking.
Oh no!
Should we call it off?
No way!
What will Azusa think?
She'll be thrilled, of course!
I'm relieved that everyone's so nervous about this.
Who wouldn't be?
"Give Me Wings" was the very first
song I ever heard you guys play.
And that's how the Light Music Club got started.
And then Azusa joined us.
And provided a really big boost.
Azusa's "cutting" always keeps everything so sharp.
While Yui always goes for power.
Look who's talking.
You know what?
It was Azu-nyan who gave us our wings so we could fly.
She's a cute little angel who brought warmth, and
love and happiness to all of us for the past two years.
An angel?
You know, you may be right.
What?
What do you think?
Perfect!
Don't you think it's a little corny?
No, I think it's just right!
Maybe this song will become Azu-nyan's wings.
It will!
At least, I hope.
It will! Because it's packed to the brim...
with all of our love for Azusa!
I just really hope she likes it.
Shall we have tea?
Sounds good.
Sure.
I'll take a sweet dumpling.
Those rock!
Oh! This one's for Azu-nyan.
So, how are we gonna do this?
As leader, I'll walk up and say,
"Azusa, there's a song I want you to hear."
Next comes Mugi.
"We all worked together and wrote it for you."
I hope I don't flub it.
Well, you'd better not laugh, Mugi-chan.
Wait a second.
Whenever we discuss this we always...
Oh, Azusa.
Excuse me.
I thought that maybe I'd make tea for you today.
Well, you can't.
Azu-nyan, can you come here?
I see now.
I think Azu-nyan really liked her song.
Yeah!
Huh? Are those tears I see, Mio?
No, I just have a runny nose that's all.
After all, who's got time to cry, Mio?
That's right. We're all happy college students now.
What optimists you guys are.
You know, we're going to have to start
eating more mature snacks with our tea.
Correct!
Nothing changes.
Ah, Mio's recovered.
Did you guys realize that the Death Devil
song we played, was also written as a farewell?
You're kidding!
Whoa, different tastes, I guess.
I guess that means we just carried on an old tradition.
By total coincidence.
So where do we go next year?
Next year?
For Azu-nyan's graduation trip.
Are we going?
Why not?