[music playing]
GENMA: The winner is Temari.
-Huh, what the--
-Uh, man, I'm beat.
Ugh, what a waste!
Why?
What is he thinking?
Doesn't he want to be a chuunin?
-What can you say?
It's Shikamaru.
-I wonder, do you think he
has the motivation for this?
-I've wondered that same
thing myself so many times.
KURENAI (VOICEOVER):
Even so, his tactics
and ingenuity are far beyond
those of your typical genin.
If that had been a real mission
and he'd been leading a squad,
he would have succeeded.
The battle was won
the moment he caught
Temari in that
shadow possession.
I guess you could say he won
the battle, but lost the match.
ASUMA (VOICEOVER):
That boy's lack
of drive can sure
be frustrating.
Still, there's
something to be said
for not having a
killer instinct.
It means he never lets his
emotions cloud his judgment.
He never panics.
He's able to calmly assess
his tactical situation
and determine the
wisest course of action.
He even has the
wisdom to retreat
if his position is untenable.
He has something a lot of
the others lack, clarity.
That's a vital trait in a
chuunin and in a leader.
-He may not be as motivated
as some of the others,
but, you know, it's not such
a bad thing for a squad leader
to trust his head
more than his gut.
He'll get in a lot
less trouble that way.
-You said it.
A squad with a
hotshot for a leader
is a squad that's not
going to survive very long.
Some of these kids
don't understand
there's not much point
in completing a mission
if your whole team
gets wiped out.
That's not what being
a chuunin is about.
-If you're scoring them
on that, Naruto and Neji
failed the test.
Not that they don't
have talent for a genin.
Still, I can't help feeling
Shikamaru gave up too soon.
What do you think?
-Well, one thing
I'm sure of, he's
got a lot better chance
than that Naruto kid.
-(OUTRAGED): What
the heck was that?
Forfeiting the match
when he had it won!
Geez!
Uh!
Man, that really ticks me off.
That lazy son of a-- I'm going
to give him a piece of my mind.
-And to think that lazy
kid's going to be a chuunin.
-Hey, I want to talk
to you, you idiot!
-(NONCHALANTLY): Eh, who are
you calling an idiot, idiot!
-Why'd you give up?
Are you really that lazy?
Or, are you just a big chicken?
-Hey.
It's over.
Let's just forget it.
OK?
NARUTO: Are you kidding?
No!
It's not OK.
You had that match won--
-Would you skip it?
NARUTO: --and I
want to know why.
-Are you forgetting?
There's another match.
NARUTO: What kind
of guy does that?
I mean to quit right
when-- huh, another match?
-Huh!
Yeah, that's right!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Dancing
leaf, squirming sand.
AUDIENCE 1: (EXCITED) HA!
At last!
This is the one we've
been waiting for.
Uchiha's next!
AUDIENCE 2: Yeah, but who's this
so Gaara guy he's up against?
don't know.
He's a mystery.
But he doesn't stand a chance
against this Uchiha kid.
[laughing]
Don't get too excited.
I heard that Sasuke Uchiha
had to pull out of the match.
AUDIENCE 1: What!
No way!
AUDIENCE 2: They
he's still injured
from some accident that
happened in training.
AUDIENCE 1: (ANNOYED)
That's perfect .
So you're telling me
I came all this way
and missed two days
of work for nothing.
AUDIENCE 3: (IMPATIENTLY)
Come on Uchiha!
Let's go!
AUDIENCE 4: Well,
it seems fairly
clear this Uchiha
is bound to win.
-I wouldn't be so sure.
I like the look of this
stranger from the Sand village.
I'm putting my money
on the mystery man.
[laughing]
-That's the thing about
this level of competition.
The only thing you
know for sure is
that you never know
what will happen,
CROWD (IMPATIENTLY): Come on!
Ah!
What are you keeping
us waiting for?
OK, we're here.
We paid!
Where's Uchiha?
Where's-- Sometime
this week, OK?
Come on!
Come on.
We waited so long.
-Lord Hokage, I'm afraid there's
still no sign of Sasuke Uchiha.
He hasn't arrived at the arena.
-Right.
Then, we have no choice.
We'll just have to proceed.
We've kept these good
people waiting long enough.
KAZEKAGE: 10 more minutes.
-Uh.
-Huh?
-Surely, we can give
him another 10 minutes.
This is what the crowd's
been waiting for.
It would be a cruel
blow to cancel.
They might even turn ugly.
After waiting this long, surely
another 10 minutes won't hurt.
-Uh, Lord Hokage?
[booing]
-There is something in what Lord
Kazekage says, I must admit.
Very well then, we'll give
Sasuke another 10 minutes
to appear before
canceling the match.
Go.
Tell Genma my decision.
-Right.
GENMA (VOICEOVER): Looks
like Sasuke is out of luck.
Too bad.
Would have been a good match.
-Lord Hokage wants to
wait 10 more minutes.
GENMA (VOICEOVER): I see,
a 10 minute reprieve, huh?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Sasuke.
-Hey!
Is that who I think it is?
-Yeah.
Yeah, it's him all right.
-Uh!
Man, I swear if he doesn't
show, I'll kill him.
I swear I'll kill him.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Come on, Sasuke.
Come on.
-Welcome, glad you
both could make it.
-Yeah, what a surprise!
Go right on in.
-Roger!
-Hm, well Lee, ready to go?
-Yes, sir!
-You've missed most
of the first round.
The only match left is between
Sasuke Uchiha and that Gaara
kid.
-Huh?
But what happened
with Naruto and Neji?
-Well, that was the
most amazing thing.
The Hyuga kid actually got beat.
-Uh!
ROCK LEE (VOICEOVER):
Naruto beat Neji?
That is something.
Well done, Naruto!
Congratulations!
GUY (VOICEOVER): Lee will always
be a winner where it counts,
in his heart.
[booing]
CROWD (IMPATIENTLY): We
came here to see a fight!
Boo!
-Temari, what's going on?
What's up?
Is he really not going to show?
GAARA: He'll be here.
-Huh?
CROWD (IMPATIENTLY): Sasuke!
You suck!
Boo!
Come on how long--
-He'll definitely be here.
[booing]
-Man, this crowd'll tear him
apart if he doesn't show.
And if they don't, I will!
-Where the hell is Uchiha?
How does he expect them to wait?
[laughing]
-Perhaps his injuries
really were serious.
Perhaps he's lost his nerve.
It doesn't matter to me, if he
forfeits, I still win my bet.
GENMA (VOICEOVER): 30 seconds.
[booing]
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Hurry, Sasuke.
Hurry!
-What's he thinking?
I bet he's planning some
big entrance or something.
Well, I'm not going
to be impressed.
GENMA (VOICEOVER): Time's up.
So that's that.
All right, the time
limit has expired.
So I'm, officially,
calling this match--
[wind blowing]
-I told you he'd come.
-Sorry, we're late.
You wouldn't
believe the traffic.
-And you are?
-I'm Sasuke Uchiha.
I'm Sasuke Uchiha.
-(RELIEVED) Ah, Sasuke!
-So he made it in time. -Hm?
-(HAPPILY) Ah!
Rock Lee!
AUDIENCE 5 (VOICEOVER):
Finally, Uchiha!
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
Damn, what a show off!
Making us all wait around like
he was emperor of the universe.
-Huh!
So you decided to
show up after all.
I was betting you wouldn't
come cause, sooner or later,
you'd have to face me.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
Naruto was just
saying how he was sure
Sasuke would come.
-So what about you?
Did you win?
-You know it!
-Huh.
Well, don't get too
full of yourself.
You're still a loser.
-Sorry if we kept you waiting,
but, um, how late are we?
I mean, it's not
like Sasuke is, well,
disqualified or anything, right?
-Like master, like
pupil, even down
to your lousy sense of time.
-Well, what about it?
-You know, you were so late
that we extended the deadline
for you, twice in fact.
And it's lucky for you we
did because you just made it.
No, he's not disqualified.
-Oh, that's a relief!
You had me worried
there for a minute.
So we're OK.
Hm?
-Just make sure you
don't lose to this guy.
-Got it.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): Don't worry.
You're one of the ones I
want to fight the most.
-Hey, Sasuke!
Don't lose cause I want
to fight you myself.
-Got it.
[cheering]
-Woohoo Sasuke!
Yay!
CHOJI (VOICEOVER):
Huh, a minute ago,
she was cheering just
as loud for Shikamaru.
Geez, women are fickle.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): So,
I'm yesterday's news already.
Well, I can't say I blame them.
I'm looking forward
to this one myself.
-Sakura, what's it like to
be on such an amazing team?
-What do you mean?
-You know.
First, Naruto surprises everyone
by beating Neji Hyuga, oh,
and then you've got Sasuke
whose like the superstar.
Everyone wants to see his match.
You're like the All-Star team.
ROCK LEE (VOICEOVER):
Sasuke is fighting
that Sand ninja Gaara, whom
I was powerless against,
and Naruto won
against Neji, whom
I'd always wanted to defeat.
And all I get to do is
stand here and watch.
It's so frustrating.
GUY (VOICEOVER): Ah, Lee
KAZEKAGE (VOICEOVER):
Huh, at last.
-All right, Gaara,
come down here.
-Come on Naruto.
They don't need us here.
-Oh.
Uh.
SHIKAMARU: Let's go.
And I'm going to take the stairs
this time if you don't mind.
-Come on, are you still upset
that I gave you a little push!
You ought to be grateful.
[heavy breathing]
TEMARI (VOICEOVER):
This isn't good.
He's got that look again.
-OK, listen.
Gaara, don't let him
throw off the plan.
-Now's not the time
to talk to him,
not unless you want to
get yourself killed.
-Huh?
Hey, let's go.
NARUTO: Will you hurry up.
Come on!
SHIKAMARU: Relax Naruto.
You're going to give
yourself an ulcer.
-Huh?
-What is it?
Heh?
-You puny kids think this
tournament is about you,
but it's really about the people
who bet on you, or against you
in your case.
You see, our master's got a
lot of money on the other guy
to win.
-Got it.
That means you got to lose.
-Well, so what's
it going to be kid?
-Maybe he's too scared to talk.
-Huh!
[heavy breathing]
[screaming]
[gasp]
THUG (DESPERATELY): No!
Please no!
No!
[screaming]
[exhale] If we'd have
come up the stairs even
a second earlier, that
could have been us just now.
I have never in my life
seen anyone kill like that
without even batting an eye.
Things don't look so good
for your friend at all.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Sasuke.
-OK.
Here we are at last.
[music playing]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): What in
the world is Gaara's deal?
I've never seen that kind
of look in a person's eye.
I'm not even sure he's human.
Sasuke doesn't know
what he's getting into.
He didn't see what we just saw.
I've got to find Kakashi Sensei.
I've got stop this fight.
Next time, Bushy Brow's
Jutsu, Sasuke's Style.
Oh man, Sasuke's about to wish
he never showed up at all.