[music playing]
[theme music]
TSUNADE: Your next mission
is for the daughter
of an affluent feudal lord
who's looking for a body double.
I don't know where
she heard about you,
but it turns out you're
her spitting image.
She was pretty adamant,
said she wouldn't
work with anyone else but you.
-So a body double, huh?
Is this princess being
targeted by someone or what?
-I think it's more
accurate to say
she's the one doing
the targeting.
-OK.
-Well, anyway, I'm
sure you'll do fine.
You're one of the
best and brightest
we have in the Leaf Village.
Besides you'll have
someone to assist you.
-Assist me?
[door opening]
Huh?
-Hey!
Grandma Tsunade!
I hear you've got a mission for
me-- helping some feudal lord?
[screaming]
-Lady Tsunade!
-It's the best I could do.
Everyone else in
the village is busy.
[screaming]
-(ANGRILY) You mean I
have to be alone with him?
-Afraid so.
Just try to make
the best of it, OK?
NARUTO: The client is the
daughter of a feudal lord.
Oh, man, I must really be
coming up in the world for them
to trust me with a big
mission like this one.
-Yeah, well, I wouldn't whoop
it up too much if I were you.
You have a gift for
screwing things up.
[laughing]
-Don't even sweat it.
This will be a piece of cake.
You just leave everything to me.
-You really are a piece of work.
[sighing]
[music playing]
NARUTO: "Ino Screams!
Chubby Paradise!"
PRINCESS: My thanks to
you for coming from afar.
INO (VOICEOVER):
That's the client?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Well, they
do sort of look alike, but--
INO AND NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
There's one big difference.
[laughing]
-I know.
You don't have to say a word.
I see it written
all over your faces.
You're thinking my
physique doesn't exactly
match up to that
of my body double.
Right?
It's all right.
You can admit it.
-Oh, uh, not at all-- we, um--
-To be honest, lady, I don't
think you two look anything
alike.
-Zip it!
-It's all right.
I don't blame you.
I think this will
clear things up.
-Huh?
NARUTO: Oh man!
Ino, it's you!
-That's how I've always
looked until a short time.
But I plumped out like this
when Father hired a matchmaker.
They're brokering an
arranged marriage for me.
NARUTO AND INO: You're kidding!
-My prospective husband is
Chikara from the Land of Udon.
Ever since I first laid eyes
on his manly photograph,
my feelings for him have
grown deeper and deeper
with every passing day.
With our first meeting almost
here, I've been a wreck.
My heart won't stop pounding.
My cheeks are as red as beets.
It's gotten so I can't
even sleep at night.
[hungrily eating]
And with all the stress,
I've been eating just
about anything I
can get my hands on.
-Well, of course you got fat.
What did you think
was going to happen?
-Of course, I've already taken
appropriate counter measures.
I'm taking a special
supplement, which
reduces carbohydrate intake.
Easy Peasy Slim SP.
-I'm guessing it
didn't work too well.
-I should have known better.
And now look at me.
How can I ever meet the man of
my dreams looking like this?
So that's where you come in.
Here's the plan.
Tomorrow, you're going to
take my place at our meeting
and do whatever you
have to to make sure
that darling man
wants to marry me!
[screaming]
-So the whole reason
you hired a body
double was just for this
meeting or whatever it is?
-What do you mean?
What's the matter with that?
-Well, you know, when you
hear the words body double,
you're thinking of a situation
where lives are on the line.
-What are you talking about?
The Princess's entire
life is at stake here.
This is major.
-Oh, thank goodness.
So you can appreciate
a heart in love.
-Are you kidding me?
What woman doesn't?
A girl always wants to look
good for the man she yearns for.
-Even if she's a fake?
-Oh, get over it, would you?
It's not our fault
you men prefer
girls who are fit and trim.
Huh?
-You know just what
I'm going through.
I'm counting on you.
-It will all be fine.
Leave it to me.
-Well, even if this little
meet and greet works out,
he's still going
to see you later.
-Don't worry.
By the time the
wedding rolls around,
I'll have lost all
this extra weight.
I have a plan for
getting my figure back.
Substitution slender!
It's the dietary aide I'll be
replacing all three meals with!
-I guess exercising is
out of the question.
-Rest easy, Princess.
Once I've worked all
my magic on this guy,
he'll only have eyes for you.
PRINCESS: I used to
always come and play
in this annex
during my childhood.
If I hide in here, I
can use these pipes
to listen in on any
conversation in the house.
-Wow.
That must be pretty convenient.
-But I would give anything
just to meet him in person.
NARUTO: Why?
What's the deal?
Is he really that big of prize?
[giggling]
NARUTO AND INO: OK.
-(HAPPILY) Well,
of course he is!
There's nobody else like
him in the whole wide world!
Now, look, just make sure
that he falls for me, OK?
-You're in excellent hands.
I thought you weren't
feeling motivated.
NARUTO: Well, hey, a
mission's a mission, right?
All I can do is hold
my nose and plunge in.
-Just stick to the
plan, though, OK?
[gasping]
Huh?
[music playing]
-What the heck is this?
-The music is getting louder.
[music playing]
-Huh?
-It's so bright.
-Uh?
[dinging]
-The world abounds
with handsome men,
and yet there's one
who towers over all.
-His glistening side-long
glances follow the Land of Udon
like the sun!
-Worship at the foot of the
glorious Prince Chikara!
-Bow before his Majesty!
[music playing]
-Sorry.
It appears I kept you
waiting, Princess.
-This is the man I'm
supposed to win over?
-That guy's an even bigger
loon than Guy Sensei is!
PEOPLE (IN BACKGROUND): Hiza!
Hiza!
NARUTO: Oh boy.
-Huh?
[music playing]
-I'm so sorry,
pretty lady, but I
suffer from a little
low blood pressure.
-I don't think low blood
pressure's his problem.
[screaming]
[laughing]
-What?
-Do you always scatter flower
pedals wherever you go?
-Flowers are a blessing.
So relaxing for
the mind and body.
Wouldn't you agree, Princess?
-Yeah, sure, I guess.
-All righty, what's
say we begin?
[snapping]
-(WHISPERING) I don't get it.
This guy's not really living
up to the picture she painted.
I mean, he's a nor--
-Come again.
-Shut it!
These sweets are enormously
delicious, aren't they?
[laughing]
Excuse us for a moment.
[running]
NARUTO: What the heck was that?
-A woman's intuition.
He seems a bit like Choji.
You were about to head
into taboo territory.
-I got you.
-Oh, for crying out loud.
She told us he
would be handsome!
That's not exactly how I'd
describe Casanova back there.
-Yeah, but, they're kind
of perfect for each other.
-There's got to be
some mistake here.
No woman in her right mind
would fall for that giant tub.
-I don't know.
Maybe she's into that.
[groaning]
-That's impossible!
Just look at him!
He's a stuck up,
overweight, Lothario!
He's a freak!
A goon!
Something isn't
right around here!
Do you read me?
Do you?
-Uh, yeah, I think I got it.
PRINCESS: What are you saying?
Of course it's Chikara.
Don't be silly.
Who else would it be?
That darling man means
everything to me.
-I thought so.
[sighing]
-He's the paragon of elegance.
I wish that I could
see him in person
with these two eyes of mine.
-What are you going to do?
We've all got problems, right?
-(ANGRILY) Look!
Just do what you have to
do to seal the deal, OK?
Now, quit your complaining
and tell her to get to work.
-You got it.
I'll go get us back on track.
-Still feeling a tad
nervous, are you?
Well, how about a little
music to lighten the mood?
-Uh, no, that's OK.
(WHISPERING) How did it go?
-Not good.
It looks like this is our fella.
She said she wants you to plow
on ahead with the meeting.
-(WHISPERING) You've
got to be kidding.
-This is the mission
we were given.
-(WHISPERING) Yeah, I
know that, knucklehead!
-So tell me, you care
for roses at all?
-Yes, very much.
-Wonderful.
I'm rather taken
with them myself.
They speak the language love.
-Uh, but doesn't
the meaning vary
depending on the
color of the blossom?
Yellow, for example, indicates
your wish to break up.
[laughing]
-Aw, now, that's just
a load of nonsense.
[snapping]
A flower's just a flower.
They don't know nothing.
[groaning]
[music playing]
[laughing]
-This is for you.
[screaming]
-(NERVOUSLY) Oh,
I, uh, uh, sorry.
(YELLING) Wait up!
[groaning]
-Uh huh?
[screaming]
-This is impossible!
I can't do it!
I just can't do it!
She's just going to have to
find herself another lookalike!
-Come on, Ino.
Take a breather.
Just do your best.
You'll be fine.
-Forget it.
He repulses me.
-Oh!
I got it!
Pretend he's a weirder
version of Choji.
-Choji's got meat on him for
the sake of his ninjutsu.
What this young prince is
packing it on for is beyond me.
-Boy.
Tell me how you really feel.
-I need to talk to the princess.
-Huh?
Hold on a minute.
Where are you going?
What the?
I just don't get her.
Well, it looks like it's on me.
Time for this Shinobi to put
his nose to the old grindstone
and get the job done!
[laughing]
[water running]
-So you've got a problem, too?
-Look, I'm not judging
you or anything,
but I think you should take a
pass on the prince of yours.
He's not all that bright in the
head, if you catch my meaning.
-Oh, nonsense, he's the most
passionate and wonderful man
of the world.
-You sure?
-The reason I hired Leaf ninja
for this mission is you're
supposed skill in substitution!
You're a professional
Shinobi, aren't you?
Now, get back out there
and finish the job already!
[groaning]
I wouldn't say
the atmosphere has
been all that congenial so far.
You need to ramp up your
game and charm that man!
[moaning]
INO: Sorry! to have
kept you waiting!
-Oh!
That's it!
Now you've got the idea.
Huh?
-(ANGRILY) Oh!
For the love of--
-Hey!
Wait a sec!
[stuttering]
-P-- P-- P-- Princess Fortune?
[moaning]
-I'm sorry, Prince
Chikara, but do you
think you could help
loosen this sash for me?
-Uh, well, I, uh--
[moaning]
-With sugar on top?
INO (IN BACKGROUND): Oh my gosh!
The ceiling is
swarming with bugs!
They're gigantic!
-What?
[screaming]
-Mind distraction jutsu!
-Swarming with bugs?
Do you see anything?
-Man, I hate bugs.
Whoa!
What the?
-(WHISPERING) What the heck
do you think you're doing
in there?
CHIKARA: Huh?
Where's the princess?
WOMAN: I don't know!
She vanished!
-What's going on around here?
This is getting really annoying.
Ugh!
I need to see what's
happening in there.
-What did you have
to go butting in for?
I had him in the
palm of my hand!
-You little idiot!
Why on earth are you dressed
like Princess Fortune?
-Look!
I've skimmed through enough
of pervy sage's novels
to know this is the kind of
thing that works on guys, OK?
-I can't believe you would stoop
to such a disgusting level!
[groaning]
Pervert!
No one would ever mistake
you for a comic book hero,
you filthy little toad!
-(NARUTO'S VOICE)
Say what you like,
but I was making a lot more
progress than you wer--
[groaning]
-Anything more
you'd like to say?
(VOICEOVER) I'd better wrap
this up before anyone else
sticks their nose into things.
[laughing]
-(NARUTO'S VOICE) That Prince
ain't seen nothing yet.
If we expect to bring
this mission home,
then she's going to
need my help in there!
[yelling]
CHIKARA: Oh, Princess,
where did you run off to?
[giggling]
-Please forgive me.
I've been so nervous
meeting you today,
I guess I flew off
in a bit of a panic.
-You really seemed like a
different person for a moment
there.
-I'm so sorry.
But you're such a striking
man, Prince Chikara.
It's almost overwhelming
being this close to you.
-No!
I can't have you
feeling this way.
What say we change
the atmosphere?
-Uh, in that case,
uh, let me, uh--
-(INO'S VOICE) Hi
there, Chikara, honey!
[gasping]
[screaming]
CHIKARA: (NERVOUSLY)
Outside the door!
-Yes, love, is something wrong?
-Out that door just now!
I just saw a whole
other princess!
[laughing]
-How could that
be, you silly boy?
(ANGRILY) Naruto!
It's very flattering, though.
You feel so deeply, you conjure
visions of me at every turn.
CHIKARA: Visions?
(NERVOUSLY) No.
I'm telling you!
-Look no further.
Uh--
[gasping]
-Pr-- Princess Fortune?
-(VOICEOVER) Aw, nuts,
I wasn't thinking.
You have to forgive
me, my prince.
I couldn't bear the
thought of your eyes
on anything else but me.
-All this passion is
blowing me away, darling.
All right then, your wish
is my command, little lady.
[snapping]
[gasping]
-I can see you're
burning up here,
and I'm aiming to fan the flame.
-(VOICEOVER) What do I do?
-It's all right.
You don't have to hold back now.
[kissing sounds]
[screaming]
PRINCESS: (SCREAMING)
What are you doing?
You can't kiss him!
-Huh?
[groaning]
-Let me make this clear, OK?
I don't want you kissing
that man, you got it?
-That's the last thing I want.
Honestly, you couldn't
have come at a better time.
-Look, I don't want to hear it.
The most you're allowed to
do in there is hand holding,
do you read me?
-Quiet!
Stop making such a racket.
CHIKARA: She vanished
into thin air again.
WOMEN: Oh, Princess?
INO: This is bad.
I have to get back.
-Don't you try any
funny business in there.
-I think I can handle that.
Anyway, we can't keep
standing around out here.
If he sees us together,
then we're busted.
Now, hurry, Princess,
back to your room.
-Yeah, I'm going.
Huh?
[groaning]
[sneezing]
-That Ino drop kicking
me in the lake.
Who does she think
she is anyway?
I'm frozen to the
bone because of her.
[shivering]
[groaning]
Oh, great, of course
I got to go now, too!
[groaning]
Without a bathroom in sight!
Oh well, I guess if
no one's looking!
[groaning]
[humming]
[screaming]
-(YELLING) What the hell
are you doing with my body?
-(NERVOUSLY) Uh, uh-- I mean--
-You shameless little!
Get away from there!
-I can't stop now!
[shrieks]
-I can't just shut it off!
It doesn't work that way!
-Come here!
[screaming]
Wait until I get
my hands on you!
[yelling]
[water running]
-I wasn't ready to reveal the
inner workings of my heart
quite yet, but I've come to
realize that these feelings
I hold for you are real.
-Princess.
-I've harboured this secret
love for the longest time now.
[screaming]
-I'm yours if you'll accept me.
-Well, uh--
[crashing]
What the?
Now, what could that noise be?
-I don't know.
[raining]
-Huh?
-Huh, it's raining.
-What a beautiful rainbow!
Huh?
PRINCESS: (YELLING)
Stop it already!
NARUTO: (YELLING) I told you!
I can't!
[music playing]
[groaning]
CHIKARA: Is that you, Princess?
[screaming]
-(ANGRILY) Naruto!
-(ANGRILY) You nasty
little gutter snipe!
-(NERVOUSLY) Forgive and
forget, though, right?
-(YELLING) Not in
a million years!
[screaming]
[yelling]
-Can somebody tell me
what's going on here?
-Oh, sorry, the
thing is that-- uh--
-Well, all right, then.
I don't think we can
keep this up any longer.
My apologies for
hoodwinking you like this.
But you were right.
Actually, I am Princess Fortune.
-Are you telling
me the girl I was
with all day is an imposter?
-I'm afraid so, yes.
-Good gravy!
What is the meaning of this?
I'll be honest with you.
This isn't really the
grand finale I had in mind.
-You've got it all
wrong, Prince Chikara!
-Can it!
[gasping]
[screaming]
Now, this is what haunts
my dreams at night.
That body is the very
pinnacle of perfection.
Bravo!
-Huh?
[music playing]
[laughing]
-Well, how about it, Princess?
How about you and I hook
our wagons together?
-Oh, a thousand times, yes!
PEOPLE: Hail the future wife!
Bravo!
[laughing]
[cheering]
-Huh.
Who'd have thunk it?
-I don't get it.
Does this mean the mission
was accomplished or what?
I'm lost.
-So, let me get this straight.
I just spent the entire
day throwing myself
at a man I wouldn't want to
touch with a ten foot pole,
and after suffering
through for what
felt like an eternity
was for nothing?
[sizzling]
NARUTO: Ah, well, it all worked
out in the end, though, right?
They seem to make a
happy couple at least.
-You don't understand.
That's not the problem.
He tread all over a
young girl's heart.
I can't believe a goofball like
that would just cast me aside!
-Didn't even give you a second
look at the end there, did he?
-(ANGRILY) Oh, cram it!
You don't have to remind me.
-You never know what's going to
do it for somebody, I suppose.
-Oh, please, that's
a load of hogwash!
One guy is the same as another.
You all like a woman
with a slim figure.
If I expect to compete out
there, I've got to diet!
Diet!
You hear me?
-Hey!
Hey, wait up!
Ino!
INO: (YELLING) Diet!
[theme music]
LEE: Naruto!
Let us forage the bittersweet
memories of youth together.
NARUTO: Huh?
LEE: No need to be shy.
I am ready both
in mind and body.
NARUTO: What the heck
are you babbling about?
LEE: So long.
So long I have waited
for this moment to come.
NARUTO: I don't have a clue
what you're talking about.
LEE: No.
Here I come, Naruto.
I hope you will be my first.
NARUTO: (NERVOUSLY)
Wait a second!
[screaming]
NARUTO: Next time-- "Viva
Dojo Challenge-- Youth
is All About Passion!"
[theme music]