THEME SONG: [Japanese]
[knocking]
BAKI: Open up, now.
-Huh?
-So what's up?
What's all the ruckus?
-(ANGRILY) You idiots.
Didn't I tell you not to let him
out of your sight for a second?
-Huh?
Oh.
-Oh no.
Gaara's gone.
-Yeah.
But where?
-This is bad.
Very bad.
NARRATOR: Hospital Besieged.
The Evil Hand Revealed.
[bird chirping]
[sand falling]
-Man.
Is he ever going to wake up?
Maybe the kid croaked.
[sigh]
[birds chirping]
-You're wasting your time
if those are for Sasuke.
-Ino.
-So you haven't heard
the news that he still
hasn't come back yet?
You're a little behind
the curve, aren't you,
billboard brow?
-As a matter of fact, I
was getting it for Lee.
The last one must
be wilting by now.
-Yeah, you're right.
SAKURA: Lee, you
shouldn't be out of bed.
-191--
SAKURA: Stop it.
-(ANGRILY) Keep away from me.
Do not count me out.
I am not through yet.
-Here you go.
-Thank you.
-Tell him hi.
I hope he's feeling better.
SHIKAMARU: The sand stopped.
What's up with that?
Did they forget to
wind it or something?
What a drag.
So, you decided to wake up, huh?
-Where am I?
What is this?
-The hospital.
They said you've been out
cold like this for three days
straight.
-Three days?
(ANGRILY) Three days straight?
-Uh, yeah.
More or less.
-(SHOUTING) Shikamaru, when's
the final competition begin?
-Tomorrow.
-(SHOUTING) What?
Are you crazy?
Why the heck didn't
you wake me up sooner?
I can't be lying around
here at a time like this.
I've got to be getting ready.
And Pervy Sage.
Where's Pervy Sage?
That old coot's supposed to
be supervising my training.
-Hey, calm down kid.
Get a grip.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
-(SHOUTING) Where
are my clothes?
I've got to get dressed.
Where'd they put them?
Where are my clothes?
Oh come on, where are they?
-Oh man.
This kid gives me
such a headache.
I liked him better
when he was in a coma.
(SHOUTING) Would
you knock it off?
(CALMLY) Now listen.
You don't want to
be freaking out
the day before a
big competition.
Resting can be the best thing.
Are you OK?
Is something wrong?
-Yeah.
I'm really starving.
-Is that all?
Man, stop scaring me like that.
Oh, look at this.
-Hm?
-i went to all the trouble of
getting this stuff for Choji
and then the doctors told
me he couldn't have it.
Such a drag.
But at least we can eat it.
-Choji?
You mean he's here
in the hospital too?
-Nothing to worry about.
All he's got is a bad
case of indigestion.
He ate one short rib too many.
-I should've figured.
That's just like him.
-Yeah.
Well, you two are
just lucky I'm around
or you wouldn't
have any visitors.
Here.
-Oh, wow.
This looks delicious.
-What?
What is it now?
[laughing]
-Let's eat it in front of
Choji, it'll drive him crazy.
SHIKAMARU: Man, that's mean.
I like it.
-What the-- where is everybody?
Out to lunch?
Hm.
Oh well.
Huh?
[clock ticking]
-Hm.
[bird chirping]
-OK.
Well.
Hope you like it.
[moan]
-I'm still starving.
[knock]
-Huh?
Come on, don't torture
me like that, Shikamaru.
[wind blowing]
-Oh.
That's right.
[groan]
[screaming]
-But why?
He failed.
Why save him?
-Because he's-- he's my student.
And also because he
is precious to me.
-What am I?
[screaming]
-I can't move my body.
[shout]
-Ah!
-(SHOUTING) What the heck do
you think you're doing in here,
you rat?
-Hey, man.
Go easy.
I'm using my shadow
possession jutsu.
So when you're bashing
him, you're bashing me too.
You got it?
-Oh, sorry Shikamaru.
Out with it.
What were you trying to pull?
-Hey, Choji.
Feeling better?
-Oh.
Ino.
[giggling]
(VOICEOVER) All right.
A pretty girl with food.
This is my lucky day.
-Well?
Are you gonna tell us
what you were gonna do?
-I was going to kill him.
-What?
-(VOICEOVER) This guy's
one cool customer.
Look at him.
He's not even phased by my
shadow possession jutsu.
-You already beat him
once in the competition.
What's your problem?
Wasn't that enough for you?
Do you have some kind
of personal grudge
against him or something?
-I have nothing against him.
It's nothing that complicated.
I simply want to
kill him, that's all.
-(SHOUTING) You know what?
You're sick in the head.
You're crazy.
-Yeah.
You think we're going
to just stand by and let
you do whatever you want?
You sick selfish psycho.
(VOICEOVER) This guy
gives me the creeps.
There's always been
something weird about him.
Scary.
If he decides to
make a move, I'm
not sure we'll be
able to stop him.
-If you don't stay
out of my way,
I'll have to kill
you two as well.
-(SHOUTING) Oh really?
Well let's just see you try it.
-Hey.
Whoa kid.
Take it easy.
(VOICEOVER) Best thing
to do is try and bluff
our way out of this.
Yeah.
We watched your last
match against Lee.
We know you're tough.
But you know, Naruto and
I have a few little tricks
up our sleeves as well.
We were holding back
during the competition.
There are things you
haven't seen yet.
On top of that, hey,
it's two against one.
So don't be a fool, OK?
Just take my advice
and go quietly.
-I'll say it once more.
If you get in my
way, I'll kill you.
-(VOICEOVER) OK, plan B.
-(SHOUTING) And
I'll say it again.
Let's see you try it.
-Back off, will you?
We don't want to go there.
This guy fights like he's mad.
Like he's a demon or something.
-He can act like a demon if he
wants to, but you know what?
I got the real
thing inside of me.
-They told me
Naruto was in here.
From the mess someone's made
of that bed, he probably was.
Well I guess that
means he's all right.
[sand falling]
-Idiot.
Leave this to me.
What's the point
of getting him mad?
-A demon, huh?
My demon is as real as yours is.
From my birth, my
upbringing was not
what most people would
consider a happy one.
To ensure that I became
the strongest of Shinobi,
my father had cast
his ninjutsu on me,
infusing my unborn self
with the sand spirit.
I destroyed the life of a
woman who gave birth to me.
I was born a monster.
-(VOICEOVER) A sand spirit?
-Its name is Shukaku and
it's the living incarnation
of an old monk of
the sand village
who'd been sealed
up in a jar of tea.
-Yeah.
Some kind of demonic jutsu.
But to use it on a baby?
Before it's even born?
Man, that's creepy.
-(VOICEOVER) Can it be true?
He's got one inside of him too?
-(SARCASTICALLY) Gee.
What a swell guy your
dad must've been.
He really must have
loved you a lot.
-You speak of love?
Don't measure me
by your standards.
Love.
Family.
The only emotional ties
I have to my family
are the ones I'd like to
wrap around their necks.
They're only ties of hate.
Given life by the
death of my mother,
I was brought into
being and nurtured
as the salvation of the village.
I was the Kazekage child.
My father taught me
the innermost secrets
of the Shinobi.
He pampered and protected
me and left mt to myself.
For a time, I thought
that was love.
And that was when
everything started.
-When what started?
-What was it?
Are you gonna tell us or not?
So go on.
What started?
What was it?
-In the six years since
I became six years old,
my father tried to destroy me
more times than I can count.
[gasping]
-You just finished saying
how your father pampered
and protected you.
So which is it?
-Those who get to be too strong
are apt to become feared.
The jutsu that gave me
birth had unbalanced
something in my mind.
Even the fools in
my village finally
realized I had
emotional problems.
My father, the
Kazekage, had created me
as his ultimate weapon.
But I eventually became a
threat to the very village
I was meant to save.
By the time I was six, I
became a figure of terror
to the villagers.
To them, I was a
relic of the past
that they wished
would disappear.
So you see, I had failed
at the one purpose
for which I was given life.
What then was left for
me in this existence?
Why go on living?
For a long time, I couldn't
find an answer to that.
But in order to live,
you need a purpose.
To exist for no reason is
the same as being dead.
-What is this guy talking about?
-(VOICEOVER) I know just
what he means, exactly.
He's-- he's the same as me.
-Then in time the
answer came to me.
To put it simply my
reason for living
is in the killing of others.
For years I lived
in fear of those
who were sent to murder me.
But now I am at peace.
I killed many
would-be assassins.
And it was while I was
doing it that the truth was
made clear to me.
I live solely for myself.
I love only myself.
As it was the death of my
mother that first gave me life,
now it is the death of
others that sustains me.
That makes me almost
happy to be alive.
And there's no end to it
as long as there are still
people to kill in this
great, wide, crowded world.
I will never disappear.
-(VOICEOVER) This freak.
He's out of his mind.
-(VOICEOVER) I was alone too.
I didn't know what I was
here for, why I was alive.
Until Iruka sensei came along.
He saw what was in me.
He gave me a purpose,
a reason for living.
But this guy had no one.
He had to find the
answer on his own.
And this is what
he came up with.
To kill in order to live.
Could I have ended
up like that if--
[gasp]
We're so different, but we're
so close to being the same.
No.
I don't think I
can beat this guy.
-Hey, where you going?
What's wrong?
[sand falling]
-(VOICEOVER) He shouldn't
be able to do that.
Not with my shadow
possession jutsu on him.
[gasp]
-Naruto.
Hey, wake up.
Oh man, what a drag.
Naruto.
-Now, let me feel alive.
-Incoming.
-All right.
That's enough.
Save it til tomorrow.
That's when the final
competition begins.
You're just wasting it today.
Is that what you want?
-Don't leave me alone.
I'm not bleeding
but it hurts a lot.
What am I?
[gaara breathing]
-All the same, I will kill you.
Just you wait.
I'll kill you all.
[footsteps]
THEME SONG: [Japanese]
-Hey.
Konohamaru, what's going on?
I thought you said
this was a shortcut.
Come on, I'm going to be late.
The final competition's
about to start.
Everything I've
trained for, lived for.
The whole point of my
existence up til now.
And what am I doing?
Messing around with you
on this stupid shortcut.
Next time.
The Final Rounds, Rush
to the Battle Arena.
[moan] That's what I get
for listening to a kid.
THEME SONG: [Japanese]