[theme music]
TSUNADE: Are there
more than last month?
-You bet there are.
Now even people in
the outer reaches
know you were appointed
Hokage, lady Tsunade.
Word is out.
That's why we've been
getting so many bills.
And they're all addressed
to the Hidden Leaf Village.
-This Hokage thing is more
headache than I thought.
Hm.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER):
My name is Tsunade.
I'm the Fifth Hokage of the
Village Hidden in the Leaves.
Now I'm stuck dealing
with a debt that
only seems to get worse.
Not only that--
NARUTO: Grandma Tsunade!
Come on!
Let me go!
If there's no
missions now, then why
can't I go and
search for Sasuke?
Huh?
-Because you were ordered
to stay and train, Naruto.
That's why.
-Hey, Grandma Tsunade!
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER):
There's him too.
NARUTO: The treasure hunt is on!
-Get him defense!
Goal!
Sorry, pal.
Not this time.
Hahah!
Of couse I didn't score.
I'm playing offense and
defense against myself.
And there haven't been
any missions lately.
I wonder if Pervy Sage
is gonna come back soon.
I can't train them
myself, you know.
[bark]
KIBA: Ah.
Looks like somebody
beat me to it.
NARUTO: Huh?
Kiba?
Akamaru?
-Darn it.
I thought I might be able
to train in peace here.
-Are you by yourself?
Where are Hinata and Shino?
-Shino's busy backing
up another squad out
on a mission with
Kurenai-sensei.
And Hinata told me she was
just gonna train at home.
-It sort of feels like
we've been fired as ninja.
-Don't say that.
You're bumming me out.
HINATA: Naruto, Kiba.
[bark]
-Hinata.
-Weren't you supposed to be
doing your training at home?
-There was a call sent
out from the Hokage.
She needs us immediately.
-Wait.
Really?
-All right.
Our first real mission
in like forever!
A treasure hunt?
TSUNADE: That's right.
And for this mission,
our client happens
to be an old
acquaintance of mine.
-My name is Agari Kaisen.
Please, take a look at this map.
It will show the location
of what you're looking for.
A treasure worth several hundred
million ryo lies buried there.
[whistle]
-That's a lot.
Do you know how many
Ichiraku special
ramens I could buy
with that much?
-I don't think you could
eat that much ramen
in your entire life.
-Awesome!
-Wait a sec.
You already know where
it is on the map?
Then is this job
really something
you need to hire a shinobi for?
-It is.
For you see the treasure
is an area that's
quite difficult for ordinary
people to travel to.
I have even attempted
it more than once,
but I couldn't manage it.
It was impossible.
-So now you're going to have
the shinobi give it a shot, huh.
-The deadline is in three days.
If you succeed, Agari will
give you a special reward.
Proceed with caution.
-Ma'am.
-A mission like this'll be
a walk in the park for us.
-You're right.
This mission shouldn't
be much trouble.
However, if for some
reason you three fail--
-What?
[sigh]
TSUNADE: If for some
reason you three fail,
I'm sending you
back to the Academy.
You'll re-enroll in
the Academy and redo
all of your ninja
training from day one.
-But why would you
make us do that?
-Well, I went back and looked
up your mission success rate
over the past few months.
Naruto, yours is
decisively poor.
-Huh?
-In particular, I see that
whenever you're teamed up
with Kiba and Hinata, you're
the worst team we've got.
KIBA (VOICEOVER): Now
that she mentions it,
we did blow that earlier
mission with this lineup.
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
We also failed
when it was the three
of us along with Shino
looking for the bikochu.
-I can tell I've struck
a nerve, haven't I?
-That's
-No fair.
Naruto's got the awful record.
Why should we have to
go back to the Academy?
-Collective responsibility is
fundamental in ninja teams.
Everyone takes
blame for a failure.
Got it?
-Yes, ma'am.
-We'll be fine.
No way are we going to fail
at some dumb treasure hunting
mission.
-Just be sure you don't
drag us down again.
Who?
Me?
If anybody's going to drag the
team down it's gonna be you.
-But if we don't
succeed this time,
then I guess we'll have
to take the same classes
as these little
children, won't we?
IRUKA: What's up, guys?
Well, well.
The three of you are back again?
-Iruka-sensei?
-You guys must miss your
old Academy days, huh?
You know, you're welcome to
come back anytime you like.
NARUTO: No way.
I'm never going back again!
-Hm.
I wonder what's up with them.
NARUTO: I'm going to make this
mission such a huge success
it's going to put
grandma Tsunade to shame.
-Yeah.
There's no way I'm going
back to the Academy.
Especially not on
account of your mistakes,
-Hey.
What about collective
responsibility?
You can't just blame
me for everything.
-Or really?
Then explain why whenever
you haven't been on our team,
our success rate has
always been pretty high.
-Fine.
Then I'm gonna prove
to you which one of us
is really been a burden to this
team, and which one's an asset.
-Go ahead.
I hope you do.
HINATA (VOICEOVER): Uh--
I hope this goes well.
-Huh?
Aw, man.
It's a total dead end.
-So the path only
goes this far, huh?
The map says there's a
river up ahead that way.
How should we cross it?
-Hm.
Look it.
We can cut straight through
that hilly part there.
No problem.
-What are you?
A moron?
Mountain terrain
isn't that easy.
You can't just zip
through it like that.
I say we go this way.
[laughter]
-And you're the one
calling me a moron?
That's the long way around.
-Hm.
OK, then.
You wanna go both ways and
see who gets there first?
-Suit yourself.
But there's no way
you're gonna win.
-All right, then.
Fine.
The finish line is that boulder.
And go!
Come on, Akamaru.
-I got this one in the bag.
-Wait for me, Naruto!
Naruto.
-Yeah.
What's up?
-Don't you think we're
climbing up too high?
-Nah.
I know what I'm doing.
Ow.
[scream]
-Naruto!
-It's gonna be OK.
Even with these setbacks
we're gonna be faster.
[chuckling] Yes.
I beat him!
Something smells good.
Huh?
-So you finally made it.
-Kiba.
-You were taking so
much time I figured
I should cook us some grub.
Now then, which way next?
-I got it.
If we take a shortcut this way
we'll get there in no time!
-Naruto, wait!
-Huh?
We go again.
-Water.
Huh?
-Here.
Bottoms up.
-This way's definitely faster.
I'm sure of it.
-Hey there.
I had such a good nap.
See the thing is,
Akamaru and I regularly
train in mountains
like this one.
Which is why we know so much
more about this kind of terrain
than you.
-Ah, shut it.
NARUTO: Knock it off!
Don't be acting all big just
cuz you won two or three times.
KIBA: Not two or three times.
Five times!
-Oh yeah?
Why don't we see who's--
-Knock it off!
HINATA: Naruto, Kiba, stop it!
NARUTO: Cut it out!
-Naruto and the others
should be back pretty soon,
shouldn't they?
-I'm not so sure.
This mission might seem
like a piece of cake.
Truth is, it's not
going to be easy.
They're probably figuring
that out right now.
-Well, it is a
limestone cave, but--
-Come on.
What are we waiting for?
The dumb map says treasure's in
a limestone cave, doesn't it?
-Hold on a minute.
The limestone is supposed
to be further ahead.
We shouldn't have been able
to find it this easily.
-Please.
How many limestone caves could
there possibly be around here?
Nah.
This is the right one.
Let's go, Hinata.
-OK.
-Hey.
Don't just--
-I can't see anything in here.
-It's a dead end.
-What?
No way.
-Naruto, Hinata!
Watch out, you two!
Get out of the way!
[bark]
-Huh?
Agh!
-Do you think that
blast finished them off?
-No, From what we know, these
ninja are tougher than that.
[bark]
-What the heck just happened?
Do you think an enemy followed
us into the cave or something?
-No.
Akamaru's saying he
didn't smell anyone
else other than the three of us.
It must've been an accident.
I tried to explain to you that
this wasn't the right cave,
-Ah, get real, will you?
We were looking for a limestone
cave and one was front of us.
A normal person'd
think we found it.
-Hey.
Don't give me any of your lip.
I just saved your
butt back there.
-I didn't ask you to save me.
I was doing just fine.
-Why you!
-Come on, you guys.
Please don't fight.
-Huh?
-A fragment from the
ceiling must have hit you.
-Are you OK?
-After all that, it seems like
I'm the one dragging us down.
-Huh?
No way.
You didn't do anything.
In fact, I probably
should've been more cautious.
-Yep.
As always, it's your
fault again, Naruto.
-What?
-Ah, it doesn't matter.
There's no way I'm going to
let your stupidity land me
back at the Academy again.
Akamaru and I will find
the treasure ourselves.
-What are you
talking about, Kiba?
We're a team.
We gotta do this
mission together.
-Yeah, Kiba.
It doesn't hurt too bad.
-From here on out,
the obstacles we face
are going to be way tougher than
anything we've passed so far.
The kind of terrain that only
the best shinobi can possibly
get through.
It would be almost
impossible for someone
with an injured leg.
Besides, we can't just
leave an injured teammate
all by herself, can we?
We need someone to stay
back and take care her.
-Yeah.
So why does that have to be me?
-You really think you'll find
the treasure by yourself?
You can't read a
map worth a darn,
and you don't know nothing
about mountains like these.
And to be honest, we've
already wasted a ton of time
because of decisions you made.
You can rest easy.
I'll take care of finding
that treasure, and none of us
will have to go
back to the Academy.
Let's get going, Akamaru.
[barking]
-Kiba, wait.
Let's talk about this.
Ah, this stinks.
-Now.
-Naruto!
-Huh?
Huh?
-HINATA: Are you
awake yet, Naruto?
-Hinata.
HINATA: I'm over here.
-Huh?
Wait.
What?
You look like-- why
are there two Hinatas?
-Oh, Naruto.
-Wait a sec.
You're using a Clone
Jutsu or something?
You're not telling me--
you're not twins, are you?
-No!
-OK.
Then one of you
turned into Hinata
with the Transformation Jutsu?
[whimper]
-Oh, man.
How am I supposed to tell
the two of you apart?
-I'm the real Hinata.
-You kidding me?
Even your voices sound alike.
I know.
I should ask you both a question
that only the real one could
possibly know the answer to.
All right.
Can you tell me the
name of Hinata's father?
-Hiyashi Hyuga.
-Uh-- that didn't work.
I guess that wasn't the greatest
question, since I didn't even
know his name.
-What?
-Naruto.
-This is the kind of thing
I need Kiba and Akamaru for.
They could probably
tell by the scent
which girl is the real deal.
-No.
Not even a ninja dog could tell.
This one is no ordinary
Transformation Jutsu.
-Hey, weren't you the client
who hired us for this gig?
What are you doing here?
-I hired you, but it
wasn't the buried treasure
I was really after.
It was your faces.
-Faces?
-That's correct, young man.
I already have your face.
-I'm Naruto Uzumaki.
Believe it.
-What the heck?
He looks like me.
-Now that you're
all tied up, I'll
be setting out to
get my last face,
-Leave it to me.
I'm the best.
-This must be the place.
Inside of the cave is
just as the map says.
There's no doubt.
[bark]
-Under this rock, huh?
I'll get it in one shot.
Huh?
Here we go.
It was surprisingly
easy to find it though.
Is something wrong, Akamaru?
NARUTO: Kiba, hey.
Is that you in there, buddy?
-Kiba.
-Naruto?
Hinata?
Why are you here?
I told you guys you
could head back home.
-What's your problem?
We came all this way.
-The mission was for the
three of us after all.
-Hinata, how you feel?
I mean, is your injury OK?
-Yes.
I just needed to
rest for awhile,
and then I could move on again.
-Wow.
Nice going.
I can't believe you
already found the treasure.
Let's grab it, and bring
it back to the village, OK?
-You got it.
KIBA (VOICEOVER): Hold on.
How did these guys find
this cave so quickly?
They didn't even have the map.
, Plus, Naruto has zero
sense of direction,
and Hinata has a bum leg.
Akamaru doesn't seem to
suspect anything is wrong.
Am I being paranoid?
[thud]
-Ah, they've returned.
NARUTO: Kiba, Akamaru!
[whimper]
-You see?
What did we tell you?
Even a ninja dog's nose can't
sniff out the difference.
-Shall we begin?
-Face Copying Jutsu.
HINATA: What's happening?
-We also copied your
faces the same way.
-As you can see, when performing
the Face Copying Jutsu,
the person being copied
must be close by.
What's more, it
takes a bit of time,
but once the face
has been copied,
it's an impeccable
Transformation Jutsu.
Even the victim's family
can't tell the difference.
-No way.
-Kiba, wake up!
Kiba!
-Hey, what is this?
Who are you?
-I'm Kiba Inuzuka.
So you both were--
what is going on here?
NARUTO: Kiba!
HINATA: Down here!
-Then those must
be the real ones?
[groan]
-How dare you!
Who are you people?
-We are at the Kedoin
Clan, a clan that
wields the Hidden
Face Copying Jutsu.
-So what the heck do
you want with our faces?
-Now that we look
like you guys, we'll
just walk back into the
Hidden Leaf Village.
And when we get
inside, we're going
to mess up the place real good.
[laughter]
[theme music]
KIBA: Like I said,
missions never
go well with you on the team.
NARUTO: This is no
time to complain.
They're heading for our village!
KIBA: All right then, how
do we get out of here?
HINATA: Listen.
NARUTO: What about Rasengan?
KIBA: No good.
They'll notice.
NARUTO: Then use
your Fang Over Fang.
KIBA: Same thing, you dope.
HINATA: Naruto.
NARUTO: Fine.
Now what do we do?
KIBA: I'm trying to think.
HINATA: Naruto!
KIBA AND NARUTO:
Don't try to stop us!
HINATA: No.
It's not that.
I can use--
KIBA AND NARUTO: Oh, that.
NARUTO: Next Time--
Run, Dodge, Zigzag!
Chase or be Chased!
[theme music]