[theme music]
-All right, Guy.
We'll leave Sasuke
in your hands.
-Master Jiraiya?
-Hmm.
-Find the Lady Tsunade.
Bring her back to us.
-Don't worry, you
could count on us.
We'll have her back in
the village in no time!
-[laugh]
-Naruto, nothing impresses
me more than guys, kid.
Come here, let me give you this.
Lee got stronger with this.
-Really, what, what is it?
-Check it out!
It's breathable,
retains moisture,
and offers complete
freedom of movement,
all in one sweet package.
If you where it
while you training,
you'll notice a
difference immediately.
They really grow on you.
Pretty soon, you'll be wearing
them all time, just like Lee.
I've got a bit of a
thing for them myself.
-Oh, man!
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
If you're going
to walk around
carrying that thing,
you ought to pack a hand
mirror or two, you idiot.
-Pretty cool, huh?
-Don't even think about it.
I mean, look at that guy.
-Huh?
-Man, now that is goofy.
-All right.
This is it.
Huh?
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER): This is the
biggest gambling hole in town.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
I know that he's
the one you're really after.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
You're right.
Naruto is the prize that
the Akatski are after.
And we will have him.
-What's up?
-So, Pervy Sage, what
exactly do those guys
want with me, anyway?
Come on, out with a Pervy Sage.
You know, don't you?
-Don't get the wrong idea.
It's not you they want.
It's what's inside of you.
-What the hell is
this thing, anyway?
Some horrible demon that
terrorized the Leaf Village.
That's why everyone is
so afraid of it, right?
So why do these
guys want it so bad?
-The Nine-tailed
Fox has appeared
in times of consequence,
all through the ages--
a ghastly spirit destroying
all that lays in its path.
As powerful as any act of
nature, men trembled before it.
As for what they would want
with that malicious monstrosity,
that's a hard question
to answer, Naruto.
I honestly can't say.
I suppose with the Nine-Tails
sealed up inside you,
they might be thinking
of somehow seizing
control of that power,
bending it to their will.
It's a bitter pill to swallow
knowing that those, too,
will be after you now.
But that is your fate.
Not to worry, though.
After all, you will
have me around.
-Oh well, I'll just have to
hurry up and get stronger.
No other choice.
All right.
Let's find the Tsunade
woman you're talking,
so she can fix up
Sasuke, and we get down
to some serious training.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER): The kid
has got a one-track mind.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): A
new training begins.
I will be strong.
--[scream] This place has
the highest minimum in town.
-Don't get your
panties in a bunch.
Let's do this.
-Oh, wait for me.
-Hmm.
-What now?
-This beautiful
woman that you've
got us out here
scouting around for,
is she the Tsunade
that you mentioned?
-Hey, not bad, kid.
You're pretty sharp, aren't you?
Why, what's on your mind, then?
-Well, you said she was one
of the three legendary Sannin,
the same as you,
right, Pervy Sage?
-That's right.
What's your point, already?
-How old is she?
-Same age as me.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Yuck, she's ancient.
MAN (VOICEOVER): Huh?
Wait, she's--
-Here's all my cash.
You think I could
get some chips?
-She's going all in.
-Looks like a
pretty big spender.
Who is this broad?
-You are kidding.
You never heard of her?
She's the one with
the crazy nickname.
-Nickname?
-So, what's this Tsunade
lady like, anyway?
-Ah, curious, are you?
-Yeah.
-What can I tell you.
Well, for one thing,
she's kind of unpleasant.
Plus, I guess there's
the fact that she's
known far and wide as a
die hard gambler and all.
-Great.
This should be a
piece of cake, then,
if she's as famous as all that.
-Oh, she's famous, all right.
You might even
call her legendary.
-So what's this crazy
nickname she's got?
-The Legendary.
-Legendary?
[laughter]
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER): Why
are they all laughing?
-The Legendary Sucker.
But as legendary a
sucker as she may be,
I doubt she's going to
be all that easy to find.
-Why, what makes you say that?
-She's not the type to
grow old gracefully.
Probably using some kind of
jutsu to mask her appearance.
She's actually 50
years old, but I'm
sure she'll look more
like she did in her '20s.
That's not all.
The word on the
wind I hear of late
is she started transforming on
the fly, going from her teens,
to her 30s, her 40s--
all so she can cut out
on any money lender
she's in too deep with.
-That's awful.
Aww, man.
She sounds like a charmer.
-Yeah, well Tsunade's
always loved gambling more
than anything.
It's too bad she never
had any luck-- or skill,
for that matter.
She was made a
sucker so many times,
the name just stuck with her.
But then she would
just borrow money
and skip out on her debts.
It brings me back, I tell you.
-Hey, we don't have
time for nostalgia.
-What?
-Come on, do you have a plan
for finding her or what?
-Not exactly.
We might have a little
work ahead of us.
But I'm sure you and will
come up with something.
-Uh, so you don't even have the
slightest idea how long this
is going to take, do you?
-Not a minute will be wasted.
All our time on the road will
be devoted solely to you.
-To me?
-We've got to get you stronger.
Time to train.
[groan]
-OK!
-Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
Hold on a second.
I already told you,
I'm not having that.
I don't want to be
seen walking around
with someone wearing
that, that, that thing.
-Come on, Pervy Sage,
what are we waiting for?
Let's start my training already.
-All right, don't get
ahead of yourself now.
I have to train you while we
gather information on Tsunade.
Otherwise, it's not going
to mean anything to you.
-Huh?
Gather information?
-In this town.
-Whoa!
Ah man, this is
going to be great.
I've never seen anything
like this before in my life.
-Downtime is important.
So have a little fun before
we start your training.
This festival will be
going on for a while.
We'll hunker down
here until it's over.
And then we'll start
your training here too.
-All right!
-Oh, baby, that is one
fat frog you've got.
Your filthy rich.
-Yeah, I've got a
pretty big stash.
I've been saving up bit
by bit from my missions.
Catch you later!
-Stop right there, Naruto.
-Huh?
-I'm going to hold onto
your wallet for you.
-Hey, what do you
think you're doing?
-Here, you can have
this much to spend.
-What?
Only 300?
-I don't want to hear it.
Honoring the shinobi's
three prohibitions
is the duty of any
upstanding ninja?
-The three prohibitions?
What are you talking about?
-You're kidding.
Don't you know?
The three prohibitions
are a trio
of temptations that
will bring a shinobi
to his ruin-- those three
prohibitions are alcohol,
pretty women, and,
worst of all, money.
-Yeah, well none of
those things really
apply to me all that
much, so we're cool.
I mean, I'm underage,
so I can't drink yet.
I don't really get
the whole woman thing.
And I worked so hard to save
all that money that I really
don't feel like
spending a ton of it.
-You little fool!
Don't take money lightly.
Once you start spending,
you'll never stop.
Money possess a frightful power.
This woman, Tsunade,
that we're searching for,
has ruined herself
with the pursuit of it.
-Pretty big talk coming
from someone so addicted
to the ladies.
-I'm going to go see if I
can gather some information.
Here, I want you to hold
on to my bag for me, OK?
If you happen to
get lost somehow,
you can always rely
on my tracker toad
to sniff out my scent.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER): I've
got to keep reminding myself
he's still just a kid.
-OK, the first thing I need
is little something to eat.
Can I get an order
of octopus dumplings?
VENDOR: Sure thing.
NARUTO: Three
potatoes with butter.
VENDOR: Coming up!
NARUTO: Six
chocolate-covered bananas.
VENDOR: Okie dokie.
NARUTO: Six piece
of apricot candy.
VENDOR: Thank you.
NARUTO: Three orders
of okonomiyaki.
VENDOR: Here you go,
syrup is on the side.
-One extra large order
of fried noodles, please.
-You've go it that sure is a
lot of food you got there, son.
You don't plan to eat all
of it yourself, do you?
-Huh, well that was
kind of the idea.
-Here you go.
-Uh.
I think I might
have eaten too much.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I wonder
how everyone is doing.
Kakashi sensei, Sasuke, Sakura?
I'm going to train
hard every day
and come back to
you even stronger.
Wait and see.
But first, I'd better
work off all that food.
Last one.
Bulls eye!
Right on target.
[cheering]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): All
that shuriken training
wasn't for nothing.
Huh?
-Man kid, you stink.
-Yeah, we'll see.
Get a load of this.
-Not so fast.
-What?
Attention shinobi--
ninjutsu strictly forbidden?
Oh.
-Thank you.
-Careful kid, you shouldn't
walk around with that mask on.
-Hey, it's the Pervy
Sage's checkbook.
1, 10, 100-- look
all those zeroes.
Jeez, he should be treating me
right now if he's this loaded.
For crying out loud.
Cheap old geezer.
Not much left.
One more stand, and that
will be it for the day.
-We've got to get you stronger.
Time to train.
-Hey, how's it going.
I'd like to get two
grilled squid, please.
And make one of those big
enough for a grown-up.
-OK, coming up.
Got sent on a squid run, huh?
Tell you what.
I'll throw in the
kid size for free.
-Thanks a lot, Mr.
You're the man.
-Oh, you think so, huh?
Well, you're getting half
price on that other squid, too.
-Wow, thanks!
- Good grief, where
did he run off to?
-[laughing]
-Huh?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Was that Pervy Sage?
--[laughing] What can
say, I love the ladies!
Oh, hey kid, Had your fill
the festival already, huh?
-I need a refresher.
What were those
prohibitions of yours again?
What's the matter with you?
You're breaking all three
in one go, you dirty--
-Uh, wait, Naruto.
-Wait, shmait.
I can't believe you squandered
all my hard-earned savings!
Stupid, stupid, stupid!
Lousy good for nothing!
Look at my froggie,
it's flat as a pancake.
-Watch it.
Look what you did,
you little punk!
-Huh?
-You stained the boss' brand new
designer suit, you street rat.
You're paying for
that, $100,000 large!
-What?
You're telling me that
suit costs $100,000?
-That seems a little bit
of a stretch, fellas.
You expect us to believe that
monkey suit is worth $100,000?
-You looking for
trouble, old man?
You'll shut your yap if you
know what's good for you.
-The boss used to be a
Chunin from the Hidden
Village of the Stones.
The Legendary Dark Ninja
feared across the land.
-Aw, this I've got to hear.
The legendary what, now?
-You're asking for it, pal.
Just keep pushing.
-Naruto, this is perfect timing.
I have a new jutsu
I want to show you.
Now, pay attention.
-Enough already.
-That was awesome.
-And I was holding back.
Oh, you guys are hardly
worth the trouble.
-Wait a minute,
you're the legendary--
-Sorry about that.
I guess we kind of
messed up your stand.
Here, this should cover it.
-Oh, thanks a lot.
Now then, my good man.
I'd like to buy
every balloon you've
got, including water balloons.
How's that sound?
-Fine by me, I guess.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): That
was no ordinary hand move.
What the heck kind
of Jutsu was that?
-Naruto.
Let's get going.
Time for you to train.
-Yes, sir!
All right.
It's finally time to
get down to business.
-Here you go.
Have a water balloon.
-Huh?
What the heck is this for?
-Just think about it.
You saw the Jutsu
I performed, right?
And how would you describe it?
-You sent that guy
spinning like a pinwheel.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER): Ah,
he's not quite getting it.
But I've got an idea.
-Good.
Spinning.
There you go.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
He's spinning
the water in that balloon
without even moving his hand.
Whoa!
-With the tree
climbing exercise,
you learn to gather
and maintain chakra.
With the water
walking exercise, you
learn to release a
steady amount of it.
Both of these you've
mastered, correct?
With the water balloon
exercise, you'll
learn to create a stream
of chakra, spinning it,
as you so apply put it.
-I'm supposed to create
a stream of chakra?
-Don't worry.
I'll go into more detail on
how the Jutsu works once you've
gotten a handle of the basics.
First, gather the
chakra in your hand
using the tree
climbing technique.
Then release a
steady stream of it
using the walk on
water technique.
And finally, use the
chakra to push and churn
the water inside of the balloon.
-Wait a second, I get it.
So what you're
aiming for, then, is
to spin the water
inside the balloon
until it eventually pops.
-Attaboy!
You're starting to
catch on quicker.
OK, we'll train until
the sun goes down.
NARUTO: Yes, sir!
[theme music]
-I'm breaking this
water balloon if it's
the last thing I ever do.
-Oh, I like your heart, kid.
You might just master it yet.
Oh, I think the water
is starting to move.
The question is always,
when is it going to pop?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next
time, keep on training.
Pop goes the water balloon.
Hey, why can't I
break this balloon?