[theme music]
-That mark.
He's in league with the people
who attacked this village.
-Huh?
That's a lie!
-It's the truth.
I saw that mark the
night they came.
[villagers screaming]
-Please!
Please!
-[crying]
No!
Please help me!
-That's enough!
-[grunts]
-Ugh.
-[whimpers]
[screams]
-That's the exact same
mark the bandits had.
-No way.
-But how come the report
by the medical team
didn't say anything
about the markings?
-Byakugan!
It seems this type
of marking only
appears on the body
when it sweats.
-I think you'd better go.
-[gasp] Why would we leave?
-Because I'm going
to take care of him.
-You're going to what?
No way!
I won't let you do that!
-Why would you protect this man?
Is the Leaf Village his ally?
-We have nothing to do with him.
But the fact is, this
guy doesn't remember
anything that
happened in his past.
His memory is totally blank.
-He doesn't remember?
-He has amnesia.
We traveled here to
piece together his past.
-Well, then, now
you know everything.
He's a filthy bandit.
And whether or not
he may have amnesia,
it makes no difference to me.
-Hold on a minute.
If you were to punish
someone who can't even
remember his crime,
it wouldn't be right.
-Shut up!
-If it's revenge you want,
go ahead and take it,
as long as you wait
until after my friends
and I get this
man's memory back.
I promise I won't stop you.
-Speak for yourself.
I won't ever let you
kill him, not even then.
-Listen, Neji's right.
If we restore his memory
and get him to talk,
we can find out who those
attackers really were.
And if we use this guy
as a bargaining chip,
we might be able to
save your village.
-It's true.
There's no escaping
the situation.
This man must be kept alive.
-Keep quiet, Naruto.
We need this man on
our side, or else, he
isn't going to let Menma live.
-Hrrrm.
-[sighs]
I'll stitch up his wounds.
Hold him steady.
-Huh?
Who's that?
Huh?
-[grunts]
Aargh!
Aah!
NARUTO: I don't get it.
He seemed like such
a kindhearted person.
But he's really a
low-life bandit?
-Maybe the amnesia just made
him act like he was good.
-It's just got to be
some kind of coincidence
that he has the same
markings as those guys did.
If he was evil deep
down inside, he
couldn't act that nice, even
if he did lose his memory.
-Well, either way,
we'll know everything
once he starts remembering.
-I was-- I was one of
the bandits, wasn't I?
-You're awake?
You must have heard us talking.
-Uhh.
-Listen, don't worry
about any of that.
We still don't know
what actually happened.
It's just all theories
at this point, OK?
-[grunts]
-You need to rest and
let that wound heal up.
-[groans]
-I'm going to take a
look around the area.
-That guy is mine.
If your people try
anything funny with him,
you're going to pay for it.
-When the time comes,
you'll get your shot.
-Uhh.
[grunts]
[sighs]
[panting]
I did it.
Ugh.
Huh?
-[sobs]
MENMA: Fuki?
You heard, didn't you?
-There he is!
Get him!
It'll be vengeance
for everyone we lost.
-Stop right there!
We don't know for
certain that Menma
was one of the bandits
who attacked you!
-You're just as much to
blame if you stand with him.
MALE SPEAKER: What's going on?
-Huh?
Neji.
-Naruto.
-Hey, Tenten.
-Why did you let him out?
-It's my fault.
I must have fallen asleep.
-I let my guard down because I
thought he couldn't stand up.
-Damn it.
-Listen, everyone.
The guy's got total amnesia.
I'm telling you,
even he doesn't know
if he was one of
the bad guys or not.
Ugh!
-We gave you fair warning.
If you three protect
him, you're going
to suffer the same fate as him.
[villagers yell angrily]
MALE SPEAKER: Come on, get him!
They're going to pay
for what they did!
-We need to get him out of here!
-I'm fine.
Go!
-Huh?
-They have every
right to be angry.
I'm to blame.
I deserve all of this.
-You'll be killed.
-If I must.
-Menma, come on!
What are you saying?
Huh?
-Byakugan!
It's them.
-The drawbridge.
Raise the drawbridge!
-Huh.
-Right.
We're on it.
-No good.
Be careful of the Leaf Ninja.
And find me a way
inside this wall.
MEN: Sir!
-Now's our chance.
Everyone hide.
You go, too.
-Don't worry.
The three of us can
handle these guys.
-Right.
-Fuki, come on.
-It worked for two places.
-What?
They were here a second ago.
-It's like they just vanished.
-Both of you, quiet!
NEJI (VOICEOVER): The wind.
Of course, that
strange tone mixed
in with the sound of the wind.
They've got us in a genjutsu.
-Be careful, you two.
We've been put under some
kind of sonic genjutsu.
-You caught on too late.
[flute music]
-[grunts] My body--
-It's heavy.
-What the-- I'm paralyzed.
MENMA (VOICEOVER):
Canceling sound.
-Something released
the paralysis.
-That little backstabber!
-Here they come.
-No prob!
Leave them to me!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
-It's steel time!
Hm, what's the matter, kid?
You finished already?
That was easy.
I don't even have
a scratch on me.
Huh?
-I wasn't trying to hurt you.
I wanted this.
-You can't!
[ocarina music]
-That sound.
It's helping!
Let's do this.
-Rotation!
[men yelling]
-Did you see that?
You're next, buddy.
You won't get away!
-[gasping]
Huh?
-[gasp]
-[snickers]
Ugh!
-Huh?
-Here.
This is special
to you, isn't it?
-Look, behind you!
-[grunts]
-Ugh!
-Hey, your voice, it's back!
-I-- thank you.
-Now, you'd better hurry
back to the others.
-OK.
-Huh?
Ungh.
-Menma!
You all right?
-Yeah.
-Hey, my buddies and I
took care of those bandits.
-But what about their leader?
What about Shiin?
-I-- yeah, sorry.
I chased after him,
but he got away.
-He did.
This is terrible.
Now that Shiin knows
the villagers haven't
fled the town, he'll
use his last resort.
Way up at the upper
end of the river,
there's a dam built to store an
emergency reservoir of water.
Even during an extended
drought, the village
would have plenty of water
resources to draw from.
His plan is to blow
the dam and sweep away
the entire village
with a giant flood.
-What?
-He doesn't care as long
as the mine is intact.
-Oh, man.
To stop a flood
that big, we'd have
to move a bunch of
mountains or something.
-Mountains?
[gasp]
That's it!
We need to move the mountains.
Naruto, you've got to
take me to the mine now.
-Wha--
-There should be a stash
of paper bombs kept
inside the mine.
-Paper bombs?
What are you planning
on doing with those?
-I'm going to blow
up the entire mine.
All that gravel and sand
will fill up the valley.
Maybe the flood
waters can be stopped.
-This is bad.
I hope we aren't too late.
We got to hurry, Menma.
-Uh, Naruto, there's something
that's been eating away at me,
and I need to tell you.
-Come on, can't it
wait till later?
-I-- I remember
everything about my past.
-That's great.
But right now, we got
to focus on stopping
this flood from happening, OK?
-No, this is something I've
got to get off my chest.
I lost both my parents
when I was very little.
And Shiin's clan took
me in and raised me.
Even though they were
a relatively small band
of shinobi in the
Land of Rice Paddies,
they made a name for themselves
because of their strong will
and determination.
However, about a year
ago, a new shinobi village
was founded in the
Land of Rice Paddies--
the Village Hidden in the Sound.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): The
Hidden Sound Village.
-One by one, Shiin's clan
lost their most skilled ninja.
They kept defecting over
to the Sound Village.
Before long, the
feudal lord stopped
hiring the clan altogether.
Shiin was still
leader of the clan.
He needed to
provide for his men.
So he set his sights
on this village's mine.
The plan was just to scare the
villagers and chase them off.
But they resisted.
And things turned ugly.
I wanted to escape.
I tried to run, but--
-What are you waiting for?
Did you forget what your job is?
Do I have to do it for you?
-Father!
Father!
Get up!
[wailing]
-Don't you touch her!
-Ugh!
You--
-Aah!
-Watch out!
[grunts]
Aah!
I'm one of them.
A member of a clan
full of criminals.
It would have been better
if I had fallen to my death.
At least, that ending
would have been a just one.
The image of all those
villagers dying at our hands
was too much.
I wanted to forget
every bit of it.
And so, like a coward, I used
a secret jutsu passed down
to the clan that
erases one's memory.
However, the jutsu didn't
work like it's supposed to.
It didn't last.
My vile memory came
flooding back to me
after only a few hours.
-Are you telling me you could
remember this whole time?
-I'm sorry.
-You!
Get off of me!
I can't believe you didn't
come clean and tell me
the truth from the get-go.
Your lies put a lot
more people in danger!
-The truth was too shameful.
I couldn't let our
clan's sins be known.
Don't you see?
I wanted to stop Shiin's group
from wreaking any more havoc.
-Uhh.
-That's why I was
pretending to have amnesia
so I could turn over a new
page and protect the village.
I needed help.
I thought if I could bring
the mighty Leaf Ninja here,
you would be able
to defeat them.
I knew what Shiin
was capable of.
And I knew I couldn't
stand by and watch
more innocent villagers die.
Fate spared my life.
And now, my purpose is
to save those people.
-Your purpose?
-Do you see now?
I had to tell you those lies.
I needed the help
of the Leaf Ninja
to stop Shiin from carrying
out his final plan.
-Huh?
-I was hoping to round them
all up during their raid
on the village earlier.
But since I've come
this far, I guess
I'll have to stop the flood.
Naruto, thank you.
You'll have to take
care of Shiin for me.
No matter what happens,
you must stop him.
-Why are you giving me--
-Because this is goodbye.
Somebody has to set off the
paper bombs inside the mine.
-What?
If you do that, there's
no way you're going to--
-Thanks to you and your
friends, Naruto, my life
is going to mean something.
-Ugh!
Aah!
[rumbling]
-Oh, what's that rumbling?
-I'm sensing a chain of
large explosions occurring
upstream from here.
-But if the dam
breaks, the village
will be engulfed in a mudslide.
[murmurs]
-Neji.
[rumbling]
-Here comes the flood.
-[gasping]
Hm.
So long, my friend, Naruto.
-Menma!
No!
-Huh?
-Wha-- what's happening?
-It appears that the mountain
exploded and blocked the water
flow.
-So then, does that mean
the village is safe?
-It does.
-Oh, this is great.
-How could he?
How can he just
sacrifice himself?
Menma!
That scum.
He won't get away!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Hold it right there!
-What?
Another pest interfering
with my plan?
You think I'd fall for
that easy jutsu, huh?
Now, die!
-If Menma's not here
to defeat you, I will!
-What?
-Rotation!
-[grunts]
-He gave his life to
save these people.
-Despite his evil deeds in the
past, deep down he was good.
-Goodbye, mister.
-I owe him an apology.
-We didn't know it
then, but in the end,
wiping away that memory
was the only salvation
that Menma needed.
-Well, I promised you we'd
eat this ramen together.
And I always keep my word.
-So do you really think
he's going to be all right?
-If I know Naruto,
we only need to worry
if he loses that appetite.
Over time, he'll get
past this on his own.
-But until then,
he'll probably think
about losing his friend
whenever he eats ramen.
-And that's OK.
Bad memories stay
with us forever.
They even make us stronger.
It's how we grow as people.
-Man, that was so delicious.
Bye, Menma.
[theme music]
MAN: A backup mission
from the Sand Village?
WOMAN: A gang called the Four
Celestials kidnapped a student
from the Sand and are
making their getaway
to the Land of Fire.
Gaara and the rest
are in pursuit.
MAN: It sure sounds
like an ambush.
WOMAN: I leave the
strategy to you.
Take any Genin you want and
leave within a half hour.
That's your mission.
MAN: Hang on a second.
WOMAN: What is it?
MAN: I think I'm
going to need Sakura.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next
time, "The Targeted Shukaku."
[theme music]