[theme music]
-All right, listen up Ino.
I'm not going to fight
with you over Sasuke.
-Sakura, you'd better
watch your step.
You have any idea who
you're mouthing off to?
Don't press your luck with
me little billboard brow.
-Did you hear stuff?
Sakura was so mean.
That's out of line, isn't it?
She sure made Ino mad.
I've never seen
her look so scary.
-Hm, yes.
But there's more
to it than that.
-Huh?
-Sakura isn't the kind
of person to do things
like needlessly flaunt her own
power, callously hurt people.
But she also doesn't like
having Ino take pity on her
and pull her punches.
SAKURA AND INO (VOICEOVER):
This time we do this right.
No holding back.
A fair fight.
And I'm going to win!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
"The Ultimate Battle.
Cha!"
INO (VOICEOVER): Just
a plain old jutsu?
-This isn't just some Ninja
Academy graduation exam.
Do you really think
you can beat me
with a basic ninja
art like that?
INO (VOICEOVER):
If I look carefully
I can find out which
is the real one.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): I've
sent chakra to my feet
for a burst of speed.
And then--
-What?
[shout]
[grunting]
-I'm not some cry baby any more.
You play with fire and
you're going to get burned.
Let's see your best Ino.
-It's not like I needed
your invitation, you know.
I'll give you my best, but
you're not going to like it.
-You're doing awesome
Sakura, awesome!
Believe it!
-Powerful strikes using chakra.
Top notch considering
she's a rookie.
-Huh?
-I've never seen
Sakura this good.
-Hold on.
You're not saying
she's better than me?
-No.
You're that's greatest.
Sending chakra all
throughout her body
and using it in conjunction
with a well timed jutsu?
I don't even think that Sasuke
could have done it better.
Well, even from the
start of her training
she was extremely good
at chakra control.
So this isn't a surprise.
ROCK (VOICEOVER): Yeah!
Magnificent movement Sakura.
[grunting]
ROCK (VOICEOVER):
No matter how good
Sakura is, Ino is just as good.
This battle will rage
for quite a while.
[punching]
INO (VOICEOVER): Man.
Since when did she
get this strong?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
(STRUGGLING) I can do this.
I know I can.
SAKURA AND INO:
You little-- Argh!
[grunts]
-Whoa
-At this rate this
battle will never end.
-This has been going on so long.
They've been at
it for 10 minutes.
-This isn't how this
was supposed to go.
How can you be evenly
matched with me?
-I guess you're right Ino.
You're obsession with
your looks and your hair
can't be surpassed.
I've been training too hard
to worry about that stuff.
-You're going to pay for that.
I've had enough of
you making fun of me.
-What an idiot.
Ino's falling for her trap.
She's so riled up
by Sakura there's
no telling what she'll do.
-Oh man.
I hate it when she's like this.
-Huh.
You think that'll help?
-Uh-oh I think she's
totally lost it this time.
-That's it!
[growling] See.
I don't need this.
NARUTO: And I thought
she looked scary before.
-All right.
I'll put an end
to this right now.
Get ready to tell everyone that
you lost to me Billboard Brow.
-Wait.
Don't tell me she's going to--
-Could it be?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Uh.
Oh.
If I recall, that sign is--
-I knew I recognized it.
It's the Mind
Transfer jutsu sign.
-Oh man.
That fool.
-Look, I know you're frustrated.
But that's pointless.
-Oh yeah?
We'll just see about that!
-Ninja art Mind Transfer jutsu.
It's a jutsu that
allows the user
to take over their
opponent's spirit
and wrest control of
their body away from them
for a few minutes
by discharging all
of their own spiritual
energy and striking
their enemy with it.
But despite its power,
there are major flaws
to this formidable jutsu that
makes it extremely dangerous.
First, the user's
discharged spiritual energy
can only fly straight, and it
moves at a very slow speed.
Second, even if the spiritual
energy misses the enemy
it can't return to the user's
own body for several minutes.
And this, in battles that are
most often measured in seconds.
I should add that while the
spiritual energy is gone,
the user's body, your body
Ino, can't move at all.
It'll be little
more than a doll.
-The Mind Transfer jutsu
is only used for spying.
It's not a battle jutsu.
Ino, using that jutsu here
wouldn't just be a bad idea,
it would be a fatal mistake.
-It's a powerful jutsu.
But as long as Sakura can dodge
it, it's not really a threat.
Plus, if she can avoid
it, she can attack Ino
without any resistance.
If that happens,
Hayate will be forced
to bring the match to an end.
-So what?
I don't care.
I won't know unless I try.
-If you miss, it's all over.
You do know that, right?
-She's only supposed
to use this with me,
so I can immobilize
the enemy first
with my Shadow Possession jutsu.
If she uses it this
way it'll never work.
-There's no way
she'll hit Sakura.
-Huh?
-Don't do it!
-Nina art Mind Transfer jutsu!
[dart sound]
-Did it work?
-Ha, ha, ha.
What an unfortunate choice Ino.
-So it's all over right?
-I can't believe she did it.
-You're done Ino.
No way!
-You fell for it Sakura.
Ha!
I finally caught you.
-It can't be.
-Ha, ha, ha.
I'm afraid it can.
All those hand signs earlier
were just an act to fool you,
to trick you into running right
into the trap I laid for you.
And It worked.
Now you can't move
at all can you?
You're being held by a special
rope that's made from my hair
with my chakra poured into it.
Now that you're trapped
I can take over your body
and make you say that you're
giving up on this match.
-There's no way I'll ever
miss with this jutsu now.
-Now I see.
-That little fool.
So losing it was
just an act too.
-You gotta get out
of there quick!
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
[grunting] I can't move.
-Now, Mind Transfer jutsu!
-Ha, ha, ha.
That's really unfortunate.
-Ino missed.
-Hm, no wait.
-Sakura has been--
-Nice one Sakura.
-Not quite.
NARUTO: I don't get it.
What's with Ino,
and with Sakura?
I mean, Sakura's acting really
strange, don't you think?
This is her chance.
Do it already Sakura!
Attack!
-Ha.
It's futile.
-The Mind Transfer jutsu worked.
Sakura's done for.
-Huh?
The Mind Transfer?
Does that mean that--
that Sakura has?
-Yes.
I'm afraid so.
Sakura's spirit has been
completely taken over by Ino.
-What?
-Ino's spirit is
inside of Sakura now.
I'm guessing that Ino's
goal is probably--
INO (VOICEOVER): And
just like that it's over.
Now then Sakura, if
you'd be so kind.
-Now, I, Sakura Haruno, would
like to say that I with--
NARUTO: No!
Sakura don't!
-Gah, man, that kid's
just so annoying.
-You worked so hard
to get here Sakura!
Don't disgrace yourself now by
losing to that lame Ino girl!
-Yell all you want.
There's nothing you can do now.
-Uh.
Huh?
What?
[grumbling] Ah!
What's happening?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Naruto's so annoying!
Yeah, he's right.
I can't let Ino beat me.
-Oh, Sakura.
This can't be happening.
-What's wrong are
you withdrawing?
Well, are you or not?
[screams]
-No, I won't be withdrawing.
Not today or any other day.
[punch]
-Ya!
You're mine!
-Which one is it?
-What in the world?
How can this be?
-Sakura.
INO (VOICEOVER): No way.
Ah!
But my jutsu is unbeatable.
-Ino, you're going to be in way
bigger trouble than you've ever
seen if you don't get
out of me right now!
INO (VOICEOVER): Ah!
-What's up with Ino?
Something looks wrong.
INO (VOICEOVER):
[struggling] No!
I can't hold on to her!
-Release!
-It can't be.
She did it.
She shattered Ino's jutsu.
-She must have used
up too much chakra
before attempting the jutsu.
So she didn't have enough
chakra to do it right.
-How can you have
two spirits in you?
Just what are you anyway?
-Someone who's just as
strong as she is beautiful.
I mean, a girl's got
to be tough if she's
going to survive
something like this.
-Once you're caught
in that jutsu
it's certainly not easy
to cast out the invader.
Ino's lack of
chakra contributed.
That's for sure.
But even more
important than that
were Sakura's defiant heart
and her combative attitude
towards Ino.
It also seems Naruto had
something to do with this.
His voice awakened
Sakura's spirit
allowing her to casting Ino out.
Just like I've seen in Naruto,
Sakura's fighting spirit
is stronger than the others.
So she can overcome
obstacles that otherwise
would be beyond her abilities.
[grunting]
-But now both of them
are almost out of chakra.
This battle will come
down to brute force.
SAKURA AND INO:
This ends right now!
-Since neither combatant is able
to continue, by double knockout
no one gets through the fourth
battle of this preliminary.
This match is over.
NARUTO: What?
Sakura!
ALL: This can't be.
NARUTO: No way!
-Very well then.
-Good grief.
-Hey, Ino!
-Sakura, no!
-Sakura, wake up!
Are you OK?
-Shh.
-I don't think that
treatment will be necessary.
They'll probably just wake
up after a little while.
But they both certainly
put up a great fight.
-Yeah.
Despite her success
with Naruto and Sasuke
I didn't think Sakura had
what it takes to win here,
but she's grown a lot.
She may not have done as
well as she would have liked,
but still, a lot of
good happened here.
I really feel that it
was the right choice
to send her to
these Chunin exams.
-I'm so ready.
After watching that last
match, I'm fired up.
-So this is another genin
from the Sand Village.
-Go Tenten!
-This should be
interesting to watch.
[moaning]
-So you're finally
waking up, huh Sakura?
[gasp]
-Come on Tenten!
Use the power of youth!
-Nice Lee, let's
hear that support.
You can do it Tenten!
-Take her down Tenten.
INO: Our match is already over.
[gasp]
-So did I-- did I lose then?
-That's no fair.
I'm the one who wants to cry.
To think I tied with you.
I still can't believe
that happened.
Here.
Guess you finally got a flower
to bloom, a beautiful flower.
-Ino.
[giggles]
-But Sakura, the
next time we fight,
you don't get to take the
easy way out by fainting.
And don't forget, I won't
just hand over Sasuke to you.
Understand Sakura?
-Oh yeah?
Well, that goes double
for you Ino, you ugly pig!
-For the fifth match,
Tenten, Temari, get ready.
[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Anyone who says
that women are weaker
than men obviously
hasn't seen them fight.
As for me, I think that
these women are way scary.
And what can I say
about you Shikamaru?
Well, a lot actually.
You're a boring, lazy, average,
ordinary, good-for-nothing.
If you don't start putting
your whole heart into things
this exam will be over
real soon for you.
Next time, Killer Kunoichi
and a Shaky Shikamaru.
It just doesn't get much
more exciting than this!