[theme music]
-Does Moso really live here?
Come on, look at this place.
TENTEN: Yeah.
He's a very important official.
I expected luxury.
Golden sliding panels,
stuff like that.
NEJI: Keep your voices down.
You're being rude.
-No, it's quite all right.
The trappings of wealth and
power don't interest Lord Moso,
so he lives frugally, as
suits a man of his wisdom.
-Yeah, that's great and all, but
this is the most important guy
in the country after
the feudal lord, right?
So how come he acts
like he's broke?
-Naruto.
[laughing]
-My, my, how shameful of me to
receive you in such squalor.
-My Lord Moso.
-Huh?
You mean this old guy
who looks like he should
be working in some
dumpling shop?
[laughter]
-The old guy from some
dumpling shop, am I?
-Eh.
You gotta me kidding me.
-You idiot.
-Neji!
Hey!
What's the big idea?
-Please, my friends, make
yourselves comfortable.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I take it you are the
ninja from the Village
Hidden in the Leaves?
-From your right, Lord, allow
me to introduce Naruto, Neji,
and Tenten.
-Hm.
I hear you came face to face
with a Cursed Warrior that
appeared in Lord Moso's
residence last night.
-Yes, we did.
-Well then, how did it go?
Did you figure out the true
identity of the Cursed Warrior?
-You betcha, we did.
Turns out it's a real ghost.
-A ghost?
Oh, you don't say.
-You shouldn't just assume that.
-But it appears out of
nowhere and flies around,
because it's a ghost, Neji.
-Yeah.
And don't forget how when
we knocked off his helmet,
the armor was empty.
-There's always a
rational explanation
if you know where to look.
Sir, I'll give you my word.
I'll get to the bottom of this.
-Your resolve is
encouraging, young man.
we just installed
a new feudal lord.
This is no time for unrest.
Please eliminate these harmful
rumors of the Cursed Warrior
as soon as possible.
You are our only hope.
-Uh.
-I beg of you.
-Here are your chicken wings.
Dig in.
-You don't gotta tell me twice!
These look awesome!
That Moso dude seems like a
good guy, even if he is cheap.
-Oh yes.
For example, Lord Moso
allowed me to become a page,
saving me from poverty.
-The son assumes the throne
of his father, supported
and guided by a wise
second in command.
At first glance, it looks
like a stable government.
-What about the rumors
saying the old feudal lord
is back from beyond the
grave as the Cursed Warrior?
-Jealousy.
Maybe somebody doesn't
approve of the current feudal
lord having succeeded him.
-Got any idea who'd want
to say stuff like that?
-I hate to say it, but the
first one who comes to mind
is Lord Kome.
-You mentioned that name before.
That strategy guy who wanted
to become the big boss himself,
right?
-OK.
But then why would the Cursed
Warrior pay his place a visit?
-Maybe it was done to try
and deflect suspicion.
-You're a genius!
Yeah, that's gotta be it!
And, now that we figured
the whole thing out,
we nab old souffle or
toupee, or whatever
his name is, and
convince him to fess up!
Come on!
Pay for my wings and let's go!
-Idiot.
We can't just charge in
there without any proof.
-He is one of our
top strategists, so--
-Aw, man.
Way to spoil my fun.
-Your current feudal lord, Sagi.
I'd like to meet with him.
-I'm sorry, but Lord Sagi isn't
seeing anybody at this time.
-Aw, but you and Sagi are
bosom buddies, well, ain't you?
Help us out.
come on, please?
-Childhood friend
is a bit better.
-Sitting out here's gonna
help us meet Sagi how?
-It's worth a shot.
Many of his fondness
memories are of this lake.
Many of mine, as well.
Back when we were
children, Lord Sagi
would always come here to play
with his little sister, Lady
Toki.
I figured he might come around
today with his attendants,
if we're lucky.
-Only if we're lucky, huh?
-Sh.
Look.
There he is.
-Huh?
-Excuse me, Lord Sagi.
We've arrived.
-Thank you.
-Wow.
So that's Lord Sagi, huh?
What a cutie.
He's definitely my type.
-My watch's hands haven't moved.
Not since that one
fateful moment.
-Hey.
What's he doing just
sitting in there?
-Thinking back to
happier days, probably.
His memories of Lady
Toki are the only thing
that can comfort
my Lord's heart,
and even that
comfort is fleeting.
-Byakugan!
NEJI (VOICEOVER): This
feeling of menace--
but where is it coming from?
If it's not above the ground--
-It's coming from there!
In the water!
-Assassins!
Protect Lord Sagi!
-Not today!
-All right.
Who the heck are
you clowns, anyway?
Darn it.
You're not getting away!
-Wait!
Naruto!
-Huh?
What am I waiting for?
-They set off a paper
bomb in the water.
-That was a close one.
Chased after them
any further, and that
would've been the end of you.
-Whoa there.
Whoa.
Easy now.
Lord Sagi.
Are you all right?
-Yes.
I am unhurt.
-I'm glad.
Lord Sagi, it's
my great pleasure
to introduce these ninja
from the Hidden Leaf village.
They have come to our
land to figure out
the true identity of
the Cursed Warrior.
-They shouldn't have bothered.
Let me guess.
This was Moso's idea, wasn't it?
-Yes.
Because he feared for
your life, Lord Sagi,
and with very good reason.
If these three hadn't
been here, then--
-Hold your tongue.
-Forgive me.
-Wait just a second.
Don't you realize how
dedicated this guy is?
You don't know how he feels.
Chishima cares about
you, even if you don't.
And this mission?
Man, we're working for peanuts!
But the Hidden Leaf
Village agreed to send us,
'cause this guy's
such a loyal friend.
-I don't require his help.
-How very annoying.
-What did you say?
-That friendship is now
consigned to the past.
I have become a feudal lord,
but he remains the page
now and forever.
I have risen to great heights.
I can no longer see him.
-You dissin' friendship?
Go ahead, ya big snob,
and say it again.
I dare ya!
-No, Naruto!
-Hey, what gives?
Come on, let me go!
Guys like this are
just askin' for it!
-Guys like this
are feudal lords.
-Would that this shuriken had
buried itself in my throat
after all.
Proceed.
-Yes, my lord.
-Jeez, who does that
guy think he is, anyway?
-Gee, he's a feudal
lord, remember?
-Please try to find it in
your hearts to forgive him.
-Huh?
First that blowhard
called you worthless,
and now you're defending him?
-Sagi never used to
act like this before.
But his father and little
sister died one after another.
It was then that
his heart grew cold.
I understand.
-So that's what it was.
-But he'll turn back into
his old, kind self someday.
He just needs some time.
-Yeah.
I'm not holding my breath.
-The shuriken from before--
it has an odd shape, doesn't?
-Hm?
Let me take a look.
-Wait.
This weapon.
Is it familiar to you?
-Yes.
There are no ninja
in the Land of Birds,
but some of the guardsmen are
receiving special training.
-Do you think this is a
weapon those people would use?
-Yes.
-So then who commands
the guardsmen?
-Well, all of them answer
to the tactician, Lord Kome.
-Say what?
Kome again.
Yeah, I knew it.
NEJI: Use the Cursed
Warrior persona
to confuse the
public, this creating
a rift between
Lord Sagi and Moso.
Kome's original gambit
was divide and conquer.
But their relationship endured.
By Moso summoning
us here, Kome knew
this would all
soon come to light,
pushing him to try and
assassinate Lord Sagi.
-If we already figured out that
much charge, let's charge on in
and kick some tail.
-Hold your horses.
No charging.
Not until we find
the hard evidence
to support our hypothesis.
-So you're telling me
you want to be sure?
-And they said you
couldn't be taught.
-Neji.
Look at that.
-That's gotta be Kome.
I'd bet you anything.
-To think he'd go somewhere
without attendants,
even though the Cursed
Warrior might appear.
-All right.
Stay close.
-It's that temple, where
the Cursed Warrior showed up
last night.
-Something's fishy about this.
[gasp]
-He appeared again!
-Shh!
-Byakugan.
What?
It can't be.
-There.
Hard evidence.
See, I'm charging!
-Hey!
Naruto!
-I'm on to you, and
your so-called ghost!
-Who's back there?
-The jig is up, Kome.
The Cursed Warrior is
just one of your flunkies.
Yeah, what do you think of that?
-Excuse me?
-Where do you
think you're going?
-Naruto!
Get down!
-Bulls-eye!
Yeah, I got him!
-He's still kicking!
Not only is it a ghost,
but it's a ghost in armor
who knows how to take a hit!
-He made a whirlwind?
-Darn it!
Now I can't even see
the Cursed Warrior.
-Byakugan!
Shuriken shadow clones?
Eight Trigrams Palm Rotation!
Are you going to help,
or just stand there?
-Sorry.
I just never thought a
ghost could use ninjutsu.
-Listen.
It's not a ghost
inside that armor.
It's a ninja.
And quite a wily one, at that.
-This matches the shuriken
they threw at Lord Sagi
earlier today.
-He knows everything
that's going on.
We need him alive.
-I understand.
I'm on it!
-It doesn't matter
what this guy knows
if we can't get through that
whirlwind and take him down.
-Naruto.
-Huh?
-Don't let me down.
-All right.
I'll give it my best shot!
-Hey, Tenten!
Keep his attention
focused on you.
Hit him with
everything you've got!
-Roger!
No good!
I didn't even scratch him!
-That's fine!
Just keep doing it!
-Now, Neji!
Time to do your thing!
-Gentle Fist Art, Eight
Trigrams, 64 Palms.
Two Palms!
Four Palms!
Eight Palms!
16 Palms!
32 Palms!
64 Palms!
-All right!
We did it, you guys!
-And this time we get to
see who's hiding in there.
-Why don't you take off
that mask and say howdy?
Huh?
-What is that stuff?
-Anyone else freaking out
that it's empty again?
-No-- this isn't possible.
MAN: Lord Kome,
we've confiscated
a suit of white armor, and a
number of guardsmens' shuriken
from a storeroom
within your residence.
The Cursed Warrior incident
and the assassination attempt
against Lord Sagi were both
orchestrated by one man,
and you're the prime suspect.
We're bringing you in.
Will you go quietly?
-I have no choice.
-Thank you all so very much.
I can't imagine
but that this will
help set Lord Sagi's
heart at easy.
-Looks like our work
in this town is done.
-Those guardsmen don't
waste any time, do they?
I mean, we only contacted
Lord Moso with all this
about an hour ago.
NEJI: It was different.
-Huh?
-Tonight's Cursed
Warrior was different.
There was an energy inside,
from a living, breathing human.
-A human being?
-But you said you
didn't feel anything
like that when we
fought him last night.
-I know.
-So the vibe was different.
OK, what does that mean to us?
-It means, there isn't
one of them, but two.
[theme music]
-Why are we returning
to the village?
We don't know what's
really going on.
If we're gonna investigate,
we just start here, right?
What?
I wonder if this weird
thing is-- Oh, I get it!
To think he'd use
this to get around!
Pretty clever there,
Cursed Warrior.
Huh?
Why did it appear here?
Next time, Too Late For Help!
[theme music]