[theme music]
-[laughs]
-Naruto!
CHOJI: Incoming!
-Thank goodness.
You're just in the nick of time.
-Oh, yeah!
Hey Naruto, you OK down there?
-Never better.
You saved my life just in
time to crush me to death.
-Just doing my job, man.
-Ahh!
-Chubbies rule!
-Choji, don't do it!
It's not going to work on him!
-No fair.
-[laughs] Isn't water amazing?
Whatever you throw
my way, this bubble
will protect me from the
impact In here, my defense is
iron clad.
-That is kind of cool.
-Now what?
-Flower Ninja Art,
Bloom Myriad of Flowers!
-Whoo!
You save me there.
-Where'd he go?
-Shouldn't play with fire.
Somebody could get hurt.
-No matter how many knives
you have up your sleeve,
all the water in the
ground is at my disposal,
waiting to be used.
-So how do we beat a
ninjutsu that never runs out?
Maybe we better--
-Run really fast?
-It's called a tactical retreat!
-Sorry, but you're
not getting away.
Summoning jutsu!
Dinner time!
[music playing]
-This way!
We got to keep running!
If that water catches
us, we're sunk!
-They're coming around
on this side also!
-They're trying to head us off!
-[laughs] Better not slow down.
My pets haven't been fed
for a very long time.
-We can't outrun them forever.
-You think?
Guess we'll have to
beat him up after all.
-Great!
How?
Nothing we're trying has
hurt this guy even a little.
-Darn it!
Ah!
Notice anything weird
about the way he runs?
-Huh?
Yeah?
Like what?
-I don't know.
-Why did you ask then?
-Wait a second.
Naruto, are you talking
about how he holds his tonfa?
-Oh, yeah, huh?
This guy carries his tonfa
like they're dowsing rods.
-That's what it is.
-It's called dowsing.
You just concentrate hard
on what you're looking for,
and they react when you're
getting close to it.
-What, dowsing rods?
Of course!
Naruto, Choji,
maybe there's still
a chance we can win this fight.
-Huh?
-If those tonfa are the
secret of his attack,
then maybe-- follow my lead!
-I think it's time we bring
this chase to a finish.
NARUTO: Shadow Clone Jutsu!
-Huh!
Child's play.
You're not getting away from me!
-I'm not going anywhere!
-Huh?
[laughs] You almost had me
there for a second, didn't you?
But not quite.
-What the--
-I'm starting to
think that maybe I've
been going a little
too easy on you.
-Ahhhh!
-Hey, what's all
the yelling for?
-Run, Choji!
Run for your life!
-Huh?
Yaaa!
[screaming]
-Ah!
-Yurinojo, you've
got to be more-- oh!
-Yurinojo!
Choji!
Get out of there!
Behind you!
Look behind you!
Just turn around!
-Hmm?
-I said you need to turn around!
Turn!
Look!
-Ahhh!
-Choji!
-[screaming]
--[laughs] Fight's
over, time to eat.
Our special for
tonight, raw shinobi.
-Oh, this fight is
over, all right,
but all you're going to get
is a big knuckle sandwich.
-How's that?
-Bottom's up, Choji!
Drink that water
as fast as you can!
-Hmm?
Um-hm!
-[laughs] Clever, but pointless.
I'll just keep calling up
more until I finished you all.
What's wrong?
Where is it?
-Sorry, but you're
in for a dry spell.
-What do you mean?
-The water you depend on
is nowhere to be found.
Take a good, long look around.
That's right.
We're standing on solid
rock, and so are you.
[thump]
-Urp!
Oh, you needed that?
-Yurinojo's onto your secret, so
no more funny stuff out of you.
You know, he wasn't
the only one who
thought you were acting fishy.
When I went to check
the trap earlier,
I took a shortcut that led
through this huge outcropping
of rocks.
I half expected
to see you there.
In fact, I was kind of
surprised you weren't.
Now I understand why.
YURINOJO: The answer was
right in front of us.
Naruto never saw you
when he took his shortcut
because you were steering
clear of areas without water.
You wielded those tonfa
not only as weapons,
but as dowsing rods.
And as soon as you
couldn't rely on them,
we were able to lure
you onto drier terrain.
-Hold on.
So that was the reason
you cracked my tonfa?
-Clearly it wasn't
mere coincidence.
-Of course if wasn't.
Yurinojo was able to figure out
exactly what you were up to.
-I got a lot of
water weight now,
so this one's going to hurt.
-Watery Human Boulder!
-Ahhh!
[laughter]
-He threw a shark
at the wrong ninja.
-Yeah!
-Oh!
-Huh?
-Yurinojo!
-It's my ribs.
Don't worry about me.
There are three of these thugs.
Go on, make sure
the princess is OK.
I beg of you.
-Consider it done.
Choji, stick around
and make sure he's OK.
YURINOJO: Thanks.
-Hinata may be fast,
but I can catch up.
--[gasping] I have
to rest for a while.
-Good idea.
We can wait for the
others right here.
-[gasping]
We will do no such thing.
After I'm done
catching my breath,
you're going to escort me to
safety, and that's an order.
-But Naruto and the others
haven't shown up yet.
-Well, that's their
problem, isn't it?
If they do get into trouble
out here, it's their own fault.
I wanted to use the
peasants as decoys,
but you three insisted
on the long way.
We'd all be home free by now
if you ninja weren't so soft.
-How could you after
what happened to
-What's the problem?
Every ninja risks his
life to perform his duty,
and Kikunojo was aware of that.
Even if he dies, if
I'm alive then there's
still a chance that
the Land of Greens
might exist as it once did,
but that hope perishes with me.
-Princess--
-Hinata, you can't imagine
the things I've been through.
Taken from my parents and held
hostage in a foreign land,
bullied night and day.
But that suffering has
taught me a valuable lesson.
I realized while I was just
a child anyone foolish enough
to put their faith in people
deserves whatever they get.
Someone like your friend
Naruto, for instance,
who let's his emotions
cloud his judgment
instead of focusing on
the mission at hand.
A ninja like that who's too
weak to get the job done
is worthless.
-What do you know about Naruto?
You don't get to stand here
and judge him like that!
At least you had a mom and dad.
Naruto's an orphan.
He lives all by
himself, totally alone.
He's worked hard, trying to
win everyone's acceptance
and become the next
Hokage, giving it his all.
He's had a difficult
life himself,
but he would never
think of sacrificing
somebody else for
his own well-being.
You know why?
Because he's a good person,
and a good ninja too!
-And he's not the
princess of a feudal land.
-I-I'm sorry.
That was very rude of me.
-Hm!
Hinata, you're pretty fond
of Naruto, aren't you?
-Uh--
-Say no more.
Let's wait for the
others, shall we?
-Yes, of course.
-That pack must be really heavy.
Let me give you a hand.
-Oh, uh, thank you.
-Ah!
Stupid girl.
I'm not dying out
here, and that's final.
-Well, don't you look fierce
down there in the dirt.
-Jiga.
You got to help me.
I'm your brother.
-Doesn't matter to me, because
with you out of the picture,
instead of me getting
a third, Renga and I
can split the profits in half.
-But Jiga--
-It's nothing personal.
-Wait!
Listen to me.
No!
What are you doing?
Jiga!
Ahhh!
-[laughs]
-Hinata!
You all right?
-Naruto.
Oh!
Where is the princess?
-Beats the heck out of me.
I was about to ask you.
-I said let's wait for the
others, then I turned away,
and then--
-How'd you let an amateur get
close enough to clobber you
in the back of the head?
-I'm-- I'm sorry.
-She's out here somewhere,
and now she's all by herself.
-Naruto, wait.
Maybe we should head
back to the Hidden Leaf
and ask the Hokage
what to do about this.
-No!
We don't have time
to go ask for advice.
There are still two
more of these evil ninja
punks sneaking around.
And if the princess gets
caught by either of them,
they're going to snuff her out.
-But this isn't the mission
we were sent out to perform.
What if we can't
handle the other two?
Maybe we're not good enough.
-Good point.
You're right, Hinata.
This isn't the mission
we came out here to do.
But the princess, she's
running for her life,
doing the best she can, and
now she's doing it by herself.
Yeah, she's bossy and mean
and acts like the world
revolves around her, I know,
but what kind of person
would just writer her off?
-Well, if that's
how you feel, then--
-Here's the plan.
Yurinojo took a hit
to the ribs earlier.
You help Choji take care
of him while I go on ahead
and save the princess.
See you later.
-Naruto, be careful.
-Right over there!
MALE SPEAKER: Your reflexes
are pretty good, kid.
I see how you could beat Ruiga.
-I'm guessing you're
the second Janin then?
MALE SPEAKER: Well, gosh.
To think that a great ninja like
you knows about little old me.
You're lucky.
It's an honor getting
destroyed by Jiga.
Definitely something you can
brag about in the afterlife.
-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
-Huh!
-[gasps]
-How stupid do you think I am?
-This guy's no push over, and
what kind of ninjutsu is that?
Ahh!
-Didn't meet ninja, huh?
Once Renga and I have
bled this country dry,
we'll give your village a visit.
-What makes you think I'm
going to let you do that?
What the--
-Surprise.
You didn't know I had
magnetic ninjutsu.
-Ahh!
-Had enough?
Ahhh!
[music playing]
HARUNA (VOICEOVER):
I'm going to live
through this no matter what.
-Ahh!
-This is your tomb.
Hope you like it.
-Nah, ain't my style.
You can use it instead.
Oh, yeah?
Come on!
-[laughs]
-Man!
What the heck's
going on around here?
-What should I do?
I've been looking for Choji
but I can't find him anywhere.
Maybe they're not
out in the open.
Maybe they're in hiding.
Yes, of course,
that's probably it.
[music playing]
But this-- this is
Naruto's headband.
He's in trouble!
-While I was growing up, I
drank iron every single day.
Thanks to that, I have plenty
of metal floating around
in my body that I can use
as a magnet whenever I want.
And in case you hadn't noticed,
this mountain is full of iron.
As long as I fight you
here, I'm invincible.
-So you're a walking
magazine, huh?
-That's one way to
put it, but I also
have the power to magnetize
the things that I touch.
Would you like to
see an example?
All those rocks behind
you should do the trick.
-So how are you going to touch
them from way over there?
-Easy.
I already did.
Ninja Art, Magnet
Infinite Meteors!
Second one!
Third one!
-Ahh!
HINATA: Naruto!
-Huh!
Who have we here?
Don't worry, I'll take
extra good care of her.
[music playing]
-Hinata, stay away!
You were right.
This Janin is more
than we can handle.
-[laughs]
-Naruto!
[theme music]
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
What should I do?
My gentle fist won't work
against his ninja art.
It's tough, but I can't beat
him if I fight him head on.
But if I don't beat him
soon, Naruto's going to-- no,
I'm not going to
let that happen.
I'll find a weak
spot in this jutsu.
I'll stop this guy if
it's the last thing I do!
I promise!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Next time, "The Byakugan
Sees The Blind Spot!"
HINATA (VOICEOVER): I'm going
to give this one attack my all!