[MUSIC - HEARTS GROW,
"WAVERING"]
-Hey!
Hold it down in there.
Sorry if I kept you waiting.
But Naruto Uzumaki
is on the scene.
[growling]
-Just so you know, you're
not taking Gantetsu.
[panting]
TODOROKI: That's Gantetsu.
No.
Is that-- It can't be.
-You brat.
So you managed to
get out of my net.
-Your net's not so tough.
I could chew right through it.
I eat nets like
this for breakfast.
Heh heh heh.
[gnawing]
-Go ahead.
You can chew on that all day.
-Eh-heh-heh.
[crunching]
-Don't worry, Gantetsu.
I'll get you out of here.
-It's a waste of time, you fool!
[glass shattering]
NARUTO: Gah!
Think you can stop me?
I'll get out of this.
You just wait!
-Not alive you
won't, little boy.
-Aah!
-Naruto!
-Heh heh.
[explosion]
-Oh.
-You're going down.
[thud]
-I hate to steal
your line, but I
think you're the one going down.
-Huh.
Shadow clone jutsu!
Get going!
Like I said, you're going down!
-Ah.
-Heh, heh, heh, heh.
[wind sound]
-What?
What's that?
-Pardon me for dropping in.
-The kid!
The kid caught inside my net
knows where our treasurer is.
-Oh.
[crashing]
-Well done, Monju.
[evil laughing]
-Akio!
-Akio?
-(IN UNISON) Oh no, Akio--
where is he taking them?
-Thanks a lot.
-Gantetsu, did I hear you right?
Did you call him Akio--
the boy who was taken?
-You heard right.
That is his name.
That boy is your-- he
is your younger brother.
-Oh.
-Huh?
-He is?
-No, that's a lie.
Akio was-- he died.
In the flames.
I saw it myself.
[muffled screaming]
-Akio!
[wood crashing]
-You should know.
It was you who killed him!
-No, you're wrong!
-No way. Not Gantetsu.
He didn't kill anyone.
He saved Akio's life.
Same as he did with all of us.
-Five years ago-- it
was five years ago
that I first woke up to the
evil I'd been a part of.
When I found myself
carrying Akio.
-Akio!
Aah!
-Todoroki!
-You mustn't do that.
You'll only inhale the smoke.
I thought by saving
the boy maybe
I could make amends for
what we'd been doing.
But it wasn't enough.
[coughing]
There would always be
more of them to save.
More young victims like Akio.
That was when I first
came up with my plan
to destroy the Ninja Dropouts.
-Oh!
-You really mean that?
-Gantetsu--
-Gantetsu, are you all right?
-They didn't hurt you, did they?
-(IN UNISON) We were so worried.
SAKURA HARUNO: He rescued
them all from villages
that were attacked.
He secretly took care of
them with the treasure
he stole from the gang.
Since Akio was the
oldest, he helped
Gantetsu look after the others.
They're like a family now.
Gantetsu is like their father.
-My little brother-- to
think I found him only
to lose him again.
[sobbing]
-Akio!
[wind blowing]
-And just where do you
think you're going?
-I know where they've gone.
I'll find him.
I'll get him back.
-I'll get my brother
back, not you.
Your only job is to
show me where they are.
Then just stay out of my way!
-I understand how you feel.
But don't you think you're
forgetting something?
After all, he saved these kids.
He saved Akio too.
You wouldn't even have a brother
if it hadn't been for him!
-What is it you want?
Do you really expect me
to be grateful to him?
He's a murderer and a thief.
Have you forgotten
he's part of the gang
that killed my
mother and father?
GANTETSU: He's right.
My guilt can't be so
easily washed away.
Do whatever you want with me.
But after we get Akio back.
-All right then,
but I'm coming too!
-As am I. Sakura, you stay
and keep an eye on the kids,
all right?
-Leave them to me.
[cawing birds]
-Hey, are you OK?
-For years, five long years,
I've lived hating that man.
[muffled screaming]
I can't change the way I feel.
It's too late.
-The important thing right now
is saving your little brother.
-Yes, I know.
And I will save him.
I will not fail this time.
[beating and crying sounds]
-Ahh!
-Where is it, brat?
Where is the treasure?
AKIO: Ahh!
-Where have you and
Gantetsu hidden it?
Come on, talk.
-No matter what you
do, I'll never tell.
-Aren't you the
little tough guy.
[crickets]
-(WHISPERING)
That's the hideout?
It's the size of a village.
GANTETSU: The big one's
where Shura lives.
He's the leader.
I'm certain that's
where we'll find Akio.
-Akio.
[gong]
-Hey, don't just go
running in there.
Terrific.
[clattering woodblocks]
-Great.
Now they know we're here!
-Ahh!
Ha!
-Oof.
-Ugh.
[sounds of fighting]
-Go on ahead.
Let me handle this.
-Got it. they're all yours.
-Oof.
TODOROKI: Akio!
GANTETSU: This way.
The cellar.
That's where Shura would
take him to question him.
-He's a fully trained shinobi.
No telling what this
guy's got in store for us!
-Best if I go first.
TODOROKI: Akio!
-Todoroki, wait!
-Gantetsu, out of the way!
-Stay back!
NARUTO: Gantetsu!
-Akio, I'm here!
-Hey, are you all right?
[evil laughing]
SHURA: Only one rat was
caught in the trap, eh?
NARUTO: Shura!
SHURA: That is
one stubborn brat.
He wouldn't tell me a thing.
But I've thought of another
way of finding the treasure.
So I have no use
for any of you now.
[fire and explosion]
[groaning]
[evil laughing]
-Don't just stand
there, get after him!
Don't worry, I'll be fine.
These bars are nothing.
[groaning]
NARUTO: OK, if you're
sure about this.
Todoroki, I'm leaving
them in your care.
[whimpering]
[sounds of fire]
-Hm? Heh.
'Til we meet again.
-Multi-Shadow Clone jutsu!
[explosions]
[groaning]
[whimpering]
[bars creaking]
-Here, take Akio.
Hurry!
[whimpering]
-Hey, snap out of it!
[breaking wood]
[wind blowing]
-Hm?
-Ahh!
SHURA: Ninja art-- blood rain!
[shooting]
-You're going to
pay for what you've
done-- starting right now!
[explosion]
-Ahhh!
-No!
[coughing]
[muffled screaming]
-(IN HIS HEAD) So
that's what it was.
He was-- he was
trying to say Akio.
And I thought, all
this time I thought--
[gasping]
-Give him to me Gantetsu.
Hurry!
-Mm.
-Brother.
I always knew you'd
come for me someday.
-You're going to
be all right, Akio.
-Brother-- it really is
you, my brother, isn't it?
[wood crashing]
-That's the end of
the Ninja Dropouts.
-Yeah.
-Good riddance.
Hey, whatever
happened to Naruto?
-Huh?
NARUTO: Look out below!
-Oh?
NARUTO: Don't give
up, don't despair.
Naruto Uzumaki at your service!
Ahh!
[chirping birds]
-Thank goodness
you're all right!
[children cheering]
SAKURA HARUNO: Hey,
are you OK, Akio?
AKIO: Yeah.
SAKURA HARUNO: No, you're not.
You're hurt!
AKIO: Don't worry.
I'm all right, really.
-They had a pretty
rough time, Sakura.
You better take a look at him.
-Right, I'm on it.
-Treat Akio first.
No more interruptions.
Take me to the capital.
TODOROKI: In my heart I can't
forgive you for the crimes
you committed.
But it's true.
You saved my brother.
I'll report there
was a rescue attempt.
All of the Ninja
Dropouts were killed,
and the prisoner
along with them.
-Oh!
-You mean it?
-You sure, Todoroki?
[children cheering]
-You'll be staying too, right?
You belong here with Gantetsu
and all these other children.
I wasn't much of a big brother.
Here's your chance
to be a better one.
Be their big brother.
-I'm going to try.
What is it?
-Something I was going to
give you five years ago.
-Thanks brother.
That means a lot.
-Let's be off, Leaf Ninja.
-Right!
[children cheering]
-See you later!
-Good bye.
-Good bye everyone.
NARUTO: Uh, one thing
we forgot about.
How do we find our way out
of here without Gantetsu?
-Well we can't go back.
-This looks familiar.
Are we going in circles?
-Oh, without something to
eat I cannot go another step.
NARUTO: Somebody send out a
mission to rescue the mission!
THEME SONG: Japanese lyrics...
-Naruto, what on earth
were you thinking?
-What?
He was hurt, so I took
him to the hospital.
-But to bring an outsider
into the village?
-Yeah, he's OK.
Trust me.
-How do we know what he is?
He has amnesia.
How do we know he's not
an enemy spy, or worse?
-What do you say,
Grandma Tsunade?
GRANDMA TSUNADE: I'll
allow it this time.
But you're his keeper.
And I'll hold you responsible
for everything he does.
Now get out of here!
NARUTO: Next time,
"Vanished Memories!"
[music - saboten, "scenario"]