[theme music]
-Sasuke!
Are you gonna run off again?
-So it's you.
Hopeless little knucklehead.
She sent you, huh?
-I did everything I could.
I tried, but I couldn't stop
him from leaving the village.
At this point, there's only
one person who can stop him.
Only one who can save him.
Naruto, it's all up to you.
Naruto.
This is a one in a
lifetime request.
Just bring him home.
Please bring Sasuke back to me.
-Like I already told Sakura.
It's over.
Just leave me alone.
Look at you.
What's with the angry face?
-Iruka-sensei, why does
a great ninja like me
have to be in the same group
with a slug like Sasuke?
-Sasuke had the best scores of
all the graduating students.
Naruto, you had
the worst scores.
To create a balanced group,
we put the best student
with the worst student.
-Just make sure you don't
get in my way, loser.
-This is no big deal.
I can go without
eating for days.
For weeks!
Believe it.
This is no big deal.
[gurgling]
-No problem.
-Here.
You-- You know, you asked Sakura
for advice when she was here.
So what did she tell you?
Let's go back.
-All right!
-You should see the
look on your face.
You look like a total loser.
-Huh?
Why did you--
-You.
I hated you.
-I didn't ask for this!
I didn't ask for you to save me.
-I don't know.
My body just moved.
There was no time to think.
You have to save Sakura if
it's the last thing you do.
-Sasuke.
You--
-I can hold him here
a little longer.
I lost everything once.
I don't ever want to
have to see that again.
My trusted comrades falling
right in front of me.
-Why?
Why are you doing this to us?
Sasuke.
I don't get it!
What happened to
make you like this?
Why are you doing it?
-Why should you care what I do?
It's my concern, not yours.
I have my own path
to follow now,
and neither you nor anyone
else can steer me from it.
I will tell you this much.
My days of playing ninja with
you kids at the Leaf village
are done.
-I'll handle him.
This guy is mine.
-Choji.
-Get going.
Hurry!
-Now, get going.
I'll be right behind you.
-Neji.
-Hang on!
-Kiba.
-Kiba!
Akamaru!
-Now, Naruto!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Shikamaru.
Ha, she fell for it.
-Well, what are you waiting for?
Go!
The thumbs up, Naruto, remember?
You gave it to Sakura.
You made her a promise.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Bushy Brow.
-Do not worry.
I can finish this one.
I promise.
-All of them.
they all risked their lives.
And why?
To save you!
-Well, wasn't that nice of them?
-Since no one has
anything to add,
I saved the most
important thing for last.
For as long as I've
known him, Sasuke and I
haven't exactly
been close buddies.
In fact, I don't
really like him at all.
All the same, Sasuke's a ninja
belonging to the Hidden Leaf
village.
He's a comrade, and I'll put my
life on the line to help him.
That's the way of our village.
-Not so fast!
You're gonna tell
me your comrades
risked their lives for nothing?
[thud]
-My comrades, huh?
If I'd stayed with
comrades like you,
I'd never have
gotten this strong.
Now I'm going to
where Orochimaru is.
-Are you out of your mind?
Orochimaru killed
the Third Hokage
and did everything he could
to destroy the Leaf village!
Whatever it is that
you're expecting from him,
you think he's gonna
give it to you for free?
All he wants is to use your
body like a new suit of clothes!
There'll be nothing of you left.
You'll never get
out of there alive!
You think I'll stand
by and just let
you throw away your entire life?
-None of that matters now.
The only thing that matters
to me is achieving my goal.
If you insist on
getting in my way,
well, then it can't be helped.
-Well, if you aren't
going to listen to reason,
then I'll do this by
force if I have to!
[laughter]
-What have you got
to laugh about?
I remember you laughing
the last time we met.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
The last time.
-What's so funny?
-I'm not laughing
because it's funny.
I'm just psyched.
'Cause I know that today is the
day when I finally beat you.
-Remember how thrilled you were
at the thought of beating me
to a bloody pulp?
What's wrong?
Where's your smile now?
-Shut up!
That was different!
Maybe I felt that way at first,
but you were different then.
-Let's just do this.
-Put on your
headband, and we will.
I'll wait.
-Not to worry.
I don't need that fit thing.
-Just do it.
Come on!
-There's no reason to put it on.
'Cause you won't be able to
make a scratch on my forehead.
-That's not the point.
Come on, you know
putting your headband on
is a testament to fighting on
equal terms as a Leaf shinobi.
-There you go, acting all
high and mighty again.
You don't honestly
believe that we're equal?
-Heck yeah I do.
All this time I've
never once thought
that I was inferior
to you in any way!
-You're a complete
embarrassment.
-Stop it!
-I didn't mean-- I never really
wanted that kind of fight.
Even now, I still don't.
-I couldn't give a
damn what you want.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): What is it?
This sudden burst of power
radiating from within me.
[laughter] So this is the
power he was talking about.
I can feel it growing,
flowing through my body.
If that's what I'm
capable of now,
wait 'til I unseal
this curse mark.
Imagine the power!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Incredible.
He's changed.
He never was this strong before.
You're crazy, Sasuke!
Wake up, will ya?
Before it's too late!
-I have woken up.
Don't you see?
That guy who dreamed of a
happy future full of peace
and friendship-- he was
the one who was asleep.
That's why I left the village.
That's why I've gone
in search of power.
It's not the future
I dream of anymore.
Only the past-- that's
where my dream lies.
-Wow, Itachi.
You nailed every target.
Even the one in the blind
spot behind the rock.
All right.
Now it's my turn!
-No, Sasuke.
It's time to go.
-What happened to the
new shuriken jutsu
you promised to teach me, huh?
-It'll have to wait 'til later.
I have an important
mission in the morning,
and I need to prepare for it.
-Hmph.
You're such a big, fat liar.
-Sorry, Sasuke.
Maybe some other time.
-Ow!
-Hm?
-OK, just watch this.
ITACHI: Hey!
Be careful!
SASULE: Whoa!
Ow!
[laughter]
-How come the one who
twisted his ankle is
the one who's laughing?
Or maybe you were
just looking for a way
to get out of walking home.
-No way.
That's not it.
It's just that I can't stop
thinking how I'm finally
going to start at
the academy tomorrow.
(VOICEOVER) I'm gonna give
it nothing but my best.
I'm gonna do so well that even
Father will be proud of me.
I'll make him see he has more
than one son he can count on.
-I'm warning you.
You're making a big mistake.
SASUKE: Like I said.
A future with you guys
isn't what I want anymore.
Fire Style.
Dragon Flame Jutsu!
[theme music]
-My body's overflowing
with power.
Feels like nothing can stop me.
And it keeps getting stronger!
This is power I
never could've known
if I'd stayed at home in the
Leaf with you and Sakura.
Don't you see that, Naruto?
But it's not enough.
This power, this burning hatred.
It's still not enough!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Next time, Brothers!
Distance Among the Uchiha!
[theme music]