[theme music]
-All right, kid.
You'd better come out of there
if you don't want to get hurt.
-I'm no kid!
And if you think we're handing
him over to you, you're crazy!
-Ninja Dropouts.
-Well, if that's
the way you want it,
then it's your funeral.
-Multi Shadow Clone jutsu!
-Ha!
Ninja Art-- Blood Rain!
You just didn't listen.
Augh!
-Todoroki!
All right, you!
Aaaaugh!
-My jutsu isn't ninjutsu--
it's a murder jutsu.
-Sakura!
[choking]
-That was close.
Are you going to be all right?
-Yes, just barely.
More importantly,
where is Naruto?
SHIP'S CAPTAIN: [coughing]
Is-- is everyone all right?
SHIPMATE: Yes, sir.
But Captain Todoroki
and the prisoner
are nowhere to be found.
SHIP'S CAPTAIN: What?
-Naruto.
-Where is he?
-Farewell.
-Get these off of me, you jerk!
-Watch out!
-Ugh.
-Huh?
[ship creaking]
-Hm?
-Huh?
Ah!
Aaah!
-Waah!
-I had him.
-Mother!
Father!
Akio!
Aaaaugh!
-Too bad-- your friends
can't save you now.
-Todoroki!
There you are!
Are you both all right?
-Yes, we're both fine.
-So what do we do now?
I mean, who knows how far away
Sakura and Bushy Brow are.
-I know what I must do.
My mission is to make sure
he is delivered to justice.
-Huh, easier said than done
with a ship split in half.
[gasp]
-Here they come again.
We've got to run.
Hey, we've got to get moving.
-I won't allow him to escape.
The safest thing is to
finish him off right here.
-What are you up to?
What the heck do you
mean, "finish him off?"
-He's certain to be found guilty
and sentenced to death anyway.
We can save them the trouble.
Better that than to let
his friends rescue him.
-Take it easy, they
haven't rescued him yet.
Let's go!
Your mission's the same as mine.
We're supposed to guard him, not
be his judge and executioner.
-I warn you, if you so
much as try anything,
your head will roll!
-What?
Uh!
Come on, move it!
[panting] That
will do it for now.
We've lost them.
-Just as well--
you seem exhausted.
-We've gone so deep
into this forest,
I just hope we can
find our way out.
TODOROKI: Don't worry,
we'll take our bearings
from the moon's transit.
We can't go back to the river.
Instead, we'll continue
on through the forest
to the capital.
That is my mission.
-Are you sure about that?
-What do you mean?
-I heard what you said.
You said you were ready to
finish him off on your own.
-That was when I
thought I had no choice.
-If you say so.
Then let's get moving.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I just
hope Sakura's all right.
-Where is he?
-Naruto will be all right.
He can handle himself.
-I guess.
-If we just keep moving, we
are bound to hook up with him.
-Follow me!
I sense something.
-Where is it?
[gasp]
-Above us!
-Ugh!
Well, Lee?
-We follow him.
If the enemy has
captured Naruto,
he will lead us to them.
-Hey.
-What is it?
-There's something I don't get.
We're supposed to be
following the moon, right?
Well then, how come the moon's
back there following us?
-Hm, that's peculiar.
-What the heck is going on?
GANTETSU: It's the
Forest of Bewilderment.
Once you get lost in
this place, you'll
never find your way out again.
-Whoa, he spoke!
-Nobody said you could talk.
Be quiet, prisoner!
-Wait, hold on a minute.
Maybe he knows something.
What is the Forest
of Bewilderment?
-All right, prisoner, tell us!
-I know everything about it.
This place is our hideout.
-It's your what?
-So then all this time when we
thought we were escorting you,
you were leading us
into your own hideout!
GANTETSU: It's the perfect
hiding place-- the fog,
winds that blow from
every direction,
magnetic fields so strong
that compasses are useless.
Someone who doesn't know this
place and gets lost in it,
is lost forever.
-Oh, yeah?
Well, I'll find my
way out all right.
-Not alive you won't.
-Oh.
-What?
-It takes someone
like me, who knows
every inch of this forest.
Listen, you'll never find
your way out without me
to guide you.
-What?
-Hm, good idea!
If this forest is
your gang's hideout,
you must know it like the
back of your hand, huh?
All right, then.
It's a deal.
You'll be our guide.
-What?
Are you mad?
-Our guide-- yes, you'd like
that, wouldn't you villain?
I believe you, when you say this
wretched place is your hideout.
That would explain why
you and your friends
are able to maneuver your
way through it so well.
-There you go!
-That's why we can't trust him!
Don't you understand?
All the time he's pretending
to lead us out of here,
he'll be leading us
deeper into his lair!
-Uh.
What do you think we should do?
-We have no choice.
We need to finish him-- now.
Or he'll most surely finish us.
-Whoa, uh, slow down.
-No one will care.
The world's better
off without him.
-Todoroki, wait!
[gasp]
-Who did that?
GANTETSU: Everything my comrades
and I stole from others,
I stole from them.
They wanted to know where I hid
it, and they didn't ask nicely.
My comrades aren't
coming to rescue me;
all they're after is the
money I took from them.
And once they have
all that money,
they'll want me
as dead as you do.
-Oh, is that right?
You expect me to believe that?
-Wait, hang on a second.
You said yourself, you believe
this is their hideout, right?
Which means that the others
must know their way around it
as well as he does.
Hm, which means that--
-Which means what?
-Hmmm, it doesn't really matter
if his friends are coming
to rescue him or to
tear him limb from limb.
The point is they're
coming, and we're
on their stomping grounds.
Which means they know
where they're going,
and we don't have a clue.
I think we have to trust him;
he's the only chance we've got.
Hm, well am I wrong, or what?
[crickets chirping]
[birds singing]
-Are you sure you know
where you're going?
-Yes, don't worry.
I'm taking a route they'll
never be able to follow.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I wonder if
we really can trust this guy.
Huh?
[gasp]
-Augh uh!
Ahh.
But why?
-Its venom has no effect on me.
I'm used to it.
-Really?
Because it sure would affect me.
-Yeah.
[water rushing]
[birds chirping]
-Well?
-What is it?
Is something wrong?
-No way!
Ugh!
-Aaaugh!
-Ugh.
-Ahh.
SHURA: [laughing evilly]
Man, you fell for it.
Ooh, get it?
You fell for it.
That's a good one!
-Hmmm.
-Watch it!
Ninja Art-- Crimson Mud!
Aaaugh!
[gasp]
-He he he.
He he.
Huh?
-Well, looks like
you fell for it.
That was the old Shadow Clone
and Transformation jutsu combo.
-The what?
-Shadow Clone jutsu!
Now it's my turn
to pick the game.
Aaaaah, Rasengan!
Huh?
Uh.
[gasp]
-Aah!
-I'm going to bury you.
-Grrr.
-Well first, you've
got to catch me, jerk!
-That won't be hard!
TODOROKI: Naruto!
[gasp]
-Gantetsu, stop!
I knew it!
You won't get away!
Huh?
[water rushing]
-[grunt]
-What the hell are you doing?
-[grunting]
[banging]
-What's that sound?
[growl]
-Here.
-What?
-What the heck?
Aaaah!
Shadow Clone jutsu!
Rasengan!
[evil laughter]
-Ugh!
Your timing couldn't have
been better-- thanks a lot.
[gasp]
-Ugh.
Uh.
-Hm.
-So you guys want to
tell us who you are?
-It appears that they
would rather fight.
TODOROKI: No, I won't
be fooled by you.
I won't!
-I'm going to stick
with you, big guy.
You seem to know
what you're doing.
-Huh?
-Aaaaah!
-Todoroki!
Ugh!
-Ya!
-Augh!
Ugh eh.
Uh.
-Ugh.
-Grrr!
-Stop it, Todoroki.
This isn't what your
mission's about.
You're supposed to get
him to the capital alive.
-Not this one-- he must
pay for what he did!
-What are you talking about?
-Let him live?
No, not him!
He slaughtered them all-- my
family, my little brother!
[gasp]
-He did what?
Gantetsu.
[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): OK,
maybe Gantetsu's as bad
as you say, but revenge
won't solve anything.
It won't bring your
family back, and you'll
be breaking your vow to deliver
him alive to the capital.
I don't know, it's
hard for me to believe
he could be as bad as that.
-But anyway, it doesn't matter.
If you won't listen
to reason, you
leave me no choice but
to stop you myself.
If you want him, you'll
have to go through me!
Next time-- Memory of Flames.
[theme music]