[music playing]
[theme music]
[rattling]
KIDOMARU: Heh.
It's over.
Huh?
What?
[groaning]
-(VOICEOVER) Just barely.
That was close, but I
was able to throw it
off course a little.
There's no mistake.
He's caught on to the
secret of the Byakugan.
-(VOICEOVER) Huh?
What's going on here?
How did he?
[panting]
What gives?
How could I miss it
by 15 centimeters?
[groaning]
I see-- that chakra.
All this time, he's been
releasing a steady flow
and surrounding himself with it.
And such a wide range.
It's no wonder he
sensed the arrow coming.
He was able to throw
off its trajectory.
[laughing]
It's got to be
killing him to keep
expending chakra on that level.
But if he doesn't keep it up,
he won't be able to dodge.
There's no doubt about it.
It's just as I thought.
My arrow was totally
invisible to him.
[groaning]
-(VOICEOVER) He makes
no pointless attacks.
He's been culling
information with every move.
[groaning]
And he's discovered the
weakness behind my eyes.
Impressive.
[groaning]
He's the strongest
opponent I've ever fought.
-(VOICEOVER) He's got
360 degrees of vision.
He can sense all attacks
within a 50 meter radius.
But for some reason,
he wasn't able to evade
a few of the kunai.
Why couldn't he evade them?
Of course!
Because he couldn't see them!
Or rather, his seemingly
perfect jutsu has a blind spot.
So if one of those kunai
hits that blind spot,
he can't react.
That's what that other jutsu
was for-- to compensate
for the blind spot
in his defense.
[crashing]
I've analyzed all my
attacks and fully grasp
the implications
of their outcome.
He has a blind spot
immolating from a small point
just behind the first
thoracic vertebra.
[groaning]
[metal clanging]
[laughing]
As long as he keeps
that blind spot moving,
it will be hard to sling
an arrow down its path.
That's not enough to stop me!
The gentle fist
is useless if you
can't get close to your enemy.
And you can't even
think of approaching me
right now in the
state you're in.
All you can do is run.
It doesn't matter if
you struggle or not.
Either way, you're going to die.
[panting]
Huh.
Looks like you're
almost out of chakra.
(YELLING) The weakest one in
the game always goes down first!
[panting]
It's useless.
[crashing]
[rumbling]
[gasping]
-(VOICEOVER) A thread?
I see.
He's using it to--
[groaning]
[grunting]
-(VOICEOVER) The trajectory was
thrown off by the trees, huh?
[grunting]
[groaning]
If that's the case, I'll
add a little spin this time.
Even if this one
hits a tree, it'll
slice right through
to find its target.
And just like the
first time, I'll
spin a thread
infused with chakra
to control the arrow until
it gets within his range,
even if he's moving.
I'll just pinpoint
his blind spot
and plunge the arrow into it.
[groaning]
[panting]
Still on your feet, huh?
-(VOICEOVER) He's strong.
Much stronger than I am.
I'm almost out of chakra.
I can't dodge another attack.
[panting]
Is this it?
-I vow to win!
[gasping]
-(VOICEOVER) Naruto.
What would you do, I wonder?
[panting]
I've had enough.
Besides, it's not like I
can dodge it anyway, is it?
[wind blowing]
-(VOICEOVER) He stopped moving.
Well, better safe than sorry.
Striking accuracy
120% destructive
power-- absolute maximum!
[explosions]
[groaning]
[arrow flying]
(YELLING) Got him!
[groaning]
[crashing]
[music playing]
[laughing]
-Here.
Gentle fist!
[music playing]
[groaning]
-(VOICEOVER) What?
What the-- he's still-- no!
That last shot should
have killed him!
-And chakra built
substances don't
stand a chance against
my gentle fist attack.
-Gentle fist.
Of course.
He funneled the last of his
chakra through the thread.
[squawking]
-(VOICEOVER) Eight crows.
And again, I couldn't
see one of them.
[gasping]
Where is he?
[falling]
[groaning]
-(VOICEOVER) He damaged
several of my internal organs,
but I can still move.
[groaning]
[panting]
-(VOICEOVER) You're a failure.
[laughing]
-I told you.
I just don't know
when to give up.
-Huh.
Why fight a hopeless battle
trying to defy your destiny?
-(ANGRILY) Because people
called me a failure!
I'll prove them wrong!
(YELLING) It may be the Hyuga
way to cave into destiny.
It's not mine!
I'll change the way of the Hyuga
clan after I become Hokage!
-(VOICEOVER) It's your
speciality, after all.
I was careless.
-My clones were pathetic.
That's right.
I flunked the shadow
clones jutsu every time.
[groaning]
So don't come whining to
me with this destiny stuff.
And stop trying to tell me
you can't change what you are.
You can do it, too.
Because after all, unlike
me, you're not a failure.
[groaning]
Naruto.
-Well, boys, it looks like it's
just the three of us left now.
-I don't think you have
to worry about that.
Choji and Neji are going
to catch up in no time!
Choji's got his
trump card with him.
And don't forget-- I fought Neji
in the Chunin exam, so I know.
-You know what?
-That guy is a true genius.
[music playing]
-(VOICEOVER) I cannot lose even
if my enemy is far stronger.
Even if my body should
fail me, I cannot lose.
[groaning]
There is a reason I cannot lose!
[music playing]
[grunting]
-(VOICEOVER) I let
it drag on too long.
I played too hard.
[groaning]
[yelling]
[screaming]
[groaning]
[music playing]
-(VOICEOVER) I can't
build up any chakra.
But how?
You should be dead!
Why are you still alive?
-I couldn't have
evaded you anyway.
So I decided to take
the hit deliberately.
And I know my weakness
much better than you do.
(VOICEOVER) Hm.
There were eight birds.
The Byakugan does
have a blind spot.
But knowing the direction
your strike was coming from,
I could release chakra
just to that one point
and watch for your attack.
Moving just a few inches
to evade the worst
was no great feat.
I'm seriously hurt.
But I'm still alive.
[panting]
[laughing]
-So you did it on purpose, huh?
Knowing you were going
to die here anyway.
Why would you go that far?
-You are the strongest
enemy I have ever fought.
But there is a reason
why I cannot lose.
Once-- not so long ago-- the
strongest person I ever fought
out of everyone said to me--
[coughing]
You can do do it, too.
Because after all, unlike
me, you're not a failure.
Those were his words.
All this time I've been called
a genius, so I cannot lose.
I can't let down those
who believe in me.
[music playing]
Heh.
The weakest one in the game
always goes down first.
That's what you said, wasn't it?
[panting]
[coughing]
Well, look where we are now.
[panting]
Fate isn't something
for you to decide.
[groaning]
-I don't know.
You look like you're sitting
at death's door, too, kid.
[groaning]
-Neji, my son.
The Hyuga bloodline trait
flows stronger in you
than in any other
member of our clan.
[gasping]
-But I will not die
as easily as this.
[laughing]
-Go ahead.
Try all you want.
There's no way you can stop it.
It's too late.
Sasuke Uchiha has
fled to the Sound
Village of his own free will.
[groaning]
Sasuke is in the darkness.
[panting]
-No.
-Hm?
-Naruto, sometimes your eyes
are even better than mine.
There's someone who can
find him in the darkness.
And save him from this path.
KIDOMARU: Huh.
Sasuke belongs to
Lord Orochimaru now.
I don't care who it is.
They can't save him.
NEJI: He will!
[groaning]
Because Naruto, it was you.
It was you who saved
me from the darkness.
[groaning]
-Talking rubbish
right up to the end.
[choking]
[groaning]
-(VOICEOVER) I haven't been
pushed this far since Kimimaro.
[panting]
[heart beating]
-(WEAKLY) Curse you.
[heart beat fading]
[music playing]
NEJI (VOICEOVER): Everyone,
the rest I leave to you.
[music playing]
[theme music]
[dog barking]
-Yahoo!
The enemy is close.
I can feel it.
-All right!
Let's pick up the
pace, you guys!
-Now that we outnumber them,
it's time for a little payback.
BOY: Oh, yeah, don't forget
it's four against two.
NARUTO: Four against two?
BOY: Yeah, double their numbers.
NARUTO: Hold on, how
do you count four?
BOY: What, are you an idiot?
There's me, Akamaru,
Shikamaru, and you.
You know how to
count, don't you?
[dog barking]
NARUTO: Next time-- "The
Vessel Arrives Too Late."
[theme music]