[theme music]
RAIGA: Why?
Why do you go so far?
-I will become so
strong that Guy-sensei
can smile at me with pride.
Because that is my
way of the shinobi.
-I see.
That explains it.
Your whole life is devoted
to this sensei of yours.
Well, maybe this Guy
person can be the one
to hold your funeral!
What with all your hard
work and devotion I'm sure
he'll shed a tear!
-Ninja Art Thunder
Dragon Tornado!
-Hustle now, hustle.
-Come on, mom.
Quit pushing me.
I can't run that fast.
This thing is too heavy.
-That's enough of that.
I said hustle.
We don't have time
for your nay-saying.
[screaming]
-Please, hurry.
We don't have much time.
-Right.
You guys, I'm gonna go on ahead.
-Go get him, girl!
-Where'd he vanish off too?
Did he evaporate to the bone?
[gasp]
-Hey!
Come on, Lee.
Snap out of it.
-Hustle!
Hustle!
-Huh?
[panting]
-Hustle.
Hustle.
-I can't run anymore.
-Grandma Sancho, quick!
The Curry of Life!
-You got it.
Nice and hot!
Now get going.
We can look after Lee for now.
You just worry about getting the
curry to Neji and Naruto, dear.
-Ranmaru, wait here.
OK?
-Mhm.
-I'm going to go
ahead and find Naruto.
Take care of everyone.
-Ow!
-You're helping too.
Now get your butt over to Neji!
-Sure thing, mom.
No problem.
-Now then.
I need you to hold Lee's
mouth open, all right?
-Oh.
Sure.
-Down the hatch.
[chewing]
-Even the Curry of Life
couldn't help the poor boy.
[scream]
-Heavens!
Guess he's OK.
-You doofus.
This isn't the time
to go passing out.
[scream]
-What the heck do you
think you're doing?
-Does that mean you're awake?
-Wait.
Hold on a minute?
What are you doing here?
I thought you fell off
the cliff, didn't you?
-It was just a trap, Naruto.
You couldn't figure that out?
-Are you kidding?
I can't believe I fell for that!
-Neji.
Neji.
-Here.
It's the Curry of Life.
Try to eat some of it.
You'll feel better.
-Neji?
Neji!
[eating sounds]
-Thank goodness.
it's good to see you
on your feet again.
-The earth is spinning.
-He's acting kind of
funny, don't you think?
-Oh dear.
Quickly now!
We don't have much time.
Put the Curry of Life in here.
Pot and all.
-OK.
-Hot!
Ow!
Agh!
Ugh!
Oh no!
Not the curry!
GRANDMA: Oh, my my, my my, my.
-This is bad.
-Nothing to do about it now.
We have to get going.
-It was that bottle of wine.
-Do you think he's
going to be OK?
-Well, the truth is
we had bit of a mix
up with the ingredients.
But that's all right.
It should be just as
effective I believe.
-Hm.
Yeah, but--
[laughter]
[thunder]
-Hm?
Mercy.
He's headed over
in our direction.
-Don't worry, Sancho.
I'll go out and talk to him.
-Hm?
So you're still alive
after all, are you?
Well, this time I'll
do the job right!
-Raiga.
-Ranmaru.
I don't believe it.
You're alive.
-Why's Ranmaru here?
-It's complicated.
He offered his own
chakra to Raiga
and brought him back to life.
-What?
-But all of that effort
wiped Ranmaru out.
Raiga found him unconscious
and assumed he was dead.
-So that's what he
was raving about.
He kept talking about Ranmaru
looking down on him from above.
-There is a silver lining.
I got Ranmaru back to the
Curry of Life shop at least.
-Thanks for filling me in.
-Nothing will ever
separate us again, Ranmaru.
Now, let's off these brats and
get back to strewing mayhem
like we always have.
-Whatever you say, Raiga.
-Where did all
this fog come from?
-It's OK.
We're together again now.
I'll be your eyes.
-Yeah. that's right.
As long as I have
you at my side,
there's nothing for me to fear.
-Yes.
Let's leave now, Raiga.
-What about them?
-Don't worry.
They're all dead.
-Enough said.
Time to seek out new prey then.
[gasp]
-They're heading right for that
steep cliff in front of them.
-I don't get it.
What the heck does
Ranmaru think he's doing?
-He wouldn't-- Is he trying to
atone for his sins with Raiga?
I think he plans to lead
them both over the cliff
to their deaths!
-Are you kidding?
-What's your problem?
Jerk!
Huh?
-What was that?
RANMARU: Lee!
-Hey there.
How's it going?
Here I come!
-What is he doing?
You little brat.
You're pretty quick
to recover, huh?
-Eh-heh.
-Huh?
Quit playing with me!
What?
He's fast.
[scream]
-Ranmaru, are you relocate OK?
-Yeah.
-I need you to stay
put, all right?
-No!
Take me with you.
-Ranmaru!
Ranmaru, where are you?
You little-- You'll
pay for this!
Ninja Art Thunder Armor!
[slurred mumbling]
-Bring it on.
-I'll destroy you!
-Here I go.
[groan]
That was quite a blow.
If I hadn't donned
my Thunder Armor,
I'd be giving myself a funeral.
So that I always remember
how hard you fought here,
I'll take care of your funeral!
NARUTO: Not so fast!
-What do you think you're doing?
RANMARU: I've brought
you the Curry of Life.
I want you to try it.
RAIGA: What?
RANMARU: If you do, you'll
understand you're not alone.
It's spices blend together like
the feelings of all mankind.
RAIGA: What are you saying?
RANMARU: We've hurt too many.
Please.
We have to stop.
RAIGA: No!
That's enough!
You've always been
my eyes and ears.
If you don't stop spouting
this selfish nonsense,
we can no longer be as one.
-Strike me with
your lightning then.
If I die, the mighty
Raiga falls as well.
For we will always be as one.
-Ranmaru.
I won't be able to remember
you the way you were anymore.
I have to give you a funeral!
-Raiga, stop it!
Right now.
Multi-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
-Huh?
That is a lot of Narutos.
I-- I must have been out
of it for a little while.
-You little snot!
It doesn't make a difference
how many of you there are!
-Neji!
Wake up!
[groan]
-What are you doing, Neji?
Lets go.
Here.
Eat this and pull
yourself together.
We're in a lot of trouble.
-But that's--
Great.
Now you've done it.
-This kid risked his
life to say save you.
You'd really kill
him by your own hand?
-Ranmaru betrayed me.
He broke his promise to
stay at my side forever.
-That's because he doesn't
want to be by himself anymore.
Ranmaru has people
that care for him now.
He knows his life will
be better laughing
with the rest of the world,
instead of crying with you.
-Naruto.
-Look, Ranmaru.
You were planning
on ending your life
with this guys, weren't you?
You put that out of your head.
You're free now.
Trust me.
I'm not going to let Raiga
hold anymore funerals.
Not for you or for anybody!
-Hey.
I've heard just about
enough of your crap,
you little pipsqueak!
-What did you say?
-Don't underestimate me.
You stand before Raiga
Kurosuke of the Mist,
once counted as a member of
the Seven Ninja Swordsmen.
I don't take orders
from the likes of you.
-Yeah.
That's right.
I almost totally forgot.
A long time ago, you were
one of the Seven Swordsmen.
You never did answer
my question before.
Kisame.
You know him, don't you?
RAIGA: Kisame.
I can't stand that lowlife.
Next time I see him he's
getting a funeral for sure.
NARUTO: What?
RAIGA: I despise him.
I hate all the Seven
Ninja Swordsmen!
Ranmaru, you're the only one
who's ever been a friend to me
in this life.
RAIGA: But you
don't need me now.
You've made other friends.
We'll never be two halves
of the same soul again.
-Raiga.
RAIGA: Impudent wretch!
Who was it that taught you
about the outside world
to begin with?
A funeral is is!
[groaning]
-Clone Spinning Axe Kick!
Shadow Clone Body Slam!
RAIGA (VOICEOVER): Ranmaru,
you're finally free now.
-Raiga.
-Come, lightning!
Give me a funeral
worth remembering!
RANMARU: Stir the
pot nice and hot.
Stir-- Ow.
-Come on Let me hear you.
You can't made the one
and only Curry of Life
unless you put your all into it.
Now stir it like you mean it.
-Is that so?
-Mom!
What the heck did
you do that for?
-Don't you mom me!
It's about a hundred
years to soon
for you to be preaching
about the family curry.
You and this child
are on equal ground!
You're starting your training
over from the beginning!
-Come on!
-Grandma Sancho?
-Huh?
-It is time for us
to get going now.
-Thanks for your help.
-Yeah.
I know you'll take
food care of Ranmaru.
-He's in good hands.
His training will be merciless,
but before you know it,
he'll be cooking
the Curry of Life.
-Ranmaru, Karashi,
best of luck to you.
-Thanks.
-Hold on a sec.
The Village Hidden in the Leaves
is more than just a hop, skip,
and a jump away, you know.
I've whipped up a
special batch that'll
give you 10,000 times
the strength you'll
need for the journey.
Now have a seat and get
some food in your belly.
-Huh?
-That's the reddest curry
I've ever seen in my life.
-Yeah.
No kidding.
My eyes are burning
just looking at it.
-Wow!
Such culinary delights!
-What the?
NEJI: Lady Tsunade will kill
us if we don't get back soon.
NARUTO: Oh yeah.
Yeah, yeah!
We're really sorry, but
we better get going.
TENTEN: Wait up, you guys!
-My goodness.
It's not every day
you meet children
so well mannered and kind.
-No!
My curry!
[theme music]
NARUTO: One's duty
as team captain--
give out effective orders
to your subordinates
and carrying out
the mission while
protecting the lives
of your squad Oh man!
That is so cool!
It's like they were
writing about me!
The shinobi destined to
be top dog around here.
All right.
This'll be my fast track
to the title of Hokage!
Next time-- Follow my Lead!
The Great Survival Challenge!