[theme music]
-Akamaru!
[barking]
-Wait up, Akamaru!
-Naruto, I, uh-- Well, I--
I made some lunch for you.
If you're hungry, go ahead.
-Ah, thank you.
Hm.
You gotta be kidding.
Why are you guys acting
all goofy out here?
This isn't a picnic, you know?
-You're right.
Sorry.
-Aw, come on.
Lighten up, will you?
This mission's gonna be a cinch,
even with only three of us.
You made the stink about
it being boring, remember?
-Hm.
This missions boring
and I don't wanna go!
Go catch some petty thief?
Come on!
Anybody could do it!
Why's it gotta be us?
-Look, Naruto.
I would just send Kiba,
Hinata, and Shino out
as a squad like
usual, But the thing
is, Shino's already
gone out on a mission.
And I figured sending you along
would be better than nothing.
-What'd you say, grandma?
I am so way better than nothing!
-We'll all do our best.
-This mission is kind
of a snooze, you know.
-Well, no point
picking a team leader.
Not for this one.
Your mission is to capture
this man, Gosunkugi, also known
as The Nail.
He stole the Misogi
tea jar, owned
by the Land of
Tea's feudal lord.
He's keeping his head
low, hiding somewhere
in the Land of Stone we believe.
Enough talk.
Get moving.
I want him caught ASAP.
-I thought this mission
couldn't possibly
get any lamer than it
was, but it just did!
-Akamaru.
Dig in.
You know, the occasional
easy assignment never hurts.
Nothing wrong with
taking it easy.
-Exactly!
If it's so easy, let's
just get it done!
What if Pervy Sage comes
back to the village
and I'm stuck out here?
-I'm sorry, Naruto.
Forgive me.
I just-- Well I was so
happy to be sent out
on something with you.
-Huh?
What are you mumbling
about, Hinata?
Can't hear you!
And how come your
cheeks are so red?
You're a weird one.
-Well, good news,
Mr. I'm-In-A-Hurry.
Look.
The Land of Stone's on the
other side of that pass.
Might as well eat it.
No point being bored and hungry.
-I sure didn't expect to
be eating my own face when
I woke up this morning.
Oh, wow.
Seriously, Hinata
you're gonna make
somebody one heck of a wife!
-What?
Once heck of a wife!
-There's post station one.
Let's check it out.
KIBA: Looks a little
rough, don't you think?
-Hm.
The Bounty Hunter
from the Wilderness!
Why are they staring at us?
Don't all these slackers
have somewhere to be?
-I'm not getting the easy
vibe on this one anymore.
[growling]
-What is it, Akamaru?
What do you think?
That Gosunkugi guy-- you
figure he's here somewhere?
[growling]
-Speak of the devil!
-Huh?
-It's a photo.
-Well, at least it's
of the right guy, so.
-Reward.
Three million.
So, what's that about?
-Hey, look.
They've been put up
all over the place.
-All right.
I'm gonna ask the
locals what's up!
How's it going?
-Can I help you?
-Oh, we're not customers.
We just has a question.
-Is that so?
If you kids ain't buying
nothing, then beat it.
-Well, if that's the
way it's gotta be.
One ramen!
-Hook me up with a
cheeseburger, and some milk
for the little guy.
[barking]
[laughing]
-A cheeseburger and milk?
You gotta be kidding me!
-Hey, and the ramen.
You can't forget that.
-I don't care much for smart
alecky brats, so get out!
-We've got the
money to pay for it.
-It ain't about the money.
-Well, shouldn't carry
such a big bag of coins.
Isn't safe.
I'll do you a favor
and hold onto it.
I mean, you wouldn't want
one of these ruffians getting
his paws on your dough.
-Hey, you in or out?
The cards are getting cold.
-I'm coming.
Just keep your pants on.
You want some of
this money or not?
Huh?
You stupid or something?
Let it go.
-You're the one who's
gonna let it go!
You like that?
-You mouthy little brat.
You wanna fight me?
-Something like that, genius.
Bring it on!
-You punk.
-Are we really gonna do this?
-Yeah, Naruto.
Look.
-Hm?
Man.
This is bad.
-Glass of milk, if you please.
-Who the heck's this guy?
-Right.
Coming up.
Enjoy.
-Much obliged.
Now, now.
No need to be shy.
Drink up.
Courtesy of that gentleman
over there, Old Mr. Cueball.
-So I'm Old Mr. Cueball, huh?
Real funny, jerk.
And why would I buy milk
for some random mutt?
You gotta death
with or something?
-One Michizo [inaudible].
Reward if captured.
The credit goes to you, barkeep.
You can take the milk
money out of his bounty.
And buy yourself a new
table while you're at it.
Feel free to keep the change.
-That guy's strong.
-I'm sorry.
Was he yours?
My apologies.
-Hey!
Wait up!
-Something you want, young man?
-That was awesome.
What's your name old guy?
SAZANAMI (VOICEOVER):
Old guy, is it?
Hmph.
-The name is Sazanami.
I'm a bounty hunter.
-That is so cool.
-Old guy!
You know what?
That one thing you did
earlier was totally amazing.
-Hm?
That business with
the sword, you mean?
-You drew your sword on
Old Mr. Cueball so fast,
I couldn't even see it.
-It was really surprising.
-When someone says in
the blink of an eye,
I bet you that's the kind of
thing they're talking about.
-When you're a
bounty hunter, you
stare death in the
face every day.
I could have more
lives than a cat,
but it wouldn't help any
if I can't draw faster
than the guy in front of me.
-Well shucks howdy!
So what do you bounty
hunter guys do?
-Well, it's simple.
Sometimes people
put out a reward
on the bad guys who are too
tough to catch for free.
Bounty hunters round
up those bad guys
and earn the reward, or bounty.
It's the same thing.
-I get it.
Then this guy has a
bounty on him too, right?
A really big one!
-That's a picture of--
-But how come they put so
much money on this guy's head
if he's nothing but
your everyday crook?
-An every day crook,
you called him?
Boy, that man's a
hardened killer.
He's murdered dozens
of people for the sake
of robbing their courses.
They don't get any
worse than this fella.
-No way.
-Are you kidding me?
Can that really be true?
They didn't tell us
anything about it.
-Well, perhaps the feudal lord
who's paying for this mission
didn't even know it himself.
-A mission, huh?
-Uh huh.
The three of us are
Hidden Leaf ninja
out on a super
important mission.
We came to this town
to capture Gosunkugi.
SAZANAMI (VOICEOVER):
Hidden Leaf?
-Is that so?
You mean you kids are ninja?
Well, I'll be.
Can't say I've ever
met a ninja who
wasn't old enough
to shave before.
-Hey!
Don't make fun of us!
Got it old guy?
-Begging your pardon there, kid.
Didn't mean to rile you up.
What's say you let
me make it up to you?
Some milk, maybe?
-Get serious!
Do I look like a puppy to you?
Ramen!
-Yeah.
I'll forgive you
for a cheeseburger.
-I guess, if it's OK,
then I'll have ramen also.
-Fair enough, then.
Right this way.
Ramen and a cheeseburger
from that place?
When pigs fly.
-Hey old guy!
What about miso ramen with pork?
-Fine by me.
Have whatever you like.
-So, where the
heck are we going?
Man, we're not even
in the town anymore.
Hey!
I don't see any ramen shop.
-This should do.
I don't see a ramen shop either.
Guess I'll just have to
forget about my treating you.
Would've been a tasty last meal.
I'm sorry you're gonna miss it.
-What are you saying?
-This is the end of the line.
You kids are going
to die out here.
-Now wait a sec!
What's the big idea?
-Well, you three kids
know Gosunkugi is here,
and that is a right fatal fact.
-Yeah?
So what?
Why does it matter?
-Gosunkugi is my prey.
Mine alone.
I'm not handing him over
to you or anyone else.
-Well, good for you.
So why don't you go catch him
already and leave us alone?
-Sorry.
Wet behind the ears
though you may still be,
it doesn't change the fact
any that you're Leaf ninja.
It's better to have
fewer competitors.
Best to have none whatsoever.
-Don't do this.
-Now.
-Hinata!
-You rat!
-Naruto, help!
-Ninja Art, Beast Mimicry!
All Fours Jutsu!
-Ain't that a sight?
Your move.
-I'm way faster than this guy.
Darn it.
Where'd you go?
-You're too slow.
Just you and me, son.
We gonna do this the
easy way or the hard way?
-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
-Bravo.
-You're gonna pay for
this, you hear me?
-This ends now!
-Up here!
Now, gotcha!
-Well, almost had me there.
Forgive me, kid.
I did what I had to do.
I'll defeat him
whatever the cost.
[barking]
-Akamaru.
-Aw, man.
For an old guy, he
kicked our butts.
Hinata, are you
feeling all right?
-Uh, yeah.
-Where is Sazanami?
-Huh?
Could he have gone
after Gosunkugi?
-What are we just
sitting here for?
I'm not letting him
beat us to the draw.
-Ugh.
Come on.
Where did that old guy go?
[barking]
-What do you think?
Figure he skipped town by now?
-Going after Gosunkugi.
[barking]
-We're counting on you, Akamaru.
-I'm hunting bigger game,
but I don't see him.
GOSUKUGI: Quiet, you
opportunistic hyena.
-I waited a long time for
you to make your move.
-Unfortunately, I
have an important task
that needs attending to.
Time is money, so let's kill
you as cheaply as possible.
Ninja Art.
Torpedo Nail.
-Gosunkugi-- it's over.
-Should've watched your step.
[shout]
-It's over.
Now finish him off!
-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Gosunkugi, we're placing
you under arrest!
-Curses.
Reinforcements.
Retreat!
-Not so fast!
SAZANAMI: Wait.
-Huh?
-Don't go.
It'll be the death of you.
-Old guy!
You alive?
Hey.
Sazanami!
-Don't you go after him.
He's too strong for you three.
-How could such a tough
old coot get beaten?
-Think about it.
Gosunkugi isn't
just another thief.
He's a shinobi, same as us.
-A shinobi, huh?
-Sazanami!
Huh?
-So are you one of
Gosunkugi's goons?
I remember you.
You were at that tavern.
Yeah, sitting at the table!
-Man, what was that
guy's problem, anyway?
Huh?
What's this?
A wanted flier?
-What a dummy.
I mean, none of us even
look like Gosunkugi.
-Naw, man.
It's somebody else.
This fugitive who
calls himself Tokichi
is a murderer known to have
killed a family of three.
He has a bird-shaped
birthmark on his chest.
-A bird-shaped birthmark?
It couldn't be--
-Hinata?
What is it?
-His face is covered with
scars, so I can't tell.
but he has a birthmark--
shaped like a bird.
-So there's a bounty
on the bounty hunter?
-Man, could this
mission get any weirder?
What's going on?
[theme music]
NARUTO: A long time
ago, but not really,
on an overcast,
clear day, a day that
was night right from
the start, the righteous
rogue Sazanami's past
unwinds and frays!
Ah, Gosunkugi, the fatal foe.
Though the truth is uncovered,
sometimes a shinobi's
gotta do what a
shinobi's gotta do.
Hey, Gosunkugi!
Give yourself up, or else!
Next time, Hunt or be Hunted,
Showdown at the OK Temple.
[theme music]