[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Old man Genno.
[loud slurping]
-You're right.
This ramen is quite
delicious!
-Isn't it?
[slurping soup]
-(VOICEOVER) Why would
he be doing this?
-There.
That's one paper bomb
that won't be going off.
-Well done, Tenten.
-We can breathe easier now.
-I'm afraid not.
-(TOGETHER) What?
-Our problems are
just beginning.
SHIKAMARU: Yeah.
If Genno ever finds out
that we discovered this one
and deactivated it,
he might find a way
to set off all those other paper
bombs before we can do anything
about them.
-Yeah.
You're right.
[loud bang]
Ah!
Choji, you jerk!
You almost gave
me a heart attack.
-Sorry.
Hm-hm.
-(VOICEOVER) So far there's no
sign that anyone's picked up
on what we're doing.
SHIKAMARU: OK.
So now we put everything
back the way it was.
-Right.
Got it.
-And you guys, go back to
your kunai knife target
practice like nothing happened.
Just don't hit the bullseye.
-Right.
Understood.
-Man, it's lucky we're no good.
What if one of us
had hit it before?
-Hey!
You were there yesterday.
I did hit the target!
-No, you only came
close, remember?
-What do you mean?
I hit it.
I totally hit it.
TSUNADE: A bomb on
almost every corner.
-Lady Tsunade, we
must evacuate everyone
as quickly as possible.
-Whoa!
You're joking, right?
-What do you mean, joking?
-When we start the evacuation,
he'd know that we're onto him.
Genno might just go ahead
and blow up the whole village
right then and there.
-I see.
Naruto and the others are
searching for the paper bombs
now.
Let's wait and see how they do.
-Huh.
[whimpering]
-Akamaru?
[quiet whimpering]
KIBA: You onto something boy?
[barking]
-He found one!
-Way to go!
Attaboy, Akamaru.
[bark]
[buzzing]
-How's it going?
-Almost there.
-Good work!
-The rest is up to you.
-I've got it.
-Eh.
Uh.
Unh!
-Uh, have you got it yet?
-Not yet.
Eh unh!
A little more.
Almost there.
-Uh, Naruto, please be careful!
-Unh!
Come here, you
stupid little-- Unh!
-What in the world are you
children doing back here?
-Huh?
Oh, uh, I, uh, lost some
money between the walls here,
that's all.
-I'll come back and fish
it out with a broom later.
Don't worry.
-Yikes!
No way, lady.
It might go off!
I mean, thanks, but I'm really
starving for ramen right now.
-He really is.
-Ichiraku ramen?
Well, no wonder.
Good luck!
-Yeah.
Thank you.
-Thank you.
-Eh.
Oh, brother.
That was a close one!
-Good job, Naruto.
SHIKAMARU: We need
more manpower.
It'll take forever
finding them all this way.
-Yes.
But there are no other
Shinobi left in the village.
-Wait.
There might be one or two.
They have nothing else to do
but sit around and complain
all day, so why not
put them to work,
even if they're not
in the best of shape?
-Huh?
-Wait!
You're not talking about--
-Who sits around and
complains all day?
It's our duty as village
elders to give advice
to those who are
less experienced.
Not that you're wise
enough to listen.
-So you can still
sense troubles brewing
despite your age
and infirmities.
-Watch it!
You're not as young as you
look yourself, you know.
-What?
How dare you. (IRATE) Listen
here, you old bag of bones--
-I suggest you watch your
temper, and your mouth,
eh, Hokage?
-[growls]
-We have a general
idea of the situation.
Where do you want us to search?
-I have the perfect
place for you to start.
-Huh. (DERISIVELY) I can't wait.
-The Hokage has met her match.
That old lady is good!
-No kidding.
-Yeah.
Good and scary.
-Ah!
Quickly!
Let the power of youth
drive you forward!
The Leaf Village is threatened!
-I appreciate their help.
But those two really
get on my nerves.
-Well, we'll be able to
find those bombs in no time,
once Guy-sensei and the others
get back from that wild goose
chase we sent them on.
-Yeah.
I only wish it was
as simple as that.
-Shikamaru.
What are you thinking?
-Something about
this bothers me.
How could one guy
have planted them all?
And when?
There are so many
paper bombs out there.
It doesn't seem possible.
-Yes.
You're right.
-[sighs]
-There's got to be more to
this than meets the eye.
(VOICEOVER) I keep
getting this feeling
we're overlooking something.
Something Important.
-Mm aww!
So close!
-Hey!
What's wrong with you?
You're not supposed to
be trying to hit it.
-Oh, yeah.
I forgot.
-OK, my turn now.
I'll be sure to miss.
-I know you will.
You couldn't hit
it if you tried.
-How does it look?
-The paper bomb disposal's
progressing smoothly.
And I've detected no
sign of Genno anywhere.
LEE: I wonder what
he could be up to?
-Sending us all the way to
the outskirts of the village.
She's as much a slave driver
is the Third Hokage was.
-You'd almost think
she was trying
to get us out of the way.
Wait 'til we get back.
I'm going to give that
woman a piece of my mind.
-As if this Genno fellow
would waste his time hiding
bombs here.
Honestly, there's never
been anything out here
worth blowing up.
-Aren't you
forgetting something?
-What's that?
-They were planning to build
that expensive new shopping
district here at one time.
-That was more
than 30 years ago.
What does that have
to do with anything?
-Hm?
Well, well!
That looks like--
-Yes.
-Take a look at this.
-What about it?
The jutsu has been written
in a slightly differently way
on this one.
-You're right !
The writing's not even the same.
-It doesn't look that
much different to me.
-What do you mean?
Are you blind?
-So it's a weird one.
And?
-It's not weird to us.
In fact, it's very familiar.
-That's how the jutsu was
written back in our day.
-You're saying that this is a
paper bomb from way back then?
-Surprisingly enough, most of
the paper bombs we're finding
are the old kind, like that one.
-And look.
This maps shows how
all the hidden bombs
are distributed
throughout the village.
-Hardly any of them
have been planted
in the most densely-populated
residential areas.
At the same time, these
empty outlying areas
where no one are absolutely
crawling with them.
-Why?
What's out there?
-Nothing now.
But at one time, there was
going to be a bustling shopping
district there.
-But what could it all mean?
-Putting all the facts
together, the antique paper
bombs, their
location, and the fact
that they were all hidden
without us being aware,
it can only mean this
trap was set 30 years ago!
-A 30-year-old trap.
-It's ridiculous when
you think about it.
That in all that time,
not a single person
in the whole village ever
noticed they were there.
-Ridiculous?
No.
It's easy to miss something
you're not looking for.
And who would have
expected the village
to be riddled with explosives?
-And as hidden as
well as they were,
they'd never be found unless
someone was using byakugan.
-So you think Genno found out
about these bombs someone set
30 years ago and decided to
make them part of his trap?
-But if we never found
them, how did he?
-30 years ago!
(EXCITED) Hang on!
-Shikamaru?
Where are you going?
-Wait for me!
NARUTO: OK.
There's area's all clear.
Let's keep going.
Come on!
-Oh, unh!
Uh.
-Huh?
Hinata!
What's wrong?
-It hard using my
byakugan for so long.
I'm just a little
tired, that's all.
-Really?
You OK?
Let me see.
-[gasps]
-Well, you feel feverish.
And you're all red.
-Mm.
I'm OK.
I'll be fine if I just
rest for a minute.
-Are you sure?
OK, then, just take it easy.
You wait here, and
I'll deliver the ones
we found so far to
Grandma Tsunade.
(YELLING) Don't you go anywhere!
I'll be right back!
-Mm.
-It was right on this
very spot that the old man
was standing when
I first met him.
And I thought he was just
some nice old guy who
liked ramen as much as I do.
Huh.
I wonder, was he looking
up there for a reason?
Eh.
Unh!
Huh?
Eh.
Why would this be up here?
GENNO: Well, well.
-Huh?
-So you found me out, huh?
Old man?
-Can't let you go
back to your friends,
now that you've discovered me.
-30 years ago?
That would have been when my
father was master carpenter.
I remember, he had to
hire a lot of outsiders,
just as we're doing now.
I'm not sure how complete our
records are for that period.
-Anything might be of help.
Plans ledgers, anything.
-What is this about, Shikamaru?
Fill us in!
-The recommendation.
What happened to it?
-Which recommendation?
The first letter
of recommendation
that disappeared?
The one that led us
to suspect Genno?
-There's one thing that's been
bugging me this whole. time.
You see, I think
it was Genno who
made that recommendation
disappear.
But then, why would he
feel he had to do that?
And the only explanation
that I can come up with
is that the first
recommendation was phony, too.
-What are you getting at?
-But that letter's
just been sitting here
all these years, so how
would he even know about it?
-Because I think Genno
himself is the one
who used that
letter 30 years ago,
when he first came to work here.
At least, I think so.
The first one was
a good forgery,
indistinguishable
from the real thing.
The second referral
was much clumsier,
almost like he wanted
it to look like a fake,
compared to the first one.
-But why?
-He wasn't concerned
about whether we found out
he was an impostor this time.
But he didn't want
us to start getting
suspicious about that referral
letter from 30 years ago.
That's why he got rid of it.
To conceal the fact that
he was here then, too.
-Mm.
-It was him.
It was Genno who went around
planting all those paper
bombs here 30 years ago.
NARUTO: Why?
Why are you doing this, old man?
-I suppose you've never heard
of the Heat Devil Village
in the Land of Mountains.
I was born in that village.
-Huh?
(VOICEOVER) Heat Devil Village?
-You don't know it?
-No.
-That's why this
bingo book you brought
us states only that
Genno's place of birth
was the Land of
Mountains, nothing more.
-Specifically,
Heat Devil Village
in the Land of Mountains.
-The village
disappeared, and its name
is not found in most records.
-30 years ago, Heat Devil
Village and the Village Hidden
in the Leaves were at war with
each other, an endless war.
Neither side would
give an inch, and we
were locked in a
bloody stalemate.
One night, knowing their
main force was away,
we launched a sneak attack
against their village.
With one strike, we turned the
tide of the war in our favor.
SHIKAMARU: The history
books will tell you
that three months later,
an armistice was signed
and the war was over.
But those three months
are the mystery.
Everyone expected
Heat Devil Village
to counter-attack or strike back
in some way for what we'd done.
-Here it is, my father's
diary from that period.
-Really?
-Yes.
He kept it faithfully.
He never missed a day.
Here.
-Aw, thanks!
"I had a man from the Sand
Village show up at the site
today with a referral
from a master carpenter.
His skills aren't
all that great,
but I've hired him, as
I need the manpower."
Look at the date!
A week after the attack
on Heat Devil Village!
-So you think that man--
-Was Genno.
I'd bet my life on it.
GENNO: That was the
mission I'd been given.
To infiltrate the
Leaf Village, and hide
paper bombs in every corner it.
The plan was for our forces to
launch an attack at the same
as the bombs went off.
It was to be a devastating blow.
I took my time and chose
my targets carefully.
I concentrated on the
busiest parts of the village,
hoping to do the most damage.
We didn't have as
many Anbu Black Ops
lurking about back
then, so I was
able to move around the
village quite freely.
It took me two
and a half months,
but at last, I had set
all the paper bombs.
There was nothing to do but
wait for my comrades to arrive.
But alas, my
comrades never came.
-Why?
What happened to them?
-It was at that point that the
warlord of Heat Devil Village
died in a tragic
hunting accident.
The man who took
his place was one
of those who preferred
peace, and he
accepted the terms
of the armistice.
-Right about then, Genno
stopped coming to work.
I wonder why.
-He had finished setting
the bombs and disappeared.
-So I prepared to
return to my village.
I thought the armistice
would only be temporary,
and that I'd soon be sent
back to fulfill my mission.
Little did I suspect
that there would
be no more missions for me
or anyone from the Heat Devil
Village.
-Two weeks after the armistice,
the Village Hidden in the Vale
attacked them, and Heat
Devil Village was destroyed.
-Destroyed?
-The timing was perfect.
They were still very weak
from a long war with us.
-And thanks to the armistice,
all their defenses were down.
-"No sign of Genno.
It's been two months now.
I wonder what's
happened to him."
-But it doesn't make any sense.
Why now?
Why come back to the Leaf
Village after all this time?
Is it just to fulfill
your stupid old mission?
For what?
According to you, your village
doesn't even exist anymore.
So what's the point in
destroying ours, too?
Or is it that someone's
given you a new mission
to destroy the Leaf?
-Oh, no.
Rest easy.
I'm not here because
anyone sent me here.
-Duh.
Then why have you come?
-Well, you see, it just
seemed like such a waste.
NARUTO: A waste?
Wh-what are you talking about?
-I've grown old.
Each day I'm alive
could be my last.
I thought, what a shame
it would be for me
to pass into darkness
without anyone ever knowing
about what I've done.
So why waste them?
Why not use them before I die?
-You serious?
You'd destroy this whole
village just so everyone
will know what you
get 30 years ago?
And I thought you were
just a friendly old man.
So the only reason you
bought that ramen was--
-To get information
about how things
stood on the Leaf Village.
-Darn it!
(IRATE) You lying jerk!
-You'll understand when you've
lived as long as I have.
-Never!
I'll never understand, no
matter how long I live.
And I'm going to
live really long!
-You'll see soon enough.
The minute I spring my
trap, you'll understand.
-You're not going
to spring anything!
My friends are finding and
deactivating all your paper
bombs right now.
So forget it!
No way it's ever
going to happen.
No way!
-Eh he-he-he-he-he!
That's very
enterprising of them.
But what makes you think
that my plan was simply
to blow them up?
-Whoa, wait a minute.
I thought before you
died, you were going to--
-You have a one-track
mind, my boy.
I said I wanted to put
them to use, that's all.
-What?
-They don't have to be blown up.
I can make excellent use
of them in other ways.
Ha!
-Eh!
-A real Shinobi
anticipates his enemy.
He's always thinking two
or three moves ahead.
Remember that!
-Uh! [gasps] Eh!
LEE: Shikamaru!
-Hm?
What is it, Lee?
-The Academy students.
They are getting tired.
What now?
-What Academy students?
-Those kids throwing kunai.
-Oh, them.
Are those guys still at it?
-(ANGRY) They're at it because
you told them to stay at it,
you idiot!
-Oh, yeah.
I guess I did.
Well, OK.
Tell me they've done
enough and they can quit.
After all, we don't
want one of them
hitting the target by accident.
Ah!
-What is it?
-Now I get it.
So that's it!
It never made sense that such
a careful thorough the guy
would leave the detonation
of his device to pure chance.
-What do you mean?
-A Shinobi as smart
as Genno would
want to make sure
the paper bombs were
timed to go off
for maximum effect.
That is, if it really matters
to him whether they go off
at all, which I'm starting
to think it doesn't, it's
just a diversion.
He's really after
something else.
[ending theme song]
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): Things
are about to get real ugly.
Choji.
CHOJI (VOICEOVER): What?
What is it?
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): Quick!
We've got to see
the Fifth Hokage
and tell her not to let our
forces return to the village.
CHOJI (VOICEOVER):
Well, why not?
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
Whatever kind of trap
Genno really has
in mind, I've got
a feeling he's
going to spring it
the moment they
enter the village.
CHOJI (VOICEOVER):
(DISBELIEVING) No!
You think?
HINATA (VOICEOVER): Shikamaru,
Choji, come quickly!
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): Hinata!
What is it?
HINATA (VOICEOVER): It's Naruto.
He's in trouble!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next
time, "Multiple Traps,
Countdown to Destruction"!