[theme music]
-This is crazy.
-No matter how many there are,
The result will be the same.
-I'll give you credit.
You're a lot smarter
than I thought.
And a lot more persistent.
-On top of that, I'm a nice guy.
Well, most of the time.
You'll have to excuse
my bad manners.
I'm not normally in the
habit of slugging a lady.
But then, looking at
you, you don't really
fall into that category, do you?
So I guess it's OK.
-You may have
escaped my genjutsu,
but don't let it
go to your head.
You're still a worm.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
She's not completely
immobilized by my
shadow posession.
I've gotta make this count.
Just a little more.
Even at this range, with
her bound up as tight
as I can make it, she's still
got enough chakra to push back.
Gotta keep the pressure on.
Let up for a second,
and I'll get hammered.
That's it.
If this jutsu doesn't
finish it once and for all--
KIBA (VOICEOVER): OK,
Akamaru Hang in there, boy.
What is this?
Whatever it is, it
doesn't look good.
-And then there was one.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): This guy.
He's incredible.
All those shadow clones and
not one of them got through!
-It's calm at last.
The moment I've
been waiting for.
The first step toward achieving
Lord Orochimaru's design.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Sasuke.
Hey Sasuke!
What are you hanging out
with these losers for?
Come on, buddy.
Let's go home!
[laughter]
-Sasuke?
Come on.
-Let's go back.
-All right.
We both made it.
We climbed all the
way to the top.
-You're one of the ones
I wanna fight the most.
-Let's-- Let's go home.
Come on.
Everyone's there
waiting for you.
Sasuke.
You-- You hear me?
Talk to me!
-Just bring him home.
Please bring Sasuke back to me.
What is wrong with you?
Have you gone deaf or something?
Hey, wait!
Sasuke!
-It's no use.
Now die.
Who's this?
-It is I, the rejuvenated
Leaf Village's handsome devil.
Rock Lee!
-B-- Bushy brow?
But, what about your injuries?
-Do not worry about me, Naruto.
Go get Sasuke.
-Huh?
Really?
Are you sure?
-Go on.
Get going.
I can take care of things here.
This one's strong.
Good.
-OK, but just be
careful, will you?
He uses his own
bones for weapons.
-His bones?
Interesting.
-Watch yourself.
This guy's strength
is beyond belief.
-Well, what are you waiting for?
Go!
The thumbs up, Naruto.
Remember?
You gave it to Sakura.
You made her a promise.
-I'm gonna bring Sasuke
back home no matter what.
And that's a promise
of a lifetime.
-Do not worry.
I can finish this one.
I promise.
-I don't think so.
-You die!
-I dislike being ignored.
-Ah.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Good luck, bushy brow.
-You can not afford
to be distracted.
(VOICEOVER) Yes!
My body is responding well.
-Still, no matter how you look
at it, with Sasuke bottled up
in that coffin, there's not
a team of Genin on earth
that can take on
that bunch and win.
-Obviously the
two of us can't be
of much help in our condition.
But if you put together
a special squad,
send out a team of
Jonin to back them up--
-That's out of the question.
Ever since Orochimaru's
attack, we've
had to defend
ourselves with merely
a fraction of our
former strength.
Other lands have begn
to sense our weakness.
Every day we're faced
with growing dangers,
both from within
and from without.
Even at the risk of
letting the Sharingan
fall into Orochimaru's hands.
What I need is every Jonin
here to defend the village.
-But, my lady, the
problem of Orochimaru--
well, it won't just go away.
-If he regains his powers,
sooner or later he'll be back.
-Of course he will.
I'm well aware of that.
I'm not a fool.
And that's why I've already
taken certain measures.
Huh?
-She's in here.
TSUNADE: Guy!
What is it?
Did something happen
on your mission?
-No.
It went without a hitch.
And then I ran back as swiftly
as my feet could carry me.
Who cares about my mission?
Tell me, how did
Lee's surgery go?
I gotta know!
-It was successful.
In fact, I've OKed him to
start training tomorrow.
Going easy at first.
-Well, he probably should
stay in bed, but you know him.
-I'm afraid we have
a problem, my lady.
It's Rock Lee.
He's disappeared from his room.
[sobbing]
GUY: No!
[shout]
[battle cry]
-The next one will be your last.
-He must have slipped
out last night
while I was Genma and Raido.
GUY (VOICEOVER): Why, Lee?
-Little fool.
He must have gone after them.
What's more, he must
have been half delirious.
Instead of his prescription,
he took a bottle of elixir
that I had left in here.
-Bottle of elixir?
Oh, no.
-Guy, What's the matter?
-Something happens when
Lee drinks an elixir.
Even a sip, and well-- things
can get really out of hand.
-Out of hand how?
-Leaf Hurricane!
ROCK LEE (VOICEOVER):
He is too fast.
I cannot land a single kick.
Your agility is impressive.
And you have a most
singular style.
-Your style's too direct.
Almost obvious.
It's over.
-One moment, please!
I am so sorry, but I
have to take my medicine
at a certain time.
And that time happens to be now.
Excuse me.
It will take just a minute.
To be honest, I never
really liked medicine.
GUY: I first noticed
this phenomenon
on the night I took
Lee to a restaurant
to celebrate his perfecting
the Reverse Lotus.
Thinking it was water,
he drank some of my sake.
A teeny weeny little
cup, barely a sip.
That's when things
turned really ugly.
-What do you mean, exactly?
-First, there was
this ominous silence.
A moment later, the entire
restaurant was a disaster area.
As if, as if a
tsunami had hit it.
-Whatever it is, it is the worst
tasting medicine I have ever--
[giggling]
-Strange.
What sort of medicine is it?
-A disaster area?
Why?
What happened?
-It was a horrible sight.
The horror!
Lee was like
something possessed.
A beast.
It was pure destruction, the
likes of which I've never seen.
-Huh?
-What are you staring
at, you stupid jerk?
Why, I oughta-- don't--
don't move, bonsey.
I, uh-- I
GUY: I knew then what Lee was.
A natural born master.
Yes.
A master of the drunken fist.
-Sasuke!
[theme music]
LEE: Oh, Guy-sensei
I wish you were here
to see how I have
mastered the Shinobi
secret of reading
the double bluff!
It was perfect!
He fell for it like
a bun of tricks!
Or a ton of blicks.
Bricks!
What-- What is this
strange feeling?
Like I am floating?
Like I could conquer the world?
That is it!
Nothing can stop me!
NARUTO: Next time,
The Beast Within!
[theme music]