[theme music]
-Well?
Come on, Pervy Sage!
I'm on pins and needles.
What's this new jutsu
you're gonna teach me?
The last time around it was
the walk on water jutsu!
Ooh, is it walking through fire?
Or wait.
Maybe walking on air.
Aw, come on, Pervy Sage!
Let's hear it already!
-All right.
Enough with the
Pervy Sage already.
You have no idea how
amazing a guy I am, do you?
-What?
Amazingly pervy?
-Gah!
You-- All right, listen up.
The Toad Sage is only my cover.
Allow me to reveal
my true identity.
From the north to the south
and the east to the west,
Not even the spirits
can defeat this Sannin.
The White-Maned Toad Charmer!
A red hot ninja who strikes
fear in the hearts of men!
Master Jiaraiya!
Yes.
I'm speaking of none
other than myself.
-Uh huh.
[cawing]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Jiaraiya!
Naruto's Potential Disaster!
-Uh, Atafuku town.
That's 10 kilometers from here.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
No, it's Otafuku town.
-Ah.
-Oh, hey, hey hey!
Wait a seocnd!
Pervy Sage!
-Look, kid.
I told you already,
it's Jiaraiya.
Come on.
-So, the fact that suh a big
wig Pervy Sage chose me as his
travelling companion must
mean something, right?
I must be a potential
genius in the making.
Aw, man.
It's just like I always thought!
Come on, come on, come on.
Why'd ya choose me, huh?
-Well, the truth is,
kid, a long time ago,
the Fourth Hokage used
to be a disciple of mine.
-Huh?
-And you bear such a striking
resemblance to the Fourth
that it's almost laughable.
Sorry, that's the only
reason I got for ya.
-So, wait.
I'm like the Fourth?
Holy crap!
That's awesome!
-What's up with you?
-Oh, man!
If I'm like the
Fourth Hokage, that
means I possess the same
level of genius he did!
I'm on my way to
Hokage after all.
Woo-hoo!
[shouting] Yippee!
Huh?
-Hm?
-Gah!
No, no, no!
Wait!
Ah, no, I just stepped
in some dog doo!
-The only similarities you
share with the Fourth Hokage
is pigheadedness and that
spiky blond hair of yours!
-What was that, you
senile old perv?
Not again!
[sigh]
[construction sounds]
WOMAN: Sakura, come here.
-OK.
WOMAN: Would you take these
dumplings over to Ino's house?
-To Ino's house?
These?
WOMAN: That's right.
Don't be a bother and
stay too long, all right?
Everyone is so busy these days.
-Yeah, Mom, I know.
See ya in a bit.
Oh, hey.
I should bring some of these
over to Sasuke later, too.
I wonder if he
has a sweet tooth.
Oh, and Naruto, too.
He'd probably eat
just about anything.
-Hey, Kakashi-sensei.
Can you teach me Chidori, too?
-Look, I know you want
to learn, but it's not
as simple as all that.
-What the heck is that?
How is that fair?
Come on, show me!
-Sasuke, thank you.
I mean, you know, you protected
me from the sand, right?
-No.
-Huh?
-All right.
To start, try gathering up
some chakra in your palm.
-Ha!
Got it!
-It wasn't me who rescued you.
It was Naruto.
-Am I getting it?
Am I getting it?
-Oh, come on, Sasuke.
You're just being
overly modest again.
Sure, Naruto's gotten stronger,
but against a sand ninja?
-I'm telling you the truth.
You should have seen him.
Naruto fought tooth and
nail to save you, Sakura.
He displayed a kind of strength
he'd never shown before.
-Naruto--
[groan]
-Rescued me?
-Come on-- Chidori!
Chidori!
What the-- Chidori!
-Right.
I'll save some for Naruto, too.
-I wasn't-- I wasn't
able to do anything.
I don't ever want to
have to see that again.
Watching all my best friends
falling right in front of me.
-No matter what happens, I
swear I'm going to protect you.
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Summoning Jutsu!
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): Naruto j
gets stronger and stronger.
Compared to him, I--
-I'm pretty certain you
could go toe to toe with him.
Though I'm not sure I could.
He's on a whole other level.
-Yeah.
If we faced each other,
both of us would be killed.
A rather unappealing outcome.
Even if there were
more of us, the result
would remain the same.
-Never thought I'd have
to go up against one
of the legendary Sannin.
If we fight him, then
both the Uchiha clan
and the Seven
Swordsmen of the Mist
will have their names
dragged through the mud.
-True.
But still, even the
strongest of opponents
always has a weakness.
NARUTO: Boing, boing.
[mumbling] Boing.
Ha ha ha!
[mumbling]
-Keep it up.
You'll be cursed.
[giggling] NARUTO:
Hey, pervy sage.
-Hm?
-What kind of a student
was the Fourth Hokage?
-Well, I think
it's safe to say he
rose to greatness
because of my tutelage.
So to land me as a
sensei-- well, kid,
let's just say you
hit the jackpot, OK?
-Huh?
-Oh, what?
You don't believe me?
A good sensei will naturally
beget good disciples.
That goes without saying.
-So wait a second, pervy sage.
If that's true, then who
did you have as a sensei?
-Who, me?
I first studied under
the Third Hokage.
-The Third, huh?
-Yep.
This was back when the Third
Hokage was still a young spring
chicken.
-The Hokage-- a spring chicken?
-That's right.
I was a young buck
myself back then.
-Young buck?
I, uh, got a little tangled up.
-What'd I tell you?
Those curses are no joke.
So wait a second.
If you studied
with Kakashi, that
means you must have gone
through the bell training.
Am I right?
-Huh?
Yeah.
I did.
Forgot about that.
Only I was tied to a stump.
Man, I forgot how
bad all that sucked.
-What?
You too, huh?
-Huh?
Me, too?
-Uh--
-Me too, what?
-Forget about it.
Just hurry up and put those
things back where you got 'em.
-Easier said than done.
I'm kinda-- tied up.
-There are two bells.
And since there are only two--
-One of us will get
tied to the stump.
-You're pretty quick on
the uptake, Orochimaru.
-All right!
I got this one in the bag.
-I want you to come at me
with the intent to kill.
-Well, Jiraiya, looks like
I win our little wager.
Enjoy your time on the stump.
-Aw, just shut up, you
flat chested cutting board.
-What did you say?
You annoying little perv!
-OK, that's enough,
enough, Tsunade.
You and Orochimaru head home.
-You're unbelievable,
you know that?
How can you be a ninja
if you keep falling
for the same obvious
traps over and over again?
-Yeah, but--
-You could learn a few
things from Orochimaru.
-It's always the same
thing with you, Seinsei.
Orochimaru this and
Orochimaru that.
-Hm?
-The transparency
jutsu I use is flawless
when I'm out researching.
-Oh, boy.
I'm not even sure I
want to know where
you are with transparency.
-I haven't been
caught peeping yet.
It's true, I swear!
-All right, then.
If you're so sure
of yourself, I'll,
uh, have to tag along next time.
-Wow, Sarutobi-sensei.
You're a perv.
[laughter]
-Huh?
Huh?
Hey, what is it?
Come on, spill it.
What's so funny, pervy sage?
-Huh?
Ah, you know, kid, just
what I was saying before.
A good teacher produces
good disciples.
-Huh?
What are you talking about?
-Just make sure
everything's back the way
it was, and let's go.
-Yeah, yeah.
I did it.
See?
-They're trouble.
But from the look of
things, it doesn't
appear they've found Naruto yet.
-That's what's crazy.
It doesn't add up.
I mean, they had already
infiltrated the village.
It should be easy for them
to find Naruto around here.
Besides, Itachi knows
Naruto's face already.
-Shh.
-Kakashi.
Why's Kakashi asleep?
And why is this
room full of Jonin?
What are you doing?
What the hell is going on here?
-Uh, not much, really.
-Hey!
Is it true that
Itachi has returned?
And that he's come
here to get Naruto?
-Idiot.
-Aw, why does this
always have to happen?
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): So he's
come back to the village, huh?
And he's after Naruto?
What does this mean?
[gasp]
-Hey, Sasuke.
-Where is Naruto?
-Well, I don't know.
I just got here myself.
I wanted to give
Naruto some-- sweets.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): If Naruto
gets caught, he's dead.
I won't let that happen!
Old man, Naruto
stopped in here today.
Do you know where he
went after he left?
-Oh, sure.
Naruto.
That's right, let me see, now.
He met Master Jiraiya
here around noon.
They had a little
bit of ramen, then
they said they were
heading off somewhere.
-Where to?
-Hm.
Now that I think
of it, I believe
he mentioned that outpost town
a ways out from the village.
Yeah.
And then he set out
with Master Jiraiya.
-Jiraiya?
-Yeah, Jiraiya.
He's one of the
legendary Sannin.
Now, if you want
to find him, you're
looking for a
great big ol' fella
with a head of white hair.
-A big guy.
White hair.
-Hey!
Aw, come on.
If you're going to stop
by to ask some questions,
the least you can do
is order some ramen.
-Get your candy here!
-Hm.
Oh, man.
This town is pretty weird.
JIRAIYA: Naruto!
-Huh?
-We're gonna crash here tonight.
-What?
But why?
I can still walk.
-A disciple should
always obey his master.
-Look, I just want to
learn some jutsu, OK?
-Yeah, no kidding.
That's what makes
you a disciple.
Hm?
-Hm?
[giggling]
-Naruto!
Oh yeah, oh yeah, oh
yeah, oh yeah, oh yeah!
Here's the room key.
I want you to go right up to
the room, train for a little,
work on your chakra,
then get to bed, OK?
-Oh, so I suppose
you're gonna tell me
it's time for the
grownups to play now.
Is that the vibe
here, you big perv?
-The outpost town
isn't that far off.
-Aw, man.
Every single time I'm
with that pervy sage,
I always end up getting shafted.
-This is it.
-Get your candy, here.
Get your candy!
-Guess I'll just have
to go door to door.
-Here's to you.
-Starting to think he has no
interest in training me at all.
[groaning]
-That one there, you like it?
-Mm-hm
-Hoo!
You see, 100 out of 100.
I never miss!
-Is there a dopey looking
blonde kid staying here?
About my age?
He's traveling with an old man.
A guy with white hair.
-I'm sorry, but this inn is
for women only, I'm afraid.
[grunting]
-Is there a goofy looking
blonde kid stay here?
Around my age?
With a big, white
haired old man?
-Actually, we only have
older guests here today.
-Mm.
This has got some
real zip to it, hm?
-Uh, guys, when did we decide
it was nap time in here?
-Is there a dopey
looking blonde kid
about my age staying here now?
He's traveling through the city
with a big guy with white hair.
-White hair, you say?
-Are they here?
-Hm.
Did I see someone like
that at the shift change?
I wonder.
-This is kind of a bitter drink.
Can you handle it?
OK, bottoms up!
-Oh, yeah!
A blonde kid and a
white haired old man.
-So they're here, then?
What room number?
-Let's see, now.
That would be room number
one on the second floor
at the end of the hall.
Huh?
[knocking]
-Ah, what now?
Are you telling me she
dumped you already?
[knocking]
-I heard you the first time!
OK, hold on.
Let me just unlock it.
-Naruto!
You're not--
[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Damn it.
My body is frozen.
I'm getting a bad feeling here.
There's something
about this guy.
He's not your average
shinobi, that's for sure.
He's got Sharingan,
Just like Sasuke.
That means he's from
the Uchiha clan.
Is this who Sasuke
was talking about?
Next time, Roar, Chidori!
Brother Versus Brother!