[theme music]
-Still no sign.
Where in the world
are you, Idate?
-Sir.
That matter you asked
us to investigate.
We finally uncovered some proof.
-Oh.
I see.
Good.
Well done.
-M'lord.
Is something wrong?
-It's fine.
Nothing to worry about.
It
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): I
have to focus my chakra.
That was really close.
Sasuke.
Are you OK?
Naruto.
Good luck.
You'll have to protect Idate.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
The Last Leg.
A Final Act of Desparation!
Hate to break it to you, but
your poison won't work on me.
-Heh.
-Go on, laugh.
You're gonna pay for what
you did to my friends.
-Take it easy.
I wouldn't want you
feeling left out.
You'll join them soon enough.
-I wouldn't be so sure
of that, if I were you!
IDATE (VOICEOVER): Naruto.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
What do I do?
Rasengan won't work
against that sword.
That doesn't matter now!
Sakura and Sasuke
need me to help them!
-Ha.
Still want to play
the hero, huh?
Forget about it. they were
dead once they hit bottom.
-Zip it!
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
-Well.
Not a bad trick there, kid.
But it's not gonna
help you run away.
-Whatever, pal.
Who said anything about running?
-Huh?
-It's useless, Naruto!
That Jutsu won't work on him!
-Better listen.
-Naruto!
-You're no better than
than that Uchiha failure.
Is there anyone in Hidden Leaf
who's not a complete idiot?
-Shut up already.
I'm saving them, you hear me?
-You don't honestly think
they're alive after that fall,
do you?
You should've run while
you had the chance.
-I won't.
I won't abandon my friends.
I'll never run away!
I haven't forgotten my
answer to the tenth question!
-What are you even
talking about?
-One more time.
Take this!
-You little fool.
-Rasengan!
-Naruto!
-You still don't get it.
You have no chance of winning.
-Damn it.
What is that?
Sasuke must've
made a crack in it.
That's it.
I just aim for that.
I can win!
-What?
Haven't had enough yet?
Come on, kid.
Give it up already.
-Aw, shut up!
Shadow Clone Justu!
This is it!
Sasuke gave me this chance,
and I'm not gonna waste it!
-Naruto.
-Just hold still!
Sasuke!
They changed into water clones!
-I know!
-You've gotta trust me, Idate.
I promise we'll protect you.
-Sa-- Sakura.
-Hurry, go on ahead.
I promise we'll be
right behind you.
-Sakura!
-Idate!
-Gotta do something.
-This is bordering
on ridiculous.
I've always hated
people who don't
know when they should quit.
-This is as far as you go.
-Hm?
Enough of your cheap tricks.
What the-- Hm.
That's enough heroism for one
day, don't you think, Idate?
NARUTO: Over here, pal!
We're not finished!
Up here!
Rasengan!
-This can't be happening!
[shouting]
-Naruto!
You did it!
-Naruto.
I don't believe it.
That was really incredible.
-Yeah, well-- Sakura!
SAKURA: Naruto!
Idate!
-Sakura's all right.
-She's still alive.
-And don't worry.
Sasuke's fine!
-Hold on!
I'll have to out of
there in no time!
SAKURA: You idiot!
Forget about us and just
get to the finish line!
Time is running out!
-Oh yeah, that's right.
But what the heck
do we do about this?
-Leave it to me.
If we cut the rope, we'll
be on the other side
in about two seconds.
-Uh, yeah, I got you.
-You know, I-- I've never really
thought that highly of myself.
But even when I
didn't, Boss Jirocho
always put his faith in me.
-The Wasabi family has
complete faith in you.
I have faith in you.
IDATE: That never
happened before.
No one ever trusted
me with anything.
And that's exactly why I wanted
to win this race for him,
no matter what was
standing in my way.
But it turns out just
wanting it wasn't enough.
There were so many times
I almost lost hope.
-Watch out!
IDATE: But whenever
that happened,
you guys risked
your lives for me,
no matter how
useless I'd become.
-Hang on tight.
Here we go!
Naruto, forgive me.
I should have trusted you
guys right from the beginning.
-So, what are you
telling me this now for?
Save that kind of
stuff for after you've
crossed the finish line.
-Yeah.
You're right.
Here.
Use this.
-Idate!
-Now, let's do it.
-OK!
[screaming]
[crowd gasping]
[crowd booing]
-Heh.
Please, you know you love me.
[screaming]
-Naruto!
We're heading straight
for the rocks!
-Yeah, I know!
Don't worry, I'm on it!
Gotta focus chakra to
the bottom of my feet.
For cryin' out loud, I'm
almost out of chakra!
Come on, now.
Just a little bit more!
[shout]
-Way to go, Naruto!
Now hurry up and get
to the finish line!
-Sit tight, Sakura!
I'll be back to help
before you know it, OK?
All right.
Let's get going, Idate.
-Right!
-Come on.
Keep runnin', Fukusuke!
-Don't let up 'til
the race is over!
-Aw, shut up.
Tell me something I don't know.
Stupid idiots.
This is my big moment.
What are they trying
to do, ruin it?
MAN: Hurry up!
-Finally.
There's the great
Todoroki Shrine up ahead.
-Well, this is it.
-Oh, no.
-Excellent.
-Idate.
-Come on, go!
-You can do it!
-Hurry!
-Here he comes!
It's Idate from
the Wasabi family!
[cheering]
-You can do it!
-What the--
-Idate!
-You idiot!
What are you doing, Fukusuke?
Come on!
-I'm not gonna lose.
No matter what happens,
I am not going to lose!
I'm not giving up 'til
the end of the end!
-Forget it!
No one's pulling
ahead of me now.
Not after I've
come all this way.
-All right!
-He's doing it!
-Dammit!
He's right on top of me!
I won't lose, y little runt!
Dammit!
-Come on, Idate!
Keep going!
You can do it!
-Boss.
-Keep going!
Idate!
[shout]
[cheering]
-I did it.
[laughter]
-Idate.
That was a good race, son.
You did very well.
-Please, sir, forgive me.
I'm truly sorry.
-Why apologize?
You are the winner of the race.
You do realize that, don't you?
-No.
Please, boss, let me speak.
I beg of you-- I really
want to apologize.
I'm truly sorry.
-You're not making any sense.
You really are an
odd one, aren't you?
-You did very well, Idate.
-You really came through.
-Well, go on, then.
This is your day.
They're all waiting for you.
-Right.
[cheering]
-Hey!
You did it!
-You lousy piece of trash!
-You've brought shame
upon the boss' head!
I hope you're ready for
what's comin' to ya.
-I'm sorry!
-The winner, Idate Morino!
Representing the Wasabi family.
-Yay!
CHEERING]
-Well, that's that.
GIRL: Wow!
He won!
-It looks like he
finally did it.
-Hold on.
That's enough.
-Huh?
Kyuroku?
-It seems this kid rode on
the back of a hired ninja
for part of the way.
That's a violation.
-What did you say?
-I have proof.
Just take a look at
this photograph, huh?
They have to make it here
by their own strength.
Those are the
rules of this race.
The boy must be disqualified.
Which means that Fukusuke
Hikyakuya of the Wagarashi
family is the winner.
-What?
It can't be!
-But wait a minute.
That was--
-I'll hear none of your excuses.
Jirocho, you gave your word.
I want the Wasabi a family
to disband immediately.
-Just a moment.
There is no such rule.
Stop talking nonsense.
-But-- my lord!
-But what?
Are you suggesting I let
the Wagarashi win simply
because you wish it?
-No.
Of course not.
-Perhaps the reason you
want to win so badly
is that it would mean an
end to all the bribes you've
been accepting.
Look here.
You ignoramous.
you'll give up your position
and don a monk's robe.
-Yes-- Yes, sir.
-And you, Kyuroku.
-Yes?
-I have heard a great
deal about the evil deeds
you have committed.
Your crimes against the
people of Port Degarashi
are unforgivable.
From this day forth, the
Wagarashi family is no more.
Is that clear?
-Yes, sir.
[laughter]
-An auspicious day.
Now let us consider
this matter ended.
[cheering]
-I want to thank you for
all your help, Naruto.
-Yeah, well, it was my pleasure.
-I've come to get the wounded.
-Ibiki-sensei.
-Big brother!
-Where is the wounded?
-He's right over here.
-OK.
Let's get him on the boat, then.
-Oh.
Right.
-Um, excuse me.
-What is it?
-Oh-- never mind.
-Big brother.
Big brother!
Hold on!
-Who are you?
Only one person called me that.
And he died three years ago.
IDATE (VOICEOVER): Big brother.
I've figured out the answer
to the 10th question.
I'll never betray
a comrade again.
I know what it means
now to trust in others.
IBIKI (VOICEOVER):
You've grown up well.
-So long, Idate!
See you again someday!
-Yeah, we'll see you.
You take care.
-You got it.
You guys come back any time.
-Hey boss, take care
of yourself, OK?
-Yeah.
-Buh bye!
-So long!
IBIKI (VOICEOVER): Always
interesting, this kid.
It's no wonder the Fifth Hokage
has taken a shine to him.
-Naruto!
Thanks again!
-Idate!
Next time I see you, we'll
have to spar a little!
-Sasuke.
Does it hurt?
-No, it doesn't.
-Oh good.
Don't worry.
Those wounds will heal once
we get back to the village.
-Sure.
AOI (VOICEOVER): I see
that the stories are true.
I'd always heard that the
last of the great Uchia clan
was a hopeless loser
unworthy of his family name.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): I
wasn't able to beat him.
But Naruto-- Naruto was.
[theme music]
SAKURA: Sasuke, Naruto.
What's happened to both of you?
Come on.
This is a hospital.
Sasuke's recouperating.
You should know better, Naruto.
Stop messing around already.
Geez, what is this?
Why is this happening?
NARUTO: Next time,
The Battle Begins!
Naruto Versus Sasuke!
[theme music]