[music playing]
[theme music]
[sighing]
[music playing]
NARUTO: "Viva Dojo Challenge!
Youth is All About Passion!"
-Oh.
Long time, no see, Naruto.
You back from some
kind of solo mission?
-Yep.
I just had to deliver some
letter for Grandma Tsunade.
-Oh yeah?
Then you'd better report
to her office right away.
-Where do you think
I'm going Man,
I know I've only
been gone for a week,
but the village seems
an awful lot different.
Huh?
[thud]
That sign wasn't here before.
"Dojo Challenges?"
What?
This way, huh?
[grunting]
[groaning]
It's a tight squeeze.
Is that it?
"Welcome to Hot Blooded Dojo."
Who the heck would
build a dojo out here?
Huh?
[screaming]
LEE: I have been waiting.
NARUTO: (CONFUSED) What?
LEE: You have
accepted my challenge?
Good.
You may attack me
from any direction.
-Huh?
Uh, Bushy Brows?
-No move.
Then I will come at you.
-Huh?
What the heck?
Hey!
What's the big
idea, Bushy Brows?
It's me!
[groaning]
-Naruto?
[panting]
-Man, that was a close one.
-So, my first dojo challenger
will be you, Naruto?
I could not wish for
a better challenge.
-Huh?
LEE: I will fight
with all my heart.
-Fight?
Hey!
Wait just a min--
[gasping]
-Leaf hurricane!
[screaming]
[crashing]
LEE: Have some tea.
So you only came to take a look?
-(GRUNTING) Mhm.
-Well, if you had told
me so in the first place,
you might have avoided
getting kicked.
-Sorry, but it was kind
of hard to talk to you.
You were too many slamming
me through a wall!
LEE: Oh, yes.
I do apologize for that.
NARUTO: Uh, yeah.
So, is this your very
own dojo, Bushy Brows?
LEE: It is.
I've been building it piece
by piece for a long time
and finally finished
construction six days ago.
So I distributed this flyer--
not only in Hidden Leaf
Village, but across nearby
towns and villages, too.
LEE: NARUTO: You don't say.
I just got back from
a mission today,
so I must have missed it.
-Oh, is that so?
-Hey, uh, what's up with
building your own dojo?
Ahh!
-This dojo will help
me further my training!
-What?
Your training?
-You see, I have been so
preoccupied with my missions
lately, I have not
been able to devote
enough time to
developing my skills.
And even when I did, it was hard
to find experienced practice
partners, so I could
not train effectively.
-Hmm.
-Just when I was
wondering what to do,
I saw something in another
village on a mission.
[people talking]
MAN (BACKGROUND): I
issue a challenge!
MAN: Yes, sir, this way.
-Hm.
I have traveled far and wide in
order to perfect my training,
and now you will see my skills.
However, if I win this match,
I will claim your marquee
as my own.
-Dojo against dojo?
Very well.
I accept the terms
of your challenge.
-Ready!
We fight!
-That is when I realized
that if I open my own dojo,
someone with this
high level of skill
would surely come
to challenge me.
I worked hard to build
the dojo so that finally I
could get some real practice.
But so far, no one
has shown up yet.
No one to challenge me.
-Ohh, I think I get it.
Huh?
[gasping]
-Since you have wandered
in here, what about you
issuing a challenge?
-Huh?
LEE: And if you win, I will give
you my hand-painted marquee.
-That's great, but
I don't need one.
-Please do not say no, Naruto.
Fight me!
[yelling]
-(NERVOUSLY LAUGHING)
Come to think of it,
I totally forgot to
report to Grandma Tsunade.
I better book it over there.
See you around!
-Uh.
Naruto!
(YELLING) Please be
my first challenger!
NARUTO: Darn it.
I spent too much time
at that dumb dojo,
and now Grandma Tsunade is
going to tear me to shreds.
Oh man.
I better steer clear
of Bushy Brow's dojo
until he calms down.
GUY: What?
Lee's dojo?
-Huh?
Bushier Brows Sensei?
-Hm.
Naruto, did I hear
what I thought I heard?
So, while I was
away on my mission,
Lee was so desperate
for practice
that he decided to open his own
dojo in order to train himself?
[crying]
NARUTO: Huh?
-I have taught my pupil well.
I, Might Guy, am both
moved and impressed!
-Hm.
The problem is not
a single challenger
from a rival dojo has
shown up to fight him.
-Huh?
How dare the other dojos
treat him like this!
Lee's hopes and
dreams unrealized!
I'll hunt down
all those cowards,
and I won't go easy on them!
-But, uh, if you
do, wouldn't that
leave even fewer folks
to spare with him?
-Huh?
Gosh darn it, you're right!
What do I do?
[slurping]
Huh.
Of course.
If no one from the other schools
will come challenge Lee--
-Huh?
-Well then, why don't
I just pay him a visit?
Except I'll be disguised
as a fighter who
comes to spare against him.
-Say what?
-Yes, I will act out the part
of Lee's first dojo challenger.
[gulping]
-Huh?
[laughing]
-A perfect disguise,
if I do say so.
No one would imagine it's
me in this crazy getup.
Here I come, Lee!
[foot steps]
-Guy Sensei!
-Huh?
[panting]
I found you.
-If it isn't Sakura.
So, what's going on?
-Guy, forgive me
for bothering you
when you've only just returned.
We just received an
emergency distress
call from Shikamaru's
squad, which
was on a transport mission.
We're flying blind.
We don't know how
strong the enemy is,
and that's why if
we make a mistake
in our initial
encounter, this might
turn into something major.
-Judging from the reports,
they shouldn't be too far away.
-So they're close.
-First, do some recon to
confirm the situation.
And if it looks like
they need reinforcements,
you know what to do.
-Right.
On my way.
[door opening]
[door closing]
-Does anyone have a clue why
he was dressed like that?
-[? i don't know. ?]
-Huh?
NANAFUSHI: What's with
this strange fellow?
Whatever.
I'm sure he wouldn't mind
m e borrowing his form
to infiltrate the
village while he's away.
[laughing]
Yes, the Village
Hidden in the Leaves.
I, Nanafushi, shall find out
every last detail and weakness.
Huh.
-And this challenger
you met, he really
traveled here from another dojo?
NARUTO: Well, that's
what he told me,
so I got no reason
to think otherwise.
He said he saw your flyers.
-Well, if that is the
case, where is he?
-(VOICEOVER) Ugh.
Come on, Guy Sensei.
How long are you going
to keep the kid waiting?
-Naruto, he is not here!
So instead, I would like
to spar against you.
-(NERVOUSLY) What?
[groaning]
(VOICEOVER) No, not again!
Uh, hold on, let me
just go look for him.
-Ugh!
Naruto!
Let us work up a
vigorous sweat in battle!
-Huh.
He's coming back again.
-I knew that outfit
wasn't a good idea.
-(VOICEOVER) What?
Outfit?
What's he talking about?
-Huh?
Uh, Sensei?
No way.
That's your disguise?
Everyone can tell it's you!
-Uh, yeah, I'm with you.
I didn't think it was
a great idea either.
[laughing]
(VOICEOVER) Oh no, can it be?
Have these people discovered
my true identity already?
NARUTO: Bushier Brows Sensei!
(ANGRILY) Would you hurry it up?
-Wh-- what is it?
-Quit messing around!
We gotta get you over
to Lee's dojo ASAP!
-Huh?
-If you don't show up, then
I'm going to have to fight him,
and that ain't happening.
Let's go!
[laughing]
-See you soon!
-Did he seem weird to you?
-No weirder than usual.
-(VOICEOVER) Excellent.
I'm safe, thanks to this boy.
Perhaps I'll stick
with him for a bit
until I get a lay of the land.
Where are we?
-Duh.
This is Bushy Brow's dojo.
Seriously, you couldn't come
up with a better disguise
than that ridiculous thing?
-Hm?
-Well, whatever.
Lee must be tired of waiting,
so try to do a good acting job,
OK?
-(VOICEOVER) Acting?
What is he talking about?
-Hey, Bushy Brows!
I found him!
LEE: I have been waiting.
Now, we will fight to see
if you can best my dojo.
[gasping]
Come in.
I am ready.
-Uh-- I, uh--
-Aren't you supposed to say,
I issue a challenge now?
-Oh, is that right?
-I, uh, issue a challenge.
-Do I hear a familiar call?
So you come to try and
destroy my dojo's reputation.
Well, I accept.
And if you can beat me, then
you can claim my marquee
as your own.
(VOICEOVER) Well-- uh,
he really thinks I'm
a challenger from a rival dojo?
Absurd.
[gulping]
And he's just a kid.
Oh well, got no choice.
I'll go easy on him.
OK, here I come.
-Ready!
-(VOICEOVER) Huh?
Where'd he go?
[groaning]
-Huh?
-(VOICEOVER) What just happened?
[grunting]
[groaning]
-(VOICEOVER) That--
that little brat!
LEE: Hi-ya!
[grunting]
[screaming]
GUY (VOICEOVER): He's strong!
[yelling]
-(VOICEOVER) What the
heck are you doing?
I know you're only
pretending to lose,
but you at least have to
make it look interesting.
I get it.
He's not fighting because Lee
would recognize his technique.
-(VOICEOVER) Even
if I had nine lives,
I'd use every one of
them against this kid.
[groaning]
I need to wave the
white flag and get out
of here while I can still walk.
Wait.
-Huh?
-I submit.
-But that means?
I did it!
I bravely fought out my first
challenger from another dojo!
-That's not what it means!
-Huh?
-What he meant by I
submit was it's time
to submit the official
challenge to you.
-Huh?
-In other words, he's just been
warming up this whole time.
But now he's ready
to really throw down.
Right?
-(VOICEOVER) What's
this kid talking about?
-Of course.
Now I understand it.
[gulping]
-You do?
Against such a
seasoned veteran, I
thought it was strange
that I could fight off
the challenge so easily.
-(VOICEOVER) It's not strange.
There's nothing
strange about it!
-In that case, I will go all
out and not hold anything back!
-(VOICEOVER) No way!
You mean he was
holding back before?
[groaning]
-(VOICEOVER) Wow.
Bushier Brows Sensei is
a pretty darn good actor.
He almost has me fooled.
The way he's getting
pummeled, you'd
never think he was a master.
GUY: What?
You were only been
attacked by monkeys?
-They managed to grab all the
snacks Choji was carrying.
But at least the cargo's safe.
That's something.
[sighing]
-All my snacks-- stolen.
-Anyway, Ino mistook it
for a real enemy attack,
so she panicked and sent
out a distress message.
-(ANGRILY) Don't blame me!
It happened so fast!
Besides, it's all your fault
for taking so much junk
food in the first place!
-Look, these were only available
for a limited time and only
in the Land of Tea.
Green tea pork-flavored
chips are super rare.
When a connoisseur of
snacks finds a limited offer
like this one, it would
be a crime for him
not to take as much as he can.
-(ANGRILY) And how
is that my problem?
-(ANGRILY) What did you say?
-(ANGRILY) You heard me!
[groaning]
-Shikamaru, you must
have had a rough time.
-Right back at you.
The way you're looking.
What the heck happened to you?
GUY: Huh?
What do you mean?
What's wrong with how I look?
INO: Here.
-Oh, that's right.
I haven't got time
to sit here and chat!
I've got to get
back to Lee's dojo!
(YELLING) Wait for me, Lee!
-Huh?
-Uh huh.
[screaming]
-(VOICEOVER) Sensei, you're
overdoing it on the getting
beaten up routine.
[screaming]
-Huh?
[crashing]
-Shall I finish him off?
-Hold it!
Time out!
-Hm?
[groaning]
NARUTO: Come on.
Fight him back a
little, will you?
-(VOICEOVER) Believe me.
I would if I could.
-If Lee doesn't find
this challenging enough,
he'll want more, and I might get
stuck being his next punching
bag.
-Well, actually--
NARUTO: Yeah?
-It's been one extreme
mission after another,
and I haven't had any sleep.
-Oh, well, that explains it.
-If I got a little rest, I
think I might recover, but--
-Uh?
-While I take my rest, won't
you please do me a favor
and act as his
opponent for a while?
[screaming]
-Come on!
-Huh?
Now what?
-I'm almost there, Lee!
-Was that Guy again?
-I could have sworn
he already came back.
-Hey, sorry to keep you waiting.
-Huh?
To have withstood
such a fierce attack,
yet you are standing
there unharmed.
What a fighter!
The world is so vast, but
somehow an amazing challenger
found me.
For today's experience alone,
this dojo was worth it.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
There's no way
I'll ever win if I just
use my taijutsu alone.
Luckily, I've got my
own style of fighting!
-Here I come!
-Shadow clone jutsu!
LEE (VOICEOVER): Of course!
A fighter of his caliber
would know ninjutsu.
Leaf hurricane!
The real one is right above me.
[yelling]
Primary lotus!
Oh no!
Another clone!
-Fooled you!
Let's try this again!
-So, you will make more clones?
[laughing]
-Don't hurt me, Lee!
LEE: Sakura!
-It's me, Lee!
Be nice to me!
Take it easy!
-So-- so many Sakuras
all in one place!
Lucky day!
How moving!
I have never known
such happiness
before in my entire life!
-Snap out of it!
-Huh?
[yelling]
-We did it!
[groaning]
-I guess I forgot.
This is a fight against
a fierce challenger.
A clever ruse.
But I will not fall for
the same trick again.
Even though they may
look like Sakura,
they are really
just phony replicas.
-Lee, that was so mean.
[bell ringing]
-This is ridiculous, Guy Sensei!
Come back!
-(VOICEOVER) For a
couple of spoiled brats,
they sure do fight at an
exceptionally high level.
This Hidden Leaf
Village-- I suppose
that the rumors that it had lost
its strength were just lies.
[lee yelling]
I need to do more snooping
around to get the real story.
[lee yelling]
This form has
become a challenge.
Unless I change, I fear it will
just cause more trouble for me.
That's much better.
Well then, time to shove off.
-Uh, hold it right there.
(VOICEOVER) What?
The real deal!
-I understand that
you are one, Rock Lee,
the master of this dojo.
-(VOICEOVER) Oh great, I guess
I'll have to play along with
this for a moment.
Yes, that is true.
I am indeed Rock Lee, and I
am the master of this dojo.
[laughing]
-Well, then, hello.
I challenge you for
the title of your dojo.
Rock Lee, I shall defeat you and
claim your marquee as my own.
-Huh?
-We begin.
[screaming]
[panting]
-You put up a good fight.
-Yeah, you did, too.
[crashing]
-Huh?
[groaning]
-Help me!
-What?
Bushy Brow?
-Me?
GUY: [inaudible]
[crashing]
[screaming]
-What?
Another dojo challenger?
NARUTO: Guy Sensei?
What the heck took you so long?
-Na-- Naruto?
I am confused.
What is going on?
GUY: If you can't defend
against this basis attack,
there's no use even
talking to you.
Your training is a
complete failure!
-Wait!
No!
I'm not him!
-You don't deserve
your own dojo.
It's just way too soon.
Such naive thinking.
Well, I know how to fix that!
[crashing]
[screaming]
I hope you can forgive me, Lee.
It was tough love.
-The challenger's true identity
was actually Guy Sensei?
-What the?
You're the real Lee?
Then who did I just
punch through the wall?
-Never seen him before.
Who is he?
-Why me?
[groaning]
[knocking]
-Come in.
Oh, Guy.
You brought Naruto and Lee.
What perfect timing.
I was just about to call
you all into my office.
-Why?
Is something else going on?
-We just now received
an intelligence report.
-A ninja from the
Land of Valleys
named Nanafushi is rumored to
be spying on the Leaf Village.
-Huh?
-I'm concerned that he may
have already infiltrated
the village.
I want you to go search for
this Nanafushi immediately.
Capture him.
[gasping]
-That's the fella?
-Do you think you
know where he is?
-It's him!
-Oh.
-I have no idea what's
going on, but you
can call that mission complete.
[crashing]
GUY: Well then,
we'll be on our way.
TSUNADE: Hey!
Don't just leave
him on my floor!
SHIZUNE: Wait!
Guy!
Hold on!
TSUNADE: I demand
an explanation!
Guy!
Lee!
Hey!
Naruto!
[theme music]
[thunder]
TSUNADE: Past midnight
when the trees are asleep,
in the small hours
of the morning
when the forest is deathly
calm, a lonely signpost
tells of the
destruction of a clan.
Suddenly, a strike of
thunder and a heavy rain
begins to fall.
What could be the true
identity of the iron castle
that appeared out of nowhere?
Next time-- "The Mysterious
Curse of the Haunted Castle."
[theme music]