[theme music]
[chuckling]
-You really shouldn't
lower your guard, sensei.
[panting]
-Now I'll correct my mistake
and bury you once and for all!
-Whatever you're
planning it's too late.
It's over.
I've won.
The Leaf Village will fall.
-I carry this title in trust for
those Hokage who came before,
and those who will come after!
I am the third Hokage!
Get ready.
For I am about to
perform a jutsu that even
you haven't seen before.
Sealing jutsu.
Reaper Death Seal!
NARUTO: Forbidden
secret technique.
Reaper Death seal.
OROCHIMARU: A jutsu
I haven't seen?
[growl]
HOKAGE (VOICEOVER):
I've got to hurry.
This darkness is dangerous.
OROCHIMARU: Well, must I
make you show it to me?
-Huh?
[grunting]
OROCHIMARU: What's the matter?
Are you planning to let
your predecessors pummel you
to death?
Are you going to show
me this jutsu or not?
HOKAGE (VOICEOVER): Hurry.
Hurry.
-Finally it's done.
And not a minute too soon.
OROCHIMARU: Aw.
What's wrong?
You're reeling from
fatigue already?
HOKAGE (VOICEOVER):
Now all that's
left is to catch hold of him.
-I have you!
[groaning]
I won't let go!
I summon thee!
[panting]
-The darkness vanished.
What is this jutsu?
-Sarutobi!
-Forgive us, Sarutobi.
-We made your life difficult.
-And forgive me, first lord
Hokage, second lord Hokage.
Now!
Seal!
-You sacrificed your people.
-All these villages
are a part of me,
just as I am a part of them.
Being Hokage means
believing in your people,
just as much as
they believe in you.
-Do you hear?
Guide the people
and believe in them.
For it's from among
them that the one
will come who will carry
on when your time is done.
Beginning tomorrow
you are Hokage.
-You were meant to guide
them, not toy with them
as if they were dolls.
-Are you finished, sensei?
Have we had enough
of this nonsense yet?
-The people put
their faith in you!
Enma, Come!
I've got him!
-Striking Shadow Snake!
-Damn you!
-Now to finish it!
OROCHIMARU (VOICEOVER):
What is this I feel?
[groan] This is bad!
-Now die!
-We have to hold
them off somehow.
-Where's our back up?
IBIKI (VOICEOVER): It's
out of our hands now.
JIRAIYA: Ninja Art Summoning!
Bring down the House jutsu!
-But that jutsu!
Long time no see, Ibiki.
My, my.
What have they been feeding you?
You used to be such
a little squirt.
-Master Jiraiya.
-Jiraiya?
One of the Sannin?
-All right, you baby chicks.
Open wide those beady
little eyes of yours!
Watch closely.
When it comes to dealing with
strange otherworldly freaks
and monsters no one's better
than a strange hermit ninja.
Thank goodness that
Jiraiya's here.
Now, unless you want to
make this frog really mad,
you'll never bother us again!
So that pain in the neck
Orochimaru has finally started.
Where's Hokage?
-The battle arena.
-I see.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
Don't die on us, old man.
[grunting]
[groaning]
-Old man!
Why didn't you dodge it?
-Sarutobi.
-There was no need.
The one who cast the
Reaper Death Seal, in order
to send his enemy's
soul to oblivion,
must sacrifice his own
life if it is to work.
It's a jutsu with a heavy price.
[gasp]
OROCHIMARU (VOICEOVER):
I can't use my jutsu.
-There was no need
to dodge the blade.
My fate is sealed.
-It is a jutsu of the great
hero who once saved this village
Once the seal is
complete, I will die.
But I will die knowing that
I've taken you with me.
-So then, this is the jutsu
that sealed the Nine-tailed Fox
spirit.
HOKAGE: Inch by inch, your
soul will be dragged out of you
and sealed forever!
OROCHIMARU (VOICEOVER): My
body-- I can't make it move!
-Another moment or two and
you'll be able to see it.
It's nearly half way out.
You'll be able to bid a
last farewell to your soul,
but not to your suffering.
For those souls that
are sealed by this jutsu
are doomed to
suffer for eternity
in the belly of the Reaper,
never to rest in peace.
There the souls of the
sealed and the sealer
are forever intertwined,
bound together by hatred,
locked in ceaseless combat
until the end of time!
-What is that?
[wailing]
OROCHIMARU (VOICEOVER):
That thing is the Reaper?
[wailing]
-You old fool!
Do you really think
I'll just stand here
like a frightened
child and do nothing?
[groan]
Go on, sensei.
Hurry up and die.
-All right now.
Stay together.
[whimpering]
Now everyone keep quiet.
-Oh, Konohamaru.
-It's not going to collapse
on top of us, is it?
-No way.
Don't worry.
We'll be fine.
Even though this tunnel under
the mountain is really old,
it's strong too.
They knew how to build
things back then.
My grampa told me that and
my grampa's always right.
That's right.
So no worries.
We're going to be just fine.
[groan]
-It's coming.
But which one?
So it's Uchiha.
KANKURO (VOICOVER):
What about Temari?
-You through running away?
-Who says I was running?
I'll take you on.
No problem.
-Wait!
-Temari?
When he showed up
and you didn't, I
thought he must have finished.
-He could have.
And why he didn't I don't know.
I guess I didn't delay him
for very long time, did I?
-It's OK.
Every second gives Gaara
more time to recover.
And the more chakra Uchiha
is forced to use up,
the better for us.
[chuckle]
-There it is.
-Oh, what?
Someone's shampoo?
-No.
I smell Sasuke.
He's not alone.
I smell others with him.
He's caught up to them.
-At last.
-Sasuke.
-They're close together
and they've stopped moving.
Could mean a fight.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Be careful, Sasuke.
-We should hurry.
PAKKUN (VOICEOVER): What
are all these other smells?
A bunch of them all
converging on the same spot.
-Smells like we're not the
only ones tracking Sasuke.
There's something
else out there.
-Really?
Where?
-Who is it?
Friend or foe.
-I don't know, but--
-But what?
-It isn't human.
[gasping]
-I've got this, Kankuro.
Get Gaara out of here.
Go on.
-Temari, you take
Gaara and go on ahead.
-Huh?
-You're all worn out.
Look at yourself.
Go on.
You'll only get in my way.
-Wait a second.
-Get moving!
Hurry up.
-All right.
-OK, Uchiha.
Time you picked on
someone your own size.
-Heh.
Whatever you say.
SHINO: Hold on.
-I've got dibs on
him first, Sasuke.
-What do you want?
-Shino?
How did you find us?
-I planted a beetle on
you as you left the arena.
A female beetle.
She gives off a
very faint scent.
Nothing you could detect, but
the male of the species can.
He has a very strong
sense of smell
and he'd follow her anywhere.
[gasp]
Sasuke Uchiha, it's Gaara
you're really after.
that is, because your
match against him
was left unfinished.
-Heh.
-Well I have similar unfinished
business with Kankuro.
Because our match
never even started.
-I withdraw.
So please, advance
to the next match.
-He's mine.
Leave him to me.
Go.
-Well, all right then.
If you're sure you're OK.
-Don't worry.
Give me 10 minutes and I'll come
after you to see if you're OK.
-Don't waste your time.
By then my work
will be done too.
[chuckling]
-You clueless fools.
You don't know
what you're in for.
Imagine something more monstrous
than your worst nightmare.
Only it's real.
-Hm.
I've having a little
trouble picturing it.
Why don't you go
ahead and show me.
-Oh.
It's not me.
If you're ever unlucky enough
to catch up with Gaara,
that's when you'll see it.
But first course,
you'll have to beat me.
[theme music]
GAARA: You are strong, Uchiha.
You have friends
while I have none.
But you are strong of purpose.
Unyielding, and in
that we are the same.
But my purpose is stronger.
For only by destroying
you can I exist.
I kill to live Uchiha!
And you are my prey!
NARUTO: Next time--
astonishing truth.
Gaara's identity emerges!