[theme music]
-His level of chakra
is unbelievable.
It's so much that
my skin is crawling.
-I feel the same
thing in my nose.
-Mizuki.
-What's the matter?
Too chicken to make a move?
-Oh, yeah?
-Naruto, hold on!
Stay back!
-He is stupid.
-Naruto, you OK?
-If I were in your shoes, I'd
be more worried about myself.
IRUKA (VOICEOVER): He's fast.
And he's so strong.
[mizuki laughing]
MIZUKI: This must be the power
Lord Orochimaru promised.
I've become unstoppable.
I almost scare myself.
Well, aren't you impressed?
Mizuki, please stop.
Don't do this.
I beg you.
-Tsubaki, don't!
-I don't care what
might happen to me.
I'm begging you,
you have to stop now
before you take this too far.
Please, Mizuki.
Come home to the village.
-Tsubaki, I'm touched.
But if you truly care that
much about helping me,
why don't you be useful
and get out of my way?
-Oh, no.
Tsubaki!
-What?
-You're too slow.
-Iruka sensei!
Take this Shadow Clone Jutsu!
-Still using the same
boring attack, huh?
You sure haven't
gotten any better.
-He vanished!
-No, wait.
He didn't vanish.
He just moves really quickly.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): He's
accelerating and moving
into our blind spots.
In that case-- everybody!
We need to watch every
inch of this forest!
Uzumaki Whirlpool Formation!
-I see what he's up to.
Even an idiot gets a
bright idea now and then.
It doesn't matter.
If you're smart enough
to think that up,
maybe you're smart
enough to know
how much you're gonna suffer!
-Here he is!
-I knew I spotted him!
-You didn't spot me, boy.
You only saw me 'cause
I wanted you to.
-I got ya now!
No way.
I can see him, but I
still can't hit him.
-It's no trick.
I'm not predicting your attacks.
You just move so
slow, it's easy.
-Huh?
MIZUKI: Hey, you had it coming.
Stupid demon fox.
Come on.
You can't just give
up that quickly.
I want you to taste
the same agony
I've endure for years and years.
The fun's just starting.
Right, Naruto?
There's still much
more enjoyment to come.
Like this.
[naruto yelling]
-Stop it, Mizuki.
Don't you lay
another hand on him.
-Stay out of this, Iruka!
Do you have any
idea how long I've
been waiting for this
moment to arrive?
I've been yearning for this
ever since the day I first
met you-- to finally
take my revenge.
With my new power, I'm going
to savor destroying you both.
Stand up and watch, Iruka.
I'm going to start
with your friend.
-Mizuki--
-Now, there you go.
Good job.
-Let's do it.
-Come on!
That was pathetic.
You're so not even in
the same league as me.
Fate has made my body
into the ultimate weapon,
and now, I finally
get to obliterate you.
-What are you talking
about, the ultimate weapon?
When all your power depends
on some unnatural potion,
it's not true power.
-That's so like you.
Always acting better than me.
Go ahead.
Try and beat me using that
true power you love so much!
You'll never be like me.
All your life, you've just
been some insignificant teacher
who allows your own village
to use you like a puny pawn.
You're jealous of
the way I live.
I know you want m power.
But even if you
practiced for 100 years,
you'd never be able to learn it.
This is only the
beginning of my wrath.
I'm going to get even
stronger than this.
Soon, Orochimaru will share
his hidden jutsu with me.
-You don't honestly believe
that's gonna happen?
-I'm getting tired of you
acting like you know everything.
I think it's time to
end all this-- just
like old times,
only this time, I'm
gonna finish you off
once and for all.
Ready to say goodbye?
-Naruto, why?
-Mizuki, don't you lay
another hand on my sensei!
-This is all so perfect.
Nothing ever changes, not even
down to the smallest detail.
One exception-- I'm much
different this time.
The only reason I was
defeated in our last meeting
was because I underestimated
that conniving demon fox.
-What is he turning into?
-I won't let my
guard down again.
I'm calling on all my
strength to crush you.
Now, let's all
have some real fun.
-Sorry, guys.
I can't hold on.
-Choji!
Great.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
If only I knew
I little more information
about these behemoths.
-Big bro, my body
feels much lighter now.
-Yeah, same here.
Almost weightless, huh, Raijin?
-OK.
Time to do us some clobbering.
-Right on.
Time for clobbering.
-Oh, come on.
[grunting]
-What the heck is this?
My body is frozen.
-I can't even move an inch.
-What?
Paralysis genjutsu.
TSUNADE: Looks like I
made it just in time.
-Huh?
You held them long enough.
Good work, Shikamaru,
Ino, Choji.
Now, leave the rest to me.
-The-- Fifth Hokage?
-I don't believe it.
Lady Hokage showed up in person?
-Lady Tsunade?
-I'm sorry I found out
about this so late.
But I wouldn't have imagined
these two morons were somehow
involved with Mizuki.
-Man, the Hokage.
-Thank goodness she's here.
-I can't move.
-Well, well.
Fujin and Raijin.
We run into each other in the
darnedest of places, don't we?
-Yeah.
-Uh, hi.
How you been, Tsunade?
-I hope you have
a good explanation
for what you're doing here.
-She's so strong.
-More like she's so scary.
-Now, then.
Isn't there something
you should say?
-We're sorry.
We're sorry.
-Please forgive us.
We won't do it again.
TSUNADE: You're telling
me the only reason
you obeyed Mizuki was
because he promised you
that there was a feast
waiting at Orochimaru's place?
FUJIN AND RAIJIN: Yeah.
We're so sorry.
-We had no chance
against those two.
They're such high level ninja.
-I wonder what happened
to make those oafs so
scared of Tsunade.
-I don't even want to imagine
what she might have done.
-Come on.
Even you two shouldn't
fall for such obvious bait.
OK, everybody.
Mizuki's heading up
into those mountains.
Naruto and Iruka are
probably with him.
You three rest up a
bit, and then we'll
get going after them.
-But wait.
Aren't you forgetting something?
I mean, what are we
going to do with them?
-Oh, you don't need to
worry about them anymore.
They know what'll
happen to them if they
cause us any more trouble.
I've decided to let them
go home on their own.
Now, Fujin, Raijin--
to be 100% clear,
if you are one minute
later, you get no dinner.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Come on, bro.
We can't just stand here.
Let's hurry back to prison
before we're too late.
-We gotta get back for dinner.
Dinner!
-Amazing.
Those guys sure can hustle.
-Well, if a person doesn't get
a proper dinner, he could die.
-Um, that's only
true for you, Choji.
-I don't get it.
His force is even greater
than it was earlier.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I can't
let him take me down like this.
After all, he may have a
clue about where Sasuke is.
-Naruto.
-Iruka, are you going
to be all right?
-Yeah.
-Hey, did you notice
what I noticed?
-What are you talking about?
-He's slowing down.
That jerk's power level
has increased tenfold,
but his movements are
getting sluggish and slow.
-You think he
transferred the chakra
he was using for speed to power?
-I don't know, but
something's different.
IRUKA (VOICEOVER): Naruto
can't last much longer alone.
But if Mizuki's
speed has dropped,
I might be able to
take advantage of it.
All right.
Just hang in there a
little more, Naruto.
-Are you impressed,
you little brat?
Do you appreciate the body
Lord Orochimaru gave me yet?
I'll tear you apart
with my bare hands.
-You-- you should just tell
me where I can find him.
Where's Orochimaru hiding?
I'm not gonna ask again.
-And why would I give a little
runt like you that information?
-Well, he sure wasn't in
the Hidden Sound Village.
-How would you know that?
Did you go to the
Hidden Sound Village?
-The compound was
already completely empty.
And Sasuke and Orochimaru
weren't there anymore.
-You must have really given
that one a lot of thought, huh?
I don't know where you heard
about the Village Hidden
the Sound.
But if you're trying
to throw me off
by telling me some stupid
bluff, it's not gonna happen.
I'm too smart.
You're gonna meet your maker.
Listen to me.
Don't you ever lie to
me like that again.
-Naruto, this way, fast!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Iruka sensei.
-Ha ha!
If you're so great,
why can't you catch me?
You
-Coward.
You won't get away.
No!
-OK.
Jump now, Naruto!
-All right!
-Huh?
No.
This is--
-Seal and capture perimeter.
-No!
Capture and arrest jutsu?
-[inaudible]!
-Amazing.
That jutsu is-- he learned
the fourth Hokage's jutsu.
That was Rasengan.
-Hey, you all
right, Iruka sensei?
-Naruto, that was fantastic.
What an incredible job.
NARUTO: Sensei,
this guy didn't know
the Hidden Sound
Village was abandoned.
So that makes me think he's
not really with Orochimaru.
-More of your filthy lies.
-Mizuki.
-I don't understand.
This is the ultimate body
given to me by Lord Orochimaru.
I'll go to the
Hidden Sound Village
and he will-- [vomiting]
-Iruka sensei, what's going on?
TSUNADE: It's just
as I suspected.
-Grandma Tsunade!
-Lady Hokage?
-His body's cellular
structure is disintegrating.
-You little bast-- what
have you done to me?
-It's not Naruto's fault.
This is caused by
the formula you took.
-What?
That's impossible.
-You're getting a taste
of your own medicine.
You see, that potion
wasn't fully developed yet.
-The last prisoner has
been recaptured, ma'am.
And we looked after Shizune.
She was injured quite badly, but
there's no threat to her life.
-I see.
Thanks for your hard work.
-That's good news, huh?
It's nice to hear
Shizune's gonna be OK.
TSUNADE: Orochimaru probably
discovered that potion
by accident while he
was trying to develop
some other illegal jutsu.
All we know is
that that substance
absorbs the DNA of
animals and combines it
with the human genome.
It draws huge primal
power out of the body,
but it only lasts a short while.
As it works, it puts
an incredible strain
on host' body cells--
stress that far exceeds
the limits of the human body.
It's too dangerous
for anyone to use.
IRUKA: But why would
Mizuki do that?
-I don't know all the
details of his involvement.
It's safe to assume Mizuki and
Orochimaru had joined forces
at some point.
However--
IRUKA: Now that bond is broken.
-Yes.
Sadly for Mizuki, Orochimaru
only used him as a play thing.
It was all a joke to him,
letting his ally march off
with some useless potion.
But Mizuki is one lucky guy.
An average shinobi would
have certainly lost his life.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): Although,
he'll never be a shinobi again.
-It's all pretty
unfortunate, isn't it?
-Actually, I kind
of had a feeling
it was gonna end this way.
-Did you really?
-But I can't quit
after one setback.
I'm gonna keep searching for
clues until I can find Sasuke.
-Tsubaki, I--
-Don't you dare pity me, Iruka.
-You shouldn't speak.
Next time we meet, I
promise I'll take you down,
and the little squirt, too.
-I'm sorry, but there's no way.
While you were pursuing
your selfish dream,
Naruto's been at work
honing his ninja skills.
There's no way you can
catch up with him now.
-Mizuki can never go back
to being a shinobi again.
-And you, Tsubaki?
-I'm thinking about
starting a new life as well.
But before that, I
must atone for all
of the trouble I
caused the village.
-Ah, what a beautiful sunset.
Well, let's get
back to the village.
-I don't give up.
I can't give up.
Hey, I did it!
-All right.
Since you all did such
a terrific job today,
I'm gonna treat you guys to
a meal at Ichiraku Ramen.
-No way!
You're so awesome, Iruka sensei!
-I want a big slice
of barbecued pork.
-I want all three kinds of ramen
noodles-- butter, soy sauce,
and miso.
-Hold on, Iruka.
Before that, you
need to get Naruto
to Leaf Village Hospital.
-Why?
I told you I feel OK.
-Don't argue with me.
SAKURA: Lady Tsunade!
-Hm?
-I did it!
I mastered the first level!
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): Incredible.
Her training only just began.
Could should be a genius
and surpass Shizune?
-Hey!
Sakura, over here!
IRUKA (VOICEOVER): I guess
you saved me this time around.
Naruto-- who knows how
strong he'll become?
[theme music]
-I can't take it anymore.
How am I supposed
to figure out where
Sasuke is if I'm
just sitting around?
And Grandma Tsunade's
telling me I
can't make any moves on my own.
If things keep going like
this, we'll never find Sasuke.
Come on, think.
There's gotta be something--
some small chance,
anything that'll
lead us to Sasuke.
Next time-- the Search for
the Rare Bikochu Beetle.