[theme music]
[rocks crumbling]
[popping]
[wood creaking]
JIRAIYA: Summoning Jutsu!
[boom]
-Naruto, grab on!
[splat]
-All right, pull him up.
Hurry!
-Not so fast!
Nngh.
Another clone!
-Over here!
Now it's my turn!
[thud]
-Rasengan!
Spiral Chakra Sphere!
[roaring]
-Aaugh!
[thud]
-Augh.
-Just be careful, Naruto!
There are two more
of them out there.
-Huh?
-Huh!
Speak of the devil.
-Kagero.
Come on, let's get outta here.
-Hey!
Hey!
[whoosh]
-Mmph.
Man, they're quick!
Especially when
they're running away.
-Naruto, it seems to me
you're forgetting something.
-Huh?
-What about Sakura?
-Dah!
You're right!
Hey, Sakura!
[crack]
-Dah!
-Naruto!
-I was worried!
Thank goodness
you're OK, Sasame.
[gong]
-Yeah, she's fine.
We're both fine.
Thanks so much for asking.
-Uh.
What's wrong?
You mad about something?
[wind]
-Here's a good spot.
Let's take a break.
-So, who's this pretty young
friend of yours, Sakura?
-OK, that's close enough!
-What do you mean?
What's going on?
-Whoa!
Just keep away from her, OK?
-Hmm?
Doh!
Are you serious?
You think I'd make
a pass at her?
She's too young for
me, for one thing.
And anyway, you think that's
all I ever think about?
-Just about all.
Sounds like Sakura's finally
caught onto you, Pervy Sage.
And it's about time, too.
-For the last time, I told
you not to call me Pervy Sage!
-I can think of worse
things to call ya!
-Knock it off, the two of ya!
Come on, the girl's
frightened enough already!
JIRAIYA AND NARUTO: Sorry.
-What a couple of jerks.
Anyway, this is Sasume,
a former clan ninja.
Her cousin was taken away
by Orochimaru not long ago
and she's been
searching high and low
trying to find him ever since.
-That's right.
Those goons who attacked
just now were after Sasame
to keep her from finding
Orochimaru's hide-out.
-Ah.
The Fuma Clan again, eh?
-Huh?
What do you mean, again?
-In the last village,
I made contact
with some men who said they
were once part of the Fuma Clan.
-You're kidding!
You actually picked up
some useful information
instead of just messing around?
-Whoa!
I never woulda thought.
-I was a little
hungry and thirsty,
so I wandered into
this nice litlte tavern
and it turned out to
be their hide-out.
-Ah!
So you were goofing off!
I bet there were some pretty
girls in there, too, huh?
-Hey, let's have a little
more respect for your teacher,
if you don't mind!
What's Sakura going to think
if you keep talking this way?
-Oh, I stopped respecting
you a long time ago.
-I see..
I'm sorry to hear that.
-They were from the Fuma Clan?
-Yeah.
Their leader's name was
Hanzaki or something.
-Hanzaki and his
followers are traitors
who abandoned our clan.
-Are they?
-What was it that happened
between you and these men?
-After I taught them a lesson
for trying to steal my money,
I questioned them
about Orochimaru
and his possible whereabouts.
Sadly, they were no help at all.
-If you're sure you
wanna find his hide-out,
I can show you the way.
-You can, really?
-Yes.
-Ha!
Well, what're we waitin' for?
-Nngh.
-That would of
yours hasn't healed.
Don't push yourself.
-I'm all right.
There.
-Huh?
SASAME: That's the entrance
to the village hidden
in the Sound.
Orochimaru's lair lies deep
within those mountains.
SAKURA: So somewhere
behind those mountains,
we'll find Sasuke.
-Welp!
No use standing
around here then.
Come on, guys, let's get movin'!
-Wait!
Not so fast!
-Ack!
[thud]
-What is it now?
-Yeah, we really should hurry.
We don't want to be caught
out there in the mountains
when night falls.
-Yeah, that's right!
Sasuke's just a
stone's throw away
and you want to stand
here thinking about it?
-There's no telling what's
happening to him, even now.
Why in the world do
you want us to wait?
[stomach gowling]
-Huh?
-What was that?
-[chuckling nervously] Nothing!
I'm just a little
hungry, I guess.
-You're kidding, right?
You want a snack break?
-No shinobi goes
into battle hungry!
In a few steps, we'll be
entering enemy territory.
There will be little
time for eating then.
This is our last chance.
So!
I suggest you eat while you can.
[sighing]
-Eat up, it's not half bad!
-Well, I guess we might as well.
-Actually, one of the ladies in
the tavern took a liking to me.
She was the prettiest of
the whole bunch. [laughing]
She made all this with
her dainty, loving hands,
just for me.
Isn't that great? [laughing]
SASAME: I know, I'll
go make us some tea.
-Perfect!
Good idea.
[crackling fire]
-Mmm!
You're right, Pervy Sage.
This is good!
SASAME: Here you go.
The tea is ready.
-Mmph.
Mmph.
-Here.
Here you go.
-Ah, thank you.
-Tea?
-Yeah.
Thanks a lot, Sasame.
But you need your
strength too, you know.
Come on and have
something to eat.
-I will.
[sipping]
-Ungh!
[clatter]
[thunk]
NARUTO: Pervy Sage!
Dah.
-Naruto!
What-- What's-- nehh.
[gasps]
[footsteps]
MALE SPEAKER: [laughing]
Sasame's signal.
So she did it.
MALE SPEAKER: And that
means the fools are ours.
-Nngh.
-You haven't recovered from
that beating you took, Kagero.
You wait here.
-No mistake, they're definitely
from the Leaf Village.
When he finds out we beat
a bunch of Leaf ninja,
Lord Orochimaru
will have to restore
the power of the Fuma Clan.
He'll have to.
-Yeah.
MALE SPEAKER: Come on, let's
bring him the good news.
MALE SPEAKER: Even better,
we'll bring him their heads
as souveniers.
[footsteps]
--[gasping] I must
be getting close.
Huh?
[breathing heavily]
-We thought it must be
spies from the Leaf Village.
Never thought we'd
find you, Sasame.
-Kamikiri!
Jigumo!
Kagero!
MALE SPEAKER: Strange
place for a reunion .
-Arashi!
Isn't he with you?
Where is he?
-Oh, well, uh, Arashi's
with Lord Orochimaru.
He's undergoing some
special training.
-Then take me to him.
I wanna see him.
-The only way to do that
is to join up with us
and serve Lord
Orochimaru as we do.
Then you're sure to see him.
[gasps]
-So, how did it go?
-Well, well!
Good job.
-I've done my part.
Now you'll take me
to Arashi, right?
[shing]
-You bet.
Just as soon as we put these
three to sleep for good.
-[gasping] What do you mean?
You said you only wanted to
capture them and take them
to Lord Orochimaru so
he could examine them!
-He will examine them.
But only from the neck up.
[shing]
-You can't!
No!
I won't let you do it.
They helped me--
-Shut up.
-What?
-Uh!
Impossible!
Our paralyzing
powder didn't work?
-Didn't work 'cause
we didn't drink it.
What do you think
we are, idiots?
OK, Sakura!
[thunking]
[poof]
-Substitution Jutsu.
-You'll keep an
eye on her, right?
-Just leave her to me.
Hang in there, Sasame.
You'll be OK.
-Nngh.
-I don't know what you
did to that poor kid
to make her do this, but
you're gonna pay for it!
-You're wrong.
We didn't make her do anything.
She did it herself.
She wanted to do it.
-Gimme a break!
-It's true, kid.
SASAME: All right, what do I
have to do to see Arashi again?
MALE SPEAKER: Oh, it's
nothing very difficult.
We just want you to put
those three spies to sleep,
that's all.
-And then kill them?
MALE SPEAKER: Don't worry.
We'll just take them to Lord
Orochimaru to be examined.
-They won't be hurt, right?
-If we manage to
pull this off, think
how grateful Lord
Orochimaru will be.
-Hanzaki says that all of you
are being used by Orochimaru,
that he'll throw you away
when he's through with you.
-Hanzaki is a traitor who
abandoned his own village!
We're friends of
your cousin Arashi.
Are you going to listen
to us or a traitor?
-Lord Orochimaru has
given us his word
that he'll restore our clan
to its former honor and power.
Sasame, you're young, but
you're as much a Fuma as we are.
Help us to make our
clan great once again.
-Nngh.
I don't care what you say!
It still sounds like
you tricked her!
-That's a small price to pay
for the sake of the clan!
[shing]
[kring]
-You punk!
Hngh!
[crash]
[kring]
-Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Here I come!
Hyah!
Mmph!
Nngh!
[popping]
-Uzumaki Barrage!
[crash]
-Uh oh, this doesn't look good.
-Heh.
Ptooh.
Rasengan!
[thud]
-Nngh.
-Don't think you're
getting off that easy!
After what you did to that kid--
-Naruto!
-Huh?
Nngh.
Ah, great.
Not him again!
Our old friend with
the earth-style jutsu.
But I doubt his ninja art
will prove as effective
in this hard, rocky terrain.
-It is time.
The ant-lion appears
from beneath the earth
and spreads its
wings in the sunlight
for only a brief moment.
And with it's birth, the
Kagero you know dies.
[gasps]
-Watch yourself, OK?
[cracking]
[slap]
-Huh?
What is this?
-Naruto, look!
-Huh?
-That's incredible!
-That guy is really a girl?
-Lord Orochimaru has promised
that our clan will spread
its wings in the sun once again.
But for that to happen,
I must sacrifice
all I must use the
ninja art I can
perform but once in a lifetime.
Kagero's Ninja Art, Ephemera!
[zapping]
-What the heck is that?
-Quick, Naruto!
Over here!
[blasting]
[rocks crumbling]
-Naruto!
[gasps]
[squishing]
-This is familiar.
I get the feeling
I've been here before.
-Yes, the Toad Mouth Trap Jutsu.
There are few things on Earth
stronger than a mountain toad's
stomach, so I summoned
it to protect us.
-Good move, but-- nngh!
Guh.
It melted away.
-Worse would have
happened to us if we'd
been struck by her chakra.
[poof]
[gasps]
-I believed him.
I thought it was for
the good of the clan.
I wanted to believe.
[zap]
-What-- what happened to her?
-She sacrificed herself.
Gave everything she had for
what she'd been led to believe
would be the
salvation of her clan.
-Orochimaru.
The Fuma are no
different than us!
They love their clan,
just like we do!
To play on people's
feelings like that,
to take their feelings
of love and pride
and twist them into a force
for evil-- how low can you get!
Get ready, Orochimaru!
Because I'm coming and I'm
going to take you down!
[gasping and groaning]
-Where-- where are we?
-Kagero, why--
Kagero, why did you
risk your life to
save the two of us?
Crazy fool.
Nngh.
[organ music]
-Please, my lord.
Our fallen comrade
doesn't have long to live.
Only you, with your
mastery of medical jutsu,
can possibly save her.
-I want you both
to bow your heads,
put your hands to your
hearts and contemplate.
Contemplate the many ways
in which you have failed me.
-But, my lord!
We've risked our
lives in your cause!
Every order you've
given us, we've obeyed!
You promised you would
restore the Fuma clan!
-You must acknowledge
our service to you!
-There is only one way
left for the two of you
to atone for your failures.
[gasping]
-Lord Orochimaru!
[shring]
-Forgive our betrayal!
[slashing]
-Aaugh!
[thudding]
[laughs diabolically]
[theme music]
NARUTO: So that's
Orochimaru's hide-out, huh?
JIRAIYA: It's just
like him to build
his lair in a hole
in the ground.
SAKURA: So Sasuke must
be somewhere in there!
What are we waiting for?
NARUTO: I'm with you, let's go!
SAKURA: Right!
JIRAIYA: Slow down!
We don't know what we might find
in there-- demons, serpents.
Take it easy.
NARUTO: Ha!
Bring 'em on!
What do I care
about a few snakes?
And there's no
demon alive that's
gonna keep me from
rescuing Sasuke and Arashi.
Next time, "Pure Terror,
The House of Orochimaru!"
[theme music]