[theme music]
-Well, for starters, you could
wake up the spiritualist medium
to release that jutsu.
-How am I supposed to do that?
CHIEF TOAD: Just fire
off a few rounds at him!
Then again, I'm not particularly
good at transformation.
-Huh?
-Don't worry about it.
You shall act upon my
will and make a handsign.
A combined transformation!
Conjure up something
with fangs and claws.
Here we go.
Transform!
NARUTO: Beyond the limit
of darkness and light.
-It can't be.
-Boy.
They're not messing around.
-It's not safe here anymore.
-This isn't going to work.
His power just keeps increasing.
-Come on.
He just needs to a
good smack to the head.
-Tell me something I don't know.
Here we go!
-Now take this!
[growl]
[scream]
-OK, kid.
You're on!
-Let's do it!
Rise and shine!
[groaning]
How's that?
-Good.
Not much time has passed
since the medium went under.
that one blow should
have done the trick
-Aw, That's just great!
Give me a break.
I just got here!
-The jutsu's already faded.
-We may have released the
jutsu, but this guy's still
got some fight left.
[grunt]
Haaa!
GAARA (VOICEOVER)He
disrupted my jutsu.
Sand Coffin!
-Help him, pops.
-I got him.
-The Chief's tongue
is surrounding me.
-You think I'm a fool?
[groaning]
-Damn.
How much strength does
this guy have left?
This ain't good.
Naruto and I have already
used up all of our chakra.
[groaning]
-I'll wipe you from
the face of the Earth.
I will not cease to exist.
[groaning]
-It doesn't make any sense.
I'm shocked that not just
the sound but so many
Sand jonin would
try to infiltrate.
-Well, think about it.
That's why they call it war.
-Something's wrong.
It's unheard of for two
shinobi to last this long.
-What the hell is
going on in there?
OROCHIMARU (VOICEOVER):
He still has my arms.
I can't use any jutsu.
Don't you think it's about
time you took a rest, old man?
-I won't let this village be
swallowed up by your ambition.
-Nothing can stop my ambition.
You are going to die here.
I don't care if you
are Third Hokage.
You are nothing but
a withered old fool.
Do you honestly believe
you have the strength
needed to stop me now?
Have you even the
slightest idea what's
befalling your precious
little village.
OROCHIMARU: Even as
we speak, the shinobi
of the Sand Village
as well as my own men
have made their presence known.
It won't be long before your
people are annihilated down
to every last woman and child.
The Hidden Leaf Village will
cease to exist! [laughter]
Sir, it's empty.
-The place is deserted.
-Something's not right.
-Huh?
-Why are we meeting with so
little resistance around here?
We're standing in the heart
of the Hidden Leaf Village.
-Sir, I--
-And another thing.
We've been here for a while now.
How come we haven't seen a
single woman or child yet?
-Ah?
[whimpering]
-Konohamaru?
-Are you OK?
Where are you going?
-I-- uh-- gotta
use the bathroom.
-Oh.
Yeah.
So do I.
-Yeah.
me too.
-Ah.
What the?
Konohamaru?
we are in the middle
of a crisis here.
Do you have any idea what's
at stake if they find us?
Now get back in that
room and you keep quiet.
-Yeah.
I know, but you
don't understand.
I've really gotta go.
-You'll just have to hold it.
-I don't know if I can
really do that, sensei.
-Boy.
You've got to be kidding.
All right.
Come along with me.
-I'm not going to make it!
[groaning]
-Aaah!
I guess that's all of them.
-For now anyway.
-Hayate, I will
avenge your death.
I promise.
-That's the signal.
Let's go.
-Right.
-For all your cunning,
you still don't get it,
do you, Orochimaru?
Do not to underestimate the
shinobi nobody of this village.
-Uh-- uh
-Are you all right?
Um-- yeah.
-So, is the evacuation complete?
-Yeah.
This here's the last of them.
-Huh?
What are you talking
about, sensei?
-If the village is
under attack, then there
are very specific guidelines
we have to follow.
-The very first step, wipe out
the enemy's advance forces.
And then if it becomes
clear that can't happen,
we immediately step
things up to Phase Two.
-The total evacuation of
every civilian to safety.
We'll move the
women and children
into shelters that
are strategically
hidden throughout the village.
Once that's been taken care
of, we continue to Phase Three.
-So what's Phase Three?
-The elimination of the
enemy by any means necessary.
-So then--
-As soon as we're ready, we
launch our counterattack.
-Huh?
-Not another step.
You are done here.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): No.
Sakura.
-You have to save Sakura, if
it's the last thing you do.
NARUTO: Sakura, I
swear I'll protect you.
-Believe me.
I will kill you.
I will not cease to exist.
-I'm running out of time.
I have to stop this monster
before it's too late.
Come on.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
I don't need much.
Just give me-- give
me some chakra!
[shouting]
-What are you all waiting for?
He's just one man.
-Whoa!
-The Leaf VIllage's
spirit is strong.
You'd do well to remember.
-My-- my body-- I can't move.
-Come on, fellas.
You've never heard of the
Shadow Paralysis jutsu?
Then you're going to
love this next one.
The Leaf Village's
Shadow Strangle jutsu.
[scream]
-Expansion jutsu!
[shouting and screaming]
-Mind Destruction jutsu.
-What are you doing?
Stop it.
Stop!
[scream]
-Hm.
-Reminds you of the good
old days, doesn't it?
-You bet it does.
-The Inoshikacho Trio is back.
-Let's go, Kuromaru.
-Right.
-Never mind the odds our
Leaf shinobi are up against.
They'll lay down their
lives for this village.
HOKAGE: How little
you understand.
Mastering every jutsu
will not give you
unsurpassable strength.
-The poison in my body is--
-Try not to move, Shino.
I've injected my parasites.
They're neutralizing the poison.
-Dad--
HOKAGE: It was one
of my first lessons.
It's not until you've protected
someone precious to you
that the true strength of
the shinobi can emerge.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I'm
going to protect everyone!
Get ready, you crazy monster!
-Die!
-I-- I've had it with you!
-Did-- did he win?
-A plain old headbutt, huh?
Well, he's not the most
elegant fighter I've ever seen,
but to dredge up the chakra
he needed, worn out as he was,
he might be the biggest
knucklehead I've ever
come across, but I
haven't seen a kid
with this much promise in ages.
Wish I could stick around
to see how this ends.
But I've reached my limit too.
Gamakichi, it's
time we went back.
-OK, pops.
Let's do it.
[grunting]
[panting]
-That's it.
I can't go any further.
I've used up all my chakra.
And from the look
of you, so have you.
You a and I a lot alike.
More than you know.
We shouldn't be doing this.
-All right, then.
You and I both know I
haven't the strength left
to rip all of your
soul from its shell.
You and I both know that.
And yet, your ambitions
end here and now!
-This isn't over!
There isn't any
stopping my ambition.
-Yours is an obsession.
This need to be drown
yourself in jutsu.
And for this transgression
you shall be punished!
I shall take away all the
jutsu you hold so dear!
-What did you say?
Impossible!
You wouldn't dare!
-The seal is set!
[groaning]
-My-- my arms--
-There you have it.
Your arms are
useless to you now.
And without those arms, you will
never form another handsign.
Ninjutsu is forever
out of your reach.
Your loathesome dream
of crushing this village
dies here!
-You feeble, old man!
Give me back my arms!
-Your foolishness is
unparalleled, Orochimaru.
My one regret is that I
couldn't take you with me.
Farewell, disciple.
May we meet again
in the next world.
-You decrepit old man.
How dare you!
How dare you take
my jutsu from me!
HOKAGE: Where the tree leaves
dance, one shall find flames.
[growling]
HOKAGE: The fire's shadow
will illuminate the village.
[grunting]
HOKAGE: And once again,
tree leaves shall bud anew.
[theme music]
IRUKA: Hokage, the
aspirations you once
held have been passed down
to another generation shinobi
here in the Hidden Leaf Village.
One day, the flames
of their hearts
will burn big and bright.
It won't be long before they
illuminate this village,
as you yourself have done.
NARUTO: Next time-- the
Third Hokage forever.