[theme music]
-Hey, look.
It's Lady Tsunade.
-Oh, hey you three.
-You all visiting somebody
at the hospital, too?
-Yes.
-And you, Lady Tsunade?
-Mmm.
Oh, well--
-She just doesn't want
to stay in the office.
-Ah, zip it!
-Hmm?
-Hey, Hinata!
Try not to faint when
you see Kurenai-sensei.
-Come on, don't bring
that up right now!
-Something happen I
should know about?
-When Naruto was
in the hospital--
-Shino, don't!
-She took one look at Naruto
all wrapped up in bandages
and keeled over.
-Kiba!
This-- this is different!
I'll be fine this
time! [gasping]
-I finally found you!
Grandma Tsunade, there's
something I want to say to you!
Oh, hey.
Hinata.
-Naruto!
-Hinata, Hinata, what's
the matter with you?
HINATA: He's only inches away!
-Huh?
Your face is looking
a little red there.
You OK?
You got a fever?
Let me feel your head.
[smack]
[squeals]
[gong]
[yells]
-Augh!
Hey, Hinata!
You got to be kidding!
Are you OK?
Get a hold of yourself, will ya?
-Ahh, Naruto!
I don't know what to say.
NARUTO: "The Search for
the Rare Bikochu Beetle!"
-Mmph.
-Arf, arf!
-Ahh!
-Hey, you finally woke up!
-So you're saying Mizuki
didn't know anything?
-Lady Tsunade even
interrogated him herself.
He didn't have any
information that
would lead to Orochimaru's
current whereabouts.
-So after all that trouble,
he was nothing more than one
of Orochimaru's pawns.
-So it would seem, yes.
-And we still don't
know where Sasuke is.
-Not a lot to show for the
knock-down, drag-out fight
with Mizuki.
-That's got to be
killing Naruto right now.
NARUTO (OUTSIDE): Grandma
Tsunade, this isn't fair!
You gotta let me!
TSUNADE (OUTSIDE): When
I say no, I mean it!
-You're right.
And thanks to him, Tsunade
can't focus on any of her work.
Naruto's been breathing
down our neck,
asking for permission to
go off in search of Sasuke.
She couldn't take it anymore and
snuck out of her office, but--
-Yeah, he was lying
here in wait for her.
HINATA: Naruto.
-Come on, already!
How many times are
you gonna make me ask?
Let me go out there
and look for Sasuke!
-Look, enough is enough!
Quit Pestering me.
It's not going to happen!
-Gimme one good reason!
-Oh, I don't know.
Don't you have some
training to do?
--[growling] The Pervy
Sage is gone, OK?
--[growling] We have zero leads
on either Orochimaru or Sasuke,
all right?
How do you think you're
going to find him?
-Look, I'll figure it out, OK?
If we're out of leads, I'll
just have to go dig some up.
I'm begging you to let me go.
-You're as stubborn as a mule!
NARUTO: Yeah?
Look who's talkin'!
Now can I go or not?
TSUNADE: Forget it!
NARUTO: When I put my
mind to something--
TSUNADE: Ah, shut up!
A thousand times no!
[smacking]
-Huangh!
Byakugan!
[shing]
MALE SPEAKER:
Excellent work, Neji.
Give it another
half-step on that one.
NEJI: Right! [breathing heavily]
HINATA: Sorry to
keep you waiting!
-Hmm.
[heavy breathing]
-Why don't we take a
little break, Neji?
-OK.
-Have something
to drink as well.
-Thank you.
I will.
-It's a shame Hinata
wasn't able to stay.
It would have been good
for her to observe you.
-Then Hinata prepared this?
-It would be a help to the girl.
Watching you would likely
improve her own training.
[labored breathing]
[shing]
-Byakugan!
[kring]
[sighs]
-Let's take a break.
-K.
-Great, time to eat!
KIBA: That was pretty well done!
I'd say you're getting closer
to perfecting the technique.
HINATA: I owe it
all to you guys.
It's so kind of you to help
me train like this every day.
-SHINO: We're a team.
When your comrade is in a
fix, you offer a helping hand.
It's only natural.
-Comrade, huh?
[sighing] I imagine if
one of your comrades
is gone all of a sudden,
it must be awfully hard.
KIBA: Naruto, huh?
-Mmhmm.
Isn't there some
way we can help him?
-Yeah, I know.
I'd like to help him
out some way, too.
But--
[dog whining]
-You guys both heard what Lady
Tsunade told him yesterday.
Sasuke's trail's gone cold.
SHINO: Well, there is
one thing we can try.
-Yeah?
Like what?
The bikochu beetle.
-The bikochu beetle?
You're referring to the rare
breed of insect, correct?
From what I'm told,
they die off ages ago.
SHINO: When it became clear that
they were close to extinction
The Aburame Clan immediately
stopped using them
so that the remaining
few might survive.
-Lady Tsunade, what are
these beetles, exactly?
-To be honest, it's
no big surprise
that you haven't heard of them.
The bikochu haven't
been put into use
since before the last
of the great wars.
They're a species of beetle
used by insect handlers.
Once their larvae are
hatched, they quickly
move into the chrysalis phase
and emerge as full grown Imago.
They're then familiarized
with a specific scent
so that they can later track it.
No matter how faint
that scent has become,
their olfactory perception
is several times greater than
a ninja hound's.
Their usefulness in
espionage is hard to dismiss.
However, the bikochu only lay
eggs once every several years.
-It just so happens
that this is that year.
And this is the season
when they hatch.
-Well, whaddya know.
-And I'm betting Sasuke left
most of this stuff behind,
didn't he?
-If we expose one of these
beetles to his scent--
-Then it'll hopefully
lead us straight
to Sasuke's current location.
-Mmm.
-What's the probability
of finding one now?
-Frankly speaking,
not very high.
Maybe around 10%.
-A whopping 10%, huh?
[footsteps]
--[sighing] As you all know,
the situation in the village is
fairly grave at the moment.
I don't have the luxury of
letting my genin lounge around
and play.
However, fortunately or
unfortunately, Kurenai
has been hospitalized,
which leaves
Squad Eight without a mission.
[gasps]
-But what'll sitting
around get us?
I'd rather put my money
down on that 10% chance.
-Huh?
You mean--
-Shino Aburame, Kiba Inuzuka,
and Hinata Hyuga, your orders
are to go seek out to a bikochu.
EVERYONE: Got it!
-I'm designating
Shino as leader.
And as for you, you
lousy little sneak!
[thunk]
[crash]
-Ow!
HINATA: Naruto!
-You'll go no matter
what I do, right?
-You got it!
--[sighing] I guess there's
no point trying to stand
in your way.
All right, this is your
last chance, you got me?
If you don't come back here
with that beetle in tow,
you're to give up on
Sasuke once and for all.
Are we clear?
-Not a problem!
I'll find you that
but without fail!
-Good!
I'm holding you to that, OK?
-Yah!
No sweat, lady!
I got this one in the bag!
-Cool it, hot shot.
[smack]
HINATA: Naruto.
[rustling]
-Where are you?
[door sliding open]
-Hinata.
HINATA: Good morning.
-Neji will be here
soon for his training.
Have the tea ready
as usual, please.
-Oh, well--
-Hmm?
What's the matter?
-Actually, I have a mission.
-A mission, huh?
Well, that's all
there is to it, then.
-I'm heading out now.
-Try not to be a burden
to those around you
if you're able to help it.
-[gasping] I will.
[footsteps]
[gasping]
-Um, sorry about that!
I'm in a bit of a hurry.
-Her response was so quick!
Hinata.
NARUTO: Hinata!
What too you so long?
HINATA: I'm sorry!
-All right, then.
I'd say it's time we got movin'.
Let's go!
[vroom]
-Heh?
What's wrong with you guys?
What're you dragging
your heels for?
SHINO: It'll take
a shinobi two days
to reach the beetles'
habitat by foot.
No need to rush right
out of the gate.
[galloping horses]
[screeching halt]
-We don't have time to waste!
What happens if the eggs
hatch before we get there?
SHINO: The eggs of the
bikochu beetle only hatch
on a day after it's rained.
I don't see any clouds
in the sky, do you?
-Well, yeah, OK, but what
if this one time they--
SHINO: Naruto!
-What's the matter?
SHINO: I am the
leader of this team.
While we're on this mission,
you will follow my orders.
--[growling] Kiba, how the heck
you put up with this weirdo is
beyond me.
-Yeah, you get used to it.
-I'm sure that things will
great once you get to know him.
-[chuckling] That'll be the day.
SAKURA: Hup!
TSUNADE: Naruto and others
set out a little while ago.
SAKURA: I see.
TSUNADE: You didn't
want to go with them?
SAKURA (TO HERSELF): With
them searching for insects,
the couldn't do
better than Shino.
Hinata's got her Byakugan
and Kiba and Akamaru
have their noses.
I'm not really sure
what I could add.
All I need to focus on now
is become a medical ninja
as fast as I possibly can!
-Shino, what's the matter?
SHINO: Sun's going down.
We'll camp here.
-K.
-You got it.
-Huh?
What?
Why are we setting
up camp already?
This is crazy!
I'm not even close
to being tired yet.
Come on!
Let's cover more ground!
SHINO: Naruto!
I am the leader of this team.
-Eek.
Right!
You're the boss.
I hear ya.
SHINO: OK, let's turn in.
-Huh?
We're going to bed already?
SHINO: Many animals
and plants rise
with the sun and
slumber when it sets.
If we're searching
for insects, we
must understand the
rhythm of living creatures
with our own bodies.
NARUTO: Yeah, but the sun
just set a few minutes ago!
SHINO: Naruto!
I am leading this team!
NARUTO: OK!
I get it, already.
Blargh.
This is stupid!
There's no way I can fall asleep
so early. [yawning] [snoring]
-Big shocker, huh.
Shoots his mouth off
about not being tired
and he's the first one out!
Typical.
[crickets chirping]
[water rushing]
-I gotta whiz.
[whizzing]
-[sighing in relief] Huh?
Huh.
What's that?
[water rushing]
[footsteps]
NARUTO: A waterfall!
Huh?
Is somebody over there?
[splashing]
[tinkling]
-Uh, hey, uh--
[splash]
-[inaudible] Sorry about that.
I didn't scare you, did I?
Huh?
What the-- Where'd they go?
NARUTO: Achoo!
Ugh.
-What's wrong, Naruto?
Did you catch a cold?
-Yeah, I guess so.
[yawning]
SHINO: Still tired
after all that sleep?
NARUTO: Well, the
thing, is I went out
to take a whiz last night
and saw something amazing.
HINATA: Achoo!
-You catching a cold, too?
-Oh, no.
I'm OK.
-So, uh, what was so amazing?
-A waterfall!
With a beautiful woman
standing in the middle of it!
-Get out!
-And every time
she moved her arms,
the water moved along with them.
I tell ya, it was awesome.
-What'd you do?
-Well, I tried to speak to
her, but she disappeared!
-I don't know, Naruto.
You sure you weren't
dreaming or something?
-Aaugh.
I'm not sure what it was.
KIBA: Yeah, I knew it.
NARUTO: Hey, Hinata.
Your face is all red.
You must be coming
down with something.
HINATA: Uh, I'm fine, really.
SHINO: These are edible.
This will be our meal for today.
-OK, sounds good.
-This'll help our food
supply last longer.
[barks]
SHINO: A word of caution--
on rare occasions, this fruit
can grow to the size
of a human being.
Those ones aren't safe to eat.
Avoid them at all costs.
KIBA: Come on,
nobody'd be dumb enough
to eat something that big.
NARUTO: Om nom nom.
HINATA: Naruto!
NARUTO: Huh?
KIBA: He's eating it.
NARUTO: Hmm?
[stomach rumbling] Aaugh!
Ugh!
KIBA: Naruto!
We're going on ahead.
NARUTO: [moaning] I'm--
I'm right behind ya.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
[stomach rumbling]
[gasps]
NARUTO: Oh, uh, just a second.
I'll be right there.
[crickets chirping]
[labored breathing]
[footsteps]
NARUTO: Hey, how we doin'?
We almost there yet?
SHINO: Yes.
This is it.
-Hmm?
Wha!
Oh, wow!
I've never seen anything
like this before.
KIBA: Doesn't look very
hospitable for people
around here.
SHINO: You're right.
That's why it's a
paradise for insects.
[gong]
-No way.
You don't mean--
HINATA: So you
think, down there--
KIBA: That's where
our creepy crawler is?
SHINO: Yep.
This will be easier
than the chunin exam.
[gasping]
-Ack!
Aw man.
This cliff's falling apart.
Can't get a grip!
SHINO: Naruto!
-Eh?
Huh?
SHINO: As your leader,
I'm warning you--
-At a time like
this, what is it?
SHINO: Don't fall.
-Thanks for the words
of wisdom, genius!
I don't need you
to tell me that!
Eh?
-Naruto!
[insects rushing]
-Nngh!
Aw, man!
[thunk]
-[gasping] That was close.
Huh?
Oh, those were insects.
SHINO: I warned you, didn't I?
[ding ding]
-Dahh!
When this is all over, I'm
going to kick that guy's butt
all over the village!
SHINO: This is it.
The forest of the bikochu.
Let's go.
EVERYONE: Mmm.
[footsteps]
MALE SPEAKER:
There's no mistake.
Those are Leaf shinobi.
MALE SPEAKER: They're not
passing through, though.
There's only one reason
why they would come here.
FEMALE SPEAKER: Yeah, the
same reason we are here.
The bikochu.
MALE SPEAKER: They're
not taking a single one.
FEMALE SPEAKER: Because
all of the bikochu
belong to the Kamizuru Clan.
[theme music]
NARUTO: What!
You mean it's the
one in this photo?
I know that bug!
-Really?
NARUTO: Aw, man.
Don't tell me it was a bikochu!
KIBA: Wait, are you serious?
Where did you see it?
NARUTO: I heard it scuttling
in the kitchen one night
and wailed a slipper at it.
SHINO: Wait a second.
HINATA: Naruto--
SHINO: I think you're
actually talking
about the common cockroach.
NARUTO: Next time,
"What's the Difference?
Don't All Insects Look Alike?"
[theme music]