[theme music]
[baby crying]
WOMAN: (SINGING) Natsuhiboshi,
why are you so red?
Because I had a sad
dream last night.
My eyes are red from the tears
I shed, swollen as I cry.
-There you are!
-Neji!
Naruto!
-What happened to them?
-Our shinobi friend
struck again.
-What?
He came back?
NARUTO: Yep.
And this time they took Sumaru.
-They got him?
-Yeah.
-Regardless, our first
order of business
is to make sure these
people here are all right.
Help us carry them back.
-Right.
Will do.
-Yes, of course.
-Mizura.
Naruto!
-They were jumped by
that ninja in the mask.
-No one's badly hurt.
They're merely unconscious.
-Where-- where's everybody else?
-Tenten and Lee have got 'em.
They're bringing them back now.
-I see.
So Sumaru's with them?
-Uh-- uh--
-He was taken away by
the masked shinobi.
-That's right.
He took him off into
the Valley of Death.
We couldn't go after him.
-The Valley of Death?
-Did he inhale much of
the gas in the valley?
-Don't worry.
I've put him in a state
of suspended animation.
The gas didn't effect him.
-I can understand wanting to
use him to bait your trap,
but all the same--
-These are children
from our own village.
-I always suspected
you'd lose your nerve.
Well, it's too late.
Your hands are far too
dirty to play the saint now.
So enough of that.
For now we'll let them think
the other masked shinobi took
Sumaru.
Once we have the
star back, well,
we'll leave it to them
to sort it all out.
-Hm?
-Oh, Mizura wasn't
feeling too well.
He's taking a break
from training.
-Byakugan.
What?
-Mizura!
-How are you feeling?
-Lie down.
You need to rest.
-No one can afford to
rest at a time like this.
-I know it can't
be easy, but you
must try not to push yourself.
-I'm fine.
I can walk by myself.
-Huh?
-You see?
I told you you have to rest.
-I'm all right.
Let me be!
-Mother!
No!
Mother!
Father!
-No, Sumaru.
Don't cry.
Your parents died defending
the star and our village
to the very best
of their abilities.
Look up, Sumaru.
Look up at the sky.
There is a treasure
that can be seen only
from the Village
Hidden in the Stars.
If you would claim your
shinobi birthright,
then the village and the
star are yours to defend.
Be strong, just as
your parents were.
Make them proud of you, eh?
-Lord Hoshikage.
-Hmph.
There.
Yeah, that ought to do the job.
-Naruto.
-Yeah, what's up?
-At this rate,
Mizura won't make it.
I sensed a disturbance in his
chakra, so I looked into it.
Even as he rests,
his chakra is working
at an alarming,
unsustainable rate.
It's too much for
his body to take.
His systems will soon fail.
-Are you serious?
His own chakra's
going to kill him?
-Without a doubt.
-But how?
-It's because of
the star training.
-Huh?
-The star has a unique power of
triggering a surge in chakra.
The problem is most ninja
are incapable of controlling
this surge.
Their bodies give out,
and they collapse.
Or worse.
This is what happened to Mizura
in the middle of his training.
The Third Hoshikage
stopped the star training,
because it was proving far
too dangerous for our people.
NEJI: But you're doing it again.
-That's because of Lord
Akahoshi, our current leader.
He decided to resume the
star training six months ago.
-But that's crazy!
Somebody's gotta make him stop!
-We were born and raised here.
We don't fear the star training.
We undergo it proudly.
-But why?
-We've been raised to
believe there is no greater
honor than to serve the village
as a Hidden Star shinobi.
For that, we'd
sacrifice anything.
Even our own lives.
-Unbelievable.
-Go on.
Let's see if that gets
your attention, Natsuhi.
-Hotarubi, protect the star.
Protect Sumaru.
Akahoshi's chakra.
-Go ahead and take it.
It'll help you
get around easier.
I mean, just until
you get better.
MIZURA (VOICEOVER):
Thank you, Naruto.
But I never will.
-They say his condition's
stabilized, at least.
-Then for the moment, I
guess, everyone is all right.
-Something's not right.
Not by a longshot.
Hokuto and Mizura,
the way they're always
thinking about the village.
And Sumaru, too.
Same thing.
The village, the village.
-What are you saying?
-I mean, I know
how they feel when
it comes to defending your
village and your friends.
I'd do the same thing.
I'd be willing to
risk everything.
Even my life.
-Of course.
We all would.
-Right.
-Well, this isn't the time
to try and figure it out.
Right now, we've
gotta catch that thief
and get the star back.
-Yeah, but, if they
didn't get it back,
at least they wouldn't have to
suffer through that training.
-Tenten has a point.
-Yeah.
Without the star,
they can't train,
which means they put
the village at risk.
If they do train, they
put their lives at r-- Ah!
I give up!
It's to confusing.
I don't know what to do!
-We fulfill our mission,
which is to protect the star.
And that means that we
have to get it back.
What these people choose
to do with it after that
is none of our affair.
-Yes.
You are right.
-OK.
-All right.
Let's do it.
-Lee and Tenten, I want you to
investigate the village leader
one more time.
-What?
Again?
-I want to know why that
flying shinobi would
risk his life going into
the valley of death.
And if he already at the
star, why kidnap Sumaru?
-Good question.
Why would he?
-The shinobi who
grabbed the star
had a very different chakra
from the one who took Sumaru.
-What?
-So you mean--
-Yes.
They're two different shinobi.
-But what does that mean?
-That this mission is more
complicated than we thought.
-As I expected.
Very impressive ninja
art Kujaku, Lady Natsuhi.
-Where is he?
What have you done with Sumaru?
-First thing's first.
I'll take the star,
if you don't mind.
-Not until I get Sumaru.
-First the star.
-No.
-Very well.
Then I'll just have
to take it from you.
[snickering]
-What's so amusing?
-That you actually believe
you're a match for me.
-I don't think you realize that
after you left the village,
there were a select
few of us who
secretly continued our training.
-Ha.
You think you finished the
star training all on your own?
-You're about to learn that I'm
more than a match for you now,
Lady Natsuhi.
Ninja Art Kujaku!
Beast!
-The fool.
He leaves me no choice.
Ninja Art Kujaku!
Beast!
-Her power is great.
Yasaka!
Shizo!
Go on.
-My lord.
-What are you up to, Akahoshi?
-You'll just have to stay
to find that, m'lady.
-Neji.
What is it?
-I just detected a
massive flow of chakra.
-The shinobi?
-It has to be.
Who's there?
-Friends from the Leaf.
The shinobi who stole the
star has just now reappeared.
-Lord Akahoshi is
trying to delay him.
-Please, you must come and help.
-You got it.
We're on our way!
-The shinobi is powerful, and
Lord Akahoshi is all alone.
-He won't be able
to hold him long.
NARUTO: Just show us the way,
and leave the rest to us.
-There is no one here.
-Huh.
TENTEN: Their presence
is very faint.
They must have gone
out a while ago.
-It seems an ideal
opportunity to poke around.
-Right.
-Ninja Art, Phantom Jutsu.
-Huh?
Lee?
Since when do you know ninjutsu?
-All clear!
Come on in, Tenten!
There is no one here!
-What the-- That's not ninjutsu!
It's very--
-Suspicious.
[door sliding]
-Hm.
LEE (VOICEOVER): Oh, no.
TENTEN (VOICEOVER): Oh, boy.
-Funny.
Thought I heard something.
-It's been set up
like a hospital room.
I can see there's
somebody in the bed.
-But who is it?
TENTEN: Wait, is that--
-It is Sumaru!
-Why did you force
Sumaru and the others
to resume the star training?
The Third Hoshikage must've
warned you how dangerous it is.
Why would you do it?
-You yourself are
the answer to that!
-What?
-Look your chakra.
It's incredible!
Imagine an army of
100, or even 10 ninja
with powers like yours.
The five great hidden
villages combined
would be no match for us!
It's not too late, Natsuhi.
Together you and I can make the
Hidden Star village invincible.
-Ah!
It hurts.
It hurts!
-Why does my body feel
like it's on fire?
-Make it stop.
Make it stop!
-Help me!
-Enough.
-Please!
-Enough!
All those young
lives thrown away.
-Their horror must
never be repeated.
If you think I'll let
you start that again!
-Wait, Natsuhi!
Remember, I still have Sumaru!
[gasp]
You're helpless, aren't you?
As long as I have your
precious little Sumaru,
you can't do a thing!
-The shinobi's closing
in on Akahoshi.
-Yeah?
Well I'm about to
close in on him!
-Hold on.
He's too strong for
a frontal attack.
-Don't sweat it!
I've got a plan!
-You do?
-I'll neutralize his chakra.
You guys take care
of the rest, OK?
-Well, we need to move quickly.
No time to argue.
Very well, but be
careful, Naruto.
-Don't worry, I will!
OK!
Multi-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
All right shinobi!
Let's take him down!
-So, him again.
NEJI (VOICEOVER):
I thought as much.
That chakra is too
powerful to get through.
-Huh?
Where's the real one?
NEJI (VOICEOVER): I see.
It wasn't a crude frontal
assault after all.
Those clones were
merely a distraction.
Not bad, Naruto.
-He did it.
Incredible.
-Huh?
A woman?
AKAHOSHI (VOICEOVER): Heh.
The Leaf brat actually did it.
Plenty of time to
find the star later.
Now it's my chance to finish
Natsuhi once and for all!
I can see she'll be of
no help in fulfilling
my ambitions for our village.
-Ninja Art, Kujaku!
Beast!
-Naruto!
Look out!
-What the-- Ah!
-Naruto!
[scream]
-Huh?
-What is it, Mizura?
Something wrong?
-Uh-- no, it's nothing.
MIZURA (VOICEOVER): Naruto.
-Mother.
[scream]
[theme music]
-Ah!
I have just had an
extraordinary revelation!
-Care to share it with us?
LEE: I have had my
doubts about this Lord
Akahoshi and his
suspicious behavior.
And now I have finally
just realized--
TENTEN: What?
LEE: I believe that one of the
masked shinobi is Akahoshi!
TENTEN: Neji already
said that, remember?
LEE: Then you agree
with me, Neji.
You are really sharp.
[sigh]
NEJI: Can we move on, now?
TENTEN: Next time,
Hoshikage, The Buried Truth.
[theme music]