[theme music]
-[screams]
Huh?
[music playing]
-Wh-- with him-- Why?
Damn it.
SASUKE: That the
best you can do?
Thought you were stronger.
Well, if that's all you've
got, I guess I won't need it.
-What?
-Oh, come on.
You haven't realized yet?
I'm not using my Sharingan.
-Don't mock me.
-You don't have what it takes,
not the strength or the desire.
-You're still too weak.
You don't have enough hate.
And you know something?
You never will.
-If I'd just keep palling
around with you guys,
I would never have been able
to gain this much power.
[music playing]
-So, now I know what
is needed of me.
Only through hatred,
and power, can
I hope to surpass my brother.
[birds chirping]
-Itachi, I can walk.
-Don't push yourself.
-OK.
Oh--
-What's up?
SASUKE: That building is
where father works, isn't it?
-Mhm.
It's headquarters for
the Leaf Police Force.
-I was wondering, how come
the crest of the Uchiha clan
is part of the Leaf
Police Force insignia?
-Well, what do you know,
You finally noticed.
-Course I did.
-Right.
Let me see if I can
explain it for you.
It was the Uchiha clan's
earliest ancestors
who established the police
here in the village.
So, when they created the
symbol for the organization,
they used the family crest.
Since a long time
ago, the Uchiha
have always ensured
the peace here.
The crest is a testament
of our clan's pride
and a way of life centuries old.
Over the years, the Uchiha
clan has grown smaller.
But even now, nearly all of
us are a part of the force
and work to uphold the
peace in this village.
Which is good because only the
most exceptional of shinobi
can weed out the criminals
hiding among their brethren.
-Wow, Dad is the coolest.
Are you going to
join the force too?
-Well, I'm not sure.
-Why not?
Oi, when I grow
up, I'm definitely
going to enter the police force.
And Father's coming to
tomorrow's entrance ceremony.
It's the first step to my dream.
-That's right.
[music playing]
-You're late, Itachi.
What have you been doing?
-Father--
-I need to talk to you.
Let's go.
[laugh]
-That's my boy.
For you to have come
this far just six months
after making chunin-- about
tomorrow's special mission.
I've decided to
go along with you.
-Tomorrow?
-If you complete
tomorrow's mission,
Itachi, your entrance into ANBU
Black Ops is all but assured.
Do you understand?
-You don't have to worry
about me out there.
And more importantly--
-Father, you see,
tomorrow afternoon is--
-This mission tomorrow,
it's not just about you.
Your performance will
reflect on our entire clan.
-Actually, I'm going to
pass on tomorrow's mission.
-What are you talking about?
That's insanity.
You know how important this is.
You'll do no such thing
-I have to.
Tomorrow is Sasuke's
entrance ceremony.
Our family has to attend.
Its customary at the Academy.
You received a notice, remember?
-All right, I get it.
I'll be at the Academy tomorrow.
[birds chirping]
-Your left leg,
be sure to ice it.
-OK, Big Brother.
He's so distant.
[music playing]
-My congratulations
to all of you.
You have a lot of
hard work ahead of you
as you walk the
path of the shinobi.
But I expect great things.
I know you will do the
Leaf Village proud.
-Oi, it seems like
only yesterday
that you were here
for Itachi, huh?
And you're his spitting image.
-Uh.
-Thank you for your help
with both of my boys.
-Oh, not at all.
It's been a pleasure.
That boy of yours
is a true prodigy.
There hasn't been
another one like him
in the history of the Academy.
-Please, you're being too kind.
-Nonsense.
We expect big things from
you, as well, Sasuke.
-Become a fine shinobi, just
like your older brother.
-Yes, Father.
[music playing]
-Hey, that's Uchiha, right?
-Wo-- wow, I wonder
if he's a genius too.
-Yeah, he has to be.
-Huh?
-Oh man, I thought recess
was never going to get here.
These classes are such a drag.
-Shikamaru, you want some?
-Seriously, not every single
break has to be a snack break.
You know what I mean?
[music playing]
[dog barking]
[laugh]
FUGAKU: That's my boy.
You'll go far in the ANBU
ranks, no question about it.
[dogs barking]
-It's still not good enough.
I have to do better.
I've got a long way to go.
-Sasuke, this is
your day off, dear.
You need to give
your body some rest.
-Ow.
-You don't have to
push yourself so hard.
-I know, but they say
Big Brother graduated
from the Academy in just a year.
-Times have changed, sweetheart,
and your brother is special.
[laugh]
FUGAKU: That's my boy.
[birds chirping]
-All right, these
are your report cards
for the first term.
[crowd groans]
-Keep excelling like
this, and you'll
be just like your
brother in no time.
-Oh, hm.
[birds chirping]
-Father, I wanted you to
say, that's my boy, to me.
FUGAKU: -Come again,
what do you mean
you can't participate
in the assembly?
I don't really think you
understand your position.
-I'm setting out on
a mission tomorrow.
-It's the middle of the night.
Why are they up
with the lights off?
-What are you talking about?
-I can't tell you.
The mission is covert.
-Hm.
Itachi, you also serve as
the Uchiha clan's pipeline
to the Village Nerve Center.
You know that, don't you?
-Yes.
-Well, make sure
you don't forget it.
You will be at that
meeting tomorrow.
-Sasuke--
-Uh, ah.
-Use the bathroom
and go to sleep.
-OK.
-What are you doing roaming
the house at this hour?
Get to bed.
-Yes, sir.
[crickets]
[crow squawk]
-Father only cares
about you, Itachi.
-You probably hate me, huh?
It's all right.
people often think
ill of shinobi.
It's only logical.
-That's not how I feel.
He's right, though.
I do.
I do feel that way.
-Huh, being the best isn't
all it's cracked up to be.
When you have power, you
become arrogant and isolated
from the world, no matter
how coveted and sought
after you are in the beginning.
But with us, it's
different because you and I
are flesh and blood.
I'm always going to be
there for you, even if it's
only as an obstacle
for you to overcome.
Even if you do hate me, that's
what big brothers are for.
-Is Itachi in there?
We need to talk.
Get out here.
-What's going on?
What are you all doing here?
-There were two people
who didn't show up
at yesterday's assembly.
Do you want to tell me
why you weren't there?
-The meeting Father was
talking about last night,
he didn't go after all.
-You're in the
ANBU Black Ops now.
I know, full well,
you can be called away
at the drop of a hat.
And that's the case
your father was
trying to make when we
asked why you weren't there.
-But we're not your father.
You will be getting any
special treatment from us.
-I understand.
I should have been more careful.
Will that be all
then, gentleman?
-Sure thing.
But you know what?
Before we go, there's
just one other thing.
-Mhm.
-Do you know anything about
Shisui Uchiha ending his life
in Naka no River?
-Ending his life?
-Shisui was the other guy who
never turned up at the assembly
yesterday.
It's funny.
If I remember correctly,
you kind of looked up to him
like an older
brother, didn't you?
-How terrible.
Forgive me, I haven't
seen him at all recently.
What a tragedy.
-Yeah.
Well.
At this point.
The police force
sees no other choice
but to launch an all-out
investigation into the matter.
-Investigation?
-This is a note
Shisui left behind.
We've already had it analyzed.
There's no question,
this is his handwriting.
-But if it wasn't homicide,
why the investigation?
-It'd be no great
feat for someone
who possesses Sharingan
to copy his handwriting.
-The most talented
of all our clan,
feared as Shisui
the teleporter--
he was a man who
would do anything,
take any mission, if it was
for the good of the clan.
-Hard to imagine a man
like that ending his life,
don't you think?
-You shouldn't judge
people by their appearance
or by your own preconceptions.
-We'll leave that with
you for the time being.
Take it to ANBU Black Ops
and put in a request for them
to start sniffing
around on this, as well.
-Understood.
-Let's just hope we get
a lead on this soon.
By the way, we have our
own connections inside
of ANBU Black Ops.
You try and sweep this
investigation under the rug,
and we're going
to know about it.
-Why don't you just
come out and say it?
You believe I had a
hand in this, don't you?
-Yeah, that's
right, little punk.
-Listen, Itachi.
If I find you
betrayed this clan,
I want you to know you'll
pay for your wrongs.
[punches]
[groans]
-Like I said before,
appearances and preconceptions
aren't going to
tell you anything.
For instance, you've
made the mistake
of assuming I'm a patient man.
The clan, the clan-- you
overestimate your own abilities
with no idea of the
depth of my own.
And look at you now,
groveling in the dirt.
-I've never seen him
like this before.
-Shisui, Shisui, I've been
keeping an eye on you recently.
The strangeness of your
behavior-- half a year
into your time at ANBU, it
was impossible to overlook.
What the heck are you playing
at, you filthy little wretch?
-Obsessed with the organization,
obsessed with the clan,
obsessed with our lineage--
a worthless compulsion
that enslaves us and
limits our capabilities,
leading us to fear what
you don't understand.
-Stop it, Itachi.
What on earth is
the matter with you?
Itachi, you've been
strange lately.
-Nothing strange about me.
I have my own duties
to fulfill, that's all.
-So what's your story?
Why didn't you come last night?
-To achieve the next state.
-What are you talking about?
-Oh.
-I've had enough.
There's no hope left
for this pathetic clan.
Since a very long
time ago, the Uchiha
have always ensured
the peace here.
The crest is a testament
of our clan's pride
and a way of life centuries old.
-That's my boy, you'll go far
in the ANBU ranks, no question
about it.
-The people of this
clan are all the same.
You focus on the
trivial and lose sight
of what's most important.
Change is impossible in
this fog of ignorance.
How can we evolve when
regulation is all we know?
-Such arrogance.
That's enough.
If I hear one more
word of this nonsense,
I'll have you
thrown behind bars.
-Hm, being the best isn't
all it's cracked up to be.
When you have power, you
become arrogant and isolated
from the world, no matter
how coveted and sought
after you are in the beginning.
-Brother, why?
-Well, what's it gonna be?
I cant take this anymore.
Please sir, just
give me the order.
-Big Brother, you have to stop.
-Huh?
-I'm not the one
who killed Shisui,
but I apologize for the
words I have spoken.
I am truly sorry.
-Hm, he's been pretty tired
lately, up to his ears
in missions from
the ANBU Black Ops.
-But, Captain--
-ANBU are under the direct
control of the Hokage.
Even if you wanted to
arrest one of them,
we would need to
get a warrant first.
As for Itachi, I take full
responsibility for him.
You've my word.
[sigh]
-Very well, sir.
-I hope that woke you up.
Now you know I'm
not messing around.
-Ha.
-We had a bit of an
interruption that day.
But that won't happen this time.
-Ah.
-Let me show you the true
power of the Sharingan.
[theme music]
-What's wrong, Naruto?
What are you holding back for?
Or is this the full
extent of your power?
So you went on and on about
you Nindo, your ninja way.
And this is the best
you can do, huh?
Ha.
Give me a break.
In this state, you're
not even worth defeating.
NARRATOR: Next time, Father
and Son, the Broken Crest.
[theme music]