[theme music]
-Huh?
What's this?
A wanted flyer?
This fugitive who
calls himself Tokichi,
is a murderer known to have
killed a family of three.
He has a bird-shaped
birthmark on his chest.
-A bird-shaped birthmark?
It couldn't be.
-Hinata?
What is it?
-His face is covered with
scars, so I can't tell,
but he has a birthmark
shaped like a bird.
-So, there's a bounty
on the bounty hunter.
-Man, could this
mission get any weirder?
What's going on?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Hunt or be Hunted!
Showdown at OK Temple!
NARUTO: Where do you think
you're going old man?
Just take it easy
and go back to sleep.
-Let me go.
Don't try to stop me.
Gosunkugi will be mine.
-And how do you plan on
doing that in your weakened
condition?
You're not in any
shape to fight.
[bark]
-Late last night,
we were attacked
by another bounty hunter.
Care to explain why
one bounty hunter is
trying to nab another
bounty hunter?
-This is my business, not yours.
-Your injury again.
-Get back!
-Stay still. don't move.
-I never committed any crime.
-OK, then.
How do you figure this wanted
flyer with your picture on it?
-Gosunkugi was the
one who did it.
He killed a totally
innocent family of three,
and he did it just
to steal some money.
-Wh-- What are
you talking about?
What happened?
SAZANAMI: Long ago I lived
in a tiny village, sandwiched
between two great nations.
I was a swordsmith.
I was poor, but for me, it
was a very pleasant life.
Until the day of the festival.
I was walking along,
on my way to deliver
a sword that had been ordered.
And I was hurrying, so I
could get to the festival.
When suddenly--
[scream]
SAZANAMI: For some reason,
the door was already open.
It's-- it's Tokichi.
I'm delivering a sword.
[crash]
[screaming]
SAZANAMI: I told everyone
what had happened.
But no matter what I said, the
villagers wouldn't believe me.
They said I was
the only person who
hadn't shown up at the festival.
And the wounds
found at the scene
were from a very unique blade.
A blacksmith can make
any kind of weapon--
so they thought it was me.
-Stand up, Tokichi.
-Hey!
-Tokichi!
-Quick!
After him!
SAZANAMI: On that day,
I became a fugitive,
wandering aimlessly
from town to town.
My own village had sent
out warnings about me.
Mine was among other
wanted posters.
There was even one for the
man who killed that family.
I made a vow to capture
Gosunkugi with my own two hands.
Once I clear my name, I
will return to my village.
I needed information
about the killer.
Anything.
So despite the bounty on my own
head, I became a bounty hunter.
-And that's what
you meant when you
said we were
standing in your way.
-The only way I can
prove my innocence
is to capture the
real culprit myself.
Then I can finally
return to my home.
Please, step aside
and leave him to me.
-Hey, you're talking
to a ninja here, buddy.
When we get a mission, we
see it all the way through.
Even if the worst
were to happen,
we won't let him get away.
Let's go.
-Are you sure that was
such a good idea, Naruto?
-Gosunkugi is an animal.
We gotta take out that guy
no matter what the risk.
-Yes.
Naruto's right.
-Besides, we can't just let
a guy in Sazanami's condition
track him down on his own.
Not only would he
fail, he might end
up getting killed by
Gosunkugi himself.
-I won't fight back.
You can have it.
The bounty on my head.
-You're wounded.
I could take you so easily.
But before I do,
I want Gosunkugi.
Well, I guess I'll
let those kids take
care of the hard part for me.
HINATA: The Land of
Stone, post station two.
Everything in this town,
politics, economy, military,
it's all administered by monks.
-Aw, man.
This whole place is
nothing but temples!
HINATA: The head temple, the
big one on that mountain,
it's called the OK Temple.
NARUTO: Hey, Hinata,
what's that bell?
HINATA: That was created
as a tourist attraction
to get people to
visit the temple.
It's the Golden Bell.
-That's dumb.
Look at that thing.
It's practically
screaming come steal me.
-Wait a second.
I bet Gosunkugi is
after that bell.
I know Gosunkugi's
gonna steal that bell,
but I wonder how he's
gonna pull it off.
[whining]
[sniffing]
-Naruto.
-Hm?
-You-- You're Gosunkugi's men!
-They're trying to box us in.
Surround us.
-Just like they did
against Sazanami.
Byakugan!
There's more of them.
Watch out!
-What?
Sazanami?
-I can handle these guys.
-All right!
Let's go!
Eat this!
So, what are you
doing here anyway?
-I just came to
settle the score.
-Yes, but your wound is still--
-Don't worry.
I won't be in your way.
I just want to get him first.
Think of it like a competition.
-Heh.
Sounds fun.
I accept your challenge.
-We can't even start your little
race surrounded like this.
-I still sense
nails underground.
He's waiting for the
right moment to strike.
-I will have him.
-The bell.
It reached the top.
-Darn it.
Is he--
SAZANAMI (VOICEOVER): No.
-The nails underground
have stopped moving.
The jutsu must've worn off.
-What?
NARUTO: Aw, man.
We fell for it.
-Gives new meaning to the
phrase nailed down, doesn't it?
NARUTO: Look.
He's gotta be up by the bell.
Let's go.
-Hold on.
We've gotta be careful.
Don't forget that the bounty
hunter from last night
is also trying to get Gosunkugi.
-Hmph.
Don't worry about him.
We'll get your man first, and
no one'll stand in our way.
Come on!
-How awful.
-That guy is a monster.
-Unforgivable.
-Where the heck is Gosunkugi?
-He's gonna get away if
we stall too much, Naruto.
-There isn't enough time to
come up with any kind of plan.
We have to do this in one shot.
-Right.
-Gentle Fist!
-Akamaru!
[bark]
-Ninja Art, Beast Mimicry.
[barking]
-Ready?
Man Beast Clone!
Fang Over Fang!
-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Na-Ru-To!
Uzumaki Barrage!
-All right.
Well, that knocked him out.
-Great.
So where's Gosunkugi hiding?
[barking]
-That way!
-That's him, all right.
-He's all ours now!
Come on, you wanna clear
your name, don't ya?
So start acing like
a bounty hunter
and show him what
you're made of!
GOSUNKUGI (VOICEOVER):
Ninja Art, Flying Nail Mist.
-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Special delivery!
-Ha.
Too slow.
[screaming]
-Heh, heh.
See you around.
-He's getting away.
SAZANAMI: You're
forgetting something.
-What?
-Me!
-Wait.
Please, just hold on.
Please, I beg you!
-I'm not cold
blooded like you are.
And besides, if I
killed you, I wouldn't
be able to prove my innocence.
-Well, guess we lost
the competition.
-Sure did.
[bark]
-Huh?
-Fugitive Sazanami, AKA Tokichi,
you've hereby been apprehended.
And you, fugitive
Gosunkugi, your crime spree
is over as well!
There are countless
charges against you,
so I'll be turning you over to
the government for punishment.
-Oh, man!
-Darn it.
We can't help.
The authorities
have got him now.
-You murder!
-Bring back the
family you killed!
-We'll treat you the same
way you treated them!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Darn it.
-You've got a lot of nerve.
How dare you put up
these wanted posters
without a real investigation!
-Not so sure.
Honestly, I--
-Sazanami was not the
culprit of this crime.
No.
It was this man.
The infamous thief Gosunkugi was
apprehended and has confessed.
And the sword he
used has been seized.
Therefore villager Tokichi
is acquitted on all counts.
-What do you have to say, jerks?
You made me track down some
innocent guy for nothing.
What are you going to do?
-Why are you helping me?
-It all started with some
sob story I overheard.
To a bounty hunter
like me, the truth
shouldn't have made
any difference.
Even so, I had to
find out for myself.
I needed to make
sure you were really
the horrible criminal these
posters said you were.
-You.
-I got a name, you know.
Gatsu.
You and I are bounty hunters.
We're part of the
same trade now.
-Gatsu.
-Tokichi, we are so sorry.
-Please forgive us, Tokichi.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Everything
turned out well, Sazanami.
-Let's go.
-Yeah.
-You know, after
all this time away,
I'm kind of getting homesick.
I guess I missed the
good old Leaf Village
more than I thought I would.
-Oh, yeah?
Well, a failed mission's
still a failed mission.
The Fifth Hokage's
gonna chew you out.
-What did you say?
You failed yet another mission?
-Forget what I said.
I don't want to go home.
[laughter]
[theme music]
NARUTO: Sneaking in while making
a big ruckus, a chubby skinny
guy!
In the scorching rain,
within the disaster,
a deafening silence!
Tsunade's guess
hits the jackpot.
Kakashi's guess is a bust!
You might have heard
of this somewhere,
the unprecedented story
of Mondai and Potcha.
And that's where I come in!
Hey, guys!
Let me join the training, too!
Next time, The Appearance
of Strange Visitors!
[theme music]