[theme music]
-Aw, man.
I'm exhausted.
Some big important solo mission.
Breaking my back,
rebuilding their fortress.
It's grunt work,
not shinobi work.
Ow.
I'm about to fall apart if I
don't get some serious R&amp;R. Ah,
a hot spring, great!
I can't wait to soak my bones.
Listen to me, I sound
like an old man.
What the heck was that?
Shadow clone jutsu.
Wah.
-Thank you very much.
-Pardon me, but who are you?
-I am a delivery ninja.
NARUTO: Please, Mr. Postman.
-24, 25, 26.
They're all accounted for.
Thanks to you, Naruto,
my delivery record
will remain spotless.
-I'm glad.
But what are deliver
ninja, anyway?
-A special service entrusted
with the most important
documents and parcels.
We risk our lives to
deliver them safely.
-So you're like a mailman?
-No, there's a big difference.
Mailmen don't have to risk
their lives, but we do.
-I get it.
You're a mailman
that risks his life.
-Oh, never mind.
Anyway, I have a
schedule to keep
and many things to deliver.
I must be on my way.
Hey, wait, what's your name?
-596-03.
-That sounds more
like a zip code.
Any place will do as long
as it has a hot bath.
SHOPKEEPER (VOICEOVER):
We have lovely lounge.
-Maybe not that one.
It sounds a little crazy.
Wait a minute, that voice.
-I bet you say that to
every girl you meet.
-Only the pretty ones.
-Ah!
Pervy Sage!
-Who the devil's calling me?
-Well, Pervy Sage, you
want to explain yourself.
You're supposed to be away
from the village on some kind
of important mission,
and meanwhile, I'm
just sitting there waiting
for you to get back.
Well, if you've got this
much free time on your hands,
we can start my
training right now.
-Hold on a second, Naruto.
There's a reason I'm here.
-Save it.
You'll just come up
with some phony story.
-It's not like that.
-It's research for my book.
You see, I've almost finished
writing the very last volume
of "Makeout Violence."
-That's your big
important mission?
-No, but I am on a mission
and it is important.
And that's why I'm here.
-OK, what's this mission about?
-Well, believe it
or not, my sources
tell me that someone from
the Akatsuki organization
will arrive in this
town sometime the day
after tomorrow.
-The Akatsuki?
Do you think it could be Itachi?
-I have no idea,
nor do I have a clue
what would bring them here.
And I won't find out until
the day after tomorrow,
so instead of just
sitting around,
I thought I'd use the
time productively.
-Exactly.
What a great idea.
We could squeeze in
two days of training.
-Uh, yeah.
Actually, that's not
really what I had in mind.
You see, it's this book.
I promised my publisher
I'd get it off
to them today or tomorrow, and
they're breathing down my neck.
-Oh, come on.
I've been waiting forever
to get in some training.
-Tell you what.
You help me while I finish
it, and we might have time
to squeeze in a little training.
-Ah, kink in my shoulder.
Hey, is that tea ready yet?
Great.
Thanks.
Now, I've forgotten what
I was going to write.
I need a long, hot soak.
-Of all the sensei I
had to get stuck with.
-[laughing]
-There he goes
again, more research.
-It's vital that
the secret documents
get to the Lord of the
Land of Fangs in time.
-I'm told that the delivery
ninja stop at this very inn.
-Perfect, then we'll
just leave it to them.
-Delivery ninja?
-The steam's clearing.
I'll get a good view.
This is just the
sort of inspiration
I need to finish my book.
-Drat.
-How the hell am I supposed
to get inspired by that?
-Use your imagination.
Isn't that what a writer does?
-Yeah, for fairy tales.
But I deal in realism.
The real thing.
So would you mind doing
that jutsu, you know,
thing of yours?
-Will it really help
you finish faster?
-Definitely.
-Sexy hand jutsu, ultimate
steam bath version.
-Hi, Jiraiya.
-Pathetic.
Well, a lot of good
that did for me.
Huh?
He hasn't written
one stinking word.
I double checked the address.
Now to seal it up
and it's ready to--
[groaning]
-The documents.
Oh no.
-Guard these with your life.
-We never do anything less, sir.
-Oh, my aching head.
Hey there, can you
deliver this for me, sir?
-Well, if it isn't Naruto.
Thanks again for
your help yesterday.
-Hey, Eight it's you
Mr.-- hey, wait a minute.
It'll come to me.
-596-03.
See?
-What kind of name is that?
Sorry.
Anyway, will you
take this for me?
-I'm sorry, I'm going in
a different direction.
Come on, please?
It's super important.
-Well, well.
If this isn't perfect timing.
-What's he, a shadow clone?
-Why no.
This is 463-72.
Here, I believe this address
is in your district, isn't it?
-It certainly is.
-Good, then I'll leave it to
you, whatever your name is.
-I'm 463-72.
-That's great.
Just deliver it.
Rise and shine, Pervy Sage.
-You let me fall asleep?
-So, are you ready
to start my training?
-What are you talking about?
I gotta finish that
manuscript first.
-No, you don't have
to worry about that.
I finished the thing myself.
It's on the way to your
publisher right now.
From now on, you can devote
all of your attention
to my training.
Isn't that great?
-Are you insane?
If they read that
gibberish of yours,
they'll never let me
write another book.
-Do you think so?
Really?
It's that bad?
Sorry.
-Maybe, maybe it's not too late.
Tell me, how did you send it?
-I gave it to one of
those delivery ninja guys.
-Great.
The delivery ninja.
The most ruthlessly efficient
messengers in the world.
They'll give their lives to
deliver anything anywhere.
War, flood, fire,
nothing can stop them.
After him, Naruto.
Hurry.
We've got to try and catch him.
We've got to get that
manuscript back at all costs.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
There's no doubt
he would have taken this path.
It's the most direct route.
The problem will
be closing the gap.
These delivery ninja are trained
for speed and they never rest.
-Hey, Pervy Sage, can we
slow down the pace a little?
I'm dying here.
-Shut up.
It's your fault that
we're in this mess.
Anyway, you wanted to
start training, didn't you?
To a ninja,
everything's training.
Just think of it as a
test, an endurance test.
-Well, now that you
put it that way, OK.
NARUTO: How are we ever going
to follow him through that?
It's like a maze.
If only Hinata or
Neji were here.
They're Byakugan
would come in handy.
-Byakugan.
Why didn't I think of that?
-Wait a minute, that's
your Rasengan, isn't it?
-Oh, sorry, miss.
[scream]
-Wait, wait, it's all right.
[chuckling]
-Hey, don't start that again.
Keep your mind on the job.
-There he is.
Hurry, Naruto!
-Right, coming!
-Hm, it's a hold up.
-Wait.
Stop, please.
-If you thieves think I'm
falling for that, you're fools.
-Hold on, there's been
a terrible mistake.
This boy gave you the
wrong package this morning,
and we need it back.
-We're not thieves, honest.
-I'm sorry, but there's
nothing I can do.
Once the package has been
entrusted to our care,
we must deliver it to
it's proper destination,
even at the risk of our lives.
-But if I don't get it
back, my career is ruined.
-You have my sympathies.
-OK, you forced me to do it.
Sorry about this.
-Poor guy.
We was only doing his job.
-Don't start with me.
Just keep in mind that
this is all your fault.
Huh?
What the heck is this?
This isn't my manuscript.
-When I bumped into
those guys this morning,
the envelopes must have
got switched somehow.
-Switched?
This is a secret
communication from the Lord
of the Land of Claws to the
Lord of the Land of Fangs.
Everyone, at least everyone
I've spoken to about it,
says the Claw and the
Fang hate each other,
and they're on the
brink of open warfare.
Oh, but this-- this
is an offer of peace.
The Lord of the
Land of Claws wants
to sign a peace
treaty with the Fang.
Well, that's a good
thing, isn't it?
Peace is a lot better than war.
-You bloody fool!
The fact that the peace
offer is here with us
means that the
manuscript of my book
is on the way to the
Lord of the Fangs.
-Ew.
-He'll think it was send
by the Land of the Claws
as some kind of insult.
-You're right.
And that will mean war for sure.
-We're off to the Land of Fangs.
-We're off where?
Ah.
-We've got to stop that
package from being delivered.
-I've been robbed.
This outrage must not
be allowed to stand.
-That's someone's alarm signal.
-This is delivery ninja 463-72.
463-72.
My mail bag has been robbed.
A tall strange looking old man
and a boy traveling together.
-Headed west.
Believe their next
target to be 596-03.
-All units in the area
are to respond at once
to apprehend the
thieves for the honor
and integrity of the
delivery ninja service.
-Straight up this river
lies the Land of Fangs,
and there's no other way to
get there but by water craft.
Hopefully, if we
keep our speed up,
we'll be able to catch
him before it's too late.
-Well, any time you
want to switch places.
-Are you complaining again?
I told you before, just consider
this part of your training.
NARUTO: Not that again.
-What are they doing?
-Reinforcements have arrived.
Paddle, Naruto.
Hurry, switch places with me.
Rasengan.
-It seems such a waste
of an awesome jutsu just
to power a row boat.
-We're trying to prevent a war.
We've got to be willing
to use every single weapon
in our arsenal.
-Right.
-You take over.
-Oh, OK.
Shadow clone jutsu.
Rasengan.
-Look, there he is.
Ahoy there!
Stop!
There was a mix up of
documents this morning.
These are the documents you
were supposed to deliver.
-Trust us, you've
got the wrong ones.
Just take a look.
-I'm sorry, but I can't.
Once a package has been
entrusted to a delivery ninja,
he's absolutely forbidden from
ever opening it or examining
its contents.
-Listen, if you deliver that
package to the Land of Fangs,
it could start a war.
-I'm sorry to hear it.
Nevertheless, rules are
rules, and I have my duty.
-Oh man, you're too much.
-We're here, the Land of Fangs.
-I warn you, I will
not let you interfere
with the performance of my duty.
-OK, if you insist.
I guess we're going to have
to do this the hard way.
-Special delivery.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER): Naruto?
Which one's our man?
-The one we want is-- uh,
-596-03, see?
-Oh yeah, it's 596-03.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
OK, where is he?
NARUTO: Well, uh, uh, there!
Up there.
-Naruto, you go after the
one with my manuscript
while I take care of
the others down here.
-OK, got it.
All right, that's
as far as you go.
Just hand it over.
-In the name of
the delivery ninja,
I order you to stand aside and
allow me to perform my duties.
-Not that same old song.
Well, then in the name of
the Leaf Village ninja,
I'm going to take that package
off you no matter what.
-We'll just see about that.
-Sexy harem jutsu
swimsuit edition.
-Look, girls, delivery ninja.
[goofy laughing]
-I just love a man in uniform.
-No, no, no, no.
I have to get a grip.
I will not let
myself be distracted.
Excuse me, I have
a delivery to make.
Delivery ninja always delivers.
he lets nothing deter
him from his duty.
-Hey, don't be that way.
Where you going?
Why so rude?
Come on and stay.
The fun's just beginning.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
OK, this isn't working.
-Hey, come on.
Help me out here, everyone.
-Sure.
-Delivery for the Lord
of the Land of Fangs.
-Thanks.
I'll see that he gets it.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Unbelievable.
This guy must be
made out of stone.
-That's it.
It's over.
-So that means there's
really going to be a war?
-Wha-- what is the
meaning of this.
The original manuscript
of the next volume
of the "Makeout" series?
That Lord of the land
of Claws, ow could
he have ever guessed
my guilty secret.
The "Makeout" series
is what I live for.
Send word to the Land
of Claws that their gift
has been received with thanks.
There will be no war.
I don't want to be disturbed
for the rest of the day.
-I'm not sure what
just happened,
but at least there
won't be a war.
-Yeah, that's the good news.
What about my reputation?
That's my manuscript but
with your gibberish in it.
-Rise and shine.
Today's the day that Akatsuki
guy is supposed to arrive.
We'll make him tell
us what he knows
about Sasuke, right, Pervy?
Pervy Sage?
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
Sorry, Naruto,
but there's been
a change of plans,
and I didn't want to wake you.
I'm off to track the
Akatsuki on my own.
-What a dirty trick.
Well, at least I got
some training in.
That's something, I guess.
[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Ready, guys?
Let's move out.
-Wait a second.
-Our mission is in the
Village Hidden in the Stars.
One of their stars is
in trouble or something.
-Naruto.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Man, I'm
so fired up for this one.
And we've all got to work
together, right, guys?
Let's show these people what
the Leaf Village ninja can do.
Whoa there.
What makes you
think you're coming?
-That's right, Naruto.
You're not even assigned
to this mission.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): What?
Next time, "Encounter, The
Boy with the Star's Name."