[music playing]
[theme music]
[foot steps]
-Hm?
[creaking]
Excuse me, my lady,
but the skies above
are looking a bit threatening.
We should seek lodging for
the night before it rains.
-I see.
Thank you.
Please carry on then.
-Very well.
-This fog is impenetrable.
-I can't see a thing out there.
[moaning]
-What is that?
-Is there anything wrong?
-Lady Chiyo.
[moaning]
[gasping]
[growling]
[screaming]
[music playing]
-It seems that Lady Chiyo
of the Land of Honey
was on her way to
visit her family back
in the Land of Candy.
When she didn't show up,
her relatives grew nervous
and sent out a party
to look for her.
Unfortunately, her carriage was
found in pieces on the road.
From what they can gather,
Lady Chiyo and her attendants
just up and disappeared.
-OK, so what's the story?
You want us to track her down?
-That is correct.
Your nose and Hinata's eyes make
you perfect for the mission.
And Naruto was--
well, available.
-(ANGRILY) What's that
supposed to mean, grandma?
Are you saying I don't
bring anything to the table?
-That's accurate, isn't it?
[grunting]
-Uh, I don't know.
I mean, I've always thought
you've had a lot to offer,
Naruto.
-Ha!
I can always count
on you, Hinata.
Now, rattle off a few
of my better qualities
for old grandma!
No need to be shy, right?
What would you say
my better points are?
-Oh, well, let me see
now-- uh, I guess--
-(ANGRILY) Ugh!
Come on!
It's not that hard a question!
[giggling]
HINATA: I-- I didn't mean to--
-All right, zip it you two.
I don't have all day here.
-There isn't anything weird
about this mission, is there?
-Hm?
Weird like how?
-Oh, well, uh-- you
know, like, ghosts maybe?
-Are you kidding?
You're not telling me you're
scared of spirits, are you?
-Oh, well, maybe a little.
[giggling]
-Ghouls and ghosts are
just a bunch of hooey.
Get going already and
stop wasting my time!
-Sure thing.
Just tell us where we're
going, and we'll take off.
-Kubisaki Pass.
-Kubisaki Pass?
Doesn't that mean broken neck?
I knew this was
going to be trouble.
-(ANGRILY) Idiot!
A ninja doesn't get
scared by things
that go bump in the night!
Now get out of my office!
[gasping]
-I'll take my chances
with the ghost!
-Later!
[panting]
-All right then.
Good bye.
[sighing]
-Every day it's the same
thing with that kid.
-If I'm not mistaken,
Lady Tsunade, that pass
is where the capital of the
Land of Next used to be.
I'm sure the ruined castle
of the Kubisaki clan,
which met its demise
some 50 years ago,
must still be standing there.
-And what of it?
You can find ruined castles
just about anywhere.
You don't have a touch of
Naruto's cowardice, do you?
-No, my lady.
I just meant that--
[music playing]
-Hey.
This is it.
NARUTO: Kubisaki Pass, huh?
I don't know why, but this
place gives me the creeps.
[raining]
KIBA: Ah, great, it's
starting to rain.
Let's hustle.
[screaming]
-Ah, man, it's really
coming down now.
[running]
[thunder]
-A castle.
-That's funny.
I've never heard
of one around here.
HINATA: I'm getting
a bad feeling.
NARUTO: That's what I'm saying!
This is the creepiest
mission ever.
-Maybe we should check it out.
I bet we find some clues here.
-Let's go have a look.
-OK.
We're getting soaked
out here anyway.
-What's the hurry?
It's just a little rain!
HINATA: It's magnificent.
-Wouldn't it be sort of rude to
go barging in all of a sudden?
I mean, it's a little late
for company right now.
-Come on, don't tell me
you really are scared.
-Wh- why would you think that?
Don't be silly.
-Don't worry, Naruto.
-Let's go.
[raining]
[screaming]
-Do you see that?
The door just opened
all on its own.
[thunder]
[gasping]
HINATA: We're sorry to
be intruding like this,
but is anybody home?
KIBA: Well, the lights are on.
-(YELLING) Do you mind if we
take shelter from the rain
here?
[dog barking]
KIBA: Hey!
Akamaru!
Wait up!
-Is there anyone at home?
-Uh, hello?
-Something sure
smells good in here.
-Hm.
This dish is still warm.
-Think we just missed
whoever was here?
-Huh?
KIBA: What's that?
NARUTO: One scary looking fella.
-The master of the castle maybe?
-I don't know.
That would make him a
feudal Lord, wouldn't it?
And that would mean
the surrounding area
was the capital of this region.
But we're right
on the border now.
Akamaru!
[dog barking]
What are you doing up there?
You can't just help
yourself to dinner.
[dog whining]
-Hm.
[screaming]
-What's the matter?
-Come on, don't
startle us like that.
-(YELLING) Yeah, bu-- but that
painting's eyes just moved!
-You idiot.
Paintings don't move.
Stop being such
a wuss, will you?
-Hey.
This table is set
for seven people.
-What's so special about that?
-Well, the party that went
missing from the Land of Honey
had seven people in it.
Which means the Lady
and her attendants
could be somewhere
in this castle.
Why don't we split
up and look for them?
-Huh?
What do you want
to split up for?
No reason to break up a
perfectly good team, right,
guys? (YELLING) All
for one, one for all!
-Aw, give it a rest, Naruto.
Quick acting like such a baby.
Try to focus on
the mission here.
[groaning]
-All right!
You don't have to be
such a bully about it.
I know, OK?
-Huh.
NARUTO: Hey, come on, wait up!
(NERVOUSLY) I was just kidding.
[thunder]
-Guh.
Man, I am not cut out for this.
I can barely handle going to
the bathroom on my own at night.
[gasping]
I don't like like place!
[panting]
[gasping]
[bells ringing]
[thunder]
[screaming]
-(SCREAMING) Not again!
Kiba!
Hinata!
Akamaru!
Where are you guys?
I don't think I can handle
this place on my own!
[sniffing]
[barking]
-You smell him, too, don't you?
That's a human scent
we're picking up.
[floor creaking]
In here.
[grunting]
There's no one here.
MAN (VOICEOVER): Devour!
-Who's that?
Is someone there?
[crashing sounds]
What's going on?
Take that!
[grunting]
[moaning]
[growling]
[screaming]
[buzzing]
-So many books.
Hm.
"Kubisaki Castle-- it
happened 50 years ago.
With the castle
surrounded by the enemy,
our people were
brutally slaughtered.
And the few lowly samurai
holed up within these walls
held little hope of
seeing another nightfall.
My thirst for vengeance lives on
in every stone of this castle.
I promise to devour any man
who dares step foot inside.
Koza Kubisaki."
Devour them?
MAN (VOICEOVER): Devour.
[gasping]
-What is this?
Koza Kubisaki!
[gasping]
[screaming]
[groaning]
-Darn it!
[screaming]
[water running]
[groaning]
-Hm?
Hinata!
Hey!
Hinata, come on, snap out of it!
-Huh?
Naruto?
[dog barking]
-Huh?
-Naruto!
Hinata!
You all right?
-Am I glad to see you!
[water dripping]
KIBA: A castle that
fell 50 years ago?
NARUTO: Oh, please.
-Well, that's how far
the scroll dates back.
It says anyone who enters this
place will be eaten alive.
-I guess we were kind
of swallowed up, huh?
[gasping]
[screaming]
-Naruto!
-You OK there, buddy?
-Ahh, man, that hurt.
[loud boom]
[gulping]
[screaming]
-That's him!
We're really sorry.
-What is he doing here?
-He's not one of the Kubisaki.
With armor like that, he
must have been an enemy.
-There's more of them over
there with different armor.
[gasping]
HINATA: The bear the armor
of the Kubisaki clan.
[groaning]
NARUTO: (NERVOUSLY) Let's hurry
up and get out of here, huh?
[foot steps]
[gasping]
-That's the armor he was
wearing in the painting.
-Do you think it's him?
The real ghost of Kubisaki?
[gulping]
-You really think so?
-Wh-- what is that?
NARUTO: Ugh!
He's melting!
[dog barking]
KIBA: Weird.
Man, that is rank!
-I'm telling you, something
not right around here.
Hinata?
-Right.
[speaking japanese] All of the
walls are flowing with chakra.
But why?
KIBA: Everything's moving.
NARUTO: The walls-- it's
almost like they're alive.
-Maybe I can break through.
Gentle fist!
[grunting]
[gulping]
[groaning]
[screaming]
-Oh man, are you
all right, Hinata?
[groaning]
I've actually seen something
like this once before.
Inside the stomach of a giant
toad the pervy sage summoned.
KIBA: Inside its stomach?
So wait a minute.
Does that mean this
smell is stomach acid?
HINATA: Koza Kubisaki
invoked the art
of summoning before
his stronghold fell.
And whatever he called
forth was big enough
to swallow the place whole.
And the moment we set
foot inside the castle,
we were gobbled up, too.
-I don't get it.
Why would he tell his
pet castle to eat us
like some sort of snack?
What did we ever do to him?
-I don't know.
[woman screaming]
KIBA: What was that?
Huh?
-Help!
I beg you!
-Are you the Lady from
the Land of Honey?
-She's embedded in the wall.
HINATA: We're from the
Hidden Leaf Village!
Don't worry!
We were sent to rescue you!
[grunting]
-Here Let me bust you out!
[groaning]
No use!
[growling]
-Don't worry!
I'll get you out!
[groaning]
-Oh man, the walls in here are
drawing all these people in
and absorbing them.
And they're reverting
back to normal.
At this rate, we'll
be pulled in, too.
Naruto!
Hinata!
We've got to get out of here!
Man beat clone!
(YELLING) Fang over fang!
MAN (VOICEOVER):
I am the castle,
and by order of Koza
Kubisaki, all who enter
shall be devoured.
[screaming]
[groaning]
-Naruto!
[screaming]
[grunting]
[whining]
MAN (VOICEOVER): Devour!
-What do we do?
How are we going to get
out of this guy's stomach?
-I don't know.
[yelling]
-If this creature
was summoned, there
will be a contract somewhere.
Tear up the scroll,
and this thing
goes back to where it came from.
-No kidding!
[yelling]
NARUTO: Hinata!
-Right!
[speaking japanese] Found it!
Up there somewhere
in the castle tower!
-How the heck are we supposed--
ah-- to get up there?
-The walls are back
to normal again.
[door opening]
-Huh?
-Who is that?
-It's Koza Kubisaki.
NARUTO: Nuh-uh.
I'm not falling for it twice.
That's just another phantom
created by the summons.
HINATA: Wait.
He's different from before.
-What do we do?
-I think he wants
us to follow him.
[gasping]
-Wait.
Where the heck did he go?
-Naruto!
Look over there!
NARUTO: Hey!
It's the scroll!
[moaning]
-The walls are
starting to move again.
Just grab it.
NARUTO: Right.
[groaning]
-Look at that.
The summoned animal's true form.
[gasping]
-The acid is starting
to build up in here.
Come on, hurry.
Let's wind things up.
-Hold on a second, Kiba.
What if we send this beast
back to where it came from,
and it ends up taking
us along with it?
-We're running out of time.
We'll just have to
take our chances here.
[dog barking]
-Right.
[groaning]
Did that do it?
[moaning]
[screaming]
-Naruto!
-What are you doing?
[moaning]
Over there, Naruto!
You should be able
to tear through!
-OK!
Shadow clone jutsu!
[inaudible]
[groaning]
[screaming]
-Hey!
Are you OK?
[groaning]
KIBA: He must have
died resenting
those who seized his castle.
[groaning]
HINATA: But he also led us to
where the scroll was hidden.
NARUTO: You figure
he finally decided
to let go of his grudge?
KIBA: Seems that way.
Or heck, could be he thought
50 years was long enough
to keep that summoned
animal in his service.
Maybe he just wanted to let
the poor old beast return home.
-Think so?
Then maybe he needed
help releasing
that creature from its
imprisonment-- freeing it.
HINATA: And now
it's finally home.
[theme music]
[music playing]
NARUTO: Hey, Bushy
Brow, how'd it go?
GIRL: Something is wrong.
NARUTO: Wrong?
What do you mean?
GIRL: His exam
results were grim.
Really grim.
NARUTO: Huh?
That bad?
GIRL: Yep.
It doesn't look good.
NARUTO: No way.
Does that mean Bushy Brow--
GIRL: Afraid so.
[screaming]
NARUTO: It can't be
that bad, can it?
Say it ain't so!
Next time-- "The
Third Super-Beast."
[theme music]