[theme music]
-Hm. [chuckles]
[gasp]
Huh?
-[grunts]
What is this?
[grunts] Who do
you think you are?
[panting]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): "Battle on
the Bridge, Zabuza Returns."
-Good morning, everyone.
[yawns]
-Here.
-Oh, thank you.
-Naruto is not here.
Looks like he was
out all night again.
-He's gone completely crazy.
He's out climbing
trees in the dark.
He could be dead
by now, you know,
from using up too
much of his chakra.
-Well, I certainly hope he's OK.
A child spending the
night in the woods alone.
-There's nothing to worry about.
Naruto is a goofy kid, but
he's also a full-fledged ninja.
He can handle himself.
-Sakura's right.
Naruto is such a loser.
He's probably lying out
there dead somewhere.
-Sasuke?
-I'm going for a walk.
-Uh, but we just started eating.
Huh?
[door shuts]
That was fast.
-You'll catch cold
if you sleep here.
Wake up.
-[groans]
Hmm.
Who the heck are you?
Oh.
Uh, uh, I mean, hi there.
Where did you come from?
You know, what are you
doing out here and all that?
-I'm gathering herbs.
-Herbs?
-Yes, that's right.
They're for treating
illnesses in human wounds.
-You start work early, huh, sis?
-I like it early.
It's calm.
But I didn't think I'd find
anyone sleeping out here
in the woods.
-[chuckles]
I'm training.
-Hm?
So are you a ninja?
Because I noticed that
headband you're wearing.
Or are you just making
a fashion statement?
-You noticed that?
All right!
Only super-cool
ninja can wear these.
-Oh, really.
I see.
That's very impressive.
-[laughs]
-But does that mean
you're training
for something dangerous?
-I'm just developing my
skills, so I can get stronger.
-You seem very strong now.
Isn't that enough?
-No, no.
I need to get
stronger and stronger.
I have to keep practicing.
-Oh, so why is it so important?
-So I could become the
best ninja in my village.
And everyone will know who I am.
And they'll all respect me.
There's also a
certain person, a kid,
that I have to
prove something to.
-So are you doing it
for this certain person?
Or are you doing all this
training for yourself?
-Uh-huh.
-[chuckles]
-What are you laughing about?
What's so funny?
-[chuckles]
Is there someone
who's precious to you?
-Someone who-- what
are you saying, sis?
What do you mean "precious"?
-Uhh.
[dog barking]
Uh.
[dog snarls]
[dog yelps]
[dogs growling]
Huh?
[footsteps approaching]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Hm.
What's she thinking?
-You see, when a person has
something precious that they
want to protect, then they
become genuinely strong.
-Hm?
Hm.
-This is our village.
So we've got to do
everything we can to help.
I'll protect you with my life.
All of you.
-If you ever lay a hand on
my sensei, I'll kill you!
Yeah, I hear you.
I know exactly
what you're saying.
-You will get
strong, very strong.
-[chuckles]
-Goodbye.
We'll meet again some time.
Oh, by the way, I'm a boy.
-[gasp]
Nah!
No way!
He's prettier than Sakura!
-[grunts]
[groans] Oh, I've seen a lot of
weird things in my life before,
but this one takes the cake.
Ow!
Hey, what did you do that for?
-You twerp.
-Cut it out!
-Did you just forget
about breakfast?
You're such a loser.
-Duh?
[chuckles]
-[grunts]
SAKURA: Naruto?
Knowing Naruto, he
could be anywhere.
And Sasuke hasn't
come back either.
I wonder where they are.
-Hm?
-Uh!
-[chuckles]
-Whoa, Naruto can climb that
high now using his chakra?
That's great.
-Hm.
-What do you think?
High enough for you guys?
I mean, it's a
long way down, huh?
[gasp]
Aah!
-Oh, Naruto!
-Uh-oh.
-Aah!
-[screams]
Ha-ha!
Just kidding.
You guys really fell for it.
[laughs]
-We were worried
about you, Naruto.
I'm going to strangle you!
Shut up, you dork!
-Why do I think this
is going to end badly?
-[chuckles]
-Huh!
-Haah!
You just had to push it,
didn't you, show-off?
-Aah!
[groans]
-You really are a
total loser, Naruto.
-Naah!
Sasuke!
-Aw!
All right, Sasuke!
You're the best!
-If I'm still sane by the
time I finish their training,
it'll be a miracle.
-Naruto.
Humph.
Naruto Uzumaki, huh?
-You're recovering quickly.
-[grunts]
Just a little longer, Haku.
-Yes.
-[panting]
-Let's go back.
-All right.
-Now, they're both late.
I wouldn't have expected
that from Sasuke.
[door opens]
-What have you been up to?
You look like something
the cat dragged in.
-[chuckles]
We both made it.
We climbed all the
way to the top.
-Good.
Now, we move on.
Starting tomorrow, you're
both bodyguards for Tazuna.
-[laughs] All right!
-Ugh, you are such a loser.
[laughter]
-In a few more days, the
bridge will be finished.
I have you to thank for that.
-You've all done great.
But you've still
got to be careful.
-I've been meaning
to ask you this,
but I haven't had
the chance until now.
Why did you stay and protect
me even after you found out
I lied to bring you here?
-"Those who stray from the path
of justice have no courage.
But under the wing
of a strong leader,
cowardice cannot survive."
-Huh?
-That was a quote
from the First Hokage.
-Hm.
-[gasping]
-[sobs]
-[grunts]
If you care about
something, keep trying.
Protect it with both arms.
Inari, don't cry.
-But why?
-Hm?
What did you say?
-Ungh.
All this stupid training
is just a waste of time.
Gato's got a whole army.
They'll beat you down,
and they'll destroy you!
These cool things you all
say, they don't mean anything.
No matter what you do,
the strong always win
and the weak always lose.
-Just speak for yourself.
It won't be like that for me.
You got that?
-Why don't you be quiet?
Just looking at
you makes me sick!
You don't know anything
about this country.
You're just butting in!
Always laughing
and playing around.
You don't know what
it's like to suffer
and be treated like dirt!
-Listen to yourself
whining and complaining
like some sorry little victim!
-Uhh.
-You can whimper all
day for all I care.
You're nothing but a coward.
-Hm!
-Naruto, you went too far!
-[grunts]
-Naruto.
-[sobs]
KAKASHI: Can I talk to you?
Naruto can be a little
harsh sometimes.
But he doesn't hate you.
Your grandfather told us
what happened to your father.
You probably don't know
this, but Naruto also
grew up without a father.
In fact, he never knew
either of his parents.
And he didn't have a single
friend in our village.
-Huh?
-Still, I've never seen
him cry, sulk, or give up.
He's always eager to jump in.
He wants to be respected.
That's his dream.
And he'll put his life on the
line for that-- in a heartbeat.
My guess is he just
got tired of crying
and decided to do
something about it.
-Oh.
Hm.
-Even though he's young
and still learning,
he knows what it means to be
strong, like your father did.
I think he knows better
than any of us what
you are going through.
-Oh.
-What Naruto told you earlier,
as cruel as it sounded,
he's probably told
himself that 1,000 times.
OK, I leave Naruto
in your hands.
He's pushed his
body to the limit.
Overdoing it, as usual.
So he may not be able
to move today at all.
[snores]
-What about you?
You are still
recovering yourself.
-Why?
Do I look wobbly?
I'll be OK.
-Come on.
Let's go.
-Still wasting time
licking your wounds?
I hired you to do
a job, you know!
Are you listening, Zabuza?
Hey!
-Haku, you ready?
-Yes.
[hammering on bridge]
-Uhh.
Naah!
Why didn't somebody wake me up?
Where is everybody?
Where did they all go?
-Oh, Naruto.
Your sensei wanted
to let you rest.
You got the day off.
-[grunts] I knew it!
They ditched me!
See you!
[door shuts]
[grunts] They could
have woken me up!
Hm?
-Hold on!
What the heck is this?
[men groaning]
What happened?
Someone was here.
Someone got to them!
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
Could it be?
TSUNAMI: Inari!
Would you give me a hand here?
Inari!
INARI: I'll be right there!
-This mist.
Sasuke, Sakura, get ready!
I knew he was still alive.
He just couldn't
wait for round 2.
-Kakashi-sensei, it's
Zabuza, isn't it?
This is his Hidden Mist Jutsu.
[heartbeat]
MALE SPEAKER: Sorry, I
kept you waiting, Kakashi.
I see you've still got
those brats with you.
That one's still trembling.
Pitiful.
-[gasp]
Heh.
-Uh?
-I'm trembling with excitement.
-Go on, Sasuke.
-[grunts]
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
I can see it.
ZABUZA: Ooh, so you could see
they were water clones, huh?
The brat's improving.
Looks like you've
got a rival, Haku.
-So it seems.
THEME SONG: Cultivate your
hunger before you idealize.
Motivate your anger,
make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain,
never coming down.
Break into the contents,
never falling down.
My knee is still
shaking, like I was 12.
Sneaking out of the
classroom, by the backdoor.
A man railed at me twice,
though, but I didn't care.
Waiting is wasting
for people like me.
Don't try to live so wise.
Don't cry 'cause
you're so right.
Don't try with fakes
or fears 'cause you
will hate yourself in the end.
Don't try to live so wise.
Don't cry 'cause
you're so right.
Don't try with fakes
or fears 'cause you
will hate yourself in the end.
Don't try to live so wise.
Don't cry 'cause
you're so right.
Don't try with fakes--
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
OK, so I slept late.
Don't think I'm going to miss
the action because of that.
Whoa, Inari, look at you!
You're getting brave, partner.
Well, your dad was a big hero.
So maybe it's your turn now.
Wait a minute.
What about Kakashi-sensei
and the others?
If they're in danger, I've
got to get over there!
Next time, "Haku's Secret
Jutsu-- Crystal Ice Mirrors."
To survive this one, I'll have
to kick butt like never before!