[theme music]
-TSUNADE: Ah.
This is so relaxing.
Peace time is such
a wonderful thing.
I can just sit here drinking
as much sake as I want to.
-This is not the time to be
loafing around getting drunk!
It's so rare when the
village is at peace.
You should use this time
to do your paperwork!
-Why does it seem like no
matter how much paperwork I
do, there's always more?
-Because you never see a single
item through to completion,
Lady Tsunade!
-There's unrest brewing
among the Kamizuru Clan?
-That's a communique from
the ANBU unit stationed
in the Land of Earth.
Though Kamizuru
doesn't sound familiar.
-The Kamizuru Clan were the
legendary insect-handlers
of the Hidden Stone Village.
Long ago, they
were so well known
many considered them
equals of the Aburame Clan.
But over the years, they've
practically died out.
These days, hardly anyone
even remembers their name.
-I've never heard
of them before.
-Well, this says they
might cause some trouble.
But there aren't too
many of them left.
I don't think it's anything
we need to worry about it.
NARUTO: What's the difference?
Don't all insects look alike?
This is crazy.
There's so many
insects around here.
-This whole forest is
like a bug paradise.
-There's no chance we
can get stung, is there?
-Almost none of these
insects can harm humans.
But just in case, I
have the Aburame Clan's
secret repellent.
Though I would
prefer not to use it,
since it would also
repel the bikochu.
-Great.
Then what's the point of
even bringing it along?
-Just as I thought.
That kid in the
lead is definitely
a member of the Aburame Clan.
I never thought we'd
bump into one of them
in a place like this.
-Do you think they're after
the bikochu just like we are?
Huh, Jibachi?
-Well, if someone
wanted the bikochu,
they would have to come
to this exact place
at this time of year.
-Remember.
The fate of the
whole Kamizuru Clan
rests on the outcome
of our mission.
No matter who stands in our
way, we must get that bikochu.
SHINO: This is the
female bikochu.
Remember it down to
the smallest detail.
-No problem.
-OK.
Got it.
-Hey.
You know, I've seen one before.
-You've seen it?
Are you sure?
-Where did you see one, Naruto?
-Well, uh-- one
time, I accidentally
left some food out, and they
started coming out of nowhere.
A whole bunch of 'em everywhere.
So those were bikochu.
Those things should be
easy for us to catch.
-You're kidding me.
-Um-- Naruto--
-No.
Those were just cockroaches.
-Eh?
Cockroaches?
-They're not remotely the same.
-Come on.
This bug is
completely different.
-I don't know.
They look the same to me.
-Well, they're not!
-Coming across these guys might
be the good fortune we needed.
-What are you talking
about, Suzumebachi?
-It's been ten days since
we started our search team,
and we haven't even found
a trace of the bikochu.
But if that kid from
the Aburame Clan does--
-Yes.
You're right.
But do you actually
think those three
kids could catch a bikochu?
-I can't be sure.
All of them appear
to be merely genin.
If they do manage
to catch one though,
we'll be waiting right here
to take it away from them.
-Ah, man.
All these insects
look totally alike.
-Insect Summoning Jutsu.
No.
None here.
-Is this it?
Ah, it's different.
[bark]
-Heheh.
-Try not to be a burden
to those around you,
if you're able to help it.
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
This mission,
I'm the one who
volunteered us for it.
I've got to find that beetle.
Byakugan!
-Oh no.
I can't sense things
as small as insects.
Huh?
-Hm?
-Shino, Kiba!
-Hinata, did you see them too?
-Oh.
You already know.
-They must not know
we're aware of them.
-Unfortunately for them,
almost our entire team
are specialists in
detecting hidden enemies.
What should we do, Shino?
After all, you are the
leader of this mission.
-If it comes to a
fight, the insects
may get caught in the
middle, and there'd
be a danger of
injuring the bikochu.
As long as they
don't make a move,
let's just keep an eye on 'em.
-All right.
-I wonder if Naruto
noticed them.
-If he did, he'd be yelling
and screaming by now.
-Let's not stir things up.
Don't tell him.
NARUTO: Hey!
Shino!
I found one!
I'm telling you!
I found a bikochu!
[gasping]
-He found one already?
-Impossible!
-When we spent
ten days searching
and couldn't find one?
No way.
-Oh, Naruto.
You did it.
-Are you positive?
Cuz last time--
-I wanna see it.
[giggling]
-Well, this is the bug, right?
See?
It's exactly like that
photo you showed us.
Guess I must be some sort
of insect hunting genius.
Huh?
-Does it look the same to you?
-Uh.
Uh.
-The one you have
is a goliath beetle.
-Ah!
It's not the same thing!
-The bikochu isn't
active at night.
-So--
-I suppose we might
as well call it a day.
NARUTO: Shino!
Yo!
Shino!
I spotted one!
This time I'm 100%
certain of it.
-It's probably a completely
different insect.
-Naruto.
[bark]
-100% sure.
Over here.
Hurry.
If we don't get there
quick it'll fly away.
KIBA: So why didn't you
just bring it with you
in the first place?
NARUTO: Cuz I saw it
resting in a tree.
-The shape of the antennae
is certainly the same,
and all the
characteristics match.
-See?
I knew I'd found the
right one this time.
-But-- um-- Naruto--
-I'm pretty sure this
is a different insect.
-Huh?
What makes you say that?
KIBA: It's way too
big to be our bug!
How would you ever get this one
to sniff out scents, you dummy!
-That's easy.
I can handle him!
-I should warn you.
It's quite ill-tempered.
That species gets angry if
anyone touches its nose.
And they've been
known to eat humans.
-What?
Heheh.
[elephant trumpet]
NARUTO: Shino, didn't you say
there were no dangerous insects
here?
SHINO: I said there
were almost none.
Not zero.
[screaming]
-Kurobachi, Jibachi, I am
beginning to seriously doubt
those guys will ever
catch a bikochu.
-I think you're right.
HINATA (VOICEOVER): If I'm
going to locate something
as small as an insect, I need
to focus my chakra better.
SUZUMEBACHI (VOICEOVER): Hmph.
Way out in the middle of nowhere
and she's still training.
That's admirable.
SHINO: The air
pressure changed, which
means the weather is shifting.
-I felt it too.
There's a breeze now, and
it's getting more humid.
No doubt it's about to rain.
-Huh?
Aw.
But the weather's perfect.
HINATA: No.
I sense clouds off
in the distance.
-We need to find those beetles.
You see, the bikochu only
lay their eggs when it rains.
They mature quickly, and the
following morning the larvae
emerge from the egg.
-In other words,
if it rains today,
they'll be fully
grown by tomorrow.
-It's the end of the season.
This may be our last chance.
If we let them slip
through our fingers,
it won't be possible
to search for Sasuke.
-That can't happen.
We can do it.
I'll find one of those
bugs no matter what.
Come on.
Don't rain.
Don't start reading yet.
Where is this dumb thing hiding?
You've gotta come
out before it rains.
-Oh, Naruto.
-Suzumebachi, what
are we gonna do
if these guys don't end
up finding a bikochu?
-Remember.
The Aburame Clan was
responsible for the downfall
of our proud Kamizuru Clan.
SUZUMEBACHI (VOICEOVER):
We'll finally
get revenge for our clan
by taking out an Aburame.
-Those tag-alongs,
I'm worried they still
haven't made a move on us.
-They must have
figured out that we're
searching for the bikochu,
which means they're just keeping
their distance waiting
for us to find one.
-Oh.
I get it.
So their plan is to wait
until we discover one,
then steal it from us.
They should find
their own beetle.
[barking]
-The rain.
-No.
Not this one either.
I thought I told you not
to rain yet, darn it!
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
We've run out of time.
-Try not to be a burden
to those around you,
if you're able to help it.
HINATA (VOICEOVER): It's true.
I didn't do anything to help.
NARUTO: Come on.
There's still a chance.
-Naruto.
-I gave my word, and
I won't break it.
That's what my ninja
way is all about.
HINATA (VOICEOVER): He's right.
The mission was my idea.
I'm responsible.
If Naruto hasn't given up yet,
then I can't give up either!
SHINO: Hinata.
The rain.
It might actually be
to your advantage.
-What do mean, Shino?
-Think about it.
When the surrounding
temperature cools,
it's easier to see the heat
signature of living creatures.
HINATA (VOICEOVER): Naruto,
I'm not giving up either.
Byakugan!
Focus.
Concentrate more.
I have to control my chakra.
Smaller, smaller!
I can see them.
Those are insects.
No.
No that one.
That's wrong too.
Wait.
What's that?
Is it?
There it is!
-Naruto, look!
On the side of that tree!
I found a bikochu!
-Huh?
Get back here.
All right!
I got it!
We did it!
We got the beetle!
[barking]
-There's no mistake.
It's a female bikochu.
-I did it!
I'm amazing!
-Wow.
I gotta admit.
I didn't really think you
could pull it off, Naruto.
-I'm proud of you, Naruto.
-Aw, Hinata, Thanks!
It's all because of you!
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
Naruto is hugging me.
[barking]
-Akamaru?
What's the matter?
All right!
It's an egg!
SHINO: She spawned.
-Really?
-A new beetle will
emerge tomorrow.
-And then we can train
it to recognize and find
Sasuke's scene, right?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Sasuke,
nothing's gonna stop me.
I will find you.
-Heh.
It looks like they
finally found one.
-Meaning the time has come.
-Let's go.
-Naruto, he-- all of a sudden
he pressed his face so close
to mine and I--
-Nice.
You were able to dodge my kunai.
-Pretty nimble
moves for a genin.
HINATA (VOICEOVER): Oh no.
They must be the ones
who've been following us
all this time.
-But let's find out if
you can evade this attack.
Ninja Art Honeybee Jutsu!
-No!
Not bees!
No!
Can't--
-So you noticed, huh?
My special honey.
You can't escape.
It's far too strong!
-I used up all my
chakra earlier.
-I'm afraid this bee
has quite a sting.
-Naruto.
-Do you smell anything, buddy?
[whimper]
-Nothing.
I thought for sure
that those others
would make some kind
of move on us by now.
But there hasn't been
any sign of them yet.
-There's a possibility that
we overlooked something.
-Hey, Naruto.
-Hm?
-Where's Hinata?
-She went to go wash her face.
-Huh?
-Yeah.
But it's been a while now.
I wonder what's
taking her so long.
-Oh no.
-Huh?
What's up?
-Naruto!
Down!
SHINO: There's a note.
KUROBACHI: We're holding
the kunoichi brat hostage.
If you want to get
her back, we'll
trade her for the bikochu.
Bring it to the top of the
eastern hill at midnight.
-Darn it.
I knew they'd make a move.
-Hinata.
[theme music]
NARUTO: There's
nothing else we can do.
SHINO: It's too
early to give up.
KIBA: But we don't even
know where Hinata is.
SHINO: No.
There's still one place we
can try to recover Hinata.
KIBA: You mean at the
exchange for the bikochu?
SHINO: It's our only chance.
NARUTO: I've gotta rescue
Hinata, and protect
the bikochu.
I can't fail on this.
Next time-- A Battle of Bugs.
The Deceivers and the Deceived.
[theme music]