[theme music]
-Well, Tomari, what's up?
-He's close.
Very close.
-I knew it.
What do we do?
-Leave everything to me.
-Well, that was close.
-Whoa.
What was that?
-Trip-wire traps.
They're certainly not making
Sasuke's job easy for him.
-Sasuke.
Do you think he
might have been--
-Oh, don't worry about Sasuke.
It'd take a lot more than
that to get rid of him.
He'll be fine
PAKKUN (VOICEOVER) I
sure hope you're right.
OROCHIMARU: Now then,
shall we begin this?
First, let me restore
these dear old companions
of yours to something more
like their former selves.
And then, if you're
ready Sarutobi-sensei.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): An unrivaled
match-- Hokage Battle Royale.
-They're coming alive.
What the devil kind
of jutsu is that?
A forbidden one.
It's a summoning jutsu
called reanimation.
Normally, a summoning
jutsu requires
the blood of the
casting it, but I've
heard that this
jutsu, which summons
the dead to the
world of the living,
demands the sacrifice
of a living body
to be used as a vessel
for the dead soul.
-Then those are
not their bodies,
but two living sacrifices?
-Right.
But then the living
body is encased
in a shell of dust
and earth that
takes on the appearance of the
dead spirit's earthly form.
Those spells he implanted
in their skulls,
they sap the spirits
of their will,
and transform them into his
puppets, mere killing machines.
[laughter]
-Now they're complete.
-You demon.
They look just the
same as I remember.
-Have you ever felt
the joy and fulfillment
of humiliating and destroying
the one you once called sensei?
No.
I suppose not.
Perhaps vicariously
through me you'll
get a hint of what I mean.
Just a taste, before you die.
-Lord Hokage!
Don't be deceived
by their appearance!
That is not the first
Hokage, nor the second!
Whatever they may look like.
-I'm aware of that.
All right.
Let it begin.
Fire Style!
Dragon Flame Bombs!
[chuckling]
-Water Style.
Water Wall!
-Huh?
-Amazing.
To cast so powerful
a Water Style
jutsu where there is no water.
It's beyond belief.
-It's no less than I'd
expect from a former Hokage.
-Water Style!
Water Shockwave!
HOKAGE (VOICEOVER): Earth Style!
Mud Wall!
[shout]
[grunting]
-As quick and strong
as ever, I see.
[groaning]
HOKAGE (VOICEOVER):
Fighting the two of you
at once is quite a challenge.
The hidden jutsu of
the first Hokage.
-Secret Earth jutsu.
Deep Forest Creation!
[groaning]
[shout]
-He uses his chakra
as a life source.
So this is the
legendary Secret Earth
jutsu of the first Hokage.
He who brought peace to the
land and founded the Hidden Leaf
Village.
-Looks to me that
this fight is over.
Eh, sensei?
[groaning]
IRUKA: We're all here I see.
Good.
All right then.
Let's start evacuating
the building.
That's it.
No rushing.
No panicking.
-Konohamaro, is something wrong?
You look like you
have a tummy-ache.
-Mm.
That's not it at all.
[groaning]
Ninja Art Summoning jutsu.
Monkey King Enma!
-Hm.
So, a pesky newcomer
has arrived.
That old monkey, Enma.
-It's you again.
I should have known
this would happen.
You fool, Sarutobi.
you should have killed
when you had the chance.
-Better late than never.
-Heh.
It's too late now.
[groaning]
-Quickly!
Enma, Adamantine Nyoi!
-Stop him now!
Do not let him transform.
-All right then.
Understood!
[grunting]
Transform!
-At last.
-Unbelievable.
I never dreamed I would live to
see this-- Hokage level combat.
-Good for you, old man.
At least you've made this
a little more interesting.
HOKAGE (VOICEOVER): What of it?
One swing of the
grass longsword--
-Are you ready, Enma?
ENMA: No matter how
strong my body is,
the grass longsword
will still hurt me.
-He's mine.
-Lord Hokage!
-That was foolish.
Trying to fight the three of us
without using your Shadow Clone
jutsu.
-That's right.
He didn't use.
But only because
he couldn't use it.
To disperse his chakra
among a pack of clones
and then create more
when those has fallen,
such things are beyond him now.
He hasn't the reserves
of chakra he once had.
It's true.
He's grown old.
-Oh, are you all right, sensei?
Don't tell me you're
through already.
You?
The great sage who has mastered
all the jutsu of the Leaf
Village?
The legendary
professor and warrior?
Oh, I'm so disappointed.
[laughter]
-Lord Hokage!
Please get up.
You must!
Without you the Leaf
Village is lost.
Lord Hokage!
-Save your breath.
He can't help you now.
[chuckling]
-What's wrong with
you, Sarutobi?
Surely you didn't
summon me just for this.
To watch you crumble.
What are you waiting for?
Now is the time to defeat him!
HOKAGE (VOICEOVER): Orochimaru.
-Orochimaru, you're a fool!
-Huh?
[grunting]
ENMA: It's over.
I'm going to snap
you like a twig.
It should have been
done years ago.
[shout]
[grunting]
HOKAGE (VOICEOVER):
I should have known.
It's useless attacking
their bodies as long
as their souls are bound to
this earth by Orochimaru's will.
So be it.
I have only one weapon left.
The fourth Hokage's jutsu.
First lord Hokage,
second lord Hokage,
forgive me for using
it, but I must.
-What is it, sensei?
You look a little out of breath.
Long day?
You poor thing.
All you really want is to take
a long quiet nap, isn't it?
[chuckling]
-Why are you're laughing?
-Should I be weeping?
It's sad to see how
old you've grown.
You who were once hailed
as the Supreme Shinobi.
-Whoa.
-What the hell's going on?
Who or what is that?
-What is this?
Who the devil are you?
-You have lost it, old man.
Don't you recognize me?
It's me, Orochimaru.
-It can't be.
Then you've mastered even
that forbidden jutsu?
[chuckling]
-You're no longer human.
You're a demon!
[laughter]
SASUKE: I finally caught you.
Did you really think that
I'd let you get away?
-Oh, geez.
-If it isn't Sasuke Uchiha.
-This is as far as you guys go.
[theme music]
HOKAGE (VOICEOVER): You were
one of a kind, Orochimaru.
The most brilliant
and gifted ninja
in that time of
war and darkness.
In you I thought I had
found the one to succeed.
How blind I was.
What a trusting fool.
And it is that
blindness of mine that
has led to all this
pain and death.
It's time I corrected my
mistake and buried you forever!
NARUTO: Next time-- a
mistake from the past!
A face revealed!