[theme song in japanese]
-You think all these paper
bombs are just a diversion?
-That's right.
-It can't be.
-It could.
Genno is the man who
would go even further.
After all, he is
the Trap Master.
-Remember.
Think.
His actions till now.
What's the old man up to?
He steals the plans for key
facilities in the village.
Then pretends to blow himself
up in front of the Black Ops.
Meanwhile, a Super
S-Rank Alert draws
most of our Shinobi
away from the village.
Meaning that Genno's free to
look around wherever he wants.
But then why scatter
the stolen blueprints?
That's evidence he
might still be alive,
and everyone on the
outside is going
to come rushing back to the
village as quick as possible.
Why we he want that to happen?
Unless he gets us focusing
on paper bombs and draws
all the Shinobi
back to the village.
Maybe that was his
intention all along.
Could it be?
-The paper bombs in the
village were only a decoy?
-You don't see the paper bombs
right here in this cabin?
-Huh?
Are those-- all
these paper bombs.
What are you doing?
Tell me.
Do you know anything
of the geology
of these mountainside images?
-Geology.
What do you mean?
-It's important.
The nature of the rock from
which these images were carved
out, though the plateau
towering behind the Leaf Village
is composed of rock,
which is extremely dense,
it contains narrow fissures
running through it.
You see, it can be easily broken
if the right amount of force
is applied along those fissures.
The mountainside images were
created using this technique.
Today and 30 years ago
aren't the only times
I've come to the Leaf.
I've been in this
village several times
checking things
out very carefully.
Finally, my calculations
are complete.
I know just where
the paper bombs
must be set to thoroughly
destroy the plateau.
-Huh?
-Nobody would think of attacking
the mountainside images.
We're in the middle of paper
bomb disposal operations.
No, the images will be fine.
But if somehow
that whole plateau
was to crumble and fall--
-Which means that the Leaf
Village [loud explosions]
would be buried
under earth and sand.
The Village Hidden
in the Leaves--
-Will be crushed.
-Hmm?
-Choji, we've got
to tell the Hokage.
-Hmm?
-We've got to make sure that the
guys returning don't come back
into the village.
-Shikamaru, good news.
Guy sensei and the others
have just returned.
-Hurry up.
Now that Might Guy
is back, the enemy
is going to have to
change its plans.
-Ah, we're too late.
-Why?
What is the problem?
-Shikamaru, Naruto needs us.
-Huh?
-Why do that?
Why destroy the whole village?
If you do it, it will mean the
lives of innocent people, too.
You want that?
And every building you ever
worked on will be gone forever.
This is so wrong.
If revenge is what you're
after, I'm telling you,
it's not going to work.
It never works.
Not like that.
OK, you listen to me, old man.
I'm here to stop
you in your tracks.
-Impossible.
-No way I'll let you
set those bombs off.
-You're wrong.
The fate of this
village was sealed
the moment you set
foot in this cavern.
Even if you can defeat
me, the triggering device
will activate the
second you leave here.
It would appear that
everyone has come back now.
All that's left is to activate
the triggering device.
And now the Hidden
Leaf Village will
suffer the same devastating
fate as the Heat Devil Village.
-Sorry, old man, I
won't let you do it.
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
-Too late.
It's no use.
The idea of a boy like
you disarming all my traps
is inconceivable.
-Yeah, you're right.
It would be next to
impossible if I was alone.
But luckily, I've
got my friends.
-These would be the same
friends you did nothing but hurl
insults at and
badmouth Ichiraku?
-Yeah, I get in plenty of
fights with those guys,
and they still can't
tick me off sometimes,
but they're my
friends all right.
They are all Shinobi who will
help me protect the Leaf.
No matter what
weird traps you set
or where, they'll manage
somehow, and there's nothing
you can do about it.
-Then I had better wrap this
up before they have the chance.
Now defend yourself.
--[inaudible] Cutting it a
little close aren't you?
Kiba, Akamaru.
How did you find me?
Ha, you can thank
Hinata for that.
She thought it was strange you
just bug out for no reason.
So she used her Byakugan
to search for you.
-But even the Byakugan
shouldn't be that effective.
You did very well to find us.
-Nah, we had a pretty good
idea where to start looking.
Shikamaru got it
in through his head
that the final trap was in
the mountainside images.
-Shikamaru did?
-Interesting.
Well, I guess I may have been
taking my young opponents too
lightly after all.
-Yes, you seriously
underestimated us.
Are these insects?
-That's right.
You're finished now.
-Aaagh.
Get down, you two.
[explosion]
-Move in.
-He blew himself up.
-No, he didn't.
-Huh?
-It's a substitution.
It seems he switched just
before being devoured.
-And now it's over.
What is this?
-Heh-heh.
-It's the Shadow Strangle Jutsu.
-You figured out my plan?
-Yep, checkmate, old man.
No you just come
right over here.
Choji, get a hold of him.
-With pleasure.
Oh, no, the Shadow.
Shikamaru, what did he do?
He must have had himself rigged
so that a smokescreen would
be triggered if we touched him.
Choji, on the right.
-Human Bullet!
-Now the Leaf
Village is finished.
-Oh, no, is that--
-But why?
Why didn't it explode?
-Yeah, tough luck.
We already disarmed
that paper bomb.
-And all the devices you set
up in the mountainside images,
we disarmed those as well.
-Just give it up, old man.
It's over.
-That's right, end of the line.
-Fleeing is useless.
-No matter how
incredible a Trap Master
you think you might be,
our teamwork is going
to beat you every time, old man.
Just face it.
-I could no more give up
than I could stop breathing.
-Aw, get real real, will you?
No matter what you may have set,
you know we're going to get it.
-How could I show
my face to my son?
-What?
-Huh?
Where'd he go?
-He's over there.
It seems you haven't disarmed
all my explosive devices.
So at last, I win!
--[inaudible] it's
going to be crushed.
-Calm down.
Don't be fooled.
It's just a [inaudible] Jutsu.
Release.
-Naruto.
-Summoning Jutsu.
-Oh.
-He's getting away.
-Leave it to me.
Mind Transfer Jutsu!
All right.
It worked.
-Neena?
-Hey, why'd you break the Jutsu?
-What's the matter?
-The pain was just too much.
The old man's body is--
-What?
-He's putting himself
through all this fighting
while his body in agony.
-You will not escape.
Naruto.
-Alas, I am no match
for such a strong master
of the taijutsu form.
-I cannot agree
with you there, sir.
On the contrary.
You're a recorded accomplished
practitioner of taijutsu.
-That was amazing.
I can't believe it's over.
-I am afraid it's not.
-Huh?
-What do you mean?
What do you mean it is not over?
-Where's that big bird
he summoned earlier?
-Huh?
-Look, over there.
A paper bomb's on his foot.
-What?
-The image of the third Hokage.
I concentrated on the
crack running through it.
The device I used on it was
different from the others.
The rock there is even more
unstable than the other areas,
so I set up an explosive device
targeting that vulnerability.
If there is an explosion
there, the other paper bombs
will go off at once,
because of the shock
wave generated by the first one.
-He set a paper bomb up there?
-And we overlooked it.
So that's why you
summoned that big bird.
It's the trigger that's going to
set off a string of explosions.
At long last, my wish
is finally coming true.
-It is here.
-OK.
It dodged them.
-Clearly, we'll
never bring it down
by attacking from long range.
-I'm going to defend the
Leaf Village no matter what.
I'll just have to blow him
away with my [? rasengan ?]
before he lands.
Shadow Fall Jutsu.
-[inaudible] Jutsu.
-Gotcha.
No worries, Naruto.
-Thanks a bunch, Choji.
Hinata.
-Well, Shikamaru
suggested I read the birds
in movements with my Byakugan
and give you directions.
-Huh?
-The rest is up to you.
-OK, ready when you are.
-Right.
Byakugan.
Not yet.
Let it come a little closer.
-Here we go.
I'm going to do it.
I'm going to protect the
same village [inaudible]
risked his life to protect.
-Naruto, now.
Go.
-Well, thank god.
Hey, where'd it go?
-Above you.
-Hold still.
-You're not getting away.
-Aaagh- hah.
-Oh, god, what was
that all about?
-All right.
-Aw, yeah.
We did it, Hinata, we did it.
-Yeah, we sure did.
-He's all beat up inside.
Incredible.
It's amazing he lasted
as long as he did.
-Old man.
-Such a shame I wasn't able
to leave my mark on history.
But I did have fun.
-Huh?
What do you mean you had fun?
Come on, wake up, old man.
What did you mean by that?
Please.
Stay with me.
-Naruto.
No.
It's not.
My son, proud as a peacock after
feeding me at a treasure hunt.
Treasury hunt?
-Did anyone notice?
-Huh?
-Throughout this
whole thing there
hasn't been one casualty
in the Leaf Village.
-Huh?
-Old man, Genno, come on.
Come on, open your eyes.
Old man, Genno.
-I figured it out, Shikamaru.
The boy in this
picture is Genno's son.
-Genno's son?
-He followed in his
father's footsteps,
and became a Shinobi.
But lost his life when the Leaf
invaded Heat Devil Village.
-Apparently, Genno
was seeking vengeance
for the death of his son.
That's why he did this
to the Leaf Village.
-To begin with,
maybe, revenge might
have been his first
motive for coming here.
But then--
-Hmm?
But then what?
-Something was
kind of bugging me,
so I check out the
explosive device
that had been set in the
academy one more time.
The circuit was broken, So
it wouldn't have gone off
even if the trigger
had been hit.
-You don't think he might
have just made a mistake?
-Genno was a master
at setting traps.
It's unlikely he'd make a
simple mistake like that.
-Um-hmm.
You have a point.
-The same with the traps
in the mountainside images.
A number of defective
devices were purposely
mixed in with the paper bombs.
Even if the whole darn
thing had gone off,
the damage would probably
have been only a few cracks
to the carvings.
-So then he never
seriously intended
to destroy the Leaf Village.
-Then, what was he doing?
-He was on a treasure hunt.
-Huh?
The whole thing was
a treasure hunt?
-Yeah, it makes a
lot more sense if you
look at it in that light.
He started out planning
to destroy the village,
but he changed his
mind after meeting
Naruto who's the spitting
image of his son.
I'm sure the old
man probably knew
he wasn't going to be
living much longer.
So he decided that
whatever time he had left,
he was going to have
some fun with it.
He probably wanted to recapture
the feeling of treasure hunting
with his son having us search
through all the traps he
had set.
-So that's what it was.
-Well, of course, it's
all just a theory.
-So that old man wasn't
necessarily a bad guy?
-I knew it all the time.
It's like I've
always said, anybody
who likes Ichiraku
Ramen can't be all bad.
-Huh?
I remember the guy
saying he didn't
like eating ramen all the time.
-Well, Ichiraku
Ramen is different.
-Um-hmm.
-There's no way you can go
through life with something
you hate being on
the menu everyday.
You are so right.
-Old man.
-Naruto.
-When enemies come to
the Hidden Leaf Village,
it's not always going to be
as easy as it was this time.
Someone like Orochimaru will
always be waiting in the wings
to attack us for real.
-That just means we gotta
make sure we're always
ready for anything.
-Right.
-But it's such a drag.
We gotta keep our strength up.
-This is our duty.
To protect the Hidden
Leaf Village, all of us,
working together.
[theme song in japanese]
-Thanks for your
support everyone.
-As a small token
of our appreciation,
our next episode is kind
of special with someone
who hasn't appeared for a while.
And some great battles, too.
-Whoa.
What's that about?
Sounds great.
-Make sure you're
tuned in for it.
-So who's our special guest.
-It's a secret.
-You won't even give me a hint?
Our next episode is the
top five Ninja battles.
And if you miss it,
you're going to feel silly
when you don't have a
clue, but all your friends
know what happened.
So don't miss it.