[theme music]
-This guy.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
This isn't going
to be easy as long as
he stays like this.
But I have no choice.
Gotta save my friends.
It's all up to me.
Light Versus Dark, The
Two Faces of Gaara.
[laughter]
-And that's exactly
why you can't win.
As long as you fight
for the sake of others,
you'll never advance
beyond this level.
Only one can remain
undefeated, and only he
will feel what it's
like to truly exist.
Forget your friends,
and fight for yourself.
-You're insane.
Forget my friends?
-The trivial feelings like
friendship and loyalty
cloud your focus,
and you'll die.
-Yeah, yeah, keep
talking while you can,
cuz I'm about to shut
you up once and for all.
-You don't understand
what real strength is.
-I'm taking you down!
[groaning]
-Why?
Why, Yashimaru?
Why did you do it?
I don't understand.
Tell me why.
-Love is the heart's desire to
serve someone precious to you.
To watch over them.
To care for them, like
my sister did for you.
[sobbing]
After all, you're
special, Gaara.
I hold you very dear to me.
-I thought, Yashimaru,
if I'm precious to you--
how could you?
-It was an order.
You see.
I was ordered to
kill you, Gaara.
By lord Kazekage, your father.
-My father?
[sobbing]
Why me?
Why would my father?
YASHIMARU: You were born with
the Shukaku, a living sand
spirit, inside you.
All these years you have
been watched and studied
as part of a great experiment.
It became clear
that you could never
control it, the Shukaku that
possesses the power of the sand
itself.
The day is coming when
your existence would
be too dangerous
for the village.
It had to be done before then.
-You-- you had to
obey my father.
You didn't have any choice.
-You're wrong.
I had a choice.
Yes.
Lord Kazekage made his
wishes known to me,
but I could have refused
if I had chosen to.
I suppose it's because deep in
my heart, I hate you, Gaara.
I've always hated you.
My sister died bringing
you into this world.
I can't forgive you for that.
I told myself that you were
all that was left of her.
And since I loved her,
I should love you.
I tried, but I never could.
It wasn't her
choice to have you,
to be made a human sacrifice.
And so she died
cursing this village.
The day she died, I
felt a wound in my heart
that I knew would never heal.
-Unlike an injury
to the body, there's
no medicine for a wounded heart,
and sometimes it never heals.
-A wound to the heart?
-Your name is the one
your mother gave you.
Your name is Gaara, the
demon that loves only itself,
as you must love no one else.
Care for no one's
existence but your own.
Fight only for yourself.
In that way you will
be sure to survive.
This is the dying gift
your mother left you,
but not out of
maternal affection.
It was not from love that
she gave you your name.
It was from her undying
rage at this village.
It was part of her curse that
you should survive and grow.
[whimper]
Her hate lives on in you.
You were never loved, Gaara.
Never.
But now, this is the end.
[sobbing]
-There's no question that my
sister and always loved you.
[crying]
The sand automatically
rushes to protect you,
just like the love of a mother.
I believe your mother's
will is carried
in every grain of that sand.
[sobbing]
It's love, Gaara.
YASHIMARU: Love no one else.
Care for no one's
existence for your own.
Fight only for yourself.
-So that's Gaara.
Me.
I understand now.
I'm alone.
I'll no longer care about
anyone and love anyone else.
I'm all alone.
I am all that matters.
[roaring]
What's the matter?
Why don't you attack?
Don't you care what happens
to your precious friends?
[groaning]
-Sakura!
Let her go!
HOKAGE (VOICEOVER): Naruto's
just standing there.
That's not like him.
Why's he hesitating?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
I've got to find a way
to save Sakura no matter what!
But how?
That's it!
This is gonna use up a
heck of a lot of chakra,
but it's time to bring
in the Chief Toad!
-Huh?
-Summoning jutsu!
-What is it?
What do you want, kid?
Well, whatever it is, I hope
you brought along some treats.
Cuz of you think I'm doing
anything for nothing,
you're wrong!
-Oh, give me a break!
I'm really starting to
hate you stinking frogs!
-Oh, ho-ho.
Anti-amphibian, huh?
Well, take that, you big bigot.
-Listen.
I don't have time to play
games, you slimy little squirt.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
I can't believe it.
After all my training,
this is the best I can do?
I'll just have to make it work.
I'm the only one
who can save them.
-Worried about the others?
That's your big mistake.
When I fight, I fight
for me and me alone.
[groaning]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
He's transforming again.
-Only by attacking and
defeating me can you free her.
And you should hurry.
With each passing second
the sand will harden.
Until it crushes her to death.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Sakura.
TEMARI (VOICEOVER): He's
getting closer and closer
to a total possession.
And if that happens,
none of us will survive.
[growl]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Those eyes!
-Sand Shuriken!
-Ah!
Yoink.
[grunting]
-Wow.
Boy, are you pathetic.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Shut up.
-So-- uh-- who the heck
is this freak anyway?
-I'll grant you this, sensei.
You're very persistent.
Why doesn't it move?
Why are you so hard to
kill, you old buzzard?
-Have you forgotten
already, Orochimaru?
I told you before.
The village hidden in
the leaves is my home.
And I am the central
pillar of that home.
-A pillar?
-You're nothing but a rotten
old stick that's about to fall.
-As long as there
is one villager who
will fight for his friends, lay
down his life for his fellows,
this pillar will stand.
The village will survive!
-We shall see.
-Heh.
Don't underestimate the Hokage!
It can't be.
Impossible.
You must have used up almost
all of your chakra by now.
-That is not how you
measure strength.
True strength comes
from more than chakra.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Eyes full of loneliness.
I've seen that look before.
In myself.
Now he's turning into
a monster, like me.
I remember how I hated
them, because they
hated me and I couldn't
understand why.
I wondered why I even existed.
-The fox spirit that
killed Iruka's parents
and destroyed our village
has taken over your body.
You are the Nine-Tailed Fox.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
That's when I found out
I had this demon inside me.
It wasn't my fault, but
everyone acted as if it was.
That just made it worse.
But then--
-Hey.
How about we take a
ramen break, Naruto?
-Yeah!
Great idea!
With extra barbecue pork!
-Pfeh.
You're such a
loser, I don't even
know why you bother training.
-I don't need training!
I could clobber you right now!
-So, did Sasuke say anything
about how he feels about me?
-No.
Uh-uh.
-Oh.
-But, Sakura, If you want to
know how I feel about you,
well-- uh-- wait!
Where are you going?
What's wrong?
Aw.
Time to chow down!
-Naruto, you won't live
long on ramen, beans,
and barbecued pork.
If you want to be
a ninja, you've
got to eat your vegetables.
You know.
The green stuff.
Like this.
-Bleh!
Green's about my
least favorite color!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): A
few people came along
who paid attention to me.
That made it better.
It was all right
then, even though I
had this monster inside me.
Even though everyone else
acted like I didn't exist.
Because it meant that
I wasn't alone anymore.
For the first time in a long
time, I was happy again.
Really, really happy.
They made me remember
how good life could be.
They made me glad to be alive.
But when I think back to
where I was before I met them,
it's scary.
Nothing but pain and darkness.
What would I be like if I
had stayed there all alone.
That's how come I
can understand him.
GAARA: It's all a
distant memory now.
Why do I exist, I
used to ask myself.
And then I found out.
I exist to wipe out every
other existence than my own.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I
don't know how it happened,
but this guy's been
there all alone
in that same bottomless
pit of darkness and pain.
He's still there.
That's why he has no one.
He fights only for himself.
Maybe he's right.
Maybe it's made him stronger.
Maybe it is a weakness to
have friends you care about,
to know what happiness is.
Can I really win
against a guy like this?
[groaning]
-What's the matter?
Are you afraid of me?
Or are you still thinking of the
best way to save your friends?
Fool.
Forget them.
Think only of yourself.
Love only yourself.
That is what it means
to be the strongest.
What's wrong?
You were so bold
and cocky before.
Show me your strength.
Let me grind it into
dust before your eyes.
Attack, you coward.
Fight me or I'll kill
the girl right now.
[grunt]
-OK!
You asked for it!
Multi-Shadow Clone jutsu!
-Wind Style!
Sand Storm Devastation!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
He just blew 'em away.
Not good.
-I think I'll toy
with you a while.
I'll watch you
abandon your friends
and beg for mercy
before you die.
-Naruto.
-What-- what the?
[chuckle]
-And again!
[grunting]
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
Come on, Naruto.
-What-- what's this feeling?
-Sand Shuriken!
[grunting]
-What's this-- this strange
feeling getting stronger?
-He-- what's he doing?
-Flowing through me
as if I was on fire!
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): Naruto.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
I see it now.
I can't lose.
-Weakling.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
I have to beat him.
Even if it kills me!
[theme music]
NARUTO: All right!
Anyone who's ever
doubted me, anybody
who thought I was joking when
I said I'd be the next Hokage,
well sit back,
shut up and watch.
Cuz I'm gonna give this
guy a demonstration!
He's about to see my best work--
Transformation jutsu, Summoning
jutsu, Shadow Clone
jutsu, you name it!
They don't call
me the number one,
hyperactive, knucklehead
ninja for nothing!
He won't know what hit him!
Next time-- Naruto's
ninja handbook.
Believe it!