-Summoning jutsu!
-Hey.
Long time, no see.
-Sorry, but we don't
have time for small talk.
We've got a mission.
-That's the Village of
Artisans, unless I'm mistaken.
-Yeah.
The village has a
reputation for creating
some of the finest
ninja tools around.
They're used throughout
the five great nations
because of their high quality.
But rumors have been
swirling around lately.
-What kind of rumors?
-Something about them
developing an ultimate weapon
to attack the five
great nations.
-Uh-huh.
So then our mission is
to infiltrate the village
and conduct a search to
find out whether or not
this ultimate weapon
really exists, right?
-You got it.
-Just leave it to us.
[theme song]
-[laughing]
-Hey, listen.
Something's weird.
-W-what do you mean?
-I mean the entire
village is deserted.
But I found something
even stranger than that.
-What?
-There it is.
-The coffin of Seimei,
the founder of the Village
of Artisans.
But where's his body?
-You see?
This is seriously weird.
-So they took everything
and abandoned their village.
But where did they go?
-Ugh, if I don't get
something to eat soon,
I think I'm gonna fall over.
In fact, I'm gonna
go all out and have
them put two eggs
in my ramen today!
[laughing]
Huh?
[scream] What the heck?
-I hope you haven't
been waiting long.
-Not at all.
I just got here a
few minutes ago.
-That's good.
Here you go.
I wanted to make
sure you got it.
-Yeah, right.
Why do I always get stuck?
-[laughs]
-Hold it right there.
-Hm?
-What do you think
you're doing sneaking off
for a secret
rendezvous like this?
Did you think I wouldn't
find out about it?
-Naruto!
-Huh?
-How?
How could you do this?
Sakura, after all the
times I've asked you out!
-What are you talking about?
Have you completely
lost your mind!
[growling]
-You mean it's just an errand?
-Yeah.
A new poison was
just discovered,
so Lady Tsunade sent me with
this list of ingredients
to give to Shikamaru's dad so he
could analyze them in his lab.
-Oh, man.
-You really shouldn't
jump to conclusions.
-Guess you're right.
-Oh, I forgot to tell you
guys that Lady Tsunade just
received a status report from
Temari and the Hidden Sand
Village.
-What kind of status report?
-Yeah, what's up?
-Well, I guess the Hidden
Sand Village has recently
started a ninja
training program,
and they've adopted the
same curriculum as the Leaf.
The only thing is Temari
and her two brothers
are going to be the instructors.
-They're what?
-How did someone
as mean and nasty
as her get to be an instructor?
-Really?
So Gaara's there too, huh?
-Before you begin
combat training,
you must first
choose a weapon that
suits you both
physically and mentally.
Yes?
-I'm sorry, but is it
absolutely necessary
that we all choose a weapon?
-Huh?
-Uh, why do you ask?
-If all of us have
weapons, there's
a chance we'll end up
hurting each other.
Someone could get killed.
-Your weapon is like--
-Huh?
-Forget it.
It's not important.
-This isn't a game
you're playing.
-If you were to go into battle
with that frame of mind,
you wouldn't survive.
-Uh, I'm sorry.
-Hey, if you're
going to make Gaara
mad by asking stupid questions
like that, you're on your own.
-For your combat
training, you'll
be working in a
group with one of us.
You may choose which instructor
you want to work with.
-I don't know.
-Gaara, would you smile already?
Don't look so mean.
Lighten up.
No one will want to
be in your group.
-I hear my dad telling someone
that Gaara was the Hidden Sand
Village's ultimate weapon.
-Whoa.
-They say if he
gets mad, he could
destroy the whole village.
-He's scary.
I don't want to go in his group.
-All right!
I'm with Temari!
-Yeah, me too.
[chatter]
-It's really awesome.
She's got fans--
-He's the better
leader, isn't he?
-Cool.
-He was about to tell
us something earlier.
-Excuse me.
Will you be my sensei?
-Are you sure you want that?
-Please teach me.
-Hmph.
-What's your name?
-Uh, it's Matsuri.
-Matsuri.
You must choose a weapon.
-[scream]
-What's the matter?
-Uh.
-I want you to
attack me with that.
Attack like you want to kill me.
-Yes sir!
[scream]
-Beware a demon
with an iron club,
but that doesn't apply to you.
-Yes, sir.
Then which weapon do you
think would be best for me?
-Hm.
-This is called
the rope javelin.
-I've never heard of it.
-The sharp blade at
the end of the rope
is not meant for offense.
Its purpose is to keep
enemies at a distance, which
allows you to use the rope
to incapacitate your enemy.
You must practice
until the rope becomes
an extension of your body.
-Yes, sir.
-Who the heck are you?
-Is this all the Sand
Village shinobi have got?
-Hang on.
We'll let this one live.
He'll be a useful tool
in drawing our man out.
-What happened?
Kankuro, be be careful.
Who did this to you?
-Please.
Gaara.
He's-- you've gotta hurry.
-[scream]
-What's wrong?
-When I was young, I
stood by helplessly
as my parents were attacked
by so many weapons.
It's just so hard now.
-Tell me your reason
for wielding a weapon.
-Huh?
-I remember.
-Who are these two?
Who are they to you?
-Those guys are-- they're my
friends, that's what they are!
And if you even think about
hurting them any more than you
already have, I promise
I'll take you down!
-I'll never forget his face
when he said those words.
-That's Gaara.
He's the one we're after.
-It's a good thing
you showed up, Gaara.
We were just coming to get you.
-One of the ninja patrols
was attacked by somebody.
-They had strange weapons, and
they referred to themselves
as the Four Celestials.
They said to tell
Gaara-- tell him
that we know he's
the ultimate weapon,
and we issue him a challenge.
If you don't accept
the challenge,
they'll take someone
close to you.
They'll keep taking
one person a day
until everyone you
care about is gone.
-Hey there.
You're Gaara's
student, aren't you?
I'm sorry, but you're going
to have to come with us.
-What's this doing here?
-Hold on.
Must be headed northeast.
-Matsuri was the first to go.
-But you know as well as I
do that Matsuri means nothing
at all to the Four Celestials.
They want you.
-Yeah.
-We must notify
the Jonin Council.
-They have identified themselves
as the Four Celestials,
and they've headed
to the northeast
to a small strip of land
between the Land of Rivers
and the Land of Fire.
It's near the Leaf
Village, so I've
asked them to assist us in this.
Temari, Kankuro,
and Gaara, you're
to leave immediately and
track these criminals down.
-That doesn't make sense.
They've already told us
that they're after Gaara.
If he comes with us, it
would be like walking right
into their trap.
-He's right.
It makes more sense
to send another unit.
-This might just be a
diversionary tactic.
If we sent an entire unit, the
village would be vulnerable.
-In that case, then, why
don't you come along with us?
Well?
-The enemy is obviously
after the Shukaku.
Gaara is the Sand's
ultimate weapon.
-If we already know
that, then why?
-Although he is powerful,
the ultimate weapon
is also a double edged sword.
If they destroy each other,
they'd be doing us all a favor.
-It seems the least I
could do is go with them.
-No.
This is something they
must do without your help.
I have another mission
that requires your skills.
-Are you coming?
Well?
-Sorry, but I'm afraid
there's another mission
that requires my attention.
Go.
After all, the captive
is your student.
-[growl]
-Come on, then.
Let's get moving.
-You think this girl's
going to do the trick?
-Why would he care about a kid?
-So what do you think?
Will he come?
-He'll come, because he
knows if he doesn't, we'll
just keep picking off those
close to him until he does.
-That looks like--
-Hm?
From the Sand Village?
Oh my gosh.
-Gaara?
Why?
-We're not sure yet.
The four challenged
Gaara and then took off.
The hostage is a girl he'd
taken on as a student.
They grabbed the girl
and then took off
from the Land of Rivers heading
toward the Land of Fire.
As of now, only Gaara,
Temari, and Kankuro
have been assigned
to pursue them.
I'm afraid that's
all the information
we have at this point.
-So based on that, I'm
supposed to set up an operation
to track down these arrogant
idiots who want Gaara?
-Yes.
It's important we maintain
our relationship with the Sand
Village.
-But they've given
us nothing to go on!
-They had even less
information to go
on when we asked
for their assistance
during the Sasuke incident.
-You can't compare this
situation with that!
It would be a different story if
we knew where they were going.
We could set up an ambush.
-None of the Jonin or
Chunin are available.
They're investigating
the Artisan Village.
Shizune.
-Right.
-You may select any of the
Genin who are on that list.
Time is of the
essence, so you need
to gather them together and be
on the road within 30 minutes.
-What about Sakura?
I don't see her name
anywhere on the list.
-No.
She's involved with her
medical ninjutsu training now.
-I'll accept the mission.
However, I have one condition.
-What?
-Let me borrow
Sakura for this one.
-Why Sakura?
-I thought I was
always the late one.
What are we waiting for?
Let's get going!
-We're still waiting
for one more.
-Oh no.
Don't tell me it's--
-Huh?
-Sorry!
Couldn't leave on a mission
with an empty stomach,
so I stopped by Ichiraku
for a bite to eat.
-That's no fair!
How come you get to eat?
What about--
-All right.
Now that everyone has finally
arrived, let's get moving.
-Huh?
What?
You've got to be kidding.
I heard this was
some big mission,
and all the Genin in the village
have been assigned to it.
-Everyone is here
who's supposed to be.
-Oh, that's messed up!
I mean, I know Sakura has
training and all, but what
about Shino, Neji, and Hinata?
Shouldn't they be here?
-That's true.
I noticed that Akamaru and
I are the only ninja here
with any scouting abilities.
-So what you have
organized is a no nonsense,
take action group of ninja.
-That's right.
In fact, I'm calling this
Team Return the Favor.
-Huh?
-That's so lame.
-You guys remember when the
Sasuke incident went down?
The Sand Village was right
there to help us out.
So now we're
returning the favor.
You got a problem with that?
-Come on, guys!
Let's go return us a favor
from a long time ago!
-In case you've forgotten,
you're not in charge.
-[bark]
-We'll take our orders from
Shikamaru, the squad leader.
-Ugh.
Whatever!
But we gotta hurry up and decide
on a plan so we can get going!
What do you think?
Should we use the same strategy
as from when Sasuke left?
-Ahem.
There are definitely
similarities
to the Sasuke incident.
However, I believe
this pursuit and ambush
will require different tactics.
The trail's cold, so
Byakugan and Akamaru's nose
won't be as much help this time.
-I hadn't thought about that.
-I know it's unconventional,
but it's our only choice.
We'll break up
into squads of two,
and you'll work together
as a single unit.
You don't leave your partner
under any circumstances.
We'll pay back our debt
to the Sand Village,
but I don't intend to
pay it with our lives.
You all need to watch
yourselves out there.
-Right.
I wouldn't have
it any other way.
-Ino, you'll be with me.
-You got it.
-Choji, you go with Kiba.
-I'm counting on you, Choji.
Let's go.
-All right!
-[barking]
-Lee, you're with Naruto.
-Right!
Please refrain from
any indpendent actions.
-You don't have to talk to
me like I'm a little kid.
-The four people Naruto
mentioned earlier
have already gone ahead.
-Four people?
You mean Shino, Neji,
Hinata, and Sakura?
-Yeah.
They've been sent on
a different route,
and won't be participating
in the battle.
-Why the heck not?
-Isn't that sacrificing
a lot of our firepower?
-We'll conserve our
strength while they
search for the enemy.
And once the battle begins,
they can focus their energy
on healing the wounded so
that we can keep on fighting.
I had to think long and
hard about this strategy,
and your lives depend on it.
-All right!
Just you wait, Gaara!
I'm gonna make sure
I return that favor!
[theme song]
TEMARI (VOICEOVER): One of
them's a wind user, huh?
This is going to be fun.
She can deal with me.
KANKURO (VOICEOVER): Fine, then.
I'll take the guy who's
swinging around the sword that
looks like a toy.
TEMARI (VOICEOVER):
All right then.
Go ahead, Gaara.
GAARA (VOICEOVER):
Will you be all right?
KANKURO (VOICEOVER):
Don't worry about me.
These guys aren't worth
breaking a sweat over.
TEMARI (VOICEOVER):
Hurry up, Gaara.
She is your student, after all.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Next time, Sand Alliance
With the Leaf Shinobi.