[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Deadlocked!
Sannin Showdown!
-How you doing, daddy?
-Uh oh, he's looking at us!
Watch out!
Yo, Gamatatsu!
Time to skiddaddle!
-Say what?
But it's just getting exciting.
-Shut up and get moving!
-Manda, Orochimaru,
Katsuyu and Tsunade.
The dear old faces
reunited once again.
Did you bring a hanky, Jiraiya?
I think I'm going to cry.
-You old fool.
I didn't summon you here
after all of this time just
to listen to your stupid jokes.
This rivarly's gone
on long enough.
It's time to end it.
Today, I'm putting
Orochimaru out
of our misery once and for all.
-Well, Orochimaru, why
have you dragged me here?
You know I don't
like being summoned.
Maybe I should just eat
you and be done with it.
-No.
Please don't talk
that way, Lord Manda.
You'll be well rewarded for
your trouble, don't worry.
-Who do you think you're
talking to, you little bug?
What would the likes of you
have that I could possibly want?
Bah!
So, Orochimaru,
when this is over,
I'll expect 100
human sacrifices.
KABUTO (VOICEOVER):
If Manda finds out
that his master can't
use any of his jutsu,
he's more than
likely to betray us.
This was a mistake.
No matter how hopeless
things looked,
he never should've
summoned Manda.
Not in his condition.
-Katsuyu, see to the boy.
Take him to Shizune quickly.
-Yes, my lady.
At once.
-There.
I'm ready!
-Shizune, Please
look after the boy.
-Naruto.
-The battle t come promises
to be a most fearful one.
You and this clone
of myself must
take the boy somewhere safe and
see that no harm comes to him.
This is the wish
of your mistress.
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER):
Lady Tsunade.
-I'm going to pop
you like a balloon,
you stinking dirty toad!
-Then please, come
on and try it.
I've always wanted
a snakeskin wallet.
-Orochimaru, you're no
longer fit to be one of us.
Your evil days are
finally at an end.
-One of us?
What an insult.
-After this, there'll be one
less Sannin in the world.
-Acid Slime!
-I'll start with you!
-Now, Katsuyu!
-Yes, my lady.
-They're coming!
-I can see them.
-Tsunade!
Keep back!
Time for oil, Bunta!
-You got it.
-Fire Style, Toad Flame Bomb!
-Hm.
That did it.
-You think?
No.
Too easy.
Of course.
He just shed his skin.
Bunta, look out below!
-Yeah, I feel it.
-His tail?
Huh?
-There.
Take that.
OROCHIMARU (VOICEOVER):
Fighting one
Sannin would be hard enough.
But two?
-Tsunade!
-I've often wondered
what it would
be like to wring that
pretty neck of yours.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): No chakra.
Can't get lose!
-You say you can't be
killed by a blow in battle,
but what if I keep squeezing
the life out of you
as quickly as you can
regenerate it, huh?
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): I
haven't the strength.
How long?
How many more seconds
can I keep this up?
I can't give in!
I have to give it
everything I've got!
OROCHIMARU (VOICEOVER):
Impossible!
-Come on.
I'm just getting started!
Take this!
Damn it.
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER):
No, Lady Tsunade!
Not that.
She's reached the
end of her strength.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): After all
that, he's still conscious.
What do I have to do?
-Everyone has their limits.
Yes, even you.
-Shut up!
Can't rest.
Can't let up for a second!
This is the big one!
Where I bet it all!
Where I put my life on the line!
-Lord Orochimaru!
-Oh no you don't!
This isn't over 'til it's over!
Hold still!
(VOICEOVER) I keep pounding
him and pounding him,
but something's wrong.
Why don't I feel like
I'm getting anywhere?
No matter.
This will finish it.
Give my regards to hell.
KABUTO (VOICEOVER):
Insane strength.
And he took the
full brunt of it.
-It's over.
-Yeah.
-Lord Orochimaru--
-He made me clumsy and careless.
I'd eat you both
right now, but I
won't be swallowing
solid food for weeks,
thanks to this hole in my mouth.
But if we meet again-- well,
he'd better hope we don't.
-Huh?
-Tsunade-- so, you refuse
to heal my arms, do you?
Very well, then.
I don't need you.
There is one other way.
And I will destroy
the Leaf Village.
Depend on it.
I hope we'll all meet again
very soon when I once more walk
among you.
Until then, my dear old friends.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): His face.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
That explains it.
Someone else's body.
That explains the feeling
I had as we fought,
that he was different somehow.
-When I return with
the Elixir of Life,
I'll show you what it
means to be truly immortal.
-We'll meet again.
-Wait!
(VOICEOVER) With cracked ribs
a broken foot, I'm useless.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): The
side effects of the jutsu
are kicking in.
Already, my body is--
-Tsunade, you never could
recognize a fool's bet
when you saw it.
-To be Hokage.
That is my dream!
-I'll give you one week.
If you can master that jutsu
by then, I'll admit I'm wrong,
and that you're worthy
of becoming Hokage.
I'll even throw in my necklace.
-Yeah, I'll show
you who's stupid.
Just you wait!
Give me three days, and I'll
have that jutsu down flat!
-Ha!
Watch what you say, kid.
I might just hold you to it.
-After all, I'm the
grandson of the Hokage
who built the Village
Hidden in the Leaves.
-Remember, like you
always say, a man
never goes back on his word.
-Right.
And I give my word, I'll follow
our grandfather's footsteps
and be just like him.
To be Hokage.
That is my dream.
-I love this village and the
people in it with all my heart.
I want to protect them.
It's all that's kept me going.
To be Hokage.
That is my dream.
-Dan-- take this.
I want you to have it.
The jutsu's side effects.
Lady Tsunade--
-Huh?
I see.
-It's all right.
If I rest a bit, my younger
form will be restored.
I'll go into town.
Then, when Naruto's
recovered, we
can head back to
the Leaf Village.
-Tsunade--
-No more first names.
You know what you've
got to call me now.
NARUTO: What?
The Fifth Hokage?
-Mm-hm.
-Unbelievable.
I'm out of it for a few minutes,
and I wake up to find out
she's the Hokage.
-Is, uh, something
bothering you, Naruto?
What's wrong?
-Come on.
Shouldn't the Hokage be kind
and wise, and everything?
Like the old man used to be?
And she's-- well,
mean and greedy.
And with a nasty temper.
And she's not all that smart.
Nothing personal or
anything, but it's a big job,
and I'm not sure
if she's up to it.
-Right, well, Lady Tsunade, are
you ready to order something?
-On top of that, she's
a 50 year old lady
who uses jutsu to look
like a young woman.
I just wonder if we really
want a Hokage like that?
You know, someone
who's living a lie.
-You want to take
this outside, kid?
-Hm.
(VOICEOVER) Here we go.
It's deja vu all over again.
-I may not be anyone's idea of
perfect, but I am Hokage now.
And even though I
shouldn't dirty my hands
on a little squirt like you,
one finger's all I'm gonna need.
-Not this time, grandma.
And stop calling me squirt!
Right now, I'm just a kid, but
I'll be Hokage myself one day!
-Oink.
-You asked for it!
No.
Not the forehead again.
-You'll grow up
to be a fine man.
And a great Hokage too.
-You bet!
-Oink Oink.
-OK.
Let's go home, everyone.
To the Leaf village.
-Whoa, wait a second!
I haven't eaten yet!
[laughing]
NARUTO: Hey!
What's so funny?
I've been unconscious.
I'm starving!
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): Do
you see him, Nawake, Dan?
Be at peace, my beloveds.
Your dream is still alive.
In him.
[theme music]
NARUTO: This is the life!
A little R&amp;R. Pervy
Sage is happy,
and Grandma Tsunade
is off somewhere else,
so I'm happy too!
I mean, I deserve a
vacation after what
I've been thr-- Uh oh.
Trouble in paradise.
Somebody trashed my room!
Why?
Oh, this is great.
I finally get a little downtime
and all heck breaks loose!
I'm gonna end up needing a
vacation from my vacation!
Next time, Kidnapped!
Naruto's Hotspring Adventure!