[music - Asian Kung Fu
Generation, "Far Away"]
-I will-- I will be Hokage.
I will.
-And how you gonna do that?
By lying flat on your face?
I got news for you.
I'm gonna be Hokage!
-Transform!
[laughter]
-You've been here
three years and can't
do a decent transformation?
-I don't have to
pretend to be Hokage.
You just wait!
Some day I'm gonna
be Hokage for real.
Then you'll be sorry!
-Yeah, right.
On what planet?
Come on.
Do you really believe a weakling
like you could be Hokage?
You must be weak in the head.
HINATA (VOICEOVER): No.
You're wrong, Kiba.
-Sorry, but-- you can
forget about being Hokage.
Because I'm the top
dog around here.
Surprise attack--
Naruto's secret weapon!
-You're kidding.
You're a real glutton for
punishment, aren't you?
OK.
It's your funeral.
I'm gonna make sure
you don't get up again.
Let's go, Akamaru!
-How many times are you
gonna use that move?
-Just once more!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Man, they're fast.
-Fang Over Fang!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): The
same trick as before.
And it's working
just like before!
It's like fighting in the dark.
I've gotta find a way out.
Or else--
-Ha!
Looks like you've
run out of gas, kid.
-Yeah?
Bring it on, dog-breath.
'Cause no matter
how many clones of
yourself you make,
I'll still have enough
gas to beat you!
-Ha!
You always got a
snappy comeback.
Let's see you come
back from this!
Ready, Akamaru?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Gotta
find a way to counterattack.
Problem is, I don't now
which one to attack!
Which one's the real Kiba?
I can't tell them apart!
-What's going on?
I can't see.
HINATA (VOICEOVER): Oh, Naruto.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Wait a second.
That's it!
Transform!
-Here we go!
-Very clever.
-Huh?
-Wait.
You'll see.
-Whoa.
Perfect!
Good one, Naruto.
Brilliant!
-It's genius.
He's made himself
look like Kiba,
so now Kiba doesn't know
which one to go after.
He's got to be careful, because
he might be attacking Akamaru.
-And meanwhile, Naruto is
safe attacking either one.
Brilliant idea!
Woo-hoo!
-He's got him
completely stymied.
Ha!
-OK.
So I see you've gotten better
at the transformation jutsu.
But you forgot one little thing.
I admit, you look just like me,
and that threw me for a minute.
But I still know
which one is you.
You can't hide from me.
Wanna know why?
I can smell you, kid.
There's just no getting
past our sense of smell.
Tough luck.
KURENAI (VOICEOVER): By
concentrating his chakra
in his nose, Kiba can make
his sense of smell 1,000 times
more sensitive than average.
It's easy for him to distinguish
people by their scent.
-Game's over.
SHINO (VOICEOVER):
What happened?
Kiba's nose got them mixed up.
But how?
KIBA (VOICEOVER): No way.
It's impossible.
So it's you!
Messing with me!
What?
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
Well, this is
coming from the original
class clown, after all.
KURENAI (VOICEOVER):
Kiba was fooled.
-Atta boy!
-That was just amazing!
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
I get it now.
Ha!
Way to use your head, Naruto.
When Kiba saw through his
disguise and sniffed him out--
he had the presence of
mind not to reappear
as himself but to transform
again, into Akamaru.
And that made Kiba forget
all about his sense of smell.
He believed what he saw.
And that's when he
lost his advantage.
-Who would have thought
the Naruto I used to know
could ever be that smart?
-Little squirt.
-The smart shinobi is careful
how he uses his jutsu.
Otherwise it's liable to
come back and bite him
on the butt, dummy!
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
Hey, that's my line.
Sort of.
KIBA (VOICEOVER): Arguing with
this kid is a waste of energy.
I can't play his game.
Gotta keep calm.
Keep calm.
OK.
I still have the advantage.
I'm a lot faster than he is.
He can't keep up with me.
All I have to do is watch for
an opening, slip in behind,
and take him down with
my All Fours jutsu.
That's right.
No worries.
If I just keep my head there's
no way I lose this match.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
Careful, Naruto.
Your opponent has
calmed himself down.
So what's your next move?
-So, are you finally
getting serious, Kiba?
Good.
That means it's time to
unveil something special
I've been saving.
My super-secret killer move!
-Your what?
You gotta be kidding me.
-Huh?
Where'd he come up with that?
-You can leave it to Naruto
to have a trick up his sleeve.
Well done!
-Ha!
Super-secret killer move.
Get outta here.
It's a bluff!
-Yeah?
Well, try me and find out!
KIBA (VOICEOVER): Come on, Kiba.
Don't let this punk get to you.
Just stay calm.
Stay in the game.
-You ready?
-Whatever he's got
in mind, I'll just
make sure he doesn't
get a chance to try it!
Beast Mimicry-- All Fours jutsu!
Well, what are you waiting for?
-No, Naruto!
-Naruto!
-I knew this kid
couldn't hack it.
-On your feet, Naruto!
-He's coming at me so fast.
I don't have a chance
to build up my chakra.
-Hey, what's wrong?
Just gonna stand there?
-Man, he's fast.
-Too fast.
Naruto can't make
his hand signs.
SHIKAMARU: (VOICEOVER) Too fast.
Too strong.
Naruto's out of his
league against this guy.
HINATA (VOICEOVER): Oh, Naruto!
-Take this!
I will be Hokage.
I will never lost to
you or anyone here.
-Dream on, kid.
How can you beat me when
you can't keep up with me?
Hey, kid!
Heads up!
-Naruto!
-You wanted me to get
serious, so I got serious.
You get it now?
You were just kidding yourself.
You never even had a chance.
Huh?
-I absolutely will not lose.
Guess that means
you're out of luck.
-I'll give him one thing.
The kid doesn't give up.
-Mm-hm.
-Naruto's like a bad cold.
Kiba just can't seem
to shake him off.
-Come on.
I don't care who
it is, I just wish
someone would win
this match already.
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
Come on, Naruto.
Hang in there.
-Atta boy!
Look at him.
He's starting to crack.
You've got him right
where you want him.
-Now, Naruto!
Go for it!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): This
guy's gotta have a weak spot.
I just have to find it.
Hey, what are you waiting for?
You tired?
-You're a scrappy little
squirt, I'll give you that.
KIBA (VOICEOVER):
He's on his last legs.
This next one oughta do it.
-That's enough of this.
It's time to unveil
my new technique.
-Go for it!
Too late.
I got you now.
[fart]
[sniffing]
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): Who said
Naruto had run out of gas?
The poor guy's jutsu
lead him right into it.
-And with his sense of smell
1,000 times more sensitive than
average--
-Oh, nasty!
Ugh!
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): Was that
his new super-secret killer
move?
I wonder.
He always was unpredictable.
-Whatever works, Naruto!
You slowed him down, at least.
-I wish I could
say I planned it.
But anyway, the time has come
to unleash my new technique.
Shadow clone jutsu!
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
What's he going to do?
-You've kicked me around
pretty good so far.
Now it's payback time!
-Well?
-Uzumaki Barrage!
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): Hm.
A new technique?
I'd say he picked that
up from watching Sasuke.
-Lion's Barrage!
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): At
least he changed the name.
Sort of.
-The winner is Naruto Uzumaki.
-Woo-hoo!
-Yes, Naruto!
That's my teammate!
Way to go!
-Unbelievable.
Who would have thought
he could beat Kiba?
-A major upset.
-Mm-hm.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
I can feel it.
I'm getting stronger.
Ha!
It was nothing.
Piece of cake.
HINATA (VOICEOVER): He's coming.
What do I do?
-Na-- Naruto.
-Huh?
You say something?
Hinata?
-I-- thought-- maybe--
-Huh?
KURENAI (VOICEOVER): Hinata?
Well, well.
-Uh-- what's, uh-- this?
-It's a healing ointment.
-For me?
What for?
-Take it, Naruto.
Go ahead.
-Thanks, Hinata.
That's, uh-- real nice of you.
KURENAI (VOICEOVER): You have
nothing to be ashamed of, Kiba.
Who could have imagined he
would be such a strong opponent?
NEJI (VOICEOVER): Silly Hinata.
Not a care in the world.
[music - Rythem, "Harmonia"]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): This Neji
has always gotten on my nerves.
Acting like he's so
superior to everybody,
like he's some kind of
royalty or something.
OK, Hinata.
It's time to take
him down a peg.
Come on, you can do it!
Show him that just
'cause you're quiet
and a nice person,
that doesn't mean you
can't knock his block off!
Next time-- "Byakugan
Battle: Hinata Grows Bold!"
My money's on Hinata.