[music playing]
[music - Asian Kung-Fu
Generation, "Far Away"]
-Let me do you a favor and
end this battle quickly.
-You can't end it
if I end it first.
First strike, [inaudible]!
-Huh?
Nnngghh!
-Whoa!
What's up with that guy's body?
That's freaky!
I wish I could do that!
-I dislocate every one of my
joints, softening my body.
Then with my chakra, I
can control it perfectly.
-With just his chakra?
Whoa.
-The more you struggle,
the tighter I'll squeeze.
I don't know what you're
carrying in there,
but as long as I have ahold of
you, it makes no difference.
I could break your neck
right now if I wanted to.
And I will, unless you give up.
-Heh.
You wanna bet?
-You wanna die?
-You fool, you're the
one who's gonna die here.
[snap]
-I think he broke his neck.
-Huh?
-What's the big deal?
[sigh]
MISUMI (VOICEOVER): Tsst.
What a fool.
Too bad he didn't surrender.
Oh, well.
[crackling]
Huh?
[gasp]
-Now it's my turn,
so say goodbye.
[grunting with effort]
MISUMI (VOICEOVER):
This is just a puppet,
and the real ninja was
in there controlling it!
He's a puppet master!
-He controls it with
chakra from his hand.
[strangled cries]
-Enough.
I give!
Aaaahh!
-But if your bones
are all crushed,
just how much more
flexible you'll be.
[coughs]
Vo: That was close.
I almost stopped the
match in the middle.
But it's a good thing I didn't.
-Unnh!
-Because his opponent
is unable to continue,
the winner is Kankuro.
-Two against one is hitting
below the belt, isn't it?
I mean, is that thing
even fair, Kakashi-sensei?
-It's not really
two against one.
It's a puppet,
not another ninja.
-Yeah, it's just a
Puppet Master jutsu.
He's controlling the
puppet with chakra.
It's a ninja tool,
like a shuriken.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Everyone
here wields their chakra
perfectly.
And I thought my chakra
abilities would give me
an edge over the others.
So much for that idea.
SAKURA AND INO (VOICEOVER):
Kuroichi Rumble:
The Rivals Get Serious.
-[gasp] Mm.
Ino.
-You sure are jumpy, Sakura.
I know why.
I mean, even Sasuke collapsed.
And it's probably
just 'cause he's
so great that that's
all that happened.
Frankly, I don't
even want to imagine
what'll happen to
you if you compete.
I think it's best if
you quit, don't you?
It's pointless.
That won't work on me.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): If
I made it through that,
I can make it through this, too.
-I won't quit.
Not ever.
In fact, I can't wait.
Hyahhh!
Bring it on!
[coughing]
-Now let's continue.
It's time to begin
the fourth battle.
[digital beeping]
-Well, no matter who's
picked, it'll be two weirdos.
This contest is
chock-full of them.
-Well, you're one to talk.
-Yeah, good point.
People
-Hey, gimme a break!
[giggles]
-Ahem.
This isn't a time for laughter.
-Huh?
[gasp]
-I never thought I'd fight you.
Or at least I didn't think
it would happen this soon.
Don't expect me
to go easy on you.
ASUMA (VOICEOVER): Ino was
a stand-out among the rookie
female shinobi, so she
has a good chance to win.
But with Sakura as
her opponent, can she
bring herself to fight
hard enough to do it?
-Of all the people for
Ino to go up against,
it would have to be Sakura.
What a mess.
-I know.
I hope Ino will be OK.
Vo: Let's all hope.
So what's it going to be, Ino?
-Go, Sakura!
You can do it!
Don't lose!
-Begin.
-Yah!
-Oh no!
I just knew it.
-Sakura's totally
blowing Ino out
of the water in this battle!
-What a fool.
-What did you say to me?
-You wanna make something of it?
Then go ahead,
'cause you'll lose.
-Who do you think you are?
NEJI: That's it?
That's as good as Kunoichi can
get at hand-to-hand combat?
-What?
-It's not because they're
girls, you know, Neji.
-Huh?
-It's just that those
two are using kid gloves.
It doesn't matter if you're
a man or woman in battle.
-Huh?
Uh, using kid gloves?
-Unh!
[gasp]
[smack]
-Kunoichi have a
special role to play.
They must learn not
only ninjutsu but also
a wide range of knowledge
and refinement as women.
If you can't blend
in to enemy territory
by adopting the customs
of the women there,
you'll never be able
to succeed as a spy.
In any event, today's
class is flower-arranging.
-Hm?
TEACHER: Now then,
everyone, go into the fields
and gather distinctive flowers.
STUDENTS: Yes, ma'am.
SAKURA: Ino!
Wait up!
-Wow.
What a klutz.
-I'm just not very good
at this kind of stuff.
What about you?
-Hmph.
That's not good,
considering you're
named after a cherry blossom.
OK, look.
It's simple.
I'll explain it, all right?
The first thing is, find a
main flower for your bouquet.
Then you find other flowers
that complement the main one.
You see, flowers have to
highlight each other's beauty.
There's really nothing to it,
once you know all the tricks.
For example, look.
Uh?
INO: You see those cosmos
flowers over there?
Well, if they were the main
flowers in your arrangement,
then the thoroughwort
flowers you picked
would complement them.
-Oh!
-Cosmos flowers are also
called autumn cherry blossoms,
and they're the prettiest
flowers in the fall.
Their name comes from an
old word that means harmony.
They can harmonize with
all the other flowers,
and any autumn grass would
go just perfectly with them
in a flower arrangement.
-Uh-- mm.
-So, tell me, do I look as
pretty as the cosmos flowers
now?
Come on, am I cute?
-Uh, yeah.
-Sheesh!
Took you long enough to say it.
[giggles]
-Well, well, you
sure look like you're
having a lot of
fun, Billboard Brow.
Hah!
You know, you're still nothing
but a helpless little girl,
Sakura.
So don't go strutting around
like you're hot stuff, got it?
[cries out]
-Aah!
Aaaahh!
[thud]
-Fami!
INO: Sorry!
That head of yours is so empty
that I mistook it for a vase
and thought I'd better
put flowers in there.
-Ino!
-It's aconite, a shinobi flower.
I guess it really
isn't that poisonous,
but still, you might
want to spit those out
when you get a chance.
-Uh?
[screaming]
[giggles] I forgot to say
only the root is poisonous!
[giggles]
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Ino is so great!
She knows practically
everything.
Her clothes are so stylish,
and she's way cute.
She's even good
with her shuriken.
And her ninjutsu
is awesome, too.
Compared to that, I'm nothing.
-Hey, what's wrong?
-Ino, if you're a cosmos flower,
then am I just a thoroughwort?
-Mmm.
[sigh]
Now why would you say that?
-Uh--
well, let's see.
Actually, I don't think you're
a flower at all, Sakura.
You're still a bud,
waiting to bloom.
--[laughs nervously]
Yeah, you're right.
-All right, listen up, Ino.
I'm not going to fight
with you over Sasuke.
-What did you say?
-I'm not the weak,
needy girl I used to be.
You're not even on my
radar, and you're not
Sasuke's type, Ino-pig!
-Sakura, you'd better
watch your step!
Do you have any idea who
you're mouthing off to?
Don't press your luck with
me, little Billboard Brow!
-Did you hear that stuff?
Sakura was so mean!
That's out of line, isn't it?
She sure made Ino mad.
I've never seen
her look so scary.
-Hmm.
Yes, but there's
more to it than that.
-Huh?
-Sakura isn't the kind
of person to do things
like needlessly flaunt her own
power, callously hurt people.
But she also doesn't like
having Ino take pity on her
and pull her punches.
-So I'm a bud that
hasn't flowered, huh?
Say, um, Ino?
-Sorry, what?
-Why did you give
me this ribbon?
What's it supposed to mean?
-Well, actually,
let's just say that I
thought it would be a real
big waste for you to wilt away
as nothing but a bud.
I mean, how said is it if
flowers don't ever bloom?
[wind whistling]
For all we know,
that little bud--
it might become a flower even
more beautiful than a cosmos.
[giggles]
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Thank you, Ino.
Thank you.
-Hey, come on.
We gotta finish our assignment.
SAKURA: Oh, OK.
INO: What's wrong, Sakura?
SAKURA: Um, I got some
dirt in my eye when I fell.
INO: [laughs] You're so clumsy.
[giggles]
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Ino, all along,
I've tried to live my life by
what you said to me so long
ago.
I thought that if I tried
hard enough, I could do it,
that I could become a
beautiful flower instead
of a bud always waiting
but never blooming.
So I set my sights
on you, because I
wanted to be like
you from the start.
You set an example
for me that gave me
a goal to strive toward.
And it's because of that that
I made it as far as I did.
It's why I'm here today.
But now I don't want
you to hold back.
It's time I surpassed you.
But if I don't face your very
best, then there's no point.
-What-- what in the
world is going on?
-What do you mean?
-Why are those two
getting so worked up just
looking at each other?
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): Hm.
He just can't see
that he's exactly
the same way when
it comes to Sasuke.
-Well, Naruto, rivalry
is a tricky business.
Not that I would know.
-Hm?
-[laughs] Oh, hi there.
MIGHT GUY (VOICEOVER): Ugh.
What else would I expect
from my old rival Kakashi?
Yet another glib,
senseless statement.
Man, it burns me up
when he acts so cool!
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Guess what?
I got put on the
same team as Sasuke.
-So why are you
telling me this now?
-I won't lose to you.
Not anymore, Ino.
-Sounds like a good idea to me.
And no matter what happens,
I won't lose to you either,
Sakura.
OK?
INO (VOICEOVER): The ribbon!
SAKURA: I'm giving this back.
-Hmph.
That's a gift.
It's to hold your hair back.
I mean, that headband's
really supposed
to go on your forehead, right?
-From here on, I'm
no longer someone
who's going to chase
after you, Ino.
When this goes on
my forehead, then
that's when I'll become--
I'll be a true shinobi.
[wind whistling]
INO: That's a good plan.
Me too.
-Until then.
-Heh.
I understand, Sakura.
SAKURA AND INO (VOICEOVER):
This time, we do this right.
No holding back.
A fair fight.
And I'm going to win!
-Rrraahhh!
-Aah!
-Whoa!
[gasp]
[music - rythem, "harmonia"]
INO (VOICEOVER): When did
Sakura get this strong?
This'll be harder
than I thought.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): As
I expected, Ino's great.
But I won't lose.
I absolutely will not lose!
INO (VOICEOVER): I
can't believe it!
We're evenly matched now!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I'm
not who I used to be.
I'm better, stronger!
SAKURA AND INO
(VOICEOVER): The next blow
will decide this battle!
INO (VOICEOVER): Next time,
the Ultimate Battle Tchah!
I won't lose this battle, even
if it's the last thing I do.