[theme music]
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): No matter
what darkness may await me,
I will meet it head on.
And whatever happens,
I will get that power.
It's getting pretty late.
What was that?
I could've sworn there
was someone there.
The lights.
It's too early for
everyone to be in bed.
What is this?
Wha-- What is going on?
What is happening?
Uncle.
Auntie?
Oh no.
Father and mother.
Father?
Mother?
[shuffling]
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
Somebody's in here.
Move.
Father!
Mother!
Big brother!
Itachi!
Father and mother are
both-- I don't understand.
Who could do all this?
Wait a sec.
What are you--
What have you done?
Big brother!
-Foolish little brother.
I almost pity you.
Mangekyo Sharingan.
[scream]
-Stop it!
Itachi, why are you
showing me all this?
Why-- why did you
do this, brother?
[scream]
-Auntie!
Uncle!
Why?
Why did you do this?
Itachi, why?
-To test the limits
of my ability.
-To test your ability?
That's why you did this?
You're telling me that was
why you butchered them?
-It is of great importance.
-What are you saying?
[shout] You're out of your mind!
I'm scared.
I'm scared!
[scream]
Please,
I don't wanna die!
It's a lie.
This isn't like
you, big brother.
It can't be.
-I have acted like
the older brother
you desired for one reason.
Because I wanted to discover
how powerful you were.
I needed to find
a worthy opponent
to test the limits
of my own abilities.
You have that unique potential.
Now I've made you hate me.
Now you have the
desire to defeat me--
which is exactly what I'm
going to allow you to live.
Don't you see?
It's all for my own benefit.
Like me, you may
be one of the few
who can use Mangekyo Sharingan.
But there is a catch.
Take the life of
your best friend.
You must kill him.
-That's a lie.
-Kill him.
Just like I did.
-Do you know anything
about Shisui Uchiha
ending his life in Nakano River?
-Shisui was the other guy who
never turned up at the assembly
yesterday.
It's funny.
If I remember correctly,
you kind of looked up to him
like an older
brother, didn't you?
-You're saying that was you?
Itachi, you killed Shisui?
-I did.
How else do you think I
obtained these powers?
In the main hall
of Nakano Shrine,
underneath the seventh
tatami mat from the far right
is the clan's secret
gathering place.
There you will find
a secret document.
An explanation of the
Uchiha clan's jutsu.
It tells of the visual
jutsu's true purpose.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): What?
The true purpose?
-If you discover
how to activate it,
you will be the third person
to obtain the Mangekyo
Sharingan, including myself.
To ensure that happens, that's
enough reason to let you live.
Well, that's all.
Oh, don't worry.
You're not worth killing.
My foolish little brother.
If you wish to kill me one
day, in hate and revenge,
surviving such an unsightly
manner as this, by all means,
flee.
Cling to your wretched
life, and then, one day,
when you possess the same
eyes, come back and face me.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): A dream?
Yeah.
That's what I heard, too.
That boy was the only one
who survived the massacre.
-Someone said they think
he has an older brother.
Is that right?
-Yeah, he does, but no one
knows where he is right now.
-Oh.
-I can't believe it, that the
elite Uchiha clan could just
be--
-Hello there, Sasuke.
What tasty treats can
I get for you today?
WOMAN: Good morning, Sasuke.
Heading off to
school now, are you?
-Ah huh.
-I saw your brother earlier.
He's grown into such a man.
He's an excellent
shinobi, isn't he?
Graduating the Academy
the age of seven,
and first in his class.
And he was a Chunin
at 10, wasn't he?
-Yeah.
And he could use Sharingan
by the time he was eight.
-That's right.
How could I forget?
That boy is the pride
of the Uchiha clan.
No doubt about it.
-Sasuke, dear.
Welcome home.
Sasuke?
Hold on a minute.
-What is it?
-Mom?
[meowing]
SASUKE: He's only thought
of Itachi before now!
-Your older brother's your
older brother, and you're you.
But your father has always cared
very deeply about both of you.
ITACHI (VOICEOVER): In the
main hall of Nakano Shrine,
underneath the seventh
tatami mat on the far right,
is the clan's secret
gathering place.
-I see now.
So that's what it all means.
-What do you say, Want to go to
the candy store after school?
-Huh?
No way.
You can get away with that
stuff 'cause your mom's nice.
But if my mother found out
I didn't come straight home,
man, I'd be in some
serious trouble.
-Did you hear?
Apparently the entire
Uchiha clan was murdered.
-Yeah.
That's what my dad
was telling me.
-They say that Sasuke's
the only one who survived.
-Now then, that's my boy.
-When we're alone
and no one's around,
the only one he
talks about is you.
-I wish I knew what kinds of
things he said to her about me.
ITACHI (VOICEOVER):
If you wish to kill me
one day in hate and revenge--
-Brother.
No matter what
darkness may await me,
if it means killing you,
I will meet it head on.
And whatever happens,
I will get that power.
From this point on,
I am an avenger.
NEJI (VOICEOVER): Wherever he
is, Sasuke is in the darkness.
If we all stay
put here, we won't
be able to catch up with him.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Neji.
It's just like you said.
Sasuke is in the depths
of darkness right now.
He really wants to kill me.
I can't believe it.
What am I to you now?
We were comrades.
Or have you just
forgotten all about that?
Are you telling me that all
the things we did together
in Squad 7 mean absolutely
nothing to you now?
-No.
(VOICEOVER) And whatever
happens, I will get that power.
They weren't meaningless.
One thing was worthwhile.
Our friendship.
We became best friends.
-We became best friends?
Then why are fighting?
-I just told you.
Because we're friends,
there's far more
meaning in destroying you.
-I can't understand that.
But what I know is that for some
reason, you want to destroy me.
Right, Sasuke?
[theme music]
NARUTO: Sasuke, are you trying
to take me down for real?
What you told me
before, I don't know
whether you really
meant it or not.
Maybe it was just a lie.
Maybe I'm the only one who
thought we were friends.
If that's the case-- well, I
guess I'm completely pathetic!
Aren't I, Sasuke?
Next time, For A Friend.
[theme music]