[theme music]
-Summoning jutsu.
That just had to work.
What the heck is the difference
between a frog and a tadpole
anyway?
NARUTO: Live or die.
Risk it all to win it all.
-Come on, jump.
-OK.
-Look, Purvy Sage, can't you
act like you believe in me?
-He collapses again.
But I suppose it's no surprise.
For three weeks now he's been
getting through his training
on guts and determination alone.
-Lord Hokage?
-What is it Anko?
-I'm sorry.
But I'm--
-You're what?
Are you feeling guilty
that you returned alive
from the Forest of Death?
There's no need for that.
After all, you no longer have
a connection to Orochimaru,
right?
There's no ninja alive
today in the Village Hidden
in the Leaves who could ever
even hope to defeat him.
I, myself, probably
would not be his equal.
-I wish the Fourth
Hokage were still alive.
-You shouldn't say such things.
It's only because he
sacrificed himself and died
that our land was saved.
Besides, that's all in the past.
It's a story from 13 years ago.
He's gone.
And we can't change that.
We must do what we
can with what we have.
-Yes, sir.
-Very well.
I'm going out to
get some fresh air.
And, Anko, don't blame yourself.
PURVY SAGE: Come on.
Open your eyes already.
-Hey.
What was that for?
-Oh, that.
To knock sense into you
since you have none.
-I don't?
Look at you.
-You've been training
for three weeks.
And you're still at this level?
If you continue like
this, it's pointless.
-Hey, that's not true.
Give me a break.
I'm trying as hard
as I can here.
-Maybe you are.
Maybe you're not.
If you want to succeed
at this summoning jutsu,
then you must do it like
your life depends on it.
-What do you think
I've been doing?
I train every day
like I'm going to die.
If you have time to
complain about it,
teach me a trick to to do it.
-A trick?
Well, I don't know.
-What?
You're not going to teach me?
-You need to put
your life at risk.
-My life?
-That's right.
It's no joke.
Even so, are you
willing to do it?
-Of course.
I always risk my life.
There's no point in anything
if you don't go all the way.
-I see.
All right.
Follow me.
-So what the heck are we doing
at a place like this any way?
You're not looking for
more girls again, are you?
-Say, that's not a bad
idea at all, Naruto.
But, no, I'm not.
This is about bathing.
We must purify our bodies.
-Huh?
OK.
Something weirder than
normal is going on here.
-What a nice bath.
Oh, yeah, it's just like heaven.
Truly in heaven.
-Hey, Purvy Sage.
-I'm the Toad Sage.
-Yeah, well, whatever
you are, what
does taking a bath have to
do with the summoning jutsu
anyway?
Hey?
Hello?
I'm talking to you.
What?
What is it?
Why'd you stop?
-Hey, Naruto, tell me, is there
something you like to eat?
-Huh?
NARUTO: All right.
I'm going to eat.
This is great.
Why can't the training
be like this every day?
-Good.
Now eat up.
It may be your last meal.
-Huh?
-Oh, nothing.
Nothing at all.
Anyway, eat up.
Yeah, that's right.
Eat like there's no tomorrow.
-I don't know what's so funny.
And I don't care.
I got food.
Hit me, chef.
Seconds on that ramen.
-OK.
NARUTO: One more.
CHEF: Here you go.
NARUTO: This time
with barbecue pork.
CHEF: You got it.
NARUTO: Ah.
Oh, man, I'm stuffed.
Thanks a bunch, Purvy Sage.
He left?
-Thank you.
-I've never seen
anything so empty.
PURVY SAGE: So are you full now?
-Quit your messing around.
You were supposed to
treat me to that meal.
-You, fool.
I never said I'd treat you.
-But you're supposed to.
You're the grown-up.
-Say, Naruto, do you happen
to have a girl that you like?
-Huh?
-I asked if you
have a special girl.
You know, someone close to you?
-Well, I don't know.
I mean, kind of.
Sort of.
I guess you could
say I like her.
-So who is it?
-No one.
Just Sakura.
-OK.
Let's go see her.
Because you're going
to give her a big hug.
-What?
This is part of my training?
-Well, yeah.
I mean, it's close enough.
-Yes.
All right.
Let's go.
But, if I do hug her,
Sakura will-- no,
this is part of
my training, too.
I have to do it.
I have to be strong.
But of course, I'm also
going to be black and blue.
And Sakura won't want to
talk to me for a while.
But still, if I
want to learn how
to do this summoning jutsu
right then this can't be helped.
But Sakura's going to-- no.
But then again--
-Just go already.
-OK, what do you want?
-Um, well, you see--
-Look, if it's money you
want, you can just forget it.
I'm not giving you any.
-No, that's not it.
It's just I, uh--
Oh, man how can I say this?
If I tell her it's
for my training,
I'm going to get
wailed on for sure.
-If it's nothing,
I'm going home.
-No, no, wait a minute.
This is it.
This is my chance.
Here I come, Sakura.
-What do you think you're doing?
Back off.
-Ow.
Well, so much for that.
-Wooh.
What a punch.
Ah, yes, young love.
-Hey, if I do this, can
I really summon a frog?
-You bet.
Of course.
Absolutely.
Without a doubt.
-Are you sure?
-Is there anything else
you've always wanted to do?
-Huh?
Anything?
-What?
What are you--
-To tap into his enormous
chakra and use it.
I'm certain that it's
extremely difficult
to control that kind of power.
It's also true that Naruto's
body is too small a vessel
to contain the
Nine-tailed Fox's chakra.
It's likely that because that
chakra put such a burden on it,
Naruto's body normally
suppresses it.
If the key to drawing out
the Nine-tailed Fox's chakra
is danger and emotion, he has
to physically experience them
until he can learn to summon
the chakra on his own.
Please forgive me for what I
am about to do, Fourth Hokage.
-Where-- where are we?
Tell me.
-Stand up.
-What?
What's going on?
-Your training ends right here.
-Huh?
But I haven't done anything yet.
-Naruto, starting now you
must stare death in the face.
-Death?
-That's right.
To stave off the
horror of death,
you must release
enormous chakra.
Once you experience
that, you'll understand
how to release the red chakra.
If you don't wish to die,
do something about it.
Now.
All right, Naruto.
Now we shall see if the strength
that's been given to you
is a blessing or a curse.
-If I don't grab onto
something, I'll die.
Now.
-It is impossible, Naruto.
You have to recognize that.
The rocks are too slippery.
And falling at that speed, with
the limited control of chakra
that you possess, you can't
possibly cling to the rock.
Naruto, you must see it.
You can only depend on the
chakra of the Nine-tailed Fox
now.
This time, you have to
turn the key yourself.
-If I go on like this, I
really am going to die.
Die.
-Today's history
class will be outside.
As you're all aware,
on this rock face
are the sculptures
of the Hokages.
They're in order from the left.
There's the First, the Second,
the Third, and the Fourth.
You probably could
have figured that out.
-The old man sure
looks different
up there than he does now.
I mean, he used to have hair.
-Iruka Sensei?
So who's the Fifth Hokage?
-That hasn't been decided yet.
Maybe it'll be your
favorite teacher.
-So working in an
occasional joke
to make for an engaging
history lesson, eh, Iruka?
-Oh, Lord Hokage.
-Whoa, it's the Third.
-Hey, old man, what
are you doing here?
-I just wanted to look at
the mountainside images,
like you students are doing.
-Well, you've come
at a great time.
Would you care to join me?
This is the man
whose likeness is
carved up there
on that mountain.
He's the great Third Hokage.
The Third Hokage was
called the strongest
and even considered a genius.
He was also called Professor.
-I am still here.
Talk about me in
the present tense.
-Yes.
Of course.
Sorry.
-Come on, are you really strong?
-Yeah, cause you don't look it.
-Yeah, that's for sure.
-Hey, stop it.
If you're granted
the title of Hokage,
it means only one thing.
That you're the strongest
in this entire land.
-Yeah?
Than I'm going to
be the Fifth Hokage.
I mean, I'm way strong.
And handsome, too.
-Well you won't make it with
the grades you have now.
-At least you have confidence.
Ah, just look at you.
You're all so young, unlike me.
There might be
someone among you who
will take the name of Hokage.
Remember, you have
just one life.
So don't choose a road
that's impossible.
It doesn't matter what you do
if you live and die as you like.
However, no matter what
route you end up taking,
remember to protect the people
that are precious to you.
-The people precious to us?
-That's correct.
The ones you appreciate the
very most and trust and love
with all your heart.
Do you have people
like that in your life?
-Mm-hm.
Yeah, I do.
My dad and my mom.
And my big brother, even
though I don't like him much.
Oh, yeah, and my
dog, [? gunta. ?]
-I have some, too.
My friends.
-Me, too.
-So do you have
people like that, too?
-Yes, I do.
Of course.
-Really?
Who?
-Well, I have my grandson,
Colonel [? hamaru ?].
And I also have all the
people in this village.
Just as it was for
you, back then.
NARUTO: What?
Huh?
[growling]
-This feeling.
It's the red chakra again.
[growling]
[roar]
-What is this?
What is this?
It's huge.
-Come closer, little boy.
-Um--
-How wonderful it would
be to kill and eat you.
But this accursed
gate confines me.
It's that infuriating
sealing spell.
-You're-- you're
the-- Nine-tailed Fox.
Of course.
The red chakra is
this guy's chakra.
-Why are you here, foolish boy?
What do you want?
Or have you simply come
to offer yourself to me
so I might feast
upon your marrow?
-All right, look you stupid
fox, you're in my body
and you owe me rent.
So for payment, I'll
take your chakra.
You got that?
[laughter]
NINE-TAILED FOX: Well, I
suppose I can't kill you, can I?
After all, if you die, I die.
Your courage is most
impressive, little boy.
Very well.
As a reward for making it this
far, I will loan you my chakra.
-This is it.
Summoning jutsu.
-Well done, kid.
-What's this?
Where in the world am I?
[theme music]
NARUTO: Yeah, finally I got
the summoning jutsu to work.
Listen, giant toad, from
today on, I'm your master.
Whoa.
OK.
Nevermind.
You know, what big boss,
you can be in charge..
Either way, I'm just glad
I pulled that jutsu off.
Next time, he flies,
he jumps, he lurks.
Chief Toad appears.
I got to say, this guy
is seriously scary.
I've never seen a
toad like him before.
[theme music]