[theme music]
-[yawning]
TAZUNA: You always is lazy?
Where's that weird blonde kid
and the one with the attitude?
-They're training
climbing trees.
-To tough for you?
-No.
In fact, I'm the best.
That's why the sensei
sent me here to guard you.
-You're joking.
-Tazuna, uh, I need
to talk to you.
-Uh?
What about?
-The thing is,
I've been thinking
a lot about the bridge.
And I decided I've push
my luck far enough.
I want out.
-Now you're going to quit
on me, just like that?
You're kidding!
-You know, I stayed on
because of our friendship.
But I'm putting my life on the
line every day I stayed here.
Gato and his thugs will
show up eventually.
-Hmm.
-When they do, they'll
kill you and the bridge
will never get finished anyway.
It's a lost cause, Tazuna.
Why don't we stop now
while we can still
get out of this alive?
-No chance.
This is our bridge.
Our island is poor, and
it will stay that way
until this bridge connects
us to the mainland.
Commerce, trade,
and hope-- that's
what we're building here.
-There's not going to be
much if we're all dead.
-It's already noon.
Let's break for lunch.
-Tazuna, let's not
end it like this.
-Save your breath.
Oh, and Giichi, don't bother
coming back after lunch.
NARUTO: The land where
a hero once lived.
Ahh!
Uhh!
Why is it so hard?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I'm not
going to lose out to you.
-Um, where are we going?
-You want to eat
tonight, don't cha?
I got to pick up some
things for dinner.
MAN: Theif, Thief!
-Oh.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): What's
wrong with these people?
TAZUNA: Here we are.
-Welcome.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
This is a store?
There's nothing here.
-Hehe.
-Whoa!
You pervert!
-No, no, I was--
TAZUNA: Wow, you really
surprised me back there.
Girls around here
don't fight like that.
-They should.
Something's
seriously wrong here.
Again!
Hey, buster!
-Please?
[giggling]
-Hmm.
Uhh, here.
-Aw, thank you.
TAZUNA: This is how it's
been since Gato came here.
The children suffer.
And the adults are afraid
to stand up to him.
They've lost all hope.
That's why we have
to finish the bridge.
It will bring
commerce and trade.
But much more importantly, that
bridge is a symbol of courage.
We must restore the
spirit of our people.
When the bridge is
finished, people
will start to believe again.
They'll believe that they
can live with dignity.
We can't let Gato stop us.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Sasuke,
Naruto, we have to help them.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
He's still climbing.
That's impossible.
SASUKE (VOICOVER): Damn.
He's catching up
to be inch by inch.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Ahh!
No, no, no!
If I think about Sasuke
I'll lose my concentration.
Believe it.
Come on, Naruto.
Center yourself.
Hey, you're good at this.
How about some advice?
SASUKE (VOICOVER): All right.
Chakra requires
spiritual energy.
So if you get all anxious
and frantic, it doesn't work.
You have to relax, and
totally focus on the tree.
That's how you get
a steady chakra
flow in the bottom's
of your feet.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Relax, focus on the tree.
Yeah, I can feel it.
I'm going all the way this time.
SASUKE: Hey, Naruto.
-Sasuke, what are you doing?
I was trying to focus my chakra.
SASUKE: Well, uh, you
know, the thing is--
-The thing is what?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
That's strange.
He never talks to me.
What's he up to?
-You-- you know you asked Sakura
for advice when she was here.
So what did she tell you?
-I'm not telling you.
[elephant trumpeting]
TAZUNA: Hahaha.
Hey, this is fantastic.
It's been ages since
we've had so many guests
around our table.
-(TOGETHER) I want some more.
Huh?
-Don't eat so much if
you're going to puke it up.
-I have to eat.
-And I have to be more than him.
It's the only possible way I'll
get strong enough to beat him.
-That's true.
But puking won't help you.
-Excuse me, this
picture is torn.
Is there some reason for that?
Inari, you kept glancing
at it all through dinner.
It looks like there was
someone else in the picture,
but they got torn out.
I mean, that's kind
of strange, isn't it?
-It's my husband.
-They used to call him
a hero in this land.
-Inari, where are you going?
Father, you can't talk about
him like that in front of Inari,
you know that.
-Inari's so-- I mean,
what happened to him?
-Hmm.
Is there a story behind this?
-He wasn't his real father.
He came into our family later.
And he brought so
much happiness.
He and Inari were very close.
In those days, Inari used
to laugh all the time.
But then, all that ended.
He never laughs
or smiles anymore,
ever since the day
everything changed.
The word courage was
stolen from this island.
We were left feeling
powerless, hopeless,
and Inari suffered the
most, ever since that day,
ever since it happened.
-Tell us.
What happened to Inari?
-First you need to know
about the man, his father.
The man who taught
us the word courage,
who was a hero in this land.
NARUTO: A hero, really?
-You can decide
that for yourself.
He came here about
three years ago.
-Pochi!
Pochi, no!
-That's not his name.
Starting today his
name is Shooting Star.
And he's my dog now.
-No he's not.
He's my dog and his
name's not Shooting Star.
I've had him since
he was a puppy.
He's my friend, and he
doesn't belong to you.
-Just shut up!
[pochi howling]
-See what happens when
you don't listen to me?
Now I'm not going to lift
a finger to help him.
OK.
You can let him go.
-Why did you do that?
My dog is going to drown!
Ha!
If he's your dog, then
jump in and get him.
Be a big hero and
save your friend.
After all that big talk, you're
not going to let him go under,
are you?
INARI (VOICEOVER): I've got
to jump in and save him.
I've got to, but--
AKANE: Haha, he won't even
help his precious little Pochi.
INARI (VOICEOVER):
I, I can't swim.
And I'm scared.
I'm sorry, Pochi.
-Hey, you made such
a big deal about him.
Go get him!
-I think you went
too far, Akane.
I mean, he could really
drown or something.
-Ahh!
Help!
Please!
-Forget about it.
-I don't know.
-You say one more word
and you're going in next.
Got it?
-I don't want to die!
-Pooch!
Pooch!
-Interestingly enough,
at that exact moment
Pooch figured out
how to dog paddle.
[dog howling]
-Pooch!
-Hey, Shooting
Star's running away.
Get him!
INARI (VOICEOVER): Oh, no.
I can't breathe.
KAIZA: Waking up, huh?
Finally.
I had a little talk
with those kids.
They won't bother you again.
Here, eat.
INARI (VOICEOVER): Am I alive?
Is this for real?
-Did you pull me out
of the water, mister?
-Have a bite to eat, first.
Then we can talk all about it.
Hm, I see.
Your dog abandoned you too, huh?
In my country, dogs
are very loyal.
They stand by their masters.
Then again, you abandoned
the dog first, so what can
you expect?
-I really wanted to save
him, but I just froze.
I was just so scared.
I guess that I just
don't have any courage.
-Hey, come on.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
You're a kid.
When I was your age,
I was scared too.
It's no big deal.
But always remember
this: live your life
so you have nothing to regret.
If you care about something,
protect it, no matter
how tough, no matter how sad,
you've got to keep trying.
Even if you have to put
your life on the line,
protect it with both
arms, never get in.
-His name was Kaiza.
A simple fisherman
who'd come here
from another land to
follow his dreams.
After that, Inari and
Kaiza were inseparable.
The boy had never
known his real father,
so you can imagine
what it meant to him
to have Kaiza in his life.
He looked up to him and
followed in his footsteps,
like a real father and son.
Kaiza spent more and
more time with us,
until he just naturally
became a member of our family.
And then when this town needed
him, he became something more.
-We've got trouble, Kaiza.
The flood gate's and
the water's rising.
If we don't stop it, the lower
district will be flooded.
-What?
-Father!
-Inari, get me some rope.
Hurry.
-Right.
MAN: See where the gate is?
We need to get a line out
there to pull it closed.
-A line?
You have to swim out
there to do that.
It's impossible.
No one can make it
through that current.
-If we don't do it, the whole
district will be wiped out.
It's the only way.
KAIZA: I'll do it.
MAN 1: Kaiza.
MAN 2: Don't be foolish.
MAN 3: You'll never make it.
-Father.
-Don't worry.
Nothing can stop your dad.
This is our village,
so we've got
to do everything we can to help.
KAIZA (VOICEOVER): If you care
about something, protect it.
Even if you have to put
your life on the line.
Protect it with both arms.
Never give in.
-Father, I know you can do it.
MAN 1: He made it.
He tied the rope on.
MAN 3: All right.
Let pull it closed.
MAN 2: Everybody, come on.
-From that time on, Kaiza was
considered a hero in this land.
He taught us all the
meaning of courage,
and Inari was so
proud to be his son.
But it wasn't long after that
Gato showed up and took over.
He terrorized the whole village.
Only Kaiza stood up to him.
Gato couldn't have a local
hero getting in his way.
It took his whole
gang to stop one man.
GATO: You overplayed
your hand Kaiza.
All that talk about
how you're going
to protect this village
with your two arms.
Those arms aren't much
worth now, are they?
Still got that defiant
look in your eye though.
Well my men will
get rid of that.
get to work on him.
-Get down there.
-[laughing]
KAIZA: [screaming]
GATO: Listen up.
This man has defied
the Gato Corporation.
He has disturbed the
order of this land.
His punishment is execution.
-[crowd murmurs]
-Let this be an example so no
one will dare stand in our way
again.
-Father!
-Inari don't.
-Do it.
-Father, no!
Daddy!
[explosion]
-You told me that
you'd protect me,
and this land with
both your arms.
You made me believe
you could do it.
But it was just a lie.
TAZUNA: Since then,
Inari has changed.
So did Tsunami.
And all our people.
We lost our will.
-Ha. there's no such
thing as a hero.
Only stupid kids believe that.
-What are you doing
down there, Naruto?
-You better take the day off.
No more training.
You've used too much chakra.
If you push any harder,
it could kill you.
-I'm going to prove it.
-Prove what?
-I'll prove that,
that it's true.
That in this world,
there are real heroes.
[music: Akeboshi, "Wind"]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Huh?
You want something lady?
I'm in training
right now, because we
don't know when Zabuza
will strike next.
See, I got the message
loud and clear.
You have to protect
you care about,
but to do that you
have to be strong.
I'm getting stronger every day.
I'll show Inari there
are heroes in this world.
Next time-- Battle
On the Bridge!
Zabuza Returns!
I'm going to kick
more butt than ever.
Believe it.