[theme music]
[chirping]
[sniffing] Uh-oh.
-What is it?
-Hey.
What's wrong?
You want to clue me
in on what's going on?
-Smells like they're in motion.
Sasuke along with two
of the other ones.
And they're moving fast.
Smells to me like
Sasuke's chasing them.
-Huh?
-You sure?
-But there are two more
still there not moving.
-So what?
Who cares about them?
We've got to catch up to Sasuke!
Come on!
-What is it?
What's the matter?
-The two that are left
are about to fight.
I can smell it.
-Huh?
Even if it means
losing some time,
we should go around
just to be safe.
-Are you crazy?
We don't have time to lose time.
So what if they're fighting?
Big deal.
I say full speed ahead!
-Oh, grow up, Naruto, will you?
Who knows what'll happen if we
get caught in the crossfire?
What we don't have time
for is to get mixed up
in someone else's
fight, no matter
how much you might
get a kick out of it.
-What are you talking about?
Who says I get a kick--
-Listen, kid.
Our mission is to
bring Sasuke back.
We should try and avoid
any fighting if possible,
let alone go out
and look for it.
Come on.
-Right.
Let's go.
-OK.
OK.
I'm coming.
KANKURO (VOICEOVER):
Puppetmaster jutsu.
-I am member of the Hidden
Leaf Village's Aburame Clan.
When we fight, no matter
how puny our opponent is,
we don't mock them.
We face them with full strength.
-Heh.
Bring 'em on.
[groaning]
-Temari.
Put me down.
-You sure you're
strong enough, Gaara?
[groaning]
Gaara!
TEMARI (VOICEOVER):
There's no telling
how long Kankuro
can delay Uchiha.
Every second counts.
-If we don't keep moving,
the whole plan will fail.
-Leave me alone, Temari.
Go away.
you are nothing but a nuisance.
Beat it!
I don't need you.
[groan]
NARUTO: Astonishing truth.
Gaara's identity emerges!
[grunting]
SHINO: Poison on the blade.
-It's no use.
TEMARI (VOICEOVER):
Sasuke Uchiha?
Did he get past Kankuro already?
No.
It was too quick Someone
else must have shown up.
-I have no idea what
scheme you Sand Village
clowns have got going, but I'll
stop it, no matter what it is.
Besides, I'm dying to
see what you really are.
[groaning]
-Gaara, no!
[gasp]
Oh no.
It's happening.
Any second he's going
to let that thing out.
No.
Not now.
Not now!
No, Gaara!
Remember our mission!
-We're so alike, Uchiha.
I don't have
friends as you have,
but they're not what
makes you strong.
It's your purpose that does it.
In that way we're alike.
You!
But mine is the
stronger purpose.
For only by
destroying you and all
you represent can I
even prove that I exist.
Only by killing you can
I know what life is.
-What is it?
-I sense a trace of
blood lust in the air.
All right.
Come on out.
So it's you.
-Tell me.
What Is your true purpose.
Why is it that you seek power?
-Like it's any
business of yours.
Beat it.
You're interrupting my training.
-I see it.
You have the eyes.
Eyes that seek power and
will do anything to get it.
Even kill.
Eyes full of hate like mine.
We're the same.
You.
You are my--
[screaming]
You
Are to my prey!
My prey!
TEMARI (VOICEOVER):
It's started.
-A substitution.
-You're making this too easy.
That did it.
Huh?
KANKURO (VOICEOVER):
Those damn bugs again.
-You made a clone of bugs,
then snuck up behind me.
Not too bad.
-It was simple really.
I can tell from your jutsu that
your strength is long range
attacks, not close combat.
Furthermore, you have to
focus all of your chakra
and attention on manipulating
that puppet of yours.
And that, of course, leaves
an opening in your defenses.
-Thanks for the dissertation,
but I'm just getting
started here.
Don't worry.
If you really want to see how
deadly my ninjutsu can be,
then you're in for a real treat.
You haven't seen half
of what Crow can do.
So far he's been playing nice!
-Huh?
Poison smoke bomb.
Must have inhaled some.
Meanwhile, the attacker
hides and waits
for it to take effect.
[panting]
-Listen, everyone.
Even if the enemy shinobi
do manage to get up here,
don't panic.
Just quickly get into
the hidden chamber.
Don't worry.
Your jonin and chunin
sensei are here
to protect you, even if
it costs us our lives.
-Whoa.
-What is it, Konohamaru?
-Don't worry.
It's not as bad as it looks.
Our people will
drive the enemy away.
-Mm.
[crackling]
-Lord Hokage's face
is beginning to crack.
IRUKA (VOICEOVER):
That's ominous.
KONOHAMARU (VOICEOVER): Grampa.
[groaning]
[panting]
HOKAGE (VOICEOVER): To have
come this far-- this far.
To have his cursed
soul in my hands
and not have the
strength to finish it!
This decrepit old body!
Is it not enough that
I'm prepared to die?
OROCHIMARU (VOICEOVER):
You might even
have succeeded, if you'd been
perhaps ten years younger.
[chuckling]
-Sarutobi, kill him now.
Because if you do not,
the village is finished!
Doomed!
Do you understand?
-Yes.
I understand.
[groaning]
-Never.
Foolish old man.
[groaning]
[gasping]
-Now.
Let me feel it.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): That eye.
The same eye as before.
[shouting]
Looks like I may not finish
this before you catch up
with me after all, Shino.
-The poison's spreading
slowly through his system.
Now to finish it.
KANKURO (VOICEOVER): What?
More bugs?
He shouldn't even be moving
with that poison in him.
-Huh?
KANKURO (VOICEOVER): Let me
put you out of your misery.
-What the?
What-- what's going on?
KANKURO (VOICEOVER): What
the hell's wrong with it?
-Huh?
KANKURO (VOICEOVER): No!
-It's no use.
He can't move now.
My friends have burrowed
into every one of his joints.
He's kindling now.
KANKURO (VOICEOVER): So
that's what he was after.
He wanted me to attack, so he
could get his creepy-crawlies
to infest Crow's body.
Now they're going after
my chakra puppet strings.
Why?
Right.
I forgot these
things eat chakra.
My strings are leading
the bugs right to me.
-Hm.
SHINO (VOICEOVER): He severed
his chakra strings himself.
-Heh.
Heh heh.
KANKURO (VOICEOVER):
What a sucker.
He doesn't know I can
reestablish control
over my puppet in
the blink of an eye.
It's what makes me an
expert puppetmaster.
And so what if Crow's
body is out of commission.
I don't need his body.
Every part of him
is a lethal weapon!
Looks like you
underestimated me, Bug-boy.
For the last time.
There's enough poison on
that to drop an elephant.
So, you're dead.
What the hell?
But how?
Huh?
These stinking beetles.
They are through my chakra
strings at the source.
[groaning]
-But how?!
I don't get it!
I was sure to cut the strings
before they could find me!
-And there's your explanation.
You were so worried about them
approaching from the front
that you failed to observe
the swarm of beetles
coming at you from behind.
All this time
they've been slowing
closing in on you,
drawn to your headband.
-Huh?
To my what?
-When I just swung
at you earlier,
I only pretended to miss.
What I really wanted
was to plant a beetle
on your headband.
[gasp]
-But that doesn't explain where
the rest of them came from!
-I hate having to explain
the same thing twice.
-Shino?
How did you find us?
-I planted a beetle on
you as you left the arena.
A female beetle.
She gives off a
very faint scent.
Nothing you could detect, but
the male of the species can.
-So then, this bug
crawling on my forehead--
-Is a female.
Yes.
[screaming]
-The poison-- it spread
through my whole body.
SHINO (VOICEOVER):
Looks like I may not
make it after all,
Sasuke Uchiha.
-Is he human or monster?
-Why do you hide, Sasuke Uchiha?
Do I frighten you?
[whimpering]
-Are you shocked
by my true form?
Come out, come
out, Sasuke Uchiha.
To live, I must kill.
And you are my prey!
[theme music]
SASUKE: Human or monster,
his speed and strength
are incredible.
Without my Sharingan to help
me predict his movements,
I'd already have been
chopped to pieces.
I can't stay on defense
forever, but how can I attack?
What would stop him?
Chidori?
Do I have enough
chakra to do it?
NARUTO: Next time--
Sasuke's decision.
Push to the edge!