[MUSIC - SNOWKEL, "NAMIKAZE
SATELLITE"]
-Ah, I haven't chowed down on
Ichiraku Ramen in like forever.
Thanks to all these missions
I haven't been at home much
lately.
-Yeah.
A bowl of ramen after
a mission is the best.
Spreading its noodly goodness
throughout your body,
revving you up.
-No kidding.
Feed me some ramen
and I'm ready to go.
Ramen!
Ramen.
-Sorry, closed for the day?
-No.
It can't be.
I fought my way through all
of those tough assignments
with nothing but dreams
of Ichiraku Ramen
to get me through the night.
-Hey.
That smells like ramen.
-[sniffs] Yeah, you're right.
-No doubt about it.
There's definitely ramen afoot
somewhere in that restaurant.
-Yeah, ramen!
-Mix it, stretch it, boil it.
Burn copper pot, burn.
-Feast your nostrils on that.
Whatever soup that
is, it's never
been served as part of
the Ichiraku menu before.
-Oh.
So then he must have closed up
shop to figure out a new item.
-Hey, who's up there?
[yelling]
-All right, one large miso
pork ramen, and toss in an egg.
-Goodness.
You boys sure went through a
lot of trouble to get my ramen.
Sorry about braining
you like that.
-It's cool that you want to add
new stuff to the menu and all,
but next time do it after
you close for the night.
-Here.
Give this is a taste.
It's the least I can do.
-All right.
Get a load of that!
-It's Ichiraku's new
item on the menu.
-Here goes nothing.
-Hey, show some respect.
You forgot the cardinal
rule of trying out
a new type of ramen
for the first time.
Step one, try the soup.
Get to know the lay of the land.
[slurping]
-Ah, awesome.
-Step two, swim the noodles
in the broth, then taste.
[slurping]
-Mm.
-Hold on.
Tastes like it needs
something more.
-The party's over, guys.
The noodles are
outclassed by the soup.
The soup is rich and full
of flavor, well heeled.
With this you've
taken Ichiraku's Ramen
to the next level.
However, the noodles
are the same, the usual.
And you know they're never
going to see eye to eye.
I cannot give it
a passing score.
-I figured you would say that.
-Huh?
Whoa, don't look so
down in the dumps.
You'll get it right.
Hey, Ayame, I'm out of water.
Wait a second.
Where the heck's Ayame?
-With ramen this back
I'll never win Ayame back
from the ryouri-nin.
My poor child.
-Teuchi!
-Turns out it was
just exhaustion.
I gave him some
supplements, so he'll
be better after he
gets a little rest.
[sighing]
-That said, I think
he should take a break
from the shop for a little bit.
-He's been overworking
his arms, that's for sure.
I mean, just look
at the swelling.
-Hey, I totally
forgot about this,
but before Teuchi
keeled over, he
was mumbling about Ayame
and the ryouri-nin.
Think it means anything?
-Well, I think Ayame is
his daughter, isn't she?
But what's a ryouri-nin?
-Who knows?
-You guys never heard of them?
-Ryouri-nin is the term they
use for the ninja chefs.
-Huh?
The ninja chefs?
-What do you know
about them, Choji?
-Let's just say I've heard
my share of the rumors.
One of the problems shinobi
run into on missions
is that of food.
Because you can't kick any
butt if you're hungry, right?
They used to just bring
food pill rations with them,
but that got old.
They're big on vitamins,
yeah, but short on flavor.
What if, though, what
if they could sit down
to delicious meals while
they were out on assignment.
The success rates
would skyrocket.
Based on that idea,
a new profession
was born, that purveyor
of culinary ninjutsu,
the ninja chef.
-Huh?
-OK, so they're ninja
chef guys, but I still
get what they have
to do with Ayame.
-They kidnapped her.
That's what they did.
-What?
What do you mean?
Are you saying they took her?
-Please, tell us what happened?
-Looking back, it all
started two weeks ago.
-Welcome.
Take a seat.
-And here's your large ramen.
-An excellent job, just
like I always, Teuchi?
-Hakkaku.
It was Hakkaku, a
figure from my past.
Long ago we apprenticed
under the same ramen master,
but we chose different paths.
I became a ramen shop
owner, he a ninja chef.
-I came here to
ask a favor of you.
-Go ahead.
If it's anything within my
power, it's as good as done.
-This wondrous phantom
recipe that you're said
to have developed.
I must possess it.
-My phantom recipe,
you called it?
I'm sorry, but you lost me.
-Recipes are more important
than life itself to ninja chefs.
Your feigning ignorance
is understandable.
But please, give it to me.
I beg of you.
-I didn't have the slightest
clue what he was talking about.
But Hakkaku left my
shop convinced as ever
that I was just playing dumb.
Ayame, let's get this
place ready for businesses.
What the?
What's that tray doing there?
Ayame!
HAKKAKU: I've taken the liberty
of kidnapping your daughter.
If you want her back, you'll
hand over the phantom recipe
without delay.
-Curse that's crazy Hakkaku.
-But why didn't you
contact the Hokage
as soon as you found out?
I'm sure she could
have helped you.
-Sure, I could have
gone running to her.
But what might happen
to Ayame if I did?
Besides, in the ransom note he
did give me a second option.
If I can whip something up that
really knocks Hakkaku's socks
off, he'll give up on this
crazy phantom recipe thing
and return my daughter to me.
-Well, is anything good enough
to impress him that way?
-I just don't know.
But a chef's thrown down
the culinary gauntlet.
I have to answer the call.
-Oh.
Now I get why you were monkeying
around with the new ramen.
-Yeah.
I got the soup exactly
how I wanted it.
Just perfect.
But now I can't seem to
get the noodles just right
no matter how many new
batches of them I crank out.
A bowl of that
mediocre ramen isn't
going to win Ayame her freedom.
And my cooking challenge
is only a day away.
What on earth am I going to do?
-I can't imagine Ichiraku
without Ayame being there.
It'd just feel empty.
That settles it.
We're going to help you
win this challenge, Teuchi.
We'll give those guys
the best ramen ever.
-Because that's the way we're
going to get Ayame back.
-Yeah, let's do it.
[laughing]
-You guys.
Here goes your crash
course in noodle craft.
First you want to make sure
you mix the ingredients well.
If you don't, the noodles won't
all have a consistent flavor.
Then you have to knead it.
Make sure you show
the dough who's boss,
or else the noodles
won't be firm.
-Are you going to be OK?
-Hey, don't worry your
pretty little head about me.
Then you give them
a good pulling.
-Whoa.
-It's important for
you to get the noodles
so that they're
all equally thick.
You don't want them looking
different after you boil them.
All right, your turn.
Telling someone how
to do it is easy.
But actually making
noodles, that's
a whole other kettle of fish.
It takes five years to
become an accomplished chef.
Them getting the hang of it by
tomorrow, that's crazy talk.
Maybe Hakkaku and
the others will
let Ayame go free if I
agree to take her place.
-Hey, Teuchi, you're
not asking yourself
how you're going to get her
back after we lose tomorrow,
are you?
-Of course not.
-Glad to hear it.
If we didn't plan on heading out
there and winning this thing,
we wouldn't have offered.
-If they think they can kidnap
people whenever they want,
they've got another
thing coming.
-Experience is cool and
all, but real cooking
know how comes straight
from the heart.
-Yeah, that's the spirit.
We'll show those guys what kind
of awesomeness Leaf Village
shinobi can bring to the table.
-Afternoon, Hakkaku.
Sorry that we're late.
-Ready to hand over
the phantom recipe?
-If so I wouldn't have my
whole kitchen on my back.
-Going with plan b?
You are a fool.
Fine.
But that humdrum
ramen you served
me before isn't going
to do the trick.
-Where's Ayame?
Is she all right?
AYAME: Father, help!
-Ayame!
-Save the family reunion
until after lunch.
-Can you do me a
favor and let me
have a few extra
hands in the kitchen.
-This is high stakes
cooking, old man.
Those kids will be more of
a hindrance than a help.
But if it'll make
you happy, all right.
Begin the cooking challenge.
Can you please the
finicky palates of we
who make the meals in the
shadows, the ninja chefs?
-There are so many of them.
-This ain't the time
to stand and stare.
Let's begin.
The preparation for
the soup is all done.
I'll knock out the other stuff.
But I'm leaving the
noodles up to you.
-Yeah!
-Listen you two.
The whole question of whether
or not Ayame gets to come home
depends entirely on
how we do with noodles.
Failure isn't an option.
-It seems like he did a
bang up job on that soup.
The aroma wafting off of it
certainly smells delicious.
It's wetting my appetite, yes.
Ah, but the noodles,
my young friends.
Can you really make
noodles that will live up
to such a regal broth?
-First we got to make sure
we mix up the ingredients.
-Amateurs.
I thought so.
Get a load of the way they're
man handling that dough.
It's criminal.
-We practiced making
noodles all night long.
-Yeah, but they still
weren't anything
to write home about,
even after all that.
-No excuses.
We got to make sure these are
the best noodles they've ever
tasted.
-Naruto!
[laughter]
-Come on, children.
At the very lest you should
try to make it edible.
-Got to mix it fast.
-Got to do it smoothly.
-And mix it evenly.
Now we got to knead the dough.
-Hey, look, Sakura.
See?
Kakashi Sensei.
-Don't play with the food.
-Way to go, Sakura.
[laughter]
-Ow!
You're too strong for
your own good, Sakura.
You got to learn
how to control it.
-It's your own fault for messing
around at a time like this.
-I wonder if--
-Well, that's it.
The last of the ingredients.
-No worries. because this
time I know the three of us
are going to get the job done.
-Leave the mixing to me.
NARUTO: Wait up, Choji.
Mind if I jump in
and give it a whirl?
-Go for it, man.
-Hey, Sakura, tell me.
Last time I checked, the three
of us were shinobi, right?
In that case, I'm thinking
we should show them
how to do those
noodles ninja style.
Step one, shadow clone jutsu.
Rasengan Ichiraku style.
-Ah, what the?
He's using chakra to mix
the ingredients together?
Of course, he's using the
raw power of the chakra
to fold the ingredients together
into a sublimely uniform dough.
It'll be mixed down
to the cellular level.
-Sakura.
-What's up?
-It's Pervy Sage.
-Naruto!
What did I tell you?
-What?
She's pounding it
with so much fury,
now those noodles
are going to have
the most perfect
firmness I've ever seen.
-Thanks, Sakura.
Choji.
-I also am a shinobi
from the Leaf Village.
Partial expansion jutsu!
Both hands.
I'm going long on this one.
Oh, yeah!
--[cries out] Truly a
peerless batch of noodles.
And if those should find
their way into Teuchi's soup,
this match is over.
No.
We cannot lose today.
The very future of the ninja
chefs hangs in the balance.
-OK, now they just
have to be boiled.
Go for it.
-All right, you leave it to me.
-I wouldn't do that.
-What?
-Huh?
-The ramen may be
exquisite, true enough,
but who are you
going to serve first?
-Who gets it first?
-He's right.
That's the ninja chef way.
-What's the ninja chef way?
-Among the ninja
chefs, there was
one rule esteemed
above all others.
-The first guest
to arrive is also
the first guest to whom
you serve any food.
-No matter how delicious
that ramen of yours may be,
if you flout this honored
tradition you're disqualified.
-Seriously though, I
can understand that.
If some guy comes late
and gets to eat before me,
I raise a stink.
-There are 100 ninja
chefs assembled here today
and they all arrived within
moments of each other.
That means you
have to find a way
to serve ramen to 100
people at the same time.
You're only four people.
How can you even hope to
serve us all simultaneously?
-I did mention before that
we're ninja, didn't I?
Shadow clone Justu!
-What is this?
-All right, hoist them up.
-Thanks for waiting, you guys.
Dig in.
-The taste is the issue.
If the ramen still fails to
impress us, you still lose.
[slurping]
-[laughs] Superb!
-So good.
-I have never encountered
ramen this good.
-So that means?
-We win the challenge and
Ayame gets to come home.
-All right!
-The truth of it is, we ninja
chefs now find ourselves
in a serious pickle.
-A serious pickle?
-What the heck are
you talking about?
-Creating delicious
meals that ninja
could enjoy doing
their missions.
That's all we've ever
wanted to achieve.
Why settle for bland
fare, we thought,
when it could be healthy and
portable and tasty as well.
But we pursued taste too far.
We flew too high.
Oh, it was delicious all right.
Mission accomplished.
But they packed it in.
The ninja grew portly,
chunky even to the point
where they couldn't
complete their assignments.
Now people say, great,
our shinobi are fat.
Perhaps we don't need
the ninja chefs anymore.
If we ninja chefs were to
have any hope of enduring,
we had to venture into the
greater world of cooking,
find the phantom recipe
and make it ours.
-Then what?
-If we make the
meal in question,
we can improve a
ninja's performance
as we did before, but
without weighing them down.
-But what kind of
recipe would do that?
-The scum recipe.
We heard its legendary.
-The scum recipe?
-We sent out our informants
to canvas the land
in search of it.
We heard that it was to be found
at Ichiraku Ramen Shop, run
by my old associate Teuchi.
-What?
-Uh, don't look at me.
I haven't the slightest idea
what you're talking about.
-Our contact heard
you mention it.
--[laughs] The fools must
never know I have the recipe.
-Uh, hey, Teuchi?
-Oh, that one.
-What?
-Are you serious?
-You do have it.
-Yeah, but you're
wrong about the name.
Is called the skim recipe.
[bird cawing]
-The skim recipe?
-The trick do any
good soup or stew
is to skim off the
layer of gunk that
accumulates on
top of the liquid.
I experimented for awhile,
really perfecting my skimming
method and made a whole
recipe that centers around it.
Guess I called it the
scum recipe once thinking
about that layer on top.
Yep, just your garden
variety slip of the tongue.
-It's a significant
slip of the tongue.
-Yeah if it had slipped any
worse it would have fallen out.
-Hey, don't forget that
we won the cooking match,
so you have to give
Ayame back to her father.
-Oh, that's right.
Well come on.
Where is she?
AYAME: Father.
-Ayame?
Ayame?
Is that you?
-Don't you recognize me?
-What happened?
Ayame always used to look so--
-These ninja chefs
weren't bragging
when they said they cooked
up some delicious meals.
I may have had
seconds a time or two.
Why, did I gain
that much weight?
-Ayame!
-Ichiraku's got a new item?
-Huh.
So it's that one ramen we
made to get Ayame back?
-Yeah, right.
It's a special diet ramen,
real popular with the girls.
-Diet ramen?
When you said it was
popular, you weren't kidding.
-Oh, Naruto.
Come on in.
-Looks like you've slimmed
back down to normal again.
-I couldn't have done it
without father's diet ramen.
-Huh?
Where is Teuchi anyway?
-He are the diet ramen
along with me to supportive
and, well, see for yourself.
-Hey, Naruto.
-I think there's such a
thing as being too thin.
[music - chaba, "parade"]
-OK, does anybody have a
question about this mission?
-Yeah, I've got a big one.
How come I got teamed
up with you guys?
-No questions?
All right then, let's move out.
-Hey, yoo-hoo,
question right here.
-We're heading to
the land of the sea
to eliminate the
demon of the ocean.
You guys had better
do an excellent job
and make me look as
good as possible.
-Wait, come on, listen to me.
-Time to get going.
Quit your complaining
already and fall
in line like a good
little underling.
-Listen to me!
Just listen already!
Next time remember
it's The Lost Page.
[music - chaba, "parade"]