[music playing]
-What is this?
Where am I?
Who's this?
It's me, a long time ago.
Father and Mother
shouldn't have died.
It didn't have to happen.
They're all dead because
I wasn't strong enough
to save them.
My whole plan has
been destroyed.
-Battle formation Ino-Shika-Cho.
-Ino.
But why?
-I'm tired of you showing
off in front of Sasuke
and trying to get
all of the credit.
-These Leaf Village
worms will be
sorry they squirmed
their way into something
that doesn't concern them.
-Are you two crazy?
What are we doing here?
These guys are bad news, man.
-Don't look at me.
It was Ino's idea.
But what are we supposed to do?
Just sit back and let a
girl do all the fighting?
-Sorry for dragging
you both into this.
But we are a three-man
squad, right?
All for one and one for all.
-Yeah.
What's meant to happen will.
-This ain't teamwork.
I call this suicide.
Let me out of here!
Please, let me go!
-You're getting on my nerves.
-Better a live sheep than
a dead lion, right fatso?
-Did I just hear that right?
What did that guy just say?
-Uh oh.
He just pushed Chogi's
button big time.
-You want to try
saying that again?
-I said you're smart to get
up while you still can, fatty.
-Who are you calling fat?
I'm just a little chubby, OK?
[inaudible]
-Huh?
-That does it.
Now this is personal.
It's a fight to the death
between Leaf and Sound.
-Excellent.
He's totally lost it.
-Good job.
Thanks a lot.
Now we've got to live with him.
-Don't worry.
It won't be for long.
We've gotta get rid
of these clowns.
Sasuke is the target.
-Oh, Sasuke.
-Sakura.
Your teammates are down.
Look after them.
OK, Team Ino.
Let's show them who's boss.
-Got it.
-Formation Ino.
-Shika.
-Cho.
-OK.
Take it away, Chogi.
-My pleasure.
Expansion Jutsu!
Followed by leaf style Taijutsu!
Human boulder Jutsu!
-You've got to be kidding.
Maybe I'm supposed to
laugh myself to death.
Slicing sound wave!
It shook the airstream!
This thing is
spinning way too fast.
My sound wave can't control it.
And if I try going
supersonic on it,
it's liable to rip my arms off.
-Zaku!
-Oh, no you don't, mummy man.
Time to put you under wraps.
Ninja Heart Shadow
Possession Jutsu!
-What's happening?
-Just me and my shadow.
-What is it?
Why are you just
standing there like that?
-It's some kind of
paralysis Jutsu.
-Ina, I'll leave
the girl to you.
-OK.
You got it.
Just take care of my
body while I'm gone.
-Sure.
-Ninja Art Mind Transfer Jutsu!
-Enough of this.
Kane!
What's wrong with you?
-Party's over, fellas.
Take it easy.
One false move from either
of you, and your teammate
here gets it in the neck.
You don't want that to happen.
So here's what you do.
Just drop the scroll
and walk away.
When you're far enough away
that I can't sense your Chakras,
I'll let her go.
-I don't get these guys.
Something's wrong.
Hey, Chogi!
-Incoming!
-What is it?
What are they up to?
-This is bad.
-I don't feel so good.
-I-- I don't
understand you guys.
What kind of monster would
attack their own teammate?
-I guess monsters like us.
-You see, we don't play
this game by your rules.
It's not the
scrolls we're after,
or even passing this test.
-What the?
-Sasuke.
-I hate it when it does that.
-So, your paralysis Jutsu has a
pretty limited duration, I see.
-Shadow Possession Jutsu.
Get your Jutsus right.
-Whatever.
And I see that your
teammate is able to slip
her soul into her opponent.
Very clever, but dangerous.
Anything that happens to
Kane happens to her, too.
So if, say, Kane were to die--
-What are you going to
do, kill your teammate?
-Well, if push comes
to shove, yeah.
-Oh, man.
What a drag.
-Yeah, no kidding.
-Did you really think
you could beat us?
Face it.
You ninja are just
a bunch of hacks.
-From a second rate village.
-That's pretty tough talk.
I guess that makes your
village third rate.
-I wonder if any
of you amateurs are
ready to take on the real thing.
-What?
-It's Lee's team.
I wondered when they'd get here.
-Lee!
-You it.
-These Genin keep popping out
of the woods like cockroaches.
-It looks to me like somebody
used our teammate as a punching
bag.
No one does that and
gets away with it.
-Those eyes-- he's not
just looking at us,
he's seeing through us.
-No more playing around, Tenten.
Full power.
-What's the matter?
Neji?
-That Chakra.
-Well, are you going to
stay up there all day,
or are you going to come down
here and do something about it?
-Actually, it
looks like it might
have been taken out of my hands.
-Because I was
weak, everyone died.
I couldn't save them.
If only I'd been stronger.
If only I'd had more power.
Instead, you stood by
and watched them die.
So helpless, like
lambs to the slaughter.
If only you were stronger.
If only you had more power.
-Sasuke!
You're awake.
-Sasuke.
That's Sasuke?
-Sakura.
-Sakura, who did this to you?
Who was it?
-Those marks, they're
all over his body.
-Sasuke, what's happened to you?
-Don't worry.
I'm all right.
It's only the power
flowing through me.
In fact, I've never felt better.
He gave me this gift, and he
made me understand what I am.
I'm an avenger.
To follow my path, I must
have power at any price.
Even if it means being
consumed by evil.
-And now I see those
marks on the neck
that the girl spoke of.
You were a curse mark.
Who would have
thought he'd survive?
More than survive.
-Sakura, tell me, which one of
these people did this to you?
-That would be me.
-Ino!
Hurry up and get
back in your body.
You don't want to
get involved in this.
You too, Chogi.
Come on, get out there.
-I'm coming.
-Mind transfer, release.
-Atta girl.
Good to have you back.
-Shikamaru, what's
this all about?
What's going on?
-How should I know?
-What is this?
-This changes everything.
His Chakra is too
big, too powerful.
We can't fight that.
-Dosu, what's wrong?
You're not getting
cold feet, are you?
-No!
Saku, you don't understand!
-Watch this.
I'll take care of the
whole bunch of them
in one fell swoop!
Super sonic slicing wave!
What do you know?
Blew them all away.
-Not quite.
-Zaku!
Such speed.
He got both his teammates
out of harm's way
in the blink of an eye.
-Fire style phoenix
flower Jutsu!
-I don't think so.
Try this!
In the flames, Shukien!
-Zaku, get down!
-His Chakra, it's
completely different.
It's fiercer, darker.
Can that really be Sasuke?
-You seem to be very proud
of these arms of yours.
You must be very
attached to them.
-No!
What are you doing?
-You wanted Sasuke.
You want power, don't you, boy?
-It looks like you're
the only one left.
I hope you make things
more interesting
than your friend did.
-No!
It's not-- it can't be.
Whoever that is,
it's not Sasuke.
No!
Stop!
Don't do it.
Stop, please.
-The marks have receded.
We're safe for now.
-Sasuke.
-You're strong, Sasuke.
Too strong.
We can't hope to defeat
you the way you are now.
We'll strike a deal.
I give you this scroll,
and you let us go.
It would seem we
underestimated you.
But at least we found out
what we needed to know.
For the moment, we're even.
But if it should happen that
we ever again meet in combat,
I promise you, we
won't run or hide.
-Wait!
Who is this Orochimaru anyway?
What's he done to Sasuke?
And why Sasuke?
-I don't know.
All I know is that we were
told to target Sasuke.
And we did.
I don't know why he sent
us to assassinate someone
on whom he'd
bestowed such powers.
I don't why Sasuke even
survived the curse mark.
There are many
things I don't know.
-Hey, you guys OK?
-Ino, you look after Lee.
We'll check out the kid.
-Right!
-That was no normal Chakra.
I had no idea the Uchiha
clan were so strong.
-Sakura is in danger.
I'll protect her.
Don't worry, Sakura.
It's OK.
I'll save you.
-Woah.
Somebody ought to kick
him and wake him up.
This is embarrassing.
-Can I kick him first?
-Just what am I?
-Sasuke.
[music playing]
-Hey, what is it, Akamaru?
You want to go for a walk?
You hungry?
Well, did you lose
your chew toy?
Oh, I know.
Just use any tree.
It's OK.
Ow!
What was that for?
-Next time, Akamaru trembles,
Gaara's cruel strength.
-Hey, has he had all his shots?