[theme music]
JIRAIYA: A hot spring?
TSUNADE: That's right.
Just up the road here,
there's a sweet little down
with a beautiful hot spring.
-hot spring Resort.
It says here the hot springs
promote health and beauty.
-Forget it.
We've got a long way to
go before we get home,
and everyone's there
waiting for us.
-You know, for once
I agree with him.
We really ought to
be getting back.
For all we know, the
village could be in trouble.
-Oh, loosen up.
One day's not gonna make
that much difference.
I hear it's popular with women,
and they allow mixed bathing.
-Hm?
-What's up?
Where you going?
-Oh, um, I got this kink
in my uh-- Well, everyone
deserves a break once in awhile.
-That's not what you were
saying just a second ago!
So, it's settled.
Come on, let's go.
-Oink.
-It's her, all right.
No doubt about it.
-I don't believe it.
We finally found her.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Kidnapped.
Naruto's Hot Spring Adventure!
WOMAN: Welcome!
Welcome, good people!
And pig!
WOMEN: Welcome!
-Cannonball!
-I can't say I'm
having much fun so far.
Just me and the knucklehead.
When's the mixed
bathing gonna start?
-Since we've got time
to kill before dinner,
I think I'll hit the
Pachinko machines.
-Really?
You sure you don't wanna
try out the hot springs?
-Please.
With those two
buffoons in the water?
Forget it.
Let's go.
-Oink.
-Hm.
-That's enough for me.
You getting out?
-Not quite yet.
I'm going to soak
a little longer.
-Uh huh.
-I'm ready.
Anytime now.
Welcome, ladies!
-Gotta admit, that felt great!
Huh?
Gah!
I've-- I've been robbed!
Oh no, the necklace I won
from Grandma Tsunade is gone!
No, wait.
Maybe I put it somewhere else.
Maybe-- Huh?
If you want your necklace
back, pay us the money you owe.
The Akagi family will be
waiting at the three cedars
on the hill outside of town.
-What money?
Who the heck do I owe money to?
-Well, they're
females, I suppose.
But, uh-- Ugh.
The only problem is,
they're the wrong species!
This, uh, isn't quite
what I had in mind.
[groan]
-Hey!
Akagi family!
I'm here!
Are you in hiding or what?
Come on out already!
-Hm?
-What do you want, kid?
-That's just what I
was about to ask you!
I don't owe you guys any money.
I've never seen you
before in my life,
so give me back my
necklace right now!
-Your necklace?
What do you mean?
-Wait.
We couldn't have got
it wrong, could we?
-That's it!
That's my necklace!
Wait a second!
-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
[thudding]
-Well, I wanted humans
and I've got humans.
If only it wasn't a
bunch of fat guys!
-Who you calling fat, grandpa?
-Are there any human
women in this town?
-Huh.
So it's really Grandma Tsunade
who owes you the money.
-Right.
She's called the
legendary sucker.
She always loses, and she
lost at our village too.
She was broke, so
we took her IOU.
Right here.
This is what she owes us.
-Ah!
Whoa, that's-- That's
a lot of zeroes!
-My name is Senta, and this here
is Bunzo More than three years
ago, the head of our family
sent us out to collect the debt.
BUNZO: We set out from
Akagi Mountain knowing
we couldn't come back
without the money.
But the trail was cold.
We searched everywhere.
SENTA: We'd hear rumors
that she was here or there.
Always somewhere else.
BUNZO: She has a
reputation for being
hard to find when
you wanna find her.
And it's true.
SENTA: At last, we got
some solid information.
She'd been seen in the area,
headed toward this village.
BUNZO: So we staked out a spot
on the road outside of town
-I get it it.
And that's when we came
along with Grandma Tsunade.
That still doesn't explain
why you raided my room
and tore it apart.
-She may be an easy
mark, but we've
heard she's a tough customer,
so we figured we couldn't just
show up and ask her nicely.
We'd never get our
money back that way.
-No, you're probably right.
-Everybody tells us that the
necklaces is as precious to her
as her life.
We thought she might
pay to get it back.
-Brilliant!
But you found the necklace
in my room, remember?
-We never thought--
it didn't occur to us
that the necklace
was no longer hers.
-Maybe-- You know her so well.
Maybe you could ask her to
kindly give us our money?
-Huh?
It's not like I
know her that well.
-Please!
If we don't get
that money back, we
can never return to our village!
-Our wives and
children are all alone.
-Please, young friend.
Won't you help us?
-Argh!
-Well, I guess that's that.
Let's go.
-I can't get a break.
Damn.
I'm completely cleaned out.
-Now that we're finished
having fun in here,
let's go try out the hot spring.
-Shizune.
-Huh?
-My suitcase is
at the front desk.
Get it.
[shriek]
-But that suitcase has got
everything you own in it.
-You can't really mean you
want me to bring it here.
-You know I never walk away in
the middle of a losing streak.
So quit lecturing me
and go get it now!
-All right, all right!
-Is it-- Why, it is.
-What the-- What
are you doing here?
-At last, I've got women
and plenty of them.
But still.
-Aren't you cute?
I hoped for women who still
had their own teeth, you know.
-Is this the one?
-Yes.
Thank you.
-Excuse me.
You're with Lady
Tsunade, aren't you?
-Yes.
-This letter arrived for
her just a few minutes ago.
-A letter?
From whom?
Ah!
Lady Tsunade!
We've got trouble.
Huh?
Lady Tsunade?
She's not here.
-Oink.
-All right, Tonton.
Put that nose to work.
Which way did she go?
-Oink.
Mm-mm.
-What do you mean no?
What's wrong?
Of course.
The smell of sulfur from the hot
springs covers up everything.
Then I guess we'll just
have to do the hard way.
Lady Tsunade!
-Oink.
-Lady Tsunade!
Oink!
Where are you?
Lady Tsunade!
-Oink.
Oink.
-Lady Tsunade?
Lady Tsunade!
Lady Tsunade, where are you?
It's no use.
What am I gonna do?
SENTA (VOICEOVER): We
have Naruto Uzumaki.
If you want him back
unharmed, bring the money
you owe the Akagi family to
the three cedars on the hill,
outside of town.
-What now?
We have to help Naruto.
On top of that, if word gets out
about Lady Tsunade's gambling
debts, maybe the village
won't make her Fifth Hokage
after all.
It could ruin everything.
-Oink.
Oink!
-All right.
Since we have no choice, we'll
have to do it on our own.
What do you say, Tonton?
-Oink.
-You really think
this is gonna work?
-Of course it will.
Don't worry.
-Hey!
She's coming.
NARUTO: Am I glad to see you.
-Stop right there.
You know who we are, right?
Am I right?
-You're a couple of
errand boys for the Akagi.
-Let's keep this simple.
You're gonna hand over every
single penny that you owe us.
-Yeah, or else we'll, uh, take
care of your little friend
here.
-Hurry!
Give 'em what they want.
-Do what you got to do.
I couldn't care less
what happens to the kid.
-Huh?
-What did she say?
-OK, but then what
about our money?
-Things just go
from bad to worse.
I know it's mixed bathing,
but this is too damn mixed!
(VOICEOVER) I just need
to be patient, that's all.
Ow!
My foot!
TSUANDE: So what part of
it don't you understand?
It doesn't matter to
me what you do to him.
-Why, you-- nasty old witch!
TSUNADE: Actually,
wait a minute.
Now that I think about
it when I become Hokage,
I'll need people
like him to serve me.
So I guess I'll
save him after all.
-I knew you wouldn't
let me down.
-This is all they've got at the
moment, but it'll have to do.
Go on, take it.
-You won't mind if I just
check it out, will ya?
-Huh?
-I know I'm a little short,
but it should at least
cover the interest on the loan.
-Hmph.
-What?
-It was all fake?
-Ow!
-You're not gonna pay
them what you owe?
-Shut up.
It's none of your business.
-But they can't go
home u pay them back.
What happens to them?
-What happens?
What do you mean?
-I've tried being sneaky,
now it's time to use force!
-Naruto's shadow clones?
-So Naruto's on the side
of the Akagi family.
This isn't going to be
as easy as I'd hope.
NARUTO: It's not like I
thought she'd just quietly hand
the money over, but to
be that mean about it.
-What do we do now?
-She's got a huge suitcase
she carries around with her.
My guess is that's where
she keeps her money.
If we could just get our hands
on that suitcase somehow.
-Look at her.
Calmly sitting there
drinking and relaxing
while I'm behind held hostage.
BUNZO: There's the suitcase.
But how do we get it?
-Don't worry.
I've already thought of that.
-Oh, Lady Tsunade.
There you are.
Hi.
What's that?
Is that your suitcase?
Why, yes it is.
I'd better take it to the front
desk to make sure it's safe.
Well, have fun.
Phew.
-Ha ha!
Told ya I could get it!
-Way to go!
-Well done!
-Huh?
-Why, you old-- that
was a dirty trick!
That does it.
You're no Hokage.
You've no right to
call yourself Hokage
when you won't even pay
back the debts you owe.
Don't you get it?
These guys can't go
home without that money.
They'll never see their
wives and children again
if you don't pay them.
How can you do that to them?
-Naruto.
-Is it 'cause they happen to
come from a different village?
Is that why you don't care?
Well, I can't serve
that kind of Hokage.
No way!
Hand it over!
Here!
Go on!
Run for it!
-Oh-- right!
Don't look now, but I
think she's gaining on us!
-Here goes nothing!
-You hit her!
-Oink!
-Tonton?
TSUNADE: Naruto!
-Huh?
-Hand over that
suitcase right now.
Or you'll be sorry!
-Here!
Give it to me quick!
Good.
Ah!
Gotta be careful not to let her
nail me with a direct attack!
One false move and I'm toast.
-Watch out.
Comin' through.
-Comin' through!
-Excuse us!
-Hey, what's goin' on?
-Stop this!
You fools are making a
spectacle of yourselves.
-Well, we wouldn't be if we
didn't have you chasing us!
Time for some
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
-OK.
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
-What just happened?
-Don't know.
Let's leave it to the kid.
-This is bad.
If people find out
what's in that suitcase,
it'll be a distaster!
[laughter]
-My goodness, those certainly
were the days, weren't they?
-It's hard to believe
we were ever that young.
To good times.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
-Please forgive my
interruption, sir.
-Yes?
What is it now?
Can't you see we're busy?
-I'm afraid I can't wait.
Ah!
-A clone!
Another clone!
Wrong again.
Damn.
This is getting ridiculous.
Where is he?
Where's the real Naruto?
There!
That's him!
Stop!
-Naruto!
Naruto!
Get back here, you little--
Oh, when I get my hands on you!
-Wait, Naruto!
-That's enough of this!
NARUTO: Grandma!
Let me go!
What are you doing?
Cut it out!
Ow!
Put me down.
Put me down!
-I'll put you down when--
-We hit the jackpot!
-We've got it.
-They got it after all!
-Hm?
-IOUs?
-Every single one.
-We'll never go home again.
-What do you think you're doing?
And right in the middle of town.
-Huh?
Wait, hold on.
Wait a second!
How come there's two
Grandma Tsunades?
-So you're involved
with this too, Shizune?
What the hell is going on here?
Out with it!
-Well, you see, Lady Tsunade--
-Shizune?
It was you?
-You two.
You're from the Akagi
family, aren't you?
-B-- Boss Jirocho!
-Who?
-You don't know who he is?
He's a very powerful man.
Boss Jirocho from
the Land of Tea.
-He's also an old
friend of mine.
We just happened to bump into
each other earlier today.
-You're Senta and Bunzo,
if I'm not mistaken.
It's good I found you.
I have a message for you.
-Wha--
TSUNADE: My debt to the
Akagi family is old news.
I paid it off a year ago.
-Well, what do you
know about that?
-You were there, Shizune.
Don't you remember?
When we passed by their
village last year?
-I-- I forgot.
-Where is it?
-Here.
-I received a letter from
the head of the Akagi family.
I'm just gonna read the
part that applies to you.
If you see Senta and Bunzo,
tell them the debt has been paid
and they can come home.
Shuguro Akagi.
-There.
You see?
-What a waste.
I went to all that
trouble for what?
For nothing!
SENTA AND BUNZO: Thank you
for all your help, Naruto.
Now we can go home
knowing we did our best.
-Well, goodbye and
good luck, guys.
-The same to you.
And thanks again!
-So, hey.
If there was no money
in that suitcase,
how come you cared so darn
much about getting it back?
-Well, I didn't think
it was a good idea
to let everyone in the
world see all those IOUs.
The people of the
Leaf village might not
be so eager to make her
Hokage if they knew.
-You worry too much, Shizune.
Who cares if I run
up a little debt?
-Yeah.
And anyway, that Jirocho
guy said it himself.
I mean, she's paid
off all her debts.
-Well, no.
Just the Akagi one.
-Huh?
-Don't be such a worry wart.
-Oink.
Oink oink.
-Really?
We forgot something?
-Oink.
Oink oink!
-Hm?
Must be hearing things.
I thought the women were here.
[theme music]
NARUTO: Grandma Tsunade!
It's amazing!
You cured Sasuke
and Kakashi-sensei!
-Don't get too excited yet.
The village's troubles
are just beginning.
NARUTO: Got it.
Don't worry, I'm on the job!
MAN: That's comforting to know,
but wh-- where are you going?
NARUTO: Can't fight
on an empty stomach!
MAN: Well, why not?
You've fought on an
empty head often enough.
NARUTO: Next time, Tsunade's
Warning, Ninja No More!
I wonder what she means by that.
[theme music]