[theme music]
-As long as the
score isn't settled,
my heart is as
broken as this watch.
We are both stuck
forever in the past.
-Sagi, no.
Revenge is a poisoned
blade that saves
the most fatal cut for
the man who wields it!
-Fine, so long as I
take Moso down with me!
This darkness could devour
my soul, and I'd welcome it.
-It's just as you said, brother.
All this time, I have
fostered my hatred for you.
I've lived my life for
one single purpose.
-Sasuke!
-It ends here!
Enough!
You're dead!
My days of playing ninja with
you kids of the Leaf village
are done.
Now I'm going to
where Orochimaru is.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I
won't let it happen.
Not again.
I'll never allow you to
throw your own soul away!
Revenge consumed a friend of
mine until nothing was left,
and the only way that's
gonna happen to you
is over my dead body!
-I will see this through to
the end, and if you're not me,
then you're against me.
You'll never understand.
Ever!
-A fake wall!
-I will have my revenge.
I'm sorry, but you leave
me no other choice.
-What the heck is that?
-It's a cage.
-What do we do now?
NAGARE: Farewell and good
riddance, Hidden Leaf Ninja!
-Lightning Blade!
This should do it.
[shout]
[scream]
-How did you figure it out?
-Simple, really.
I've been keeping an eye
on that jutsu of yours.
-Now I remember who you are.
Kakashi Hatake, the copy ninja
with the secondhand Sharingan
eye.
-Your jutsu is nothing
compared to Gaara's original.
Just a cheap, shallow imitation.
All you're doing is hiding your
body somewhere out of sight
and using chakra to
manipulate the rocks and sand.
-We are ronin, outcasts
with no village.
The dregs of ninja society.
That's why we travel
from place to place,
stealing what jutsu we'd
find, sharpening our skills
without benefit of school
or clan, looking for a land
to call our own.
But then, no matter
how hard we try,
I guess this means
there are limitations
we can never hope to surpass.
-Huh?
The feudal lord's
palace is over there.
MAN: Nothing yet!
MAN: Come on.
Give me a hand with this.
MAN: All right.
I'll be right there.
MAN: Lift, lift.
There we go!
-Hurry up!
Lord Sagi may be trapped in
the rubble, for all we know.
-Yes sir!
Faster!
Dig!
-Get these bricks!
-Man.
What kinda guy does
something like that?
Should've hit him
when I had the chance.
Could he be more of a jerk?
KAKASHI: Maybe.
What'd I miss?
-Kakashi-sensei!
Sagi squashed us like a
bunch of bugs and ran away.
We were just trying to help.
Man, what an ingrate.
-Please, try to find it in
your heart to forgive him.
-What do you mean?
-The angry young man who
attempted to kill us back there
is not the real Sagi.
-Say what?
Nothing fell on
your head, did it?
-Avenging the deaths of his
father and younger sister
is all that he cares about.
I'd even go so far
as to say that he's
possessed by the spirit of his
father, the late Feudal Lord
Owashi.
-Possessed.
By Owashi?
You're such a kidder.
Yeah, right.
-You shouldn't assume
that he was joking.
-Fine.
Can we just drop it now?
You know I hate ghosts.
They freak me out.
-Give it a rest.
This is no time for you
to be chickening out.
Come on.
We have to find Lord Sagi.
-Yeah, well, you know, we
have no idea where he went.
KAKASHI: If the feudal
lord truly is possessed,
his need for vengeance will
draw him back to this place.
He will return, and very soon.
[crying]
-No, Sagi, please--
please don't leave me.
First father dies, and now you.
I can't bear the pain
of losing you both.
Dearest father, and brother,
lend me your courage,
that I may rejoin you.
Sagi?
But aren't you-- I promise,
your murder will be avenged.
Then time will
pass once again are
you, whose hands were
stilled too soon.
TOKI (VOICEOVER): I swore
that I would make this right.
Until then, however long
it may be, I live as you.
CHISHIMA (VOICEOVER): I know
Lord Sagi will be here tonight,
looking for a
showdown with Moso.
He'll see this through to
the end, one way the other.
-Huh?
-Heh.
Lord Sagi does his faithful
subordinate a great honor
in coming to see him.
A feudal lord is surrounded
by guards, but not the Cursed
Warrior.
He shall fight and die alone.
Fire Style.
Fireball Jutsu!
-What?
-Ha.
How pathetic.
A ghost swooping into battle
on a child's plaything.
I bid you welcome,
Cursed Warrior.
CHISHIMA (VOICEOVER): Lord Sagi.
-Mock me if you choose, Moso.
I will give you reason
enough to fear me.
-Save your breath.
It's among the last
you shall take.
-Fitting epitaph.
-Yes.
That's right.
Moso is just the face with
which I dupe an unwitting world.
My real name is Hoki, member and
leader of the Wandering Ninja.
With no village of our own,
we drift from place to place,
flotsam on the waves,
stealing the jutsu nobody
will deign to teach us.
But the years sit
heavy on our shoulders.
Our patchwork clan tires
of this vagrant existence.
That's why we've been
looking for a land in which
to end our wandering
and set down roots.
-So the truth comes out.
You've been planning
to take over
from the moment
you arrived here.
-How dare you judge our motives,
you spoiled, feudal whelp.
Fortune has favored you.
We of the wandering
ninja suffer in a way
you could never
begin to understand.
I see no harm in poor
unfortunates wanting
to find a place
they can call home.
But we could never
have come this far
had it not been for your father.
I assumed the guise of
Moso and charmed my way
into Lord Owashi's confidences.
All the while, the fool
never suspected a thing.
A dramatic bit of genjutsu
was enough to convince him
of Moso's magical process, thus
he brought me into the fold
as a trusted adviser.
Kome alone had sense
enough to harbor suspicions
about what I was up to.
So I painted Kome
as a malcontent--
after killing your father.
-That was you?
you're the one who
murdered my father?
-With pleasure!
And after I kill you tonight,
no one will stand in our way!
-Your evil ends here!
My dead cry out for vengeance!
-Can it be?
-Yes.
That's right.
Sagi's younger sister, Toki.
-Lady Toki?
-This is for my
father and brother!
-Shadow Possession Jutsu!
Well, well, Toki.
Observe how our respective
shadows intersect.
That's Shadow Possession
Jutsu, and you are now
mine to command.
Impressive.
I never imagined you were alive.
The wandering ninja
will control this land,
never to wander again.
And you, who lived as Sagi,
will now die like him!
-Lady Toki!
Don't give up hope!
-Chishima.
-So, you're still alive, eh?
-I didn't know it
was you, Lady Toki.
How could I have
ever been so foolish?
-Touching display.
Now die!
NARUTO: I heard everything
this power just told you.
Leave the rescuing to me, Sagi!
Toki!
Whoever!
-Naruto.
-Empty words!
My shadow compels you
to cut yourself down!
NARUTO: Real proud of that
shadow stuff, aren't you?
Too bad it's just another one
of your lame genjutsu tricks!
-Curses!
-Lady Toki.
NARUTO: Hey, Moso!
Shadow Possession is
Shikamaru's jutsu.
It's way our of your
league, you big liar!
Man, even your ninjutsu's fake!
-Show yourself!
-It's Naruto!
-Which one?
NARUTO: We all know what
you're trying to do!
Give it up now or I'll teach you
a lesson you don't wanna learn!
-Ah, yes.
The Leaf village brat.
Using clone jutsu, eh?
Fire Style, Phoenix
Flower Jutsu!
Those are solid?
Could they all be shadow clones?
NARUTO: Ha!
Sasuke's jutsu's
got you beat, buddy!
I hope you're ready,
'cause it's my turn now!
-Really?
Well, Kakashi Hatake.
I should have known
you'd be here.
-So you're Hoki, leader of
the infamous wandering ninja.
Your reputation precedes you.
A shinobi who's ever
creeping from place
to place in search of new
prey, like a bat in the night.
-Pampered ninja from
a wealthy village
can't begin to
understand what life
is like for the less fortunate.
-Wrong is wrong!
-We of the Leaf are taught
to face our difficulties
with honor.
That is the true
way of the ninja.
People like you who try to
better their lot through deceit
are ninja in name only.
Nothing but common thieves.
-Ha.
Elitist pig!
Summoning jutsu!
[roar]
-Those dragons look
like a real deal.
-But how?
-Wait!
-No way!
[scream]
-That's enough!
-Hm?
Just a projection?
-So the dragons he
summoned were fake as well.
-And It looks like he ran
off while we were distracted.
-He's in the mention.
-Not for long!
-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Come back and fight
me, you big chicken!
I know he's here, but where?
HOKI: Look closer, Leaf Ninja.
-Huh?
-In-- in the screen?
HOKI: If you want Toki back,
simply come and get her.
-Yeah?
And how's that?
HOKI: Foolish boy.
Step into the boat.
-Genjutsu?
HOKI: Why do you hesitate?
Are you frightened,
Hidden Leaf puppy?
-Puppy, huh?
We'll see about that!
It really worked.
Who are they?
[giggling]
[wicked laughter]
[theme music]
NARUTO: Maybe you don't
know it, or even care,
but Chishima always
believed in you.
Seriously, this guy
loved the Land of Birds
with all his heart,
and he'd do anything
for a friend, even when that
friend turned his back on him.
I know who you are, and I
know what you mean to him,
but even so, I'll
never forgive you!
You've said enough.
Time for you to pay!
Next time, When Egrets
Flap Their Wings!
[theme music]