[theme music]
[music playing]
-All right, the
rules for this match
are the same as in
the preliminaries.
The match continues until one
of you dies, or admits defeat.
However, I can stop the match,
but that's solely my decision.
[laughter]
NARRATOR: "Bushy Brow's
Jutsu, Sasuke Style."
[crown noise]
-Huh?
-Hello, Guy.
How are you feeling, Lee?
Are you all right?
-Kakashi.
-Kakashi Sensei.
-Oh, right.
Sorry about that.
You must have been worried.
Sorry for not keeping in touch.
-Uh, mhm.
-Uh oh, Sakura's going
to get really mad.
-I don't mind.
That's OK.
[sigh]
[music playing]
-It's too hard to see from here.
Sasuke-- Listen, sensei--
-Hm?
-You know that there was a
mark on Sasuke's neck, right?
Well, is it--
-It's nothing to worry about.
-Uh.
-A mark?
[sigh]
-So, that's that.
-Hm.
KAKASHI: One, two, three,
four, five, six, seven, eight.
Eight of them.
Eight members of the ANBU Black
Ops in an arena this size.
That's nowhere near enough.
What could Lord
Hokage be thinking?
-Well, not knowing how
the enemy's going to act,
the ANBU Black Ops have probably
been disbursed and stationed
around the key parts
of the village.
-Huh?
-It's starting.
We can't afford to
let our guard down,
but for now, at least, we
need to watch this match.
VOICE: Ha ha.
This is going to be awesome.
-Kakashi, I'm going to be
carefully watching your pupil
to see if your
training was any good.
After all, I'm still your rival.
-Huh, sorry.
Did you say something?
[bell]
-Oh, you make me
so mad, Kakashi.
Why do you always
have to act so cool?
[seagulls]
-Both of you, to the middle.
[music playing]
-Begin!
-So this is the sand
Kakashi talked about.
[groans]
-Huh?
-Please, I beg you.
Don't get so mad at me.
Mother--
-What in the world
is he talking about?
-Early, early-- I know, I made
you taste such awful blood.
I am so sorry.
But this time, I'm sure that
it'll taste so very good.
-His conversation
has started already.
This is dangerous.
-I Know.
This is the first
time I've seen Gaara
get like that before fighting.
That's how powerful
an opponent Sasuke is.
Watch.
[groans]
-Thank goodness, he's
finally calmed down.
[heavy breathing]
[music playing]
-Come on.
-Hey Naruto, do you
remember yesterday?
What Gaara said?
-Ha.
-I do, for sure.
[music playing]
-All the same, I will kill you.
Just you wait.
I'll kill you all.
-That's what he said,
but then he didn't do it.
It was the perfect
opportunity, buddy.
I don't know.
It was like he didn't
even see us or something.
-Uh.
[wind]
-Now, let me feel alive.
-We're not good enough,
not for that guy.
-Right now, the only person that
can make him feel anything--
-The only one is Sasuke.
-And I live solely for myself.
I love only myself.
And there's no end to it
as long as there are still
people to kill in this world.
[thunder]
-I will never disappear.
[heavy breathing]
GAARA: Naruto--
[drums]
[wind blowing]
-Here goes.
[music playing]
-The sand shield
became a sand clone.
[music playing]
-Huh?
-Uh.
It's passed, just
like that other one.
[music playing]
-Incredible, he's almost as
fast as Lee's normal speed.
-It is almost like a mirror
image of my own taijutsu.
[music playing]
-So that's your sand armor, huh?
-Come on.
-Hey, thanks for all
your help, ANBU guy.
So, it looks like Hinata's going
to make a full recovery if she
can just get some rest.
-Oh, is that right?
[growl]
[barks]
-What's wrong?
What, you know this guy?
Come on, there's
no way you could.
He's an ANBU Black Op.
[barks]
-Hold on, I don't get it.
What are you talking about?
At the examination-- huh?
-This is what he's
talking about.
[music playing]
[rumbles]
-Come on.
If you won't do it, then I will.
[music playing]
-He's fast.
-Even--
[music playing]
-What's the matter, Gaara?
Is that all you've got?
[music playing]
-Uh, amazing.
-I'm going to tear
off all your armor.
[music playing]
-His speed's basically the
same as Lee's, with his weights
removed.
-That's exactly
like Lee's taijutsu.
Sasuke has way more speed
than he ever did before.
[music playing]
-Remarkable, Sasuke.
Really remarkable.
You are truly a
genius, a greater ninja
than I ever imagined.
I mean, how many years did it
take me to attain that speed?
And you achieved the same
result in just a month.
[music playing]
[heavy breathing]
-But it sure looks like it
takes a lot of stamina for him
to maintain that speed.
-What's Gaara going to do now?
That sand armor uses
up too much chakra.
It won't last for
very much longer.
-Mhm, mhm.
[music playing]
-His training--
what did you two do?
-Hm?
-To get to such a
level, in a mere month.
-Sasuke has copied Lee's
taijutsu with his Sharingan.
So, during the taijutsu
training I did with Sasuke,
I simply had him imagine
Lee's movement and copy it.
Sasuke mastered that taijutsu
only because he knew Lee.
Of course, Sasuke
had to work very hard
to master it, even
with his Sharingan.
-But that sand ninja, he
is way too tough for that.
He cannot be taken down
with only that taijutsu.
-If Kakashi saw the battle
between Gaara and Lee,
then why did he--
[wind blowing]
[gunshots]
-After all, that taijutsu
Sasuke learned from Lee
can't suddenly work against
an opponent that even Lee
himself couldn't defeat.
But Kakashi must
have known this,
so why did he have Sasuke
master only taijutsu?
-Uh.
[wind blowing]
-What then, was left for
me in this existence?
Why go on living?
But in order to live,
you need a purpose.
To exist for no reason is
the same as being dead.
-What is this guy talking about?
-Then, in time, the
answer came to me.
To put it simply,
my reason for living
is in the killing of others.
For years, I lived
in fear of those
who were sent to murder me.
But now, I am at peace.
[clears throat]
-Huh?
-Shikamaru, we have to go talk
to Kakashi Sensei, right now.
-What are you planning to do?
Hey, wait.
-I've got to stop him.
I've gotta stop the match.
-Gaara couldn't possibly be
planning to use that jutsu.
[music playing]
-So, he's used all
the sand as a shield.
Because of the sand's
density, I didn't
think it could create
something this hard.
So, he's absolutely protected.
[music playing]
-The sand-- he's
covered his entire body.
-What an effective
and vexing defense.
Will Sasuke be able
to get around it?
NARUTO: Kakashi Sensei!
-Huh?
-Oh.
-Hm?
-Narutro.
[heavy breathing]
-Wha-- what is it Naruto?
-Sensei, please.
You just have to stop
this match, right away.
-What?
-Oh.
-The guy Sasuke is
fighting is completely
different than the rest of us.
He's about as far from
normal as you can get.
-Naruto, slow down.
What are you trying to say?
-He thinks his point in
life is to kill people.
Don't you see?
If this continues,
Sasuke will die.
[chanting in Japanese]
[wind blowing]
-Oh.
[music playing]
-No doubt about it,
it's that jutsu.
This is bad.
Gaara isn't even thinking
about our plan at all.
-Uh.
-You've gotta believe me.
[music playing]
[laugh]
[theme music]
-Sasuke, once I fought
you, and I arrogantly said,
it is no use if your eyes
see me if your body is
too slow to do
anything about it.
But, now you've nearly the
same super speed as I do.
And on top of that, you
also have your Sharingan.
NARRATOR: Next time-- "Late
for the Show, but Ready to Go!
The Ultimate Secret
Technique is Born!"
-I wish I could fight
like you, Sasuke.