[music playing]
[music - Asian Kung-Fu
Generation, "Far Away"]
NEJI: Hey, you.
Loser.
-Hm?
-I have two pieces
of advice for you.
First of all, if you intend
to call yourself a shinobi,
stop that stupid
cheering of yours.
It's disgraceful.
And second, once a
failure, always a failure.
You can't change that.
-Hmph.
We'll just see about that.
-[growls]
[gasp]
-Aaah!
What are you doing?
ROCK LEE: Naruto, I get
where you are coming from,
believe me.
But the rules say all fighting
must be done officially
in a match, the loser
beating the gifted genius
through sheer willpower--
now would not that
make for an exciting match?
NARUTO: Hinata, I
give you my word.
I vow to win!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Gaara versus Rock Lee:
The Power of Youth Explodes!
-Whoa, Choji, glad I'm not you.
I mean, you've still got
the toughest ones left.
I wouldn't want to
face any of them.
That creepy guy from
the Sound Village?
And Rock Lee's got to be
tough if he took on Sasuke.
And especially not
that Sand Village guy.
I don't even like being
in the same room with him.
--[whining] I'm not
feeling so good.
Maybe I ought to go ahead
and forfeit right now.
ASUMA: What?
-Huh?
-You know, if you win,
I'll take you for barbecue.
-Wha?
Come on!
-Choji, come on, don't worry.
If it gets bad, we'll step
in and stop the fight,
just like with Hinata, OK?
Think of it-- all the
short ribs you can eat.
INO (VOICEOVER):
That's a low blow.
Playing on his weak spot?
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
When did he
step in and stop
the fight, anyway?
-(SHOUTING) Rrrrrraaahhh!
Now you're talking!
All you can eat!
Bring it on!
KANKURO (VOICEOVER): Uh-oh,
I've seen that look before.
TEMARI (VOICEOVER): I
can sense his bloodlust.
BAKI (VOICEOVER):
That last fight,
I wonder, did it stir
up his inner demon?
KANKURO: I'm still curious
about that Neji guy.
Yeah, that might work.
-Where are you going?
-Just doing a little recon.
I'll be back.
Hey, you!
-Hm?
KANKURO: How come
you're all by yourself?
Why aren't you hanging
with your buddies?
-Huh?
What's it to you?
KANKURO (VOICEOVER): Well, well.
Touchy.
-So tell me something
about this guy Neji.
I get the feeling we didn't see
the full extent of his powers
in the last fight, did we?
So what's his story?
-I'm gonna pulverize him!
That's his story.
-OK, but that's not
quite what I meant.
KANKURO (VOICEOVER): Man, this
idiot's out of his league.
You know, you seem
like a nice guy.
I like you.
-Well, don't take this the
wrong way, but I don't like you!
KANKURO (VOICEOVER):
This kid is toast.
[coughs]
-Uh?
-Now then, we'll
continue the competition.
-All right!
This time you'll be
picked, I just know it!
You ready, Lee?
-No!
-Huh?
-I have been waiting
so long, I do not care.
I might as well go last.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
What's up with Lee?
Is he sulking?
[digital beeping]
VO: Well, come on.
Let's do this.
-Yeaaaahhh!
Safe again!
-Stop that!
-You want everyone to
know you're a chicken?
-[gasp] Lee!
-It worked like a charm.
I knew if I said I wanted
to be last, I would be next.
I simply applied
the principle which
states that sometimes the
surest way to hit something
is to stop trying to hit it.
It is a form of
reverse psychology.
-Hoo-ah!
That's my student!
ROCK LEE: I absolutely
was not going
to be last, no matter what.
Ha-ha!
I sure fooled them, did I not?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Fooled who?
-Now, then, listen carefully.
A piece of advice
before you began.
-Sir!
-(QUIETLY) Look.
You see that gourd
that Gaara is wearing?
Watch out.
There's something
weird about it.
-Good advice, sir.
-Don't write it down!
What are you thinking?
After all, you're not
going to have time
to read any notes during
the match, are you?
-Ah!
More good advice!
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): He
just figured that out
about the gourd?
SAKURA: I hope Lee
will be all right.
-Now, rock and roll!
-Yeeaahhhh!
I knew that sooner or later,
we would have to meet,
and I'm glad it is sooner.
KANKURO: I don't know
what kind of moves
that guy with the
dumb haircut has got,
but he'll never take Gaara
down, not in this lifetime.
TEMARI (VOICEOVER): He's
fast on his feet, all right,
but his kick isn't that great.
-Wrong.
-What?
-Aaiiiiii-yahh!
NARUTO: Lee's stronger
than you think.
You have no idea.
-Why are you in such a hurry?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Be careful.
MIGHT GUY (VOICEOVER):
Stay on your toes, Lee.
-All right, then.
If you are both ready-- begin.
-Hyah!
Leaf Hurricane!
Huh?
Aaaah!
Hunh!
-What is that?
-It's sand.
-That's an unusual jutsu.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): So that's
what he's got in that gourd!
SHINO (VOICEOVER): That--
-Is that all you can do?
Sand Coffin!
[grunting]
GAARA: Sand Burial.
SHINO (VOICEOVER):
That nightmare.
Not again!
ROCK LEE (VOICEOVER): A
sand-manipulating jutsu, hm?
It will not be easy
getting through that.
But nothing ventured,
nothing gained.
Rrraahh!
Hunh!
Hah!
Aaaah!
-Whoa!
-Even as fast as he is, Lee
can't get anywhere close
to him.
-The sand!
He's using it as a shield.
-He's not doing it.
The sand is protecting
him of its own accord.
-Huh?
-It's almost like
a living thing.
It'll come to Gaara's defense
without his doing anything.
That's why Gaara's
never been injured.
No one can get at him.
No one's ever even
been able to touch him.
ROCK LEE (VOICEOVER): Aah!
How is he doing it?
He's not moving a muscle!
GAARA: Well, is that all?
-Huh?
-I hope you haven't
finished entertaining me.
We haven't had enough blood.
-Huaaah!
Aaaaahhh!
SAKURA: I don't get it!
He's only using taijutsu.
Can't he see that's
never going to work?
Why doesn't he get some
distance and use ninjutsu?
-Yes, that might be a good
idea-- that is, if we had any.
-Huh?
-Lee has no ninjutsu or
genjutsu skills at all.
-You're kidding!
-Yah!
Ah!
-Oh, that's nothing.
You should have
seen how hopeless
he was when I first met him.
No talent whatsoever.
-Really?
I can't believe it.
-Yaah!
[cries out]
-Aaah!
-Mm!
-Oh!
-It's over.
[chuckles quietly]
-Uh?
MIGHT GUY: A ninja who can do
neither ninjutsu or genjutsu
is certainly a rarity.
Lee has only his
taijutsu to rely on.
Some might consider
that a disadvantage.
But that's what
makes him a winner.
-Huh?
MIGHT GUY: All right, Lee.
Take 'em off.
-Uh, but Guy-sensei, you said
that was only as a last resort,
when the lives of very
important people were at stake.
-That's right, I did.
But this is an exception.
-Really?
Really?
-Huh?
Are those--
-How old-fashioned.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
Leg weights?
Basic training equipment.
-Totally cool!
-Totally dumb.
-Ah, that is better.
Now I will be able
to move freely.
TEMARI (VOICEOVER): Come
on, you really think
you'll be able to get
through Gaara's defenses
just by dropping a couple
of pounds of weight?
[smash]
[gasp]
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
Guy, you are too much.
-All right, now go!
-Yes, sir!
-Rrrraaahhh!
Aaaahhhh!
SAKURA: So close!
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): So fast.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Amazing!
-Huh?
MIGHT GUY: I could
see that Lee had
no aptitude for
ninjutsu or genjutsu.
So he skipped that and focused
all of his time and energy
into developing his taijutsu.
That way we turned his
disadvantage into a blessing.
Now he doesn't need those
other things to win,
because he's transformed himself
into the world's greatest
taijutsu specialist.
-Haaah!
[all gasp]
[grunts]
-Hm.
TEMARI (VOICEOVER):
I don't believe it.
Gaara's been hurt!
KANKURO (VOICEOVER): Impossible!
-Whoa, that's scary.
And I thought he was
quick on his feet before!
He's been that fast
This this time?
-Yes, Lee!
Let the power of youth explode!
-Rrrright!
[squeaking skid]
ROCK LEE: Over here.
No, here!
-Good!
ROCK LEE (VOICEOVER):
A direct hit.
-He's just too quick!
That sandstorm can't
keep up with him.
Lee, you nailed him!
-That's incredible!
-I've never seen
anyone that fast!
-Makes me dizzy just trying
to keep track of him!
KANKURO: Uh-oh.
-Yeah, uh-oh is right.
Your friend with
the eye makeup is
getting the stuffing
beaten out of him!
-That isn't what I was
talking about, kid.
-Huh?
What?
[jagged wheezing]
-What the heck?
What's going on with this guy?
His face is falling off!
-It's like a shell made of sand.
-Look, there's not
a mark on the guy.
-That is so weird!
KANKURO (VOICEOVER): He
encased himself in sand, huh?
Things must be bad.
I haven't seen that look on
his face for a long time.
TEMARI (VOICEOVER): I knew it.
I sensed him getting
more and more unstable
as the Chunin Exams progressed.
[jagged wheezing]
BAKI (VOICEOVER): As I
thought, his inner demon
has been awakened.
-I don't get it.
Is he made of sand, or what?
All those blows and
kicks Lee hit him with.
Did any of them get through?
-No.
It's like he's wearing
a suit of armor.
-A what?
KANKURO: Ordinarily, those
shifting clouds of sand
are enough to shield him.
But in the event the
shield is penetrated,
Gaara can also wear
the sand like armor
as a last line of defense.
-This guy's too much!
He's got armor now?
Does he have any weak spots?
KANKURO (VOICEOVER): Huh.
If you only knew, kid.
Actually, that armor
is one big weak spot.
Unlike the sand shield,
the armor can be broken.
And then there's the
enormous amount of chakra
that Gaara has to use
to keep it in place.
That takes its toll.
TEMARI (VOICEOVER):
That's proof that Gaara
is feeling the pressure.
He would never have resorted
to the armor otherwise.
This Lee is good,
no doubt about it.
But that's not the
same as winning.
It may not be as
easy as we thought,
but the outcome's a given.
Gaara can't lose.
-Well, is that all?
ROCK LEE (VOICEOVER): Aah!
My speed will not be enough.
He is impossible to get at
behind those sand defenses.
But maybe if I can get
him up off the ground
and away from the
sand, then hit him
hard from above with the Lotus--
-Hm!
-Hm.
Get ready.
MIGHT GUY (VOICEOVER):
That's right, Lee.
Good work.
That flimsy shield of
sand won't protect him
from your high-speed Lotus.
-What are you waiting for?
-OK, you asked for it.
Hyyyahh!
-He's not floating!
-Try this!
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): What an
incredible series of kicks!
MIGHT GUY (VOICEOVER):
Even an ordinary
Lotus puts an enormous strain
on the body, let alone this.
You've got to
finish him off, now!
-Yyaahhh!
-Hm?
-Aaahh!
-Unnh!
-Now take this!
Primary Lotus!
[thud]
[panting]
It is over.
I got him!
-Right on!
-Amazing!
He really did it.
-No, I don't believe it.
-You did it!
Way to go, Lee!
-Is he-- that guy
isn't dead, is he?
[crack]
[gasp]
[hard sand crumbling]
-Huh?
-What?
[music - Rythem, "Harmonia"]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): What now?
Lee's hit the wall, and things
are just getting started!
That's what happens when you
go crazy on the appetizers
and don't leave room
for the main course.
Better get it in
gear, Bushy Brow.
Otherwise, this guy's liable
to eat you for dessert!
Next time-- Lee's
Hidden Strength:
Forbidden Secret Jutsu.
Uh-oh!
Things are not looking good!