[music playing]
-So you're the one the Leaf
trotted out for me, huh?
-Well look, I owe
you one, and there's
no way I'm letting a
girl show me up, OK?
Still singing the same old
chauvinist tune as always,
aren't ya?
Gaara and Kankuro
are chasing down
the ones who have
our village girl.
You should go help them out.
-From what I hear,
they're each squaring off
in their own separate
flights right now.
-Good to know.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): Darn it!
My shadow won't reach.
-We already have
help on the way here.
Two man squads are on route.
-Came prepared, didn't your?
-It's a bit of a drag, but if
you're going to do something,
do it right.
And this time around, there
won't be any casualties.
-Well, if one of your
comrades does go down,
try not to start bawling again.
-Huh, are you going to hold
that over my head forever?
Guess that's what
girls do best, huh?
INOUE (VOICEOVER): I'm starting
to feel like a fifth wheel
here.
-Hm, I'll take you all out.
-Here we go.
[music playing]
-Backup from the
Hidden Leaf, huh?
The Sand village
is losing its edge.
-What are you doing here?
-Hm.
Dogs will surprise you.
If you ever come
to their rescue,
they won't rest until they
return the favor, especially
Akamaru here.
[barking]
-Tell your pooch he can heel.
I'm good.
-Helps on its way
to your teammates
too, so keep your mind
on the task at hand.
-Hm, I'll pass on the lecture.
-The trash just keeps
piling on up here,
but my Dark Fang Blade should
be more than enough for the job.
You ready?
-Without all of
that chakra in it,
your sand is pretty
much useless Kid.
You could throw it
in my eyes, I guess.
Useless.
I can feel it, all that
chakra flowing into me.
(DISBELIEF) What?
You mean that whole
gorge is full of sand?
I thought he was
playing it safe.
To go this far--
-Hm.
[wind blowing]
-Uh!
-Ha!
[gasp]
MATSURI (VOICEOVER):
(WORRIED) Gaara Sensei!
[screaming]
-I wouldn't have
expected anything less.
They don't call him
the Ultimate Weapon
for nothing, that's for sure.
-The Ultimate Weapon?
-However, he's no match for
the ninja weapons forged
in the Village of Artisans.
-Ah.
Gaara!
Look at that!
He's got him on
the ropes already.
-I only wish we could help.
SHIKAMARU: That
winds incredible.
It's full of chakra.
-No, it's that blade of hers.
It's amplifying her chakra.
-So our whole strategy
depends on that sword, huh?
Well, never mind.
We're just going to have
to bring the fight to her,
get her in range of our jutsu.
-Mm.
-Now, let's get to work.
-Huh, play time's over.
[screaming]
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): She's
only worried about her distance
from Temari.
I get it.
All she's really focusing on
is our long-range fighter.
Inoue and I both
handle mid-range jutsu,
so she could just use
her wind to box us out.
What's the play here?
-Man Beast Clone.
-Partial Expansion jutsu.
-Crow!
CHOJI: Arms!
KIBA: Fang Over Fang!
-You come here to
slow me down or what?
KIBA: I totally
gave you the signal.
[barking]
KANKURO: (ANGRILY) What signal?
-We're not really
clicking too well, are we?
-You fools.
You're about to die,
have a little dignity.
-Huh, keep talking pal.
[screaming]
[explosion]
SUIKO (VOICEOVER): My
Infinite Kujaku Armor absorbed
most of the damage,
but-- Ah well, he
does carry the Shukaku
after all, little demon.
-You're powers
won't help you now.
We've got you right
where we want you.
-Ah!
-Ha!
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
What the hell do I do?
She's beyond the
range of my jutsu.
There's gotta be
something around here
to extend my shadow with.
Come on.
-Hey.
[panting]
-Huh, what's the big secret?
-Huh?
What do you mean?
What kind of idea is that?
-Just trust me.
I'll explain it later.
Now, are you going
to do it or not?
-Well, I guess I
could give it a shot.
-What gives?
-Huh?
What the--
[chuckles]
[laughing]
-Behold the craftsmanship of our
village and shudder with fear.
NEJI (VOICEOVER):
What is this chakra?
We're above water here.
I see now.
The lines of this
triangle aren't a barrier.
They run along a vein of water.
-Ninja Tool Barrier, Reverse
Scale Formation activate.
[gasps]
-Damn it all.
MATSURI: Gaara Sensei!
-Gaara was the prize we were
after from the very beginning,
you see.
We've taped into an underground
stream in the Earth below
and called forth a water dragon.
Soaked through like that, his
sand's become heavy as lead.
It's useless to him now.
-Gaara.
-Don't worry.
Lee and Naruto are both
heading over there right now.
-Those two?
-Yeah, that's right.
Your brother will be just fine.
Trust me.
Just concentrate on the
enemy in front of you.
-Fell on a pile of sand, I see.
You would do that, wouldn't you?
However-- the fight's over.
You just don't know it.
-Leaf Hurricane!
-Huh?
-The hero always saves the
day at the last moment.
-Damn right he does!
Sorry to keep you waiting Gaara.
-Naruto?
-You were there to
save our skin when
we were chasing
after Sasuke, right?
This is our chance to
return the favor for ya.
Now, go on, get moving.
We'll take care of this guy.
You've got a pupil who
needs saving, don't you?
-To think he could
press you this far.
SAKURA: Lee!
-Sakura!
-Go on.
Just leave Gaara
in my hands, OK?
You should be helping Naruto.
-(HAPPILY) Hey, Sakura!
-Absolutely.
All right then, allow me
to get the ball rolling.
-Be careful.
His armor can
absorb your chakra.
-He's right kid.
I'll suck up every bit of it.
-I see.
So we cannot rely on our
usual abilities, can we?
-Aw, who cares!
If you're out of chakra,
there's always guts.
-Right!
If there is a will,
there is a way.
KUJAKU (VOICEOVER): I was right.
The backup team hasn't
launched a single attack,
which means they have
no long-range jutsu.
I'll just have to keep
them at arm's length.
Now, relinquish your
flesh to the wind.
INOUE (VOICEOVER): All her
attention's on those two.
Now's my chance.
Mind Destruction jutsu!
SHIKAMARU: Inoue!
-What?
Are you kidding me?
You'll have to be a lot
faster than that sweetheart.
-Ha!
Also predictable.
Keep trying, hon,
you'll never touch me.
-Ha!
We'll see about that.
-Inoue, you just stay put, OK?
-K.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): Shino,
Sakura, I'm counting on you.
-One of them is wounded
by the waterfall.
KIBA: Fang over Fang!
-Gotcha!
CHOJI: Partial Expansion jutsu!
Huh?
-(ANGRILY) What the--
What are you doing?
-What is this?
Are you three trying to mock me?
SUIKO (VOICEOVER): Once I've
sucked up all their chakra,
it'll be payback time.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): I
finished the contusion,
but his chakra
loss is staggering.
GAARA: Contact
from your friends?
SAKURA: Inoue is hurt?
-(URGENTLY) Go!
-Huh?
Yeah, but in your condition--
-I'll be perfectly fine.
Now, get going.
She needs you.
-Try not to overdo it.
-Got it.
-Hey, what are you
waiting around for?
You're comrades are in trouble.
-I have some time.
This'll be quick.
-Yeah, but--
-Bushy Brow!
KANKURO (VOICEOVER):
Damn it We need
to start working together here.
Huh?
Where's the mutt?
Broken pieces from
the Black Ant.
Wait!
is it a signal?
-Where going to try
to hit him again.
Back me up with the Crow.
You be ready too Choji.
-Right.
You got it.
KANKURO (VOICEOVER):
Huh, bossing me around.
-Time for our counterattack.
-Forget it.
Your jutsu will never reach.
-Yeah, well, like they say,
you never know until you try.
Let her rip.
-Wind Style Cyclone
Scythe Jutsu!
-Huh?
Hm, better work on your aim.
What the hell was that?
(SHOCKED) What the hell?
You couldn't reach
this far before.
-Let me show you.
Doesn't matter how
clear the water is,
current's thick enough
to produce a shadow.
By lifting up the
waterfall, I've
extended the reach
of my technique.
Shadow Possession
jutsu complete.
TEMARI: All right.
Summoning Blade Dance!
[screaming]
-Well, that's one down.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
Ah, she's something else.
INOUE (VOICEOVER): I
couldn't do a thing.
I feel so useless.
Everyone here pitched
in except for me.
SAKURA: Inoue.
-Gaara!
-Ha!
All your sands gone.
What are you going to do?
NARUTO: What is he--
ROCK LEE: He's getting
sand from his armor.
-Now way!
His-- his sand should
be waterlogged now
if I absorbed his chakra.
-This is all the weapon I need.
-Are you OK Gaara?
-Now, to end it.
MATSURI (VOICEOVER): Ah!
Gaara Sensei!
-Get going.
You can leave the
rest to us, OK?
-Man Beast Clone!
[barking]
-Fang Over Fang!
CHOJI: Partial Expansion jutsu!
-Annoying little flies!
Enough!
Dragon Eyes Fang
Release Dark Sword!
What?
Damn it!
-Now, the puppet show.
Secret Black Move Iron Maiden!
[screaming]
-Show's over.
-Yeah, we did it.
GAARA (VOICEOVER): Matsuri.
NEJI (VOICEOVER): Gaara, he's--
HINATA (VOICEOVER): A
shinobi's carrying a child.
SHINO (VOICEOVER): He's
heading for the valley.
-The last one.
Gaara's chasing after him.
-Your kidding.
-Are you OK Bushy Brow?
I'm sure Sakura should
be back here any minute.
-I am all right.
-Then, I'm going after Gaara.
-Good luck to you.
I will catch up as
soon as possible.
GAARA (VOICEOVER):
No where to run.
Matsuri.
[music playing]
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): You know
who the Four Celestial's are?
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): They're
ninja from the Village
of Artisans with a history of
malice towards the Five Great
Nations.
They'd been dabbling
in elicit research,
trying to create
an ultimate weapon.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): I see.
So the people of the village
caught on and evacuated.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): Exactly.
Kakashi, I want your team
over there immediately.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): Understood.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next time,
The Ultimate Weapon Reborn.