[theme song]
-(VOICEOVER) I am not going to
be the only one to lose here.
Guy-sensei, please
let this work.
It is now or never!
To protect and maintain
one's own ninja way.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
The Fifth Gate.
A splendid ninja is born.
-His whole body's changing.
-[gasps]
-He's turning red!
-Ahh!
-What's it mean?
What's happening?
-Ahh!
-He's opened the Third Gate.
The Gate of Life.
Now he'll attack.
-Oh, no.
Not yet.
-Hm?
-The Fourth Gate.
Gate of Pain.
Open!
Ahh!
-Incredible.
No one can do that through
sheer effort alone.
The boy's truly a genius!
-Ahh!
[multiple explosions]
-Unh!
[cries of strain]
-He's faster than ever!
-Unh.
Huh?
-Whoa.
-Gotta.
-Where'd they go?
-Huh?
Up there!
-Unh.
Uh.
Hunh.
-There's Gaara, but
what happened to Lee?
-He's just done.
-(VOICEOVER) The sand can't
move fast enough to protect him.
-Hiding behind that
sand armor again, eh?
Well, we will see about that.
-Unh.
-Ah.
Uh!
-(VOICEOVER) My armor can't
withstand this pounding.
It's crumbling away.
LEE: You are a tough one.
Try this!
-(VOICEOVER) His muscles are
tearing themselves apart.
-(VOICEOVER) Is that really Lee?
But when?
How?
-One more, and we are finished!
The Big Gate, Gate
of Closing, open!
-(VOICEOVER) No human
can move like this.
Impossible to defend myself.
-Are you watching, Neji?
I was saving this ace in the
hole to use you against you!
See what you have
to look forward to?
-Uh-ugh!
Unh.
Uh.
[sash creaks and strains]
-(VOICEOVER) His sand
shield can't keep up.
-(VOICEOVER) He's in trouble!
-Whoa!
-(VOICEOVER) The Hidden Lotus.
A taijutsu combination
of such blinding
speed that no one can
defend himself against it.
Not even Neji.
Gaara's sand shield is useless.
-(VOICEOVER) Now, to finish it.
[screams]
-[gasps]
-Hidden Lotus!
[cries of distress]
-Mm mm!
-So fast.
I couldn't see a thing!
-Ya ah!
[metallic click]
-(VOICEOVER) What's happening?
-(VOICEOVER) The gourd
is turning into sand.
-Ah unh.
Unh uh eh ah.
Uh.
Unh.
-Unbelievable.
He did it!
-Gaara!
-Is it over?
-Ah?
-What's that?
Down there.
-[gasping]
-[gasp]
[strained breathing]
[scoffs]
(VOICEOVER) Unbelievable!
He cushioned his fall by
turning that gourd into sand.
[strained breathing]
[blowing sand]
-Unh.
Unh.
Ah.
-I know what's coming now.
-Sands takra.
-Uh.
Ah.
A-ah.
(VOICEOVER) Impossible.
He not only survived
the Hidden Lotus.
He is able to go on the attack.
Uh.
[straining against sand]
Ahh ahh.
-Sand coffin.
-Ahh!
(VOICEOVER) I'm not going
to be the who loses.
I have my own ninja way.
Uh ah.
-Unh.
-No.
-Now you die.
Uh?
Unh.
[breathing shakily]
[glass shattering]
Unh uh.
But why?
He failed.
Unh.
Why save him?
-Because he's--
LEE (VOICEOVER):
[laughs] I'm all right.
Getting stronger all the time.
The tuning exam.
I am going to make
you proud, Guy-sensei.
I want to show I can be as
fine a ninja as well, even if I
do not have ninjutsu
or genjutsu.
I want to prove it
to the whole world!
-Because he's, he's my student.
And also because
he's precious to me.
-Hm?
-He's precious to him?
A student?
-(VOICEOVER) That's a sentiment
that Gaara couldn't even begin
to understand.
-Huh?
-I quit.
-He what?
He quits?
-But it's too late for Lee.
He lost the match the
minute Guy intervened.
-The winner is-- uh?
-Huh?
-Huh!
-[gasps]
-Huh?
-Unh.
[gasp] It can't be!
-(VOICEOVER) After all that,
he shouldn't be able to move,
let alone stand up.
-No, Lee.
It's all right.
It's all over now.
Anyway, you're in no
condition to-- Lee.
(VOICE BREAKING) Oh, Lee.
[sobs] What have I done?
Look at you.
Not even conscious, and
still determined to show
the world what you can do.
-He's out called.
Nothing keeping him up
but sheer will power.
-Lee, you've already proven it.
[cries] You are
a splendid ninja.
-The winner is Gaara.
-[scoffs]
-Lee!
-Sakura!
There is nothing you can
do for him right now.
There are times when sympathetic
words only make things worse.
-Uh.
-Hmph.
I knew he couldn't be Gaara.
-(VOICEOVER) Still, it was a lot
tougher match than we thought.
-Unh.
Uh!
-Naruto.
-(VOICEOVER) I can't
believe it, Lee lost to him?
-Hurry!
This boy needs attention.
-Uh, uh. [gasp] Bushy-brow!
-(VOICEOVER) Lee!
- [gasps] You are his
teacher, aren't you?
-I am.
What is it?
-Will you come with me?
MEDIC 1: Careful with him.
That's right.
Easy.
MEDIC 2: The boy's breathing
is faint, but steady.
There are bone
fractures and muscle
tears throughout his body.
He's facing a long and
difficult rehabilitation.
But I'm afraid that's
not the worst of it.
His left arm and
leg in particular
have suffered massive damage.
I'm sorry.
I know how much it
means to you both,
but he'll never fight again.
His days as a Shinobi are over.
-No.
He's wrong.
It can't be true.
I get him first.
This weirdo is mine.
-No, thank you.
Right now, the only one I
want to fight is Uchiha.
-Ah!
What are you doing?
-Naruto, I get where you
are coming from, believe me.
But the rules all fighting
must be done officially
in a match, the loser
beating the gifted genius
through sheer will power.
Now, would not that make
for an exciting match?
Even if I'm the one who
is going to have to Neji.
-[crying]
GUY (VOICEOVER): Lee.
Oh, forgive me.
I couldn't bear the
thought of you losing.
I wanted you to
achieve your goal,
to prove that your ninja
way was the right way.
-Yes!
I did it!
I finally mastered the jutsu.
Yes, yes, yes!
GUY (VOICEOVER): This jutsu.
In the end, only Lee
could make it his own.
As of today, they
were all genin.
So now, tell me.
Why have you done it?
What are your goals?
Hm?
-How about me, Sensei?
I want to show I can be as
fine a ninja as well, even if I
do not have ninjutsu
or genjutsu.
I want to prove it
to the whole world.
GUY (VOICEOVER): Ah,
it was all my fault.
I should've stopped it.
Forgive me.
Lee!
-It's not true.
It can't be true!
Easy for you to say it's over!
What about Bushy-brow?
What's he supposed to do now?
Failure!
I thought you said we could win!
I thought you were going
to show how a failure can--
It was a lie, wasn't it?
Eh.
-That's enough, Naruto.
-Eh.
But Sensei, it isn't fair!
All he ever wanted
was to prove himself
against Sasuke and Neji.
-And maybe that's what
led to his downfall.
-[sobs]
-He was fixated on that
goal that he sacrificed
his body, his
future, to attain it.
And now that goal
is unattainable.
-[sobs]
-But you're wrong about
one thing, Naruto.
It wasn't just Sasuke and
Neji he was thinking of.
It was you, too.
That's right.
He risked everything
just for the hope
of meeting you in combat.
Remember that.
Be worthy of his sacrifice.
-(VOICEOVER) Lee.
I wonder if he'll be all right?
-(VOICEOVER) Lee, you didn't
understand, even at the end.
Fate will never
smile on the fortunes
of a ninja who seeks victory
by falling on his own sword,
or demanding that
others fall on theirs.
-Huh?
-(VOICEOVER) So the worst
didn't happen after all.
-Good to have you back, Gaara.
-Guy.
-Huh?
-What I said earlier,
it was out of line.
I was being a
self-righteous fool.
I realize now that if
I'd been in your shoes,
I probably couldn't
have stopped him either.
-Huh?
-Come on, Guy.
Let's go up.
They can't start the next match
with us standing here, right?
-Now then, the last
two competitors,
will you please step forward?
- [chuckling] (VOICEOVER)
So it's finally my turn.
-(VOICEOVER) Just keep
your eyes on the prize,
all you can eat barbecue.
-(VOICEOVER) My job is to
survive the main tournament
and battle Sasuke, isn't
that right, Lord Orochimaru?
I wouldn't to disappoint you.
I begin to see
through your design.
The reason you set
us against Sasuke,
but forbid us from killing him.
The curse you put on him.
We were your pawns,
weren't we, my Lord?
Put here merely to test the
limits of his abilities.
It's not Sasuke's life you want.
It's Sasuke himself.
You played us all
for fools, even me.
-All right.
The 10th and final
match will begin.
[closing theme song]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Hey, Sakura.
Where's Kagashi-sensei?
SAKURA (VOICECOVER): Naruto,
have you noticed it's--
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): We've
got to start my training
for the main tournament.
Where is he?
SAKURA (VOICECOVER):
I don't know.
With Sasuke, probably.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Ah!
Figures.
Hey, what's wrong, Sakura?
You seem kind of down.
SAKURA (VOICECOVER):
Just uneasy.
There's something not right.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Well, whatever.
Next time, "A
Shadow in Darkness".
Danger approaches Sasuke.
SAKURA (VOICECOVER):
I've got a bad feeling.