[music playing]
[theme music]
-All right, heads
up, you maggots!
The second part of
the test has begun!
-You know who we're looking for.
-Yeah.
Those three brats.
-Well all right!
Here we go guys!
-OK.
First thing we got
to do is to find it.
Are you ready, Hinata?
-Um hm.
-Take it easy, Lee.
The test's only just begun.
-That may be.
But still-- whoever
our enemies are,
I want to find them
before they find us.
-We have only one target.
Stay focused on it.
[screaming]
-Sounds like the fun has begun.
-That sounded like
someone screaming.
I do not like this place.
-Oh come on!
There's nothing to be scared of!
It's gonna be a piece of cake!
But excuse me a second.
I really gotta, you know.
-Are you kidding me?!
Get out of here!
What is this?!
A kennel?!
Not in front of me you don't!
Find a bush or something!
-Eat or Be Eaten.
Panic in the Forest.
-Ah Whew.
Ah.
Ah, yeah.
Man, that was a lot.
I wrote my whole name.
-You are such a pig!
You're really disgusting
sometimes, you know that?
-Ah.
[gasp]
[groan]
-Hey, it wasn't that bad.
Don't you think that was
going a little overboard?
-Yeah, what the heck
was that all about?
-OK, where's the real Naruto?
-Huh?
-Better watch out, Sakura.
I think he's gone crazy.
-Yeah right.
Then what happened
to that scratch
you got from the examiner?
-Huh?
-And I noticed you've
got your shuriken
holster on your left side.
Naruto's right-handed.
Your transformation skill
is worse than Naruto's.
Tell me who you are.
-So you got me.
I'm still gonna
take your scroll.
-So which one of you has it?
Or do I take you both out?
-Fire style!
Phoenix flower jutsu!
-(ANGRILY) Hey get me out of it!
-Little idiot.
-Thank you.
-Better get your
mind on the game.
A paper bomb.?
[grunt]
-Sorry.
This is one test you fail.
Now hand over the
scroll, or you die.
-[gasp] Sasuke!
-[chuckle]
-[grunt] Oh no you don't!
SASUKE: (VOICEOVER) Well, well.
Better late than never, I guess.
Focus my chakra.
[grunt]
-Huh?
-Are you all right?
-Don't just stand there, Sakura.
Chances are, this
guy's not alone.
Watch out!
The others could
strike any second now!
-I wish.
I came alone so as not
to arouse suspicion.
Big mistake.
SASUKE: (VOICEOVER)
So much for him.
For now.
-That proves that we can't
just trust appearances.
We have to come up with a way
of knowing that each of us
is who we say we are, and
not some impostor using
a Transformation Jutsu.
-Mm hm.
-All right, so what do we do?
-We need a password.
-What kind of password?
-A secret one.
Something known only
to the three of us.
And don't trust anyone
who doesn't know it.
No matter what.
OK, listen closely, because
I only want to say this once.
The question will be,
when does a ninja strike?
And the response is, a ninja
waits until the time is right,
when the enemy sleeps and drops
his guard, when his weapons lie
forgotten in the
stillness of the night.
That is the moment
for a ninja to strike.
Got it?
-I got it.
-You got one a little shorter?
-(FRUSTRATED GROWL)
SASUKE: No, Naruto.
That's it.
SAKURA: Aw, come on!
What's wrong?
Didn't you get it?
I memorized It easy.
NARUTO: Yeah sure.
I got it.
No problem.
I just thought it was
going to be a password, not
a pass speech.
SASUKE: All right then,
I'll take the scroll.
-Wait a minute, Sasuke.
I-- ah!
What was that?
-[wind screaming] [blast]
-[gasping]
-What is it now?
[blast]
-All right.
You two fan out into the
woods, and keep your eyes open.
(Evilly) I'll handle this alone.
-Sakura.
-Sasuke!
What was that?
-Stay there!
First answer the question.
When does a ninja strike?
-Oh, mm.
A ninja waits until
the time is right.
When the enemy sleeps and drops
his guard, when his weapons lie
forgotten in the
stillness of the night,
that is the moment
for a ninja to strike.
-Good.
NARUTO: [gasp] Hey!
What's up?
You guys OK?
SAKURA: -Don't come any closer.
NARUTO: Huh?
SAKURA: What's the password?
-Oh sure, no problem.
OK, a ninja waits until
the time is right.
When the enemy sleeps and drops
his guard, when his weapons lie
forgotten in the
stillness of the night,
that is the moment
for a ninja to strike.
-[sigh]
-Hm.
-Aaahh.
-Huh?
Aaahh! [groan] What was that!
You could've killed me!
-Gotta hand it to you, you're
quicker than the last one.
-What are you talking about?
What was wrong with that?
He just got the password
right, word for word.
-Exactly.
That's what's wrong.
-Huh?
-You really think Naruto
could memorize all that?
And get it word for word?
Not the Naruto I know,
not in a million years.
You'd have a better chance
teaching it to a hamster.
-Oh right.
You've got a point.
-Besides, you saw
the way this guy
moved when he dodged my attack.
That was definitely
not a Naruto move.
All right, come on
out, whoever you are.
Party's over.
-Hm hm!
Aren't we the clever one?
Tell me, if your
teammate is really
that dimwitted, why
would you come up
with a password he'd
never be able to remember?
-You see, it wasn't
meant for Naruto,
so much as for anybody
who might happen
to be nearby, trying
to eavesdrop on us.
It was meant as a trap.
And you stumbled right into it.
-I'm impressed.
You certainly haven't
dropped your guard, have you?
This promises to be
very entertaining.
SAKURA: (VOICEOVER) She gives
new meaning to the word creepy.
Where is Naruto?
-[groan] OK, upsy daisy.
Huh?
Hey, where did
Sasuke and Sakura go?
I wonder if they-- huh?
Whoa!
Oh my gosh!
That's, that's, that's
that is one big snake!
[aaghh!] Huh oh!
[groan] I can't move.
[aaghh!]
-[gasp]
-Ah!
You'd love to get your hands on
our earth scroll, wouldn't you?
It would go so nicely
with your heaven scroll.
-[gasp]
-Well, when this is
all over, one of us
will have both scrolls.
-[gasp]
-And the other will be dead.
-[screams]
-[gasp]
SASUKE: (VOICEOVER)
Is this an illusion?
[vomiting] No, it's
more than that.
Her thirst for blood
is almost palpable.
Looking in her eyes, I saw
the moment of my own death.
Who is she?
What is she?
Sa-- Sakura?
No use.
She's got it worse than me.
We've got to get out of here.
Get away from her.
She's death.
NARUTO: Let me out of here!
I'll make you sorry
you ever swallowed me,
you stinking jerk!
Let me out!
Hey, wait a second.
Here, [groan] wouldn't
you rather have this?
I was saving this
rice ball for lunch.
It's all gone!
And I'll be digested just
like that in another minute.
[screams] No!
Let me out!
Sakura!
Sasuke!
Get me out of here!
--[evil laughter] You're
paralyzed with fear.
SASUKE: [groan] (VOICEOVER)
What's wrong with me?
Move.
Come on, move Sasuke, move.
That's it.
You can do this.
Yes. [groan] That's right.
Even if it's just a little.
You've got to move.
-Very good.
Now what happens?
SASUKE: (VOICEOVER) It's no use.
[groan] I can't move.
-Don't worry, I'll
make it quick.
But I don't have to
tell you that, do I?
You've seen it
with your own eyes.
(EVIL LAUGHTER) I expected
you to be more of a challenge.
How disappointing.
NARUTO: (VOICEOVER)
I can't believe it.
Is this really how it ends?
Iruka Sensei.
Old man Hokage.
Konohamaru.
Kakashi Sensei.
Oh, Sakura.
Well, some people I'll
miss more than others.
Hm.
I don't know what
Sasuke's problem was.
The guy was always
jealous of me.
Still, we had our moments.
Like the time we
helped Kakashi Sensei
bring down that creep, Zabuza.
In a way, we were probably
good for each other,
always competing, pushing
each other in every challenge,
always looking for
that final showdown,
to prove which
one of us is best.
Hey!
Wait a minute, that's right!
We never did have
our final showdown.
We never proved who's best.
(Both Naruto and Sasuke)
I want some more!
NARUTO: (VOICEOVER) No way.
Can't just leave things
up in the air like that.
That's it.
I'm out of here.
Whether Slitherpuss
likes it, or not.
-So that's how it is.
-[gasp]
-Oh, Sasuke. [gasp]
VILLAINESS: (VOICEOVER)
A desperate move.
But a clever one.
Sasuke: (VOICEOVER) Move Sasuke.
You've got to move.
Move!
[aagghh]
VILLAINESS: (VOICEOVER) He
overcame the fear with pain.
So.
This prey is not so
helpless after all.
NARUTO: (VOICEOVER)
Shadow clone jutsu!
Sorry, but you picked
the wrong shinobi.
I'm going to be Hokage one day.
If you think I'm going to
end up a pile of snake crap
in the woods, you're crazy!
-[grunt]
-[gasp] That wound's deep.
Will you be all right?
Sasuke: (VOICEOVER) Gotta move.
Gotta get away from her.
But how?
Where?
SAKURA: (VOICEOVER) Man, I've
never seen Sasuke like this.
He's got me scared.
[gasp] Sasuke, watch out!
-Unbelievable.
I didn't even notice.
I'm losing it!
[groan] No!
Stay away!
[gasp]
-[gasp]
VILLAINESS: I sense your
fear and desperation.
It's only natural.
The prey must never
let down it's guard,
not even for a moment, in the
presence of it's predator.
(EVIL LAUGHTER)
-[gasp]
-[aagghh!]
NARUTO: Looks like
I came just in time.
-Naruto!
-Oh, and by the way, what
was that password again?
[singing Japanese]
-How do you like that?
I turn my back for one
minute, and Slitherlips
has got my teammates so
freaked, they can hardly move.
Well, I'm not afraid of snakes.
And I just spent the
last hour inside of one.
These guys.
Sometimes I wonder what
they'd do without me.
Hey, never fear.
The reptile crew is here.
Next time, Naruto's
counter-attack.
Never give in!
I don't care who this creep is.
Nobody sticks their
tongue out at me.