[theme music]
-Any second now!
Look, the water's
spinning! it's gonna
be even easier than I thought
to get this balloon to burst!
-Good, let me know
when you've done it.
Meanwhile, I'll just
get comfortable.
It's time for a little break.
-Hey, what do you
think you're doing?
-I might as well catch a little
shut-eye while I'm waiting.
This stuff helps me sleep.
[gulps]
-Hunh.
Don't get too comfortable.
This won't take long.
-Yeah, Yeah, OK.
You just let me know when
you've figured it out.
-You wait and see!
Ha!
I'll have this thing down
before you even close your eyes,
you lazy old buzzard!
[roars]
NARUTO: Keep on training!
Pop goes the water balloon!
[snoring]
-[breathing heavily] Man!
This is crazy!
What do I have to do?
-Huh?
Well, did you do it?
-Ugh!
Uhhhh, well, not quite,
but I'm really close.
Almost there!
-Ahhh.
I was hoping for maybe 40 winks,
but that was more like 840.
--[growling] Come
on, how do I do it?
How do I get it to burst?
-Guh.
Like I've said
before, you won't know
how it's done until
after you've done it.
-Ungh.
-[chuckling] However,
-Huh?
-In your case, even
though ideally you're
supposed to master this jutsu
by yourself through trial
and error-- Mmhmm,
-Mmhmm?
-Maybe I'll give
you a small hint
to point you in the
right direction.
All right, now get the water
in the balloon spinning again.
-Huh?
OK.
Nngh.
[water sloshing]
-To the right or the left?
Which direction are you
making the water rotate?
-Huh?
Well, to the left, I guess.
-Now walk over here to me.
-Uh, uh.
-Hmph!
I thought as much.
-Huh?
You thought what?
-The problem is, you're
actually a right rotation type.
-A what?
-Yeah, that's the
trouble right there.
You've got your chakra
working against itself.
A good way to build
up chakra in the body
is to spin it into a tight
spiral, like a spring.
Whether the chakra spins
to the left or the right
depends on the individual.
Some people are left rotation
types, some are right.
But if you're spinning
the water in the balloon
in the opposite direction from
your natural rotation type,
your chakra's just
counteracting itself.
Heh.
No wonder you're having trouble.
It's something that
most ninja in training
eventually figure out for
themselves, but in your case--
-Yeah, OK, but how
were you able to tell
that I'm a right rotating
type or whatever it is?
Dah!
-By the way your hair grows.
If your hair grows
to the right, that
means you're a
right rotation type.
If it grows to the
left, you're a lefty.
It's pretty simple, really.
-Huh.
If I ever brushed my hair,
I might have known that.
-You get it now?
It might help if you set the
water in the balloon rotating
to the right.
-Man, I never even
knew my hair rotated.
Forget about which way.
-I think you'll find this is the
perfect jutsu for you, Naruto.
All it requires is chakra.
No complicated hand
signs to to mastered.
With a little effort, even a
slow learner can get this one.
I know that you can do it.
-Hey!
Who you calling a slow learner?
Are you forgetting who I am?
I'm the guy who's going
to be hokage some day!
I bet you in three days I'll
have this whole thing nailed.
You won't be smiling then!
-Three days?
This jutsu was handed
down to us by none other
than the fourth hokage!
-Huh?
-Yes, and it took the fourth
hokage three whole years
to perfect it.
In terms of difficulty, this
is the second hardest jutsu
of all.
It's one of the
master-rank ninjutsu.
To learn this move
requires mastering
three different
phases of training.
The water balloon burst
is only the first.
NARUTO: It took the
fourth hokage three years
and he was the best!
-And you, who haven't even
finished the first phase yet,
you're going to master
it in three days, huh?
Yeah, right!
Knock yourself out, kid.
Meanwhile, if it's all
at the same to you,
I'm heading back to town.
I've been neglecting
my research.
It's getting late.
You coming?
NARUTO: Second from
the top in difficulty.
The fourth hokage's ninjutsu!
Heh.
I'll stick around
a little longer.
-Hmph!
See you later, then.
Don't overdo it!
[crowd chattering]
JIRAYA: Huh.
I wonder if Naruto's
got what it takes.
I can't wait to
see what happens.
-What's cookin', good lookin'?
Are you the guys
we've heard about?
The one doing research
on pretty girls?
-Yeah!
That's right!
You've heard of me?
-We'd be glad to help
you with your research.
Buy us dinner.
We'll stamp your card.
When the card's full,
we'll tell you everything.
-Woohoo!
Sounds like fun!
What's your name, sweetie?
-Uh uh!
Dinner first.
[door opening]
[cat meowing]
-Leave him alone now, Whiskers.
Come on down.
[cat meows]
-'Scuse me.
Which way's the restroom?
NARUTO: I don't have three
years to waste on this jutsu!
OK!
Here we go, Naruto!
You're gonna nail
this thing today!
Come on and burst,
you stupid balloon!
Ugh.
Nothing!
What do I gotta do?
FEMALE SPEAKER: I just
love your hair, Jiraiya.
Is that its real color?
--[laughing] Darlin',
everything about me is real.
-[growling] Gimme a break!
NARUTO: It's been
three days and nothing!
It stretches but it won't burst!
Rotating it the left
doesn't make any difference!
That dang Pervy Sage
knows something I don't.
But what?
-[laughing] Man, oh man!
I just love this town!
[snoring]
-Dah!
Ugh, what the-- Yuck.
He could seriously
use some mouthwash.
OK, gotta build up my strength.
Ahhh.
Huh?
Uh.
What-- What's wrong with me?
Come on!
Great!
Now I'm having a
nervous breakdown.
That's all I need.
-With a little effort, even a
slow learner can get this one.
I know that you can do it.
NARUTO: He said there
were no complicated hand
signs to learn.
[toilet flushing]
[door opening]
-Huh?
[cat meows]
-Hey, leave that alone.
It's not a toy!
[rubber squeaking]
[splat]
[cat meowing and hissing]
-Huh That's it!
[footsteps]
[door opening and closing]
-Nngh.
-Rise and shine, Pervy Sage.
Come on, drag those
old bones out of bed.
-Uhhh, good.
Since you're here, bring
some water, would ya?
-Some water?
Hmph!
[RUBBER SQUEAKING AND WATER
SLOSHING]
[splat]
-Yeargh!
-So that's the first
phase of training.
What's next?
-Oh, you did it, huh?
Would you mind giving me
a little demonstration?
-Watch carefully.
Keep your eyes on the balloon.
Nnnhgh!
JIRAIYA: Interesting.
-Hnnggh!
[rubber squeaking]
[splat]
-There, old man!
Whatcha think of that, huh?
[snores]
-Huh?
What?
You-- Gahhh!
-Sorry about that.
I've just been working
day and night, you
know, doing research.
NARUTO: Research, huh?
Is that what you call it?
JIRAIYA: [slurping] Huh.
Gotta hand it to him.
He found a way to do it.
By steadying it
with his left hand
and applying chakra
with his right.
It's a weird idea, but
then hey, he's a weird kid.
And weird isn't necessarily bad.
[chuckles]
Looks like you did it.
Good for you.
I guess that little tip I
gave you helped out after all.
[cat meowing]
-Actually, I've really
got him to thank.
-Huh?
-I was watching this guy
play around with my balloon
and I got a brilliant idea.
See, he kept knocking
it back and forth,
which meant the water
inside must be going back,
too, in different directions.
That's when it came to me.
-And what would be, exactly?
-I thought back to
when you were showing
me what to do that first time.
I remembered how bumpy
the surface of the balloon
got, like it was boiling.
My problem was, I was
making the water rotate,
but in only one direction.
That's why my balloon was
smooth, not bumpy like yours.
If it was going to burst, I
had to get the water spinning
in a bunch of
different directions,
bumping into itself.
So once I finally figured that
part out, the rest was easy.
JIRAIYA: Well, he still may
not be capable of executing it
with only one hand,
but he found a way.
And it works.
-Hee hee hee.
What can I say?
I rule, huh?
-OK, then.
You have successfully
completed the first step.
-All right!
[cat meowing]
-Here, let me show it
to you one more time.
Want to see it again?
Ungh.
JIRAIYA: He's used
up a lot of chakra.
Can his chakra network
withstand the strain?
And it only gets
harder from here.
-Hee hee!
-Uhhh.
All right, then.
You ready to proceed
to the second step now?
-Yeah!
Enough with the kid stuff.
What's next?
Weapons, or--
-There you go.
-Huh?
A rubber ball?
Hey!
Ah, come on.
You're kidding me, right?
-Let's see if you
can pop this one.
[splat]
-Huh?
-And let me tell you, it's a
lot harder than a water balloon.
[rubber squeaking]
NARUTO: Ugh.
This is hard.
-The first element is rotation.
The second element is force.
But this object is solid.
There's no water
inside, so it's far more
difficult to exert your
chakra rotation on it.
-Yeah, I can see that.
-I'll leave it to
you to figure out.
NARUTO: I'll have to
come up with something
new for this one.
-And in the meanwhile, I
better get back to my research.
-Hey, Pervy Sage!
Don't go away again!
Come on, stay and help
me with my training!
Don't leave me out
here by myself!
-Stop whining!
There's one part of this process
you don't seem to understand.
I said I'd be your teacher,
not your father or your best
friend.
I'm not here to hold your hand.
You have to do this by
yourself or not at all.
Stop being a child and learn how
to stand on your own two feet,
like a shinobi.
-Uh.
All right, I will.
I was just hoping before
you go you could just
show it to me one more time.
-Pay me.
-Get out of here, you
greedy old skirt chaser!
You're one to talk about growing
up and acting like a shinobi!
Why don't you act
like a shinobi instead
of a pervy old bag of bones?
NARUTO: [heavy breathing]
a Just like he said,
this is way more difficult
than the water balloon!
My arms and hands
are killing me.
Don't know how much
more they can take.
[thump]
[grunts and shouts]
-How many days of doing the
same thing over and over?
[labored breathing]
-It's one of the
master-rank ninjutsu.
Stop whining!
I'm not holding your hand.
You have to do this
yourself or not at all.
-All right.
-Hey, Naruto!
-What are you doing
here, Pervy Sage?
-I want you to hop into
town and grab me some lunch.
-Huh?
Why do I have to?
-I'm your teacher, and
a student is always
obliged to obey his teacher.
-Grrr.
-Here you go, son.
-Thanks, thanks a lot.
"I'm your teacher."
Some teacher!
What's he taught me?
Nothin'.
CHILD: I one of those, Dad!
Can I?
The frozen food on a stick.
Please?
-There you go.
-Awww.
I'm big now!
I can eat the whole
t hing myself.
-No, we'll share.
Besides, what would
your mother say
if I let you spoil your supper?
-OK.
-Say, I was wondering.
Well, um, maybe you could
stick around for a while
today, help me train?
-Sorry, no time.
I've got to go into town
and keep an appointment
with someone who's helping
me with my research.
It's up to you to figure
out by yourself, Naruto.
Otherwise, there's no
point in even learning it,
for all the good it will do you.
I thought I made it
clear three weeks ago.
Stop acting like
a helpless child!
You're a ninja.
-Haha!
Oh, sure!
Of course.
Don't worry about
me, I understand.
Forget about it.
I was just asking, that's all.
Go on and do whatever you
have to do, Pervy Sage.
-No!
You did that?
I don't think I believe you.
-Hey, it's true!
Jiraiya is no laiya!
[laughter]
[crickets chirping]
[gasps of pain]
[door opening and closing]
-Ah, geez.
What's the use?
It won't pop, no
matter how hard I try!
I'm just wasting
my time, burning up
chakra for no good reason.
NARUTO: And this pain!
The more I try to increase
the flow, the more it hurts.
But I have to.
I have to give it all I've
got or it'll never pop!
But what if all I've
got isn't enough?
That's it!
If I can work through the
pain to generate more chakra
and then push it right to the
limit of what I can endure--
nngh, not enough yet.
Not yet!
Ahhh!
Still not enough!
[grunting] Now!
Yeah!
I've got it!
[air deflating]
-[big breath] Hee hee!
-Well, well!
We seem to have made progress.
-Hmm?
Yeah, but I only made it spring
a leak, not burst like you did.
-Boy, you're getting awfully
picky all of a sudden.
Here, want one?
You've come far and
all on your own.
-Huh?
[laughing] It's delicious!
--[laughing] So, you ready
to try a little experiment?
-Sure, what?
-Give me your right hand.
-Hmm?
[laughing]
-Uh, what is it?
[theme music]
NARUTO: Focus, he says.
Focus, focus, focus!
Doesn't he know I'm
easily distracted?
It's always been my weak
spot all through training.
Iruka-sensei used to chew me
out about my lack of focus.
I wish I'd paid more attention
to him, but I was, you know,
distracted!
Focus, focus, focus!
What am I, a telescope?
Next time, "Focal Point:
The Mark of the Leaf!"
Focus on this, why don't ya?
[theme music]