[theme music]
KARASHI (VOICEOVER): Come on.
Come on.
-It appears the villagers
have come out to welcome us.
-Everyone down there looks safe.
-Then I guess the
Kurosuke Family just
ran away with their
tails between their legs.
-Oh.
-Hey, guys!
[laughter]
-Perfect.
They're here.
-Naruto, don't come.
It's a trap.
-If you value your life,
you'll keep your mouth shut.
-Karashi, I thought
you had repented.
What are you doing?
-Come on.
Did you really expect
me to shamefully go back
to that curry shop?
Now's our chance.
-Huh?
[laughter]
-You see that?
Even without sir
Raiga's awesome might,
the Kurosuke
Family's everlasting.
NARUTO: Hey.
What are you looking for anyway?
-What do you think
we're looking for?
Those stinking brats.
-Are you referring to us?
-Hee-hee.
You crushed the wrong brats.
Those were just our Shadow
Clone and Transformation Jutsu.
-Take formation.
-Ninja Art.
Black Tornado!
-Huh?
Sorry, man.
Those guys were also
made with our jutsu.
-We saw right
through your ambush.
-Now it's my turn!
-Leaf Hurricane!
-Disperse!
-Byakugan!
Two palms!
Four palms!
Eight palms!
Sixteen palms!
Thirty-two palms!
Eight Trigrams Sixty-four Palms!
-Here it comes!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Clone Spinning Axe Kick!
-The fights already over.
-Man, that hurt.
Huh?
What the heck?
That's no fair.
You could have
saved some for me!
And right when I
was finally gonna
get to try out my new jutsu!
What were you
thinking back there?
I mean, haven't you
learned your lesson by now?
-Well, Karashi?
What do you have to
say for yourself?
-It was just a joke.
-You think we'll believe
this is just a joke?
You have tormented
this whole village.
-But I didn't have
any other choice.
If I didn't do as
they told me, I
would have been killed
by the Kurosukes.
-Well, instead of
the Kurosukes, I'll
do the job with a
blow from my hammer!
-That's right.
-Come on!
-Give him here!
-I'm so sorry.
-Please, Lee.
Out of our way.
-You should strike me instead
until you're satisfied.
-Why would we punish you?
-At one time, Karashi was a
kind-hearted innocent young
man.
And I am partly responsible
for him joining a gang of thugs
like he did.
-Hm?
You're to blame?
-It was because of
my words he came
to think that power
is everything.
-Right.
That's what it.
Was I knew it was wrong,
but I had to do it anyway.
-Keep quiet Karashi.
-It is true.
Karashi was naive.
But even so, he
has a rare ability
to make life-saving curry.
Please let Karashi
atones for his sins.
Let him make curry!
And also, if Karashi
ever go astray again,
there will be consequences.
I swear I will punish
him with my two fists!
[gulp]
-Hey, listen up.
What does everybody think
about letting Lee and Grandma
Sancho handle this situation?
[murmuring]
-I don't know.
This is just so strange.
-Well, I suppose he was just
an underling of the Kurosuke
Family.
It's not like he attacked
our village himself.
Maybe it would be best to
have Rock Lee take Karashi
under his wing and see.
-Well, in that case.
-Thank you all very much.
-Uh-- yeah.
Thank you.
-And with that, our mission
is pretty much complete.
-No.
Not just yet.
NEJI: You all right?
-What does it matter if I'm
feeling all right or not?
I can't go on living
all alone like I am.
-Hey, come on.
Don't say that.
-Why don't we just leave
this weakling here?
Everyone ought to be able
to live by themselves.
But don't you need some
good friends in your life
who you can count on in a pinch?
-I'm talking about
the basics here.
I can't stand weak,
indecisive people.
-Since the day I was born,
I've always been frail.
And for most of my
life, a shabby cabin
was my entire world.
I have no memory of my parents.
I survived only because the
villagers took pity on me
and brought me small amounts
of food from time to time.
But even as fragile as I
was, I had a special power
no one else did.
-Here you go.
Th-- thanks you.
You cut your leg with a scythe.
Is it better now?
-Wait.
How did you know that?
Did I tell you?
-No.
I just knew about it.
-But-- but how?
I'm the only one who's been
here to see you since yesterday.
I saw it happen to
you from where I sit.
-No.
He's cursed!
RANMARU: as time went
on, everyone feared me.
I could see what was
happening outside.
-Did you hear?
That Ranmaru boy can see
everything we're doing.
-You mean to tell me we're
being spied on every day?
-Get out of here!
-We don't want your kind here!
-Get out of my village!
-Monster!
RANMARU: From then on, I had no
more visitors bringing me food.
All I could do is wait to die.
If it weren't for Raiga,
I wouldn't be alive.
-His past is so tragic.
I had no idea.
-Yes.
I agree.
-Raiga took me out
beyond those walls,
showing me a world I had
never experienced before.
-Ranmaru, open your eyes.
Take a look at the
outside world where
we'll be living
from now on, yes?
-Yes.
If Raiga isn't here
to care for me,
it's the same as
losing my own body.
-I think I see.
Raiga was able to become one
of the famous Seven Swordsmen,
because he was able to
borrow power from Ranmaru.
-So the two of you helped each
other to survive, didn't you?
-Yeah.
-That's not true!
Raiga was using you, so he could
do all those terrible things!
-Yes.
He might have been using me.
It's possible.
But whether good or bad, either
way it doesn't matter to me.
Because I'm just a tool to
sense things out anyway.
-Well, if that's
what you believe,
then you're not
really alive, are you?
Look.
If you're gonna
survive on your own,
you're going to have
to give it your all.
And you could start by
eating the curry of life.
That's sure to cheer you up!
-Yes.
That is right.
It will surely nourish you.
-Wait a sec.
Won't spicy curry hurt his body?
-Naruto, you shouldn't
have any either.
-What are you talking about?
As a matter of fact, the
more I eat of that slop,
the more I feel rejuvenated!
-And it was that very
curry that saved my life.
It really works!
-Until the day you
can walk on your own,
I'm going to have to
be your body for you.
Well?
-All right.
But I have one favor to ask.
-Huh?
-Byakugan.
Nothing.
I sense no life in Raiga.
-Can you see down
there, Ranmaru?
-Yes.
-Is everything OK?
-Yeah.
-Let's go.
We're done here.
NARUTO: Hey!
-What?
-Is that?
[laughter]
-One and two, one and two.
-Hey, Grandma Sancho!
-Such a racket.
What's gotten into you?
You'll get dust into my curry.
-It's Lee and the others.
They've finally come back.
-Yeah.
And Karashi is with them.
-Well, that's no reason to
forget your manners, now is it?
-But, Grandma, you mean--
well, aren't you happy?
-One and two, one and two.
-Careful.
Your snot's gonna fall in!
NARUTO: Grandma, Sancho.
I'm back.
-And Karashi is here as well.
-Oh mother.
I'm so sorry.
Please forgive me.
-Please, pardon his
behavior, ma'am.
From now on he is a changed man.
He will devote
himself to taking over
the Curry of Life restaurant
if you will let him.
-First things first.
You've got to eat.
-Huh?
Oh wow!
That looks great.
If you're not gonna
eat it, I don't
mind taking it off your hands.
-Actually, I've prepared
a plate for everybody.
Well, look at him.
My.
What a piqued little child.
-Oh, yeah.
You mind fixing up
a plate for him too?
-Make it is as mild as possible.
-Actually, I'd like
mine to be mild as well.
-As you wish.
-Mother, thanks for the food.
-That's my 300% Special
Punishment Curry.
-Spicy.
So spicy.
But it's good.
So good, mama.
GRANDMA: Dig in.
I made enough for everyone.
-Phew.
It's OK.
She made it real mild.
Hey, by the way, when you
were traveling with Raiga,
you were with the Seven
Ninja Swordsmen, weren't you?
Did you ever meet
a guy named Zabuza?
-Uh-- Zabuza?
No.
I--
-Oh.
I've got it.
There was this one
with a huge sword
wrapped in some bandage thing.
And he had these fish eyes.
-Oh yeah.
You must mean Kisame.
-Yeah.
Right.
Kisame.
So, do you happen to know where
that guy is or what he's up to?
-Uh-uh.
I heard that he slipped
away from the Mist Village.
I know his face, but I don't
know anything more than that.
[sigh] Oh well.
You still haven't eaten.
You want me to ask our host
to make you something else?
-Uh-uh.
I don't need it.
I'm not really in the
mood to eat right now.
-Thanks you so
much for your help.
-Yeah.
You solved everything.
NARUTO: Go on home and make
your village great again!
For everyone!
-Neji, where's Lee?
-His mission still
isn't incomplete yet.
[footsteps]
-Please, wait Lee.
I'm gonna die.
-OK we will take a
short pause here.
So we can do 300 push-ups!
-What?
-One-two.
One-two.
300.
This is bad.
There's going to be
a storm very soon.
-We'll be ready even if
a huge storm blows in.
With these logs we'll
form a protective barrier
around the shop.
-Thank you all.
You didn't have to.
-No, ma'am.
We owe you for your curry.
-Mhm!
-Oh my word.
Compared to you, my
Karashi is so idle.
-Hey, Tenten.
I'm worried about Karashi and
Ranmaru alone at the shop.
We're fine here.
Why don't you go back
and check on them.
-Karashi?
-Do you mean the boss
is really still alive?
-He is.
That Neji person didn't
seem to sense it back there.
But I could pick
up signs of life.
-Wow.
-Raiga.
Raiga, you meant
everything to me.
I was just waiting to
die, but you told me
we could survive together.
For me, Raiga, being
together with you
was the only time I lived.
Don't be gone.
No matter what, I can't
hold a funeral for you.
I won't let you
perish like this,
even if I have to
give you my life.
-Ranmaru!
Are you still with me, Ranmaru?
Come on.
Say something.
[groaning]
-Karashi?
[laughter]
[theme music]
NARUTO: What?
Tenten fell of a cliff?
Oh man.
We gotta go save her!
LEE: Please, Naruto.
Calm down.
NEJI: Tenten wouldn't
be that clumsy.
NARUTO: Huh?
But that's what Karashi
told us happened.
LEE: Unfortunately,
this whole thing
might be some kind of trap.
NARUTO: Wha?
A trap?
NEJI: Karashi.
NARUTO: Hold on a second.
I thought those guys
were annihilated!
Next time-- Raiga's
Counterattack!