[music playing]
[theme song]
NARUTO: Hey, where's
Sasuke's room?
NURSE: Sorry, no
visitors allowed.
NARUTO: What?
Are you kidding me?
NURSE: Those are the rules.
NARUTO: Ah, come on, lady!
-Naruto, this is a
hospital, keep it down.
NARUTO: Boy, am I
glad to see you.
I gotta ask you a favor.
-Stop right there.
I already know what
you're going to ask.
So I've been looking
for someone that
can oversee your training
for the final rounds.
-Hold on!
Why can't you train me, Sensei?
-I have other matters to handle.
I don't have time to
deal with you, Naruto.
[groans]
-Hey!
Aha!
You're going to train Sasuke
aren't you, Kakashi Sensei.
-Now, now, don't complain.
Listen, I found you an even
better teacher than me.
-Well, who is it?
-It is I.
-Uh?
You!
You closet pervert.
-Such insolence.
[music playing]
NARUTO: Ebisu Returns:
Naruto's Toughest Training Yet.
-No, no, no, not that guy.
-He's a what?
What did you call him?
-You're kidding me!
Of all the guys you
could've picked,
you pick this guy to train me?
What a joke!
He's weaker than I am.
-What makes you say that?
-I'm serious.
You should have seen him.
He saw my Harem jutsu once
and he fell to pieces.
Transform!
-Oh!
Master Ebisu.
Oh!
Master!
[screams]
-Oh no!
Not that again!
-Harem jutsu.
-Oh, it's nothing, just
a little joke we shared.
Haha.
(WHISPERS) Look,
I'll make you a deal.
Keep quiet about that
and I'll buy you anything
you want to eat.
Barbecue, ramen, you name it.
-Anything I want?
-Well, well, I had no idea
you two were acquainted.
[laughs]
-Yes, we go way back.
I will always be haunted
by that humiliation.
-I still don't get
why it has to be him?
I mean, anybody else.
-Look, you!
If it hadn't been for Kakashi,
who asked me this favor,
I would never
consider training you.
-Yeah, well then don't!
-Hey, hey, come on, you
two, let's calm down.
Listen, Naruto, you're
wrong about Ebisu Sensei.
He's a special jonin.
A private tutor, who
only trains the elite.
Frankly, he's a better
teacher than I am.
-Aww.
-Anyway, Naruto, I've got to
say that of the three genin
in Squad 7, you're the one
whose basic skills need the most
work.
That's what I want you to
focus on this time around.
-Wait!
Hold on a second!
Are you honestly
saying that I'm not
as good as Sasuke or Sakura?
[sighs]
-Naruto, no matter how
many skills you master,
the fundamentals are,
well, fundamental and yours
could be improved.
So if you really want to
become strong then just
be quiet and pay attention.
All right, Ebisu Sensei, I
leave him in your capable hands.
-I'll do what I can.
[groans]
KAKASHI: I know it seems
harsh but trust me.
It's for your own good.
Just do your best.
-Well, come on.
Let's get started.
-OK but I don't buy it.
-Huh?
-This whole thing
is totally nuts!
Even if I do need to work on
my fundamentals, how the heck
are they supposed
to get better when
I've got a teacher who's
weaker at this stuff than I am?
-I beg your pardon but who do
you think you're calling weak?
-You do you think?
Who else is standing here!
-If this is all because of that
ridiculous and inappropriate
jutsu of yours, it took me
by surprise, that's all.
I wouldn't be too hasty to
judge my abilities based
on one incident a long time ago.
-Just 'cause you ended up flat
on your back and out cold.
-All right, then, let's
put it to a test, shall we?
-Huh?
-Naruto, try and run away.
-I mean it.
I want you to try running
as fast as you can.
If you can get away from you,
I'll resign as your trainer.
-Is that a promise?
-Certainly, and
what's more, since I
know how much you
prefer Kakashi,
I think I can arrange to take
over enough of his other duties
so that he can be your trainer.
-Yeah?
Really?
-Of course.
An elite jonin never
goes back on his word.
But it's all contingent on
you being able to out run me.
-Man, this is the easiest
deal I've ever made.
So long, sucker!
[laughs]
-(LAUGHING) Piece of cake!
Eat my dust, you closet perv.
I'll send you a postcard.
Ha!
Lost him!
I guess now that
old sour puss will
have to admit he's dealing
with an exceptional ninja.
EBISU: Am I really?
Who?
If that's the best you can do,
we might as well stop right now
and save us both some time.
-Yeah?
Well, not so fast.
Just wait.
You haven't seen anything yet.
[pop]
I'm just getting started.
-Mm.
[panting]
-I gotta admit, he may
be a grumpy old stiff,
but he's better than I thought.
Keep moving.
[laughs]
[gasps]
EBISU (VOICEOVER):
Control yourself, Ebisu.
NARUTO: (LAUGHING)
There he goes again,
can't keep his
eyes off the girls.
-Just what do you think
you're doing, Naruto?
It was a good idea actually,
just not good enough.
-All right then,
give this a shot.
Shadow Clone jutsu.
Well, what are you waiting for?
Catch us if you can.
-Again, not bad.
However, you're not
the only one who
can perform the Shadow
Clone jutsu, my friend.
You can't get away.
-Not again!
That does it!
I've had enough of you!
[splat]
-All right, that's one down.
That's two down.
I've got you now!
[screams]
-Where do you
think you're going?
Ha!
Got you.
Hold it right there.
You don't.
I don't think so!
Take that!
And that!
[panting]
-Well, had enough?
[screams]
-Man!
You're a real pain,
you know that?
Why can't you just go
away and leave me alone!
-It wouldn't be much of
a chase if I did that.
I'm supposed to be trying
to catch you, remember?
-He's got a point.
-So Naruto, I hope
you have a better
opinion of my abilities now.
If you've had enough,
let's begin your training.
-Yeah, right.
Stick it in your ear.
I'm still going to get
rid of you somehow.
Kakashi is the only
one I'll let train me.
Either he trains
me or no one does!
-I see the river hasn't
cooled off your spirit.
Look at him.
He's turned the tables.
Instead of trying to escape,
he's coming right at me.
Well, Kakashi always said he was
an unpredictable knuckleheaded
ninja.
-Time I gave you some training!
Huh?
It was a clone?
-Sorry Naruto.
This game is over.
-Rats!
WAITRESS: One plain
ramen and one miso ramen
with barbecue pork.
MAN: There you go.
EBISU: Now, Naruto,
having had a chance
to observe your
technique firsthand
and going off what Kakashi
told me, it's clear to me
that one of your weakest
points is chakra control.
-Chakra control?
-Exactly.
When we compare your abilities
in this department with those
of your teammates,
Sakura and Sasuke,
your deficiency becomes obvious.
As you may know, in order to
successfully perform ninjutsu,
genjutsu, and the like, a ninja
must first build up his chakra.
-Yeah.
Like you said, I
already know that.
-I would hope so.
Well, then, let's compare
you to your teammates
in this department
and perhaps you'll
begin to see just how inferior
your abilities really are.
-You've got an annoying
way of putting things.
-As agreed, I'm buying you lunch
so just be quiet and listen.
First, let's examine how Sakura
prepares for a clone jutsu.
-Clone jutsu.
-She's perfect at building up
her chakra to its full extent
and because she's
so efficient, she
can make clones without
wasting any excess energy.
And for Sasuke, it must be said
he's not nearly as efficient
when it comes to building
up a full supply of chakra.
-Clone jutsu.
-But you see, his
control over the chakra
itself is so flawless that
he has no problem producing
five clones as
easily as Sakura can.
So the result is the
same, even if Sasuke
does waste more chakra
in getting there.
-What do you know and I
thought Sasuke was perfect
in everything.
-Wipe that smile off your face.
You are in no position to
make fun of anyone else.
-Why?
-You are no good at building up
your chakra or controlling it.
The result being you
require much more
chakra to produce to any clones.
NARUTO: What the?
EBISU: You have to
exert much more effort.
And even then, after all the
effort and wasting much more
chakra than either
Sakura or Sasuke.
-Clone jutsu.
-You can barely produce
two clones at best.
In fact, using the
same amount of chakra
you use, Sakura and Sasuke
could come up with 10 clones.
You see how the three of you
have very different levels
of ability just
on this one jutsu?
Oh well, I may have
been exaggerating
a bit in my comparison,
but the bottom line
is you waste too much of
your strength, Naruto,
and build up too much chakra.
You need to learn some
control, that's all.
-Yeah, well if
I'm such a lame-o,
how come there have
been times when
I've done better than they have?
-That's not the same thing.
That's only because you have
reserves of energy and stamina
that are hardly even human.
EBISU (VOICEOVER):
After all, how
can I expect him to have control
when he has the nine-tailed fox
spirits chakra
sealed within him.
The point is, we both know
you are strong, Naruto,
but you could be
so much stronger
if you'd let me show you how.
-Really?
You mean it?
-I not only mean
it, I guarantee it.
Now if you're
ready, let's begin.
MAN: Sir, your bill.
-Oh, I forgot.
[laughs]
EBISU: (SCREAMING) Naruto!
[cash register cha-ching]
WAITRESS: Thank you, come again.
-OK, you mind explaining
why you've dragged me
up here to these hot springs?
Is a bath part of my training?
Not that I'd mind soaking
my feet after that hike--
-Naruto!
Where do you think you're going?
That's the women's bath.
I will not allow any
disreputable behavior,
young man.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Disreputable behavior.
What's he talking about?
Like I was trying
to sneak a peek.
Huh.
From what I know about him, he's
the real pervert around here.
-What is it?
What's that look?
-Oh, nothing.
Nothing.
Anyway, what in the
world are we doing here?
Are you going to train me
how to wash behind my ears?
-Not quite, but you're right,
it is part of your training.
-Huh?
-Right here.
This is the place.
-A bath?
OK, what's going on?
-Don't take that tone with me.
Like I told you before, this
is all part of your training.
-OK, maybe you ought to
try taking it from the top.
What am I training for again?
[chortles]
-I'm going to teach you
how to walk on water.
-Huh?
-What is it now?
-Do you seriously expect me
to believe that you really
know how to walk on water?
-Of course I do!
According to what
Kakashi told me,
you've already
been trained in how
to climb a tree without
using your hands, right?
This is a variation of that.
-I don't know.
That was a long time ago.
I'm not so good at remembering
stuff that far back.
-Well, in tree
climbing, the key is
to build up chakra in
the points of contact
and then to maintain at a
steady rate of discharge.
Of course, trees are
stationary objects
so the discharge rate
remains constant.
All the same, it's
an excellent exercise
for developing basic
chakra control.
Now, to walk on water, you not
only have to build up chakra
at the points of contact, you
must also constantly adjust
the rate of discharge in
order to maintain your balance
on the water's shifting surface.
-Mmm hmm.
-This is obviously more
difficult than just maintaining
a fixed flow of chakra.
But that's what chakra
control is all about,
being able to discharge it at
a steady aura to varying rate.
You understand?
-I wish I did.
-Well, perhaps it would be
easier if I just showed you.
First, built up chakra in
the soles of your feet.
Then carefully
calibrating the amount
you discharge from each foot in
order to maintain your balance.
There, you see?
That's how it's done.
-Cool!
OK, let me give it a try now.
First, build up
chakra in your feet.
And then calibrating
a whatever it is.
Ah!
-Not quite.
[screams]
-Oh, by the way, don't
forget it's a hot spring.
You don't want to keep
falling in like that.
You'll be boiled like a lobster.
-Very funny.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
I can do this.
I got it now!
[splash]
Hot, hot, hot!
EBISU (VOICEOVER): Well, you
seem unusually diligent today,
Konahamaru.
Excellent.
It looks like my guidance
is finally paying off.
Isn't it about time you're
launching another surprise
attack against Lord Hokage?
-Naw, I don't do that
kind of thing anymore.
-That's astounding.
Well, I'm very glad to hear it.
So you understand that the
shortcut to becoming Hokage
is to do exactly as I say.
-Well, there aren't
any shortcuts here.
-Huh?
-Naruto told me that.
He said I had to learn that
if I ever wanted to be Hokage.
-Whoa.
I'm actually
starting to get this.
EBISU (VOICEOVER): Incredible.
He's right.
To think that he's already
started to master it.
I never imagined that he
would have come so far.
Indeed, there are no
shortcuts in anything.
Perhaps you were a better
teacher to Konahamaru
than I was.
It seems I was wrong
about you, Naruto.
There is more within
you than a demon spirit.
There is the heart of a splendid
Hidden Leaf Village ninja.
-Ahh!
[splash]
[laughter]
-Are you peeking in the
women's bath, old man?
I'm will not allow any
disreputable behavior.
-Oh please.
-Huh?
What on earth?
What are you doing?
-What's wrong with you?
Keep it down.
Do you want to get
us busted, you idiot?
-Huh?
Who is this guy?
He flattened my trainer.
And what's worse, he's an
even bigger perv than Ebisu.
[laughter]
[music playing]
NARUTO: I don't know
who he is, but no one
interrupts by training
and gets away with it.
Especially not some
perv in a fright wig,
riding a giant bull frog.
Guess I'll just have
to train on him.
Only thing is, I wish he
wasn't quite so fast or strong.
What is this guy, a super ninja?
Next time.
"Long Time No See,
Jiraiya Returns."
Oh, brother.
Again with the girls.
Can't anyone around here
keep his mind on the job?