[theme music]
[school bell]
STUDENT: Bye, sensei.
-Thanks, Iruka-sensei,
see you later.
-We'll see you tomorrow.
-OK.
Keep working on that jutsu.
Transformation takes
a lot of practice.
Oh, and be sure to
remind your parents
about the big inauguration.
We usher in the Fifth
Hokage tomorrow.
BOTH: OK, bye.
-Oh, Konohamaru.
-What is it, Iruka-sensei?
-Mm, oh, nothing.
I'll see you tomorrow.
-I'll catch you
later, Iruka-sensei.
IRUKA (VOICEOVER):
Looks like he's
made a bit of a break-through.
-Hey, Lee.
Coming back from rehabilitation?
-Yes, I am.
-I hope you're off
to a speedy recovery.
-Thank you, Iruka-sensei.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): To activate
all of his cells at once.
If it were just one by one,
it'd be a snap, but all of them
together, that'll be tough.
-Come on, Bushy Brow.
We need to hurry and
get a move on already.
The Hidden Leaf Village
is in a mess of trouble.
-Don't worry, Lee.
You'll get better in no time
with Lady Tsunade looking
after you.
-It's best if you give
up being a shinobi.
Find a different path.
LEE (VOICEOVER):
Sensei and Student.
The Bond of the Shinobi.
-Go, jutsu.
Transformation Jutsu.
GUY: Hey, kid.
The glory of youth is in
its unbridled passion.
You just keep chipping
away at it, son.
You'll make a splendid
shinobi some day.
LEE (VOICEOVER): Who is he?
He is so confident.
-Grab hold of life
by both horns.
That's what youth is for.
Good bye.
[laughing]
LEE (VOICEOVER): That was the
first time I met Guy-sensei.
And then--
GUY: As of today,
you are all Genin.
So now tell me why
have you done it?
What are your goals?
Hm?
-I'd rather not say.
-How about me, sensei?
I want to show I can
be a splendid ninja
as well, even if I do not
have ninjutsu or genjutsu.
I want to prove it
to the whole world.
GUY (VOICEOVER):
There's that look.
-Hmph.
-What?
What is so funny?
You think I am joking?
I mean it.
I will be a splendid
ninja just by using
taijutsu and nothing else.
-You nitwit.
Without ninjutsu
or genjutsu, you
can hardly call yourself
a ninja, can you?
Do you remember when they told
you you were the first person
to graduate who could
only use taijutsu?
They weren't saying that
because it was impressive.
They only meant
that it was unusual.
-Listen up.
If you've got the passion, that
isn't necessarily the case.
With the right amount of passion
and some healthy competition
to spur each other on,
you'll all be great ninja.
You'll still have to work
your butts off though.
LEE (VOICEOVER): Passion.
-Hahaha.
LEE (VOICEOVER): I-- I was
captivated by Guy-sensei,
by what he said and what he did.
-Late again by 17
minutes and 32 seconds.
-How about we skip this today?
-We've tied each
other at 48 wins.
Today's face-off will put
one of us in the lead.
-You're not going to take
no for an answer, are you?
All righty then, it's my turn
to name the challenge, right?
-Rah!
So what will it be?
A round of taijutsu?
A 100 meter dash?
Holding our breath?
Or an eating contest maybe?
-Oh boy.
-OK, I got one.
-Yeah!
Lay it on me.
-Rock paper scissors.
-Wha--?
-Are you nuts?
That's what you choose?
-You know, it's not
all about skill.
Sometimes you need
a little luck.
It'll be a good way to test
your powers of observation.
-I guess you're right.
-I don't know.
I think Kakashi's
just messing with him
so he doesn't have
to break a sweat.
-Yeah, looks like.
-All right, you're on.
And I aim to win.
If I lose, I'll take 500 laps
around the Leaf Village--
on my hands too.
-There you go again.
-That's a promise.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): Great.
Another one of his oddball
self-imposed rules.
-What on earth is he thinking?
He can't do that.
He acts like a seven-year-old.
-You are right.
That is impossible
even for Guy-sensei.
-Reckless is what I'd call it.
BOTH: Rock, paper--
-I thought I'd find you here.
-Guy-- Guy-sensei, how did
you know where to look for me?
-I know everything
about you, Lee.
I hear you've been skipping
out on your physical therapy.
You know better.
-Back when I first
made Genin, I swore
I would realize my every
dream, right here on the spot.
I swore.
And Neji laughed
at me back then.
But I meant every word of it.
I am going to be a splendid
ninja as well, even if I do not
have any ninjutsu or genjutsu.
I want to prove it
to the whole world.
I remember you told me that
with the right amount of passion
and some healthy competition,
we would all be great ninja.
And to make it happen, we
would have to work for it.
I knew I could do it.
STUDENTS: Transform!
LEE: Back in the
academy, there was not
a single person--
sensei or student--
who said that kind
of thing to me.
Your words were a relief.
Just as I was
starting to feel lost,
you lifted the fog from my eyes.
I knew all I had to
do was work harder.
And when I said
that hard work was
no match against
true genius, you
told me I was a
genius of hard work.
Thanks to you and
your encouragement,
I finally learned the importance
of believing in myself.
-The chances of surgery being
successful are 50-50 at best.
And if it fails, he'll die.
[crying]
-But-- but it's not
the same this time.
Even if I believe in myself
and try as hard as I can,
it will not make the
slightest difference.
Guy-sensei, please
tell me what to do.
Tell me, Guy-sensei.
Do you think maybe I can follow
in your footsteps some day?
How come I am the only one
being punished like this?
I have my own dreams to protect.
I do not care if it means dying.
I follow my nindo--
my ninja way.
Tell me, what should I do?
The Eight Inner Gates--
a forbidden jutsu one
can die using.
What do I do?
I am prepared for the worst.
Teach me the forbidden jutsu.
Whatever it takes for my dream.
That means everything to me.
GUY (VOICEOVER): You tried to
become a great ninja relying
only on taijutsu.
Until now, that's all you had.
It must be painful knowing
all your hopes and dreams
are about to be
ripped away from you.
-Is this one of
your students, Guy?
It's best if you give
up being a shinobi.
-Listen, Lee.
If you wish to be freed
of this suffering,
you need to make a decision.
-Do you mean that I
should be prepared
to give up on my dreams?
-If you lose your dreams,
you'll undergo pain
far worse than
what you feel now.
The two of us have a
lot in common, Lee.
Without our ninja
way to guide us,
you and I would never survive.
Get the operation, Lee.
[knock on door]
-Any progress with the
cell activation jutsu?
-At the end of the day,
this is all about chakra.
But with so many different
types of cells-- skin, internal,
muscular-- to activate
them all at once,
it's going to be
a bit difficult.
-Really?
Well that doesn't
sound too bad then.
-Are you trying to
test my patience?
-No.
I have the utmost faith in you.
-Hmph.
-You know, it is funny,
but I-- I remember
when you and Kakashi-sensei
decided to compete
against each other with a
game of Rock Paper Scissors.
He was saying that
skill was not enough,
that sometimes you need luck.
And this surgery is 50-50 too.
Live or die.
But this is not some kid's game.
-And what happened after that?
You do remember, don't you, Lee?
-Hm, 500, as promised.
[villagers laughing]
-Shoot.
Come o-- on.
If I lose, I'll take 500 laps
around the Leaf Village--
on my hands too.
That's a promise.
-What on earth is he thinking?
He can't do that.
He acts like a seven-year-old.
This is nothing.
Lee, what are you
doing out here so late?
-What about you?
It is not like Kakashi-sensei
is out here to see this,
and neither is anyone
else for that matter.
-When a man struts around like
a peacock acting like Mr. Big
Stuff, he should keep his
promises even if it kills him.
That's a promise.
What is it?
-Why do you do this?
Every time you're about
to start something,
you make up these crazy rules.
-Now that's an
excellent question, Lee.
I've got to hand it to you, son.
You always get
right to the point.
OK, I'll tell you.
But remember, this is
just between you and me.
-Why?
What is it?
-All right, that truth is a
ninja's self rule is the key--
the key to victory.
-Self-- self rule?
-Listen, Lee.
The point of all these
rules is to stack the deck
against yourself each
and every time you
set your sights on
a new objective.
It's about giving
yourself an obstacle.
Instead of seeing it as 500
laps of punishment for losing,
I see it as the path of
beating Kakashi the next time.
By leaping that hurdle,
it'll be that much easier
to achieve my next goal.
-Oh, I see.
-Take today.
By chaining myself
to those 500 laps,
I forced myself to take
something as trivial
as a game of Rock Paper
Scissors with an almost
deadly seriousness.
That's the first benefit.
-Mhm.
-And besides, even
if you lose, I still
have put in several hundred
laps around the village.
If you want to toughen up, it's
the ultimate two step program.
-That is brilliant.
-All right, I still
have a little more left.
Upsy-daisy.
-I am coming too.
I have my own rule to follow.
-Hey, be careful.
Don't push yourself, Lee.
-If I cannot keep up
with you, Guy-sensei,
that means I just have to
push myself even harder.
-Hm?
-I want to be like you, sensei.
And as long as I
keep at it, I am
sure to be a splendid
ninja someday.
That is a promise.
-Right.
Well in that case, I'm
adding a new rule--
if you aren't able to keep up
with me for the rest of my laps
around the village, I'll put
every last ounce of my being
into training you.
If I train you with
all my soul, there's
no question you'll
become a splendid ninja.
That's a promise.
-Of course.
How could I forget?
It was the day when
you first taught
me the principles behind
our self-imposed rules.
-You worked hard, Lee.
There's no doubt in my mind
the surgery will be a success.
You have the power to
shape your own destiny.
And on the 1 in 1,000-- no, 1
in 1,000,000 chance something
should happen to go wrong, I
will die right along with you.
Since the day I
met you, my nindo
has been to train you
to become the most
splendid ninja possible.
That's a promise.
You and I are too alike.
We cannot survive without
our ninja way to guide us.
-G-- Guy-sensei!
[crying]
[laughing]
GUY: All right, let's go, Lee.
LEE: Yes, sir.
-Lady Tsunade.
-From this day on, I shall
protect the Hidden Leaf Village
as the Fifth Hokage.
[crowd cheering]
[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Ugh,
his defense is flawless.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Losing
your cool won't help, Naruto.
Just wait for the next mission.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
That's right.
The next mission's
an overnighter.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Our best
shot will be at the inn.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Got it.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Once we get there,
we just wait 'til he
lets his guard down.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
And that's when--
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
BOTH: The mask comes off.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Next time-- Gotta See!
Gotta Know!
Kakashi-sensei's True Face!
Come on, what are you
hiding under there?