[theme song]
-Why are you here?
-Disappointed?
I expected a friendlier
reception after all this time.
-Don't tell me you've come here
to assassinate Lord Hokage.
-No, not yet.
I don't have quite enough
followers to attempt that.
But I've heard such good
things about this village,
I thought I might
want to make it mine.
[moaning]
Oh, it's the mark, isn't it?
I put that same curse
mark on a young man
just a little while ago.
Very promising prospect.
-You haven't changed, I see.
He'll die before he serves you.
OROCHIMARU: Very possibly.
I'd say the odds are
1 in 10 against him.
But the kid may
survive as you did.
-It sounds like you
want him badly, huh?
OROCHIMARU: Oh, jealous?
Is that it?
You can't forgive me can
you for using you and then
tossing you aside.
In some ways, the boy has even
more potential than you had.
You see, he's inherited
the sublime abilities
of the Uchiha clan.
And his physical
condition is excellent.
Yes, he might very well be
the heir I'm looking for.
At the very least, he
makes thing interesting.
Whatever happens, make sure
no one stops the exams early.
Three of my followers
are also candidates.
I look forward to
seeing how they fare.
Bear this in mind,
if anything happens
to deprive me of
my fun, it means
the end of the Leaf Village.
-All right, that's enough
resting up, I think.
The other teams will be
calling it a day soon.
And that means it's
time to strike.
You know the plan, we
split up and fan out.
Whatever happens, whether we
make contact with another team
or not, we meet up
back here in this spot.
Got it?
-No sweat.
-Roger.
-All right then, let's move.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Bushy Brow's Pledge:
Undying Love and Protection.
-[sigh].
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): No,
I can't fall asleep.
I have to protect these two.
-Oh, wow.
I slept really great.
-Naruto.
Sasuke.
-Did you take care of
us this whole time?
-Thanks, Sakura.
We're all better because of you.
-I'm glad you're OK.
[rustling]
-Now you'll see what
it's like to be prey,
panicking and frantically
running away from a predator.
And that predator is me!
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
My voice is gone.
All our voices are gone.
It was just a dream.
Oh, I can't believe
it's daytime already.
[rustling]
Oh, no.
A squirrel?
Oh man, don't surprise
me like that, little guy.
That was too close.
-I thought for sure
that would work.
Do you think she saw the paper
bomb we put on the squirrel?
-No, that wasn't it.
-Hm.
Then what was it?
What are you thinking?
-I'm thinking we need to
go closer and find out.
So let's get going.
-Hm.
OK, if I can catch
all 20 of those leaves
before they hit the
ground, then Sakura
will fall in love with me.
But if I cannot, then she
will never return my feelings.
That is the challenge I
am going to give myself.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Those
eyebrows are so bushy.
You're such a weirdo.
LEE (VOICEOVER): I cannot
believe she said that.
I will show her I am worthy.
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight.
Yes, I am going to get them all.
Ooh.
19.
One left.
Hm, what is that?
Phew, that was close.
This paper bomb explodes after
a certain amount of time.
Who would do such
an awful thing?
-All right, stop
hiding and come out.
-Shoot.
How could he have seen us?
We hid so fast.
-What a drag.
Now that he's found us out,
this is going to be such a pain.
-It's no big deal.
Our hide and hangout
strategy didn't work,
so we'll just use
strategy number two.
-What!
Are you serious, Ino?
-You got a problem with that?
-Trust me, this plan can't fail.
-Well, what do we got to lose?
-Ha-ha.
Wow, imagine running into
last year's number one
rookie, Neji Hyuga, out here.
-Can I have your autograph?
-Oh, it's you guys.
-Yeah.
Strategy two, where you
fall head-over-heels in
love with my beauty.
Hi, there.
I've been wanting to meet you
for a really long time, Neji.
So, hi.
-Get lost.
INO (VOICEOVER): What!
He should have been
bowled over by my beauty.
Why didn't that work?
Ugh, it makes me so angry
I could just hit something.
-Did you just raise
your fist to me?
Does that mean
you want to fight?
-No.
No way.
Of course not.
-Go away.
Even if I were to steal a
scroll from you cowardly wimps,
everybody would just
laugh at me for it.
-Sounds good to me.
-Ha, they scurry off
like cockroaches.
[breathing heavily]
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
Just as I thought,
someone like him wouldn't take
a scroll from people like us,
unless we turned on
him and attacked.
-All right.
Let's see if we can
find some weaklings.
-Yeah, well, I doubt we'll
find anyone weaker than us.
DOSU: Some lookout.
You're half asleep.
At least you don't have
to keep watch anymore.
What's the point after
we've already found you?
Now, wake Sasuke up.
We want to fight him.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): You'll
never get him, you jerks.
What do you want here?
I mean, what do you really want?
I know Orochimaru was calling
the shots from the shadows.
What's that strange bruise
on the back of Sasuke's neck?
You're behind this,
too, aren't you?
And now you want to fight him
when he can't defend himself?
-What in the world
could he be thinking?
-I can't stay
quiet after hearing
you talk to us like that.
First, I'm going
to kill this girl,
and then I'm going
to kill Sasuke.
-Wait, Zaku.
-What?
Why?
-It's so obvious.
This is the color of dirt
that's recently been dug up.
And this kind of grass doesn't
grow in a place like this.
You know, if you're
going to lay a trap,
there's no point unless you
make sure it's actually hidden.
-Ha, you're just a joke.
You threw your kunai knife,
so that squirrel wouldn't
spring the trap you set, huh?
-Now we kill her.
-Hm.
-A log.
-She also laid a trap above?
Watch out!
Nice try, little girl.
Clearly, you have no
talent as a ninja.
Someone like you needs to make
a little more of an effort,
don't you think?
LEE: Leaf hurricane.
What?
What's he doing?
-Looks like you also need
to make more of an effort.
-Who are you?
-I am the handsome devil
of the Leaf Village,
and my name is Rock Lee.
-Wha-- what are you
doing here, Lee?
-I will always appear,
anytime and anywhere
that you are in trouble, Sakura.
This was really all
thanks to you, little one.
But now it is time
for you to run along.
-But right now on this
test, I'm your enemy.
-Sakura, I already told you.
-Huh?
-I will protect you until I die.
Please be my girlfriend.
I vow to protect
you with my life.
-Yes.
Thank you, Rock Lee.
LEE (VOICEOVER): Yes.
She said yes!
Guy sensei, she said yes!
DOSU: It looks like
I have no choice.
Zaku, I'll let you have Sasuke.
I'll take care of these two.
LEE (VOICEOVER):
It does not look
like Sakura is in any
condition to fight.
-That guy with
the bushy eyebrows
is pretty good at taijutsu.
It looks like I get
to have some fun.
LEE (VOICEOVER): I am
positive that there
is some kind of
trick to your attack.
Therefore, I will not waste
my time trying to dodge it.
-Huh?
-After all, I have
seen your jutsu before.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Wow, he's tough.
LEE (VOICEOVER): Of
course, having said that,
my odds still are not good
since it is three against one.
I have to take a chance.
One at a time.
I will attack each of
them with all my might.
-Oh, man.
There doesn't seem to be anyone
around who's weaker than us.
-Not so fast.
I still think that Naruto's
team might actually
be weaker than we are.
-Take that back
right now, you jerk.
-What do you mean?
-There's no doubt Naruto
and Sakura are lame,
but I won't have you
bad mouthing Sasuke.
He's awesome.
-Yeah, whatever.
Maybe your precious
Sasuke is better in theory
than in practice.
-[grunting].
-All right, all right, I
apologize if I upset you.
What a drag.
I say one little negative
thing about Sasuke
and I get the evil eye from
his number one fan here.
-There is no way Sasuke
could lose a battle.
Ha.
But Sakura is a
different matter.
-Hm?
Hey, Sasuke has collapsed.
-Huh?
CHOJI: And Sakura's fighting.
INO: What did you say?
Hm.
Ah.
Oh, he's late.
And he's never late.
Lee is-- well, fanatical
about being on time.
Maybe he ran into the enemy.
You think--
-No, I'm sure he's all right.
But still, we'd
better go find him.
-Right.
-Yes, I did it.
I finally mastered the jutsu.
-Enough resting.
You're wasting your
precious, gifted youth.
GUY (VOICEOVER): This
jutsu, in the end
only Lee could make it his own.
-I did it.
-Lee.
-I actually did it.
-After all that practice,
I pulled it off.
-Lee.
-I guess if I just
try hard enough--
-Lee!
-I can do anything.
Wow, I really did it.
-Quiet.
Now, listen to your
sensei's awesome message.
-Yes.
I am ready to hear your
amazing wisdom, sir.
-This new jutsu, the lotus
technique is now forbidden.
-Huh?
-What do you mean?
Why?
-This jutsu, it puts a huge
strain on your body's muscles.
It's a self-sacrificing
technique.
-Huh?
-Normally, humans
only use at most 20%
of their muscles strength.
Do you understand
only about 20%?
If all of the power
were to be used,
the muscles would
disintegrate, so the brain
regulates the amount of
power the muscles can exert.
But this jutsu is different.
It uses chakra, which forces
the brain to go past its limits,
allowing for continuous
high-speed taijutsu.
In other words, this jutsu
relies on a secret technique
that brings forth power
almost to the limits
of the human body.
So you see, it's very dangerous.
There's one time
this jutsu should
be used, when a particular
condition is met.
-Yes, I see.
So what is the condition, sir?
-Are you ready?
You all need to
take this to heart.
The condition is--
the condition is--
LEE (VOICEOVER): Guy sensei,
I have to use the lotus now.
The condition has been met.
I must use the jutsu.
To protect the life
of someone precious.
-Did he disappear?
Ugh.
-Not yet.
-Oh no, Dosu.
There's no way he
can break his fall.
-Take this, [inaudible] lotus.
What is this feeling?
-Ha, got you just in time.
That impact could have
been much worse for you.
-What?
This cannot be.
-That is a frightening jutsu.
It nearly took me
out even though I
landed on this soft dirt.
Now, it's my turn.
LEE (VOICEOVER): Oh, no.
My body still has not
recovered from that jutsu.
Ah!
-Lee, no.
-Your jutsu is indeed fast,
but ours is even faster
because it travels at
the speed of sound.
Effort by itself does nothing.
Now watch, we're going to show
you something called the wall.
[theme song]
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
I'm so sick of this.
It's like I'm always
a step or two behind.
And I always need
to be protected.
I want to be more like
Sasuke, Naruto, and Lee.
Wait, did I just say I
want to be like Naruto?
Well, at least he doesn't
hesitate to jump into action.
So yeah, I want
to be like Naruto.
Next time, Sakura blossoms.
In this battle, things are going
to get real serious real fast.