[theme music]
-We're getting close.
NEJI: That's strange.
It's been quite a long
time, and we still
haven't encountered
a single trap.
Well, Shikamaru.
What's your assessment?
-It looks to me like
we've been underestimated.
They're cocky.
They think we're all dead now,
and their big guys the only one
following them.
They don't need to set a trap
for their own man, do they?
-Those idiots.
They think we're so weak.
-It seems you're right
about our enemy, Shikamaru,
and it's insulting to be
underestimated like this.
But still.
This could be our chance.
-I hear you.
Now we can take
them by surprise.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
You opponent is me!
-Jirobo's pretty late, isn't he?
-He was, but he just arrived.
-Well, it's about time.
You were gone a while.
What took so long?
-Sorry.
It took longer than I thought
to eat all that loser's chakra.
-Listen, fatso.
Don't slow us down
so you can eat more.
You see that coffin?
You're the one who's
supposed to be carrying it.
So do your job, you slob!
OK.
-Well, well, Jirobo.
Aren't you awfully
easygoing today?
-Yeah, so what?
-Well, it's just
that I'm not going
to be handing over this coffin
to you, because you're not
the real Jirobo!
[laughter] Let me take
down this one, fellas.
Sakon, Tayuya, go on.
I'll catch up.
The real Chirobo
is always scolding
Tayuya about her
rather coarse language.
-You got me.
-Ninja Art!
Spider Web Net!
Huh?
-Surprised to see me?
-Ninja Art.
Spiral Spiderweb!
-Naruto!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Kiba, Akamaru.
Now's your chance.
When he's in midair
like that, there's
no way he can fight back!
KIBA: Fang Over Fang!
I won't let you get away!
-You stole my line, punk.
You should look
down at your feet.
-You coward!
Do you really think you
can't stop us that easily?
-Why don't you shut up?
-Where is he?
-What could that fatso be doing?
This stinks!
-We did leave the
weakest one behind
to take care of those brats.
Perhaps that was a mistake.
NEJI (VOICEOVER): My turn.
-Neji!
No!
-He'a stuck!
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): Darn it.
He got me, Naruto,
Kiba, and Neji.
We followed the plan,
but it's not working.
-How'd you like to see the
inside of an air tight cocoon?
-No!
Come on.
Come on!
What the heck's this
thread made out of?
I can't cut it!
-It's useless.
My spider silk is so powerful,
nothing can break it.
Two elephants couldn't
pull it apart.
That one's able to
use shadow clone.
NEJI (VOICEOVER):
No matter what I
do, this thread
keeps sticking to me.
This stickiness must come
from combining his chakra
with some sort of fluid.
And the strength is unreal.
Even after he
releases the thread,
his chakra is still flowing
through it, giving it power.
Impossible.
The level of this jutsu
is out of this world.
It's unstoppable.
No, wait.
I've got to calm down.
Focus my chakra.
-Ninja Art.
Sticky Spider Thread.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): That's a
different color from the thread
he used before.
What's he gonna do?
I see.
It's solidifying.
-Since you'll be
my first victim,
let's make this entertaining.
I'm going to play a little game
to find out which one of you
is the real one.
-What did you just say?
-Contestant one, let's
try you at the end.
-No, Naruto!
-Oh well, looks
like he was a clone.
No problem.
Let's try another!
Whichever you are,
you're pretty lucky.
Next, let's try two at a time.
The odds will be
doubled in my favor!
You are a very lucky
guy, you know that?
But this time, I got 50-50 shot.
Here it comes!
Well, somehow he made it all
the way to the bitter end.
Well, weakling, it was
fun playing with you,
but unfortunately, the
game's over for you now.
Now die!
One down, and three to go.
Wait, where did he--
[shout]
-Of course.
He let his shadow
clones get caught,
while the real one hid
and waited for a chance
to catch me off guard.
For a wimp like
that to to come up
with such a deception
in the heat of battle--
He's not so dumb after all.
However-- It looks like you're
at the end of your rope.
How did he--
-Naruto!
Thanks for stalling him for me.
-Neji!
-I trapped you.
How did you get free?
-Arf!
-Your spiderweb
had a chakra base.
And chakra built
substances don't
stand a chance against
my Gentle Fist attack.
This guy's jutsu-- I think I'm
the only one who can handle it.
Go on, you guys.
I'll take care of him.
[whimpering]
-What's wrong, buddy?
Hey, wait, Akamaru.
Well, looks like this guy's
stronger than that big guy
we fought before.
Much stronger.
-We're going to have
to go one on one
to have any chance for success.
Isn't that what you said?
-Yeah.
That's what we agreed.
-And besides, if
we all stay here,
we won't be able to
catch up with Sasuke.
-But what about Choji?
He hasn't come back.
-Arf!
-We all embarked on this mission
to find Sasuke and bring him
back home to the village.
But that's not the only
reason that we've come.
We are on this mission to
protect a fellow shinobi,
to defend the bond of
the Hidden Leaf Village.
At the Third Hokage's
funeral, when Ikruka spoke,
do you remember his words?
-Iruka-sensei,
why do they do it?
Why do people risk their
lives for other people?
-Well, when someone
passes away, it's the end.
His past and future, all
the dreams he once had,
they disappear along with him.
This is true, even if he
dies honorably in battle,
as so many have.
As Hayate did.
All of the ties that bind him
to the living are severed.
All but one, the most
important of all-- people.
Parents, siblings,
friends, lovers.
The people who were
important to him.
And these people,
the ones left behind,
are joined together
in a great circle
by their shared memories of him.
A circle of friendship,
trust, and sacrifice
that grows larger and
stronger as time passes.
It's hard to explain it.
We remain in the
circle together.
We have no choice.
It's important to us.
-Listen.
Sasuke's out there right now,
heading toward Orochimaru.
We can't allow such evil to
take someone from our village.
That is not our way.
What's more-- Naruto.
Sometimes your eyes are
even better than mind.
Wherever he is, Sasuke
in the darkness.
Now, get going.
I'll be right behind you.
-Well, all right.
Let's do this thing.
-When you catch up with us,
make sure you bring Choji, too.
-Of course I will.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Neji--
I'd better see you again.
-Oh, no you don't!
-Byakugan!
-Incoming!
-He's pretty good.
This is gonna be fun.
-Thanks, Neji.
-Yep.
That's him, all right.
-Not so fast.
I won't let you
escape that easily.
-If you want them, you'll
have to go through me.
Not good enough.
-Well, that's just fine by me.
Besides, you're by far the
strongest one of the lot.
Aw, man.
I'm really itching
to play with you.
And we should play slowly, or
else the game's not as fun.
[laughter]
OK, the game is I'll kill you
in three minutes or less.
Ha.
You're not going anywhere.
For a wimp, you're pretty good
at handling chakra, aren't ya?
And those eyes of
yours are pretty sharp.
You fire off chakra from the
chakra points in your hands
like a sharp needle.
Then you target the thin
part of my thread with chakra
running through it,
and strike there.
Yes, I heard this
from Lord Orochimaru.
It's the technique
you call Gentle Fist.
Right?
But if you can't use those
annoying hands of yours,
then you won't be able
to cut through my silk!
That was way too easy.
Once you figure out your
opponent's rules of engagement,
games like this one
are no longer amusing.
It's only been in
a minute or so,
and I'm already tired
of playing with you.
[sigh]
-Die.
Sticky Spider Thread!
Huh?
How did he--
-I suppose you want me to
explain how I broke free.
You see, it's not just my hands.
There are chakra
points all over me.
I can emit chakra from any one.
And now, as you
would say, game over!
Gentle Fist Art, Eight
Trigrams, 64 Palms!
[theme music]
NEJI: The attack on his
chakra points was ineffective.
On top of that, he fell back
to a long distance attack
to avoid my Gentle Fist.
This guy blocks my every
move, and he reads my hands
instantly.
This could be bad.
The longer this fight drags on,
the less likely I am to win it.
And if he notices
my weakness, then--
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next
time, 360 Degrees of Vision.
The Byakugan's Blind Spot!
[theme music]