[theme music]
-[yawning]
Ugh.
Huh?
[chuckles]
Today's the day,
so let's chow down.
[slurping]
Mmm.
NARUTO: "Sasuke and
Sakura: Friends or Foes?"
-Uh?
[chuckles]
-You're mine, Naruto!
Woah, agh!
-Uh, what do you think
you're doing Konohamaru?
-That was a slick move.
That's why I respect
you as a rival.
-But I didn't do anything.
-All right.
Now fight me fair and square.
-Sorry, I've got an orientation.
-Orientation?
-That's right.
As of today, I'm a ninja.
Believe it.
-Ah.
-[chuckles]
-[humming]
[chuckles]
SAKURA'S MOM: Sakura, isn't
it time for you to get going?
-I know.
I'm on my way out now.
Chaw, how long are you
going to treat me like a kid?
I'm a ninja now.
So I'm not a little
academy student anymore.
I'm Sakura Haruno,
kunoichi in training.
INO: See you later!
Good morning, Sakura.
-Good morning, Ino.
-So they actually
let you graduate?
What a surprise.
-Those classes are
ancient history.
We're both ninja now,
and we're both equal.
I won't lose to you anymore.
-[chuckling]
-Huh?
What are you doing here, Naruto?
This isn't for dropouts.
You can't be here
unless you graduate.
-Oh yeah, do you see this?
Do you see this?
Open your eyes, Shikamaru.
It's a regulation headband.
We're going to be
training together.
How do you like that?
-Hm.
-Let me put it to you this way.
I look great in this headgear,
like it was made for me.
Believe it. [chuckles]
-(VOICEOVER) Naruto,
you graduated after all.
I'm glad.
BOTH: I'm first!
-I won again, Sakura.
-Give it up.
I had to look back to see you.
My toe was at least a
tenth of an inch ahead.
-Have you always
been this delusional?
-(VOICEOVER) Sakura.
She's smiling at me.
I think she likes
me in this headband.
-[chuckles]
-Hey, woah.
Where are you going?
-Hi, Sakura.
What's up?
-Move it!
-Good morning, Sasuke.
Mind if I sit next to you?
-Back off, Forehead.
I'm sitting next to Sasuke.
-I was here first.
-I walked into the
classroom before you did.
Everybody saw it.
-Dream on.
-Actually, I got here
before either of you.
-So did I. I'm sitting
next to Sasuke.
GIRL: No, I am.
-(VOICEOVER) Clueless.
MAN: Most promising new
student Sasuke Uchiha.
Is that him?
-Yes, he's the one.
-He's the only survivor
left from the Uchiha Clan.
-That's right.
-Hm.
Naruto Uzumaki, hm?
-Ugh.
[clunk]
-Hm?
-[grunts]
-Naruto!
Hey, stop glaring at Sasuke!
-(VOICEOVER) Sakura?
Why are they so obsessed
with him? "Sasuke, Sasuke."
What's the big
deal with this guy?
[arguing]
-Whoa.
Heh, this is great!
Sorry, did I bump you?
-What the--
-I, uh--
-[screaming]
-So, this is outrageous.
I was supposed to be
Sasuke's first kiss.
Naruto will pay for
this. Chaw!
-Ahhh.
-I will get you, Naruto.
-Huh, they are vicious.
-Ah-- hm, danger.
Huh?
-Naruto, you are so dead.
-Hey, whoa.
It was an accident.
-You're finished!
-Hold on.
-As usual, Naruto is
right in the middle
of some kind of trouble.
-As of today, you
are all ninjas.
To get here, you faced
difficult trials and hardships.
But that's nothing.
What comes next will
be far more difficult.
Now you're only genin--
first level ninjas.
All the genin will be grouped
into three-man squads.
Each squad will be led by
a jounin-- an elite ninja.
-Huh?
-Oh?
BOTH: (VOICEOVER)
A three-man squad?
-Well, someone's got to
be in Sasuke's group.
I wonder who.
-I don't know.
Chaw!  I'm going
to be with Sasuke.
So stay away from him, you hag.
-Ah, groups of three.
That'll only slow me down.
-I Want to be with
Sakura and-- well,
I don't care, as long
as it's not Sasuke.
-We want each squad to
have a balance of strengths
and abilities, so that's
how we set them up.
I will now announce the squads.
Squad seven: Naruto Uzumaki--
-Uh.
- --Sakura Haruno--
-Yeah!
-I'm doomed.
- --and Sasuke Uchiha.
-Ah!
-I'm doomed.
-I won't be with Naruto, then.
TEACHER: Next, squad
eight: Hinata Hyuga--
-Yes, sir.
TEACHER: --Kiba Inuzuka--
- Heh heh heh.
TEACHER: --Shino Aburame.
-Heh heh.
-Agh, how did you
get in his group?
-Ka-ching!
True love conquers all.
-Ugh!
-I don't get it.
What do you see in
a guy like that?
He's not so special.
-You are so beyond
clueless, Shikamaru.
Don't you get it?
-No, I don't get it,
because I'm not a girl.
-Ugh, you're so
full of yourself.
Jealousy's a terrible thing.
I'd hate to be on your squad.
-Now, squad ten: Ino
Yamanaka, Shikamaru Nara--
-Uh!
-Heh, did you say something
about hating to be on my squad?
-Ugh.
- --and Choji Akimichi.
-[crunching]
-(VOICEOVER) Ah!
Not food boy, too!
-[crunching]
-Those are all the squads.
-Iruka Sensei.
Why does a great ninja like me
have to be in the same group
with a slug like Sasuke?
-Hm.
Sasuke had the best scores of
all the graduating students.
Naruto, you had
the worst scores.
To create a balanced group,
we put the best student
with the worst student.
NARUTO: Ugh.
-Just make sure you don't
get in my way, loser.
-Ugh.
Hey, what did you say?
SASUKE: Hard of hearing?
SAKURA: Knock it off, Naruto.
Sit down.
TEACHER: Ahem.
After lunch, you'll meet
your new jounin teachers.
Until then, class dismissed.
-Sasuke, where are you?
Why did he go
running off so fast?
Since we're in the
same group and all,
I thought we could have
lunch together and get
to know each other.
-Hey, Sakura.
Since we're in the
same group, I was
thinking we could have
lunch together and get
to know each other.
-Why would I eat lunch with you?
How could that thought
even cross your mind?
-But we're in the same group.
So, you know, I just thought--
-Naruto, you're annoying.
-Sasuke, where are you.
-But, uh-- uh.
-Ugh, what a pain.
I get into the same
group as Sakura,
and he's got to be in it too.
There's got to be a
way to deal with this.
Huh?
Got it.
-All right.
If we're in the
same group, you're
going to have to follow my lead.
That's the only way it'll work.
-Yeah, yeah.
(VOICEOVER) That's
the only it'll
work because she throws a fit
if she doesn't get her way.
-Why don't you lead us
to some barbecue, Ino?
-Hopeless!
-Huh?
Naruto.
Uh!
SASUKE: Naruto!
NARUTO: Pipe down.
-Naruto!
If you so much as scratch
him, you're on my enemy list
forever.
[fighting]
-Hm, wha-- what happened?
-Heh, nice try.
Heh.
-He beat Naruto without
even breaking a sweat.
-What'd you expect?
Naruto against my boy Sasuke?
No contest.
-(VOICEOVER) Well, it's not like
there's a big rush or anything.
I'll be in the same group
as Sasuke for a long time.
But still.
How could I even
think he'd like me?
Let's face it, I'm scrawny and
small-- except for my forehead.
Why was I born with such
a big, wide forehead?
Oh?
Oh, Sasuke.
He's looking right at me.
That look in his eyes.
-Sakura, your forehead
is so wide and charming.
It makes me feel
like kissing it.
-Well, there's lots
of room up there.
[sighs] (VOICEOVER)
Grow up, Sakura.
That's just a fairy tale.
And fairy tales don't come true.
SASUKE: Sakura, your forehead
is so wide and charming.
-Huh?
-It makes me feel
like kissing it.
-Ka-ching, she scores!
This fairy tale is for real.
-Just kidding.
That's the kind of dumb
thing that Naruto would say.
-Oh.
-I want to ask you something.
-Huh?
-Naruto, what do
you think of him?
-He knows about my
feelings, and he purposely
tries to get in the way.
He enjoys interfering
and making me feel bad.
Naruto, he doesn't understand
one single thing about me.
He's just annoying.
All I really want is for
you to accept me, Sasuke.
That's all.
-You just want me to accept you?
-Yes, that's how I feel.
I'd do anything for that.
[heartbeat]
-I let my guard down.
-I got you.
Ah!
-Uh.
In class, he couldn't even
do a simple replication.
How could he combine
a replacement
jutsu with a full
shadow clone jutsu?
[heartbeat]
-It's true.
I'm desparate.
-(VOICEOVER) finally know why--
why I like Sakura so much.
I finally understand.
[passes gas]
Uhhh.
My stomach!
What timing!
Gah!
-Hey, what's the matter?
-I'll be right back.
-I didn't know that
Sasuke was so shy.
Maybe he needs a little
time to get ready.
-Ah!
Uh.
Close, really close.
My stomach was so
upset, I almost
lost control of the jutsu.
Why did it have to
happen right then,
just when she was
about to-- huh?
(VOICEOVER) She thinks
that I'm annoying?
She said that three times.
I transform into Sasuke,
get close to Sakura,
and she has to say that?
Hey, I know what I should do.
I'll make Sasuke act
totally obnoxious.
Believe it.
Then she'll hate him
even more than me.
-Ah!
Oh, Sasuke, you're back.
Don't be so shy, you bad boy.
Are you ready now?
You know, mentally prepared?
Because I am.
I mean, I'm raring to go!
Uh, hey, wait a minute!
-Where's Naruto?
-Oh, see.
There you go changing
the subject again.
Anyway, Naruto just
picks fights with you.
You know why he's so annoying?
Because he wasn't raised right.
He doesn't have a
mother or a father,
no one to teach him
right from wrong.
Think about it.
He just does whatever
comes into his head.
If I did things like
Naruto, forget it.
I mean, my parents would get
mad and I'd get in trouble.
So of course I don't do it.
But if you don't have parents
to tell you, how would you know?
He's selfish and bratty.
He's all alone.
-Alone.
Isolated.
-Huh?
-It's not about your
parents scolding you.
You have no idea what
it means to be alone.
-Wh-- why are you saying that?
-Because you're annoying.
-[gasps]
-Oh man.
I thought I was OK,
and then it came back.
I've got to hurry.
I hope Sakura's
still waiting for me.
Ah!
Sasuke, what are you doing here?
How did you get loose?
-I used the escape jutsu.
No sweat, it's a
very basic technique.
-Uh--
-Why'd you do that,
transform into me?
-I thought it'd be fun to try
out my moves on you, so I did.
-Ah, the same technique again?
-This time, you'll see
what I can really do.
You're going down for the count.
Then you'll have to
admit that I'm the best.
Get ready, Sasuke.
[passes gas]
[chattering]
[arguing]
-What a loser.
-(VOICEOVER) I'm annoying?
That's what he said.
Now I get it.
This is how Naruto must feel.
I shouldn't treat him like that.
Next time I see him,
I'm going to be nice.
NARUTO: Ugh.
-Huh?
-Maybe I ate something bad.
-(VOICEOVER) Oh, Naruto.
Smile, smile.
-Hey, Naruto!
Let's walk back
to class together.
-Did she really say that?
-[nervous laughter]
-(VOICEOVER) She'd never
smile at me like that.
Sasuke must've transformed
into Sakura to get back at me.
Trying to trick
me, eh, wise guy?
Well, forget it.
Ugh-- [passes gas]
Ugh, why is this
happening again?
Ah!
-Uh-- agh.
Dumb Naruto!
-So this is where Naruto lives.
-Yes, he'll be on your team,
along with Sakura and Sasuke
from the Uchiha Clan.
Good luck, you'll need it.
-This milk is way past
its expiration date.
One sip of this
and he'd be running
to the bathroom all day.
Seems like this kid's
just one big problem.
Hm.
-[groaning]
-Am I going to spend my
whole life on the pot?
[theme music]
NARUTO: This isn't the Kakashi
Sensei we met yesterday.
It couldn't be the same teacher
who I tricked so easily,
the one who came late to class.
Hah, no way.
I'm not giving up, no
matter what he throws at me.
A super tough test where we have
to defeat the sensei to pass?
I'll do it.
Nothing can make me go back now.
Believe it!
Next time, "Pass or
Fail: Survival Test."
Don't miss my big victory.