[theme song]
KIBA (VOICEOVER): His scent.
He's moving away.
-That was close.
-What was?
-Please wait.
From now on, we play for keeps.
ROCK (VOICEOVER): My
role now is to stall
this person as long as possible.
I would rather not resort
to more powerful attacks.
It will only leave me
vulnerable to defeat.
But my enemy is
a formidable one.
I will have to reveal my
secret technique to best him.
-Here I come.
ROCK (VOICEOVER): I just had
surgery, so I'm not at my best.
But if I only open the first
gate-- the gate of opening--
I should be all right.
-The first gate,
Gate of Opening!
Open!
Primary lotus!
ROCK (VOICEOVER): The bone
absorbed the impact of my kick.
-Your speed is impressive.
But this is over now.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): Come on.
I'm wracking my brain, here.
Why can't I come
up with anything?
I'm at the end of my rope.
I can't hold on any longer.
-You're staring
death in the face.
Shouldn't you be screaming
for mercy or something?
Huh?
-Now die!
-You're mine!
-You're gonna die, kid.
Wipe that grin off your face!
-What the hell?
-Who are you?
-What do you know?
Looks like we're
allies this time.
-Who are you?
-Allies of the Leaf Village.
-We're shinobi--
-Of the sand.
NARUTO: The sand shinobi,
allies of the leaf!
ROCK (VOICEOVER): Sand ninja?
Am I still drunk, or something?
-He is Gaara, of the sand.
-Gaara.
Is that what they call you?
Digital shrapnel!
ROCK (VOICEOVER): He fired
the bones from his fingertips?
-Impulsive, aren't you?
You're different.
When you fought against me
you had much more agility
and sharpness.
-I figured you would say that.
I am not the kind of
person who holds a grudge.
Even so-- because of you I've
had a fairly tough time of it.
-Really?
-Anyway, why have you come here?
-I owe the leaf.
I owe the leaf a great debt.
-Sasuke!
-I had heard something about
how our village had finally
made up with you traitors.
But I didn't expect you to
change sides so quickly.
-It's not like we just attacked
the Leaf Village for kicks,
you know.
We were following orders.
That's all.
Just like we're doing
on this mission.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): I get it.
The Fifth Hokage sent them.
She saved our butts.
-By the way, you
seem a lot dumber
than the last time
our paths crossed.
-Huh?
-So, are you gonna give
up again this time?
Go ahead.
I'll take care of this for you.
-Well, I'm sorry
to disappoint you,
but I'm not about to give up.
And besides, a real
man doesn't let
a woman do his fighting for him.
-Ha.
Still being all macho with
the man and woman stuff?
You talk tough, but I
know it's just an act.
Idiot.
-So this time you're on
the leaf's side, huh?
You guys are all over
the place, aren't you?
-The sound of the flute
summons her genjutus.
-I got it.
Cyclone scythe jutsu!
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
She's deflecting
the sound of the flute
and nailing our opponent
with a physical attack.
She can attack and
defend at the same time.
That's a pretty
handy jutsu to have.
TAYUYA (VOICEOVER): It's like
that girl was born to fight me.
-Well, I don't see him.
I guess Ukon must have
taken him out already.
-So, you fight with puppets?
-Hey, wait a second.
When you showed up here, weren't
you in a group of three people?
-The other two went on
ahead, because you guys
couldn't hack it.
-Listen, moron.
These enemies aren't
exactly lightweights.
Behind you!
It's no use.
I can't move.
-What is this guy?
-He's all yours, Sakon.
Finish him!
KIBA (VOICEOVER):
Where'd other one go?
-Boo.
Looking for someone, kid?
KIBA (VOICEOVER):
That body position.
I've seen it.
-Be careful.
He's about to try and enter
your body and combine with it!
-It's too late.
I can't believe it!
-What's the matter, Sakon?
-I guess that jutsu of yours
doesn't really work on puppets,
dos it?
SAKON (VOICEOVER): This
one's a puppet, too?
-Fair warning.
We sand ninja aren't pushovers
like our friends from the leaf.
Oh, and standing as close as
you are to my friend, the Black
Ant-- big mistake.
[scream]
KIBA (VOICEOVER):
I hated going up
against the sand
ninja as enemies,
but as allies they're
pretty amazing.
-What?
That hurt.
You take over, brother.
Let me rest in this
body a little bit first.
-You're so pathetic, Sakon.
-Just who are these freaks?
-This is their most
dangerous ability.
-I can't believe you let that
puppet catch you off guard.
Well, you can be sure I won't.
Its puny power and speed
are nothing special.
It'll take more than
this toy to stop me.
I healed my stomach wound.
I don't have much chakra left.
But it should be more
than enough to vanquish
these scrawny amateurs.
KIBA (VOICEOVER): His wounds
are already back to normal.
That healing ability
is unbelievable.
-I'm not usually the one who
turns into the main body.
It's hard to move like this.
-It's like they're over
there just mocking us.
-This isn't the kind of enemy
you can beat head-to-head.
Back down and we'll regroup!
-I can't back down when
they show me no respect.
-Not quite.
[scream]
-My Black Ant puppet isn't
designed to be used on offense.
Its usual function
is trapping people.
But when the Black And
is paired with the Crow,
it makes a deadly
attack combination.
-Hey, you punk!
Let me out of here!
Can you hear me?
Ahhh!
-And now let's
have a puppet show.
-Hey, let me out!
Let m out, or I'll kill you!
-Secret black move.
Iron maiden!
[scream]
Show's over.
-She must be hiding around here.
-Or she gave up.
-Not her.
She'd never run away.
-Since I'm new to
this fight, maybe it'd
be a good idea for you to
explain the situation to me.
Give me an analysis of her
skills and battle style.
-Well, first off, her
flute casts genjutsu.
She uses it to
ensnare her opponents.
And when they can't move she
delivers a lethal attack.
-Demon flute.
Chains of fantasia.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
This is bad.
Is this a genjutsu?
My body-- I can't move.
-So you said this was your
final move, didn't you?
Unfortunately, it's checkmate.
Die, little rat!
-She's a typical long-range
genjutsu-style shinobi.
Most likely as soon
as she saw your jutsu
she realized it could
counteract her own.
That's why she retreated.
Besides, it's two
against one now.
I doubt she'll
show herself again
until she's able to
cast her genjutsu.
-So it's sound.
-That's right.
Genjutsu's work by affecting
one of the five senses.
Sight, hearing, smell,
taste, and touch.
Among them the ones that involve
hearing are the most dangerous
of them all.
Not only does it allow
her to stay out of view
and keep a safe
distance away from us,
but we'll have no idea when
or where the genjutsu will
be coming from.
The idea is for us to be already
under the spell of her flute
by the time we figure
out where she is.
Ngh-- if you really want
my honest assessment,
we are at an overwhelming
disadvantage here.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
We shouldn't even
talk about facing
this kind of enemy
without close-range
ninja like Kiba or Neji.
-Listen, sooner or later she's
going to get us cornered,
and that'll be that.
I think we should
withdraw until we--
-Excuse me, did I
ask for your opinion?
-What?
-I told you to explain
the situation to me.
That's all.
You have no idea what
kind of powers I have.
If she thinks she
can hide from me
but stay close enough so
the sound of her flute
can still reach
me, she's mistaken.
All right.
Summoning blade dance!
TAYUYA (VOICEOVER): All right.
I'm far enough away.
It's time for my genjutsu.
Huh?
[scream]
-How was that?
It's finished.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): She
doesn't mess around, huh?
She's as subtle as a rhino.
She might even be
scarier than my mom.
-Pretty good, huh?
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): Oh, well.
This time I guess I should
be grateful she's so scary.
[music playing]
-I was careless before, but it
will not be like that anymore.
Now, if you would
please stand back.
I am thankful for your help, but
I will be the one to fight him.
This time with my
ultimate lotus!
Excuse me, but why are
you moving forward?
I already told you,
I am his opponent!
Come on!
NARUTO: Next time-- showdown!
Gaara versus Kimimaro!