[theme music]
[crickets chirping]
-This promises to be a
challenging mission, Lee.
Are you ready?
-Yes, sensei!
I am always ready.
-Hahaha!
Spoken like a true protege!
Well, then, let's go!
-Lead on, Gai-sensei!
[ding]
-The subjects are moving out.
And from the size of those
big packs they're carrying,
they ought to be gone for
awhile, overnight, at least.
-What a break, to think
we'd be lucky enough
to get the perfect
opportunity right off the bat.
-Well, what we were
waiting for you?
-You're right!
Commencing elite
Operation Infiltration.
-Aaugh!
-Huh?
-Ahhh!
[thud]
-Hey, get off, idiot!
Aaugh.
There's the target!
Ripe for the plucking.
Hidden Leaf Village,
here we come.
NARUTO: "The Appearance
of Strange Visitors"
MALE SPEAKER: It worked!
We look just like them.
We're dead ringers.
-Yo!
-Of course it worked.
I mean, why do you think
we spent all those months
perfecting our Disguise Jutsu?
-Their secrets will be
ours for the taking!
-Mmm. [breaking wind]
-Right!
This mission will
make us legends!
Not to mention the honor
it'll bring our village.
-We'll be famous!
And they'll give
us more missions!
[crowd cheers]
[laughing]
-OK, from now on,
I'm not Bandai.
I'm Gai from the Leaf Village.
-And I'm not Pocha,
I'm Rock Lee!
-Then let's go, Lee!
-Lead on, Gai-sense!
[shing]
[boinging]
-Now this is what
I call a village!
-Ahh!
-Ew!
-Ugh!
-Look at that!
Everyone here's a ninja!
-Stop staring like that!
You look like a tourist.
[bonk]
-Now, listen.
They've got a thing in this
village called a hokage.
He's like their chief,
and wherever we find him,
that's where we'll find
their secret documents.
-Right!
Got it.
-This guy's a big
shot, so just look
for the biggest
building in the village.
-Eh?
-Huh?
-Wait, there!
That's gotta be it!
-Something going on
at the hokage's place?
-Dah!
-What's up?
-Nothing!
Nothing-- Nothing
at all, really.
We-- we-- we're
just standing here!
We're not after any secret
documents or anything!
-Shut up!
[bonk]
-Heh, don't-- don't mind him.
-OK.
-Idiot!
-What're you trying to do?
Give us away?
-No.
Sorry!
-Anyway!
Hi, I'm Gai.
-And I'm Lee.
-Hmm.
You two don't look
like yourselves.
Are you feeling all right?
-Yeah, fine.
Never better.
-There's something
different about you.
I can't quite put
my finger on it.
-Ahh!
Look there!
A flying monkey, eating
an egg roll with his feet!
-Really?
Where?
[zooming off]
-Hey, are you guys pulling my
leg, or-- Hmm, that's funny.
[labored breathing]
-Ooh, that was close!
That nosy ninja
snuck right up on us!
-Yeah, but don't worry.
We fooled that sucker.
-You bet we did.
Our Disguise Jutsu
could fool anyone.
-Yeah.
-Woo hoo hoo!
This is gonna be even
easier than we thought!
-Yeah!
Who said the Leaf
Village was so tough?
[laughing]
-Gai and Lee impostors,
here in the village?
-Real ninja would have
used transformation jutsu
to disguise themselves.
Who are these guys?
They sound pathetic.
[oinking]
-The village must be doing well.
The wackos are moving in.
-Not that I think these
clowns pose much of a threat,
but I thought it was
worth reporting anyway.
-No matter how
harmless they seem,
we can't have intruders
running around freely.
Should we run them out of town?
-Not yet.
Hold off a while.
-Huh?
-Who knows, it might be amusing.
We'll think of them as
a sort of a training
exercise for the
people of the village.
-But, are you sure?
-I wouldn't worry
much about that.
I can't imagine anyone
being dumb enough
to actually fall
for these imposters.
[chuckles]
-Come on, Gai-sensei.
I'm beggin' ya.
Just this once!
Please, Bushy Brow?
Please?
Let me train with you
once, just for today?
Please, please,
please, please, please!
Oh, come on.
I won't get in your way, really!
-Hey!
What're we gonna
do about this guy?
-He obviously knows
them pretty well.
-Yeah, but he wants
to train with us.
We don't know any training!
-Huh?
-Come on!
You know I've been dyin' to
learn that taijutsu of yours!
I'll do anything!
Anything at all!
Name it!
Come on, please!
-We've gotta lose this kid.
-Sorry.
The answer is no.
-Heh?
Why not?
-Well, our training is
difficult and dangerous.
And of course ultra,
ultra top secret as well.
-Ultra, ultra top secret?
That's so cool!
I gotta have it, gotta have it!
Please?
Come on.
I won't tell anyone, I promise!
Please?
Please? [squealing]
-We said no!
Now go away!
-No, no, no!
-OK, you guys!
You asked for it!
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
[gasping]
-This kid can make real clones!
-And now, Harem Jutsu!
[poof]
-Huh?
What the heck?
[coughs]
-What's going on here?
[laughing deliriously]
-Oh, say yes, please!
[kissing noises]
-Ha!
Sure, why not?
-Doh!
[poof]
-What the--
-Why'd you say yes?
Now we're stuck with this kid!
-OK, OK, I know.
Let me think.
FEMALE SPEAKER: Hey,
Gai-sensei, Lee!
-Wha--
-What's going on?
Where do you think you're going?
-Huh?
-We're supposed to be
helping that farmer today!
-Farmer?
-Don't tell me you forgot!
We promised we'd help him.
Come on, he's waiting.
-Oh, uh--
-Wait!
Wait!
-Hey, is this part
of our training?
-Uh, well, uh--
-We promised to plant all
these rice paddies for you?
We must have been
out of our minds!
-Whoa.
That's a lotta rice.
-Can't tell ya how
much I appreciate
you boys lendin' a hand.
-Oh, don't give it a thought.
-They love nothing more
than helping people in need.
So long!
[splash]
-What kind of stupid
training is this?
Wait a second!
Yeah, that's it!
Back-breaking labor combined
with incredible boredom!
It's some kind of
endurance training!
Hey, I love it!
Don't worry.
I could do this all day!
-There's something not
quite right about that kid.
-Ugh.
This is not how I pictured
Elite Operation Infiltration.
-Ah, shaddup.
Let's just hurry
up and finish this.
-OK, OK.
Nngh.
Ahh!
[splash]
-Watch where you're
steppin', will ya?
-Heh, sorry about that.
-Huh?
-What's that thing?
Ugh!
-Pocha!
--[chuckling] Oops, forgot to
mention the flyin' leeches.
Might want to keep
an eye out for 'em.
-F-- f-- flying leeches?
Ahh!
-[chucklng] Yup!
They'll suck the
life right outta ya,
quicker'n you can spit.
-Ugh.
[splash]
-Ahh!
Pocha!
Hang in there, I'm coming!
Aaugh!
[slapping]
-Nngh.
And I thought it
was gonna be boring!
Man, this taijutsu training
really keeps you on your toes!
[labored breathing]
-Hoo!
That was a good work-out!
-Are we done yet?
Thought I was gonna die.
-All righty!
Ready for the next?
-Huh?
-What do we do with it?
-I need you spread it out
in that field over there.
-Nngh.
What's this training for?
-Man, this stuff is
heavy and it stinks!
-This definitely isn't
according to plan.
-Guh!
-Augh!
-You guys look a little beat.
What's the matter?
Can't you eve walk
in a straight line?
--[growling] Sure, but
any idiot can do that!
We're trying to
practice our dodging
and weaving to avoid enemy fire!
-Oh, evasive action!
I get it.
Uh, is this the idea?
Whoa, you're right!
It's a lot harder to carry
when you dodge and weave.
-Aw, what a jerk!
-Man, it's great how you
guys can turn the simplest
thing into a training exercise!
It's really impressive!
-Hey!
You wanna watch where
you're swingin' that thing?
-Huh?
What thing?
-Ahhh!
[splat]
-Ahhhhh!
[water flowing]
-Nngh.
[splash]
-Ahh.
-This is a nightmare!
-Hey, look.
What do you say we just lose
this kid and get on with it?
--[sniffing] No offense, but
I think you missed a spot.
-Just shut up!
-Who asked you?
-Gai-sensei, Lee!
There you are!
-Sakura!
Hi!
-Oh, Naruto.
What are you doing here?
-Well, you see.
These guys are teaching
me all their ultra
top-secret techniques by
letting me train with them!
-Really?
-So, is there something
you need us for?
-Oh, uh, no.
Not you.
But you two-- there's something
I really need your help with!
-Huh?
-What?
You lost your laundry?
-Not lost, exactly.
The wind caught it and
blew it way up there.
-Sorry.
Love to help, but
right now we're
really busy with
all our training.
-Please?
You're the only
ones I can trust!
Can't you think
of it as training?
Please!
I love that laundry.
-Nngh.
-I don't know what all
the big fuss is about,
but if it's really
that important,
I can get it for you, Sakura.
[boff]
-Ugh!
-You'll do it for me,
right, Gai-sensei?
Right?
-Right!
-It-- it sure is high.
And steep!
A straight fall to the bottom!
-Exactly!
One false step and forget it.
-Huh?
Forget what?
-Ahhh!
-There!
Up there.
See it?
[wind blowing]
-I think we'll take a pass.
-Yeah, right!
Good one!
With your chakra
control, Gai-sensei,
going up that cliff's just
like a walk in the park!
-He's amazing, isn't he?
I've always felt
we're so lucky having
an awesome ninja
like you around.
-Oh, well-- [laughing nervously]
-Well, ready to go?
-Uhh.
-Oh brother.
[wind rushing]
-I don't believe it!
How did we get into this?
-We're gonna die!
We're gonna die!
-Ahhh!
-Is there something
I'm missing here?
How come you guys are
doing it that way?
Why don't you use your chakra?
-Argh, because that'd be
cheating, you numbskull!
We're building up our
physical strength!
-So that's your plan!
Man, you guys never do
anything the easy way, do ya?
Always pushing
yourself to the limit!
I'm really learning a lot
training with you, sensei!
-You believe this kid?
-We're gonna die.
-Up we go!
-Ahhh!
-Sorry about that!
Whoops!
Whoa, that was a close one!
-You can say that again!
[wind gusting]
-Nngh.
We made it!
-Aaugh!
-Don't look down, you idiot!
Now come on, let's
grab this stupid thing
and get out of here!
Guh.
Come here.
Got it!
Ugh.
It's stuck.
-Well, what're you waiting for?
-Nngh.
[wind gusting]
-Hang on!
-You hang on!
-Hyah!
-Nngh!
-What're you doing?
Use your chakra control!
-Chakra schmakra!
-Ack!
I gotcha!
-Uh oh.
-Whoa!
-Ahhh!
Bushy Brow!
Gai-sensei!
-Ahhh!
[thud]
-I've had it.
-Sensei!
Bushy Brow!
-Huh?
-That was totally awesome!
And without even
using your chakra!
I'm completely blown away.
-So were we.
-Ah, there you are!
Perfect.
-Huh?
-It's Grandma Tsunade!
-I've been looking for you two.
I need your help.
-Nngh!
-It's my dear friend.
She hasn't been
feeling very well.
-You want us to what?
-You see, she's caught
a cold or something.
-Your friend's one
heck of a big slug!
She's kinda like Pervy
Sage's big toad, Right
-Yeah.
Something like that.
[clearing throat] Anyway,
I want you two to look after
her until I can move her.
I know how sensitive
and caring you can be.
-I'm sorry to be
so much trouble.
[earth-shaking coughing]
-Whoa!
-Aaugh!
-Forget it!
This is where I draw the line.
-But if we give up
now, we'll never
be able to steal their secrets!
-Yeah, you're right.
-What is this?
-Huh?
What the devil are
you grumbling about?
[click]
[earth crumbling]
-Auugh!
-I don't believe it.
Are you two
seriously considering
disobeying the orders
of your hogake?
MALE SPEAKERS:
That's the hokage?
[splash]
-Oh, man!
I never thought the
hokage would be so scary!
-Listen, we're taking
care of her precious
and dear friend, right?
It's a perfect way
to gain her trust.
Then we can steal her secrets!
-I dunno.
-So even summoning animals
get sick too, don't they?
GIANT SLUG: Itchy nose,
scratchy throat, achy all over?
Yes, it's just a
very light cold.
-A cold towel on your forehead
oughta bring the fever down!
-Thank you so much!
-OK, hold it steady now.
-Ah-- ah-- sorry,
I'm gonna have to--
[earth rumbling]
-Ahh!
-Achoo!
-Oh boy!
[splash]
-Nnngh!
-Ahhh!
-What is it, acid?
-Hey, watch where you're
blowin' that stuff, will ya?
-I'm so sorry, but I
couldn't help myself.
Ah-- ah-- achoo!
-Ahhh!
-Achoo!
-Aaugh!
-Gai-sensei, what's
wrong with you?
Why don't you get out
of that snot storm
before you're burnt to a crisp?
-Oh, shut up, you little squirt!
It's all part of the training.
We're just, uh,
working on our reflexes
and keeping calm under fire!
-Ah!
I should have known!
Everything's part
of their training,
even something like this!
Look at Bushy Brow!
Even with his butt on
fire, he's still training!
And I thought I was tough.
[slap]
-Now I get it!
All right, Gai-sensei!
Don't worry, I'm on
guard, I'm with ya!
OK, hit me with your best snot!
-Oh dear!
I have such an
aching in my joints,
and a splitting headache.
-What the-- What do
you mean, joints?
Slugs don't have joints!
-Ahhh!
-Hey, hey, watch
where you're going!
[thud]
-Ahhh!
-This village is hell.
We're in hell.
I don't think I'll survive
another minute in this place.
Ugh.
-I say we quit.
-Yeah, fine.
Nngh.
-Huh?
-Explain yourself!
Who are you?
-And why are you dressed
like my protege, Rock Lee?
-OK, that does it!
I'm sick of this game!
-Ahhh!
Super Mega Extra Hyper Attack!
-I have no idea
what this is, but I
think we are under attack!
-So it would appear.
Are ya ready, Lee?
-Our new technique?
BOTH: Double Dynamic Entry!
[thud]
-I've forgotten.
Why did we ever do this in
the first place, I wonder?
-If I never see the
Leaf Village again--
BOTH: It'll be too soon!
[ting]
-Look, fireworks!
-I don't know where they came
from or what they were after,
but I doubt we'll see
them again anytime soon.
-You certainly seemed
to be enjoying yourself.
You even summoned Katsuyu.
-Hmm.
Well, it wasn't just me.
It was a team effort, wasn't it?
-Well, now that all the
fun and games are over,
you should really be
getting back to work.
-[sighing] Yes, ma'am.
-I wonder.
Do you think Naruto
really fell for them?
-Naw, no one could be that dumb.
Not even him.
-What was all about?
Very peculiar!
-Very!
-Hey!
-Naruto!
Did you see those two imposters?
-There you are!
So you're both all right?
I thought I lost you!
-Hmm?
Gai-sensei, I
gotta admit, I used
to think you were
kind of a lightweight,
but now I take it all back!
-The way you always push
yourselves to the limit
and never let up?
I think I'm ready for
that kind of commitment.
I want to continue my training!
-What training is that?
-Yeah, good one!
So when do we get to the
taijutsu and all that?
-Uhhh.
-Huh?
CROW: Moron!
Moron Moron!
[theme music] see
NARUTO: Ghost hunting?
That's no job for a ninja!
Besides, ghosts
don't even exist!
SAKURA: Stop complaining!
A mission is a mission!
NARUTO: The ghost of
some dead warlord!
Yeah, right!
Gimme a break.
SAKURA: They say he appears
in the dead of night,
wearing his gleaming
white armor!
NARUTO: Ooh, scary!
That's so stupid!
SAKURA: Naruto!
Behind you!
NARUTO: What, where?
SAKURA: Ha ha!
So it's stupid, huh?
NARUTO: Next time,
"The Cursed Warrior!"
[theme music]