THEME SONG:
[singing in japanese]
-All right.
Thanks for waiting, everybody.
To celebrate this
show's blockbuster run,
we bring you the top five ninja
battles to date, full of blood,
sweat, and tears.
And plenty of extras
packed in, to boot!
Boy, it kind of gives you
butterflies inside, doesn't it?
-It's been four years now
since the show hit the air,
and our fifth is just
around the corner.
But without all
our terrific fans
we never would have
made it this far.
-So today we've decided
to switch things up a bit,
take a moment to look back at
the five most popular showdowns
in Naruto history, as voted
on by the people of the Hidden
Leaf Village.
-And who knows?
Maybe you'll see your
own personal favorite
in the shuffle.
With all the special guests
we have lined up for you,
you won't want to miss a beat.
-Now let's get
this party started.
Right off the bat
we'll be taking a look
at the fights that clocked
in at fourth and fifth place.
Yeah.
Here we go.
I'm the first one on the board.
Just what you'd expect
from the hero of the story.
I've got the audience
in the palm of my hand.
SAKURA: Ooh!
You're so right.
The poetry of Sasuke in
motion-- it's indescribable.
His destructive power
is mind-blowing.
Ah!
NARUTO: OK.
Uh, Sakura-- we're not really
on the same page here, you know?
SAKURA: Ah, zip it
for once, will ya?
NARUTO: Right.
-Multi-shadow clone jutsu!
SAKURA: He switches
between offense and defense
in a heartbeat.
And now for the kick!
That's it.
Hit him where it hurts!
And
NARUTO: Ahem.
Uh, Sakura-- how about
a little cheerleading
for the hero of the story, here?
SAKURA: Shut up, Naruto!
-Uzumaki Barrage!
-Fire Style-- Fireball jutsu!
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): How did
he-- what jutsu is that?
Blast.
-Chidori-- One Thousand Birds!
-Please.
Stop this.
Stop it!
-What did you have
to go and clock me
in the eye for, Sakura?
-I couldn't help myself.
I got too excited.
Now let's get back
on track and find out
who's in the fourth place spot.
-There is nothing you
can do to stop me!
Crushing Palm!
NARUTO: Man.
No matter how many
times I watch this one
it always beings me to tears.
SAKURA: I know what you mean.
I had to pull out a hanky
when I was watching it on TV.
When it aired there wasn't a
dry eye in the Land of Fire.
-Yeah.
I really thought Choji had
bought it in this episode, too.
-That's for sure.
The producers caught me hook,
line and sinker with that one.
-What is that?
Doesn't matter.
Sonic Boulder!
-Don't even try.
Because now I'm a hundred
times stronger than before.
People hold grudges
when you take something
important from them-- like,
for instance, their food.
That strike I gave
you was for eating
the last bite of
my favorite snack!
-Impossible.
This punk has so much chakra
his body's actually changed.
-And this next attack--
is for calling me
names like pawn,
fatso, and loser.
I can handle being picked
on, but what you've done
is unforgivable.
He was my best friend.
And you insulted him.
How dare you?
You can steal my very last
bite of my very best food,
you can mock me all you want.
But when you insult my best
friend-- I will obliterate you!
All of money chakra
to my left hand.
This last attack is
worth my whole life!
-Wait!
No!
Please don't do it!
NARUTO: Seeing it again like
this it really hits you.
This was fatty versus fatty.
I mean, where was the eye candy?
It was all just
huffing and sweating.
I wouldn't watch this on a
summer day, I tell you that.
CHOJI: Well excuse
me for fighting.
NARUTO: What-- Choji?
SAKURA: How long
have you been there?
CHOJI: I heard my big
battle made the top five.
NARUTO: Look, Choji,
let me explain.
SAKURA: Stay calm.
CHOJI: Human Boulder!
Boom, boom, boom!
NARUTO: Whoa!
CHOJI: I rule.
-I did it.
CHOJI (VOICEOVER):
A guy like me.
I beat him.
-Sorry for the technical
difficulties, folks.
But hey, what do you
say we just press on?
-But before we move
on to the top three,
why don't we revisit a few
of the breathtaking battles
that didn't quite
make the final cut.
Is the epic showdown you've
always liked one of them?
Let's have a look and see.
-Tori.
Water style.
Water Dragon jutsu.
NARUTO: Kakashi-sensei
will always
have the upper hand
with his Sharingan.
SAKURA: Just what you'd
expect of a jounin.
-Late again.
NARUTO: Huh?
This is an epic battle?
SAKURA: Well, sometimes you
gotta mix things up a little,
right?
-We've tied each
other at 48 wins.
Today's face-off will put
one of us in the lead.
-You're not going to take
no for an answer, are you?
All right, then.
It's my turn to name
the challenge, right?
-So what'll it be?
A round of taijutsu?
A hundred-meter dash?
Holding our breath?
Or an eating contest, maybe?
-Oh, boy.
OK.
I got one.
-Yeah?
Lat it on me.
-Rock, paper, scissors.
-All right.
You're on.
And I aim to win.
If I lose I'll take 500 laps
around the Leaf Village.
On my hands, too.
-There you go again.
-That's a promise!
-Great.
Another one of his oddball
self-imposed rules.
NARUTO: OK.
All together, now.
-Rock!
Paper!
Scissors!
SAKURA: We'll be back
with the top three
after this short break.
Stay tuned.
And now, the moment you've
all been waiting for.
The mega three.
-Starting with the third.
Let's see which battle busted
through to the upper ranks!
SAKURA: Look!
It's the Kiba-Akamaru
dynamic duo.
NARUTO: Big deal.
Those two are all
bark and no bite.
-What are you saying?
Are you telling me
you want to try that?
We can't, Akamaru.
There's nobody
here to back us up.
It'd be way too dangerous.
You understand, don't you?
If we miss we'll have
died for nothing.
Akamaru.
KIBA (VOICEOVER): I must
be a lousy master for you
to bite me like that.
OK, Akamaru.
It's just like you said.
We're all out of options.
-Wolf Fang Over Fang it is.
[laughter]
Now, Akamaru!
KIBA (VOICEOVER): Show 'em
what all that training was for!
-Dynamic Marking!
-What kind of cheap
trick is that?
-OK.
We're good to go.
Inuzuka style.
Man Beast Transformation Combo!
Two-Headed Wolf!
Take this!
-[inaudible].
-Sakon, you idiot.
On your right!
-Oh, no.
I--
-Wolf Fang Over Fang!
SAKURA: A bite on the
hand helped his master
with a tough decision.
Akamaru's popularity
went through the roof
after this fight.
Oh, what a man!
NARUTO: Man my butt.
He's just a mangy mutt of a
dog with beady little eyes.
-You got a problem with
my dog, you nitwit?
-Ahh!
Kiba?
How long you been
standing there?
I didn't even see you.
-Shut it.
Is this how you treat
a guest on your show?
We're in the top rank,
for crying out loud.
And speaking of
insulting, what's
the deal with us coming
in at number three?
-Our third place
finalist, folks.
A man and his dog.
Why don't you face the
camera and offer a few words
to everyone watching
back at home.
-Oh, uh-- thanks a million
for tuning in every week.
We could never have done it
without all your support.
I know we came in
third and all, but you
can expect some real
butt-kicking in the future.
So don't you count us out yet.
-That's pretty big
talk, there, dog-boy.
I don't recall any other
moments of greatness lately.
-I said in the future, didn't I?
That's it.
I've had enough of you.
Sic him, Akamaru.
-And now we move on to
the big number two spot.
NEJI (VOICEOVER): He's like
a totally different opponent.
His chakra activity
is staggering.
And those markings--
KIDOMARU (VOICEOVER): So, this
guy is able to see in the dark.
And to dodge an
attack from behind.
In other words he's got
360-degree x-ray vision.
On top of that
there's that jutsu.
-All right.
Summoning jutsu!
-I warn you, kid.
However strong
your defenses are,
I can find a way around it.
KIDOMARU (VOICEOVER): If he
can block the physical attacks
by emitting lots of
chakra and rotating
then all I have to do
is stop that rotation.
NARUTO: This fight
took second place?
SAKURA: Yep.
Two sharp minds pitted
against one another.
NARUTO: Eh.
I dunno.
The slow, plodding stuff
isn't really my cup of tea.
SAKURA: How come?
NARUTO: Well, it's just--
when I'm watching a fight,
I wanna see some action.
Bodies in motion.
A real slug-fest, you know?
SAKURA: But there's
more to being
a ninja than just taijutsu.
NARUTO: Hey, watch it.
That's being rude to bushy-brow.
SAKURA: Oh.
Sorry.
NARUTO: That's what I'm
talking about, anyway.
Something fiery like
bushy-brow would do.
That's what Neji's
battles are missing.
All the fire.
-Now!
NARUTO: It's too thought-out.
Too-- logical, or something.
He should just jump in there
and flatten his opponent.
-It's because you
think like that
that missions are
such a chore with you.
-Neji!
-And now a few words
from Neji of the Hyuga
clan, our second-place finalist.
-This is just silly.
You're free to evaluate
my battle, I suppose.
But participating in this
farce is utterly beneath me.
-Whatever.
At least you get to
preen like you always do.
Oh, wait.
I bet it's an appearance
fee you're after, huh?
It's too bad for you, then.
We're doing this as a thank
you to all the fans out there.
So your appearance on the
show is pro-bono, buddy.
-That isn't a problem.
I've spoken with the Hokage.
She's deemed my being
here as a mission.
I had no choice but to show up.
And since it is a mission, I'm
of course being compensated.
-Boy.
Practical as ever,
aren't you, Neji?
-You're tell me you
got paid for this?
How is that supposed to be fair!
-Just face it, will you?
My brain is built
differently than your own.
Gentle Fist!
-It seems that the big board
is out of commission so
why don't we cut to the chase
and announce number one?
Which epic battle managed
to come out on top?
-Chidori.
NARUTO: No surprises here.
It wouldn't have made sense
if the top battle wasn't
one of mine.
SAKURA: Yeah.
I don't think
there's anybody out
there who doesn't feel
this should be number one.
-Rasengan!
-Chidori!
-So how about it?
Was everyone out there
able to guess right?
The greatest battle of
all time was brought to us
by none other than Sasuke!
-Hey, hold on a minute, there.
I think you might have this
turned around a little bit.
-Turned around?
What's that mean?
-Forget it.
It's not important.
Alrighty, then.
Let's get this train
back on the tracks
and check out a little
bonus footage of yours truly
in action.
Eat your hearts out,
two through five!
-You idiot!
-Say what?
What the heck is this?
What happened to
the tape I put in?
It's not what I prepared at all.
Stop the tape!
Wait, don't look at this!
I get top billing here.
Now cut the tape,
do you hear me?
-Oh, stop making
such a fuss, already.
And now the moment has arrived.
It's time to meet
our special guest.
We bring you live and on
location to our correspondent
master Jiraiya.
-Ah!
-Can you hear me
out there, Jiraiya?
-Absolutely.
I'm picking you both
up loud and clear.
-Now tell us, are
you able to talk
about where you
are at the moment?
-Hm.
I'm kind of in a
tricky spot, here.
I can't divulge the
details of my location.
The most I can tell
you is that I'm
in a certain someone's
secret hidden lair.
-What's the deal
here, pervy sage?
What are you doing
outside of the village?
I thought you were supposed to
be overseeing my training right
now.
-Oh come on, Naruto.
This is a special episode.
Stop being a stick
in the mud, will ya?
And anyway, get a load of the
guest I've rustled up for us.
None other than Orochimaru.
-Huh?
What's going on around here?
Did you know this
was gonna happen?
-This is quite a surprise.
Orochimaru.
-Oh, it's a pleasure, dear.
But what a shame you didn't
invite me into the studio.
-You can't be serious.
As if we'd ever invite you here!
-Right you are.
We'd have been too busy anyway,
what with all our research
and amassing of jutsu.
I'm sure that you understand.
After all, I need Sasuke
to advance his strength
as quickly as possible.
-If-- if he's there--
then let us see him!
-Oh, believe, I tried
to get your young friend
to participate a little,
what with today being
a special occasion
and everything.
But sadly he's
ignoring me and has
chosen to mope the day away.
-Oh.
-Hey.
Are you gonna go on all day?
I came here to train, not to
waste my time, Orochimaru.
-Sasuke.
-It is you.
It is you, isn't it?
-I'm gonna head over to the
training hall right now.
Don't make me wait.
-Wait!
-Well goodness, now.
You've gonna and angered
my young protege.
I'll have to bid my
farewell, then, I guess.
-No, wait!
Put Sasuke back on again!
-Sakura-- I'm pretty sure
he can't hear you anymore.
-Yeah, I know.
You're right.
-Sakura--
-No, you're right.
OK.
On with the show.
Well, it's time to
say our goodbyes.
We're so glad yo could be here.
Thanks so much to
everyone for watching
and for all your support.
We hope you enjoyed all
the thrills, the spills,
and everything in between,
here on our top five big battle
countdown.
-Uh, hey.
You can't close the show
on your own like that.
And what about the
footage I was gonna
show of me kicking some butt?
-We don't have
time for all that.
Just take us to
commercial break, OK?
-What?
Man.
All right.
Whatever.
Well, sorry about that, folks.
It looks like my
little fighting montage
will have to wait
till next time.
But you can all
rest assured, I'll
be knocking your
socks off in no time.
-Anyway, thanks, everyone.
-We hope you'll all
keep watching Naruto.
See ya later, everybody.
Buh-bye!
[theme music]
THEME SONG:
[singing in japanese]
-Ah, I didn't think you
were such a stubborn fool.
-Well, your yelling
won't change anything.
-If we don't do something
she's gonna dump us.
-That's our sensei's decision.
-What about you, Hinata?
-We don't know the
whole story yet, so--
-What, you're siding with Shino?
-No, I--
-What are you guys
fighting about?
-Naruto-- Kurenai-sensei--
Kurenai-sensei is quitting.
NARUTO: Next time-- Kurenai's
Decision-- Squad Eight,
Left Behind!
THEME SONG:
[singing in japanese]