[theme music]
-What did you say?
You mean you sent
Genin after Sasuke?
-Well, what else could I do?
You know the state that this
village is in right now.
[sigh]
-Anyway, I have a
contingency plan in place.
Hey, where are you going?
You already have a
mission assigned to you.
KAKASHI: I have to go
run an errand first.
Be back in a bit.
Don't worry.
-Oh, brother.
-Kakashi-sensei, Kakashi-sensei.
It's already been
two full days now
since Sasuke left the village.
Naruto and the others
haven't come back.
And Lee's out there too.
-I know.
I'm pretty much up to speed now.
-Sensei, I-- I have
faith in Naruto, I do.
I believe in him.
But if anything were to
happen to those two, I--
-Sakura, you don't need
to worry about a thing.
Just leave it to me.
Summoning Jutsu.
OK guys, fan out
and start searching
for Naruto and Sasuke's scent.
-Did you say Naruto and Sasuke?
What's going on?
What happened to
the two of them?
-I'll explain later.
Right now, time
is of the essence.
-Right.
KAKASHI: Let me know as soon
as you pick up their scent.
I'll be there immediately.
All right, scatter.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): Well,
they did go at each other right
before her eyes.
Guess there's no point in
telling her not to worry.
[screaming]
-Stop!
No!
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): Damn.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Can't stop.
-No!
-Let it go.
You've got to forget
about revenge.
-What?
-Even if you attain it, all
you will find is emptiness.
-Shut up.
What makes you think you
know anything about it?
It's easy for you to talk.
You have no idea.
-Easy.
Just try to calm down.
So it looks like neither of us
has led a charmed life exactly,
have we?
Still, we're not
all that bad off.
At least you and I
have been lucky enough
to find new comrades
to help fill the void.
Anyway, I do know how you feel.
With the Chidori,
you've been granted
a gift of awesome power.
It's not a power to be
used against your comrade,
or to seek vengeance.
I think in your heart of
hearts, you know what it's for.
-I'll win no matter what.
-I'm not finished with you yet.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
I was too naive.
Those two could end
up killing each other.
[dog howling]
-Hm?
-Kakashi-sensei.
-I hope I'm not too late.
SASUKE: I know I said
this already, but be
honest with yourself.
You've been waiting
for this moment too.
Kakashi and Sakura
aren't here now.
Nobody's going to stop
us like the last time.
-You lousy--
-This time we settle
it once and for all.
It will be the end of you!
Chidori!
-You idiot.
Right back at you, pal.
I'll beat you into
oblivion if that's
what it's going to take
to bring you back home.
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
Rasengan!
-Our time together
wasn't meaningless.
One thing was worthwhile--
our friendship.
We became best friends.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Sasuke
actually came out and said that
to me.
And now, I'm going to put it
to the test with this Rasengan.
Sasuke, what's happened to you?
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): Damn it.
He was able to counter my
Chidori at its full power.
-Damn it.
Naruto, how far have you--
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
You pathetic loser.
Naruto.
-So, looks like you're
good for two bursts.
That's about your limit.
-What would happen if I tried
to use it more than twice?
-Well for one thing,
it wouldn't work.
But remember this, if you try to
force a jutsu, not only will it
not work, but the
attempt can drain
your chakra to absolute zero.
Worst case scenario, you die.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): I
can't waste another blow.
It would be pointless.
All we'll do is cancel
each other out again.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): That's it.
There's no mistaking it now.
You're dead serious
about this, aren't you?
You really mean to--
Sasuke.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): I have to
use some of my faster jutsu
to create an opening.
And then I'll hit
him with Chidori.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Sasuke.
-You know what they
say, don't you, Naruto?
When two shinobi
are powerful enough,
they are able to read each
other's thoughts simply
by an exchange of fists, without
ever uttering a single word.
Get it?
You've always been
naive, Naruto.
Tell me, do you
know my thoughts?
Can you tell what's on my mind?
Fire Style Phoenix Flower Jutsu.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Sasuke, I always knew
that you were alone.
At first, when I realized
there was someone else like me
around, I was relieved.
And happy too.
To tell the truth, I wanted to
approach you right off the bat.
But I just couldn't
work up the nerve.
-Whoa.
-Sasuke.
-Did you see that?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): You were
always able to do everything,
and everyone was always
fawning over you.
You were so far ahead of me,
and I didn't want to admit it,
so I started to see
you as my rival.
I didn't want to lose to you.
And with everyone
calling me a loser,
it just made things worse.
Even when we became Squad 7, I
never stopped feeling that way.
I was stubborn, and I couldn't
express what I really felt.
The truth was I really
just wanted to be like you.
You were-- you were
everything I aspire to.
That's why--
-You're one of the ones
I want to fight the most.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
You have no idea
how happy you made me that day.
It was the first time you ever
said anything acknowledging me.
You and I don't need
to come to blows
to know each other's
thoughts anyway.
Ever since that day, even
though we've never said it,
the truth is you
and I are friends.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): It's
not insignificant to me.
There's no question--
you're my closest friend.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
But now you're
seriously trying to take me out.
And I don't really
know if you meant
what you said before or not.
Maybe I was the only
one who thought--
who thought that
we were friends.
-I told you, it's
too late, Naruto.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
If that's the case,
then-- then how stupid am I?
Sasuke.
I-- I can't help it.
I don't know why.
I don't know why,
but-- but I-- I just
can't bear the thought
of seeing you taken away
by someone like Orochimaru.
-You managed to divert the
blow with your left hand
at the last second.
But in the end, it
doesn't matter, does it?
You're finished anyway.
You can forget all about hand
signs and that jutsu of yours.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
This is the end.
What is this red chakra?
Where is he getting
this kind of power?
What is this?
The wound in his
shoulder, it's vanishing.
I don't believe it.
-Sasuke.
I'm not letting
Orochimaru take you away.
Do you understand me?
I'll break every single
bone in your body
if that's what it
takes to stop you!
You're not going anywhere!
[theme music]
[screaming]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I've
heard enough of this.
I don't care what
you're thinking.
This ends now.
Orochimaru's now getting
his hands on you.
You're going back to
the Hidden Leaf Village
if I have to drag you
all the way there!
Sasuke, you are my-- Next
time-- A Plea From a Friend.