[theme music]
[screaming]
-No, no.
[screams]
[panting]
-Ah.
[grunts]
--[shouting] Go away,
leave my father alone!
-Get out of here, Fuki.
Hurry.
[gasp]
-What are you waiting for?
Forget what your job is?
Do I have to do it for you?
Out of the way.
-No, Fuki.
-Hey, I like that.
Thanks.
You won't be needing it.
-I beg you, please,
spare my daughter.
-Save your breath.
[screams]
-No!
Father, father, get
up, father. [crying]
-Humph.
-Don't you touch her.
Ah.
- Ah!
-You--
[crying]
-Here.
It's all right.
[gasps]
-Hm.
[gasping]
[screaming]
-Watch out.
[grunting]
[screaming]
-Ah.
Almost there, I've
almost gotcha.
You're mine.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Legendary
menma pickled bamboo shoots?
CHEF: Oh, it's delicious.
The problem is finding the
right kind of bamboo shoot
to make it.
It's rare, and grows
high up on the side
of steep cliffs,
very hard to find.
-That's only because I haven't
been looking for it yet.
I've got to try this menma
stuff on top of your ramen.
I'll find that bamboo
no matter where it is.
[gasping] OK, you stupid bamboo.
I gotcha.
Ahhh.
[sighs] That was close.
Hm?
It's a person.
Is he alive?
Ahh-- [screams]
-All this thunder, and
not a drop of rain.
It's creepy.
[screams]
-Hey, stop yelling.
Keep it down, this
is a hospital zone.
-You made me yell, you moron.
-Whoa, look at you.
The medical corps finally
gave you a uniform, huh?
-You like it?
Yeah, I've been waiting
forever to get one.
-Looks good.
Anyway, it's a lucky break that
I found you on duty, Sakura.
I've got someone here you
need to take a look at.
-What do you mean?
Who?
-That fella right over there.
-What happened to him?
Looks like hypothermia.
-Hypo-- what?
You mean you know this guy?
That's a funny name.
-It's not his name, you idiot.
It's what happens when your body
temperature, oh, why bother.
Yeah, hypothermia, he's
a guy I used to know.
-Really?
Well, that'll make
things easier.
-Whoa, whoa.
What do you think you're doing?
This is a leaf village hospital,
we can't admit outsiders.
-We can't just leave
him on the ground.
And I've got an important
mission, to take care of him.
-Wait, you can't just-- Naruto!
You get back here.
-Mmm.
Yeah, that's the rare
bamboo, all right.
Well done.
--[giggles] OK, slap it on a
bowl of ramen, and serve it up.
-I hate to break it
to you, but it'll
take three or four weeks
to turn these things
into menma pickled
bamboo shoots.
[cries aloud]
-They get boiled,
then fermented slowly.
Three or four weeks, at least.
-So even a little taste
now, is out of the question?
-Sometimes, the best things
in life require patience.
-So, this is your
important mission, huh?
-Uh, howdy-oh there, Sakura.
Ugh--
-I ought to put
you in a hospital.
You really thought you could
just dump that guy on me,
and then come here
and stuff your face?
-Well, yeah kind of.
-Back to the past, Jutsu.
-What's going on?
What's he doing to him?
-Shhh.
SAKURA: He's probing
his subconscious memory.
-Oh.
That reverse
hypnosis thing, huh?
-Right.
-Can you remember anything now?
I see.
-It seems he's completely
lost his memory.
-He lost his memory?
-Well, that's enough for today.
We'll continue tomorrow.
-Total amnesia, his
name, his village.
He can't remember a thing.
If he won't respond to that
Jutsu, it's a serious case.
-You didn't find
anything on him,
or in his clothes that
might tell us who he is?
-M-mm.
All he had on him
was that thing.
-Hmm.
What is it, anyway?
-An ocarina.
It's a kind of flute.
-Ocarena?
-A broken one.
-You could fix it pretty easily.
-It might be just
a temporary state
of shock causing the amnesia.
Anyway, I need you to
sign this release form.
-Huh?
What for?
-For liability.
Like I said, this is a
leaf village hospital.
We don't treat outsiders, ever.
That's why it's
your responsibility
if anything happens
because of this guy.
-Heh?
-You got a problem?
-Uh, no.
I'm OK.
Just hoping I don't live to
regret doing a good deed.
-Uh.
[gasping] What was that?
It's a fire.
That's near the hospital.
-It's all right.
Everybody, just stay
calm, and keep moving.
Everything will be fine.
[gasps]
[screaming]
-Ah-- ahh.
Forgive me, forgive me.
Forgive me.
-Hey, is anyone still here?
Hello, is anyone up here?
Answer me.
-Sakura, did you
get everyone out?
-I just finished checking again.
-Hey.
Sakura.
-Naruto?
-Is everyone OK?
-Yeah, I think so.
-Wait, where is he?
-Huh?
Now that you mention
it, I don't see him.
-My baby!
He didn't make it out.
Do something, my baby's
still inside there.
-It's still inside?
-Too late, the fire's
too big for anyone
to get back in there.
-Hurry up, and get that
fire under control.
[baby crying]
[music playing]
-I'll go in, no sweat.
-No way.
You'll never make it.
The baby's in the farthest ward.
[music playing]
-Wait, is that--
is that a flute?
It's getting louder.
Getting close.
There he is.
Shadow cloud jutsu!
-We gotcha.
Uhh-ahh.
-And look, look who
he's got with him.
-Well done.
-My baby.
-Oh my, what a relief.
-That was too close.
-Thank you, thank you.
Thank you so much.
-You're welcome.
-I can never thank
you enough, never.
-A mystery outsider
with amnesia.
Well, this is a fine
mess you've put us in.
-It's just one guy.
C'mon, you're going to
him stay, aren't you?
-You know we can't.
To allow a complete stranger
to come into the village,
and live among us?
It's unheard of.
-You can't really suspect that
he's a spy or something, not
after what he did
at the hospital.
-That doesn't make
any difference.
When it comes to the
security of the village,
we cannot bend the rules.
-I've taken responsibility
for him, haven't I?
If he does anything,
I'll handle it.
-Sakura, how's he doing, anyway?
Has he remembered anything yet?
-No ma'am, nothing yet.
-I see.
-C'mon, say yes,
and I'll promise
I'll tell you try some rare
menma pickled bamboo shoots.
-Rare, pickled bamboo shoots?
-That's right.
In fact, I was picking
the bamboo for it
after my last mission
when I found this guy.
Err-
-You were doing what?
-Ow.
-You're supposed to report
back after your missions,
not pick bamboo.
-You can let go now.
-Naruto, are you serious
about taking responsibility
for this stranger?
-Yeah, completely serious.
-Right.
I'll let the boy stay
in the village, for now.
-Lady Tsunade!
-We can't just kick
him out after he
saved the life of
one of our children.
-Now you're talking.
You won't be sorry, grandma.
My name's Naruto, by the way.
It's nice to meet you.
-Oh, I'm, uh--
-Oh, right.
We got to call you something
'til you remember your name.
Let's see.
Uh, I know.
We're going to call you menma.
-Menma?
-Yeah, for the bamboo shoots I
was picking when I found you.
-Menma, huh?
All right, it's a good
a name as any, I guess.
-Well, it's nice
to meet you, Menma.
-Nice to meet you too, Naruto.
-Well, there you go.
-Oh, this looks delicious.
-The ramen in this place
is the best in the world.
-Thanks for the food.
Let's eat.
-Oh, that's good.
[chuckles] You haven't
tasted anything yet.
Didn't you notice that there's
something still missing?
-Huh?
Oh, yeah.
There's no menma pickled
bamboo shoots on it.
-That's right.
And there's not going to be
any until that rare bamboo you
brought me is good, and ready.
-OK, but you're not going
to forget about it, are you?
-No, of course not.
[laughing] Great, I can't wait.
When it's all
ready, you and I are
going to try some menma, Menma.
It's a date, OK?
Welcome to my pad, come on in.
-You sure you don't mind?
-Nah.
From now on, my
home is you're home.
I know it looks a little
messy right now, but--
[gasps] A little messy?
-It's not that bad.
Don't be so picky.
-No, it's fine, really.
-Anyway, I say we
get some sleep.
First thing tomorrow,
you and I start
working on getting
your memory back.
-Mmm. [snoring] (SLEEPTALKING)
No more ramen, I'm stuffed.
OK, one more.
[yawning] I slept like a log.
-Good morning, Naruto.
-Uh?
Menma.
Whoa.
Everything's all cleaned up.
What happened?
Was it you?
You did all this by yourself?
-Yeah.
I couldn't sleep, so
I had time to kill.
-Well, thanks.
I appreciate it.
[yawning] Menma, what
the heck are you doing?
-Huh?
What do you mean?
I'm just taking up the
laundry, that's all.
-Ah, are you crazy?
Washing someone
else's underwear?
Forget about it, leave it alone.
I can do those myself.
-OK.
-All righty then.
The first thing we gotta do is
try and get your memory back.
A-ha.
I got it.
Heh, c'mon.
Ever seen sand dumplings?
They're from the land of wind.
They're called that because
the outside looks like sand,
but they're really good.
-Yeah?
-And these are stone rice
cakes from the land of earth.
Really crunchy, they're the
best if you like crunchy.
-M-hm.
-And the stuff next to
it is mist mitsumame
from the land of water.
Does any of this look
familiar to you, to all?
-No.
None of it.
-Too bad.
I was hoping that something
here would ring a bell,
and then we might know where
you were from, at least.
-Sorry.
-That's OK, it's not
like it's your fault.
-Naruto, thanks, but don't
worry about me, really.
-Why?
-My memory will come
back when it comes back.
If it comes back.
And besides that, you must
work to do, don't you?
-Well, yeah I do, actually.
I'm supposed to clean the
mountainside images today.
-Fine then, I'll
help you with that.
-OK.
Wait a minute.
Before we do that--
-Hm?
Where are you going?
-Excuse me, ma'am.
Could I help carry those
groceries home for you?
-Why, that's very kind of you.
-Thank you very much, young man.
-My pleasure.
I can't help noticing,
it looks like you
need some help with your garden.
-I just let the weeds
grow where they will.
Gardening's too hard
on my back, you see?
-I can take care
of them for you.
-You will?
-Uh, here.
Let me give you a hand.
-Well, thank you both.
-Ugh.
That took a lot
longer than I thought.
-Hey, Naruto?
-Yeah, what?
-They asked for our help, too.
-Really?
-Seems there are a lot of
elderly people living alone
in this part of the village.
-I appreciate the help.
-You're sure you don't mind?
-Heh?
(AFRAID) No.
-What's all this?
-They're all thank you gifts
for Naruto and that boy.
They've been coming in
from all over the village.
-What in the world have
the two of them been up to?
-I've got to say, whoever you
are, you're an unusual guy.
-Am I?
-You're so kind, and
helpful, and hard working.
In my experience, not
everybody's like that.
-I just want to live my life
the right way, that's all.
No, no regrets, you know?
-Why do you say that?
Have you remembered something?
-Oh, uh, no, not really.
-Oh, OK.
Ah.
Great, what is it?
Bird poop?
It's blood.
[gasps] [grunts]
Menma, give me a hand.
-Here.
[grunting]
-What the heck happened?
-There's someone in the village.
[grunting] Let's move.
Menma, will you stay
and look after him?
-Yes, of course.
-Ah.
Oh yeah?
OK.
Come on out, and fight.
Darn it.
Where are these guys hiding?
-Noruto.
[music playing]
-That flute again.
Menma.
What's going on?
All of a sudden, I feel an
incredible surge of power.
All right.
It's unreal.
It's flowing through
my whole body.
-Not so fast.
-Check out this brat.
-Got him.
[gasps]
NARUTO: Substitution jutsu.
-Guess I spoke too soon.
-Naruto.
You OK?
-Menma That music you played.
What was it?
Just who the heck
are you, anyway?
[gasps]
[music playing]
MALE SPEAKER: That is
no ordinary young man.
FEMALE SPEAKER: What if he
turns his powers against us?
MALE SPEAKER: Stop it.
You're talking like Menma's
the enemy or something.
FEMALE SPEAKER: We;ve got
to be ready for anything.
MALE SPEAKER: He might be
another one of those bandits.
NARUTO: Don't be ridiculous.
Let's just take it easy until
he gets his memory back, OK?
-We can't wait.
We have to find out who he is,
and capture those intruders.
-You may trust this guy
Naruto, but we don't.
NARUTO: Next time,
"Bringing Back Reality."