[theme music]
-You're an embarrassment
to our village.
Had you forgotten the reason
we came all the way here?
-I know.
I, I mean, they challenged us.
They started the
whole thing, really.
-See here's what happened.
-Shut up.
-[groan]
-Or I'll kill you.
-Ah, right.
I was totally out of line.
I'm-- I'm sorry, Gaara.
I'm sorry for any
trouble he caused.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): This guy
has an evil look in his eye.
GAARA (VOICEOVER): He stopped
Kankuro with a pebble.
Made it look easy.
This guy is someone
to keep an eye on.
Let's go.
We didn't come
here to play games.
-All right, sure.
I get it.
-Hold on!
Hey!
-What?
-I can tell from your
headband that you
come from the village
hidden in the sand.
Of course the land the fire and
the land of wind are allies.
But no Shinobi can
enter another's village
without permission.
So state your purpose.
And it better be good.
-Really.
Have you guys all been
living under a rock or what?
You don't know what's
going on, do you?
We have permission.
-[gasp]
-Of course, you're correct.
We are hidden Sand Genin.
Our home is the
land of the wind.
And we're here for
the Chunin exams.
Get the picture?
-The Chunin exams?
What's that?
Identify yourself,
powerful new rivals!
Well, I've never heard of
any Chunin exams, believe it.
-I believe it, all right,
that you're totally clueless.
-Hey, boss!
Those are the exams
that every Genin's
got to take in order to graduate
to being a full-on Chunin.
-Oh, well why didn't you say so?
I am so there!
-Huh.
Hey, you.
Identify yourself.
-Hm?
You mean me?
-No, him.
The guy with the
gord on his back.
-Huh?
My name is Gaara of the desert.
I'm curious about you, too.
Who are you?
-I am Sasuke Uchiha.
-Hi there!
I bet you're dying to
know my name, right?
-I couldn't care less.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): Hm.
Things are getting interesting.
-Hey, Konohamaru.
Do I seem uncool or something?
-Well, compared to Sasuke, yeah.
You're pretty lame.
NARUTO: Nah!
You're not going to
show me up, Sasuke!
SASUKE: Hm.
Back off, loser.
-What do you think, Dosu?
-The usual weaklings--
nothing special.
But the one from the
Uchiha clan and that desert
rat-- we should
watch them carefully.
-All right, it is time we chose
our candidates for the Chunin
examinations.
To begin, will those in
charge of the rookie Genin
step forward?
Kakashi, Kurenai, and Asuma.
What do you say?
Are there any in
your squads you'd
recommend who are
ready for the exams
despite their inexperience?
As you know, any
Genin who has carried
out eight or more
missions is technically
eligible for the examinations.
Beyond that, only you can
decide when they are ready.
Of course, most Genin require
a much longer training period--
at least twice
that many missions.
IRUKA (VOICEOVER): There's
no need to say all this.
It's way too soon
for their squads.
-So, Kakashi.
You begin.
-I lead squad seven--
Sasuke Uchiha,
Naruto Uzumaki, Sakura Haruno.
I, Kakashi Hatake,
recommend all three
of these Genin for the
Chunin selection exams.
[gasp]
-And my squad is number eight.
Hinata Hyuga, Kiba Inuzuka,
Shino Aburame, and now I,
Kurenai Yuhi,
recommend all three.
-And my squad is number 10.
Ino Yamanaka, Shikamaru
Nara, Choji Akimichi.
And now I, Asuma Sarutobi,
recommend all three.
RABBLE: Rookies?
[chatter]
-It's been five years since--
-It doesn't make any sense.
-Hold on, just a minute.
-Yes.
What is it, Iruka?
-Lord Hokage.
With all respect, the nine
names that were just given
were all my students
at the Academy.
I know their skills
and abilities.
Every one of them
has great promise.
But it's too soon.
They need more experience
before they are tested.
If they try now, they're
sure to fail the exam.
When I became a Chunin, I was
six years younger than Naruto
is now.
-Naruto is nothing like you!
Are you trying to destroy him?
-Well, they're
always complaining
about not being
challenged enough.
Maybe wiping out on the exams
will teach them a lesson.
A little pain is good?
-What-- what did you say?
-Oh, nothing fatal, of course.
But seriously, Iruka.
Relax.
-[groan]
-Listen.
I understand how you feel.
It's very personal for
you and it upsets you.
But--
-All right, Kakashi.
Back off.
You've said enough.
-On the contrary, Kurenai,
Iruka needs to hear this.
He needs to realize that they're
not his students anymore.
They're mine.
-[growl]
-[groan] Enough already.
-[sigh]
-But these exams
could destroy them!
You know that.
-Iruka!
You have made your point.
I understand.
-Lord Hokage.
-Accordingly, I have decided
that the best thing to do
is to hold a special
preliminary test.
-Pre-- preliminary test?
-[sigh] [scream]
Why, why, why?
It's always the same!
He sets the time and then we
have to wait hours for him.
-It's not fair!
-What about my feelings?
I rushed here so
fast, I didn't even
have time to blow-dry my hair!
-And I didn't even have
enough time to brush my teeth
or change my underwear!
-You didn't?
That's really
disgusting, Naruto.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): First
thing in the morning
and they're already
driving me nuts.
-Hey.
Good morning, everyone.
Sorry I'm late.
Afraid I got lots
on the path of life.
-You liar!
-I know this is a bit
sudden, but I recommended you
for the Chuning exams--
all three of you.
These are the application forms.
-Application forms?
-You're repeating me, Sakura.
This is all voluntary.
It's up to each of you.
If you don't feel ready,
you can wait until next
-All right!
Kakashi Sensai, you rock!
-Don't slobber on my vest!
Whoever wants to take the
exams, sign the application
and come to room
301 at the Academy.
It's at 3:00 PM
five days from now.
That's it.
-[laughter]
Chunin exams.
Chunin exams!
Hm.
Chunin exams.
I'll be up against a lot
of really wicked ninja!
Like the guy with the
mummy on his back!
And, of course, Mr. Attitude.
All right!
Who's the grand champion?
That would be me!
If I come out on top, becoming
Hokage will be easy after that.
-I have to accept it.
Naruto is better than
an old geezer like me.
So I'll just retire
and let him be Hokage.
-Yay!
[giggling]
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): I hope I get
the chance to fight that guy.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
This is hopeless.
I can't keep up with Sasuke.
I can't even beat Naruto!
I'll never pass these exams.
-Hey, Naruto!
Come and play ninja
with us, please!
-Sure!
I don't have any dangerous ninja
missions today, so no problem.
-Excellent!
-All right!
-[gasp]
-Huh.
-[laughter]
-[scream]
-[gasp]
Naruto!
Konohamaru!
Help!
-What are you doing with
Moegi, you big slug?
-Let her go!
Now!
-Ha ha!
[growl]
-Come on, Konohamaru!
[grunt]
-I'm with you, boss!
-Hold on!
-[sigh]
Chunin exams.
-Hey.
-[gasp]
-Sasuke!
What's up?
-Let's take a walk, just and me.
-No way!
You mean it?
-[laughter] Well, well.
He can keep up with
me at this speed.
-I'll get this creep!
Moegi!
-Oh, man.
This is bad.
Where's the boss?
We've got to find the boss!
-Are we lost, or is he?
MOEGI: No!
You let me go!
-[laughter]
I thought that Hidden Leaf
Village had powerful ninja.
But now I see you're nothing--
just a bunch of weaklings.
Hm?
Well, that's was quick.
-Hey, you!
Yeah, you!
The fat old guy!
What do you think
you're doing with Moegi?
-What am I doing?
Is that your question?
You really want to know?
-[gasp]
-If you move, the
brat's finished.
-Hey!
Why are you doing this?
She's just a kid.
Let her go!
-I want the first Hokage
scroll of sealing.
Bring it to me and
I'll let the girl go.
-The scroll of sealing?
-Um, Sasuke?
How come all of a sudden you,
you know, want to walk with me?
-Because I need to tell you to
give up on the Chunin exams.
There's no way you
can pass them, Sakura.
-I was afraid of that.
You're right.
-These ninja are very advanced
and they have no mercy.
If you try to fight them,
you could lose your life.
-But Sasuke!
you're telling me this
gives you care about me!
-I, uh, guess that's true.
-Ha ha!
Two sweethearts.
How touching.
-Get lost, unless
you want to die.
-Talk is cheap!
Ra!
-[grunt]
Now I'm really mad!
-Careful, Sasuke!
-No way!
[gasp]
-Sasuke!
Sasuke?
Sasuke!
-[mumbling]
-Don't just stand
there like a fool!
Hurry up and get the scroll!
-Oh, yeah right.
And what happens if I say no?
-Then I guess you don't care
what happens to this girl.
-What girl?
I see is two dummies-- you,
and the one next to you
made of straw.
-What?
Where'd she go?
Huh?
-She's right there with the
greatest ninja in the world.
-Yeah, that's you, boss!
You're my hero!
-A clone Jutsu?
I'll waste you, punk!
-You just don't know
when you're outclassed!
[grunting]
-Hey, boss!
We're here!
-Yeah, well, it's
about time, you guys!
-Konohamaru!
I was really scared!
-OK, it's all right.
-Did you catch him, boss?
Can we see him?
-Sure!
He's right here.
I'll show you what he-- huh?
-Hey, he used the
substitution Jutsu on you!
-Copycat!
That's what I did to him!
-I see.
-[crying]
-Ha ha ha ha!
He's finished.
And that's how you'll end up
if you take the Chunin exams.
-Oh, Sasuke!
Ha!
I'm no idiot.
I saw right through that cheap
Genjutsu from the first moment.
-What?
-Sasuke inviting me out
then suddenly acting
like he's all worried about me?
Yeah, like he'd ever.
That was a foolish mistake.
You thought I'd fall for that?
-Are you calling me a fool?
-I would if you
were really here.
But you're just an illusion.
The real ninja ran
away like a coward.
So you're just the
illusion of a coward.
-[laughter]
Are you show I'm not real?
-Yeah, I'm sure.
-[laughter]
Just what I'd expect from a
kunoichi trained by Kakashi.
But the Chunin exams will
be more than illusions.
We'll see if you can cut it.
-You don't scare me!
Illusions or not, bring them on!
The Chunin exams!
Take that, Chunin exam!
Oh, actually, I'm really
worried about them.
-[groan]
-Stay out of our village.
-So, how did it go?
-They all mad it-- your
squad and the others.
All nine Genin proved
themselves ready for the exam.
-You were right, Kakashi.
They're good.
They've all developed
very impressive skills.
Hm.
But the Chuning exams
can break anyone.
We'll see if they
can tough it out.
-Did you jear?
We're going to have
rookies at the exams.
First year Ganin.
That has not happened
in five years.
-No way.
I bet it's just some Jonin
trying to boost their egos.
-No, there's more to
the story than that.
Three of them are
from Kakashi's squad.
-Huh.
Interesting.
-But not very.
-Either way, it's
too bad for them.
-Sakura!
Hey, you're late.
-Uh, right.
Sorry, guys.
Good morning, Sasuke.
-Yeah.
What's up with her?
She's different.
[chatter]
-What's going on?
-Can you see?
-I don't know.
-[groan]
-Huh.
You're taking the Chunin exams,
but you can't even get past us?
-Why don't you just give
up now before you get hurt?
-Yeah, I think I hear
your mommy calling you.
-Please let us through!
We're supposed to go in there.
[smack]
-[groan]
-That's harsh!
-Did you say harsh?
Don't kid yourself.
We're being nice by comparison.
The exams are going to make
this look like a picnic.
-Some of you won't
survive the exams.
Others will be wrecked for life.
And some of you may go crazy.
For Chunin, it's
always life and death.
-You think it's a joke?
Chunin are qualified
to lead missions.
The lives of your squad
members are in your hands.
So you better be tough
enough to take the heat.
Delicate little girls
don't belong here.
-We're just thinning
out the heard.
You won't pass anyway.
So go home and play
with your dolls.
-Real nice speech.
Now both of you step
aside and let me through.
And while you're at it,
reverse the Genjutsu.
We can see through
your illusion anyway.
We're going to the third floor.
-What does he mean?
We're on the third floor.
-I know.
-Well, well.
-So you noticed
the Genjutsu, huh?
-Go ahead.
Tell them, Sakura.
I'm sure you saw it
before anyone else did.
-Huh?
-You have the sharpest eyes
and the best analytical skills
on our squad.
You must have seen this
coming a mile away.
-I must have?
Well, sure!
Of course.
Sure!
I spotted it right away.
This is only the second floor.
-Right!
-Huh.
Well, aren't we the smart ones?
So you noticed an illusion.
Now let's see you
deal with this!
-[grunt]
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
How did he do that?
I thought he was some weakling
getting knocked around
like that.
But he's as fast as Sasuke.
-[grunt]
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
He stopped my kick.
That's some chakra
he's got in his arm.
-Hey.
What happened to the plan?
I thought you were the one
who said to keep a low profile
and don't let anyone
see our skill level.
-I know, but--
-Never mind, its over.
Forget it.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): Hey,
what happened to the bruises
he had before?
They're gone.
Were they fakes?
-My name is Rock Lee.
You are Sakura, right?
-Huh?
-Please be my girlfriend.
I vow to protect
you with my life.
-Definitely-- not.
-Hoy!
-Because you're a weirdo.
-Aw.
-[laughter]
-Hey you.
Over here.
What's your name?
-Hm?
[growl]
Again?
It's always about Sasuke!
-It's common courtesy to give
your own name before asking
someone else's.
-Hey, you're a
rookie, aren't you?
How old are you, anyway?
-I'm not obliged to answer.
-What's that?
-[giggle]
Cute!
-A weirdo?
-[groan]
No one wants to know my name.
-Hey, Naruto, Sasuke!
Come on.
Let's go.
-Heh.
So that's the bunch of
misfits that Kakashi and Guy
have been going on about.
I guess they passed
their first test--
getting their
applications through.
-Right.
-It looks like the exams are
going to be fun this year.
-[sniff]
Yeah, for us.
But maybe not for them.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): So this is
the big, bad Chunin exam, huh?
Heh.
It's a freak show.
[theme music]
THEME SONG: Cultivate your
hunger before you idealize.
Motivate your anger to
make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain,
never coming down.
Break into the contents,
never falling down.
My knee is still shaking
like I was twelve.
Sneaking out of the
classroom by the backdoor.
A man railed at
me twice, though.
But I didn't care.
Waiting is wasting
for people like me.
Don't try to live so wise.
Don't cry because
you're so right.
Don't dry with fakes or fears.
Because you will hate
yourself in the end.
Don't try to live so wise.
Don't cry because
you're so right.
Don't dry with fakes or fears.
Because you will hate
yourself in the end.
Don't try to live so wise.
Don't cry because
you're so right.
Don't dry--
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Bowl cut,
bushy brows, and bug eyes!
This guy is freaky!
No wonder Sakura told
him to take a hike.
The weird thing
is, they say he's
one of the best
fighters at the exams.
Well, I say prove it!
Bring it on!
Just you and me!
Hey!
You and me!
Not you and Sasuke!
What's wrong, weirdo?
You chicken?
Next time, Chunin Challenge--
Rock Lee versus Sasuke.
I don't care how good
he's supposed to be.
I still say he's a freak!