[music playing]
[theme music]
[laughing]
-So you're special, huh?
You won't be so special
when I'm finished with you.
[laughing]
-There's no way
I'm going to lose.
-Sasuke, you're a monster.
-Remember if you
unleash it for too long,
the curse will start to
eat away at your body,
and once it spreads
through your body,
your former self will be
gone never again to return.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): My body.
I guess I can't
waste any more time.
My left arm.
I can't feel it anymore.
SASUKE: That power of yours, by
using it, you're taking a risk,
aren't you?
Look around.
You know where we are?
It's called the Final
Valley, the perfect setting
for this fight.
Isn't it, Naruto?
Well?
Oh right, of course.
I said there'd be no
more talking, didn't I?
In that case, I guess
we're at the end,
the end of this fight and
all the fights up to now.
-Squad seven.
Naruto Uzumake.
-Huh.
-Sakura Hunano.
-Uh.
-Yeah!
-I'm doomed.
-And Sasuke Uchiha.
-Ahh!
-I'm doomed.
-Just make sure you don't
get in my way, loser.
-You!
-You said that there
were three of us.
That's what you said and
that's why Sakura and--
-We're all on this squad,
and we're all in it together.
-Yeah, that's right.
We gave our lunch to him,
because the three of us
are one.
-Hey.
-Yeah?
-You're not hurt,
are ya, little girl?
-Hey, kid.
You're not hurt, are ya?
-You're one of the ones
I want to fight the most.
-Huh?
Hey, Sasuke.
Don't lose.
Because I want to
fight you myself.
-I don't ever want to
have to see that again, my
trusted comrades falling
right in front of me.
NARUTO: Summoning jutsu.
Sakura, I swear
I'll protect you.
-What's so funny?
-I'm not laughing,
because it's funny.
I'm just psyched,
because I know that today
is the day when I
finally beat you.
-What did you say?
Don't talk nonsense,
you inept loser.
-I won't be such a loser
after I win today, will I?
-Let's just do this.
-Put on your
headband, and we will.
I'll wait.
-Not to worry.
I don't need that thing.
-Just do it.
Come on.
-There's no reason to put
it on, because you won't
be able to make a
scratch on my forehead.
-That's not the point.
Come on.
You know putting
your headband on
is a testament to fighting on
equal terms as a Leaf shinobi.
-Naruto!
-Sasuke!
I'll win no matter what.
-I'm not finished with you yet.
-Stop it!
SASUKE: This is
the end of it all.
Chidori!
-Rasengan!
-Chidori!
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
That chakra.
This isn't good.
[thunder]
-Naruto.
I'm--
[groaning]
-It's raining.
Will it wash away the scent?
-No problem.
We're already close enough.
This way.
-Am I too late?
-Naruto.
How did it come to this?
It's Sasuke's.
-I'm too late.
Forgive me.
Naruto, knowing you, you must
have put up quite a fight.
Sasuke.
-Now then, that's my boy.
-When we're alone
and no one's around,
the only one he
talks about is you.
-Because you and I
are flesh and blood.
I'm always going to
be there for you,
even if it's only as an
obstacle for you overcome,
even if you do hate me.
Like me, you may
be one of the few
who can use Mangekyo Sharingan.
But there is a catch.
Take the life of
your best friend.
-The Final Valley, huh?
To think that Sasuke and Naruto
would battle it out here.
It's pretty ironic,
don't you think?
-Yeah.
Look at that river.
The water just rages on
for eternity like this epic
never-ending battle, as
eternal as the two founders
of the Hidden Leaf
Village, forever
standing as these statues.
Naruto and Sasuke,
as long as they live,
the cycle will continue.
-Take the life of
your best friend.
You must kill him.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): No, brother.
Just because you say it, doesn't
mean I'm going to listen.
I will get my hands
on that power, but not
the way you want me to.
I'm going to surpass you,
but I'll do it my way.
I will.
-The storm, it finally broke.
PAKKUN: Hm.
All that rain.
I won't be able to follow his
scent, but keeping Naruto alive
is more important
than finding Sasuke.
-Yeah.
[laughing]
-Things have taken an
interesting turn, haven't they?
-Indeed.
[theme music]
-I'm-- I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry, Sakura.
I made a once in
a lifetime promise
that I'd bring
Sasuke back to you.
But don't count me out yet.
I will live up to my
pledge, no matter what.
I told you I would do something.
And I never go back on
my word, because that's
my nindo, my ninja way.
Next time, "The Promise
That Could Not Be Kept."
[theme music]