[theme music]
-Why did you hit Naruto, too?
[roar]
-It was an accident.
I had to strike when
I had the chance.
Sadly, your friend
got in the way.
A tragic loss.
I've never seen anyone defeat
the Ninja Art Kujaku before.
He will be missed.
You have our thanks,
Leaf Village shinobi.
Your mission here is over now.
-But we haven't
covered the star.
-We'll handle that ourselves.
Farewell, my friend.
-Rest easy now.
I'm a friend.
-Now that I think of it, after
I got blown off that cliff,
what happened?
Somebody-- Somebody
must have saved my life.
Was it you?
-Yes.
-Hm.
It's all kind of a
big blank, actually.
But I'm still
alive, so thank you.
My name's Naruto.
I'm a ninja from the
Hidden Leaf village
who's here to-- uh,
well, I'm actually
supposed to be
protecting the star
from thieves like
you, no offense.
[laughing]
-Hm?
-My name is Natsuhi.
-Nasuhi?
Wait a minute.
Haven't I heard that
name somewhere before?
Ah!
Take a look at that red one.
Pretty, isn't it?
-Natsuhiboshi.
Never alone, the star
on high watches over me.
-Yeah, Natsuhiboshi.
That's what Sumaru called it.
He said it was the
name of the star that
watched over him
and protects him!
-Really?
Sumaru told you that?
-Yeah.
Hey lady, do know
him, something?
-He is my son.
-Huh?
Get outta here!
You're telling me
you're Sumaru's mother?
AKAHOSHI: What?
Sumaru is gone?
-Forgive me, my lord.
I was certain the
sedatives would
keep him unconscious for hours.
I don't know what happened.
-The Leaf ninja.
I have no doubt they
had a hand in this.
-So what now?
They'll find out
what we're doing,
and then, how long
do you think it'll
be before the whole
village knows?
-We'll just have to find
them and get Sumaru back
before it's too late.
-Stop panicking, you two.
Once we have the
star back, we'll
have no trouble silencing
them permanently.
-I guess you're right.
We'll tell the people of
the Hidden Leaf Village
they died while fulfilling
their mission for us.
-And if we can convince
Sumaru as well--
-I've burned Natsuhi's
chakra in my memory.
Following the remnant
trail of her chakra
will lead us
straight to the star.
-What?
Naruto went off the cliff?
-Yes.
Along with the kunoichi
who stole the star.
The only good news is I
didn't see them anywhere
in the Valley of Death.
-So you think they might
have escaped the poison
gas in the valley somehow?
-There is a chance.
-Well if that's
the case, it could
be they got out of the valley
safely, and into the forest.
What are we waiting for?
We've got to find them!
-Uh--
-Hey, what's wrong?
Come on!
Naruto was helping
us and our village.
Have you forgotten?
-No, but we should wait for
orders from Lord Akahoshi.
Right?
-Yeah.
-We don't have time to
be waiting for orders.
I'm going out there now.
-I want to go with you.
If it's to help find
Naruto, I have to go.
-Mizura, you can't.
-There has to be some
way I can be of use.
SUMARU: No.
I'll go.
-Sumaru!
-Then you're OK?
-We found him in your
Hoshikage's residence,
in a hospital bed,
heavily sedated.
-Huh?
The Hoshikage's residence?
But why?
-The shinobi who knocked all of
you out and took Sumaru away,
he wasn't a stranger
from some other village.
-No, indeed.
It was not.
In fact, it was your
leader Akahoshi.
Meaning that the
shinobi who attacked you
and the one who stole the
star are two different people.
-Brilliant, Lee, except
that Neji already said that.
-Why would Lord Akahoshi--
-But why would he do that to us?
What does it all mean, Sumaru?
-I only wish I knew, Hokuto.
But I'm beginning to suspect
that Lord Akahoshi may
be hiding something from us.
-When will you all
finally realize
that this man,
Akahoshi, is using you?
Mizura won't be the only one.
If you keep on with this
training, you'll all be sick.
Or worse.
-No way.
-No, it's a lie, no.
-You're wrong.
Lord Akahoshi would never
do something like that.
-Maybe the other shinobi,
the one who stole the star,
can explain what's going on.
-Then our next step is to find
that shinobi no matter what.
-The forest in the
Land of Bears is deep.
You're never going
to find your way
through those woods on your own.
-Very well.
Then show us the way.
-Mizura.
-No, it's all right.
I'll do it.
-But--
-You have to rest and
get your strength back.
Don't worry.
The time will come soon
enough when we need your help.
-Hm.
-Well then, any luck?
-Were you able to get
a fix on the remnants
of Natsuhi's chakra?
-Mm!
Delicious!
There's nothing like
a mom's home cooking,
even when it's in a cave.
-There's a little
more, if you want any.
-Heh, heh.
Sure!
OK then, there's still
something I don't understand.
Why did you swipe the star?
-As a matter of fact, this isn't
the first time I've taken it.
The first was 10 years ago.
-What?
-Even then, it was clear
star training was dangerous.
Our young shinobi
we were falling ill.
Or worse.
My husband Hotarubi and I
were among the lucky ones
who had survived the training.
We decided we would
steal the star
and take it far away, so that
it could no longer claim anymore
of our brothers and
sisters as victims.
An elite unit of tracking
shinobi was quickly dispatched,
and it wasn't long before
they caught up with us.
-Stop.
-It's the Third.
Lord Hoshikage.
-Natsuhi and
Hotarubi, your actions
have been rash, although
not without reason.
I have shared the same
doubts and concerns.
But, as village leader, I've had
to weigh my decision carefully.
Now, that is over.
I will terminate
the star training,
but there will be
some who disagree
and they may try to reinstate
it at some point in the future.
And so I must ask you
both to leave the village
and disappear, perhaps forever.
But keep watch.
And if you ever see that the
star training has been resumed,
you must return and
put a stop to it.
-Lord Hoshikage.
-For Sumaru.
-When our son asks
of us, please,
my lord-- Please
tell him we died.
-Yes.
I understand.
NATSUHI: No one could ever know
the truth about our leaving.
Shortly thereafter,
the Hoshikage
discontinued the star training.
He saw, as we did, the dangers,
that the potential benefits
to our village weren't
worth the damage being
done to our people.
-Neji said the same thing.
Does this training really
do that much damage?
-Yes.
It wasn't long after
we left the village
that my husband, Hotarubi,
died from its effects.
The same thing could very
well happen to me at any time.
There's no way of knowing.
-That's awful.
We've gotta get
back to the village
and tell Akahoshi that this
crazy training has got to stop!
-Akahoshi's dream of
making the village strong
is more important to him than
the safety of its people.
To show you how little
he cares about them,
he took Sumaru hostage in
order to trade his life to me
for the star.
-Huh?
You mean that shinobi with
the mask and the poison gas
was-- Don't even think about it!
-Farewell.
-What is he doing?
Huh?
So that guy was Akahoshi, huh?
What? What is it?
Is-- is there anything wrong?
-Akahoshi.
He's here with his henchmen.
-So this is it?
-Are you able to sense
where she's hidden the star?
NATSUHI (VOICEOVER):
Hotarubi, protect the star.
Protect Sumaru.
-The star is right there.
But the entrance a
sealed by that boulder.
-Uh-- so what are we supposed
to do to get rid of that?
-We could try using paper
bombs and blow it up little
by little.
NARUTO: Don't you
even think about it!
-What the--
-I thought we lost this
brat in the Valley of Death.
-Ha!
Takes more than that
to get rid of me.
Or should I say us?
-Ha.
Get back, you two.
Leave him to me.
Now then, I'll just have
to finish what I began.
Ninja Art, Kujaku.
Beast!
-Here we go!
-Huh?
-I gotcha!
Huh?
-I was ready for
that little trick.
It's the last time you'll
get a chance to try it.
What the heck?
So, Natsuhi.
You're still alive
as well, I see.
-Akahoshi, I ask you one
more time to reconsider.
Stop the star training
once and for all
and let the young
people go, and I
will leave you and the
village in peace forever.
-Ha.
Thank you, but no.
You're just as blind as that
stubborn old man, the Third
Hoshikage.
He wouldn't listen
to reason either.
He refused to understand
that the star training was
essential to keep our village
strong and prosperous.
-No.
Never.
It's too dangerous.
As long as I'm
Hoshikage, that training
will never be used again.
This matter is finished.
Leave me now.
This is madness, Akahoshi.
You've lost your mind.
-It's you who have lost
your mind, you old fool.
Now go and sleep
with your ancestors.
Your journey is at an end.
Leave it to the next generation
to give this village the power
to rival the Five
Great Hidden Villages
[maniacal laughter]
-Are you sure this
was necessary?
-It-- It had to be done for
the sake of the village, right?
-Had to be done, yes.
Now we'll resume
the star training,
and it will lead us to glory.
[laughter]
-You monster.
You've got this whole
village believing in you,
and you don't care
if they live or die!
Mizura's in the
hospital because of you.
He may not survive!
-Greatness cannot be achieved
without some sacrifice.
It's for the village.
A true shinobi understands that.
-For the village?
No, it isn't.
It's for you!
For you and some
crazy dream of glory
you've got inside your head!
-It's not your fight.
Stay out of it.
This is our village's affair.
-But I--
-Just stay back!
-Yataka.
Shizo.
-Huh?
Man, his chakra just
swallowed up both of theirs!
-Ha ha ha!
My chakra beast has
had a good meal.
Things will go
differently this time.
-Not if I can help it.
-Be careful, Natsuhi.
[theme music]
NARUTO: Neji, is Sumaru's
mom going to be OK?
NEJI: She's stable
at the moment,
but her prognosis is doubtful.
LEE: What?
NEJI: Even before
the battle, she
was starting to weaken from the
effects of the star training.
TENTEN: Her chakra
network's badly damaged.
NARUTO: But-- but grandma
Tsunade could heal her, right?
NEJI: I'm not sure.
In any case, if she tries
that Kujaku jutsu again,
I doubt she'll survive.
NARUTO: Next time, Reunion,
The Remaining Time.
[theme music]