[music playing]
[MUSIC - SAMBOMASTER, "SEISHUN
KYOSOKYOKU"]
[thunder rumbling]
-A storm is coming,
and no sign of Idate.
-Huh?
-This is bad.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Run, Idate, run!
Nagi Island awaits!
[chuckling]
IDATE: You're Aoi Rokusho.
-I was expecting
you to run away.
After all, it wouldn't be
the first time, would it?
-Don't start that!
That was all because of you.
-Now, now.
You're like me.
You've never trusted
anybody in your life.
And you've never thought
of anybody but yourself.
You abandoned your village,
betrayed your brother.
It's all about you.
You don't care what
happens to anyone else.
A person like that really
doesn't deserve to live.
[gasping]
-Die!
-Hey, Sakura.
How's your wound?
You OK?
-I'm fine.
That's the least of our worries.
Just keep going.
-Those Rain Village
ninja, you mean.
-Ha!
Are you kidding?
Those wimps?
We can handle them.
SAKURA: It wasn't us
I was thinking of.
What if they're headed towards
Idate at this very moment?
-Whoa!
He might be in danger.
-Of course he's in danger.
That's just what I'm saying.
-Ack!
Gah!
-Knock it off, Naruto.
This is no time to
be playing around.
-He's not.
Our friends have
come back again.
-Naruto.
[chuckling]
-You don't have a chance
against us underwater.
-(THINKING) I've had
it with this guy.
-Good.
The fishies have
swallowed the bait.
Water Clone Jutsu.
-Gah.
Sakura!
[choking]
-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
[rain ninja laughing]
RAIN NINJA: What good
will those do you?
They might work on dry land,
but down here Water Clones rule.
In any case, those
clones don't fool me.
I've got a hold of the original,
and I'll keep holding on to him
'til he runs out of breath.
[grunting]
[gasping]
-What the devil are they up to?
-No!
-Incredible.
His chakra is infused
in the whirlpool.
-Not bad, Naruto.
-Finally, a chance to
use all the training I
went through to
learn the Rasengan.
[gasping]
-Sakura!
Come on, Sakura.
Hang in there.
[gasping]
NARUTO: I've got you, Sakura.
Hang in there.
You're gonna be OK.
[shouting]
-Whoa, that hurt.
Hey, Sakura.
Come on.
Come on, wake up.
(THINKING) Mouth to mouth.
[gulp]
-(THINKING) It's the only way.
[moaning]
-(THINKING) Sasuke, you
know CPR, don't you?
What are you waiting for?
Go on, do it.
[heart beating faster]
[muttering uncertainly]
[sakura shrieking]
-What are you, crazy?
You perv!
[naruto moaning]
-Huh?
What is it?
-We're wasting time
we haven't got.
We need to find Idate.
-You're right.
-(MOANING) Right.
OK.
Coming, coming.
[groaning]
-Huh.
Time's running out.
Fukusuke will be at Modoroki
Shrine right about now.
[panting]
-Any chance you had is over now.
[grunting]
-Hmm.
Your running days are through.
You can't even stand up.
[moaning]
-Once the poison finishes
spreading through your body,
you'll be crossing a
different sort of finish line.
-Oof! (MOANING) You can't--
-The last finish line.
Death.
[groaning]
-What do you really think you
can do with that little pocket
knife?
-No!
Don't touch it.
[groaning]
-Gah!
Ah!
[groaning]
-You fool.
Were you hoping
to show the world
you were a man of integrity?
You could have just run away.
You picked the wrong
time to try and change
your spots, my friend.
-Gah!
Uh!
Ow!
I'm sorry.
Forgive me, Boss Jirocho.
You had faith in me.
And now I've let you down.
NARUTO: Idate!
[gasping]
-You rat.
[panting]
-Curse this rain.
-Are you in charge of
those Rain Village ninja?
-Apparently they weren't
quite up to the job.
In a contest of
genin, it appears
the Leaf Village genin
are the stronger.
-This is bad.
-But genin, no matter
how strong they are,
are no match against me.
-Well, let's find out.
-Up there!
-Ha.
[shouting]
-Hmm.
About what I expected.
No more of a challenge
than Idate, really.
I'll just give you
what I gave him.
No use in wasting
any of my chakra.
-Sakura!
-Idate!
[moaning]
-Needles.
Ack!
-Needles that deliver
a deadly poison.
No matter how strong
you may be, you already
have one foot in the grave.
-Yeah, yeah, we've
heard that before.
[groaning]
[distant booing]
-Fukusuke must have reached
the Modoroki Shrine.
The last sound you'll ever hear,
the sound of all your plans
going up in smoke.
Poof.
[crowd booing]
-No.
The Wagarashi family's
gonna win again?
-No, what have we
done to deserve this?
MAN: I miss the days when
Jirocho was running things.
MAN: Yeah.
Those days are over for
good from the look of it.
-Ugh.
I'm soaked right
down to the bone.
-Bravo, Fukusuke.
Well done.
-Don't let up.
Just keep moving, and bring
it home for Boss Wagarashi.
-Keep your hands off me.
Who asked your
advice anyway, scum?
-What did you--
-Why kill myself when
the race is in the bag?
I deserve a rest.
-A rest?
What the heck are
you talking about?
-Quiet.
-Yeah, but--
-Remember, if anything
goes wrong with this race,
we are the ones who will
have to face the boss.
MAN: Yeah.
-It's safer just
to watch and wait.
-He is gonna pay.
-Naruto.
Sasuke.
Take this.
-What do you mean, take it?
What is it?
-Lady Tsunade gave them to me.
She stopped me as we
were leaving the village.
-Here, take these with you.
They might just come in handy.
NARUTO: Grandma Tsunade, huh?
SAKURA: There.
I think he'll come around now.
It's some kind of
antidote or something.
Take one.
-Huh?
OK.
-And the other thing is, we
can't just leave him out here
in the rain.
We've got to get him
to someplace warm.
-Hey, big brother!
Look at this.
You see, I've finally
become a ninja too.
-I see.
-Of course, I know it's about
more than just a headband.
To be a real ninja,
I'll have to train
hard and complete
lots of missions.
But just you wait, I'll
make chunin super fast.
And then I'll be a jonin
just like you, Ibiki.
You'll see.
I'll do it in record time.
You know how fast I am.
Right, brother?
-Listen, Idate.
There is something
more important
to a ninja than power
or even success.
-Something more important?
-And your ignorant
boasting shows me
that you haven't
learned what it is yet.
-What do you know,
he's waking up.
-Hey.
So how are you feeling?
-Where is he?
What happened to Aoi?
-He's gone.
So you're telling me that's
that character's name?
Aoi?
-Who is he?
Do you know each
other from somewhere?
-He was a sensei I knew back
in my Leaf Village days.
-What?
You're from the Leaf Village?
-After he betrayed
the Leaf Village,
he became a jonin of the
Village Hidden in the Rain.
-Hang on.
Back up.
What are you talking about?
[groaning]
-Whoa there.
Take it easy now
You're still very weak.
What is that you're holding?
You've been clutching
that all this time.
-Damn.
All that work, all the
training, all for nothing.
-You're giving up kind
of easy, aren't you?
That's not the way for any
Leaf Village ninja to talk.
-You've got the wrong guy.
I haven't even thought
of the Leaf Village
since the day I
walked away from it.
-Walked away from the village?
-It hit me hard when I
failed the first chunin exam.
I didn't know what to do.
-You almost made it, Idate.
Don't take it so hard.
There are other ways
of becoming a chunin
besides taking the chunin exams.
-Are you serious?
-You bet.
And I know a way.
But you'll have to do
just what I tell you.
-You got it!
[crickets chirping]
-Aoi sensei?
-Here, Idate.
-Oh, there you are, sensei.
I brought them, just
like you told me to.
-Hmm.
So you did.
The Scroll of Sealing and the
legendary Blade of the Thunder
Spirit used by the
Second Hokage himself.
Well done, Idate.
-I did what you said.
So I can be a chunin now, right?
-Sure you can.
At the Village
Hidden in the Rain.
[gasping]
-We'll leave the
Leaf Village together
and bring these as
gifts to our new home.
-Uh, but--
-You can't stay here.
What do you suppose they'll
do once they find out
you stole their treasures?
-So it was all just a trick?
-If you ever want to
succeed in this world,
you shouldn't put so
much faith in others.
A little something to remember.
[angry gasp]
AOI: Well, coming, Idate?
Whatever you do, you're
a rogue ninja now.
Stay here, and they'll lock you
up forever-- if you're lucky.
[gasping]
AOI: (WORDS ECHOING) Stay
here, and they'll lock you up
forever-- if you're lucky.
[groaning]
-I never saw the Leaf
Village again after that day.
Nothing I do goes right.
I've never been of
any use to anyone.
But even so, Boss Jirocho-- even
though he knew I was no good,
he still trusted me.
He put his faith in me.
And now look what I've done.
-(THINKING) He's like
me, the way I was before.
-That's why you will never
be accepted in this village.
Die, Naruto!
[gasping]
-Naruto, get down!
[thump]
-I've never been of
any use to anyone.
[whimpering]
-Wh--why?
-Because we're the same.
-(THINKING) That's just
the way I used to feel.
IDATE: Look at me.
I'm worthless.
Everything I do goes wrong.
Aoi said it, and he was right.
I'd be better off dead.
NARUTO: Stop it!
You idiot, you just
said it yourself.
You've still got one person
who believes in you, right?
-I know that's how
you feel, Naruto.
You feel lonely,
and it hurts inside.
And I could have been
there for you more.
-One person is enough.
That's all anyone needs.
Don't even think of quitting.
Who says this race is over?
You have no way of knowing
how things are gonna turn out.
-Yeah, but--
-Come on, on your feet.
-Stop it, Naruto.
He's still far too weak to move.
-If he can't run,
then I'll carry him
on my back the whole
way if I have to.
-The other runner
already reached Modoroki.
-You're not quitting!
Understand?
-No.
Stop it, Naruto.
-Sakura.
-What are you doing?
-Stay back.
Leave them.
-Jirocho's counting
on you, and you
don't want to keep him waiting.
Pull yourself together!
-It's starting to look like he
just ran off, isn't it, boss?
-He'll come.
I trust Idate.
[grunting]
-You quit now, when
you finally have
the chance you've been
waiting for your whole life?
To show someone he
was right to depend
on you, to believe in you?
-There isn't a
faster boat around.
-Thanks a lot, Gramps.
-It's not a problem.
-The blade wasn't invented for
the purpose of hurting people.
NARUTO: Come on!
Show them what you've got!
-I'll do it.
But I'll need your help, Naruto.
-All right, then.
Let's shake a leg.
Hang on tight.
Here we go!
[panting]
[MUSIC - CAPTAIN STRAYDUM,
"MOUNTAIN A GO GO TWO"]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Blah, blah, blah.
What is it about
creeps like this?
It's not enough they
try to kill you,
but they gotta talk your ear
off while they're doing it.
It's so annoying.
Anyway, it doesn't
change a thing.
Your Boss Jirocho is waiting
for you at the finish line.
And you don't want to
let him down, right?
Who cares if this Aoi guy is
a jonin or the devil himself?
We're not gonna let
him stop us, are we?
Next time, a fierce
battle of rolling thunder.
[MUSIC - CAPTAIN STRAYDUM,
"MOUNTAIN A GO GO TWO"]