[theme song]
NARUTO: Unh.
Hey.
Perv, you awake?
One way to find out.
Hidden Finger jutsu.
1,000 years of death!
Man, he's totally out of it.
Some trainer.
He's pathetic.
OK, Frogman.
What was that all about?
Who do you think
you are, anyway?
-I'm glad you asked.
I'm the Hermit of Mount Myoboku.
The wise and immortal spirit.
That's right!
It is I, the Toad Mountain Sage!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Long Time No See.
Jiraiya Returns!
-What?
Toad Sage?
-Exactly.
-Well, listen, you
pervy sage, what are you
going to do about this?
This guy is supposed
to be training me,
and you laid him out
flatter than a bath mat!
-Well, he shouldn't have
interfered with my research.
-Your research?
-You see, I'm a novelist.
I am a writer of great
books, like this.
-Huh?
-Hm.
Hm-hm-hm-hm.
-What?
You wrote that?
-Yes!
I see you know it.
[chuckles] (THINKING) I'm famous
and it's not out in paperback
yet.
-You call that
pervy trash a novel?
Research.
Yeah, right.
Just It excuse for you to peek
at girls in the bathhouse.
[screams]
-Ah!
Look at what you've done.
You ruined my peeking.
I mean my research.
-Dirty old man.
-You little-- there's
nothing dirty about it.
I happen to be a
serious artist who's
inspired by youth and beauty.
That's all.
And--
-Yeah.
Whatever.
Like anyone believes that.
Who cares anyway?
What about my training?
-Hm?
Your training?
You mean the Walking
On Water technique
you were having so
much trouble with?
-You can do it?
OK, then it's up to
you to teach it to me.
You at least owe me that,
-Huh!
Stop bothering me, kid.
I'm busy.
-Um!
Hey, wait!
Come back here, you pervy sage.
Where's your sense
of responsibility?
You've got to train me.
-Not on your life!
I can't work with
someone who has
no respect for a true artist.
-Nunh.
TOAD SAGE: Besides,
I don't like kids.
-Uh, actually, I thought your
book, "Make-out Paradise", was,
uh, really well-written, and
interesting, and informative.
TOAD SAGE: Liar.
The purchase and
reading of that book
is prohibited for anyone
under the age of 18.
NARUTO: Oh, yeah.
But the reviews I
read were great!
-Do you really think
that's going to work on me?
What do you take
a for, an idiot?
I'm a goddamn sage!
Save your breath, kid.
You can't butter me up.
-OK!
You're right.
Sorry.
But wait.
You can't-- ah awh.
TOAD SAGE: [laughs] So
long, and good luck!
-That was cool!
I don't care if he
is a dirty old man.
That guy's the real deal!
NARUTO: Hey!
Pervy sage, where are you?
Where'd he disappear to?
[panicked scream]
TOAD SAGE: No!
No!
Wait!
[loud slap]
A-huh.
Ooh.
[crash]
YOUNG WOMAN: What do
you think you're doing,
you disgusting old man?
-I'm sorry, but you have
such a beautiful pair
of soft and lovely, uh, hands!
You really do have
beautiful hands.
How do you keep them so soft?
YOUNG WOMAN: Filthy beast!
[loud slap]
TOAD SAGE: Ow!
So much for soft hands.
Sheesh.
-What was I thinking?
This guy's really pathetic.
He's even pervier
than my last trainer.
But it's not like
I have much choice.
TOAD SAGE: Hmm.
Looks like the
women in this town
are no friendlier than before.
Still, I like them feisty!
[chuckles pervily]
NARUTO: So you've
been here before, huh?
-Huh?
You again?
-I'm surprised they don't
make you wear a leash.
You old pervert!
-Shh!
Shh!
You know, I really
wish you wouldn't
use the word "pervert."
-Oh, yeah! (LOUDLY)
Well, tell me
how you like the word "joke."
Because that's you are, mister.
A joke!
First I get stuck with a
closet perv, and now, oh,
why can't I get a
trainer that-- ah!
-Oh, put a lid on it, will you?
There you go, kid.
You can train in
there for a while.
[laughs]
NARUTO (MUFFLED ): Hey!
Hey!
Let me out of
here, you old toad!
-Ah, what I'd give
for just a few minutes
with a young, pretty girl.
[imagines female laughter]
[laughs pervily]
Ah.
Ah!
What?
What i-- what?
Ow!
NARUTO: Unh!
You can't get rid
of me that easy!
Well, what do you know?
A substitution jutsu.
Not bad, old man.
-That was close.
Ah!
[chuckles] Little squirt!
He'll have to be a
lot smarter than that
to outfox the Toad
Mountain Sage.
-Oh, yeah?
How am I doing now?
-Ah.
OK.
I'll admit you're not
totally without talent.
-So does that mean you'll
help me with my training?
-Not so fast, squirt.
It's a question of quid pro quo.
I'll give you what you
want, but in return, you
have to try and
get me what I want.
-So what do you want?
--[chuckles pervily]
You must know by now.
I like them ripe and luscious,
with curves like that, see?
And big, but not too
big, know what I mean?
If you bring me
something like that,
I will train you 'til
the cows come home!
-You will?
No lie?
-The Toad Mountain
Sage never lies!
-You got it!
Wait here.
-Hm?
(YELLING) Ah ha!
Uh um.
Too bad, kid.
It's not like we had
a contract, really.
Oh, ladies!
Can you show me the
way to town, uh?
Then I said, not with
my rice bowl, you don't.
[laughs]
[girls laugh]
[toad sage catches breath]
-That's a pretty funny story.
-(CHUCKLING) It's funny, yes.
But it's not just a story.
Every word of it is true.
-Really?
What happened next?
NARUTO: Hey, pervy
sage I'm back!
-What? [giggles]
-Did he call you pervy?
-(IRRITATED)
Worthless little runt!
I told you not to call me that.
-Look, I got you one,
just the way you like 'em!
A ripe and luscious
one with curves!
-[stutters with anger] (IRATE)
That's not what I meant,
you moron!
-(LAUGHING) Ah, yeah!
Talk about ripe and juicy!
-Dig in.
We might as well not
let it all go to waste.
-Mm-hm.
That's so true! [laughs]
TOAD SAGE: The ladies!
What happened to the ladies?
Oh!
-[burps loudly] Ah.
Man.
That was the best.
-(SADLY) Struck out again.
-(THINKING) No doubt about it.
It has to be!
-Ah, now I must be off.
I've wasted too
much time already.
-Uh, hey!
What are you talking about?
Where are you going?
What about my training?
We had a deal!
-I don't give a flying
fish for your training.
I have my research to conduct!
-Hmp!
Research, my butt!
It's not like I don't
have better things
to do than hang around with
a pervy old coot like you.
I've got to train until
I'm stronger than anyone,
because I've got to
pass the Chunin exams.
And then, someday,
I'm going be Hokage!
-Huh!
That's a good one.
Tell me, did you fall on your
head when you were a baby?
Is that what makes you this way?
Now I know you're
wasting my time.
That's not enough.
I need to get on
with my research.
And for that, I
need a lovely lady.
No fruits, no
vegetables, but a lady!
-A lady?
Oh, if that's what you wanted,
why didn't you just say so?
No problem.
[knuckles cracking]
Ha!
Ah.
[giggling]
-Nuh!
-Unh!
Ah!
-Uh-uh-uh ah-ah-ah!
[whimpers incoherently] Hubba
hubba hubba hubba hubba.
-If you keep staring like
that, I'm going to blush.
-[mumbling incoherently]
-[giggles]
-You're so, so lovely.
We got a winner!
A perfect ten!
-(THINKING) Duh.
Pathetic!
-She's just my type.
I really, really like her.
How did you do it?
Where on earth
did she come from?
-Oh.
No biggie.
I call it my Sexy jutsu.
-Yeah!
I love it.
You're a genius, kid.
This is one amazing technique!
-(THINKING) Yeah.
She seem to have effect
on a lot of older guys.
-Yeah.
So, uhm--
-So?
You'll help me with my
training now, right?
TOAD SAGE: You bet!
But only on one condition.
-Huh?
One condition?
Uh, what is it?
-Ah, [pervy laughter] uh, uh,
[laughter] I'll do it if you
promise to stay like
that the whole time.
-Ooh!
(YELLING) I was right!
You are pathetic.
You're nothing but a
lousy little pervert!
-(ANGRILY) I am not
a little pervert!
-Oh, yeah?
Then tell me, what are you?
-Na-ha-ha-ha!
I'm a big one.
-Oh.
Great.
That makes all the difference.
-OK.
We'll just pretend
none of that happened.
Now let's begin your training.
-And you really
mean it this time?
-A sage always
means what he says.
Now, go ahead and
show me that technique
you were working on before.
-OK.
Uh.
Here goes.
Hmph!
Ah uh, dih huh, nuh hut.
Mm, eh.
Huh nuh eh unh ya gah!
-Hm.
[laughs]
-Uh.
Not again.
-(LAUGHING) You really
do need help, don't you?
-Eh!
I should know by now to
take my clothes off first.
-Hey!
Go on and build your
chakra one more time.
-Can't I dry off a little first?
-Now!
Do it.
Hmph!
-Hmm.
Wha--?
Amazing!
-Huh?
-You know, you have quite
a tight sexy little body.
-Eh!
What the-- do you mind, old man?
I'm trying to concentrate here!
-Oh.
Sorry about that.
Please, go right ahead.
-Unh, jerk!
-Hm?
(THINKING) So this
is the formula
used to imprison
the nine-tailed fox.
A double tetragram seal
with an eight-signed seal.
Huh.
That way, if any of
the demon's chakra
escapes the tetragram seal,
it will be safely channeled
into, and suppressed by,
the boy's own chakra.
The Fourth Hokage.
He did this for
boy's protection.
But since then, a five-pronged
seal has been added.
An odd-numbered seal on
top of an even-numbered?
Hmm.
That explains it.
That's why the boy's
chakra and the demons
are merging in an unstable way.
It's no wonder he can't
control his chakra very well.
-[laughing] Cut it out.
What are you doing?
That tickles! [giggles]
-Oh!
Sorry about that.
(THINKING) This is the
work of someone else.
The formula is crude.
If I to guess, I'd
say it was Orochimaru.
OK.
Raise your arms up
high over your head.
-Huh?
-It's a trust exercise.
Come on!
Raise them high!
-(THINKING) Well, this is
a weird way to get started.
-Five Pronged Seal, release!
-Ah!
Uh-hoo-ah.
[coughs] Uh.
What the heck was that for?
-What?
Just pushing a pressure
point to loosen you up.
Now, go on.
Try walking on the water again.
-Uh, unh, oh.
Ah!
Whoa!
That's weird.
[laughing]
Look at that!
I'm doing it.
Just don't ask me how.
Yahoo! [laughing]
Look at me.
No problem.
Piece of cake!
[laughs] This is fun.
-(THINKING) Hah.
I think It's about
time to teach him
how to control the fox's chakra.
-Look, I'm really doing it.
Woohoo!
-OK.
Out of the pool.
-Hm?
-Come on in.
I'm going to teach you
a killer technique.
-You are?
Really?
You mean like something really
powerful and destructive?
-Now, then, there's something
you need to understand, kid,
before we go any further.
I don't think you're
even aware of it,
but you possess two
chakras within you.
-Huh?
Two chakras?
TOAD SAGE: Haven't you
ever felt the presence
of a different chakra?
-Well, I'm not sure.
Hmm.
Oh, wait!
I do kind of remember
there was this one time.
It was like, all of a sudden,
I had this weird upsurge
of power, and I didn't
know where it came from.
I don't remember
when it was exactly.
I almost thought it was a dream.
-So I see.
NARUTO: But I do remember
feeling that this was something
different than my usual chakra.
My normal chakra, well, if
it was a color, it'd be blue,
but this was red!
-I see.
OK.
That's enough
training for today.
-What, already?
What about that
killer technique?
Come on.
I'm just getting started.
Let's go!
-In training as in cooking,
a watched pot never boils.
Now let's go back to town
and have a real bath,
not one where you
just fall in, OK?
-Ah.
This is better than falling in.
-Ah!
Nothing beats relaxing after
a long day of training.
-Hey, hey, pervy sage.
So tell me about this
killer technique.
-Tomorrow is soon enough.
-Ah, cheapskate.
[toad croaks]
-We'd better get
out soon, or we're
going to be stuck with
a giant boiled toad.
[both laugh]
TOAD SAGE: Sorry, Ebisu.
It wasn't my plan to steal
your student from you.
-Oh.
That's of little importance.
Lord Hokage has had his ninjas
searching for you everywhere.
We were just beginning to think
that you would never be found,
then you turn up here of all
places, right in front of me.
He will be pleased.
-Have you told the
Hokage you found me yet?
EBISU: No.
Not yet.
-Very good.
It's better that way.
-You're after
Orochimaru, aren't you?
-No, unfortunately, I
can't say that I am.
Sorry.
-Huh?
-The only thing
that brought me here
was the chance of doing
some research for a book.
I have no desire to get involved
in any of that other business.
-What do you mean?
You can't be serious!
You know better than
anyone there's only one way
to deal with Orochimaru.
He's one of the Sannin,
the legendary Three Ninja,
and he can only be stopped by
the power of another Sannin.
Your power, Master Jiraiya!
[closing theme song]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Reading weird old scrolls,
signing contracts in blood,
memorizing the Inu I Tori Saru
Hitsuji seal, or is that
the bird, monkey, dog-- ah.
It's complicated,
and it sure isn't
like any training I'm used to.
But if it helps me get
to be Hokage, who cares?
Whatever works,
that's what I say.
Next time, "The Summoning
Jutsu, Wisdom of the Toad Sage".
I'll learn how to croak
like a toad if it'll help.