[theme music]
KAKASHI: Water Style.
--[together] Water
Shark Bomb Jutsu!
-He broke out the
same jutsu that I did.
-Not that I'm
unhappy to see you,
but what are you doing here?
-Well, you know, I asked you to
take care of those two earlier.
But I guess I got
a little worried.
OK.
Talk.
What's a rogue ninja like
you doing in this village?
Kakashi Hatake.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Eye to eye,
Sharingan Versus Sharingan!
NARUTO: What?
Aw, no way!
How come I get stuck
tagging along with you
while you do research
for another one
of your pervy books?
-Look, kid, I can
assure you this
isn't just another
research trip.
There's a woman I have to find.
A very remarkable woman.
-Well count me out, old man.
I don't have time to help
you find a girlfriend.
I've gotta get busy
with my training.
-What training?
-It's time Kakashi-sensei
taught me something new,
like that Chidori thing.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Why does he always
play favorites with Sasuke?
-I see.
Hm.
You'd just be wasting your time.
Chidori's not really your style.
And besides that, kid, the
woman we're looking for
is really beautiful.
I mean gorgeous.
-Like I care.
Look, Pervy Sage, who do
you think you're talking to?
I'm not some dumb kid you
can fool with lame excuses.
I'm not going!
-OK, fine.
Suit yourself.
And I could have
taught you jutsu
that made Chidori
look like kid's stuff.
Maybe I'll just see is
Sasuke wants to come.
-Right!
When do we leave?
I'll go pack my bag!
Stay right there, Pervy Sage.
I'll be right back!
Don't move!
-[sigh] What a knucklehead.
Still, you can't
help liking him.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): Those
eyes haven't changed.
This one's a true
heir of the Sharingan.
That means I've gotta
be ready for the worst.
-Well, well, what a surprise.
That's how you copied my jutsu.
So there really is
someone besides Itachi
with those crazy eyes.
You're Kakashi, aren't you?
The copy ninja.
-You can imagine my surprise.
I go to check out a couple
of lowlife vagabonds
in a tea house, and
I find none other
than Itachi Uchiha
and Kisame Hoshigaki,
the scourge of the
Hidden Mist Village.
-How about that?
You know my name.
I'm honored.
-I assume that bizarre
excuse for a sword
is one of the Seven Ninja
Swordsmen of the Mist?
The one called Shark Skin?
[laughter]
-I heard that you and Zabuza
had it out a while back.
-Yes.
We did.
-Go ahead.
I'd love to cut you to ribbons.
-Kisame.
Stop it.
-Hm?
-If you take this man on,
it won't be without cost.
Furthermore, it will take
time, and the commotion
is liable to bring
more Shinobi running.
Your way is inefficient,
and unnecessarily risky.
Don't lose sight of our goal.
-Let's hear it.
What is your goal, exactly?
-We're looking for something,
and we know it's here.
-And what would that be?
What is this thing
you're looking for?
-My way is more
efficient than Kisame's.
-Ninja Art, Water Style.
Water Wall!
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): The speed
of his jutsu is incredible.
I didn't even see a hand sign.
The shuriken in
his hand were just
a ruse to distract me from
this water style attack.
-You're good.
You almost anticipated my moves.
Almost.
-A shadow Clone!
His speed is too great.
KISAME (VOICEOVER):
A water clone?
Heh.
I guess my village
should be honored
he's copied our jutsu so well.
-Nice job, Kakashi.
-Get back, Kurenai!
That one's the shadow clone.
-Kakashi!
Kurenai!
ASUMA (VOICEOVER): He just
blew up his own shadow clone.
[laughter]
-I'm gonna learn a new jutsu!
Now maybe I'll finally
get Sakura's attention.
And a kiss.
I can't wait to see
Kakashi-sensei and Sasuke
when I spring it on 'em!
-Are you all right?
-Stay on your toes.
This guy was made chief of ANBU
Black Ops when he was only 13.
-All right, he's tough.
We get it.
-Tough?
You haven't seen half
of what he can do.
-For someone who is
not of the Uchiha clan,
you have mastered
the Sharingan well.
However, not being one of us,
you lack our physical strength.
And that's something
you can't copy.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): He's right.
My body doesn't
have the stamina.
-Why is it that the Uchiha
clan is known by all,
and feared by all?
I'll show you what
the Sharingan can
do when it's wielded by a
true heir of the bloodline.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
It can't be.
Oh, no.
-Close your eyes!
Don't look at his eyes!
Close your eyes!
Listen, both of you.
Whatever happens, don't look.
If you meet his gaze,
you're finished.
I'm going to have
to do this alone.
My Sharingan against his.
-Indeed, your abilities
are impressive.
They might even be enough to
resist the Mangekyo Sharingan.
However, there is
something they can't
defend against-- this
special Sharingan
jutsu called Tsukuyomi.
Only someone with the
Sharingan and Kekkai Genkai
can defeat me.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): Sasuke.
-I wonder how much
of this someone
without the Kekkai
Genkai can take?
-So it was only genjutsu.
-In the Tsukuyomi, time and
space, even physical mass--
I control them all.
The next 72 hours will
be nothing but this,
over and over.
-[groans]
That's--
-Tsukuyomi.
Time and space.
Even physical mass.
I control them all.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): Keep calm.
It's only genjutsu.
-Telling yourself
it's an illusion
will do you little good.
-Huh?
Pain is pain.
Call it what you will.
[gasping]
-Do you feel it any less deeply
by thinking it's not real?
How long will it be, I wonder,
before your spirit is broken?
-[groan]
[heavy breathing]
-Only 71 hours, 59 minutes,
and 59 seconds to go.
-What?
No!
Only a single second has passed?
[yelping]
[heartbeat]
-Kakashi?
What is it?
Can we open our eyes now?
-No.
Not yet.
-What just happened?
One second the guy's talking,
and the next thing second you
hit the ground.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
Three days in that world,
and less than a moment
passed in this one.
Why not just kill me?
If he wanted to, he could.
-Hm.
After all that, the fool's
spirit is still intact.
Meanwhile, you risked
overusing those eyes of yours.
You know that's dangerous.
-This thing you've come for.
Is it Sasuke?
-No.
The legacy of the Fourth Hokage.
-What's he talking about?
What's he after?
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): Naruto.
KAKASHI: It's been a
long time, Jiraiya.
How many years since you've
even seen the village?
-Kakashi.
I'll train Naruto from now on.
The Third Hokage
was wise to place
the boy under your supervision.
He's been well looked after.
But even someone of your
remarkable abilities
might not be enough
to get him ready.
-Ready?
What are you talking about?
-I've been keeping a close watch
on Orochimaru all this time,
ever since the day
he left the village.
It was clear that he meant
to come back someday,
and it was important
to know what
he was planning in the meantime.
For many years, I
observed his movements.
But then--
-What?
-He became part of
an organization.
-Organization?
What organization?
What's its purpose?
-No one really knows
for sure, but it's
a roving gang of nine
like-minded shinobi
who call themselves
the Akatsuki.
At first, they stuck to small
scale cloak and dagger stuff.
Nothing dramatic, but you
knew something big was coming,
considering who they are.
These are not small timers.
Almost everyone in
the organization
is listed in the bingo book as
an S class criminal deviant.
For instance, that guy
Itachi's one of them.
When nine shinobi like
that get together,
it's not because they
want to do charity work.
I'm sure you've already
got an idea by now
as to where this is headed.
Recently, the group
started splitting up.
Orochimaru went off on his
own while others paired up
and dispersed through different
areas, searching for new jutsu
to master, and other
things as well.
-And one of these things
they're looking forward
is the Nine-Tailed Fox?
-It's only a possibility,
but it makes sense.
After all, the Nine-Tailed
Fox has an incredible amount
of chakra.
Kakashi, sooner or
later, Naruto must
learn that, because
of what he is,
he'll have to live his
life watching his back.
That's the boy's destiny.
For now, focus on Sasuke.
It's up to you to teach him
how to use his Sharingan.
And I'll keep an eye on Naruto.
Leave his training to me.
-The Nine-Tailed
spirit inside Naruto.
That's what you're after?
You're not the
only ones, are you?
There are seven more of
you out there, searching.
Hunting.
I know all about you.
You call yourselves
the Akatsuki, right?
-Akatsuki?
-Kisame, we'll take
Kakashi with us,
but we don't need the others.
Get rid of them
-Severe Leaf Hurricane!
-Well, who have we here?
-The Leaf village's
fiercest beast of battle.
I'm Might Guy.
-You're Might Guy, huh?
Mighty stupid looking Guy.
-Don't underestimate him.
GUY (VOICEOVER): It's him.
Itachi.
Oh, what they must've
put him through.
-Close your eyes.
Don't look at Itachi.
You'll get caught in his jutsu.
-Relax.
I know what I'm doing.
After spending this much time
training to fight Kakashi,
I know all about Sharingan.
All right, both of you,
open your eyes, now.
-But, if we--
-Don't worry, just
don't look in his eyes.
That's the key to fighting an
opponent who's using Sharingan.
Focus on his feet.
You can read what he's
gonna do from his feet.
-All right, but that
trick sounds a lot easier
said than done.
-We haven't had
all your training.
We're not you, Guy.
-True.
It takes skill to anticipate
an opponent's moves merely
from watching his feet,
but I don't have time
to teach you now.
You'll just have
to do your best.
-So what do we do?
-Kurenai, get Kakashi
to the Medical Corps.
Asuma, you'll be my backup.
-Got it.
-All right.
I sent word for the ANBU Black
Ops, but until they get here,
we hold them off.
Just you and me.
-Interesting.
I'll give you credit for guts.
-No, Kisame.
We're pulling out.
We're not here to fight
a full scale battle.
Tempting as it may be, it's
not the way to do this.
Let's go.
-That's too bad.
It was just getting fun.
They don't know
how lucky they are.
-All right, I'm ready.
Let's move out!
-You, uh, don't think you might
have overdone it a little?
You do realize we're not going
on a trip around the world,
right?
[theme music]
JIRAIYA: Woo hoo!
Now that's a lady.
Ha cha cha cha.
-Whoa, you're right!
She's pretty!
Hey, she winked at me.
JIRAIYA: No offense, kid, but it
wasn't you she was winking at!
-She's maybe even
prettier than Sakura!
-OK, Naruto!
I've got research to do.
Finish your training
and go to bed.
-No way!
Stop treating me
like I was a kid!
Next time, Jiraiya!
Naruto's Potential Disaster!
You're the one who needs
more sleep, old man!
[theme music]