[music playing]
[theme music]
NARUTO: "A Dubious Offer.
Tsunade's Choice."
[shouting]
[thud]
NARUTO: Come on.
OK.
Once again, here we go.
I'll nail it this time.
KABUTO: You're the
only one who can
cure Lord Orochimaru's arms.
You know that.
So do we have a deal?
-I'm offering to bring
your dear little brother
and your beloved back to
life with a forbidden jutsu
that I have developed.
Come now, don't you want to
see them again, dear Tsunade?
-Think of your
brother and my uncle.
They wouldn't have
wanted any part of this.
It would be a betrayal of
them, a betrayal of yourself.
Have you forgotten
all of your dreams?
-I'll cut to the chase.
Tsunade, in all its
wisdom, the village
has come to the decision to
name you as the Fifth Hokage.
Remember the Hokage that
have come before and all
they've accomplished
for the Leaf Village.
This was their dream,
and they were all
willing to gamble everything to
achieve it, even their lives.
KABUTO: Don't decide
now, but we'll
expect your answer
within the week.
Keep in mind, if
your answer is yes,
this jutsu requires
two human sacrifices.
It will be your job to
take care of that part.
DEALER: And down they go.
All right.
Place your bets.
What do you say?
You in or out, lady?
Come on.
What's it going to be?
KABUTO: What's it going to be?
If she agrees to
our proposition,
your arms will be healed, and
you can proceed with your plan
to destroy the Village
Hidden in the Leaves,
and Lady Tsunade is
reunited with the two
people she loves most.
But if she should
say no, what then?
-Then I'd simply use force to
bend her to my way of thinking.
-You really think it
would be that easy?
-That's what you're for.
Hm.
No need to worry.
In all the world,
there is no one
who knows Tsunade better than
I, including her greatest
weakness.
She'll agree to the
proposition, I guarantee it.
JARAIYA: Now listen.
In the third step,
you've got to draw up
100% of what you've
learned so far.
And then maintain it.
In other words, keeping
the power and the rotation
of your chakra at their maximum.
NARUTO: I get it.
I can see it in my head, but
no matter how hard I try,
I just can't focus all my
chakra into a neat little ball.
-What's the point of
teaching it to someone
who can never master it?
Giving him false
hopes like that,
filling his head
with stupid ideas,
making him think he could
actually be Hokage someday?
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER):
Tomorrow then.
-Come back soon.
OK.
-Well, how about right now?
I'm just playing with you.
You take care now.
[humming]
When are you meeting
Orochimaru again?
The look of guilt on her face.
Things could be even
worse than I suspected.
One week, she said.
That worries me.
And it's been nearly a week
since Naruto slept here.
I think I better have another
little talk with Tsunade.
-It's no use.
Why can't I do it?
It's too late.
Running out of time.
-[gasp] Oh my.
Naruto, are you all right?
Naruto.
[knocking]
-What do you want?
-It's a lovely night.
You want to quench your thirst.
Unless I'm wrong,
the week you gave
Naruto is up tomorrow, isn't it?
I wonder where he is.
I haven't seen him in days.
-Beats me.
-I think I'll have
something to eat.
Bring me the special, will you?
HOST: Coming right up.
-Ah.
HOST: Here you go.
JARAIYA: Ah, now,
that looks delicious.
-Lady Tsunade.
How is he doing?
-He's collapsed from exhaustion.
And his right hand
is severely burned
from concentrated chakra.
He's out of it.
He won't wake up till the day
after tomorrow at the earliest.
Old Jaraiya was right about me.
To think I've sunk so low,
I'd bet against a kid.
Ha.
What am I getting
so torn up about?
It's his problem, not mine.
-And tomorrow?
Please tell me you're
not going tomorrow.
Why don't you answer?
Say something.
Lady Tsunade, answer me.
I need to know.
Because if you tell
me you're going--
-What then?
-I will try and stop you
if it costs me my life.
-Shizune, have you forgotten
who you're talking to you?
-What?
Are you still here?
Come on.
Sun's up.
Time to call it a night.
Oh.
Hey, wake up.
Time to go home.
Come on now.
What the-- hey, old man, you OK?
-It's important that
nothing interferes
with these negotiations.
-Your point being?
-Tsunade's companion
could be trouble.
I'd feel better
if she were dead.
KABUTO: It seems that you don't
quite trust me, Orochimaru,
at least not yet.
OROCHIMARU: I trusted in you
to act without that knowledge.
I'm planning to leave Sasuke
in your capable hands.
-Very well.
-Kabuto, wait.
You know that your
desire to stop me,
I'm afraid your only chance
is to kill Sasuke now.
You can't possibly
hope to kill me.
-Hey, where the heck am I?
-Naruto, I-- [gasp]
Naruto, what time is it?
What day is it today?
What day?
What time?
-It's Monday morning.
Why?
What is it?
It's amazing.
Are you sure you're
feeling all right?
You were supposed to be out of
it for two full days at least.
-Ha.
Not a chance.
No matter how beat
up I get, just
give me a good night's
sleep, and I'm right back
at the top of my game.
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER): Of
course, the Nine-Tailed Fox.
-Besides, I've got a date to
keep with that rotten old witch
Tsunade.
Today's the day I wipe
that smirk off her face.
SHIZUNE: So you've
mastered the jutsu?
-Uh.
No, not completely.
But close enough.
So I'll just wing it.
I'll be fine.
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER):
What am I doing?
We're running out of time.
-Hey.
-Stay here, Naruto.
You hear me?
Stay here.
What in the world?
-What is it?
Huh?
-She slipped me a mickey.
Double crossing little vixen.
She must have spiked my
drink when I wasn't looking.
I can't build up any chakra.
My body is so weak.
I don't think I can even
throw a kunai straight.
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER): Straight
enough to nearly kill me.
-Great, pervy sage.
And you're always going on about
what a great ninja you are.
What?
Did you get distracted
by her pretty face?
-Shut up!
She possesses a healer's
knowledge of herbs and elixirs.
I should have known better.
Only Tsunade could
whip up a knockout drug
that even a ninja
couldn't detect.
But still, to be caught
off guard like that,
I must be losing my touch.
-I'll kill you.
I swear.
-Are you feeling better
now, Master Jaraiya?
-I suppose so, compared
to how I felt before.
I'm back to maybe 30%.
KABUTO (VOICEOVER):
I wasn't expecting
to find Jaraiya
the Mountain Sage.
That's more than
I bargained for.
I may have to rethink this.
And Naruto, to think
you'd be here too.
-Hm.
OK, Shizune.
-Yes.
What is it?
-It's time you told us about
your mistress and Orochimaru.
What kind of deal
are they making?
-Orochimaru?
-I never imagined she
would go through with it.
And that's why I-- I didn't
say anything about it before.
But now, there's
no time to lose.
You must come with me quickly.
I'll explain on the way.
JARAIYA: Let's go then.
NARUTO: Don't forget me.
I'm coming too.
-Well, what's your answer?
-You can't be serious.
-The answer has to be no.
At least, it better be.
JARAIYA (VOICEOVER): So things
are worse than I thought.
Could it be that the
loss of those two
has clouded her judgment?
You give me no choice Tsunade.
If I have to kill you, I will.
[growl]
-I will heal your arms,
but in exchange, you
keep your hands off the village.
-[laughing] Very well.
Shall we?
-As soon as his arms
are healed, Orochimaru
is planning to destroy
the Leaf Village.
-Of course.
That's just what I'd expect.
And trust me he'll do
far more than that if we
don't manage to
stop him somehow.
-Who does this
creep think he is?
OROCHIMARU: That's
what you're for.
No need to worry.
What is the meaning of this?
Am I to understand you've
really come here to betray me?
Tsunade!
[theme music]
NARUTO: What happened here?
Someone's been using these
walls as a punching bag?
JARAIYA: From the
look of things,
I'm guessing Tsunade
turned down the deal.
NARUTO: Where is
that old lady anyway?
I've got a thing or
two to say to her.
JARAIYA: Don't get
your shorts in a knot.
She can't be far.
NARUTO: Whoa.
What the heck was that?
JARAIYA: Speak of the devil.
Sounds like they're still at it.
Come on, Naruto.
Hurry.
NARUTO: I'm coming.
You just try and
keep up, pervy sage.
Next time, "Breakdown.
The Deal Is Off."
[theme music]