THEME SONG: [speaking Japanese]
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Sasuke!
Say what you like about Naruto.
That he's a pest.
That he gets in the way.
That he's just a kid.
But at least he's--
He's doing something.
At least, he's no coward!
Sasuke!
OROCHIMARU (VOICEOVER):
Foolish little brother.
You can't kill me.
Your hate's not strong enough.
You're not strong enough.
Your life is too
precious to you.
So run.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): No.
OROCHIMARU (VOICEOVER):
That's right.
Run away and live.
Live with the shame.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): No.
-No!
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
The Sharingan revived.
Dragon Flame Jutsu.
-I knew it.
It's finally happened.
His Uchiha blood
has come to a boil.
I think I'll play
with him a little,
and learn the full
extent of his powers.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): All I cared
about was surviving, in order
to defeat my brother.
What a fool I've been!
I see the truth now.
Naruto.
Sakura.
If I haven't the courage
to face this demon,
how can I ever hope to face him?
[grunts]
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): I can see.
I can see!
[grunts]
OROCHIMARU (VOICEOVER):
You're good.
You anticipate my attacks,
and your aim is true.
You can see my moves, can't you?
ANKO (VOICEOVER):
Sun's going down.
I gotta find him soon.
My odds are bad enough as it is.
They'll only get
worse in the dark.
But why now?
What the devil
could he be after?
No matter.
He's here.
Time to finish this.
[grunts]
-Substitution!
-Sasuke!
-What a disappointment
you turned out to be.
Your ancestors weep.
The Uchiha clan should
thank me for killing you.
Silly little worm!
[gasps]
-Incredible.
A Sharingan windmill
triple attack!
[grunts]
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
Fire-Style Dragon Flame Jutsu!
[screams]
-He did it!
[gasping]
-Sasuke!
You did it!
You OK?
Don't worry.
It's all over.
[both gasping]
-No.
Impossible.
OROCHIMARU (VOICEOVER):
Such mastery
of the Sharingan
at so young an age.
You're a true Uchiha after all.
Yes, you'll do nicely.
[screaming]
You are definitely his brother.
If anything, your eyes are
even keener than Itachi's.
-(ANGRILY) Who are you?
What do you want?
[chuckling]
-My name is Orochimaru.
But as to what I
want, that will have
to wait until we meet again.
Which won't happen until
you finish this test
with the best score of all.
[gasps]
-The scroll!
OROCHIMARU (VOICEOVER):
First, you'll
have to defeat the hidden
sound ninja who serve me.
-I have no idea what
you're talking about.
But if you're finished,
why don't you just beat it?
If we never meet again,
it'll be too soon.
-Oh, he and I will meet again.
[gasps]
-Sasuke, no!
[gasping]
-Sasuke!
You!
What have you done to Sasuke?
-I just gave him a
little parting gift.
Very soon, Sasuke
will seek me out.
He'll desire my power.
In the meantime, I
enjoyed the demonstration
of the powers you
already possess.
[chuckling]
[screaming]
-Sasuke!
[gasping]
-What is it?
What's he done to you?
Are you--
It's OK.
[screaming]
Hang on.
You're gonna be OK.
[passes out]
Sasuke!
Sasuke.
[crying]
Naruto!
Sasuke's hurt!
I need you!
Naruto!
[crying]
I don't-- I don't know
what I'm supposed to do.
ANKO (VOICEOVER):
I can feel him.
He's somewhere close.
[chuckling]
-Well, well, Anko.
It's been a while.
[chuckling]
-This is no time to reminisce.
You're an S-class criminal.
Top of the most wanted list.
You've got to be taken
down, and it's only fitting
that I'm the one to do it.
Because after all, you're the
one who taught me everything.
Right, sensei?
-Not quite.
[gasps]
-Striking shadow snake!
Come out of there!
[grunts]
[screams]
[gasps]
-I've got you.
Now then.
Let me just borrow
your left hand.
-That hand sign.
[gasps]
-Right.
It's over.
You and I are going to die here.
ANKO (VOICEOVER): Ninja arch.
Twin snake sacrifice jutsu.
[chuckling]
OROCHIMARU (VOICEOVER): I'm
afraid you will die alone,
Anko.
[gasps]
-That's right.
Substitution.
[panting]
[laughing]
OROCHIMARU
(VOICEOVER): Of course.
You're one of the elite now.
A righteous warrior.
How naughty of you to be
using the forbidden jutsu
I taught you.
[grunts]
-It won't work, Uncle.
-Why are you here?
-I'm disappointed.
I expected a friendlier
reception after all this time.
-Don't tell me you've come here
to assassinate Lord Hokage?
-No, not yet.
I don't have quite enough
followers to attempt that.
But I've heard such good
things about this village,
I thought I might
want to make it mine.
[moaning]
OROCHIMARU (VOICEOVER):
It's the mark, isn't it?
I put that same curse
mark on a young man
just a little while ago.
He's a very promising prospect.
-You haven't changed, I see.
He'll die before he serves you.
OROCHIMARU (VOICEOVER):
Very possibly.
I'd say the odds are
1 and 10 against him.
But the kid may
survive, as you did.
-Sounds like you
want him badly, huh?
OROCHIMARU (VOICEOVER):
Oh, jealous, is that it?
You can't forgive me, can you?
For using you, and
then tossing you aside.
[growls]
-In some ways, the boy has even
more potential than you had.
You see, he's inherited
the sublime abilities
of the Uchiha clan.
[chuckles] And his physical
condition is excellent.
Yes, he might very well be
the heir I'm looking for.
At the very least, he
makes things interesting.
Whatever happens, make sure
no one stops the exams early.
Three of my followers
are also candidates.
I look forward to
seeing how they fare.
OROCHIMARU (VOICEOVER):
Bear this in mind.
If anything happens to
deprive me of my fun,
it means the end of
the Leaf Village.
NINJA (VOICEOVER): All right.
That's enough
resting up, I think.
The other teams will be
calling it a day soon.
And that means,
it's time to strike.
You know the plan.
We split up and fan out.
Whatever happens, whether we
make contact with another team
or not, we meet up
back here in this spot.
Got it?
-No sweat.
-Roger.
-All right then.
Let's move!
[moaning]
-At least he's finally
breathing easier now.
But he's still got a high fever.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Looks like it's up to me
for the time being.
ANKO (VOICEOVER): I've
wasted enough time.
Somebody's got to
tell Lord Hokage.
-Huh?
[sighs]
[gasps]
-I don't have time for this!
[moaning]
[roars]
ANKO (VOICEOVER): It's
a paralysis jutsu!
ANBU TEAM 1 (VOICEOVER):
So there you are, Anko!
-Man, you Anbu goons took your
time getting here, didn't you?
-Well, there's no
need to get snippy.
[moaning]
-Anko, are you all right?
What is it?
That curse mark has appeared.
But that means, Orochimaru!
-What, here?
No!
ANBU TEAM 1 (VOICEOVER): Hurry!
Let's get you up.
We'll carry you to Lord
Hokage if we have to.
-No.
No.
Take me to the tower.
-What are you talking about?
You know we have
to raise the alarm
at the first sign of Orochimaru.
That's more important
than the Chunin Exams.
-I know, but-- All right, then.
Summon Lord Hokage to the tower.
I'll explain everything there.
[chuckling]
DOSU (VOICEOVER): Found you.
All right.
Just as Orochimaru ordered.
We strike at daybreak.
And remember, our
target is the Uchiha.
-Yeah, but if the other
two get in our way,
it's OK if we take
'em out, right?
DOSU (VOICEOVER): Of course.
[birds chirping]
[gasps]
[music playing]
[speaking Japanese]
ROCK LEE (VOICEOVER):
It is I, Rock Lee,
handsome devil of the
Hidden Leaf Village.
Everything is turning out
just as I planned, Guy Sensei.
What better way to win
the lovely Sakura's heart,
than by rescuing her?
Some might say I am
seriously outnumbered,
but that is the best part.
It means the conditions
have been met,
and I can finally unleash my--
Well, my special talent, right,
Sensei?
Next time, Bushy Brow's Pledge.
Undying Love and Protection!