[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
The Beast Within.
[chuckling]
-Sasuke!
Come on!
Why do you keep
running away from me?
NARUTO: Sasuke!
[groaning]
[hiccup]
-Whoa-- whoa.
Wha.
What is wrong with you?
You know how impolite
it is to stare?
[shouting]
KIMIMARO (VOICEOVER):
He's faster than before.
-Hiya!
KIMIMARO (VOICEOVER):
That medicine he took.
Could there have been some
special ingredient in it?
-Not too shabby.
Boy.
All this jumping around is
totally messing with my head
here.
I'm OK though.
-Huh?
[snoring]
KIMIMARO (VOICEOVER):
What just happened?
Did he really fall asleep?
[snoring]
-Ah-hah!
You fell for it.
[shouting]
-It looked like I was
sleeping, but in reality I
was wide awake.
Witness the guardian
of the shinobi.
Guy-sensei, I did it.
All your training
has not been in vain!
Guy-sensei, I did it.
I-- ugh.
[snoring]
-Looks like you fell
for it again, sucker.
If you honestly think I
would fall asleep spread
eagle on the battlefield,
you are certainly mistaken!
I-- hey wait.
Hold on a second.
Where am I?
What am I doing here?
What the?
What's going on?
What is this?
-Huh.
[sniffing]
-Sake?
KIMIMARO (VOICEOVER):
Is he just drunk?
Well, if you are,
I don't think it
will hurt too much when I
send you into the afterlife.
[groaning]
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): Damn it.
I don't have enough chakra.
At this rate--
KIBA (VOICEOVER): I can't stay
in the water with this wound,
or I'm really gonna
be in trouble.
[groaning]
[snoring]
KIMIMARO (VOICEOVER):
Why can't I hit him?
-Can't you see I'm
trying to take a nap.
Buzz, buzz, buzz,
you little fly!
[shout]
-Hey.
Bring it on already.
Hey.
Come on.
What's the hold up, tough guy?
KIMIMARO (VOICEOVER): These
movements-- what are they?
GUY: I'm sure there's no
need to tell you this,
but that Kenpo brand is no joke.
The more of it you throw
back, the stronger it gets!
-Yes, I know.
One time in this
restaurant, Lee thought
he was reaching for some
water and he ended up
downing a small
cup of Dragon Fire.
LEE: Hey!
What's the idea?
GUY: Easy, Lee.
LEE: I said hey!
[laughing]
GUY: Whoa.
Whoa.
Lee.
Lee, please sit down.
LEE: Woo-cha!
NEJI: Look at your behavior!
GUY: Quick!
Get his legs.
Thank goodness I
had Neji with me..
It took the two of us combined
to finally restrain him.
-You mean you couldn't
overpower him on your own?
-Well, if he had
actually been my enemy,
I could've taken
him down no problem.
But Lee's special to me.
I could never hurt
a hair on his head.
-Of course.
-That's how bad it got
after he had one sip.
If he were to treat an
entire bottle of that sake--
-He might be
virtually invincible.
But he's just out
of the hospital.
How long will his body hold out?
-Hey, come on.
KIMIMARO (VOICEOVER): He's
using the Drunken Fist.
I've never seen it before.
-If you will not
make the first move,
then I will just have to
bring the fight to you!
[shout]
KIMIMARO (VOICEOVER): His style
of attack is fairly direct.
-Agh!
Ugh.
Ow.
What'd you do that for?
I am enjoying the
springtime of my youth!
KIMIMARO (VOICEOVER): His
moves are so unorthodox.
But more than
anything he's fast!
-I am in the prime of my youth
and making the most of it.
-Camellia Dance!
KIMIMARO (VOICEOVER): There.
-Yaa!
[hiccup]
-Gwah-yah!
[groaning]
[mumbling]
KIMIMARO (VOICEOVER): I
can't read his movements.
For him to land an attack on me?
That's quite the taijutsu.
No other choice.
-My true abilities
lie within my bones.
I'm sure the little
clone brat must
have told you before he left.
-Huh?
-I think it's time
we sobered you up.
-Sober who up?
Do I look drunk to you?
-Well, whatever you are,
I'll snap you out it.
-I said I'm not drunk.
In the first place,
I'm not even of age.
Underage ninjas should not
partake in drinking sake!
-Gah!
-Unorthodox is it not?
This is my kekkei genkai.
KIMIMARO (VOICEOVER):
Calm down, Shikamaru.
Figure out a strategy.
There's got to be
some way out of this.
[chuckling] He wasn't
able to scamper off
too far with that wound of his.
KIBA (VOICEOVER): That' it.
I can't go any further.
Are you kidding me?
He's already caught up?
[sniff]
KIBA (VOICEOVER): Wait.
-My head is pounding
like a drum.
And why is my face bleeding?
It seems I really was
drunk after all then.
Uh-- what has happened to you?
-So, your medicine
has finally worn off.
You're looking at
my kekkei genkai.
LEE: Kekkei genkai.
-My kekkei genkai freely
controls my osteoblasts
and osteoclasts.
It allows me to alter the
concentration of calcium
and form new bones altogether.
Normally, the human
body contains 206 bones.
But in my case, that number
is somewhat more negotiable.
-But bone is bone after all.
Once broken, there
is no mending it!
LEE (VOICEOVER): Such density.
Are those really human bones?
Hyah!
Very well.
-Behold, my Larch Dance.
-Gyah!
[groaning]
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
I've had it.
-Just a little bit further,
you piece of garbage.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): This is
just like that time with Asuma.
-Asuma.
-The chances of
someone stepping into
help me here are
probably close to zero.
Stop wasting brainpower on
something that'll never happen.
Just calm down.
[sniffing]
KIBA (VOICEOVER): His
scent-- he's moving away.
-That was close.
SAKON: What was?
-But how did you?
-I knew that it would work.
[chuckling]
KIMIMARO (VOICEOVER): My jacket.
-You're so used
to your own smell
you didn't even
notice it on the wind.
-So you were skulking
around in my jacket
to cover up your scent.
You seem to know a
lot about tracking.
No wonder I couldn't smell you.
Guess I shouldn't
be surprised, right?
Seriously.
How in the world am I supposed
to keep track of somebody who
can split in half?
Well, come on then.
-Please, wait.
From now on.
We play for keeps.
LEE (VOICEOVER): My
role now is to stall
this person as long as possible.
I would rather not resort
to more powerful attacks.
They will only leave me
vulnerable to defeat.
But my enemy is
a formidable one.
I will have to reveal my
secret technique to best him!
-Here I come.
I just had surgery, so
I am not at my best.
But if I only open the First
Gate, the Gate of Opening,
I should be all right.
-The First Gate, Gate
of Opening, open!
Primary Lotus!
LEE (VOICEOVER): The bone
absorbed the impact of my kick!
-Your speed is impressive.
But this is over now.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): Damn it.
I'm wracking my brain here, Why
can't I come up with anything?
I'm at the end of my rope.
I can't hold on any home longer.
-You're staring
death in the face.
Shouldn't you be screaming
for mercy or something?
Eh?
[chuckling]
-Now die!
-You're mine!
-You're gonna die, kid.
Wipe that grin off your face!
[scream]
-What the hell?
-Who are you?
-Huh?
-Heh.
Well, what do you know?
Looks like we're
on the same side.
-Who are you?
-Allies of the Leaf Village.
-We're shinobi of the Sand.
[theme music]
SHKAMARU: I had heard that
the Sand and Leaf had made up,
but--
TEMARI: It's not like we
attacked the Leaf Village
for the heck of it.
It was a mission,
just like this is.
SHIKAMARU: Whatever
you say well.
KIBA: Hey, by the way,
weren't there three of you
Sand ninja heading
this way before?
KANKURO: We had no choice but
to split up for you weaklings.
KIBA: You idiot.
Don't take them lightly.
These guys are
anything but ordinary.
NARUTO: Next time--
the Sand Shinobi!
Allies of the Leaf!
[theme music]