[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Hang on, Sasuke.
-Before we go any
further, I'm afraid you
must die just this once.
-I must die, once?
--[chuckle] You will take one
of these awakening pills.
-What's it for?
Awakening from what?
-That mark on your shoulder is
only a first state curse mark.
But those pills will stimulate
and magnify its power,
making it a level two.
-One problem, strengthening
the curse mark
will also increase its
effects on your body.
Such a rapid change
would kill you at once.
And so, to ensure you
survive the transition
to the second state, we
must give your body time
to get accustomed to it.
Several hours, at least.
After that, once the
transition is complete,
your power may even
be equal to ours.
Unfortunately, the
fact remains that even
with all these preparations,
you'll still have to die.
-So I'm dead.
What'll happen after that?
-Not to worry.
Why do you think my
friends and I are here?
We'll cast a barrier
ninjutsu to lessen
the effects of the transition.
Instead of dying,
you'll only be suspended
in a state of
half-death for a while.
-And I'm supposed to
trust you guys to make
sure this half-death doesn't
end up being the real thing?
-Listen Sasuke.
Don't forget who we are.
Orochimaru's hand
picked bodyguards.
If there's anybody who knows
about curse marks, barrier
ninjutsu, and all
the rest, it'd be us.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
One thing's for sure, I
can't afford to die.
Not yet.
-I guess I'm in your hands.
-Right.
Get ready.
We've got to do this
quickly, or we'll lose him.
Get in position.
Now.
-Four Black Mist Formation!
-Sealing jutsu.
There.
That'll hold him for now.
-Ugh, I'm exhausted.
-Who would've ever guessed that
this mission would turn out
to be such a tough one?
[wind] [gasps]
-Stay here while
we check it out.
Raido, come on.
-Right.
-Great.
It looks like we've got company.
-There's just one--
no, wait-- two of them.
-Get ready.
-They work for Orochimaru.
-And judging from the path
these four are taking,
I guess they've just
come from the Village
Hidden in the Leaves.
What you got in the coffin?
-Fighting two Jounin at once?
I'm trembling at the prospect.
GENMA (VOICEOVER): They
all have curse marks.
-You might want to
think this over.
It won't be like last time when
you jumped us all by surprise.
-Yeah, you're right scum,
you won't survive this time.
GENMA: Truse me, you
pawns of Orochimaru,
you don't want to mess
with the Leaf Shinobi.
-Where are they?
It's been too long.
-So you think maybe
something's happened to them?
-Let's go find out.
-Right.
-[wimper]
-Akamaru?
-What's the matter with him?
-He smells blood.
Somewhere nearby.
-[gasp] What happened?
-Raido, Genma!
[fading heartbeat]
This isn't good.
-Both of them taken down.
It's impossible.
-[grunt]
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER):
All I can do right now
is just try and stabilize him.
IWASHI: I'm going Shizune.
I'm going to find them
and make them pay.
-No you won't!
-What?
What do you mean?
-She's right, Iwashi.
They-- they were using
jutsu beyond the powers
of mere shinobi.
[cough] If you go after them
, you'll only be killed.
-Genma, that's enough talking.
-Here's what happened,
the scent of two newcomers
converged on the scent of
Sasuke and four others.
The two have stayed behind while
Sasuke's group has moved on.
So what now?
-Just as I thought,
Sasuke's got an escort.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
Man, this is turning out
to be such a drag.
-There's no question, we
gotta go after Sasuke.
-Who died and make you boss?
Last time I checked,
Shikamaru was
in charge of running this show.
It's up to him to decide.
-Hmph.
Well, Shikamaru?
-Since Akamaru smelled
blood, my guess
is that there was a battle
between Sasuke's group
and the two newcomers.
If we go to the spot
where they fought,
we might be able to gather
some useful information.
Of course we can't just
rush in, it might be a trap.
So when we get closer, we'll go
into full reconnaissance mode
and take it slowly.
-And while we're
doing that, Sasuke
will have crossed beyond the
borders of the Land of Fire
and out of our hands.
-OK Shikamaru, so
what's it going to be?
-We follow Sasuke.
-Way to go.
I knew you'd make
the right choice.
-One thing.
-What?
-These guys have already
been in one fight,
so they'll be on their guard.
Unless they're complete
idiots, they'll
have to know there's going to
be more ninja on their trail.
There's a good chance we'll
hit some booby traps or even
an ambush up ahead.
So from this point on,
we proceed with caution.
I want everybody,
not just Akamaru,
to put all your
senses on full alert.
If you catch a trace of anything
suspicious, sound the alarm.
We want to find these
guys before they find us.
-Ha!
Got it.
And when we do
find them I'm going
to clobber them with this
brand new jutsu of mine.
KIBA (VOICEOVER): That Naruto.
Every time I turn around, he's
got a new trick up his sleeve.
And just when I
thought I'd finally
caught up to that
little pain in the neck.
-[sniff] [wimper]
-The enemy's scent is
here, all around us.
-Everyone stop!
Look up on that tree, see that?
NEJI: A paper bomb.
I'm sure there's
five more of them.
A perimeter barrier,
that's what it is.
-A perimeter barrier?
-It's a type of trap ninjutsu.
There's a delay
after the perimeter
is breached, giving the
victim just enough time
to get to the center of the
area for the full effect.
It's a tricky jutsu, I learned
about it in one of the books
my dad used to make me read.
-Ugh.
Now we got to waste
time going around it.
Great.
-Lee, it's up to you.
You do what you must do.
HOKAGE: No Lee, it's
too soon for that.
-But Lady Hokage--
-I know you like to push
yourself, but take it easy.
Your body's still recovering
from the operation.
This is one thing you
don't want to rush.
-But I need to start training,
if only a little bit.
This waiting around
doing nothing--
-Building your physical
strength isn't the only type
of training you need.
You know what I'm
talking about, don't you?
A true ninja endures hardship
with patience and restraint.
He knows how to wait.
So just look at this as
another kind of training.
-A kind of training?
-You don't want to hurt
yourself and make things worse.
Here.
-Uh?
What is that?
-It's just some medicine
I made up for you.
Go on, drink up.
You want to get
better, don't you?
-[grunts] Yes ma'am.
-Let's head back, OK?
-Right.
KIBA: Man, this whole forest
is crawling with booby traps.
SHIKAMARU: Yeah, but luckily
they're easy to spot.
These guys are moving
fast and getting sloppy.
-Naruto, do me a favor and
watch where you're going.
I don't want to
blowing us all up.
There's trip wires everywhere.
-Tell me something I don't know.
-Naruto, hold it!
-[grunt], just in time.
Got him with my Shadow
Possession jutsu.
KIBA: Didn't I tell you to
watch your step, you moron?
SHIKAMARU: I get it.
One wire catches the
light and is easy to see,
the other is camouflaged.
While you're busy avoiding the
first, you trip the second.
-They've created a
trap within a trap.
They're clever,
whoever they are.
-All their other traps
were quick and dirty,
as if they were moving fast.
But not this one.
-They may have stopped to rest.
Perhaps one of them is injured.
Or is this part of the trap?
Byakugan!
I see them.
-Well let's go,
I'm dying to show
these clowns what I've got.
-Is that right?
Hate to disappoint
you, hotshot, but I've
got a new jutsu I've
been working on too.
-Yeah, me too.
-All right, calm down.
First we make a plan and
get everything ready.
Then, we nail these bastards.
[panting]
-It drives me crazy,
stopping and having
to rest when we
should be moving on.
-Buwo, what did you expect?
You think you can
fight a level two
battle without
feeling the effects?
-To feel like your whole
body is completely useless,
it's frustrating.
-Can't be helped if you're going
to take on two Jounin level
ninja.
If we'd held anything
back, we'd have been dead.
SHIKAMARU: That's it.
Now Kiba, the timing
of those smoke
bombs is absolutely
crucial, got it?
KIBA: I got it.
-So, split up.
Let's go.
-Looks like we've
caught them napping.
Hm?
Hold on, where's Sasuke?
-He's in there.
Inside that coffin.
-You don't mean he's dead?
-It's been sealed with a
barrier jutsu that's hard for me
to see through clearly.
Considering they went through
all that trouble to get him,
I can't believe they'd be
willing to kill him so quickly.
-Let's just hope you're right.
Huh?
[gasps] [screams]
[theme music]
[barking]
NARUTO: Give me a
break, this is crazy.
[interposing voices]
ALL: Akamaru, keep quiet!
KIBA: Hey, leave him alone.
NARUTO: Oh forget it.
Just get me close enough
to use my Rasengan,
and leave the rest to me.
Next time, Squad Mutiny,
Everything Falls Apart.