[theme music]
-Ugh!
Aah!
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
I've got him that time.
I'm starting to get the timing.
[grunts]
HAKU (VOICEOVER): He
read my movements.
But that's not possible.
-I was so close, but I
couldn't quite get to him.
-Naruto, can you do it again?
-Huh?
Of course.
Nothing can stop me.
Believe it!
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): He
doesn't want to show it,
but he's exhausted.
The Shadow Clone Jutsu
uses up so much chakra.
But thanks to him,
I figured it out.
I know how to break through.
HAKU (VOICEOVER): The human
eye cannot track my movements.
It must have been a coincidence.
-Naruto, run for it!
-Huh?
-Get out of here and
attack from the outside!
Hurry!
-Uh, all right, you got it!
-You cannot escape.
-[panting]
[grunts]
Aah!
Ugh.
You think you
could keep me here?
Forget it!
-That's it!
Fire Style, Fireball Jutsu!
-Ugh!
I couldn't get past him.
-That was good, Naruto.
-Huh?
-One more time.
-Yeah.
Let's do it!
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): There must
be a limit to his chakra, too.
I can feel him slowing down.
-Aah!
-No more games.
I need to stop this now!
This time you'll stay down!
-Ugh!
Aah!
-Uh, Sasuke!
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): An enemy
you can't see and can't hear.
It's been a long time since
I faced anyone this tough.
And Sasuke and Naruto, I don't
know if they can hold out.
Stay calm.
Think.
Where will he strike?
[gasp] The bridge builder!
-[grunts]
[both gasp]
-Hm.
-Too late!
[screams]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
"The Broken Seal."
-That scream.
That was Sakura.
What's happening to her?
Where is Kakashi?
NARUTO: [groans]
Sakura.
She's in trouble.
-We've got to break through.
-I'll bust us out of here.
-Naruto.
-I'll fake him out.
-You've exhausted my patience.
-[grunts]
SASUKE: Naruto, behind you!
-Ugh!
SASUKE: Naruto!
-Your chance of escaping my
House of Mirrors is zero.
That is absolute.
-Naruto, are you able to get up?
-[groans]
-Try not to use any more chakra.
That's only going
to help him now.
-I know, Sasuke.
I know. [groans]
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): We
can't go on like this.
He's blocking
every move we make.
I've got to find a way
to outmaneuver him.
My eyes have adjusted
to his movements.
-Looking for a counterattack?
I'll save you the trouble.
What?
-Get up, loser!
We've got to team up!
-[groans]
HAKU (VOICEOVER): I'm aiming
at his vital spots now.
But I can't get a direct hit.
-[grunts]
I know what we have to do.
Believe it, Sasuke.
HAKU (VOICEOVER):
It's not just luck.
He's fighting to
protect his friend.
That's why he's so determined.
But he can't possibly
see the needles coming.
-Ugh.
HAKU (VOICEOVER): My movements
are beyond human speed.
And yet he's tracking
them somehow.
Whatever he's doing,
I've got to stop him now.
-He disappeared.
Where did he go?
How could he just vanish?
Naruto, you'd better
not pass out again.
Come on, let's go!
I can't keep protecting
you like this.
-Well, then, don't!
I never asked for your help.
Ugh.
-Uh?
HAKU: You can't revive him.
He's reached his limits.
-[grunts]
-[chuckles]
HAKU: Impressive.
You have excellent moves.
Your attacks are very skillful.
But you've reached
your limits as well.
Motor functions,
reflexes, judgment--
your abilities are
weakening slowly but surely.
Now, you're finished!
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
Here he comes.
Stay calm, focus,
concentrate, see everything.
HAKU (VOICEOVER):
He saw every move.
But there's no way
he could do that.
Impossible.
Those eyes.
The Sharingan.
Pure.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
It's not complete,
but I could see
through his deceptions.
HAKU (VOICEOVER): So he, too,
has a Kekkei Genkai, the power
of a unique bloodline trait
passed down within a clan.
Interesting, even though
it's not perfected.
To uncover this power in
the midst of a lethal attack
is an amazing feat.
And because of that, I won't
be able to fight much longer.
My jutsu uses a tremendous
amount of chakra.
And his swift movements
also take energy.
There's no doubt that
the longer we fight,
the more he will use the
Sharingan to perceive my moves.
Even now, his eyes
are tracking me.
I can't target him directly.
He'll just block
a frontal attack.
So I'll have to throw him
off-guard by attacking
his partner.
Then I'll destroy him.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
I've got to stop him!
-Ugh!
[gasping]
-Kakashi-sensei!
-You were late, Kakashi.
You let your concern for
those little punks' safety
cloud your mind, adding
further to the fog that
already hinders your Sharingan.
Your eyes are sharp,
Kakashi, but not
sharp enough to read my moves.
Not anymore.
[snickers]
Come on, Kakashi.
I want this to be fun.
I want to enjoy myself
as I exact my revenge.
As for those brats, don't worry.
They're at Haku's mercy.
No, they're breathing their
last breaths right now.
Relax.
You'll have plenty of time
to whip out an apology
for failing those brats when
you see them in the next life.
[laughs]
-[panting]
-He said Sasuke will die.
No, I won't believe that.
I have faith in him.
Sasuke will beat them to a pulp!
Cha!
And that masked
kid, we'll make him
wish that he was never born!
I can't lose Sasuke.
Anyone who tries to take
him from me will pay for it!
And Naruto either.
KAKASHI: Exactly
-[gasp]
-I-- I believe in
their abilities.
I have faith in them.
Naruto, the number 1 hyperactive
knucklehead ninja, and Sasuke,
heir to the most powerful clan
in the Hidden Leaf Village.
-Huh, you mean--
-Yes.
His full name is Sasuke Uchiha.
The unique powers of
the Uchiha bloodline
run through his veins.
The Kekkei Genkai
is his birthright.
-Ah, I heard that
one young ninja
survived the tragedy
of the Uchiha clan.
No wonder he
advances so quickly.
But so does Haku.
No one can match him.
No one has ever stopped
his Secret Jutsu.
Even the most skilled
Jonin fall before him.
Just as you will fall
before me, right now!
-Sakura, stay with Tazuna.
-OK.
Uh, got it.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): He's right.
It's time to end this.
But he is the one who will fall!
-[groans]
-You always get in
the way, Naruto.
It never fails.
-Ah!
You beat him, Sasuke!
Huh?
-You should see the
look on your face.
You-- you look
like a total loser.
-Huh?
Why-- why did you-- uh, save me?
Why did you do it?
-I don't know why, I just did.
-And my future dream is
to be the greatest Hokage.
Then the whole village
will stop disrespecting me
and start treating me like
I'm somebody, somebody--
-Get up, loser.
-We climbed all
the way to the top.
NARUTO AND SASUKE:
I want some more!
-Why are they so
obsessed with him?
Sasuke!
-We've got to team up!
-We've done this 1,000 times!
-[grunts]
[coughs]
You, I hated you.
-Then why?
It doesn't make any sense.
Why did you protect me?
Uhh.
[grunts]
I didn't ask for this!
I didn't ask for you to save me!
-I don't know.
My body just moved.
There was no time to think.
[groans]
Loser!
[grunts]
-Sasuke!
-He-- he's still out there.
My brother.
I promised myself I'd stay
alive until I killed him.
Naruto, don't let
your dream die.
[sighs]
[faint heartbeat]
-He found-- he
found the strength
he didn't realize he had.
Why?
Because of a certain person
who was precious to him.
To save that person, he rushed
in knowing it was a trap.
He was a true ninja,
worthy of honor.
Is this the first time you have
seen a friend die in battle?
This is part of what
it means to be a ninja.
-Shut up.
I-- I hated you, too, Sasuke.
And yet-- you'll pay for this.
-Hm?
-I'm going to kill you!
HAKU (VOICEOVER):
What is this chakra?
Chakra cannot be seen,
yet it's clearly visible.
It's something ghastly.
I can feel the wrath, the
blood lust, like evil itself.
His hand is healing
and changing.
This boy, what is he?
-[growls]
-[gasp]
-Huh!
-Uhh.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): Is
Zabuza creating this?
He's not.
I know this chakra.
There's no way.
ZABUZA: What is this energy?
It's something foul.
Kakashi?
No.
It's too powerful, even for him.
Where is it coming from?
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): Naruto.
This puts everyone in danger.
Now, of all times,
the seal has broken.
I have to stop it.
-[snarling]
[grunts]
[growls]
THEME SONG: Cultivate your
hunger before you idealize.
Motivate your anger to
make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain,
never coming down.
Break into the contents,
never falling down.
My knee is still
shaking, like I was 12.
Sneaking out of the
classroom, by the backdoor.
A man railed at me twice,
though, but I didn't care.
Waiting is wasting
for people like me.
Don't try to live so wise.
Don't cry 'cause
you're so right.
Don't try with fakes
or fears 'cause you
will hate yourself in the end.
Don't try to live so wise.
Don't cry 'cause
you're so right.
Don't try with fakes
or fears 'cause you
will hate yourself in the end.
Don't try to live so wise.
Don't cry 'cause
you're so right.
Don't try--
-[snarls]
Sasuke's gone.
Look what you've done.
You're going to pay for this.
[growls]
There's nothing you
can do to stop me.
And there's no turning back.
You destroyed Sasuke's dreams.
Now, I'm going to destroy you!
[roars]
Next time, "White
Past-- Hidden Ambition."