[theme music]
NARUTO: No way.
What happened?
Where's Iruka-sensei?
-His scent tapers off here.
Well, come on.
We'd better start looking.
-I swear, if anything has
happened to you here, Sensei--
[sigh]
-Iruka-sensei!
Thank goodness you're OK!
-You're safe!
IRUKA: Somehow--
Mizuki was able to--
-Sensei-- you're injured.
-Don't worry.
I'll be just fine.
-Are you all right?
-I'm fine.
Just a little wave
of pain there.
-For someone coming.
-Huh?
TSUBAKI: The wound's not deep.
Thankfully.
-Yes.
NARUTO: Things got a little
heavy all of a sudden, huh?
PAKKUN: Hm.
Definitely something going
on between those two.
I'm guessing they're, uh--
NARUTO: Huh?
Why are you holding up your paw?
PAKKUN: You dummy, my pinky.
Look at my pinky.
-Your?
Pinky Huh?
Are you saying she's his--
PAKKUN: I'm a dog.
I pick up on these
things, you know?
-Naruto?
What are you talking about?
NARUTO: Oh!
Uh-- nothing!
Huh?
Anyway, let me introduce you.
I'd like you to meet Tsubaki.
She's Mizuki's fiance.
NARUTO: She's Mizu-- wait!
Fiance?
PAKKUN: My radar must be off.
NARUTO: Oh, you think?
-This is the second time
Mizuki has caused you trouble.
You have my sincerest
of apologies.
-So you know what's
going on then, don't you?
You're aware that Mizuki
broke out of prison.
-Yes.
The other day, he
came by my home.
I realized immediately
and tried to stop him.
But in the end, I
just let him go.
-One I have th Leaf
Village under my thumb!
IRUKA: But the way
he is now, there's
nothing you could have done.
TSUBAKI: No.
I should have tried
harder to stop him.
If you really loved me--
But I--
Give up this foolishness!
-Tsubaki.
[thud]
-Iruka, Naruto, I'm begging you.
You-- you have to
take me with you.
-Even though Mizuki--
-You probably think
I'm crazy for asking,
but this path he's on--
no matter what happens,
I have to stop him.
-Iruka-sensei!
-Tsubaki, I can understand
how you must feel now.
-So then--
-I'm sorry.
I can't allow it.
-Huh?
-But why?
-How come she
can't come with us?
-Naruto, look.
There's no time to waste.
We have to find Mizuki.
You must understand.
She would only hinder us
from completing our mission.
-Yeah, but she-- she--
-Iruka, please.
If that's the case,
then I believe
I can be of service to you.
I'm pretty sure I know
where he's headed next,
and I can take you there.
-Is that really true, Tsubaki?
-Yes.
I'm almost certain.
-But--
-I beg of you!
I know Mizuki.
He has a thousand ways
to cover his tracks.
If you waste your time
searching for him,
it will all be too late!
Please, take me with you!
-Hey.
About formula nara number 23.
-What were the results?
-The ninja herb
creeping saxifrag--
-Huh?
-Who the devil are you?
[shout]
-Tatsutori inu.
MAN: The sentries
have all taken out.
An intruder!
TSUNADE: What?
The Nara clan's research
lab came under attack?
-Yes ma'am.
We just received a dispatch
from them a short while ago.
According to this, the
insurgent's physical
characteristics match
those of Mizuki's.
TSUNADE: Mizuki's?
-Yes, ma'am.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): What
is that Naruto doing?
-It was a clever move targeting
the Nara clan's institute.
Not only is there a bundle
of narcotics stored on-site,
there's practically no
security, since it's
holed up in the mountains.
What was stolen, then?
-Well, the Nara go
to great lengths
to keep track of every
substance they use.
They were able to determine
what was missing immediately.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER):
So, they do match.
But even if he's running
around with these ingredients,
what would a mere Chunin
be able to do with them?
-Oh, uh, good work.
Thank you.
That's all.
You can go.
MAN: Yes ma'am.
-Well, I'm not
taking any chances.
There's not a whole
lot I can do until I've
figured out what
his objective is.
Even if the materials
don't tell me,
there may still be a way of
getting to the bottom of this.
Perhaps the proportions of
the formula, or the order
in which they're blended.
PAKKU: You're sure
this is the way, right?
TSUBAKI: Yes.
We just have to keep
going in this direction.
IRUKA: Tsubaki, you
said before we'd
be too late if we
didn't catch Mizuki.
Does that mean you know
what his objective is?
-Probably.
Not everything, but--
NARUTO: You have to tell us
anything you can, Tsubaki.
He only talks about
one thing now.
He wishes to seek out
Orochimaru and get his hands
on the Sannin's power.
-Are you kidding me?
TSUBAKI: The whole reason he
wanted to Scroll of Sealing
back then was to give it to
Orochimaru as an offering.
-Tsbuaki, you knew of this?
TSUBAKI: I never
told the village.
Just removing the Scroll of
Sealing is a serious crime.
And I was terrified
of what would happen
if his real objective
came to light.
I was sure he would abandon
the idea, mend his ways.
PAKKUN: Then you yourself
are not free from blame.
-I'm prepared to be judged.
IRUKA: There's something
I still don't understand.
If you knew where
Mizuki was going,
you could have gone
after him on your own.
But instead, you-- you--
-I don't want to go alone.
I might not be able to stop him.
His sins-- his sins
are far too many now.
I can't allow it to
go on any longer.
-So, Orochimaru, this is
the web you're weaving?
Although, it's not something an
average shinobi could pull off.
A technique like this could
only be executed by a master.
[knocking]
-I'm busy now.
MAN: I have an update for
you on the prison break.
-Very well, then.
Enter.
MAN: Yes, ma'am.
-We've just finished rounding
up the inmates, Lady Hokage.
They're all accounted for,
with the exception of three.
Mizuki, Fujin, and Raijin.
-Good work.
-The investigation
is still ongoing.
We're trying to track
them down at the moment.
And actually, one of
the men we captured
said something that has
me concerned, ma'am.
-Concerned?
-Yes.
Apparently he saw the three
men running off together.
-Fjun and Raijin
fleeing with Mizuki?
Oh, hell!
-Lady Tsunade?
-I'm heading out.
-Wh-- Where are you going?
-There's no need
for you to come.
If what this man says is
true, the team I sent out
won't be able to handle
this situation on their own.
-We can't keep this up forever.
If we don't think of something,
we're gonna be in trouble!
-We're already in trouble.
-Shikamaru.
I'll be out of chakra
in a second here.
-Yeah, I know.
I've gone over
every angle trying
to work out a decent strategy,
but if I let go of these ogres,
we're gonna find ourselves
in a lot of hot water.
-You little brat!
-We're no match for them
once they break free.
Otherwise, I'd have
let them loose by now.
-You're dead meat!
-The stamina these guys
possess is monstrous.
-And even though they look
like 50 tons of blubber,
it's all muscle, which
means they're probably
faster than they
appear to be, too.
-In other words, all we can do
now is keep these guys tied up.
-Then we'll just have
to keep at it, huh?
-Afraid so.
-What do you think, Mizuki?
-It's no good.
He can't go on.
He's done.
-I see.
All right, then.
Let's withdraw.
Hurry.
-I'm coming.
It's unfortunate, but those who
are no use on the battlefield
only become dead
weight for the rest.
It may just be a minor
injury but if you aren't able
to get up and fight--
[wicked laughter]
-What was that?
Is this some kind of
genjutsu, or paralysis?
OROCHIMARU: I saw you.
MIZUKI: It-- it can't be.
You're-- you're Orochimaru.
-Right you are.
MIZUKI: This is impossible.
What are you doing here?
You were supposed
to have vanished.
-Why I'm here is of
little consequence.
More important, I think,
is that bit of business
I witnessed earlier.
MIZUKI: Huh?
-You took the life of your
injured comrade, didn't you?
MIZUKI: You were watching?
-That piqued my curiosity.
It's not a sight one sees very
often among the Leaf shinobi,
who seem to devote all
their time to playing
ninja in the village.
-So, what are you-- what
are you trying to say?
I-- I didn't do anything wrong.
It was the only choice I had!
-You're a short tempered
child, aren't you?
It wasn't a reproach.
You were merely carrying
out your mission.
-That's right.
-And yet, I highly doubt
anyone in the Leaf village
would acknowledge you for that.
Am I right?
-What have you done?
[chanting]
MIZUKI: What's happening?
-Consider this my gift to you.
You'll seek it out
when you are ready.
-This is it.
[boom]
-Looks like I'm the first
person to find this place.
The eighth one on the right.
Huh?
What's happening?
-What sort of power does
he seek from that madman?
-I wish that I could tell you.
I'm not even sure when he
crossed paths with Orochimaru.
But I'm positive those
answers lie ahead of us.
You must be angry, Naruto, for
what Mizuki did to you back
then.
NARUTO: I couldn't care
less at this point.
I gave that jerk what he had
coming right there on the spot.
What's done is done.
But--
-But what?
-If he's still got himself
mixed up with Orochimaru,
then I have something
I need to ask the guy,
because there's
somebody I have to find,
and no one's going
to stand in my way.
Sasuke.
-It's up ahead of us!
-Then let's get going!
-That's everything.
With this--
[wicked laughter]
-With this I'll achieve
total perfection!
Huh?
NARUTO: This place is--
[sniff]
-Oh, that guy is up
to no good in there.
The smell on the wind around
here is giving me the creeps.
-The smell?
[wicked laughter]
MIZUKI: I was
wondering who that was.
You guys sure are
persistent, huh?
This is perfect.
I was going to take
you down, anyway.
Now's my chance.
-Mizuki.
-You lousy--
-Mizuki!
Your twisted ambitions end here.
-Pompous as ever, eh, Iruka?
Too little, too late, though.
Same as always.
-What is that?
-Beautiful, isn't it?
-Oh, no!
-You know, you pathetic
ingrates should consider
it an honor to be my first prey.
[groan]
-What on earth?
-Mizuki!
-That's almost the same as--
-But you're not leaving me a
lot of choice here, Naruto.
There's no question
that you're special.
Unfortunately--
-So this is what he was after.
-Orochimaru's curse mark?
-Mizuki.
[theme music]
IRUKA: The ultimate body?
What do you mean?
How far are you willing to
go in this quest for power?
These formulas
you're dabbling in.
It's-- it's not
real power at all.
NARUTO: Ha!
Iruka-sensei is
right on the money.
So, this is one of
Orochimaru's tricks, huh?
Well, I'm putting an end to you
and your fancy little formula
right here and now!
Next time, A Clash of Fate!
You Can't Bring Me Down.
[theme music]