[theme song]
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Finally, I get the chance
to put all my training
to use on a real mission.
-They're both caught in
some sort of genjutsu.
[sobbing]
-Yakumo?
Yakumo, is that you?
Thank goodness you're alive.
-Please help me!
-It'll be all right.
I'm here now.
No matter what happens I promise
I'll make sure you're safe.
-Kurenai-sensei.
Ah.
-So the two who went in
before you haven't come out.
Perhaps Yakumo has
been awakened at last.
You deal with
Kurenai and Yakumo.
-Right.
-While they're at
it you intercept
those other pests headed this
way and take care of them.
-Yes, sir.
-Whatever happens,
leave this to me.
That crest.
You two are of the Kurama clan?
-Kurenai Yuhi, you will
hand Yakumo over to us.
-Why?
What do the Kurama
want with her?
-This concerns our clan only.
It's no business of yours.
-This child was entrusted to
my care by the third Hokage.
-Right.
Then we'll try force!
[scream]
There's no use struggling.
What the?
-She wasn't caught
in our genjutsu.
We're caught in the
genjutsu of hers!
-But then-- where is she?
-Ah!
The pain!
-You're all right!
Ah!
-If it's a fight
you want-- well, OK!
-No!
Naruto!
-Wait!
What are you doing?
-Uh-oh!
Whoa!
That is one monster bean stalk.
Can't move!
This is not good.
-Naruto.
-Now die!
-Shino!
-Your genjutsu doesn't
work on insects.
-Work on what?
No!
What are they doing?
Ah!
[muffled shouts]
-He's gone.
-Got him.
He can run and hide, but
he can't hide his scent.
Man Beast Clone!
Fang Over Fang!
See ya later.
-Severe Leaf Hurricane!
Your half-baked
genjutsu is useless
against a well-trained ninja.
-Stop it!
Let go of me, you
overgrown weed!
-Oh, good grief.
Hey, Naruto.
Release.
-Oh.
Good morning, Sakura.
Is breakfast ready?
-Why do you always rush
in like that, you idiot?
-That's right!
Yakumo and Kurenai-sensei!
Kurenai-sensei!
-Who are these guys?
They're all unconscious.
Caught in a genjutsu
from the looks of it.
-Kurenai-sensei.
You here?
Uh, Kurenai-sensei?
Hello?
Whoa, I don't get it.
What's going on?
She's not here.
-Byakugan.
-Well, what is it?
-Kurenai-sensei is gone.
KURENAI (VOICEOVER): There's
another one still after us.
Fools.
Do they think they can
use genjutsu on me?
-Release.
What?
It's not working.
-That's Unkai.
The man who was made
leader of the Kurama clan
after my father's death.
-Unkai of the Kurama.
I won't be able to outsmart
you as easily as the others,
will I?
[laughter]
-That's high praise indeed,
coming from Kurenai Yuhi.
I'm flattered.
But why don't we avoid
this battle altogether?
Just hand Yakumo over to me.
-Hang on tight.
-Don't be a fool, Kurenai Yuhi.
How do you expect to fight
when you can't escape my jutsu?
Madness!
Curse you!
I smell blood.
I've got you now.
There you are!
Why do you protect her?
Hand over Yakumo, or the next
one will pierce your heart.
-Kurenai-sensei!
-Huh?
-No one touches Kurenai-sensei.
Not while I'm around!
-Careful!
Oh, no.
Not this again.
-Oh, brother.
Naruto, when are you
ever going to learn?
-Byakugan.
Naruto!
Above you!
-So, Byakugan, is it?
-You wanna play games, OK.
Multi-shadow clone jutsu!
Attack!
-Hm.
Shadow clones, then.
-Yeah.
And they're not illusions.
They're the real thing.
Let's get him!
-Yeah!
-Let's go!
-Uzumaki Barrage!
-I swear, I will
have Yakumo yet.
-Byakugan!
-The sedative I gave
her seems to be working.
She should rest comfortably
for a while now.
But what she really needs
is a full examination
at the hospital
back in the village.
-We're lucky to have
you here, Sakura.
Thank you.
-Sensei, you need
looking after, too.
-Yes.
I think you're right.
-Let me take a look at that.
-They've been like
that the whole time.
-I don't think
they'll be waking up
from that genjutsu
for quite a while.
-Fine.
So much the better for us.
Huh?
Look.
Is that--
-Kurenai-sensei!
-Oh, there you are.
Good to see you're
all right after all.
-Yes.
-Can't you see
she's not all right?
She's been very badly
injured, and even
thought I've
treated the wound we
must get her back
to the village.
-I'll be all right.
I'm more concerned about
Yakumo's condition.
-Yes.
Especially when our enemies
might return at any moment.
And there still
remains the question
of what became of
the three ninja
we assigned to protect Yakumo.
All right.
I'll take care of things here.
The rest of you take Kurenai
and Yakumo back to the village.
Organize a backup unit.
-They're masters of genjutsu.
You gonna be all right alone?
-Are you kidding?
With this finely-tuned
lethal weapon of a body?
You think I can't handle
their genjutsu tricks?
I can handle the
jutsu wait-and-see.
Get it?
The jutsu wait-and-see?
-Oh, boy.
-Yakumo, you're awake.
How are you feeling?
I suppose you must be kind
of mad at Kurenai-sensei
for sealing your genjutsu.
-That woman-- she hates me.
She wanted to make sure I
never mastered genjutsu.
-No.
No she didn't.
-Then why?
Why?
-Search me.
But come on.
I'm sure she had a good reason.
You're wrong about her.
She doesn't hate you.
Look, she risked her life to
save you from those people,
right?
-Those people are Kurama.
We're from the same clan,
and from the same blood.
-Well-- so if they're your own
people, then why the heck--
-Kiba, will you make sure
Kurenai-sensei gets back
to the village all right?
-It's all right.
I can get back on my own.
-Kiba!
-There's something
I need to know.
Kurenai-sensei,
I want the truth.
This Yakumo business, everything
that's been going on lately--
does it have anything to do
with why you quit our squad?
-Long ago the Kurama clan was
a mighty force in the village.
For generations they
were known and respected
throughout the Leaf as masters
in the art of genjutsu.
But some years ago their
powers began to wane.
They produced fewer and
fewer chunin and jonin.
They were a clan in decline
until a bright star, full
of promise, was born-- Yakumo.
-They put their faith in me.
As the only child of the
head family, it was up to me
to restore the clan's greatness.
Unfortunately I was frail
and often sick as a child,
and it began to appear
that I might never
be allowed to enter the academy.
This made me very sad.
I truly wanted to live
up to expectations
of my parents and the clan.
Sensing my despair, my father
went to the third Hokage
and pleaded with
him on my behalf.
-The third Hokage
recognized that there
were great powers lying
dormant in Yakumo.
So he agreed to put her under
my personal supervision.
-By order of the
third Hokage I was
given Kurenai-sensei as
my own private teacher.
But she--
-What is it?
-Kurenai-sensei, she-- she--
-But why did you do it?
-I don't know.
Maybe because I
use genjutsu too.
Maybe because I was jealous
of those great powers lying
dormant in her.
-You were jealous?
-One master of genjutsu
is enough for any village.
-No way.
I can't believe that
you would really--
-Believe it.
Now you know why I quit.
Someone capable of that doesn't
deserve to lead your squad.
-No way.
Are you serious?
You're saying she--
-It's not just Kurenai-sensei.
Everyone feels the
same way about me.
The whole village.
-What are you talking about?
-I'm still not buying it.
It just doesn't smell right.
She's hiding something from us.
-Yes, I-- I have
the same feeling.
-You're both right.
I was watching her.
Her hand trembled
with emotion when
she spoke of what
she'd done to Yakumo.
She felt it deeply.
But when she explained
her motives for doing it
the trembling suddenly stopped.
-Meaning what, exactly?
-She felt nothing.
Because that pat of
her story was a lie.
-So that stuff about
being jealous of Yakumo?
-Perhaps she's trying
to protect someone else.
-Who's so important that
she'd make up a lie like that?
Who could she be protecting?
-Then one day, by
chance, I happened
to overhear Kurenai-sensei
and the third Hokage talking.
-I'm confident that Yakumo's
powers will not fully
awaken for a long while yet.
-I see.
Nevertheless, sooner
or later, the day
will come when the dam bursts.
And then the power
of the Kurama clan
will be so great that it
will threaten the Hidden Leaf
Village itself.
But by that time it may be too
late to eliminate the threat.
-So it wasn't just
Kurenai-sensei.
It was the third Hokage
who took away my powers.
-You must have heard it wrong.
Why would the third Hokage
do something like that?
-For the same reason
that right before I
began training
with Kurenai-sensei
my father and
mother were killed.
-What?
-Our house caught fire.
The flames spread quickly--
too quickly for my parents
to be saved.
But they were jonin,
alert and highly-trained.
They'd never be caught
off guard like that.
A fire that
mysteriously broke out
in broad daylight--
the investigation
rules it was an accident.
But the report was
sealed and kept secret.
I was never allowed to see it.
-What do you mean?
Are you saying the fire
was set on purpose?
-My parents were put to death
by order of the third Hokage.
-No way.
It's a lie.
A lie!
I'm not gonna listen!
[theme music]
NARUTO: Yakumo has one story.
Kurenai-sensei tells
a different one.
Which one is true?
They can't both by
lying, can they?
All I know is that the
third Hokage would never
have done that to
her, or her parents.
For now I've just gotta focus
on getting Kurenai-sensei
to the hospital.
Why?
That could be easier
said than done!
Next time--
Gentjutsu Or Reality?