[music playing]
-Kakashi Sensei, where's Sasuke?
-Kakashi, what's Naruto
Uzumaki's condition?
KAKASHI: He'll pull through.
-And Sasuke, Sasuke
Uchiha, what about him?
What happened?
-How are the other genin?
-All right.
Lady Hokage dispatched the
first and second medical corps
to pick them up.
Emergency treatment was
administered on the scene.
Then, they were all immediately
transported to the hospital.
-They were all wounded?
-Yes.
Shikamaru Nara is doing
fine, only minor injuries.
Kiba Inuzuka's are more serious,
but not life threatening.
-However, Neji Hyuga
and Choji Akimichi
are both in critical condition.
At this point, they
could go either way.
-Everyone--
[birds chirping]
[beeps]
-It's all here,
thoroughly researched.
The medications, their
effects and ingredients-- this
is excellent.
I'm going to need more
of the deer antler.
-Yes, m'lady.
-Well sis, how is he?
-Well, no long walks for him
anytime soon, that's for sure.
-Can't you do anything for him?
You're a vet.
-Not a magician, it takes time.
But relax, his
life's not in danger.
No long walks for you
anytime soon, either.
[laugh]
-I got it.
Don't worry.
[whimper]
[music playing]
-We've been at it
almost three hours.
Your turn to take over.
-OK.
We're using the boy's
own hair as a conductor,
so focus on that.
Try to accelerate the growth
rate of the injured cells.
-Right.
-As for the chakra control, just
think of threading a needle.
-Yes, I understand.
[music playing]
-No point in making
yourself crazy, you know.
Don't you remember your
psychological training?
With every mission
comes sacrifice.
SHIKAMARU: Training and reality
are two different things.
I thought I knew about missions.
I thought I knew what it
meant to be a shinobi.
Now after this mission, my
first as a squad leader,
only one thing's clear.
I'm just not cut
out to be a shinobi.
-Honestly, all you men
with such fragile egos.
-This mission, I
thought all I had to do
was depend on everybody else.
Some leader-- I
should have done more,
but I didn't have the strength.
It's all my fault.
-What, are you afraid
you might get hurt?
-Shikamaru, a girl
disrespects you like that,
and you just walk away?
-You bet I do.
Standing around arguing
is not my thing.
That's something
girls like to do.
-And what are you?
Not a man, that's for sure.
As far I can see, you're
nothing but a coward.
You think if you quit,
the missions will stop?
Someone's got to do it.
Your comrades will be sent
out again, on other missions,
with someone else leading them.
They'll face the same
risks, and some of them
might not make
it-- ones you might
have saved if you'd
been there to lead them.
How are you going to feel then?
You've got a chance to
reflect on your mistakes
and to learn from them.
Use your failures to make
yourself a better leader.
You won't help your
friends by running away.
Instead, you should be trying
to make yourself stronger,
for their sake, so that the
next mission goes perfectly
and everyone gets back safe.
The choice is simple.
You're either a
leader or a coward.
So, which are you?
[clock tick]
[sigh]
-He's going to be just fine.
The antidote worked.
The extermination of cells
caused by the pill's affects
has been arrested.
[sigh]
-I couldn't have done it
without your help, Shikaku.
The Nara clan's sacred
medicine guide was invaluable.
The work that went into that
manual, the years of research--
well, it's quite impressive,
to say the least.
-Thank you.
-Lady Tsunade--
-Huh?
[sigh]
-Neji Hyuga is safe.
His condition has stabilized.
And there's more.
I've just heard that Kakashi
Hatake and Naruto Uzumaki have
returned, and they've
been examined.
Naruto's injuries are serious,
but not life threatening.
He's going to be OK.
[music playing]
[sigh]
-Just two-- Shikamaru,
your mission was a failure.
[music playing]
-However, everyone's alive.
That's the most important thing.
[music playing]
-Next time, the mission
will go perfectly.
[wind blowing]
[laugh]
-Sasuke, you are the chosen one.
-Yeah, yeah, whatever.
When are you going
to give me the power?
-A word of advice,
watch what you
say if you want to live long.
Don't let his physical
appearance fool you.
That's still Lord Orochimaru
you're talking to you.
Ah, the-- the intensity
of his chakra.
-Yes, he's the one.
My future lies in him.
[birds chirping]
-Now, I'm going to
where Orochimaru is.
-Just bring him home.
Please bring Sasuke back to me.
-Don't you worry one bit.
I'm going to bring Sasuke back.
I promise that on
my life, Sakura.
[door opening]
-Well, well, so
you're awake, huh?
-Shikamaru!
-I was going to go check in on
Choji and see how he's doing.
How about you?
-I just thought I'd look
in on Naruto and Sasuke,
if he's there.
-I see.
Well, at least everybody's OK.
That's good.
-So, so Sasuke's--
-Yeah, he's gone.
[gasp]
-Oh.
[music playing]
-So, they're still not
letting anyone in to see him?
-No, but they say he'll
be regaining consciousness
soon enough.
He'll be all right.
-Ah, thank goodness.
-It was a fortunate day
for this village when
Lady Tsunade agreed
to come back.
If it weren't for her,
Choji would have--
-Lady Tsunade, the fifth Hokage.
-Here for a visit?
-Oh--
-News travels fast, I see.
-Huh?
-Sakura--
-Naruto--
-I had heard that your
injuries were pretty serious.
You seem to be doing
well, considering.
-I'm sorry, Sakura.
-Uh, hm, sorry?
What have you got
to be sorry about?
-Let me guess, you got reckless
and went off half-cocked again,
huh?
Look at you now.
You look like a mummy.
-I'm so sorry.
-Hey, why do you have
the curtains closed?
It's a beautiful day outside.
See?
-I haven't given up.
Listen, I'm still going
to keep my promise.
After all, it was the
promise of a lifetime, right?
I meant It.
-It's OK, Naruto.
Really--
-He tried, Sakura.
-If I say I'm going to
do it, that means I will.
OK?
Don't forget, my
way of the shinobi
means I always stand
behind what I say.
[music playing]
-Hm.
[laugh]
[music playing]
-Naruto,
[laugh]
-Thanks, Naruto.
-I've got to focus on
healing these injuries if I'm
going to bring Sasuke back.
[rumble]
-Huh?
What the heck is that?
Huh?
Pervy Sage?
-Hey there.
[crow squawk]
-What I have to tell
you is important.
It can't wait.
From now on, you're
my only student.
I need to make a full-fledged
shinobi out of you
in three years, and I'll do it.
-But why three years?
-We've received some
disturbing information
regarding the Akatsuki.
-Akatsuki--
-We've reason to believe
you've been chosen
as their next target,
and we have three or four
years before they
come after you.
-No way, that's
not going to work.
-Hm?
-I don't have time for that.
Do you think I care about what
might happen three years down
the road?
-What are you talking about?
-Orochimaru's already
got his hands on Sasuke,
and his life is in
danger, right now.
That's what I'm talking about.
-Even though immortal,
that doesn't mean his body
can maintain itself forever.
So before his flesh
decays, a strong, new body
must be made into a
vessel for his soul.
-Huh.
I see you know all
the gruesome details
of Orochimaru's little scheme.
-Huh?
Wait, you mean you
knew all about it, too?
-Well, of course.
Don't you think
I've been studying
that immortality jutsu o his.
That's also how I know our
good friend Orochimaru won't
be able to reincarnate himself
in another body for at least
three more years.
Fortunately, he ran
out of time and had
to take over another body
before Sasuke could get there.
That means Sasuke is
safe for three years.
So you do have time.
-Really are you sure
that, Pervy Sage?
Are you absolutely sure?
-Yeah.
-Ha.
[sigh]
-Forget Sasuke.
-Huh?
-You can't help him, so
just forget about him.
[gasp]
-Sasuke went to Orochimaru
of his own free will.
No matter what you do,
he will not change.
[sigh]
-I've seen many shinobi,
so I know the type.
Orochimaru and Sasuke are
cut from the same cloth.
[gasp]
-Don't delude
yourself into thinking
that you can bring him back.
You can't.
It's hopeless, a fool's errand.
-Maybe it's easy for you to
give up on him, Pervy Sage,
but I can't.
He may mean nothing to
you, but he's my friend.
-Idiot!
Just take a look at the
condition you're in,
and he's the one
who did it to you.
Was that the work of a friend?
-No, but--
[music playing]
-Why?
Why are you doing this?
You and I have been
comrades since childhood.
Together we're part of the
three legendary sannin.
[laugh]
-What a sentimental
fool you are, Jiraiya.
You always were
blind to reality.
You couldn't see,
couldn't imagine,
what I was really
doing all along.
-It's too late to
turn back, Orochimaru.
Don't do this.
[laugh]
-How'd you get to
be such a fool?
- -All my pleading
meant nothing.
He left us and
would never return.
After the pain,
all I was left with
was a sense of
helplessness and regret.
Above all, I want to
save you from going
through that, Naruto.
If you insist on
going after Sasuke,
then you'll get no
training from me.
I'll have the ANBU Black
Ops assigned to guard you,
to prevent you from
leaving the village.
[gasp]
-You're not just
some ordinary kid.
You've got something inside
you the Akatsuki want,
the nine-tailed fox.
But if you're going
to behave like a kid,
and not listen to
what I tell you,
then I'll do what I have to do.
Eventually you're going
to face enemies far worse
than Orochimaru, and it's time
you started preparing for them.
The first thing is for
you to give up on Sasuke.
What happened was
destined to happen.
Dismiss him from your
mind and move on.
To be a shinobi, you
need more than strength
and jutsu You must
acquire the judgment
to make the right decisions.
You must become smarter.
The longer you remain
a fool, the harder
it will be for you to
live in this world.
-Fine, then.
If being smarter means
what you say it does,
I'll remain a fool
my entire life.
I'm going after him.
And I'll do it
alone if I have to.
I'll create my own
incredible jutsu.
And whenever the Akatsuki
show up, I'll smack them down!
[music playing]
-The thought of my
leaving you to come up
with jutsu on your own,
like that idiotic sexy jutsu
of yours-- no, it's
too depressing.
-Hm.
-This is more than foolish.
It's so colossally foolish,
it might even work.
We've got a lot of work to do
when you get out the hospital.
So, be ready to hit
the ground running.
See you then.
-You got it!
[drips]
-Hm, how long has it
been since we've all
come together, like this?
ITACHI: Seven years, not
since Orochimaru left us.
And now Orochimaru
has the Sharingan.
-Is that true, Itachi?
Your little brother?
ITACHI: Don't be impatient, huh.
We'll deal with our old
friend Orochimaru in time, hm.
We have only three years
in which to prepare,
and we all know what we need
to do to be ready, right?
[laugh]
-Of course, no mistakes.
Remember what we
seek-- everything,
including the nine-tailed fox.
[music playing]
NARUTO: Sakura's been acting
weird ever since Sasuke left.
I can't put my finger on
it, but kind of depressed,
fidgety, anyway weird.
And now she says she
wants to go solo,
that she'll do
better on her own.
What kind of talk is that?
I don't like the way things
are going, but I'm helpless.
Meh-- of all the times to
be stuck in the hospital.
VOICEOVER: Next
time, Deep Cover?!
A Super S-Ranked Mission!
[music playing]