[theme music]
-Maybe this way.
-This Ichiraku ramen's
all the medicine
I need to get back on my feet.
Hit me with another
big bowl, would ya?
-Comin' right up.
NARUTO: I'm tellin'
ya, this stuff's
just what the doctor ordered!
[clearing throat]
-Huh?
-When you snuck out
of the hospital,
I had hoped I might at least
find you hard at work training.
-Hi there.
Hey, any of you guys hungryt?
This is ridiculous!
MIZUNE: Here you are.
That should cover his bill.
-Thanks.
Come again.
NARUTO: Come on!
Cut it out!
This is so stupid!
I'm fine, really!
I'm fine!
-You may think
you're all healed.
You may even look all healed.
But you're not all healed.
-Hold on a second here!
Who got injured, you or me?
I'm telling you
I feel all right!
And I'll never get stronger
if I don't get out and train!
-All in good time.
Just as soon as you're
completely healed.
-You don't understand.
I made a promise to Sakura.
How can I keep it if I'm in bed?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
You're pathetic, Sakura.
This is all because of you.
Naruto-- this is a once
in a lifetime request.
Just bring him home.
Please bring Sasuke back to me.
I did everything I could.
I tried, but I couldn't stop
him from leaving the village.
At this point, there's only
one person who can stop him.
Only one who can save him.
Naruto, it's all up to you.
Was that the best I could do?
Cry and beg?
I just gave up.
Put it all on Naruto.
And Naruto didn't flinch.
He risked everything to
try and bring Sasuke back.
He put his life on the line.
Now it's time I finally
did something for Sasuke.
Time I put my life on the line.
-You can save your strength.
That rope is woven
from virgin's hair,
and that knot's a shinobi
reverse butterfly.
You could struggle all
day and not get free.
-Oh, get real, will ya?
I don't have time to
lie around like this
is some kind of vacation.
I've gotta get out there and
get going and get training,
and get strong.
-The sooner you start behaving,
the sooner that'll happen.
So do what the medics tell you.
[knocking]
-Come in.
-Uh--
-Oh, hey, Sakura!
Don't worry, I
haven't forgotten.
If it was up to me I
wouldn't still be here,
but my hands are kind of tied.
-He's making a
remarkable recovery,
but he mustn't push himself.
-No, please, I keep
telling you, I'm all right!
-Lie down.
You need to rest.
[giggle]
-Oh, well.
OK, so we'll have to
wait a little longer.
But I'm still gonna keep
my promise, no matter what.
-No, Naruto.
It's OK.
-Huh?
-Up 'til now, all I've
done is rely on you.
I see now that was a mistake.
-I don't get it, Sakura.
Are you mad at me, or something?
-No, far from it.
In fact, just seeing you has
made more than I was before.
-Huh?
-It's time I started
carrying my weight.
-Oh, Sakura.
JIRAIYA: So, I
hear you snuck out.
You wanna start
training that bad, huh?
-When did you get here?
Heyt!
Pervy sage, that's mine!
-Thatta boy.
You're recovering nicely.
In fact, we could start
training any time now.
-Hey, uh, about my training?
I was wondering, you think maybe
we could hold off for a while?
-Huh?
-I mean, believe me, it isn't
like I don't want to train.
But I just remembered
that I've got a few odds
and ends to take care of first.
you know?
-Hm.
A few odds and ends, huh?
-Please.
Just for a little while?
-I know you're there.
-Oh, uh, I wasn't
sure if you were busy.
-Enough with the
peeping tom stuff.
You've got to stop trying
to sneak peeks at women.
It's a problem--
-If I wanted to sneak a peek,
it wouldn't be at an old lady.
-Excuse me?
-No, wait!
That didn't come
out quite right.
But anyway, this isn't
a personal visit.
I'm here to make a request
of you as the Hokage.
-Hm?
Well, let's hear it.
-It's time I started
carrying my weight.
-I wonder-- could
she be thinking of--
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): It may be
the last time I ever see it.
NARUTO: Sakura.
-How did you know?
I know what you're thinking.
That I'm being foolish.
That I haven't a chance of
rescuing Sasuke on my own.
But I-- I couldn't live
with myself if I didn't try.
All this time, I've let
others do everything.
And I've been
nothing but a burden.
I haven't done one thing well.
Not a single thing.
Don't try and stop me.
-Who says I want to?
You do what you gotta do.
I'm fine with that.
As long as you don't
mind me tagging along!
-No, it's just--
-There really should
be three in a squad.
But we can pretend
there are three of us.
Right?
-Right.
-Hello, you two.
-Pervy sage, what the heck?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
So that's Jiraiya.
One of the legendary Sannin.
-Of course, you two know
what will happen to you
if you cross the border
of the Leaf Village
without permission.
It means imprisonment,
and you'll
be branded forever
as rogue ninja.
-If you're here to stop
us, you can forget it.
-Quite the contrary.
-Huh?
-In fact, you've been given a
mission by Lady Hokage herself.
It's rumored that the Sound
ninja may be holding Sasuke
in the Land of Rice
Paddies, and you're
to go there and investigate.
[gasp]
-But this requires a
squad of three people.
So starting now, you two
will be serving under me.
Any problem with that?
They're fools, but
they're determined fools.
They'll go anyway.
There's nothing we can
say that will stop them.
The result will be that we'll
lose the services of two
of our most valuable Genin.
You can't let it happen!
You can save them by giving
them an official mission
to investigate the Village
Hidden in the Sound.
-Do I have any choice?
But only on one condition.
Make sure that both of
them get back alive.
Understood?
-Don't worry.
They will, even if
it means I don't.
TSUANDE (VOICEOVER):
Maybe I'm the fool.
It's a risky mission, even
with Jiraiya tagging along.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Sasuke.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER):
The Land of Rice Paddies
that holds within it
the Sound Village.
We're in Orochimaru's territory
now, so be on your guard.
-I've gotta say, so far
this is kind of a letdown.
I would've thought at least
one of Orochimaru's goons
would have met us by now.
-This isn't what I
expected it to be like.
I never thought
the Sound Village
would be so pretty and peaceful.
-Well, it's not.
Technically, we're still in
the Land of Rice Paddies.
We haven't reached
the Sound Village yet.
-So what is this place?
-A small land, nothing special.
But its ruler was one of those
fools always seeking more.
More power, more
glory, more weapons--
and more of his
neighbors' lands.
This drew Orochimaru
like a bee to honey,
and he poured sweet words
into the fool's ear,
making him all
sorts of promises.
Of course, Orochimaru
had no intention
of making the fool any stronger.
He only seeks to make
himself stronger in order
to achieve his revenge.
You may not see any visible
signs of his presence
in this land, but
Orochimaru is here.
-So, what now, Pervy Sage?
-Will you please
stop calling me that?
-That's right.
He's one of the
Legendary Sannin.
Show some respect.
-Trust me.
When you get to
know him, you'll see
he's just a lazy old pervert.
That's all.
-What did he just say?
-Come on, let's get to it.
So, where is the Hidden
Sound Village, anyway?
-I don't know.
Bears the heck out of me.
That's the main reason we've
been sent on this mission.
To find it.
-Oh, yeah.
I see your point.
-Well then, how are
we going to find it?
-First we gather information
by finding the nearest town.
Every land has a
town where people
gather for rest and recreation.
-Uh-oh.
What did I tell ya?
He's up to his old tricks again.
Sooner or later, every
mission's about the ladies.
-There's nothing like a
town full of pretty girls
to take a man's mind
off his troubles.
So the first thing to do is
to go find ourselves a town!
-Well, it's a town.
But not much of one.
-There's nobody here.
It's been abandoned.
-Oh, there's people
here, all right.
Can't you smell
all that perfume?
OK, kid.
Hand it over.
-What?
-You know how it works.
Gathering information
costs money.
-So that's it.
You're after Gama again.
-This is it?
This is all you got?
No way.
Cough up the rest.
Oh, yeah?
Trying to hold out on me, huh?
1, 2, 3.
Aw, you're kidding.
This is really all you got?
-Yeah!
You cleaned me otu!
That's it!
SAKURA: Here's some more.
-Huh?
-It's not a whole lot,
but if it'll help.
-Gah!
Sakura, keep your money!
You don't have to
give it to him!
-I want to pay my share.
It's for the good of
the mission, right?
-Oh, absolutely.
Mission, right, yeah, right.
You two stay out of this.
Go around the town and wait
for me on the other side.
-Huh?
What the heck for?
-It's too dangerous
where I'm going.
This is a job for grown ups.
Ah-ha.
That perfume is
coming from in here.
-Welcome, stranger.
-Get a load of this fool
with the crazy hair.
-Well, they saw a fool and
his money are soon parted.
-Food and drink!
I'm in the mood for some fun.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
-It's always the same.
You're wasting your money
by giving it to him.
All that about buying
information's a crock.
He just wants to
have a good time.
-What do you mean, a good time?
-Oh, well, you know.
What grown ups do when
they-- actually, I'm
not sure what he does, exactly.
-Whatever.
It doesn't matter.
I had to try and help.
I'm tired of being the only
one who never does anything.
-Hm?
Sakura, what are
you talking about?
It's only because of you that
we're even on this mission!
It it weren't for you, I'd still
be tied to that stupid hospital
bed.
JIRAIYA: What are you
doing in a place like this?
Oh, not that I'm complaining.
A pretty face is a
welcome sight anywhere!
-Why don't you come in the
back and we'll show you?
-Yeah, let's go some place where
we can get more comfortable.
-Oh, well, I uh--
-First thing's first.
There's the little matter
of settling your bill.
-That's mine?
You sure you don't have
too many zeroes there?
Say, this wouldn't be some
kinda rip off joint, would it?
-Ha ha.
That's a very funny joke.
-Pay up, old man.
Everything you've got
if you want to live.
-Guess the joke's on me.
-Boy, it's been a long time.
What could be keeping him?
-Who knows?
But I'm getting
tired of waiting.
[rustling]
-Watch out!
-Who's in there?
Start talking, buddy.
Who are you?
Another one of
Orochimaru's hitmen?
-Did I get it wrong?
-To get that close
to us, he must've
somehow cloaked his presence.
-Well, he's not getting away!
-Wait!
Don't move, Naruto!
-What do you mean, don't move?
-Spikes, at your feet!
JIRAIYA: Naruto!
-What is it now?
[shouting]
-What in the world
is that all about?
-Uh, Pervy Sage!
What have you been up to now?
-I'll tell you about it later.
Right now, let's
just get out of here!
-Who are those guys?
-Maybe they're friends
of that other one!
-Well, if they're more
of Orochimaru's gang,
I'll hit them with my
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
JIRAIYA: No!
Don't use jutsu on
them, whatever you do!
They're nothing!
Just friends of some wicked
women I met in a tavern!
-You were in a bar?
-Skip it!
The main thing is,
this was supposed
to be a secret mission!
So we can't blow our cover by
using our ninja art on them!
Just run!
-The bags!
You're doing a great job of
keeping our secret mission
a secret, Pervy Sage!
-Let's go!
Less talk and more action!
Run, run!
-This is terrible.
What have I got myself into?
We're never gonna
find Sasuke this way!
[theme music]
-This town looks even
worse than the last one.
You two wait here
while I check it out.
-Oh not again.
JIRAIYA: It's far too dangerous.
It's no place for kids.
-Kids?
Now wait a second.
JIRAIYA: No, no.
I promised I wouldn't let
anything happen to you.
If there's going to be any
risk, I'm the one to face it,
understood?
NARUTO: Yeah, yeah,
trying to sound all noble.
I know what you're up to.
The only risk we face is you
making a fool of yourself
again!
Next time, a Town of Outlaws!
The Shadow of the Fuma Clan!
[theme music]