[music playing]
[theme music]
-I'm not going to run away.
I never go back on my word.
That's my nindo.
-You've just thrown it all away.
Dreams don't come
true when you're dead.
-Just get out of
the way, Naruto.
No.
Look out.
-Get ready to pay up on our bet.
That cursed necklace of
yours is about to be mine.
Until I become Hokage, I
don't care what happens.
I am not going to die.
OK.
Let's see you
dodge me this time.
Here goes.
-That's impossible.
NARUTO: "The Fifth Hokage.
A Life on the Line."
Rasengan!
-What's this?
JARAIYA (VOICEOVER): Well,
well, the kid actually did it.
OROCHIMARU (VOICEOVER): A child
mastering a jutsu like that.
It's unheard of.
-It's impossible, but he did it.
He actually mastered the
Rasengan in one week.
-And you?
How can you be
standing after that?
-I focused my chakra
at the point of impact.
Before he'd even hit me,
I'd started healing myself.
You see now why Lord
Orochimaru values me so highly,
not only for my skills
and knowledge of jutsu,
but most of all for my
recuperative powers.
No matter how
great the injury, I
can repair and re-energize
any damaged cells.
But there is a limit, and
I'm almost out of chakra.
Naruto, on the other hand,
doesn't have that gift.
He looks finished.
What?
No.
I never thought, even
with my healing powers,
the damage was too great.
And now I haven't
enough chakra left.
[heart beating]
-His heart is failing.
the muscles surrounding his
heart have been torn to shreds.
How the heck did
it happen and when?
Wait, of course.
That moment just
before they separated.
Kabuto must have
struck at his heart.
Stop shaking.
Get a grip.
[groan]
-How about it, Gamakichi?
Do we have to wait
for the kid to croak
before we get our snacks?
I'm getting hungry.
-Zip it, or I'll make
sure you definitely croak.
-You're wasting your time.
It's all over for him.
With my last strength, I severed
his heart's chakra network.
I cut him off from
getting any help
from the demon, the
Nine-Tailed Fox.
And he hasn't the
power to save himself.
I'm telling you.
He's finished.
Dead.
All your skills are useless now.
TSUNADE: Oh, shut up.
You'll be dead soon.
I'll see to that.
He stopped breathing.
No.
KURAMA: Dark.
It's getting dark.
The light is fading.
My strength fading.
Why?
What?
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): No.
Don't die.
Don't die. [gasp]
-Hey.
Don't forget our bet.
Told you, I'd win.
-He's still alive?
-To be Hokage.
That's still your
dream, Naruto, isn't it?
One more time.
Just one more time
for the last time.
I want those words to be true.
-Poor boy.
I really don't
think he'll make it.
-You're forgetting
Tsunade's healing powers.
Don't worry about him.
She'll have him back up
on his feet in no time.
-Perhaps so, but that's
not what I meant.
-Hm.
Forget Naruto.
I'd focus on me if I were you.
I'm the one you
have to worry about.
OROCHIMARU (VOICEOVER): There's
far more to this little genin
than meets the eye.
There's no telling
what might happen
if the Akatsuki get
their hands on him.
But if he were to die right now.
What the devil?
-He's coming for the boy.
[groaning]
-Tsunade, you are the one
person I wouldn't want to kill.
Listen to me.
If that brat is
allowed to live, it
will mean more trouble
than you and your friends
could ever imagine.
Stay out of my way.
-No.
You listen to me.
If I do nothing else, I
will protect this boy.
-Ha.
And how do you plan to do that?
Look at you.
Your body is shivering
like a leaf in the wind.
Besides, why would
you, one of the Sannin,
risk your life to
save a lowly genin?
-By saving him,
I'm saving my home,
the Village Hidden
in the Leaves.
-You really think you're
protecting the village?
-You see, this boy,
this lowly little genin,
has been chosen by fate
to be Hokage someday.
-[laughing] What nonsense.
Even if it is true, what of it?
Who cares about the Hokage?
Only a fool would want that job.
-Playing at Hokage.
It's just a fool's game.
SHIZUNE: Think of my
uncle and your brother.
It would be a betrayal of
them, a betrayal of yourself.
Have you forgotten
all your dreams?
-Remember the Hokage that
have come before and all
they've accomplished
for the Leaf Village.
They were willing to gamble
everything, even their lives
to make sure the village
survived and prospered
through troubled times.
-I won't let her do it.
She can't sit there and
make fun of the old man.
I don't care if she is a lady.
I'll knock that
sneer off her face.
-From now on, I'm
gambling everything too.
I'm putting my life on the line.
-Well, if you're really
willing to throw your life away
for the sake of one
insignificant brat,
I'm happy to accommodate you.
Now all that's left
is Naruto himself.
-Lady Tsunade.
JARAIYA (VOICEOVER):
Not enough time.
OROCHIMARU (VOICEOVER):
She's torn to ribbons,
and she can still
move that quickly.
Hm.
You really are
determined, aren't you?
I'm impressed.
-Didn't I make it
clear enough, you fool?
I meant what I said.
I will die before I
let you touch him.
-You're half dead already.
Ha.
Such brave talk.
But look at you, you're
still trembling all over.
Poor thing.
You just can't shake your
fear of blood, can you?
You see how pointless
it is, and all for what?
For the sake of an obnoxious
little boy you don't even know?
For the sake of a
worthless village
you left behind years ago?
What?
No.
You stopped the trembling.
How?
-I finally remembered something.
I've been chosen as the Fifth
Hokage of the Leaf Village.
-Wha-- what's that mark?
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER): She's
overcome her fear at last.
But that mark.
-Whatever you call yourself,
it makes no difference.
You may have conquered
your inner weakness.
But what about the rest of you?
You can hardly expect to
defeat me in your condition.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): Ha.
-No.
Lady Tsunade, wait.
Let me treat your wounds.
Please, don't break the seal.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER):
Reserve Seal Release.
Ninja Art Mitotic Regeneration.
OROCHIMARU (VOICEOVER):
What jutsu is this?
[laughing] It seems
I'm not the only person
who's been spending their
time discovering new jutsu.
This one's very impressive.
How's it done?
-My chakra, for
years, I've stored it
up in a space
behind my forehead,
saving it for just
such an occasion.
With this chakra reservoir,
my body's ability
to create new cells
is accelerated.
The cells divide rapidly,
spreading throughout my body
and regenerating
any damaged organs.
It's like having the ability
to reincarnate myself.
You see you can slash your
way at me all you want,
but I can't be killed.
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER):
What she doesn't
say is that a person, any
person, even her, can only
generate new cells a
limited number of times.
If you speed that up,
you shorten your life.
Lady Tsunade!
KABUTO (VOICEOVER): Oh no.
That can only mean--
Lord Orochimaru!
JARAIYA (VOICEOVER):
Quickly come out!
Come out!
-Do it.
Hurry!
-Ino, inu, saru, tori, hitsuji.
-(ALL TOGETHER) Summoning jutsu.
[theme music]
JARAIYA: We have walked very
different paths, Orochimaru,
but today, our
paths meet at last.
It's time to end it.
You are no longer fit
to walk among men.
OROCHIMARU: [laughing] You make
that sound like a bad thing.
Mankind, the very word
fills me with loathing.
TSUNADE: You've
grinned your last.
After today, there will be
one less Sannin in the world.
NARUTO: Next time, "Deadlock.
Sannin Showdown."