-Tad-ah!
[laughs]
So you know what time it is?
Golden time!
That's right.
Starting tonight, in
fact, starting right now,
"Naruto" moves to
a brand-new time,
every Wednesday night at 7:27.
-Hey, excuse me, boss.
-This is your lucky day!
I mean, night.
Whether you're a longtime
devoted fan or just
tuning in for the
very first time.
So now, here to get
the party started
is our brand-new theme song.
-I'm trying to
tell you something!
-Jeez, Konohamaru,
what's your problem?
Can't you see the
show is starting?
-Psst.
(WHISPERS) It's only
7 o'clock, Naruto.
-Huh?
-You're 27 minutes early.
This is actually the time slot
for the "Prince of Tennis."
-Oh, great!
Now, you tell me?
What a disaster!
What are we going to do?
I already told everybody!
-Don't look at me.
-I can't just, ugh!
Ahh!
The hell with it.
So without further
ado, it's "Naruto."
-Hey, Sakura, Sasuke!
Don't look now, but Naruto
just went and opened the show.
You guys ready?
SAKURA: No way!
I still have my facial mask on.
Stall them!
-Do we even have the
video for this episode?
-No, it hasn't arrived yet.
-Terrific.
Well, I guess I could
do my ninja dance.
But I was saving
that for next season.
On second thought,
I'll go get the video.
You guys will have to fill time.
-What?
-Think of it as a mission.
You can do it.
-Hm.
A "mission," huh?
Since you put it that way.
-Yes!
Just leave it to us, Sensei.
-"Yes," huh?
You are the one who got
us into this, you idiot!
You and your big mouth!
Sometimes, I just want to--
in fact, I think I'll do it!
-[groans]
-Oh, that's good.
Keep it up.
[theme music]
-Whoa, nice place.
What is it?
-This is the location for
the second phase of the exam.
It's the 44th Battle
Training Zone.
But we call it the
Forest of Death.
-The Forest of Death?
[rustling]
Hm?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Fake rocks?
What's up with that?
-Uh!
[panting]
That's the worst
disguise of all time.
There's no such things
as square rocks.
It's completely obvious.
KID: You saw through
my camouflage again!
You're slick, boss.
Just what I'd expect
from my greatest rival.
-Haah!
[coughing]
-I think we used a little
too much gunpowder, you guys.
KIDS: Huh?
-I'm Moegi, the sassiest
kunoichi in preschool.
Check me out!
-I love algebra.
Call me Udon.
-And I'm the number 1
ninja in the village.
Konohamaru!
And when we're all together--
KIDS: --we're the
Konohamaru Ninja Squad!
-Yeah, I knew it was
you guys the whole time.
What do you losers want?
I'm getting ready to take the
second phase of the Chunin
Exam, and you're
interrupting me.
I don't have any time to be
playing around with you guys
now.
-We didn't come to
play around, boss.
We're on official business.
-Yeah, that's right.
We came here for an
exclusive interview.
-Uh-huh.
Uh-huh.
-An interview, huh?
-We're here on
assignment to write
an article for the
academy's newspaper.
It's a big-time feature story,
all about the Chunin Selection
Examinations.
-So that's why we want to do an
exclusive interview with you.
Please tell us you're
going to do it?
-It would mean a lot.
-Humph.
Yeah, but right now, [grunts]
FEMALE SPEAKER:
Hey, you over there!
-Huh?
FEMALE SPEAKER:
What are you doing?
You're holding up the exams.
-Uh, sorry.
But Konohamaru was
telling me something
about an interview for
the academy newspaper.
-[gasp]
Oh, yeah, I forgot all about it.
Lord Hokage had
mentioned something
about them interviewing me.
-Uhh, interviewing you?
-All right, we're taking
a 10-minute break.
For those that are
scheduled to be interviewed,
please be courteous
and respectful
to reporters from the
academy newspaper.
-I thought I was the only
one being interviewed?
-No, boss.
But you are the most important.
-Oh, well, in that
case, I'll give you
an interview that'll make
it clear to your readers
why I'm the greatest ninja ever!
"Special Report, Live
from the Forest of Death."
KONOHAMARU: "Naruto and
the Rest of Squad 7."
All right, boss, first tell us
a little bit about yourself.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): OK.
-Believe it.
I'm Naruto Uzumaki.
I like instant ramen in a cup.
And I really like the
ramen Iruka-sensei
got me at the
Ichiraku Noodle Shop.
My hobby is eating
different kinds of ramen
and comparing them.
And my future dream is to
be the greatest Hokage!
Then the whole village
will stop disrespecting me
and start treating me like I'm
somebody-- somebody important.
No other Genin can
match any of my jutsu.
Even Iruka-sensei can't
help being impressed.
-Congratulations.
You graduate.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): And
now that I'm in Squad 7,
I get to prove it by going on
dangerous missions every day.
-What's your distance
from the target?
-5 meters.
I'm ready.
Just give the signal.
-I'm ready, too.
-So am I.
-Now!
-Ugh!
Yaah!
[cat snarls]
I got him!
Aah!
Ow!
KAKASHI (ON RADIO): Can you
verify the ribbon on right ear?
-[yelps]
-Affirmative.
We got a positive ID.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): The
other Genin in Squad 7
are Sasuke and Sakura.
But since I'm really
the only one that
shows any kind of promise, you
don't need to hear about them.
KONOHAMARU: Well, do it anyway.
You know, for the article?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): OK, OK.
Sasuke Uchiha is a
real pretentious guy.
All the girls think he's cool.
But they don't realize
how big a jerk he is.
-Close, really close.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Anyway, he's always
swooping in at the last
minute and making me look bad.
But one day, I'll show him.
There's also Sakura Haruno.
I'll let you in on
a little secret.
She's madly in love with me.
She'd never admit it, of course.
But I think her coyness
just makes her even cuter.
-That's it!
-Aargh!
-Boss!
Aw, what kind of
girlfriend are you?
-Get real!
In your dreams, buddy!
Rrrh!
KONOHAMARU: It
doesn't sound to me
like she's in love
with you, boss.
NARUTO: (SARCASTIC) Ha-ha-ha.
Very funny, Konohamaru.
But trust me, she is.
Anyway, putting that
aside, our squad
is a well-oiled machine
that can succeed
in any mission, no
matter how dangerous.
-[grunts]
[laughs]
WOMAN: Hey, you!
-Hm?
Oh, hi, lady.
I got rid of all your weeds.
Pretty cool, huh?
Uh, what's wrong?
-You pulled the weeds.
And you also pulled
up my plants.
-Huh?
WOMAN: Those were special
herbs I've been growing.
And you destroyed them!
[thumps]
NARUTO: Ow!
Ow!
Aah!
-Huh?
-Gaah!
Gaah!
Haah!
Aah!
-You are such a loser.
NARUTO: Hey, hey!
Not there!
We're supposed to
go the other way.
Ugh!
Hey!
I'm talking to you! [grunts]
-What a loser.
-[sighs] Of course.
He just has to choose
the biggest dog.
-Aah!
MOEGI: These are
dangerous missions?
-That's not a place for dogs!
It's a minefield!
[yelping]
-[sighs]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Of
course, I wasn't always
busy on dangerous missions.
I still had time to teach
the Hokage a thing or two.
-We can't accept this photo.
-Ugh, transform!
[giggles]
Pretty please, Lord Hokage?
-Argh!
KONOHAMARU: I don't
think this material is
appropriate for the article.
-Fine, what do you
want to talk about?
KONOHAMARU: How about the
first time you met me?
-Hm?
-Uh.
-Old man, I challenge you!
-Huh!
-I'm going to defeat you
and become the Fifth Hokage!
Waah!
KONOHAMARU (VOICEOVER):
My name is Konohamaru.
I'm the grandson of
the Third Hokage.
That means he's the
top ninja in town.
The Fourth Hokage
was the greatest hero
this village has ever known.
He protected our home
from the Nine-Tailed Fox.
And he's still
revered to this day.
-What's the matter, huh?
I thought you were going
to hit me, tough guy.
Afraid because the Third
Hokage is my grandfather?
-I don't care if he's
your grandmother!
Believe it!
-Uh!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Don't
forget Iruka-sensei.
He was the only one
who is nice to me.
And I sure did drive him crazy.
Me, Naruto, the next Hokage.
A ninja legend!
Then everyone will have
to stop disrespecting me
and look up to me.
Believe it!
IRUKA: Naruto.
-Hm?
-Why would you do that
to the Hokage faces?
-Got you!
That's my Sexy Jutsu.
-Cut the stupid tricks!
KONOHAMARU: The whole article
can't be about you, boss.
-Oh, I guess you're
right, Konohamaru.
I suppose I could tell you
a few stories about how
Sasuke screwed up.
-I've already heard
that story, boss.
Can't you talk about
anyone but you?
-I'm sure Naruto is just
talking about himself
over there with those kids.
I'll bet he never
even mentions us.
-Hm, that would
be just like him.
-The incredibly
cool Kakashi here.
What's the situation?
-The lovely Sakura here.
We've been letting the
idiotic Naruto fill time.
-So how are things
going on your end?
Are we going to have it in time?
-Oh, don't worry.
At the pace I'm going,
everything will be OK.
I should be there with
the video by the end
of the next commercial break.
I hope.
-Well, you better be.
-Kakashi-sensei?
Yoo-hoo!
Are you there?
Well, what are we
going to do now?
It's the end of the commercial
break, and he's not back yet.
-I guess it looks
like you're just
going to have to fill
the time, Sakura.
-Me?
Why do I have to do it?
-Yeah, go for it, Sakura!
-I'd shut up if I were
you, you little-- OK, fine!
I will, since I guess
I have no choice.
MOEGI (VOICEOVER): "The
Art of Being a Ninja."
Tell us about Sakura Haruno.
She's a kunoichi who
I really look up to.
She's got what it takes
to be a top female ninja.
-Notice the interplay between
physical and spiritual power.
That's the key.
Finally, the hand signs
focus and unleash the chakra.
-Transform.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Moegi, if you
want to know the truth
about Naruto, talk to me.
I'll tell you about
his different ninjutsu
without all the bragging.
First, there's his Sexy Jutsu.
-Shadow Clone Jutsu!
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Shadow clones?
Who can handle
that many Narutos.
There's also his Harem Jutsu.
-Transform!
NARUTO CLONES: Transform!
Transform!
[girl clones giggling]
-[whimpers]
-Aah!
[groans]
-Got you with my Harem Jutsu.
[snickers]
-Naruto!
-That's what he gets
for coming late.
Surprise!
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): But
most of the time, Naruto
is just being Naruto.
[sighs] Huh?
Which is not a good thing.
What I really want to talk
about is the number 1 rookie,
Sasuke Uchiha.
Not only did he graduate as
the academy's top student,
but he's also the most
popular guy in class.
He can even hold his
own with Kakashi-sensei.
I mean, he's so cool.
Oh, my!
I think I'm going
to faint. [giggles]
-There's no point
using normal attacks.
-[grunts]
-A trap!
What?
-Eyah!
Haah!
-This kid.
-Horse, Tiger Fire Style!
Fireball Jutsu!
-What?
Can he?
He can't do fire jutsu.
It takes too much chakra.
There's no way!
-Demon Wind Shuriken!
Windmill of Shadows!
-A shuriken?
He'll never touch me with that.
-Aah!
I've been waiting
to try this out.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Huh!
Could it be?
Is it a Sharingan?
ROCK LEE (VOICEOVER): So
that is the Sharingan.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Uhh, you'll never
know what Sasuke will do next.
He's amazing!
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
Genjutsu or ninjutsu.
Whatever magic he's
using, I'll see it now!
-[grunts]
I can't get loose.
-Uhh.
-[grunts]
NARUTO: Your tribute
to the great Sasuke
is putting everyone
to sleep, Sakura.
SAKURA: Quiet, Naruto.
NARUTO: Ugh!
Ow!
-Oh, admit it, Sasuke!
You care about me!
-I, uh, guess that's true.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): I
can't keep up with Sasuke.
I can't even beat Naruto.
I'll never pass these exams.
Let me tell you
about our sensei,
Kakashi Hatake, also
known as the Copy Ninja.
He uses his Sharingan eye to
assess the enemy's technique
and then copy it in an instant.
He's copied over 1,000 jutsu.
But he's always
reading his dumb book.
And whenever he's supposed to
meet us early in the morning,
he's always late.
Plus, like everyone else, Naruto
really gets on his nerves.
-Huh!
-Leaf Village
Secret Finger Jutsu!
-Naah!
[thump]
[groans]
-A Thousand Years of Death!
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): But
the biggest mystery of all
is his face hidden
under that mask.
I wonder what he
really looks like.
-Ninja Art, Summoning Earth
Style Fanged Pursuit Jutsu!
-Aargh!
-I realized if I couldn't see
you, I'd have to smell you out.
That was a summoning jutsu.
I was calling forth
my ninja hounds
that can track a scent anywhere.
Ah, the mist is
finally clearing.
And you know what I see?
Your corpse.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
I wonder, why is it
only his left eye have
the Sharingan power?
I thought it was an inherited
trait exclusive to the Uchiha
clan.
-Lightning Blade!
-His chakra is so
strong, it's visible!
He holds it in his hand.
-I won't allow you
to kill Tazuna.
-Ah, fool.
Water Prison Jutsu!
-No!
-Secret Jutsu.
-[gasp]
-Crystal Ice Mirrors!
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): There
are plenty of other ninjutsu
that other ninja can do as well.
In fact, there are so many
different types and styles
that I don't have the
time to explain them
all in this short interview.
UDON: "Rival Ninja."
Boy, Sasuke!
You're the coolest.
When I look at you,
I feel like I'm
looking at my future
self. [chuckles]
Do you mind if I get
a few quotes from you
for our article?
-Well, I guess I ought to
set the record straight.
If you listen to
Naruto, your article
will be more fairy
tale than truth.
-Oh, no, you don't, Sasuke.
They came here to
interview me, not you.
-They came here to
interview everyone, loser.
There are other
ninja here, you know.
Believe it!
-[grunts]
-The article's about me!
-Nobody cares about you, Naruto.
All you do is goof off
and get in trouble.
That's why you'll
never be a real ninja.
-Oh, yeah?
-Yeah.
Don't you remember anything?
Hey, you!
Identify yourself.
The guy with the
gourd on his back.
-My name is Gaara of the Desert.
I'm curious about you, too.
Who are you?
-I am Sasuke Uchiha.
-Hey, you.
Over here.
What's your name?
I want to know.
-Hm?
Rrrh!
Again?
It's always about Sasuke!
-It's common courtesy to give
your own name before asking
someone else's.
BOY: Hey, you with the attitude.
Hold on!
ALL: Huh?
-I want to fight, right
here and right now.
-I get him first.
This weirdo is mine.
-No, thank you.
Right now, the only one I
want to fight is Uchiha.
-Yeah?
Well, I've got news for you.
Sasuke can't compare to me.
Believe it!
Aah!
[grunts]
Ugh!
-Leaf Whirlwind!
-Aah!
[groans]
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
The students taking
the Chunin Exams are
all highly skilled.
And every one of
them is considered
to be the cream of the
crop, except for Naruto.
NARUTO: Hey!
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): Shikamaru
Nara, Choji Akimichi,
Ino Yamanaka, Hinata Hyuga,
Kiba Inuzuka with Akamaru,
and Shino Aburame.
Each one of them is talented
in their own unique way.
But I'm still better than
all of them combined.
NARUTO: Yeah, right.
That's why you got your
butt kicked by Rock Lee
because you're better than him?
You shouldn't be talking.
Even you screwed up
from time to time.
SASUKE: I'm going
to screw you up
if you don't watch it, Naruto.
NARUTO: Go for it!
Let's settle this
once and for all.
SAKURA: Guys, will you cool it?
Listen, we passed the first
phase of the Chunin Exam.
And we're about to enter
the Forest of Death
for the second phase.
I don't know what's
waiting for us in there.
But no matter what lies
ahead, we won't be afraid.
And we'll pass the
exam to become Chunin
because Kakashi-sensei
taught us to work as a team.
And nothing can break that bond.
Right, guys?
-Yeah, I guess your right.
-Teamwork, right.
-We really want to
thank all of you.
That was a great interview.
-Yeah, thanks.
-Knock them dead on
the Chunin Exam, boss.
-Don't worry, guys.
We'll make it.
KIDS: See you!
Bye!
See you later!
You're the best!
-Hey, guys!
Sorry I'm late.
I bumped into a very
cute young lady.
And naturally, she wanted
to go dancing with me.
-(IN UNISON) Yeah right!
-You don't believe me?
Humph.
Anyway, I got the video.
Do I, at least, get
some thanks for that?
-Way to go, Kakashi-sensei!
Better late than never.
OK, let's start the show, huh?
-Right, after this
commercial message.
-Aah! [groans]
[music - Rythem, "Harmonia"]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): The
44th Battle Training Zone,
also known as the
Forest of Death.
From here on, it's a serious
battle between the ninja.
Anything could happen.
[laughs] Oh, yeah!
This is getting interesting.
A life-threatening survival
game in the forest.
I'm going to come out on top.
Next time, "The Chunin Exam,
Stage 2-- the Forest of Death."
I'm going to shine once again.