[theme music]
-So that's your plan?
To destroy our village?
It ain't gonna happen.
Not on my watch.
You've got that?
-Exactly.
Four of you against
our entire village?
Dream on.
-You'd be shocked at
what we can pull off.
-He's right.
Man, it's gonna be a cinch.
A certain somebody told us
all the best places to attack.
-But who would know
something like that?
-No way!
Orochimaru told you, huh?
-Maybe, maybe not.
-You know, now that
you've heard the plan,
I guess we can't risk having
you spoil our surprise.
-There we go.
You see them?
HINATA: Paper bombs
are everywhere!
-Indeed.
And we're going to
detonate the lot of them
as soon as we've left.
-There's nowhere to run, and
nobody's gonna come save you,
so forget it.
Enjoy the stalactites.
-Well, at least you're not
heading back to the Academy,
right?
-Rest in peace.
Or pieces, I guess.
-Hold on!
Just wait a second!
-Gotta run.
Thanks for the face.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Run Dog Zig-Zag!
Chase or Be Chased!
-All we had to do was
find the dumb treasure.
Should have been a
total walk in the park.
Get stuck on a
mission with Naruto
and even the easy
stuff will kill you.
-Save the complaining for later!
Those fakers are trying
to mess up the Leaf,
and everybody in
the village is gonna
think we're the ones who did it!
-I know.
So how do we get out of
here, you big genius?
-Well, guess I
could use Rasengan.
-Ha!
What, like they
wouldn't notice that?
Geez, come on.
Then they'd ambush
us outside instead.
-I know!
How about Fang Over Fang?
-Same deal.
They would notice!
Moron.
NARUTO: Fine!
You got any bright ideas?
-Um.
There's my protective
eight trigrams.
-Good call.
We can use it to
survive the cave in
and those posers outside
will be none the wiser.
-If only these ropes were a
little bit looser, then maybe.
NARUTO: Just leave them to me!
They're "knot" a problem.
Get it?
-Can you do it?
-All right, here goes!
-Kiba.
Even Akamaru.
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
Just a little more.
We did it!
[barking]
-Here I go.
Protective Eight Trigrams!
64 Palms!
-Well, shall we head
back to the village?
Kiba!
-Uh, huh.
-Hinata.
-Yes, sir.
-Naruto.
-You better believe it!
-Hinata!
Holding up OK?
Hm.
Guess not.
-OK.
Here's an idea.
How about you cut
our ropes first,
then you can faint all you want.
[whine]
-K.
-Sounds pretty quiet out there.
I guess those guys hit the road.
Check it out.
This isn't going
to hold for long.
I vote we get out of this
cave while we still can.
[barking]
-What's that?
-Jackpot!
The treasure chest!
-Leave it alone.
It was just bait to get
us out here, remember?
The thing might be booby
trapped for all we know.
-Yeah, yeah.
But it's our mission to
bring it back either way.
And what if there
is treasure in it?
Then the joke's on them.
-Byakugan!
It looks empty inside.
No, wait.
There's a piece of paper.
-Another paper bomb, right?
-Whatever's in there
doesn't seem dangerous.
NARUTO: In that case,
I'm gonna take it!
-Come on.
Why are you even
bothering with that thing?
HINATA: Wait a second.
That chest might come in handy.
The fake Naruto
doesn't have one.
-Yeah, you're right.
Akamaru, you're
gonna be what lets
these guys know I'm the real me.
Stick to me like glue, OK?
[barking]
[crumbling]
-This cave is toast.
I'm gonna use Fang over
Fang to burrow our way out.
Don't fall behind.
-OK.
I won't.
Man Beast Clone.
Fang Over Fang!
NARUTO: You OK, Hinata?
-Don't worry about me.
Like he said, all I have to
do is make sure I keep up.
I'm OK.
-Hey!
Hinata!
-Yahoo!
-(HOWLING) Yahoo!
-That was close.
you're not hurt, right?
-I'm sorry!
-Leg still giving you trouble?
-I'm fine.
-Hey, now.
Be honest.
If your leg hurts,
tell us already.
-I didn't wanna complain
and slow down the team.
-Yeah, and how's
that working for you?
-I-- I didn't mean to--
-Seriously.
This is the very
thing that makes
us not so hot as a team, guys.
-Huh?
-Hinata worries too much
about the two of us.
Meanwhile, Naruto and I always
end up growling at each other.
-Huh.
Now that you mention it.
-If we kept stuff
like that in mind
while we're out on
missions, I think
we'd grow into a pretty
awesome trio, don't you?
-Hey, it's worth a try.
-Yeah, you're right.
-OK.
Those guys need to be stopped.
Naruto and I can handle that.
Meanwhile, you head
back at your own pace.
Be careful.
Your leg is still
injured, so don't push it.
-I won't overdo it.
-Here's the plan.
Head home at your own
pace, but be careful.
That leg is still
hurt, you know.
-Didn't I just tell her that?
Were you paying attention--
-What was that?
I zoned out.
-Thanks, Naruto.
-Come on, idea boy.
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
I won't let you down.
-I'm home!
-Hey!
You're back already?
-So they already got here?
-Kiba?
Naruto?
-I know how this sounds,
but did I come through here?
-Yeah, just now.
-All those guys were imposters!
-What did you say?
-But our ninja
hound didn't notice.
They're so good, not
even ninja hounds
can smell the difference.
They smelled Akamaru, too.
[bark]
-This is bad.
We gotta tell the Hokage.
-Right.
-Akamaru.
You remember how that tricky
old Agari guy smells, don't you?
[bark]
-Do your thing!
-Lady Tsunade.
-Huh?
-We have a crisis on our hands.
-They all think I'm
that little spaz.
-Don't pat yourself
on the back too hard.
Remember, this mission
ain't over 'til it's over.
-Right you are, and the
next step is crucial.
-Someone's coming.
-Huh?
-Afternoon, fakers.
Did you miss us?
-The fakes are gonna
get some real pain.
-Well.
So, you're still alive?
-You figure that
out all by yourself?
-Save yourselves a whole
lot of hurt and give up now.
Look around.
This isn't some cave.
This is our home turf.
-Even the local favorites
get tossed a curve ball
once in awhile!
-You're not getting away!
Hey.
Wait!
It's Hinata!
-Course it is.
I'm gonna go tell the Hokage.
Meanwhile, you should
stop those imposters.
-Good idea!
I'll catch you la--
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): We left the
real Hinata back in the woods,
so I'm really holding the
hand of some random girl.
Gotcha, little miss faker!
-How dare you take
a swing at her?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Fake me's defending
fake her from real me?
That makes my head hurt.
KIBA: Naruto!
Dude, what are you doing?
-Huh?
That isn't--
-Don't listen to him!
He's an imposter!
-Wh-- Wha--
-Well, how about that?
Here comes!
-No!
Wait, hey!
I'm the real deal!
I swear!
-But this guy isn't!
Maybe you can copy how we
look, and sound, and smell,
but you can't fake
our ninjutsu, can you?
Let's go, Akamaru.
[bark]
-Fang Over--
-He's out cold?
-Aw, that sucks!
I didn't punch hard or
use jutsu or anything.
-Hey, know what?
I slugged me pretty
good and hard just now,
but I don't feel like
I took one to the face.
-Hey you!
Attacking the village was
your big plan, wasn't it?
Fat chance.
You guys are total weaklings.
-See you!
-I can handle the fake Hinata.
You go get yourself
under control!
-Right.
Just leave me to me!
-Come back here!
[barking]
-Plat time's over!
Stop running already!
-I wonder if I checked
out too many books.
Something maybe
you'd like to say?
Like, oh, I don't know, sorry!
-Check it out!
Landed right on your
butt, 'cause it's
the biggest part of you!
Butt queen!
All hail the butt queen!
And that forehead.
More like a
fivehead, am I right?
-By the time I'm done with
you, Naruto, you won't a butt,
'cause I'm gonna kick
it all over the village!
-Sakura!
Get out of the way!
-Naruto!
Shut up!
-What's that for?
-Wait a minute.
If Naruto ran off
in that direction,
how'd he get back
over there so quickly?
-I'm off on a delivery!
MAN: Right.
Be careful.
-Dammit!
-What happened?
Are you all right, Ayame?
-Yeah.
Naruto just tumbled in
and spooked me a little.
-He what?
Naruto!
You spooked my daughter.
How dare you?
-But Sakura--
-Calm down.
I'm OK, daddy.
Really.
-No, no.
You rest up.
You've been through a lot.
I'm sure Naruto here will
be more than happy to make
the delivery for you.
-What?
You know, I'm kinda busy
saving the village right now!
-You will deliver
this food, or you
can kiss my ramen
goodbye forever!
-Sure!
Yeah!
Great!
It's not like I'm doing
anything else, right?
All done!
Have fun!
Gotta run!
MAN: All's forgiven, then!
-Thanks!
Back to finding that faker!
He could be anywhere by now!
-Another weakling.
That's two out of two.
-Don't hurt me.
Kiba.
I'm sorry.
-Do us both a favor and
can the puppy dog eyes.
That might work on a
push over like Naruto.
But I hate that stuff!
These wimps thought they were
really gonna take out the Leaf?
-Where you hiding?
You big, fake, fraidy cat!
Show that handsome face already!
Come on!
-Oh no you don't.
-Let me guess.
I stopped by earlier,
ate a bunch of good?
-That's right.
You did.
Really packed it in.
Now you're gonna
settle this bill.
-That face stealing jerk.
He went through 45 servings?
Here.
[crying]
-He dined and dashed all
over the village as me.
I hate that faker.
The only thing he's messing with
around here is my reputation
and all my places to eat!
Oh, no.
No!
[belch]
-No!
Not all my Golden
delicious Pure Heart
of Fire Ninja Way
Ramen I've been saving!
I'm not letting this fly!
You eat my special ramen,
you've crossed the line!
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
[shouting]
-Where is he?
Where's that face
stealing ramen thief?
I'm taking that ramen
out of your hide!
[angry shouting]
-This'll do for now.
Just put it on my tab!
-There he is!
-Hm?
Hm?
Yah!
-Now I gotcha!
-Hey, stop that!
[shouting]
-Calm down, already!
The impostor doesn't have a
chest strapped to his back,
so look for that guy!
-Hey, maybe he's right.
-Yeah, he is.
We all have chests.
-So who doesn't?
-That guy!
[scream]
[beating]
-When it was all said
and done, these four
were nothing worth
breaking a sweat over.
-No kidding.
Think these chuckleheads are
really Orochimaru's henchmen?
-Who knows.
I'm sure the Hokage will
tell us if they are, though.
-That's true.
Man, I'm beat.
Carting this chest around all
day was tough on my shoulders.
[bark]
-Hm?
-Huh?
-Naruto, Kiba!
Is that you?
-Cool.
Looks like Hinata
finally made it home.
-Hey, Hina!
We caught all the fakers!
-Good.
So it is them.
There's no chest on his back.
Which means this Naruto
is-- the impostor!
Gentle Fist!
-I'd hate to be the real
Naruto right about now.
[bark]
-Oh, boy.
ALL: What?
-It was a test?
-That's right.
The real objective
of this mission
was to see whether
you three could
work effectively
together as a team.
-Depending on the
task, a shinobi
will often be teamed up
with a variety of people.
Sometimes they may be your
friends, and sometimes not.
But once you're
out on assignment,
there isn't time for infighting.
Grudges become a luxury
you can no longer afford.
I gave you a mission that seemed
easy enough in the beginning,
but got harder.
And I tossed in a threat to
the village along the way
to up the ante.
When the chips
were down, I wanted
to see if you would pull
together for a common goal.
-So it wasn't real?
-Harsh, grandma.
-Some lesson.
We could have been
killed out there.
What's that about?
[laughter]
-No.
You were safe.
Lady Tsunade was very specific
about the amount of risk
to which I could subject you.
At the worst, you'd
have gone home
with some cuts and bruises.
-Since I knew Kiba
would have Akamaru,
I enlisted the help
of the Kedoin clan.
With their hidden jutsu,
their transformations
are dead on, down to
the slightest detail.
Well, how'd they do?
Back to the Academy?
-Hm.
Let me see.
They got off to a
very shaky start.
The mission was practically
over before it began.
But they managed to
capture us in the end,
so I'm pleased to
say I've decided
to give them all
a passing grade.
-Oh, yeah.
Tah-dah.
-That's the--
-Yep.
One buried treasure chest,
just like you ordered.
Check it out.
Mission accomplished, grandma.
-Honestly, you
shouldn't have bothered.
-On the contrary, I'm
glad he brought it here.
There's something in there
for you, Lady Tsunade.
A document of the
greatest significance.
-See you around, Naruto.
Nice meeting you.
-Yeah, you too.
-Take it easy.
-Right.
NARUTO: What do you think?
Are they going to
look like us forever?
-Naw.
Fake me was saying his face
will switch back to normal
in a couple of days.
-That's cool.
TSUNDADE: But-- but this is a--
a bill for the recent training?
Look at this.
He told me he'd be more
than happy to help out.
Where does he get off
charging us this much?
-If it isn't one
thing, it's another.
-My name is Tsunade,
and every day I
wrestle with a debt
that keeps growing.
-So now we have one more.
TSUNADE: When I
agreed to be Hokage,
what the heck was I thinking?
[theme music]
-No!
It's gone, gone, gone!
Where did you pt it, Naruto?
-Oh, that?
I slapped it in an envelope.
JIRAIYA: You did what?
-And I gave it to
a delivery ninja.
-You gave it to who?
-So they should be
receiving it today.
Cool, huh?
-You idiot.
At this rate, my life
as a writer is ruined!
-Whatever.
Let's get cracking with
the training, already.
JIRAIYA: Shut up and
follow me, Naruto.
We have to get that envelope
back, no matter what the cost!
NARUTO: Next time,
Please, Mister Postman!