[theme music]
-[yawning]
[grunts]
[rooster crowing]
Hm.
OK, wake up.
Here we go.
Rock and roll!
I'm ready!
A new chapter begins.
"The Chunin Exam."
[running footsteps]
-Huh!
Uhh.
-Hey, good morning, Sakura.
What's up?
Hm.
Humph.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Good grief.
Not again.
They've been like this
ever since we got back
from the Land of Waves.
[sighs]
It's like being stuck
with a couple of children.
Cha!
Hurry up Kakashi-sensei!
You've had it!
[thumping]
-Hey, guys.
Good morning.
Sorry, I'm late.
Afraid I got lost
on the path of life.
-(IN UNISON) Gaah!
-I'm ready for the next
ninja mission, Sensei.
And hey, come on.
No more of this dumb
beginner stuff, OK?
I want a chance to prove myself.
I'm talking a real mission where
I could show what I'm made of.
Aah!
I got to break out
and burn it up!
See?
-Uh, right.
I get it.
That's great, Naruto.
Now, take it easy, would you?
-[snarls]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Sasuke!
He's always rescuing
everyone on our missions,
trying to grab all the glory,
and make me look like a chump.
But he'll never
get the edge on me!
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
He's such a twerp!
-[growls]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Today is the day.
-Ugh.
-Huh!
Hah!
What's the matter?
Can't take care of
yourself, Sasuke?
Believe it!
KAKASHI: Let us know when you're
done fantasizing, Naruto, so we
can start the mission.
All right?
NARUTO: Right!
SAKURA: Could you not
be so annoying, Naruto,
just for once?
-Well, I'm going to
beat Sasuke anyway.
[grunts]
[laughs]
WOMAN: Hey, you!
-Hm?
Oh, hi, lady.
I got rid of all your weeds.
Pretty cool, huh?
Uh, what's wrong?
-You pulled the weeds, and
you also pulled up my plants.
-Huh?
-Those were special
herbs I've been growing,
and you destroyed them!
[thumps]
NARUTO: Ow!
Ow!
Aah!
[both gasp]
No!
Haah!
[yelps]
-You are such a loser.
-[grunts]
Hey!
Not there.
We're supposed to
go the other way!
[grunts]
Hey!
I'm talking to you!
Gaah!
Damn it!
-Oh, what a loser.
-[sighs] Of course!
He just has to choose
the biggest dog.
-Stop pulling, would you?
You're not supposed
to go over there!
[grunts]
That's not a place for dogs.
That's a minefield.
[yelps]
Aah!
[both sigh]
[groaning]
-Look at you.
You're hopeless, Naruto.
-[sighs]
You really are just
one big problem.
-[grunts]
Sasuke!
Ow!
-If you keep this up, I'll
finish you off myself!
-[sighs]
Guess we're not making
a lot of progress
on the teamwork thing, huh?
-That's right!
Our teamwork's all messed up.
And it's all because
of you, Sasuke!
You think you're better
than everyone else?
-Not everyone, just you.
Face it.
I'm better and
stronger than you are.
It's a fact.
Unless you have what it
takes to prove me wrong.
-[grunts]
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): They're
actually getting along
worse than before,
if that's possible.
-[grunts]
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
I don't have time
to waste on Naruto and
these lame missions.
There's still ninja out
there who can outfight me.
I've got to hone my
skills, so I can beat them.
-All right, guys.
Let's call it a day.
You can beat each other
to a pulp some other time.
Anyway, I have to file my
report on this mission.
-Whatever.
I'm out of here.
-[gasp] Wait!
Sasuke, I'll go with you!
-Uh!
Ah, ah.
[sighs]
-So why don't we--
I mean, you know,
let's do something
more personal.
I mean, to improve
our teamwork and all.
-I swear, you're just
as bad as Naruto.
-[gasp]
[grunts]
-Instead of flirting, why
don't you practice your jutsu
and make the team stronger?
Let's face it, you're
actually worse than Naruto.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
Worse than Naruto.
-[grunts]
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): He's right.
What have I really done so
far on any of our missions?
Nothing.
Sad!
-Don't worry, Sakura.
Just forget about Sasuke.
You and me can develop
our teamwork all day.
-[grunts]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Huh?
Sensei disappeared.
Is he giving us some alone time?
[rustling]
Huh?
Fake rocks?
What's up with that?
-[panting]
That's the worse
disguise of all time.
There's no such thing
as square rocks.
It's completely obvious!
KID: You saw through
my camouflage again.
You're slick, boss.
Just what I'd expect
from my greatest rival.
-[gasp]
[kids coughing]
-I think we used a little
too much gunpowder, you guys.
-I'm Moegi.
The sassiest kunoichi
in preschool.
Check me out!
-I love algebra.
Call me Udon!
-And I'm the number 1
ninja in the village.
Konohamaru!
And when we're all together--
ALL: --we're the
Konohamaru Ninja Squad!
-Yeah, I knew it
was you, Konohamaru.
Hm, hey, what are those things?
Those goggles you're
wearing on your head?
-[laughs]
You used to wear
goggles, remember?
So we're copying you!
-[grunts]
-Hey, come on, boss.
Why are you being like that?
You ought to be more excited!
-So did you want something?
-He's just trying to be cool.
-You know what we want.
Are you busy now?
-Hm, I have to train.
Believe it!
-What?
But you promised that you
will play ninja with us today.
Come on!
-Uh, he-he.
Oh, did I say that?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Uh,
if I say yes, these kids
will keep bugging me all day.
And I won't get
any training done.
-[sighs] A ninja playing ninja?
That is so twisted.
-Uhh.
Hey, Sakura.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): My ninja
skills are worse than his?
Unbelievable!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Uhh,
she's staring right at me.
I think I'm turning red.
[nervous laughter]
-Hey, boss.
Who's that girl anyway?
[grunts]
KONOHAMARU (VOICEOVER): The
way she's staring at him,
it's like her eyes are daggers.
-Ah!
I get it.
You're a smooth operator, boss.
-Uhh.
-Come on, I know that
she's your girlfriend.
-Huh?
-[chuckles]
Well, you could tell she's
really crazy about me, huh?
-[shrieks]
-Boss!
-[groans]
-[heaving]
-(ANGRILY) What kind
of girlfriend are you?
-I think she crapped him.
-Oh, no!
We got to check his pulse.
-[groans]
-You're a witch!
And you're ugly, too!
-[snarls]
-Huh?
Aah!
[shrieks]
[thump]
-Humph.
-[groans]
-Hey, Konohamaru, are you OK?
[boys groaning]
-I don't even think she's human.
Did you see how wide
her forehead is?
[all gasp]
[all whimper]
[shrieks]
[thump]
-Aah!
Ugh!
Huh?
-Do you need something?
-Huh?
-Uhh.
-All right.
Thanks for the report,
Kakashi-sensei.
How's Naruto doing?
Is he getting along OK
with the other students?
-Hm?
Well, uh, little by little.
-It's been so busy around here.
I haven't seen him since he
got back from the mission
to the Land of Waves.
I'm a little worried about him.
-Uh, you know, Sasuke
is also in our group.
Naruto sees him
as a rival, which
puts a constant
strain on the group.
But it also pushes
Naruto to excel.
So he's making amazing progress.
Someday, his skills
may be so strong,
they'll match the person he
respects most in the world--
you.
-You don't say. [chuckles]
[kids panting]
-Huh?
Huh.
KURENAI (VOICEOVER):
Hmm, I wonder.
ASUMA (VOICEOVER): Hm.
Now?
-Hm.
-Konohamaru!
-So does this hurt, punk?
-[grunts]
-Put him down, Kankuro.
Or you know you'll
pay for it later.
-Hey, I'm sorry.
The whole thing was my fault.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
Who are they?
What are they?
-You better take your
hands off him right now!
KANKURO (VOICEOVER): So these
are the Leaf Village's Genin.
-We got a few minutes
before he gets here.
Let's mess with
these punks, huh?
-[grunts]
Let go of me, you jerk!
-You're feisty,
but not for long.
-[grunts]
-[snarling]
Put him down!
Aah!
What the-- what was that?
-You're a Leaf Genin, too?
Looks like your village
is full of wimps.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): They are
outsiders from somewhere.
But what are they doing here?
-Uhh, Konohamaru!
-Konohamaru!
-Hey, cut it out.
It hurts!
-That's it!
Drop him now, or
I take you apart.
You got that, fool!
-You're the fool!
Making threats isn't
going to help, Naruto.
-You're annoying.
All of you.
I don't like runts or any
other scrawny weaklings.
So when a wimp like this
starts shooting off his mouth--
-Ow!
---I just want to
break him in half.
[both gasp]
[both whimper]
-[sighs] Fine.
I'm not involved
in any of this, OK?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
What's this guy's problem?
This is getting ugly.
-First, I'll take care
of this little squirt.
Then I'll waste the other one.
-Nooo!
-Agh!
Uhh.
-Ugh.
Huh?
Huh.
[grunts]
-You're a long way from home,
and you're way out your league.
-Sasuke!
-[moans]
TEMARI (VOICEOVER): Well, well!
Local hottie.
-Naruto!
-Oh, great.
Another wimp to tick me off.
-Get lost.
-[shrieks] So cool!
-Hmm.
-How come you're
not cool like that?
Huh?
-What do you mean?
I could have taken that guy
out in two seconds flat.
-Humph.
-[snarls]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Sasuke, you're
always trying to make me look
bad in front of everyone!
[growls]
-Hey, punk, get down here.
You're the kind of pesky
little snot I hate the most.
All attitude and
nothing to back it up.
-What?
Are you going to use
the Crow for this?
-Kankuro, back off.
-Uh.
[all gasp]
You're an embarrassment
to our village.
-Huh!
-Uh.
-Huh.
-Uh, ah, hey, Gaara.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
How did he get there?
He didn't make a sound.
Only Jonin at Kakashi's
level are that smooth.
MALE SPEAKER: I
have summoned you
for a very important purpose.
Seeing your fellow
Jonin here, I'm
sure you realize
what this is about.
-So soon?
I thought we'd have
a little more time.
-I'd take it all
the other lands have
been notified about
the coming event.
I know that some of
their Genin have already
arrived here in the village.
-And when do we start?
-We will begin in one week.
-That's pretty short notice.
-Take heed.
Exactly seven days from
today, on the 1st day of July,
the Genin will be
gathered and tested.
Only the very best will
be selected as Jonin.
THEME SONG: Cultivate your
hunger before you idealize.
Motivate your anger to
make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain,
never coming down.
Break into the contents,
never falling down.
My knee is still
shaking, like I was 12.
Sneaking out of the
classroom by the backdoor.
A man railed at me twice,
though, but I didn't care.
Waiting is wasting
for people like me.
Don't try to live so wise.
Don't cry 'cause
you're so right.
Don't try with fakes
or fears 'cause you
will hate yourself in the end.
Don't try to live so wise.
Don't cry 'cause
you're so right.
Don't try with fakes
or fears 'cause you
will hate yourself in the end.
Don't try to live so wise.
Don't cry 'cause
you're so right.
Don't try with--
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): All right!
It's time for the Chunin Exam.
If I pass the test, I
won't be a Genin anymore.
I'll be one giant step
closer to becoming Hokage.
No way I can fail, right?
Hey, who snatched Moegi?
What the heck are they up to?
Come back here!
You're not getting away!
Next time, "Identify Yourself,
Powerful New Rivals."
It doesn't matter who shows up.
I'll beat them all!