[theme song]
-What a drag.
Gotta admit.
That wasn't bad.
Timing was perfect.
You got all three of 'em
right where you wanted 'em.
that's quite a tricky tune.
Something like that must
take a lot of practice.
-It does actually.
So you figured out I
was manipulating them
with my flute.
You're not as dumb as you look.
Not that it'll do you any good.
Knowing what I've
been doing isn't
the same as knowing
how to stop me.
-You've got a point there.
I never was very musical.
Just ask my mom and dad.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
With that flute
she can manipulate her
buddies like puppets.
That song's comprised
of sequences
of modulated sound waves,
each sequence controlling
a specific movement.
Great, Shikamaru.
You can analyze
it fine, but what
are you going to do
to counteract it.
[chuckling]
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
She's right.
The fact remains.
I've got no ear for music.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Fake out!
Shikamaru's Comeback!
-All right.
If that's what you want, I'll
show you the Camellia Dance.
-What are you waiting for?
-You shouldn't be
making brash statements
like that when you
can't follow through.
-Just shut up!
-Hmph.
-How'd he do that?
-I already told you.
This piece of bone
is harder than steel.
Maybe you would like
me to demonstrate
just how strong it is.
[grunting]
[shout]
-Damn it!
-No one's ever heard
this song and lived.
Here's the finale, ninth
passage-- Demon Revolution.
[flute plays]
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
She changed the tune.
Here they come.
What's happening?
What's he doing?
Wait for it.
TAYUYA (VOICEOVER):
The instant he
realizes my material ghosts are
about to attack he evades them
He's smarter than I thought.
But--
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): I had
to use almost all my paper
and smokebombs back there.
And all I managed
to do was hide.
That white thing, it took a
bite of my physical energy.
That shuriken passed
right through him.
These things are
more like apparitions
with very little mass.
They're chakra itself,
but with an appetite.
Probably some kind
of chakra that
draws its form from
eating mental energy.
That's why they crave
physical energy.
It keeps them stable.
If I scuffle with those
hungry chakra much longer,
I won't be able to
build up my own chakra.
They're are pretty dangerous.
A ninja who can create
special chakra like me?
She must be using
some obscure ninjutsu.
Which means I should leave
those ghost things alone
and concentrate on the
one controlling them.
The quickest way would
be to go and stop
the sound of her flute.
But with those things
around it would
be impossible to
get close enough.
OK then.
The next best option would
be to capture those to three
with my Shadow Position Jutsu.
But that's not going to
happen since they never
attack me at the same moment.
If I let even one escape, he'd
get to me and that would be it.
Game over.
She hasn't left me any openings
on either offense or defense.
Heh.
She must be a pretty
good Shougi player.
Let's see.
My remaining ninja tools are
12 kunai knives, 9 shuriken,
36 feet of wire, one flash
bomb and one paper bomb.
Heh.
Oh man.
It's like playing Shougi
without any bishops or rooks.
-Did I lose 'em?
Guess that's not possible.
Akamaru!
Here you go, boy.
You should eat this.
If you don't need anything, you
won't get your strength back.
Stay with me, Akamaru.
Let's move out.
We've gotta catch
up with the others.
-Behold, the Camellia Dance.
TAYUYA (VOICEOVER):
There's no use hiding.
Unless you can predict
these guys' movements,
there's no where you
can run, little rat.
And when I find you,
I'll break you in two.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
All right.
It's time.
Everything's ready.
The only thing left is
to get it over with.
I've got nine moves.
I've got to win by then.
-Game on.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
That's one.
TAYUYA (VOICEOVER): Oh please.
My sound jutsu can't
be stopped that easily.
Whatever you've got planned to
beat me, it's not gonna work.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): Two.
TAYUYA (VOICEOVER): Now
he's scampering around
like a little rat.
Where is he?
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): Three.
[gasp]
TAYUYA (VOICEOVER):
So he's over there.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
Here's four.
TAYUYA (VOICEOVER): Cheap trick.
You can't fool me.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
Five, six, seven, eight.
TAYUYA (VOICEOVER): Scurrying
around all over the forest.
What does he think he's doing?
Huh?
Light bomb?
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): Nine.
TAYUYA (VOICEOVER): Damn!
He's making shadows
with the flashbomb.
SHIKAMARU: Shadow
Possession Jutsu!
Shadow Possession
Jutsu complete.
-Wait.
But how?
How were you able to
predict my guys' movements?
There's no way
someone like you could
have heard the
slight differences
in my musical patterns.
-That's just it.
I wasn't listening to the
music patterns at all.
Can't you think
of something other
than the melody that would give
away your command patterns?
That's right.
Your fingers.
-It can't be.
TAYUYA (VOICEOVER): He
could tell their moves
by-- he's saying he memorized
my finger positions?
-There's no way.
That's impossible.
-You extend your right index
finger and ring finger.
Then you place the
middle finger and pinkie
on your left hand the same way.
That sound seems to make the
crab man stand at the ready.
When you press with your
right thumb and index finger,
and move your left
index finger and pinkie,
that causes the big guy
with the club to charge.
While you were wasting all your
time dodging my knife attacks
and trying to locate
me, I was observing
each and every one
of your finger moves
and studying how these
thugs reacted to them.
Analyzes and memorized.
Don't even try.
They're bound by my
Shadow Possession Jutsu.
There's one rule of Shougi
that I always enjoyed the most.
Whenever you capture one
of your enemy's pieces
you can turn around
and use it as your own.
From here on I attack.
I'll use your own three
pieces to hunt you down.
What do you have
to say about that?
Shouldn't you be a
bit more worried?
You could at least pull
a knife or something.
-This flute is my only weapon.
I told you.
Not one person who has heard
the sound of this flute
has survived, idiot.
-You've got a lot of confidence.
-Dispel!
-Huh?
-What was all that about using
my own pieces against me?
Loser.
-Aw.
Aw!
-It's my move now, you rat.
What the?
-Heh.
Shadow Possession success.
What did I tell you?
I'd hunt you down
using your own pieces.
I used them all right.
Your three pawns were
just the bait I needed.
In any good strategy, the first
attack's always a fakeout.
The tactic is to score
on the second move.
-You bastard.
-Yep.
TAYUYA (VOICEOVER):
There's no other way.
Now that it's come to this,
I'll need to summon more power.
I didn't think I'd need
to go to second state
with a chump like him.
It ticks me off.
But I've got to admit.
For a little punk this
guy was pretty impressive.
-What's this?
She changed?
-Up until this
point, you might have
thought you were pretty
sharp as a fighter.
But from here on, things won't
go according to your plan.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
What is she?
No way.
Is she strong enough
to force herself out
of the Shadow Possession Jutsu?
What's up with this
tremendous chakra?
My jutsu's going
to to fall apart.
I can't worry about
conserving chakra.
I have use my other jutsu.
Ninja Art.
Shadow Strangle Jutsu!
TAYUYA (VOICEOVER):
Is he choking my body
with that shadow?
It feels just like I'm being
grabbed by a real hand.
-I am not letting you beat me.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): Darn it.
She's got incredible strength.
At this distance I
can't hold on to her.
TAYUYA (VOICEOVER): Take this.
Demon Flute.
Chains of Fantasia.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
This is bad.
Is this a genjutsu?
[groan]
-Hah.
What's he trying to do?
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
My body-- I can't move.
[groaning]
[screaming]
TAYUYA (VOICEOVER): When
I'm at second state,
my flute can unleashed
all kinds of genjutsu.
Of all of them, this
one's particularly
appropriate for that rat.
That's because--
[screaming]
TAYUYA (VOICEOVER): This
genjutsu paralyzes its prey
and traps it like vermin.
-Tell me.
How's it feel to
be the one tied up?
So, you said this was your
final move, didn't you?
Unfortunately, it's checkmate.
Die little rat!
[thud]
[groan]
-How did you?
TAYUYA (VOICEOVER): What?
He broke his own
finger with his shadow?
The pain is caused must
have broken the genjutsu?
This whole time
he kept pretending
to be trapped by the jutsu.
-I already told you this.
The first attack's
always a fake.
It's basic strategy.
The second move wins the match.
You might have
noticed my second was
a little different from before.
With the Shadow Strangle Jutsu,
the closer I am to my opponent,
the stronger might
hold on him will be.
-Darn it.
I got careless and
came too close.
-No.
That's not what did it.
It was actually something
you said to me earlier.
About how your only
weapon was this flute.
Don't you remember?
-Shouldn't you be
a bit more worried?
You could at least pull
a knife or something.
-This flute is my only weapon.
I told you.
Not one person who's heard
the sound of this flute
has survived, idiot.
-So that's why.
-Exactly.
The reason I threw my last kunai
knife right in front of you?
I missed on purpose.
You said you didn't
have any other weapons.
So I knew all along
that you would
pick it up and
come closer to me.
Hmph.
[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): No way.
This is ridiculous.
Am I having a crazy
dream or something?
No.
it's way too intense
to be a dream.
That suit with its outstanding
ventilation and supple fit.
Those eyes.
That hair.
Those eyebrows!
You!
What are you doing here?
Next time-- The
Leaf's Handsome Devil.