[theme music]
-Gentle Fist Art.
Eight Trigrams, 64 Palms!
Augh!
Eight Trigrams, Two Palms!
-Ahh!
-Four Palms!
[smacking]
-Eight Palms!
16 Palms!
32 Palms!
64 Palms!
[cracking]
[thud]
NEJI: What's going on?
Huh?
[cracking]
NEJI: The surface of his body--
[shattering]
NEJI: It's the same
material as that weapon
he spit from his mouth.
--[chuckling] Well,
well, that was close.
I know if I take just one
direct hit from that Gentle
Fist of yours, my whole chakra
network goes out of whack.
You keep me on my toes, kid.
-That material, where does
it come from, you monster?
-Impressive, yes?
My sticky spider thread is
actually a type of metal
that hardens the instant
it leaves my body.
It's impervious to chakra.
And, what's more, not only can
I secret it from my mouth as
you've seen, but from every
sweat gland in my body.
NEJI: That explains it.
No wonder my attacks on his
chakra points have no effect.
MALE SPEAKER: The spider
web net won't work on him,
and close-range
combat is suicide
against that Gentle Fist of is.
I'll just have to
keep my distance
and look for a blind spot.
-Huh?
[wind rustling trees]
MALE SPEAKER: It'll come
in a flash without a sound.
[shing]
MALE SPEAKER: Game over.
[slicing]
NEJI: The knife's just a ploy.
MALE SPEAKER: What?
-Eight Trigrams, Rotation!
[clinking]
[thunking]
MALE SPEAKER He-- he repelled
my attack with his chakra!
But how?
How did he see it coming?
Does he have eyes in
the back of his head?
[whooshing]
-We're going to go one on one
to have any chance for success.
Isn't that what you said?
Now get going!
I'll be right behind you.
NARUTO: We're gonna
have to go one on one.
-Naruto.
Sometimes your eyes are
even better than mine.
NARUTO: Come on, Neji.
You hurry and catch
up with us, got it?
[whoosh]
MALE SPEAKER: No way!
Can he actually see me?
What kind of a
freak is this guy?
-I know you're there.
Come out.
MALE SPEAKER: It's those eyes.
The chakra flow is not the
only thing they can see.
The power of his visual
jutsu is beyond belief!
NEJI: Long distance combat
is not to my advantage.
I've got to get
closer to him somehow.
MALE SPEAKER: OK, then!
I give you credit.
You've made this game
more of a challenge
than I thought it would be.
Time to start playing for real.
NEJI: He's like a totally
different opponent!
His chakra activity's
staggering!
And those markings.
MALE SPEAKER: So, this guy's
able to see me in the dark
and to dodge an
attack from behind.
In other words, he's got
360-degree X-ray vision.
On top of that,
there's that jutsu.
All right.
Summoning Jutsu!
-Nngh.
-I warned you, kid.
However strong
your defenses are,
I can find a way around it.
If he can block the
physical attacks
by emitting lots of chakra and
rotating, then all I have to do
is to stop that rotation.
Scatter!
-Nngh.
Rotation!
-[chuckling] There.
That slowed him down.
-Nngh.
-Now!
Now you die!
[growling] He slowed my dagger
with chakra at the last second!
NEJI: Neh.
What?
His web stopped my rotation.
Our chakra canceled
each other out!
Hmm.
Enough of this.
If my Rotation Jutsu
won't work, I'll
just have to cut the
threads one by one!
MALE SPEAKER: His strength
is close-range taijutsu.
So as long as I keep my
distance, I'm all right.
Just keep pounding away at him.
I've got all the
time in the world.
[chuckling]
[thunking]
-Nngh.
[cringe]
-Eight Trigrams, 64 Palms!
[thudding]
NEJI: There's no end to them!
MALE SPEAKER: Huh?
He changed his stance.
-Eight Trigrams, 128 Palms!
[thudding]
MALE SPEAKER: What?
The number of blows has doubled!
If he gets the chance to use
that on me, I'm finished.
Well, if it's a numbers
game, two can play at that!
[roars]
[spiders chattering]
[thudding]
NEJI: There's too many of
them, and not enough time!
Just as I thought!
The Rotation won't work!
[slicing]
-Aaugh!
MALE SPEAKER: Huh?
-Guh.
MALE SPEAKER: So
that's how it is!
He's been anticipating
my attacks
by combining his X-ray vision
with telescopic long-range
vision, as well as a
360-degree line of sight.
Add to all that his
lightning-fast reflexes
and this kid's got an almost
impenetrable defensive barrier.
Judging from his reaction
time during that last attack,
he's able to see and
react to the kunai knives
once they get within 50
meters of his position,
but not quite all.
Somehow or another, one
of them got through.
And that means
there's a blind spot!
-Eight Trigrams, 64-- aaugh!
-Yeah.
Just as I thought.
[breathing heavily]
--[laughing diabolically]
Now more!
[slicing]
MALE SPEAKER: This time
two should get through.
[thudding]
-Aaugh!
Nngh.
[thump]
--[laughing diabolically] I
told you I'd find a way around
your defenses!
Actually, right
through your defenses!
All those fancy moves of yours,
they're all just an attempt
to hide your blind
spot, aren't they?
Those eyes don't quite
see everything, do they?
[grunts]
-Am I supposed to be impressed?
Why bother?
The game's over!
[labored breathing]
-What is the point?
What the heck do you
hope to accomplish?
Don't make this messier
than it has to be!
Just roll over and
die, why don't you!
You can't beat me!
[gasping]
[thunk]
LEE: I am not finished yet!
--[sighing] Lee, you just don't
know when to give up, do you?
You're never going
to able to beat him
because Neji's
something you're not.
He's a genius.
-A genius?
I do not care what he is!
Even without his
talent, I can still
take him if I just
work hard enough.
-It's no use, Lee.
-Huh?
-It doesn't matter how hard you
work, you will never beat me.
The outcome has been decided.
Hinata, you are the
pampered offspring
of the Hyuga's main branch.
People can't change, no
matter how hard they try.
This match is the same.
Your destiny was
decided the moment
I was chosen as your opponent.
-Oh yeah?
Well, we won't know that
until you beat me, will we?
[heavy breathing]
MALE SPEAKER: Time
to wrap this up.
[shing]
[roars]
[crashing]
-[chuckling] Huh?
[thud]
NEJI: Gentle Fist!
-Aaugh!
-Eeyah!
[thud]
-Perfect.
That's one pest
down, three to go.
-Nngh.
[slicing]
MALE SPEAKER: I
actually enjoyed myself,
even though the ending
was predictable.
Hmm?
-Nngh.
[gasping]
MALE SPEAKER: [chuckling] That
many hits from that distance
and he's still standing?
I'll have to work on my aim.
This kid is something else.
He's turning out to be a lot
more entertaining than I ever
dreamed!
I'll have to demonstrate
my appreciation.
[cracking]
-I don't expect much
from that slob, Jirobo,
but what the heck
is keeping Kidomaru?
He shoulda caught up by now.
-You know how we always plays
about with his opponents.
He likes to keep things fun.
-Gives me the creeps
when he does that.
Too much fun and he goes off his
head and reaches Second State.
-[chuckling] Oh, indeed.
And when Kidomaru
reaches Second State,
watch out if you're
the other guy.
[labored breathing]
--[growling] Striking Accuracy,
100% Destructive Power Maximum!
Die!
[whoosh]
NEJI: There's no
wasted effort with him!
He learns something
from every attack,
and then uses what
he learns against me!
Even my Byakugan is
no secret to him.
This is the strongest
opponent I've ever faced.
I've hit the wall.
His next attack
could be the last.
I haven't the strength to
elude it, but I will not run!
I will not hide!
NARUTO: Next time.
"Losing Is Not an Option!"
[theme music]