[theme music]
-Thank you.
You did excellent work.
Kome has already
made his confession.
It seems the curses warrior was
all a ploy to stir up unrest
with the public, so he could
seize the Feudal Lord's seat.
NARUTO: And Kome told
you all that himself?
-Yes.
I know it's inconceivable.
When that Cursed
Warrior disappeared,
it was actually a soldier
pretending to be a ninja.
He used powerful hydrochloric
acid to melt his own flesh.
-Anyone else freaking out
that it's empty again?
[chuckling]
-You see the Cursed
Warrior incident is over.
Now the Land of Birds can return
to the beautiful, quiet place
it was before this mess.
-Wait.
Hold on a sec.
There's another Cursed
Warrior out there!
-Enough, Naruto.
-What gives, Neji.
-I am pleased to say your
work here is complete.
I hope you have a safe
journey back to your village.
[footsteps]
-Aw.
Come on.
What the heck was that?
You said yourself.
The first one was different
from the one last night.
Remember?
-Yes.
Perhaps multiple
people were disguised
as the Cursed Warrior.
But so what?
-But if a person was
inside that thing,
how do you explain how
it flew off like that?
-We have already been told
that this mission is complete.
So there's no reason to remain
in this land any longer.
-Besides, you
heard what he said.
Kome confessed to it.
-It still seems fishy.
I can't just pack
up and leave when
we don't know what
really happened.
-These people have their
own way of doing things.
Getting too involved
will only cause trouble.
-Heh.
Fine.
I'll just have to
do this by myself.
-Hold it.
I am still leader of this team.
-Yeah.
And what does that
have to do with it?
-The team is not yet finished
with the Cursed Warrior.
Tenten and I will study
this from a different angle.
-What?
But you just said
the mission's over.
-Naruto, you do
have a valid point.
The whole matter was
resolved much too quickly.
-All right then.
I'm on it.
-Oh.
Hi.
Where are you off to, Naruto?
NARUTO: Ain't it obvious?
To solve the Cursed
Warrior mystery again.
-What?
-Oh.
Hello, Chishima.
-Excuse me.
Naruto just said that--
-Oh.
Don't listen to him.
It's nothing.
-Is there anything
we can do for you?
-Oh.
Yes.
You have all been so
incredibly helpful to me,
and I feel badly
about how little
you were paid for the job.
-Huh?
Did you bring more?
-We can accept more payment.
Please.
-It's not.
It's a local delicacy,
bean jam stuffed wings.
-Thanks for the tip.
[sniffing]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): This place
is definitely suspicious.
Kind of makes me nervous
doing this alone.
Summoning Jutsu.
-Oh.
Haven't see you in a while.
You have a snack for me?
-Are you kidding me?
Why's it you guys?
-Dad's busy, so I guess
you're stuck with us.
-Actually, maybe it's
better that Boss Gama
is staying out of this.
Oh well.
Guess it's just us then.
Hey.
You guys have a better sense of
smell than humans, don't you?
-What do we look like?
Puppies or something?
I'm telling you.
The family reputation
has hit rock bottom.
Gamatatsu, we're out of here.
Huh?
Hey, uh-- Gamatatsu.
-Huh?
-What're you doing?
Why's the toad trying to
jump up to that branch?
-What is that moron up to?
-Big Bro Gamakichi, what
do you think this is?
Uh-oh.
Who turned out the lights?
Is it night already?
Good night, then.
Rise and shine.
-What is this anyway?
-It's a kite painted
black, genius.
-A kite?
-Look up there.
See?
-Huh?
No way.
That kite is so huge.
-Ooh.
I wonder if they had
a giant kite flying
festival or something?
-I don't know.
It's kind of boring
for a festival kite.
Wouldn't you say?
-Really?
Where'd you come up with that?
-Whoopsie.
-Hey!
Where you going?
-Whoop.
Wow.
What a trip.
-Of course.
If somebody flew one of
these under cover of night,
a Cursed Warrior
hanging off a black kite
would look like
he's flying And just
like that, the mystery of the
levitating warrior is solved.
What's next?
Someone was definitely
here that night.
GAMAKICHI: So what is it?
-The cursed warrior
came out from this door.
-Nothing special here.
Just looks like an old temple
that nobody uses anymore.
-Yeah.
It certainly does.
-Let's move out, Gamatatsu.
-Come on, Big Brother Gamakichi.
It's so nice and
cool and relaxing.
-Ah, what are you talking about?
This place should
be hot and humid.
Ah.
You're right for
once, little bro.
That is a nice, moist breeze.
-See?
Doesn't it make you
want to take a nap?
-You mean wind's
blowing from underneath?
Huh?
-What's down there?
-It's so big.
I wonder if a gigantic
worm built all this.
Or maybe an enormous mole.
-OK.
Let's check it out.
GAMATATSU: Hey, if we
meet a giant mole, how
you think we're
supposed to greet him?
GAMAKICHI: Heh.
How should I now?
CHISHIMA: So, Naruto
is still investigating
the cursed warrior.
That's very interesting.
I had better inform Lord Moso.
Hm?
-We encountered some
trouble along the way.
But at last, we found
what we were looking for.
Find him.
-Big brother, where are we now?
-Well, obviously where uh--
-Wait.
Isn't that the Feudal
Lord's residence?
-Wow.
A Lord lives there?
-That would explain
why it's so fancy.
-That secret tunnel
we found leads here?
[splash]
-What the heck was
that splashing?
-Woohoo!
Wow.
You got a pretty
nice view from here!
[muffled talking]
-Hey.
Keep quiet.
They're gonna discover us.
-Um-- Gamakichi?
-Oh, great.
GAMAKICHI: You blockhead!
-Uh-- hey there.
Good job patrolling men.
Just ignore me.
I'm not intruding or-- Listen.
I was hired by
supervising officer Moso.
I'm just here investigating
an official crime incident.
NARUTO:It'll all make sense
if you let me explain.
-Lord Sagi, we have captured
a suspicious person.
What shall we do with him?
-Huh?
Hey!
Sagi!
This guy knows me.
We met before at the lake.
Don't you remember?
This is great.
Just tell these
guys you know me.
-I've never seen
this person before.
-You what?
-He's not worth sending to
the magistrate's office.
Lock him up in the
dungeon at once.
-Yes, milord.
-Wait a sec.
You can't just walk
away like that!
NARUTO: Hey!
Come on, Sagi!
This is cruel!
Don't do this to me!
Get back here!
Come back!
[groaning]
[splash]
NARUTO: Give me a break.
This is all a misunderstanding!
I was just going after
the Cursed Warrior!
Listen.
Just talk to Moso!
He'll clear it all up!
I swear!
GAMAKICHI: Hey!
How you doing?
-Huh?
-Hi!
-I couldn't fight those
guys because they're
soldiers of the
guy who hired me.
And then you guys get caught
like that in some dumb trap.
[whimper]
-Don't worry about it.
I can bust out here easy as
long as I can use both hands.
Here.
Do me a favor and untie this.
-Right.
Give me a second here.
[footsteps in water]
[footsteps and closing door]
-Huh?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
The cursed warrior?
-Man, this stinks!
If I had both hands, this
guy'd have no chance.
aren't we gonna help him?
-If we tried anything, that
big guy'd slice us in two.
-That doesn't sound fun.
NARUTO: Just a little closer.
[NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Ugh!
Come on.
Just a little more!
-Haaa!
NARUTO: Sagi!
What the heck's going on here?
You're telling me you were
the other Cursed Warrior?
But why?
-They say that only a ghost
can accomplish true vengeance.
But that is nothing
more than a dirty lie!
This watch had been handed
down from generation
to generation of Feudal Lords.
It was supposed to be passed
on from father to son.
But no more.
The moment my father perished,
the watch stopped ticking.
It's as if it too felt
the pain of death!
[sobbing]
-The only reason I continued
this shameless life
is to my revenge.
The moment I achieve it,
I can perish as well.
-But that's no way to live.
-You have no idea what
it feels like to lose
everything you hold dear!
-You're right, OK.
I don't know!
But I do know one thing--
living only to seek vengeance
is no life at all.
NARUTO: You're a
Feudal Lord, right?
Is revenge the job
of a Feudal Lord?
Of course not.
Look.
Kome has already been arrested
for the evil he's committed.
You could just let Moso
handle it, and walk away.
Right?
-You have absolutely no
right to interfere in this.
And besides, now that you
know everything you do,
we cannot let you survive.
You have trespassed on the
land of the Feudal Palace,
and the punishment
for that is death!
-You're kidding me.
-So creepy.
These are the tombs of all
the past Feudal Lords, right?
-Yes.
This one's the tomb
of Lord Owashi.
Byakugan!
What is that?
-Wha-- what is it, Neji?
Are you seeing something?
-I sense something poisonous
inside Owashi's body.
Was he assassinated?
They've surrounded us.
-Ninja of the
Hidden Leaf Village,
hear this proclamation.
We come bearing a message
from the Feudal Lord.
Your comrade has been arrested
for infiltrating the Royal
Residence, and has been
sentenced to death.
You are ordered to leave
the Land of Birds at once.
If you don't, you
will be executed
where you stand, for the
same crime as your friend.
Draw your bows,
and fire at will!
-Neji, what should we do?
-We'll make our way
to the Feudal Lord.
We must save Naruto.
You?
-Kakashi-sensei,
Naruto's in big trouble.
-We have to find him quickly,
and mount a rescue mission.
-We can't do that.
-What?
-Sorry.
Your mission's over.
-But, sensei!
-You'll do nothing
beyond your mission.
[chirping]
[theme music]
NEJI: Are we really just
going back to the village?
KAKASHI: I told you.
Our mission in the Land
of Birds is finished.
TENTEN: But what's
gonna happen to Naruto?
KAKASHI: We can't
interfere in their affairs.
TENTEN: This can't be happening.
NEJI: I'm sorry.
As team leader, this
is my responsibility.
KAKASHI: Let it go.
Sacrifice is part
of every mission.
Next time-- the Death of Naruto.