[music playing]
[theme music]
-It's up to you, Choji.
-OK.
Expansion jutsu.
All right!
Here we go!
[music playing]
-What?
-Well Choji, there's no
other way of saying it.
That was awesome.
-Full throttle power!
Choji ablaze!
[rocks crumbling]
-They managed to escape
my barrier ninjutsu.
-He's by himself.
Guess the others went on ahead.
-You're correct.
They're nowhere to be seen.
-Swell.
And just when I thought we'd
finally caught up to them.
[clapping]
-Not a bad bit of
handiwork, you guys.
For a bunch of losers.
-What?
-Who are you calling losers?
Now that we're out,
you're toast, pal.
-Out of the way,
this guy's mine!
-Wait you two, stop!
There's no way we
can take him head on.
It's too dangerous.
-We just tore through
this clown's barrier.
How tough can he be?
Tunneling fang!
-Shadow clone jutsu!
Get a load of this, you gorilla!
-I'm going to eat
you guys for lunch!
-Try it.
-Shoulder charge!
Crashing knee!
You wouldn't even
do as an appetizer.
-Careful, everyone.
This guy's just
getting warmed up.
[explosions]
-Earth style barrier.
Earth domed prison.
-Expansion jutsu!
Human boulder!
[music playing]
-Heh.
Hardly worth the effort.
[nature sounds]
-We're running out of time.
There's no choice.
We've got to split up.
-What'd be the point in that?
-No, he's right.
[wind blowing]
With all our chakra
taken away, even
with the five of us
against him, he's
not going to be
easy to take out.
And with every
second that passes,
Sasuke gets closer
to the border.
Once he crosses it, it'll
all be out of our hands.
So we should split
into two groups.
One to stop him, and
one to follow Sasuke.
-You'll head the
second team, OK, Neji?
-Heh heh.
[rock crumbling]
So there you are.
-Neji.
You take Kiba and Choji,
and head out after Sasuke.
-You've got it.
-Naruto, you and I
will handle this guy.
-What are you going to do?
Play with my shadow again?
Don't waste my time, kid.
You already showed me
your little parlor trick,
and once was enough.
-That's funny.
I seem to remember someone
around here getting
taken in by that parlor trick.
[music playing]
[explosion]
-He's disappeared.
He's behind us!
[explosion]
[music playing]
-Earth style sphere of graves!
-Are you insane?
[music playing]
-Heads up, you guys.
There's another one coming.
Ah!
-You're in charge of this
rag-tag bunch, am I right?
When you've got an idiot for a
leader, the whole team suffers.
Know what I mean?
You don't want to
follow a guy like this.
Let me get rid of him for you.
-Expansion jutsu!
Human boulder.
Gotcha.
-Thanks, Choji.
-Oh, I try to help you guys
out, and look what you do.
I don't know which
is more pathetic,
the fool or those
who follow him.
Tell you what.
You don't want to keep working
under this glum-faced little
shadow lover.
I'll just kill you now and
put you out of your misery.
-It's time for you to
shut your big mouth,
or I'll come shut if for you!
-Naruto!
I'll handle him.
This guy is mine.
-But Choji.
-What the heck are
you talking about?
This isn't the kind of guy
you can take on your own.
-He's mine, I said.
-Yeah, but Choji, you're--
-Heh.
-Shukamaru, I'm take these
food pills for everyone.
-Choji, you're not gonna--
-Uh huh.
Don't worry.
I've got my secret
weapon with me.
-Yeah, but Choji, this is--
-Oh, this is priceless.
You think I'm going
to wait forever?
-Heads up!
-Enough of this.
I'm taking you all
out right here.
-Get going.
Hurry!
-Pills?
Those aren't food pills.
So what are they?
-First, the green spinach pill.
-Get out of my way, you joke!
Impossible.
He stopped me.
-Shikamaru, take everybody
and get out of here.
-Choji.
-What did the five of
us join together for?
If we lose Sasuke, we'll be
just what this guy says we are.
A stupid idiot of a leader,
and his band of rejects.
-You'd better catch
up with us, Choji.
You hear me?
-Yeah.
Get out of here.
Go already!
-All right, let's move you guys.
-Right.
[music playing]
-Choji.
-Once I finally finish
you off here, kid,
your friends are
going to be next.
-That might not be as
easy as you think it is.
[music playing]
-I will stop you.
[heavy breathing]
-A parting gift from Choji.
Eat up.
-Got it.
We owe you one, Choji.
Kiba.
-Thanks, Naruto.
-Shikamaru, that certain pill
we saw Choji take back there,
it seemed like some sort
of last-minute trump card.
Do you really think he can win?
-Yeah.
I mean, he said he had some
sort of secret weapon on him.
-Don't worry, Choji's
got a plan up his sleeve.
He brought along with
him the Akimichi clan's
secret triple threat.
Pills that grant a
person explosive power.
There are three of them,
green, yellow, and red.
The amount of energy that
each of those pills contains
is absolutely massive.
-Oh, I got you.
So that's why he was
acting so confident.
-Yeah.
But any pill that
works that well always
comes with side effects.
[gasping]
-Ah.
I didn't think the spinach pill
by itself would hurt so much.
-I hope he can settle things
with the green pill alone.
Just don't take
the red one, Choji.
Whatever you do.
-I'm going to finish
this all in one blow.
-Hm?
[music playing]
-Expansion jutsu!
Splky giant boulder!
[music playing]
-He's upped his rotation
and destructive power
by using those
kunai-like spikes.
Earth style terra shield!
[music playing]
-Did I do it?
-Yeah, I know.
I was just thinking
the same thing myself.
-What do you mean?
What is he saying?
-You know how Akamaru can
tell an enemy's strength
just by his scent, right?
He's pretty worried
that Choji might not
be able to take on
that gargantuan alone,
with just those
pills to help him.
-He's right to be.
If we're looking
at it objectively,
that giant's ability
is an unknown.
The chances of Choji defeating
him may be close to zero.
However, that's very
often the case in battle.
-Don't get carried
away, you little fool.
Shatter palm!
No one ever told you?
In every team of
five, there's always
somebody in the mix
who's just dead weight.
The guy who's always the
butt of everyone's jokes.
And when thick comes
to thin, he gets
cast aside, like the
worthless pawn he is.
That's who you are.
-Look, Choji.
You've got to stop
thinking about food.
Do some training for once.
-Ridiculous stunts like
this are why everyone always
makes fun of you.
You're such a fa--
-But for this kind
of thing, don't you
think your first choice
should be someone like Shino?
-Come on.
I mean how useless can you be?
Seriously.
[music playing]
-No matter how hard
I try on my own, I--
-Looks like I hit it
right on the nose.
Heh.
It looks as though the Leaf
Village is running short
on ninja, if they're sending
out bunglers like you
to be part of the search team.
What do you say we
put an end to this?
Knee slam!
Shoulder charge!
A loser right to the end.
You started out well, but
that backbone you showed sure
didn't last long.
You're the epitome of failure.
It's not your fault.
They never should have
sent a reject like you
in the first place.
You should blame your stupid
leader for choosing you.
-Shikamaru.
That's just how a battle is.
We knew from the beginning
this mission wouldn't
be child's play.
It's life or death.
-Yeah, but Shikamaru.
-I've already anticipated
the worst-case scenario,
where each of us ends
up fighting alone.
And at this point, if
we're not ready to lay down
our lives for this, we might be
able to reach Sasuke in time.
Choji is good enough
to hold his own,
but he doesn't have
a lot of confidence.
He thinks that out of all of
us, he's the weakest link.
-That's because
the guy kind of is.
I mean, anyone can see that.
That's pretty much
the whole reason
he stayed behind back
there, because he wanted
to be of some kind of use to us.
-Hm.
Just as I thought.
-Huh?
-But--
[music playing]
-Choji and I have been on the
same team for a long time.
We work well together, so
asking him is a no-brainer.
-But, Shikamaru.
[music playing]
-But I'm probably not as
good a fighter as you are.
I mean, really, if I had
been facing off against you,
I probably would have
given up the fight.
And you should just
keep being you.
-But Shikamaru, he's always--
-Huh?
-Shikamaru, he's
always believed in me.
-Choji, are you ready, buddy?
[music playing]
-He believes I really am strong.
That's why he trusted me
to handle this myself!
-Just as I thought.
Everyone's always thought
that way about Choji.
But me?
I've always known
the real truth.
-Huh?
-More than me or Neji, or any of
us here, Choji's got strength.
I believe in him.
I always have.
-Pretty aggressive chakra.
Not bad, but a far cry
from being a main dish.
-Here I come, fatso!
-Don't you call me that!
-Partial expansion jutsu!
[music playing]
[theme music]
-I can't move because
of all the pain.
I didn't think the side
effects of the pill
would be so powerful.
What do I do?
I only have the one pill left.
But if I take it, if I take
it, there's no question I'll--
-Next time, good
bye, old friend!
I'll always believe in you.
-I won't forget
him, no matter what!
[music playing]