[theme music]
-So that's your answer, Tsunade.
After all I've offered
you, you would repay me
by trying to kill me.
Fortunately, I can depend
on Kabuto's loyalty.
A good thing he arrived in time
to see the evil intent hidden
in those healing
hands what of yours.
-Yes.
She and I are from
the medical corps.
I could tell she was building
up her chakra for an attack.
-Tsunade, Tsunade.
And I was going to restore
your loved ones to you.
I even agreed to
give up my dream
of destroying the Leaf village.
-As to that, Orochimaru,
I knew your promise
to leave the village alone
was worthless, a lie.
But even so.
Even though I knew
that, the chance
to see them both one more time.
To see them once more,
if only for a moment.
To be able to touch them, to
feel them, just once more in.
To see their precious smiles.
I'm weak.
So weak that, for
a moment, I would
have sacrificed everything
just to see them again.
Just once.
For that, I was
willing to throw away
the villages and the
lives of everyone in it.
To think that I
could've been so blind.
But the memory-- It was
a memory of their faces.
-Hey, big sister!
MAN: Tsunade.
-I love them.
I love them both so much.
The chance to see them again.
To hold them in my arms!
But then, something happened
-I said it, and I never
go back on my word.
-That boy, he made me
remember something.
Something I've been
trying to forget.
-This entire village meant
a lot to our grandfather!
And I'm gonna take
good care of all of it.
After all, I'm the grandom
of the Hokage, the man who
built the village
hidden in the leaves!
-I love this village and the
people in it with all my heart.
I want to protect them.
-Right.
And I give my work, I'll follow
our grandfather's footsteps
and be just like him!
-Unlike you, I
admire the Hokage.
It's my dream to be like him
some day, no matter what.
-I want to lead them in building
a better world than this.
It's been my dream ever
since my sister died.
It's all that's kept me going.
-To be Hokage.
That's my dream!
-That's what he
made me remember.
The dream they shared.
The dream they gave
their lives for.
It meant everything to them.
You said once that all things
on Earth crumble and fade away.
I wish that were true.
I only wish this
feeling would go away,
but I know it never will.
-It seems we've
reached an impasse.
So be it.
I'm afraid you give me no
choice but to use force.
NARUTO: Breakdown!
The Deal is Off!
-Come on, Orochimaru!
-It's amazing that
in all this time,
you and I have never
actually met in combat.
-That's right.
-Don't get your hopes up.
You still have to go through me.
-No matter.
It'll be a pleasure
killing you both right now!
-She hasn't lost
any of her strength.
It won't go well for you
if she ever connects.
-I can see that.
This is not the battlefield
I would've chosen.
It's too cramped here.
-A change of scenery?
-Yes.
I think a change would be wise.
When I found her
attendant, she was
with someone who might
prove troublesome to us.
They could be here any minute.
-This troublesome someone.
Who is it?
-One of the Sannin, same as you.
-Jiraiya.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER):
No you don't.
I'm going to finish this.
NARUTO: Whoa.
What the heck happened here?
-Well, well.
I'd say something put
Tsunade in a bad mood.
She's got a foul temper.
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER): So, this
must mean she refused him.
-Well, OK, but where's
the grumpy old bat now?
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER): Her jacket.
Which way?
Well, Tonton?
-Oink.
-OK, let's go!
-Out of breath already?
Well, none of us are
getting any younger, are we?
Time to end it.
-Taijutsu was never
my forte, but--
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER):
A food pill?
That hand sign!
So, he knows medical
ninjutsu, too.
My arm.
-Yes.
I've weakened the muscles
of your right bicep
and your left thigh,
just enough so you
won't be able to reach that
incredible strength of yours.
-A chakra stopper, huh?
Well, then why not
just go for the kill?
-That's true.
With this scalpel, I
could sever an artery
or puncture your heart without
even breaking the skin.
But of course, that requires
careful aim, and a long blade.
Both of which are
difficult to accomplish
in the heat of battle.
But that said, perhaps if
I just aim for your neck!
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): Damn!
He hit my intercostals.
Can't breathe.
This kid's no ordinary
medical ninja.
I was never that
quick, or precise.
Even in my prime.
-Have to be careful to avoid
hitting anything too vital.
We don't want you
dying just yet.
Still, you're not going to
be moving much anytime soon.
Huh?
(VOICEOVER) I
underestimated her.
She shouldn't still be
conscious, let alone--
All right, then.
I guess I'll have to
stop going easy on her.
It'd be so much easier
if I could just kill her.
I try to move my right arm--
and my left leg tenses.
No-- she couldn't have--
-Surprise!
(VOICEOVER) I can
only hope it worked.
Because that was
about all I've got.
-Now I see.
-Nothing's responding right.
But it's not my muscles.
I see you've finally
figured it out.
It's your whole nervous system.
I turned my chakra
into electricity,
then sent an electrical charge
ripping through your body.
OROCHIMARU (VOICEOVER):
She attacked his lines
of communication, scrambling
the electrical impulses that
carry messages from the brain
to different parts of the body.
Cut off from the brain, his
body doesn't know what to do.
She's literally
short circuited him.
KABUTO (VOICEOVER):
To be capable of this
in her condition-- but then,
she is one of the Sannin.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER):
Don't have enough chakra
for a healing jutsu.
But I have to do what I can.
KABUTO (VOICEOVER):
When I try to move
my right hand-- my
left leg responds.
And trying to move my left
ankle moves my right shoulder.
It's tricky, but I think-- yes.
I think I've just about
figured out what moves what.
Though you had me, didn't you?
Surprise.
Now, then!
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): Impossible!
He could never have
recovered so quickly!
-So, you fear the
sigh of blood, eh?
Let's put it to
the test, shall we?
-Jiraiya?
-It's been a long
time, old friend.
JIRAIYA (VOICEOVER): Orochimaru.
Long time, indeed.
And I can't say it's improved
your looks any, old friend.
-Huh?
Hey!
Kabuto.
-Naruto.
-You've met this
guy before, Naruto?
-Well, of course I have.
We took the Chunin
exams together.
What are you doing here, Kabuto?
-Out of the way!
Oink!
-Stay outta this!
I can handle them!
So, you recovered quickly.
No matter.
You're still not at 100%.
The game's up, kid.
too late for that!
-Ah?
-Your jutsu's worn off.
Now I am at 100%.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): Blood.
-I knew that I'd
never be able to take
on two of the legendary
Sannin at the same time.
But now at least I got one down!
-Lady Tsunade!
-I don't get it.
What's going on?
I'm confused.
Did I miss out on something?
How come Kabuto and Grandma
Tsunade are mixing it up?
-I see you're as
slow as ever, Naruto.
No wonder you're no
match for Sasuke.
-Huh?
-If you want your answer,
just look at his headband.
He serves Orochimaru.
-That's right.
I'm a spy from the Village
Hidden in the Sound.
-But-- a spy?
That's impossible.
You don't really mean it?
But you-- you helped us get
through the Chunin exams.
You saved our lives.
-Only in order to gather
information about all of you.
That was my mission.
Indeed, I learned one
very important thing
about you, Naruto.
You lack any ninja ability.
You're not a bit like Sasuke.
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER): I've
never seen her like this.
Never.
You don't have to do everything
by yourself, you know?
Let me help.
I'm here to serve you.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Grandma Tsunade.
-Go on, glare at
me all you want.
You're still just a pint
sized Genin in over his head.
I admit that the demon inside of
you had me worried for a time.
But surrounded by three
of the legendary Sannin,
I see how insignificant you are.
Next to them,
you're a mere child
sitting at the grownups' tables.
Stay out of it-- or die.
-Oh, yeah?
-Naruto, no!
(VOICEOVER) My
body's still shot.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
His right hand.
I think it's hurt.
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
I'll hit him with
multiple attacks.
Then come at him from the ride,
where his defenses are weak!
Ha!
[inaudible]
My eyes!
KABUTO (VOICEOVER):
Poison needles!
My reflexes are still out.
I can't dodge them.
If I can just--
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER):He blocked
them with his headband!
-Impressive move.
I'll give him that.
-Thanks, Shizune.
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER):
So that's it.
Plasma pill.
-Plasma pill?
-Well, of course.
He's trying to replace the
blood that he's already lost.
-So, he's a medical ninja.
Like me.
-We can't have too much
blood, can we, Kabuto?
-Lord Orochimaru, isn't it
time to take the bandage
off your arm?
-So that's Orochimaru!
-Well, now we can finally
get down to business.
Shizune.
-Yes.
-I'll let you take care
of four-eyes over there.
Just leave Orochimaru to me.
[theme music]
-Am I supposed to be
impressed, Kabuto?
You gutless creep, picking
on the old lady like that!
Even though she
might not look it.
Hey.
And speaking of which,
you still owe me
that necklace, Grandma Tsunade.
I don't care if
it's unlucky or not!
We made a bet, and
I aim to win it!
I said I would, and I
always stand by my word.
That's my ninja way!
Next Time, Attack!
Fury of the Rasengan!
[theme music]