[MUSIC - SNOWKEL, "NAMIKAZE
SATELLITE"]
[breathing heavily]
[thunder]
-Where-- where--
where-- where am I?
Am I?
[wind whistling]
-[inaudible]
[gasping]
[laughter]
[thunder]
-Look out, world.
I'm going to hit the ground
running today, so stand back.
Not that it matters though.
All my missions are
so lame these days.
Huh?
-Geez, I can't believe it.
This is so unfair.
-It's not so bad.
I'm training so hard these days
I can barely keep my eyes open.
-Hey, Sakura.
-Speaking of being lazy.
-Oh yeah?
Well last I checked
you're just sitting
around a flower shop all day.
Where are Choji and
Shikamaru anyway?
-Off somewhere
with Asuma Sensei.
Oh man, I'd give anything
to be out there on a mission
right now.
-Ino was down with
a cold for a while
and the guys were sent off
on a mission without her.
-And I'm like totally
recovered now.
If I don't blow off some
steam, I'll just go crazy.
-Hey, nothing a little
training won't cure.
-Not at my house.
If my family ever find
out I don't have someone
to spar with, I get roped
into helping out at the shop.
-Whatever.
They know you'd just
skip the training
if you were on your own.
-Wait a minute!
That's not true at all.
Take it back.
I train by myself all the time.
-[laughs]
-Naruto.
-Ah!
Shino, don't sneak
up on me like that.
-Ino.
Naruto.
The Hokage wishes
to see you now.
-Huh?
Both of us?
-I was told to come fetch you.
She wants to see
all three of us.
-Huh?
-You, Shino, and me?
-Hmm.
-What kind of disturbance?
-Not sure.
Some sort of creature's
been terrorizing
our neighbor, the Land of Sea.
They call it the
demon of the ocean.
What's wrong?
You will go for me, won't you?
-Yes, milady.
-Shizune.
-Uh, yes?
-Give her the rundown.
-Oh, sure.
The Land of the Sea is composed
of islands of various sizes.
Lately vessels carrying
monetary shipments
have been coming under
attack, their cargo plundered.
-All the people on
board these ships
claim that the damage was done
by this demon of the ocean.
-And that's the mission, huh?
You want me to find this
thing and take it out, right?
-Well, almost.
There's a hair more
to it than that.
-The Land of the Sea has no
hidden village, not of its own.
So they've established
a military alliance
with their neighbor,
the Land of Water.
They make payments every
month, but the ship
carrying their
latest installment
was attacked by the demon
of the ocean as well.
-I get it.
To preserve their relationship
with the land of water,
the Land of the Sea
will do whatever
it takes to protect
their next ship.
-Bingo.
Your mission is to safeguard
the latest delivery
and take out this demon.
Your support team has
already been assembled.
The rest I leave to you.
-Support team?
[knock on door]
-Enter.
-What the?
You're that psycho proctor
from the Chunin exams.
-Yeah, good times.
Feels like it was only
yesterday, doesn't it?
-Anko Mitarashi, Sensei?
-So what are you doing here?
-Listen up.
Your mission is as follows.
Shino Aburame, Ino
Yamanaka, Naruto Uzumaki.
You three will be
working as a team
under Anko for this assignment.
What she says goes.
-You're putting the
three of us together?
-Seriously, it is kind of
a weird match, isn't it?
-I don't want to hear it.
Now look, I've
thought this through.
Each of your specific skill
sets will combine perfectly
for this mission.
I hand picked you all myself.
Now put those abilities
of yours to good use
and get the job done.
-Right.
-Hand picked?
These were the only
Genin available.
She's too much.
-[laughs]
-Something here
doesn't smell right.
-OK, you've got your
marching orders.
Zip it.
-Ow, ow, ow, ow.
All right, all right.
-Now then, let's get
this show on the road.
Go pack your gear and
meet me at the front gate.
-Roger.
-Man, that really hurt.
-Anko.
Be careful.
-Right.
-Demon of the ocean.
Has physical traits both
human and fish like.
What is this?
-These people need to
have their eyes examined.
Something like
that doesn't exist.
-Not necessarily.
This could be ninja
resorting to piracy
with genjutsu at their disposal.
-Well, whatever.
We still need to look into it.
This problem's not
solving itself.
-Of course.
-All, right, Mother
Island's at the center
of the Land of the Sea.
Let's head to the nearest
port town and charter a boat.
-Got it.
-All right.
OK, let's set sail for
the Land of the Sea.
-Why does he always
have to be gung-ho?
I've got a bad
feeling about this.
-Here you are.
So, um, Lady Tsunade?
-Hmm?
-About Anko, I was
wondering, I mean, well,
did something
happen in the past?
-Sort of.
-Wait a second.
This file.
These are her mission
records from age 10 and on.
They're so fragmented.
-Anko was one of Orochimaru's
students once, remember?
-So the passages blacked
out are connected
to Orochimaru's activity.
So they correspond to
confidential files.
-Well, some of them.
-Huh?
-For parts of it we
have no record at all.
-No record at all?
Even for the entire period
she was here in the village?
-[sighs] That Orochimaru.
He must not have wanted
anyone to know he was doing.
When he left the village,
he was careful to erase
sections of Anko's memory.
-Ah, smell that ocean air.
-Well, we made it, you guys.
Feast your eyes on
the Land of the Sea.
-So is that Mother Island then?
[panting]
-What is this feeling
coming over me?
Hey guys, just go
on ahead will you?
See if you go
rustle up that boat.
-Yeah, but Sensei--
-I have some business
to take care of.
I'll catch up with you
as soon as I'm done.
Back in a bit.
-Sensei.
-Ah, don't bother.
Come on.
Shino, what are you doing?
-You want to get left behind?
-Right.
-This curse mark is killing me.
His presence.
There's no question.
This way.
--[laughs] I know
which ones are which.
Let me see.
That one is Mother
Island, that's
Taro, and that
one's Jiro Island.
And, uh, that
one's Demon Island.
-Certainly done your
homework, haven't you?
--[laughs] Yeah, well, I
kind of have to, right?
If I want to be a shinobi with
strength and wisdom like you.
-[laughs]
-Here you are.
Uh, I'm sorry, but
that's the best I can do.
-Hey, Ino, what's wrong?
-Hold on one second.
That's kind of a low
price, don't you think?
That's high quality fish.
-Uh, well, look, I'm
not underpaying her.
It's just with all this hubbub
over this demon of the ocean,
customers have been
scarce for a while.
Sorry, but that's the
going price these days.
-You've got to be kidding me.
That fish rarely goes for--
-Wow, that's a lot of bandages.
She injure herself or something?
-No.
But there's something wrong
with her, that's for sure.
She's actually a diver.
She lives in a small town
over on Mother Island.
-Huh?
But if she's an
islander, then what's
she coming to the mainland for?
-Oh, well, uh, that's because
the other people of the island
won't do business with her.
Not long ago she-- she
was taken away by spirits.
-What are you talking about?
-You're saying that she suddenly
disappeared then, right?
-You got it.
One day a bunch of the
islanders just up and vanished.
Story is out of
all those people,
only she turned up again.
We're a small village.
She makes everyone
a bit nervous.
-It's a monster!
-[crying]
-They say she lives outside
the village now, alone.
-Oh, wow.
I feel so sorry for her.
-Looking like that and
then with all the stories
we hear, how can you
not feel on edge?
-[crying]
-Yeah, I guess.
Where'd Naruto go?
-I don't know.
-Hey What do you
think you're doing?
-Let's go.
-Are you OK?
-Yeah.
--[laughs] So, um, you're from
over on Mother's Island, right?
-No.
A ninja.
-Let me help you.
-That's OK.
-Huh?
Hey, wait.
What's up with her?
-I'm sorry but the last boat
of the day has already set out.
-You're kidding.
The sun hasn't
even gone down yet.
-There's no way you're
going to find anyone
around here who will take you
out this late in the evening.
I'm sorry, you're
just going to have
to come back in the morning.
-So much for that.
-Is there any other way
to get to the island
besides the ferry?
-Well, I can't say I advise
it, but if it's really
that important, I own a
small skiff you could borrow.
-Finally.
I've been looking
all over for you.
-It's about time.
Where the heck have you been?
-Oh, right, sorry.
-You should have said
something before taking off.
-Boy, you and our squad
leader are two of a kind,
you know that?
You both just vanish
at the drop of a hat.
No getting around it.
We've got a bumpy
road ahead of us.
-Say what?
You can't lump me into the same
category as that screwball.
She's certifiably insane.
-Who we talking about?
-Oh, well, uh.
-This lady is one loose canon.
-Hey, good job securing
us a boat, by the way.
-Sensei, where in the
world have you been?
-Oh, just off gathering
a little information.
OK, is everybody ready?
-The shinobi of the
Leaf Village are here.
-The Land of the Sea must
have pleaded with them
to come take care of
the demon of the ocean.
-Well, we should give our new
guests a proper welcome then.
-It's getting dark.
-We'll be at the
island pretty soon.
Just a bit further.
-Sounds good to me.
Mother Island full
steam ahead, everybody.
-Sun's down, you know.
Seriously, where do you
get all your energy from?
-Yeah, well, at times like
this, your state of mind is key.
-Sakura's got her hands full.
I feel so bad for her.
-We've run up against
some rocks or something.
-Hang on, Naruto.
-Eyes front, guys,
we've got trouble.
Change course.
Hurry!
-Easier said than done.
-The oar is jammed.
-Let me help you.
-Striking shadow snake!
-Naruto, leave it.
-Right behind you.
-Huh.
Showing himself so soon.
-Man, that was a close call.
-Careful, you two.
We're being targeted
from underwater.
-Oh, boy.
Well, whatever this thing
is, an underwater battle
calls for an underwater expert.
Summoning jutsu.
I'm counting on you, Chief Toad.
You again?
-Geez, Louise.
What are you calling
me here for, kid?
-Hey, look, I'm not
happy to see you either.
OK.
-Hey, whoa, hang on.
-Summoning jutsu.
Come on, Chief.
-Hey there.
Evening--
-What the heck is
going on around here?
I called for the
chief, not a tadpole.
-Are you out of your gourd?
You can't summon pops out here.
It would be a disaster.
-How come?
-We're fresh water
creatures, genius.
Salt water and frogs don't mix.
-Actually, I don't
like anything salty.
-Ah!
Then what good are you
for crying out loud?
-Shino, you keep an eye on her.
All right.
Fire style dragon flame jutsu.
Water clone?
--[laughs] You let
your guard down.
-Yeah, so did you.
-Hurts, don't it?
-There was one more?
There was another one.
I'm losing strength.
--[laughs] I'm siphoning
off your chakra.
How does it feel?
-What's happening?
-Where did it go?
There's no visibility down here.
-Hey, come on, kid.
Pull yourself together.
-Big brother, I'm
itching all over.
-Yeah, I'm reaching
my limit here too.
-Big brother!
-Huh?
Oh, boy.
This ain't so good.
-Naruto.
-What's going on?
[laughter]
-Who are you?
-Time to put all that chakra
I absorbed to good use.
Water style, furious
current jutsu.
-Ah, great.
That complicates things a bit.
-Naruto.
[music - chaba, "parade"]
-I can't believe the latest
shipment has been moved up.
-Never mind that now.
We have to find
Naruto by morning.
And hopefully learn more
about the demon of the ocean.
-It's a pretty big area
we have to search, though.
-We should split up.
-OK, then.
I'll head south.
You two take the north.
-Got it.
-This is something
new, you guys.
Tread carefully.
Let's move.
Next time, The Closed Door.
[music - chaba, "parade"]