[theme music]
-You're going to be OK.
You, know your injury could
have been much more serious.
Naruto was relieved too.
-I see that the
stories are true.
I'd always heard that the
last of the great Uchiho clan
was a hopeless loser
unworthy of his family name.
-So, uh, you must
be hungry, Susake.
Is there something
special you want to eat?
Well, I'll go pick
something up for you.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
The Battle Begins.
Naruto Versus Susake.
-To be honest with you,
I don't know what to do.
With the final exam
being suspended,
it was the opinion of many
that none of the students
should pass this time around,
and that includes you.
However, I hear that
the third Hokage
had nothing but the highest
praise for your match.
It seems he meant to
recommend you for Chunin.
In fact, all those who observed
the fight and your proctors
felt the same.
So in this case, my opinion
doesn't really matter.
From this day forth,
I hope you will
strive to achieve a level
of excellence worthy
of that headband.
Congratulations.
As of this moment,
you stand a Chunin.
-Wow.
You know, even a guy who's
as lazy as you are somehow
seems respectable
all of a sudden.
-It doesn't suit ya.
-It's not that funny.
-Funny or not,
let's have a toast
and celebrate Shikamaru's
outstanding promotion
to Chunin.
CHOJI: Yeah, let's eat.
-Choji, hey!
Lay off of the meat, we're
about to have a toast.
-Oh, sorry.
I just didn't want
it to get burned.
ASUMA: There's plenty
of meat for everyone.
Dig in.
CHOJI: All right!
[footsteps]
[clock ticking]
[sounds of children playing]
-Go away.
You don't interest
me at the moment.
Naruto is the one
you're really after.
-You're gonna end up in
the hospital again, Choji.
I mean, haven't you ever
heard of savoring your food?
-Don't worry, I figure
the more bites I eat,
the more bites I
get to savor, right?
-Come on, Choji.
That's the last piece
of meat and I cooked it.
-Last piece of meat.
This bite shall be the most
sacred bite of the entire meal
and must be consumed
with utmost care.
So back off, sister.
I'm not handing this
morsel over to anyone.
-Why do you have to
act like such an idiot?
Choji, pulling ridiculous
stunts like this
is why everyone always
makes fun of you!
You are such a fat--
-Ino.
Don't say that word.
And Choji, settle down.
A meal's not the
same as a battle.
Stop being such a pain.
We're trying to relax here.
ASUMA (VOICEOVER): Vulgar.
Short-tempered.
Lazy.
I wonder if these kids
are going to make it.
Particularly--
-Choji, you've got to
stop thinking about food.
Do a little training for once.
-Oh, Choji.
You're so lucky that you
don't have to worry about what
or how much you eat.
Let me tell you, being on
a diet can be pretty tough.
-Well, then, why are
you on a diet, Ino?
-We diet for one very
important reason, Choji.
So we can look as cute as
we can for the boy we like.
-But what if the person you like
isn't into super skinny girls?
-Hm, well, in the
first place, most boys
aren't as fat-- I mean,
most of the boys I
know like girls who look fit.
And that's true the
other way around as well.
You might think about
taking a little better care
of your body, Choji, or
you won't get any girls.
-Ha, she has no clue.
Despite what most
women seem to believe,
men don't always go
for the skinny girls.
Most guys I know,
they like girls
with a little meat
on their bones.
It just looks healthier.
Oh, yeah, and the reverse
is true too, you know?
I'd bet anything she'd be
twice as popular if she'd
put on a few pounds instead
of starving herself.
She should eat.
-You're one hilarious
guy, Shamato.
And you're kind of a genius too.
-Hm?
-That's right.
Just think about
it, even I can see
that you're way more
amazing this Sasuke
or that Neji guy ever
dreamed of being.
-I never really thought
about it like that before.
I'm just being me.
-That may be so, but
you're the only student
who actually became a Chunin
in the Chunin exam this time.
-But I'm probably not as
good a fighter as you are.
I mean, really, if I'd been
facing off against you,
I probably would have
given up the fight.
-But earlier, you heard Sensei
tell me all I do is eat and I
should be training hard--
-Like I said before,
I'm just being me,
and you should just
keep being you.
It's stupid to talk about all
the things that you're not.
Hey, Asuma says a lot of
things, but don't take him
too seriously.
Just live your life, eat your
food, and take things easy.
See you later.
I'm heading home.
My dad's been making me nervous
talking about how he actually
wants to teach me a
new jutsu or something.
-Shamato.
-Well, what it is?
-Um, just good luck
with your training.
-Later.
You're a good guy, Choji.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Yo, Sakura!
I'm here.
SUSAKE (VOICEOVER): Naruto.
-The time is right.
Head to the Leaf Village, now.
-I see.
You've made up your mind then?
-Yes.
I have already been carrying
out fitness training
to prepare for the surgery.
I will return to action as
soon as I can after I heal.
Ow!
Ow, ow, ow.
-Lee.
-Yes, ma'am, what is it?
-You can quit as a shinobi.
It won't kill you, you know?
What is it with you?
Why are you so fixated
on being a shinobi?
-It is everything to me.
I must prove that
with enough heart,
even someone with my faults
can become a real ninja.
-But it's important you
realize there is still a chance
that you could die.
-Even so--
-That's a promise.
-It is my dream.
What can I say?
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): Tell
me, what makes you so touchy
about hokage?
NARUTO: It's because,
unlike you, that's my goal.
Just watch, 'cuz someday
I will be the hokage.
To be hokage, that is my dream.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): Hm.
Such ambitious children seem
to come from this village.
Ah.
Saratobi Sensei, I can see
you were a magnificent hokage.
-The surgery is this afternoon.
You should prepare yourself.
Let's go, Lee.
Are you ready for this?
-Yes, ma'am.
-Look, I brought
you some apples.
You like them, right?
Here.
Don't they look delicious?
That's weird.
I wonder where I put
that knife I had before?
NARUTO: It's right in
front of you, Sakura.
-Oh.
NARUTO: You're so lame
getting all scatterbrained
just because you're
around Sasuke.
SAKURA: Why do you have to
come in here and annoy me?
SUSAKE (VOICEOVER): Naruto.
SAKURA: Geez, Naruto, will
you knock it off already?
NARUTO: Summoning jutsu.
Sakura, I swear
I'll protect you.
OK, OK, don't hit me.
-Sasuke, thank you.
I mean, you know, you protected
me from the Sand, right?
-No.
It wasn't me who rescued you.
It was Naruto.
-You're still too weak.
You don't have enough hate.
And you know something?
You never will.
-Done, all peeled and ready.
I'll cut it so
it's easier to eat.
Here, want to try one?
[smack]
-Ow!
What the--
-Sasuke.
-What the heck's going on?
Hey, what's with that look?
You don't have to
glare at me like that.
-You, Naruto.
-Yeah, I'm listening.
-I want you to fight me.
Fight me now.
-What?
We're in a hospital.
You just got patched
up by Tsunade.
What are you talking about?
-Shut up and fight!
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Susake.
-Do you really think
you've saved me?
I don't care if she's
the fifth hokage,
you shouldn't have gotten
her involved in this.
-What?
-After all, you did
say you want to fight.
Well, now it looks like
you've got your chance.
That is, unless
you've chickened out.
-Hey, Sasuke, wait.
Don't do this.
Naruto, say something.
This is crazy.
-Actually, this is perfect.
I was just thinking about how
I wanted to kick your butt.
-Hey, why don't you
guys talk about this?
What do you say?
-Follow me.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
What's this weird feeling?
My lower belly's all tight.
-I want to fight you too.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
And I'm getting chills.
-What's so funny?
-I'm not laughing
because it's funny,
I'm just psyched because
I know that today
is the day when I
finally beat you.
-You're right.
Naruto is the prize that
the Akatsuki are after
and we will have him.
-What did you say?
Don't talk nonsense
you inept loser.
-I won't be such a loser
after I win today, will I?
-Go away.
You don't interest
me at the moment.
-You, an idiot like you
has no business acting
all high and mighty.
-Ha, what happened to the
calm, controlled Sasuke?
Am I making you nervous?
It looks like you
picked a fight with me
and now you're too scared
to go through with it.
Is that it?
-Let's just do this.
-Put on your
headband and we will.
I'll wait.
-Not to worry.
I don't need that thing.
-Just do it.
Come on.
-There's no reason
to put it, 'cuz
you won't be able to make
a scratch on my forehead.
-That's not the point.
Come on.
You know putting
your headband on
is a testament to fighting on
equal terms as a Leaf shinobi.
-There you go acting all
high and mighty again.
You don't honestly
believe that we're equals.
-Heck yeah, I do.
All this time I've never once
thought I was inferior to you
in any way.
-You're a complete
embarrassment.
-Only because next to me,
you're embarrassed at how weak
you are.
Isn't that right, Sasuke?
-Naruto!
-Sasuke!
-Don't get cocky and
let your guard down.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Naruto.
-I've had just about
enough of this!
Monkey shadow clone jutsu!
Na- ru- to.
Uzamaki barrage!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
The tiger seal.
-Fire start.
Fireball jutsu!
-No.
Naruto!
SUSAKE (VOICEOVER): How did
he-- what jutsu is that?
-Chidori.
1,000 birds.
-Please, stop this.
-I'll win no matter what.
-I'm not finished with you yet.
-Stop fighting.
Both of you stop.
Stop it!
[theme music]
-When we became a
three man squad,
even though we have fights,
we carried out our missions
together.
But now, both Sasuke and
Naruto have moved ahead
while I'm the only
one left behind.
Sasuke, even though
you're this close to me,
I feel like you're very distant.
No matter what happens,
Sasuke, I can't see you.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Next
time, "Bitter Rivals
and Broken Bonds."