[theme song]
-We've got to hurry.
-I know.
-We're close.
-There's only two of them left.
Against the three of us.
I like those odds.
If we play it right, the
next time we meet them we'll
be able to wrap things
up once and for all.
-I'll say.
Two against three?
No sweat.
-What do you mean,
it's two against three?
-Oh.
Sorry about that, Akamaru.
You're right.
It's two against four.
I like those odds even better.
-Wait'll they see
our new technique.
These clowns won't
know what hit them.
Right, boy?
-Don't worry about a thing.
As soon as we catch
up to them all
I gotta do is my shadow clone
jutsu and the show's over.
-Well that's comforting to know.
All the same, we're working
as a team here, right?
Just stick to the plan.
-Oh-- well, sure.
-The most important thing is
to at least get them in range
before the sun goes down.
-Well, what are we waiting for?
Let's hit it!
-The sun's going down and still
no sign of Jirobo and Kidomaru.
Must have run into more
trouble than they expected.
-Who cares about them?
It's Orochimaru
I'm worried about.
It's taken us most of a whole
day, and still only one third
of the transition process
has been completed.
MAN (VOICEOVER): They
all have curse marks.
-You might want to
think this over.
It won't be like last time, when
you jumped us all by surprise.
-There's been too many delays.
-You're right.
It's not good.
At this rate we just
might be too late.
-Hurry.
They're just ahead.
-No.
We're close enough.
We'll stay right on
their tail, but we're
gonna maintain this distance.
-What the heck are
you talking about?
-We'll keep them in
our sights, but we
won't attack until sunrise.
-That's crazy!
We can't afford
to wait 'til then.
What about Sasuke?
-Yeah, he's right.
And besides, if we're gonna hit
them with a surprise attack,
it'll be an even bigger surprise
if we hit them in the dark.
-The darkness might
give us an edge
at the first moment of contact,
but after that it would only
put us at a disadvantage, right?
Don't forget what
we're really after.
We want to keep
them occupied just
long enough to get
Sasuke out of there.
That'll take precision
and split-second timing.
We need to be able
to see clearly.
We can't risk going in blind,
wandering around in the dark.
Once they knew what we were
up to all they'd have to do
is fall back and
guard Sasuke's coffin.
They could take up
a defensive position
and wait for us to come to them.
The advantage would
be all on their side.
Course, things would
be a lot different
if we had Neji and his byakugan.
-Aren't you forgetting
about me and Akamaru
and our sense of smell?
-I didn't forget about those
sensitive noses of yours.
But even so, in this
part of the woods,
they've got the
geography in their favor.
What's more-- what's the
sense of attacking now
when my jutsu's no help?
The moonlight's too dim,
and there's too many clouds
passing over it for my shadow
possession to be effective.
It's a drag, but to
be completely safe,
we've gotta wait 'til daylight.
-I don't know.
-I agree.
-What?
-Shikamaru's our leader.
And if he says we wait,
then we're gonna wait.
-I just hope I'm right.
NARUTO: The Vessel
Arrives Too Late.
-Hey, Tayuya, do you think we're
still going to make it in time?
-We were told to deliver
Sasuke by tomorrow or else,
and I don't want to find
out what "or else" means.
-By tomorrow, huh?
Well, it's not like we have
a lot of time to spare.
But we should be
able to make it.
-We better.
[screaming]
-Lord.
Orochimaru.
-They're not here yet?
Still no sign of Sasuke?
KABUTO (VOICEOVER):
Time's running out.
He can't go on like this.
-Please, my lord.
There are many other
bodies ready for you.
My lord, you may even
use mine, if you want.
-No.
It must be Sasuke.
Why do you think I've
waited this long?
-But you've run out of time!
That old man the Third
Hokage, his jutsu
was stronger than we thought!
-Behold sealing jutsu,
reaper death seal!
OROCHIMARU (VOICEOVER):
What is this I feel?
-The seal is set!
-My-- my arms!
-You can't afford
to wait any longer.
If you don't take
another body right now
you'll lose everything.
Everything!
-Lose everything?
[screaming]
-I've chosen several
suitable vessels.
I'll go get them ready.
And then I'll see to Sasuke.
Leave everything to me.
KABUTO (VOICEOVER):
Shall I use Kimimaro?
-Curse you, old man.
Curse you!
-Release.
All right.
Listen up, all of you.
How would you like
to be released
from your imprisonment?
Sadly, it's just one of you.
KABUTO (VOICEOVER):
Now to wake Kimimaro.
-Kabuto-Sensei.
It's as I thought, isn't it?
I wasn't chosen.
Once again.
-Save your strength.
You've served your
function well, Kimimaro.
It's not the Sound
Ninja Five anymore.
-But still, I-- I haven't--
-Don't worry.
Your replacement has
already been found.
He has a mark equal in power
to your Earth Curse Mark.
He's been given the
Heaven Curse Mark.
On top of that he has
the kekkei genkai.
I wonder which one
of you're stronger.
Now, now.
Calm down.
No sense in getting agitated.
-Ka-- Kabuto-Sensei--
tell me truthfully.
How much time do you
think I have left?
-Relax.
Don't try and talk.
-I've been wondering.
There must be a
purpose for people
being born into this world.
Why are we here?
What does it mean?
I've been thinking about
that a lot, lately.
I realize that finding our
purpose is the meaning.
That's why we're here.
And the ones who
find it-- they're
the only ones who
are truly free.
-Yes.
I understand what you're saying.
And meanwhile, as we
speak, Lord Orochimaru
is suffering horribly.
In fact, if something's
not done soon,
it could be the end of him.
You must ask yourself
truthfully, what should you do,
Kimimaro?
What's your purpose,
now that you're
no longer of any
use as a vessel?
At this moment a new
vessel is on its way.
But unfortunately it
won't arrive in time.
-What are you waiting for?
Open this door.
You said you would
set one of us free.
Or was that just your
way of toying with us?
And who are you?
I expected the other one.
Well, whoever--
What's going on?
I'm about to be eaten alive.
[laughter]
-Yes, you will be set free.
And before that, I will
grant you one wish.
-You used my clan
for your experiments.
Let them go.
That's my wish.
-Yes, of course.
You may consider it done.
Don't worry.
Your strength of spirit
was one of the main reasons
I chose you.
And I'd be foolish to
let it go to waste.
Your residual aura
will live on in me.
Well, then.
I thank you for your body.
[scream]
-So it's done.
And now it will be a few years
before he can transfer again.
But next time--
-It's as you say.
My damaged body is
of no use to him
as a vessel for the
transference jutsu.
That was my purpose.
And it's gone.
What is there left to
give my existence meaning?
I see now what I must do.
I was not meant
to be the vessel.
I was meant to find the vessel
and bring it safely here,
even at the cost of my life.
That is the only way I can repay
Lord Orochimaru for my failure.
The only way to give my
worthless existence some value.
-Hold on a second.
-Are we almost there?
-No.
We still have a ways to go.
But take a look.
And, of course, now
that we need them,
there's no sign of
Jirobo or Kidomaru.
-Sorry.
Just us.
-Who needs those two?
I can handle these guys myself.
-Get ready!
-Fist barrage!
SAKON (VOICEOVER): Chakra
in the palm of his hand?
-Shadow clone jutsu, huh?
[shouts]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
He caught my arm.
Just when I--
-How are you supposed
to hit anyone
with it if you can't throw it?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Hurry up, Kiba.
-Tunneling fang!
SAKON (VOICEOVER):
Damn, a shadow clone!
TAYUYA (VOICEOVER): They
maneuvered Sakon right
in front of me,
blocking my view.
They were aiming for
me the whole time.
-So what?
You think that's
gonna do you any good?
-What hit me?
-It's called a shadow
possession jutsu.
TAYUYA (VOICEOVER):
He's got me pinned down.
Meanwhile--
-Tayuya, don't just stand there.
Get that guy!
TAYUYA (VOICEOVER): No!
-What are you doing?
Get out of the way!
Can't stop in time!
-Here, catch.
-Good work, Kima.
OK.
Got it!
-You heard him, Shikamaru.
Time to pull out.
-Don't worry.
I'm coming.
-Little punks.
-They really think they'll
get away with this.
-Just as I thought.
They left themselves wide open.
Sometimes being so sure
of your own strength
can be a weak spot.
-Well, whatever.
It worked.
-It's about teamwork, Naruto.
The whole is greater than
the sum of its parts.
If we just work together,
nothing can stop us.
-You think it's that easy?
[music playing]
-What a drag.
Just when I thought we
were out of the woods,
another one of them shows up.
And there's something
different about this guy.
Something seriously creepy.
He definitely wasn't
part of my game plan.
Remember what I said about how
teamwork can beat anything?
Well, I may have miscalculated.
I wasn't expecting this.
Sorry, Naruto.
I let you down.
NARUTO: Next time,
miscalculation-- a new enemy
appears!
[music playing]