[music playing]
[theme music]
-Now, let the 10th round begin.
-You can do it!
-Fatso!
CHOJI: [grumbling] OK!
I'm going to finish this match.
It's only going to
take about two seconds,
and then I'm coming
after you, Ino!
-Fine, fatso.
If you want this
match to end quickly,
I'll just win it quickly.
--[grumble] You're
going to go down hard,
you mummified weirdo.
CHOJI (VOICEOVER): I
know his techniques
all too well from my
last battle with him.
Those holes in his arm
emit a pulsing sound.
But if I can't hear it,
then he can't hurt me.
-Ha!
Ninja arts-- Expansion Jutsu!
Now, the Hidden
Leaf Style Taijutsu.
[shout]
CHOJI (VOICEOVER): This
will protect my ears
from his attacks and
crush him like a bug.
Human boulder!
Chubbies rule!
-Yeah, all right!
Choiji, you can do it!
Crush him good for me.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
That guy doesn't
need to touch Choji to hit him
with a powerful sonic attack.
But they only work when
Choji's ears are showing.
With his head covered, it's
like Choji's wearing ear plugs.
Those sonic attacks are useless
against that big meatball,
especially when it's rolling.
DOSU (VOICEOVER):
[chuckles] He barely
has any control over
where he's going.
Now to end this-- [grunt]
CHOJI: It's no use.
My ears are covered.
-You are so wrong.
-[yells]
[screams]
[groans]
-See, the human
body is 70% water,
and water can
transmit sound waves.
In other words, when
it comes to my attacks,
your whole body is
basically one big ear.
-The winner is Dosu Kinuta.
DOSU (VOICEOVER): Lord
Orochimaru-- or rather,
Orochimaru, now do you see?
I'm more than a mere puppet.
-Hey, are you all right?
-Meat-- I want to eat some meat.
-That's our Choji, always
thinking with his stomach.
-Uh-huh.
-Even though he lost,
the least we can do
is take him out for
some barbecue beef.
--[coughs] [sigh]
It's finally over.
HOKAGE (VOICEOVER):
At long last,
we can begin the final rounds.
-And with that match, the
third exam preliminaries
are now finished.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): "A Shadow
in Darkness-- Danger Approaches
Sasuke."
IRUKA (VOICEOVER): I wonder
what's happened to Naruto.
-[laguhs]
Come on, let's go sneak outside.
Heh.
Iruka-sensei is
kind of distracted,
so this is our big chance.
-Going somewhere, Konohamaru?
You're not planning on
sneaking out again, are you?
KONOHAMARU: Uh, I need
to use the bathroom!
IRUKA: Liar!
HAYATE: I commend all
those who have advanced
to the finals for the third
level of the Chunin exams.
Well, there's one person
missing, but still,
congratulations.
-Sensei?
-Hm?
-I have a question for you.
-About Sasuke?
I'm sorry.
I don't know much
about that I'm afraid.
But I wouldn't worry too much.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): From here
on, it's up to you, Sasuke.
-Sakura, I have to leave,
so I'm counting on you
to get the details
about the finals.
-Huh?
Oh, OK.
HOKAGE (VOICEOVER): Here,
including the absent Sasuke,
we have five ninja
from the Leaf Village,
three from the Sand Village,
and one from the Sound Village.
-And now, I will
begin the explanation
of the final rounds.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Well, it's about time.
[bell gong]
[birds chirping]
-The preliminaries are done.
They're moving on
to the final rounds.
-While all of
these countries are
busy racing to expand
their military might,
the birds are still singing.
I believe that this
country of ours
has been at peace for
far, far too long.
-Then let me do it.
-Hmm?
I don't know.
How much fun would be to take
out an old man like the Hokage
anyway?
-So that's how it is.
What's the problem?
You're not still having
second thoughts about it,
are you Orochimaru?
From now on, each of
the Hidden Villages
will clash with each other in
a long and violent struggle.
Even the Sound Village
won't escape that violence.
And it's your intention
to be the trigger for all
that hostility, by using
Sasuke as a bullet.
Isn't that correct?
-[chuckles] You guess very well.
So well that it's a
bit creepy, in fact.
-You give me too much credit.
I still didn't know about your
plans involving Dosu, Zaku
and Kin.
While gathering
information on Sasuke,
I wanted to learn the skills
of those three Sound ninja.
So I clumsily confronted
them and let them attack me.
I learned a lot.
It seems that you
don't quite trust me,
Orochimaru-- at least, not yet.
-Was it necessary to tell
you, my right-hand man,
about those three ninja?
My silence is proof of my trust.
I trusted in you to act
without that knowledge.
For that very
reason, I'm planning
to leave Sasuke in
your capable hands.
The curse mark that
was give to him
appears to have been
sealed by Kakashi.
But in any event, that
is not my concern.
While there is still some
darkness left in his heart,
we must act.
And that's why I want
you to abduct him.
-It's unusual for you to
act so hastily, is it not?
-Perhaps, but there's
still a little something
that's troubling me.
-Is it Naruto Uzumaki?
OROCHIMARU (VOICEOVER): Hmm,
you're quite sharp, aren't you,
Kabuto?
OROCHIMARU: Sasuke
is driven by revenge.
He's burning to bring
down his older brother
Itachi for what he
did to their family.
He won't rest until
he achieves that goal.
And yet, when we
fought each other,
even though he knew he
couldn't prevail against me,
he came at me without
any fear of death.
I didn't think he'd be
the type of person who
would be in such a hurry
to die a meaningless dead.
According to your
information, contact
with that nine-tailed one
has altered Sasuke's heart
and mind.
So much so that Naruto now
holds a certain influence
over our Sasuke.
The think to do is to get Sasuke
away from him immediately.
Because then, it will be so
easy to make him mine forever.
Mm.
-Very well.
-Kabuto, wait.
You know if it's your
desire to stop me.
I'm afraid your only chance
is to kill Sasuke now.
You can't possible
hope to kill me.
Even if you did have the
courage, it's worthless.
You're no stronger than Kakashi.
[laughs] I'm just kidding you.
But you'd better run along now.
Don't forget I'm
trusting you, Kabuto.
OROCHIMARU (VOICEOVER):
Hmm, that face.
I wonder what's
going on in his head.
HOKAGE: In the final
rounds, each of you
will put your battle
skills on display.
You'll demonstrate
the power and control
that you've achieved in
your respective disciplines.
Accordingly, the
final battles will
commence one month from now.
-Wait, we're not going to
do it right here and now?
-This is to provide a suitable
period of preparation.
-What do you mean by that?
-Simply this-- in addition
to announcing the conclusion
of the preliminary matches
to each country's leaders,
we must also have some time
to prepare and distribute
the summons for the
final selection.
Not to mention
that you examinees
are going to need
time to prepare
for something that
is this important.
KANKURO (VOICEOVER):
This old man
sure likes to beat
around the bush.
-Look, I don't really get
what you're trying to say.
What's the point of this?
-I mean that your adversaries
and prepare yourselves,
you need time.
Even though up to this
point, all the battles
have been real
battles-- as I'm sure
you can all attest-- they
were conducted on the premise
that you were fighting
an unknown enemy.
But that's no
longer the case now
that you've battled each other.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
Yeah, seriously.
I would never have dreamed
that this guy could turn sand
in a weapon.
-So in order to make the
finals fair and just,
we're giving you this month.
Each of you must
embrace the opportunity
to practice hard and
learn some new tricks.
Because by now, everyone
here knows your techniques.
So using your old, tired
tricks is a sure way
to lose in the finals.
And remember to get
some rest as well.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): This
isn't some vacation.
I won't have any time to relax.
I've got to train
harder than ever.
[beeping]
--[sigh] I suppose brilliance
can sometimes have its
disadvantages.
We failed to avoid
Orochimaru's watchful eye,
and it's most unfortunate
for both of us.
KABUTO (VOICEOVER): He's so
young, but the seeds of evil
have already taken root,
just waiting to be exploited.
He'll be ripe for
Orochimaru's special Ninjitsu.
-Kabuto.
Most interesting.
Perhaps Kabuto really is going
to kill Sasuke after all.
[beeping]
-Well, well, Kakashi,
foiling my attack
by striking from
my blind spot, huh?
But now, are you
ready to take me on?
Next time, you should
station at least 10 guards.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
The Anbu Black Ops unit
that I assembled was
defeated so easily.
-You-- you're not an
ordinary Genin, are you?
You caught a whiff of me
and immediately readied
your weapon.
Quite impressive.
-You overestimate me.
-So what do you
want with Sasuke?
Finding you like this, I ought
to haul you in for questioning.
-What?
Just you? [laughs] I
wonder if you could.
-Are you looking to take me on?
I know who you are.
You're the Leaf Medical
Corps Chief's son.
Your name, what was it?
Kabuto Yakushi.
What are you?
One of Orochimaru's puppets?
-Even if you did
take me into custody,
you'd never be able to prove
I have any connection to him.
-Just answer my question.
-And if I say no?
-I'm the one asking
the questions.
Now give me some answers.
-Look, you'll have your
answers soon enough,
even if I'm not here.
So why don't we skip the
middleman and let me go?
-You smart-alecky little brat.
I'll teach you to mess
around with grownups.
-Come on, give me a break.
Don't be so arrogant.
The cards are clearly
in my favor here.
-I should've known.
[gasp]
I can't believe
I let him escape.
[beeping]
Impressive.
Just as I suspected,
the Dead Soul Jutsu,
where a ninja temporarily
animates and controls
a dead body, even
transforming its face.
Kabuto even stopped
his own heart
and eliminated all
traces of his scent
in order to escape by
impersonating a murdered Anbu
Black Ops ninja.
Being raised as the adopted
son of the chief of the Medical
Corps is a powerful
asset of his.
If it turns out
that someone as good
as him is working
for Orochimaru,
I've got to work harder.
-Now, with all of
that behind us,
I'd like to begin
winding things up.
But before we can
bring this to an end,
first, there is one
more important matter
to take care of for
the final rounds.
-Let's get on with it.
I mean, come on!
How long do we have to wait
until we start training?
-In a calm, orderly
fashion, all of you
are going to take one
slip of paper from the box
that Anko is holding.
-Everyone just
stay where you are.
I'll come to you.
Just take one.
-Hm?
-Good.
Now everyone has one.
Going from left
to right, tell me
the number that's written
on your slip of paper.
-I've got eight.
-Number one, of course.
-Seven.
-Five.
-Three.
-Nine.
-Two.
-Six.
IBIKI: And that means
Sasuke will be number four.
HOKAGE: Right.
Very good.
Now I'm going to tell you
about how the final selection
tournament is going to work.
-Eh?
-Is that what the
numbers are for?
Drawing lots?
-Ibiki, you may reveal which
ninja have been paired up.
-Yes, sir.
-[grunts]
DOSU (VOICEOVER): I'll
be waiting forever.
TENMARI (VOICEOVER): Is that
all the final rounds are?
A tournament?
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): I
have to fight an extra round?
I'll probably be expected
to avenge Choji's loss.
KANKURO (VOICEOVER):
Man, I'm glad I'm not
in the same hat
to draw as Gaara.
GAARA (VOICEOVER):
Sasuke Uchiha?
Perfect.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
I've got Neji Hyuga?
Right off the bat?
This couldn't be any better.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Sasuke
has to go up against him?
-May I ask you a question?
-You may.
-All right, if this
tournament, does
that mean there's only
going to be one winner?
I mean, only one of
us is going to be
able to become a Chunin then?
-Actually, it's
quite the contrary.
There are going to be several
judges for the final rounds,
including myself, the Shinobi
leaders, and the Kazekage,
the lords from the various
countries that ultimately will
be assigning your
missions to you.
Through this
tournament, these judges
will be able to make a thorough
evaluation of your abilities.
They will then decide
whether any or all of you
possess the qualities
required of a Chunin.
Even if someone loses
the first round,
they could still
become a Chunin.
-So there's actually a
chance that every one of us
who competes in
the final selection
could become a Chunin.
-Correct.
But conversely, there's also
a chance that none of you
will be chosen.
The advantage in fighting
more rounds in the tournament
is in getting more chances to
display your talents in front
of the judges who
will decide your fate.
Does that answer your
question, Shikamaru?
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): This
is just about the biggest pain
ever.
-I thank you all
for your patience.
Now let us adjourn
until next month.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
In the second round,
will it be Sasuke or
that browless freak?
He's so strong he
took down Bushy Brow
without breaking a sweat.
-Sand Coffin.
ROCK LEE: [screams]
-You're one of the ones
I want to fight the most.
-[gasp]
[groan] I need to ask
Kakashi-sensei for help.
NARUTO: Hey, where's
Sasuke's room?
-Sorry, no visitors allowed.
-What?
No visitors? are you kidding me?
-Those are the rules.
-Ah, come on, lady.
-Naruto, this is a hospital.
Keep it down.
-Huh?
Oh, Kakashi-sensei!
Boy, am I glad to see you.
I gotta ask you a favor.
-Stop right there.
I already know what
you're going to ask.
So I've been looking
for someone that
can oversee your training
for the final rounds.
-Hold on!
Why can't you train me, sensei?
-I have other matters to handle.
I don't have time to
deal with you, Naruto.
-[grumbling] Hey!
Aha!
You're going to train Sasuke,
aren't you, Kakashi-sensei?
-Now, now, don't complain.
Listen, I found you an even
better teacher than me.
-Well, who is it?
EBISU: It is I.
-Hm?
You?
You closet pervert!
-Such insolence.
[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Believe it.
I can't believe this!
I don't care if Ebisu
is an elite tutor.
What can I learn
from some closet
pervert who's weaker than me?
I don't have time for this.
I have to get stronger
for the final rounds.
If this guy's really as
good as he's supposed to be,
he's going to have to prove it!
Next time, "Ebisu
Returns-- Naruto's
Toughest Training Yet!"
No matter what, I will
win the next match.