[theme music]
-I sense that Sasuke
has stopped moving,
but he's still a
long way ahead of us.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
If Sasuke's stop,
it must mean he's
caught up to them.
Come on!
-Did I just smell what
I think I smelled?
-Huh?
What is it?
What's wrong?
-What is it?
You smell some kind of trouble?
-Strange I never
noticed it before.
Sakura, did you use the
same shampoo as I do?
Back Minty Rainforest
Mist, right?
With extra body?
-What?
Are you kidding me?
-But I wonder why my coat looks
so much glossier than yours.
-Knock it off, will you!
It's no time to be talking
about hair products!
-Sorry.
Just making an observation.
-I smell like a dog.
I smell like a dog.
-Huh?
Sakura?
-I smell like a dog.
I smell like a dog.
-Gah.
Look what you've done.
Sakura!
-Where are you going?
You won't get very
far without me!
NARUTO: A mistake from the past!
A face revealed!
-Oh, geez.
-If it isn't Sasuke Uchiha.
-This is as far as you guys go.
KANKURO (VOICEOVER): Oh man.
Gaara, where are you
when we need you?
You picked a lousy time
to be out of commission.
This Uchiha kid is trouble.
-So, what're you
going to do, huh?
-Go, Kankuro.
Get Gaara away from here.
I'll take care of this one.
-Don't be a fool, Temari.
This kid's too much for you
to handle all by herself.
-Don't argue.
Our mission is to make
sure that Gaara is safe.
He's our first
and only priority.
Don't worry about me.
This is what I've
been waiting for.
Get going, Kankuro.
-No you don't!
Damn.
-Take this!
TEMARI (VOICEOVER): Bad timing.
I would have to
face this Uchiha kid
when my chakra is almost gone.
I'm in real trouble if
he uses his Sharingan.
I've got to force him to waste
a lot of his chakra and quickly.
It's my only chance.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
Should I use the Chidori
and try to take her our quickly?
Hell, why not?
TEMARI (VOICEOVER):
Hm He's holding back.
Saving his chakra for Gaara.
-Wind Scythe jutsu!
[shout] Is that the
best you can do?
Sand Storm jutsu!
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
I've got to do something
about that damn fan of hers.
TEMARI (VOICEOVER):
Still holding back.
This fight won't
last long that way.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): Oh well.
Can't be helped.
TEMARI (VOICEOVER): Good.
I was wondering when you
were going to get serious.
-Fire Style!
Phoenix Flower jutsu!
TEMARI (VOICEOVER):
That's more like it.
SASUKE (VOICEOVER):
Now to finish her off.
Fire Style!
Fireball jutsu!
Did I get her?
-Wind Scythe jutsu!
TEMARI (VOICEOVER):
I've got you.
-You're mine.
All mine.
Hah.
What the!
A substitution?
Oh no!
-Gotta run.
I've wasted way too much
time on you already.
-Hopefully I held him off long
enough for Gaara to get away.
-Whoa.
-Wha-- what the hell's going on?
-Who or what is that?
-What is this?
Who the devil are you?
-You have lost it, old man.
Don't you recognize me?
It's me, Orochimaru.
-It can't be.
Then you've mastered even
that forbidden jutsu?
[chuckling] It's been 10
years of hard work since I
left the village.
-You're no longer human.
You're a demon!
[laughter]
-So he did it after all.
-This is why I
could never choose
you to be the fourth Hokage.
Your mind and soul are twisted!
[chuckling]
-So I've finally
been found out, eh?
Aw, such a pity.
-Orochimaru.
Explain yourself.
What is the meaning of this?
-And after I set all
those booby traps
to give me plenty of warning.
I wasn't expecting you.
I should've known.
You could get past anything.
-A steady flow of
people have gone
missing from the village--
genin, chunin, even
ANBU black ops.
Many of them were
last seen with you.
And you've been acting
rather strange lately.
-You.
A superior shinobi.
How could you have
done such a thing?
-Now I'll have to
kill you as well.
-So you admit it.
Then it is all your
doing, Orochimaru.
But why?
What exactly are
you up to in here?
-Oh well.
Since you've caught
me red handed
there's no point in
pretending now, is there?
Its research.
I'm developing jutsu.
-And for that you sacrifice
your fellow shinobi?
-It's forbidden jutsu
you're after, isn't it?
Just what is it you want?
-I want everything.
-Everything?
What exactly?
-I want to know every
jutsu in the world.
And even those jutsu
yet to be discovered.
I'm like the one who first took
blue and yellow, consciously
mixed them together and
created a new color, green.
Only in my case, the
color blue represents
chakra, the color
yellow, a hand side,
and the green, a new jutsu.
And just as there are countless
shades of color in the world,
there must be an almost
limitless number of jutsu.
To find them, to unlock
the truth long hidden
from mortal eyes, that takes
years, endless experimentation.
Ultimately, the
truth reveals itself
only to one who
proves himself worthy,
one who is willing to
sacrifice years of his life.
But alas.
I've found there are not enough
years in even the longest life.
This mortal existence
is too fleeting.
Yes.
Even if I were named
Hokage, one day I would die
and that would be the end of it.
Orochimaru, what sort of
forbidden jutsu have you
been seeking here?
-Oh.
I think you've already guessed.
Eternal youth and immortality.
able The Immortality jutsu.
a technique for eternally
recycling one's spirit
on Earth.
In a way, it's a kind
of revival jutsu.
You find a body, a young body,
pour your spirit into it,
and make it your own.
I was using my old
familiar form until now,
because I wanted
our reunion to be
a nice nostalgic one, sensei.
Growing old is a
sad, empty thing.
I only have to look at you
to be reminded of that.
You will die here, old man.
While I move on to
another stronger body.
But first, I really
must thank you
and all the Leaf Village for
preparing my next body so well.
[gasp]
-Now I understand.
It's Sasuke Uchiha.
-Exactly.
You guessed it.
It's Sasuke I want.
-So you've mastered a jutsu
that preserves your soul forever
in the bodies of others.
How many bodies
has it had already?
How many faces?
-Hm.
Two or three, perhaps.
But I'll wait for Sasuke
until he's ripened a bit.
And then when he's been raised
and trained to my liking.
Tell me.
Which face would you
prefer me to wear?
Perhaps it would be easier for
you to look on a familiar face,
as you die cursing your
brief, wasted life.
-You monster.
Lord Hokage!
[chuckling]
-You really shouldn't
lower your guard, sensei.
That's your problem.
You've always been naive.
[panting]
ENMA: What's wrong with you?
This isn't like you.
-I'm sorry.
HOKAGE (VOICEOVER): Those eyes.
Always with malice and ambition
hidden just behind them.
Almost hidden.
I had seen it.
I had seen it, but
pretended not to notice.
Your strength and abilities.
You were the sort
of student that
comes along once
in a generation.
It was a time of
war and darkness.
We had need of ninja
like you, I thought.
I wanted to believe
that in you I'd
found the one worthy
of succeeding me.
You're right.
I was naive.
And it was my weakness then
that brought all these troubles
to us now.
-What are you planning to do?
Kill me, sensei?
-Ninja Art!
Summoning Tombstone!
-But can you go through with it?
I wonder.
Sarutobi-sensei!
-Hm!
-Kill him, Sarutobi!
Now is your chance!
Sarutobi, why?
-I couldn't do it.
Now I'll correct my mistake
and bury you once and for all!
It's time to end this!
-Hm.
I'm afraid it's too late now.
-Shadow Clone jutsu!
-No.
Shadow clones?
He's going to exhaust what
little chakra he has left!
-Heh.
You'll only shorten
your life, sensei.
I think your impatience is
getting the better of you.
-Could it be?
Is he?
[casting spell]
-Yes.
That's the bunch of hand signs.
I knew it!
[laughter]
HOKAGE (VOICEOVER): So, it's
just as the fourth Hokage said.
This is the Reaper.
The Face of Death.
Invisible to all but the
one who casts the jutsu!
-Whatever you're
planning, it's too late.
It's over.
I've won.
The Leaf Village will fall.
-You're forgetting that the
Leaf VIllage is my home.
And as Hokage, I am entrusted
with my home's protection.
I am head of the household,
the central pillar!
He would destroy my home
must first destroy me.
And I warn you, it
will not be easy.
-Genjutsu!
Infinite Darkness jutsu!
-What nonsense.
In the grand scheme
of time, you're
just a trivial footnote
in the brief history
of a cluster of huts
called the Lead Village.
[grunting]
OROCHIMARU: In time,
the Hokage stone faces
will crumble and be
worn down to nothing.
-You've never
understood that it's
far more than a mere
cluster of huts.
It is a place where every
year, shinobi are born, raised,
grow old, fight and die
to protect their home.
[grunting]
These people are precious to me.
We share a home.
We share a life.
And though we may not ties of
blood, they are precious to me.
They are my family!
[chuckling]
OROCHIMARU: The pillar
of your village.
A pillar full of
termites and rot.
I don't have to knock you down.
You're already falling.
-Heh.
And if I do fall,
you still will fail.
I am only one of a long line.
I carry this title in trust for
those Hokage who came before
and those who will come after!
I am the third Hokage!
You can't stop it
by destroying me.
A new and stronger Hokage
will take my place,
becoming the pillar, roof, and
walls that defend the village.
Now, Orochimaru, get ready.
For I'm about to perform
a jutsu that even
you haven't seen before.
Behold!
Sealing jutsu,
Reaper Death Seal!
[theme music]
HOKAGE: Every year,
shinobi are born,
raised and nurtured, trained to
fight to defend this village.
I've watched them grow.
I've watched some of them die.
They are precious to me.
We share a bond stronger
than any blood tie.
You've learned many
things, and yet this you
will never understand.
They are my family,
and I allow no one--
no one to attack my family!
NARUTO: Next time--
forbidden secret technique!
Reaper Death Seal!