[theme music]
-Byakugan!
I see you.
-Well, let's go!
I'm dying to show these
clowns what I've got.
-Is that right?
I hate to disappoint
you, hotshot,
but I've got a new jutsu
I've been working on, too.
[bark]
-Yeah, me too.
-All right, calm down.
First we make a plan and
get everything ready,
then we nail these bastards.
Looks like we've
caught them napping.
Hold on.
Where's Sasuke?
-He's in there,
inside that coffin.
[shring]
[sizzling]
[gasping]
[explosion]
[thud]
-Ungh!
[coughing]
-Well, well.
I thought I was flushing
a snake out of the bushes.
But all I got was
a couple of mice.
-Uh, wait a minute.
Calm down.
We're here to
negotiate, not to fight.
Can't we talk this over
like reasonable people?
-Heh.
Let's not forget your
friends, shall we?
-Whoa!
-Heh.
Ungh!
[explosion]
--[laughing] What
good's that gonna do?
Throw all the smoke bombs
you want, I've still got you.
These threads are so fine
they're almost invisible,
but they're stronger
than they look.
You may have already
encountered them in the forest.
-Darn it.
-So that double trap of
trip wires you set, in fact,
was actually a triple trap.
Heh.
That was clever.
So I guess that makes you
the smart one of the group.
-You're about to
be the dead one.
Ungh.
My body!
What's happening?
Nngh.
-Man, that was perfect!
Kiba distracted him
and you nailed him
with your Shadow
Possession Jutsu!
-Yeah, that's right.
You're not the only ones
who can spring a trap.
Thanks for making me look
good in front of the squad.
Appreciate it.
-Very impressive.
I'd be even more
impressed if I hadn't
mastered that technique as well.
-Huh?
What was that?
-Earth-Style Barrier.
[thud]
-Earth Dome Prison!
-Ahhh!
-Nngh!
[thud]
NARUTO: "Squad Mutiny:
Everything Falls Apart!"
[creaking and popping]
-[growling] Terrific.
-What is this?
-It's a barrier of some
kind, and we're stuck in it.
-Now what?
[sniffing]
[sighing]
-Since I'm the one who
caught them, I get them.
Anyone else have a
problem with that?
-Heh.
go ahead, but we're not waiting.
When you're done with
them, catch up with us.
[grunting]
[footsteps]
-Don't take all day.
-Hey, you out there!
Let us out right now!
-Yeah, like that's
going to help!
-It seems to be nothing
more than a dirt wall.
-It's some kind of jutsu.
We should watch our step.
It could be another
trap within a trap.
-Ha!
A wall's a wall,
and there's no wall
I can't punch a hole through.
-Yeah, it's worth
a try, I guess.
After all, we do have to do
something, despite the risk.
[slap]
-Hngh!
[thunk]
-Tunneling Fang!
[rock crumbling]
-Ugh!
[sizzling]
-Nngh.
SHIKAMARU: The damn
wall's re-building itself!
-Hey.
Did you just--
-Yes, we saw it.
-[yelling] Let us out!
-It appears to be more
than just a dirt wall.
-Byakugan!
The-- the wall is--
-It's what?
The wall is what?
-Our chakra-- it's absorbing
it, as if it were a sponge.
-Huh?
-Dah.
-Ahh.
-Great.
It's not enough that they bury
us alive in this oversized dung
heap.
Now they're trying
to steal our chakra!
You gotta give these guys credit
for thoroughness, at least.
-No way.
No way they can do this to us!
Whoever you are, let us
out of here right now!
-Huh.
MALE SPEAKER: [chuckling]
Thanks for the meal.
I've almost had my fill.
-Ugh.
Nngh.
Ungh.
[labored breathing]
-I feel like all my
energy's draining out of me.
-Nngh.
Something must be
done, Shikamaru.
And quickly.
SHIKAMARU: Ahh,
man, I was an idiot
to move in without knowing
the full extent of the enemy's
powers.
Now we're trapped like rats.
-That does it!
Stand back, guys.
I'm going to bust out of here
before my chakra's all gone.
Akamaru!
[bark]
-Have a food pill.
[growling]
-OK.
Ninja Art.
Human mimicry!
And as for me, Ninja
Art Beast Mimicry!
[blast]
[fierce growling]
[clap]
-Fang Over Fang!
-Atta boy, Kiba!
Go for it!
[thudding]
--[chuckling] Go on,
knock yourself out.
[poof]
[whine]
[sizzling]
-Nngh.
Look at that.
As soon as a crack
appears, it repairs itself.
Same with the ground beneath it.
[dog whining]
-Hey.
I give us about 10
more minutes of this
before our chakras are
completely drained.
[buzzing]
NARUTO: No use!
I need all my energy to
focus for the Rasengan.
There's no way in here.
I've lost too much
chakra as it is.
[sighing] This stinks!
-Hey, out there!
Let me talk to your leader.
I've got a deal to propose.
What I'm thinking is that
you let us out of this thing,
and in return, we
let you keep Sasuke.
-Huh?
-But Shikarmaru,
what are you doing?
-My favorite part, when they
start pleading for their life.
No deal.
I've never let a
captive go before.
I'm not about to start now.
-Aw, come on.
Listen, how about you just let
me go, and keep the others?
All this fighting,
I'm tired of it.
It's really not my thing.
-You little-- if
you're selling us out,
I'm gonna wring your neck!
-Shut up, Kiba.
For once in your life.
-What did you say?
--[laughing] So
much for teamwork!
So you're really
the leader, huh?
What a fine example
you're setting
for the rest of your team.
You see a man's
true character when
he's pushed to
the edge of death.
But you're hardly a man
at all, certainly not
one who's worthy of leading
a team of ninja into battle.
-I saved the most important
thing of all for last.
-Sacrificing Sasuke and
the rest of your squad.
Ha!
So that's a Leaf Chunin acts.
-All the same, Sasuke's a ninja
belonging to the Hidden Leaf
Village.
He's a comrade, and I'll put my
life on the line to help him.
That's the way of our village.
-Did you really believe
I might let you out?
You deserve to die!
-That does it, Shikamaru,
you dirty little traitor,
let's take this outside,
just you and me!
-What do you mean,
take this outside?
How you gonna to
do that, you idiot?
We're trapped in here.
-[growling] What'd you call me?
-I called you an idiot, idiot!
-That's what I thought you said!
-That's enough!
Everybody just shut up!
-Huh?
-Choji?
-Hmm.
-What-- what's Shikamaru doing
now, meditating or something?
Why is he just squatting there?
[growling]
[munching]
-Augh!
You've got to be kidding me!
Is that all you
ever think about?
-That's Choji, for you.
Responds to a crisis
by stuffing his face.
He's a real big help.
-Forget this!
I'm gonna give
shadow clones a try.
-Don't bother.
That ninja has infused
this wall with chakra
so that it repairs itself.
Your shadow clones won't work.
You'll only deplete
your own chakra.
The fact is, multiple
attacks won't work.
Our only hope is
taijutsu strong enough
to destroy it in one blow.
-Well, Choji has taijutsu with
a knockout punch even stronger
than mine, but just look at him.
He's got other
things on his mind.
[crunching]
-Come on!
What are we gonna
do, just stand here?
Neji, I need you to
focus those eyes of yours
on the wall directly behind
you and directly behind Choji.
Do you think you have
enough chakra left for that?
-I think so.
-Hold on!
You're not going
to listen to him!
-Naruto!
You still don't get it, do you?
Don't you remember
what Shikamaru
said when we came
together as a team?
-I know I usually seem like a
pretty lazy guy, but not today.
Because now I'm responsible
for your lives too.
OK, Choji.
Try to keep your
voice down, will ya?
Kiba, are you up
for trying to put
another dent in the
wall behind Choji?
-Well, sure.
I guess.
Heh.
I don't know what's going
on, but I'm always up
for getting wild.
Hyah!
Pummeling Fang!
[thudding]
-Huh.
They've got a lot more
persistence than brains.
-Nngh.
[sizzling]
-Yes, I see it.
That's the spot!
-Hmm.
-Huh?
-OK, now, Neji, mark the
spot with your kunai knife,
will you?
Choji, are you ready, buddy?
-Shikamaru, I was born ready!
-Good.
Then let's get started.
-Wait, let's get what started?
-As I said a moment ago,
this wall surrounding us
has been infused with chakra.
However, the strength of
the chakra won't be uniform.
Some points in the wall
must be weaker than others.
Shikamaru was able
to figure that out.
-He did?
Really?
You coulda fooled me.
When the heck was this?
-He's been watching
and taking it in.
For example, when Kiba and
Akamaru attacked the wall,
while you were watching him,
he was studying the wall
and he observed that some
areas repaired themselves
more slowly than others.
[shing]
[thunk]
-That led him to suspect
that it was at those points
that the chakra was the weakest.
-Hmm.
-Still, he needed to be sure.
That's why he spoke to
our captor as he did.
It was a ruse to trick him
into giving away his position.
And it worked, confirming that
Shikamaru's suspicions were
right.
The band of chakra
running through the wall
was this thinnest and
weakest at the point
opposite his position.
That's about right, isn't it?
[chuckles]
KIBA: Ha.
And all the time we thought
he was selling us out.
I gotta hand it to him.
He not only fooled the enemy.
He had us going, too,
NARUTO: And here we thought
Choji was stuffing his face
again when he was really just
trying to replenish his chakra.
KIBA: These two guys, I guess
they haven't been working
as a team all this
time or nothin'.
-It's up to you, Choji.
-OK!
Expansion Jutsu!
All right, here we go!
[roaring] Human Boulder!
[blasting]
[roaring]
[thud]
-Nngh!
What!
-Well, Choji.
There's no other
way of saying it.
That was awesome!
[chuckles]
[theme music]
KIBA: Whoa, hang on, Choji!
Are you nuts?
NARUTO: Kiba's
right, that's crazy!
NARUTO: Choji has a point.
If we waste too much time
here, we risk losing Sasuke.
NARUTO: Yeah, but--
CHOJI: Calm down!
I have a plan, OK?
MALE SPEAKER: Are you
thinking what I'm thinking?
MALE SPEAKER: Yeah!
MALE SPEAKER: What?
What are you thinking?
MALE SPEAKER: You sure?
CHOJI: Definitely!
It's time to unveil
my secret weapon!
NARUTO: Next time,
"Full-Throttle Power!
Choji Ablaze!"
CHOJI: Just leave it to me.
Chubbies rule!
[theme music]