[theme song]
-Listen, I already
told you everything
I know about the guy.
-So you first met Genno
at the ramen shop.
-What did the two
of you discuss?
-You expect me to
remember everything?
-That's what we're
here for, yes.
-If we analyze
your conversation,
we might determine who
Genno was working for.
-Uh.
-We're familiar with all
of your conversations
over the last two weeks.
Now we want to know what
was said before that.
-You can ask me all you want.
I'm tell you, I don't remember.
-Then we'll have to put you
under regressive hypnosis.
-Huh?
Regressive hypnosis?
-Using hypnosis, we can
recover lost memories
from your subconscious.
-No way!
-Just relax.
Back to the Past jutsu.
[sound of ticking clock begins]
Let's begin.
Let yourself travel back through
the pathways of your memory,
one day ago, two days
ago, three days ago.
Further into the past.
And finally, the day
you met the old man.
Where are you?
-I'm in the woods.
I was out there
training on my own.
Then it was lunch time,
so I headed for Ichiraku,
and that's when I saw him.
-So you didn't meet in the
restaurant, but just outside.
-Hey!
What you doing?
-Huh?
Oh, me?
I was just trying to decide if I
should go into this restaurant.
Is it any good?
-You're are not from around
here, are you, old-timer?
-Dah, Well, no.
I'm a freelance carpenter.
How could you tell, young man?
--[chuckles] Because everyone
from the Leaf Village knows
that Ichiraku's ramen is the
bestest ramen in the whole
universe!
-Well, that's quite a review.
SERVER: Here you go!
Enjoy!
[loud slurping]
-You're right!
This ramen is quite delicious.
-Isn't it?
[slurping] (LAUGHING) Ah.
Thanks for the grub!
-You finished your bowl already?
-Well, I am a growing
boy, you know?
Even an extra I
can't fill me up!
-I see.
Then maybe I'll share the
rest of mine with you.
-What?
You sure?
-All yours!
-It's my lucky day!
[slurps ramen] Oh, man.
Thanks a ton!
-Mm-hm.
-Oh, man!
This is good!
[slurping continues]
That's it.
Then after we finished our
ramen, we said our good-byes.
-When did you meet him next?
-In front of Ichiraku again.
-Byakugan.
There's nothing here either.
-All right, then.
-Byakugan.
Oh.
-Nothing.
[dog whimpers]
-Looks like he must have used
some kind of odor neutralizing
element in last
night's smokescreen.
That guy came prepared.
-Then why did he get caught?
-Huh?
I guess the Anbu were just
too intelligent for him.
-Of course they're intelligent.
But he must have
foreseen that going in.
So then, why didn't
he have another escape
route planned out in advance?
-You know, you're right.
It doesn't make any sense.
But there's really no
way to find out now.
-Dead men tell no tales.
-This way, please.
-What are they doing to him?
-We're putting his
body back together.
-Do they really have to do that?
TECHNICIAN: He was
in very bad shape.
From what I understand, he had
paper bombs from head to toe.
Miss, would you like to wait
outside 'til we're done?
-Yes, I think I would.
-I'll stay, thank you.
-You will?
[exhales] You're stronger
than I am, Sakura.
-It had eggs and barbecue
pork, and he treated me
to everything.
-Does this kid only
think about ramen?
-Shh!
-Wait.
I remember one other thing.
-Huh?
-Yes?
What is it?
-He showed me a photograph.
-A photograph?
-It was a picture of some
kid who looked around my age.
It was right after
I asked the old guy
why he was being so nice to me.
-Ah, well, I have a grandson.
You see?
He's about the same
age as you are.
So in a way, you're not
really a stranger to me.
Some day, after I
retire, my grandson and I
are going to go off and live
the life of treasure hunters.
-Are you serious?
-Yes.
Oh, my word!
You finished your
bowl that fast?
-Yup. [laughs]
-Then I suppose you'll
just have to finish mine.
-Thanks, old man!
You're the greatest.
Huh?
Uh, what happened to your hand?
-Hm?
Oh.
I got this scar when I
cut myself with a saw.
-Oh.
And then after that,
the old guy gave me
more of his yummy ramen.
-But Genno has no relatives.
-So the story about
his grandson was a lie?
-We started telling
him the day after that.
Looks like we're not going to
get any more information out
of the boy.
-I doubt Genno would've
been careless enough
to divulge anything
important, even to a genin.
-An emergency communique
from Lady Tsunade.
[ticking clock]
-Ah mm.
-I see.
So nothing unusual in
any of the buildings?
-They were all built
according to the blueprints.
There are no signs of
any traps or sabotage.
-Mm-hm.
-Do you suppose that
he was just acting
like a carpenter as a cover
so he could get passage
into the village?
-Well, it's too soon to
know that for certain.
But if he just came here
to steal those plans,
there's no reason to
pretend to be a carpenter.
-By the way, while we
were combing the village,
what were you guys looking into?
-We talked to some of
this carpenter buddies
down at a site, and
started checking out
a list of all the places
that they said he frequented.
But so far, we haven't
dug up many clues.
-That's weird.
The whole list is restaurants?
-Yeah.
Seems like the only time
the old guy ever went out
was to grab a bite.
OK.
Hinata, go check
on Ino and Sakura
over at the medical center.
Neji, Lee, you guys are
with Kiba and Shino.
-(JOINTLY) Um.
-Understood.
-It's a drag, but we
should head out, too.
-Shikamaru.
-(BOTH) Hm?
-Lady Tsunade has sent for you.
-I wonder what she wants?
What?
The village hidden
in the waterfalls.
-They've moved all their ninja
into battle-ready position.
Apparently, they're claiming
it's just a normal training
exercise.
-Training exercise, huh?
-Need I say more?
They've used this tactic before.
Assemble all their forces under
the guise of a big practice
run, and end up
invading another land.
-And there's more
to it than that.
Apparently, just
before he arrived here,
Genno briefly stayed in the
Hidden Waterfall Village.
It wouldn't be
surprising to find out
there's some sort of connection.
-Hm.
TSUNADE: We've already
mobilized most of our ninja.
They're on their way to
the Waterfall Village now.
If they see anyone
crossing the border,
I told them to treat it as
a full-scale enemy invasion.
-Nuh?
-Shikamaru, take your
group and head over
to the border to assist.
-Hm.
Well, if you really
want my honest opinion,
there's no reason for us to go.
-Uh.
But, but Shikamaru--
-What are you getting at?
SERVER: Naruto?
Hey, Naruto!
-Huh?
-If you keep standing
there like a zombie,
you're going to scare
off my customers.
-Oh, uh, sorry.
Come to think of it,
I never actually saw
that guy finish a
single bowl of ramen.
There's no way he hated ramen
the entire time, is there?
But then, why was he hanging
out of Ichiraku so much?
Mm.
[growls]
-Please explain
yourself, Shikamaru.
-Sending in 10
genin and 1 chunin,
it's not going to make
too much difference
in the scheme of things.
-And what is your point?
-Something's not quite right.
-Ah.
-We're missing something
about this guy, Genno.
And I think I figured
out what it is.
All we've learned
about his life is
that he was remarkably
unremarkable.
He was an average
carpenter, did his work,
never stood out, never
made any big mistakes.
He didn't have any
friends, didn't have
any enemies, either.
If he disappeared one day,
nobody would miss him.
They wouldn't think
twice about it.
He was the kind of person
who could just fade away.
His undercover
technique was so good,
it ought to be in the
Shinobi textbooks, which
is why it's so odd that
a brilliant Shinobi like
that would let himself get
pegged by the Anbu so easily.
Doesn't it seem a
little strange to you?
-Yes, that's true.
-And then, when he
was trying to escape,
he had no problem evading
the Black Ops before,
but this time, they caught him.
For a trap expert, it was a
pretty pathetic way to go.
Not to mention the
fact that he just
gave up all those blueprints.
It doesn't make
any sense, unless--
-Well?
---unless everything that's
happened was part of the plan
from the beginning.
-Uh!
-Could it be?
-His true identity
being revealed.
Dying right in front
of the Anbu guys.
What if it was all part
of an elaborate plot?
What if he knew we'd be worried
about the Hidden Waterfall
Village, that we'd send everyone
away to face that threat?
Leaving our village
defenseless like that,
we might just be dancing
in the palm of his hand.
TSUNADE: Interesting theory.
But all the hard
evidence says we
need to protect ourselves
from this invasion.
-That's true.
But still--
-I hear you.
Sending in a bunch
of lightweights
like 10 genin and 1
chunin, it wouldn't really
change the outcome of
the battle, now would it?
-Ah?
-All right, Shikamaru.
I'll have you and
your group continue
investigating the
Genno incident.
-Mm.
Understood.
-Hey guys, where you been?
SHIKAMARU: Sorry.
Didn't mean to keep you waiting.
-Eh!
This hurts my brain.
Remind me why we have to look
through all these stupid books
again?
-Believe me, I don't
want to do it either.
But research is the basis
of good investigation.
-Yeah, but still,
there's so many numbers
my eyes can't take it.
-I'm sorry.
I looked everywhere,
but I can't find.
-OK.
No problem.
-What was that?
-Aw, he was just trying to
find the old recommendation
letter that made them realize
the one Genno used was a fake.
-Why the heck did you bother
having him dig that up?
-Just a hunch.
(THINKING) I wonder,
did they just lose it,
or did the old guy
make it disappear?
Either way, it's still shady.
I mean, the forgery's the one
he should have gotten rid of.
Ditching the old letter
does him no good.
-This is the spot where
the explosion occurred.
-Looks like somebody
already collected
the physical evidence.
-Yeah.
The Anbu leave nothing behind.
-Everyone, look!
-(ALL) Hm?
-Check out this tree.
It's burned on both sides.
-With all the paper bombs
that went off, of course
it got burned.
-Yeah, but why is it
charred on both sides?
-She's right.
If the blast came
from one direction,
there wouldn't be marks
on the back of it.
-To leave these kinds
of burns, the explosions
would have had to come
from multiple sources.
-But the Anbu saw it happen.
And they reported that
all of the paper bombs
were wrapped around the man's
body when they want off!
-Don't be so sure about that.
After all, the Anbu
had to take cover
to protect themselves
from the blast.
I doubt any of them witnessed
the actual explosion.
-(TOGETHER) Ah!
-Hey!
This one's got burns
on both sides, too!
[barking]
-The same pattern on this tree.
-Wait a sec.
What if a ring of bombs
on the surrounding trees
were set off first, then the
huge explosion in the center?
If he timed the explosions
close enough to each other,
then it might have
seemed like one blast.
-This Is a good point.
But in order to
do that, he would
have needed time to set it up.
Before he made it here, Genno
was being chased by the Anbu.
And they had him cornered
right when the bombs went off.
-Maybe they chased him, or
maybe he was leading them here.
[all gasp]
-So all along, he wasn't
trying to get away from them,
he was drawing
them to this spot?
-Hm.
It's possible.
-If that is true, then
it is safe to assume
there were other
elements to his plan.
-Can we be sure those paper
bombs really took him out?
-(TOGETHER) Oh!
-It's over.
You can come back.
-O-OK.
-I don't get it.
Wasn't his identity
confirmed by Anbu?
TECHNICIAN: Yeah.
-Oh.
-Well, what do you
mean, take a look?
I'm not a medical ninja.
How am I supposed to know
what I'm looking for?
I wouldn't even
know where to begin.
Ah.
Sakura!
Our suspect here, he
was undercover working
as a carpenter in
the village, right?
-Yeah, that's right.
Why?
Did you notice something?
-It's his hand.
It's way too clean.
My family owns a
flower shop, and I've
been serving people
there since I was little.
When I see someone's hand, I can
tell what kind of work they do.
Carpenters' hands are
much rougher than this,
with scrapes and cuts, and a
tramp ninja's hand would never
be that squeaky clean.
-And what does that mean?
-May I take a look?
-(BOTH) What?
-Byakugan!
I thought so.
There's no trace of a
developed chakra network.
This man has never
infused his chakra.
-Huh?
-And I overheard the
medics talking outside.
Even they have doubts
about his identity.
-(TOGETHER) Uh!
-This person is not a ninja!
-Hm?
-Status report.
The Hidden Waterfall
Village forces
are about to arrive
at our border, sir.
-They're fast.
And what about our defense unit?
-Our troops are
mobilizing quickly,
but they're not in full
battle position yet.
-(THINKING) If they launch an
attack before we take defensive
positions, we're done for.
-I just don't get it, sir.
Why would the Hidden
Waterfall Village--
-Whatever their reasons,
they don't matter now.
Once the enemy
crosses that river,
we must assume they
intend to wage war.
-And we will fight back, sir!
-[growling]
-Hm? (THINKING) The Academy?
I didn't see any
blueprints for the Academy.
Excuse me, sir?
Can I ask you something?
-Yes.
What is it?
-I found records
of some payments
the Academy made last month.
-What?
Last month?
Hm?
Oh, yes.
That's correct.
We were doing some repair
work to the facilities.
-Then how come there aren't
any blueprints for that job?
-What?
Of course, there are.
I don't know what to make of it.
Where do you think
they could have gone?
Hm.
[people talking outside]
-What is it now?
[people puzzling over something]
Huh?
Up there?
Hm.
-Is something wrong, Naruto?
-What's that?
-If they're going to strike us,
then what are they waiting for?
-Status report.
Sir, the enemy army that
was gathering at the border,
their forces have
started to retreat.
-They what?
-Apparently, it really was
just a training exercise.
-But then, where are
the stolen blueprints?
-What?
This looks like--
-(TOGETHER) Hm?
CHOJI: Is that
Shikamaru's house?
[gasps]
-That's a blueprint?
-Yep.
For security reasons,
they were drawn up
using a complex code that's
really tough to break.
(THINKING) But still,
why are the plans
Genno stole falling
out of the sky?
[closing theme song]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): All the
new students are totally lame.
CHOJI (VOICEOVER):
They should be
snacking on chips and barbecue.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Reading manga.
CHOJI (VOICEOVER):
Eating box lunches.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): All
you think about is eating.
LEE (VOICEOVER): You
want them to ditch class?
-Sure, even study hall.
Right!
-No, no.
Even when teacher
is present, they
immerse themselves in training.
That is a thing of beauty.
-(NARUTO AND CHOJI) It is?
-It is so inspiring
to watch, that I
shall help them
in their training!
-(NARUTO AND CHOJI) What?
Next time, "The Missed Target".