[theme music]
KIBA (VOICEOVER): I got you.
[grunt]
[barking]
-Dang it.
What's going on here?
[barking]
KIBA (VOICEOVER): I know I
hit him, but nothing happened.
And where the hell did
that attack come from?
-Get ready, Akamaru.
We'll hit him from both
sides with Fang Over Fang.
[bark]
Let's do it.
Fang Over Fang!
-Summoning jutsu!
-That's not good.
Oh well.
-I'll play a little
melody of death for you.
[grunting]
KIBA (VOICEOVER):
What's with this guy?
What the?
[chuckling]
-Why this is perfect, Sakon.
There's one of them
for each of us.
-It's hard to believe
the four of them
are taking this much time.
Do you think the
Leaf Village sent
some of their heavy
hitters after them?
Or are they just wasting
time playing around?
[chuckling]
-I can guess who's
slowing them down.
It's either Jirobo with
his appetite or Kidomaru
and his penchant for play.
-But Sakon's the most dangerous
with that temper of his.
He's never satisfied until his
opponent his dead, even when he
should leave things be.
Plus, he thinks he's the
strongest of the four,
so he's always showing off.
[chuckling]
-Oh, I don't know.
Tayuya's blood boils just
as hot as Sakon's does.
But in any case, nothing
will go wrong now
that we've sent him after them.
Kimimaro, he'll
clean up anything
that would prove
a nuisance to me.
You can be sure of that.
-Oh.
-You're not taking
Sasuke anywhere!
-There sure is a lot of
garbage scattered around here.
But trash is just
trash after all.
It simply needs
to be cleaned up.
-Shut your mouth.
-Come then.
-I'm gonna crush you!
[shout]
[punching sounds]
[flute plays]
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): So
this is her melody of death.
[flute plays]
[gasp]
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER): So she
controls him with that flute.
Darn it.
She keeps getting further away.
What do I do?
Aw, man.
This is not good.
-Akamaru!
-Ah hah.
So you're the real one, huh?
Multiple Fist Barrage!
Once more.
[chuckling]
My brother and I get
along really well.
Usually Ukon just
sleeps inside of me.
But when the moment calls
for it, he comes out to play.
KIBA (VOICEOVER): So
this is his ability.
-He can poke his arms,
legs and head out
of anywhere in my body, to
either attack or defend.
Just like this.
[barking]
-Multiple Legs Barrage!
Nothing more painful
than a three-legged kick.
Now try this on for--
-Enough, Sakon.
We don't have any
time to play around.
Let's wrap this up.
We're going to Phase Two.
-Oh all right.
You're always so
impatient, brother.
[whimpering]
-I gotcha.
You're thinking those horns
aren't just for display,
aren't you?
KIBA (VOICEOVER): You're right.
As soon as that
other guy popped out,
his chakra increased ten-fold.
Things seemed hopeless before,
but now we're really screwed.
[laughter]
-What are you in the
mood for, brother?
-Ripping him apart.
[shouting]
[grunting]
[punching sounds]
-All right.
I suppose it's time
to get serious.
I'm ending this fight right now.
-You're full of big talk, huh?
It's funny.
You took the words
right out of my mouth.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
These guys are persistent,
but I'm starting to
get the picture here.
Still, this isn't
going to be a cakewalk.
KIBA (VOICEOVER): I
think we're finished.
[barking]
-What are you saying?
You're telling me
you want to try that?
[bark]
-We can't, Akamaru.
There's nobody
here to back us up.
It'd be way too dangerous.
You understand, don't you?
If we whip out that
jutsu, we'll use up
what little chakra we have left.
And when it's over we,
won't be able to move.
If we miss, we'll
have died for nothing.
[biting sound]
-Akamaru.
KIBA (VOICEOVER): I
must be a lovely master,
for you to bite me like that.
OK, Akamaru.
It's just like you said.
We're all out of options.
Wolf Fang over Fang it is.
[barking]
[grunting]
[chuckling]
-Heh.
-Huh?
-Now, Akamaru.
[barking]
-Huh?
KIBA (VOICEOVER): Do
your thing, Akamaru.
Show 'em what all
that training was for.
-Dynamic Marking!
-What kind of cheap
trick is that?
KIBA (VOICEOVER):
OK, we're good to go.
-Inuzuka Style!
Man Beast Transformation Combo!
[roar]
-Two Headed Wolf!
[chuckling]
-All of that flourish
and it's nothing
but a big, slobbering mongrel.
-What could that
mutt possibly do?
-Take this!
-The drool!
-Sakon, you idiot!
On your right!
-Son of a--
-Wolf Fang Over Fang!
KIBA (VOICEOVER): Heh.
How'd you like that?
Wolf Fang Over Fang's
revolution speed
is so intense we can't see
anything while we're attacking.
But it'll cut you even
without direct contact.
And if it hits you, you'll
be ripped to shreds.
-Huh?
[gasp]
-Heh.
Careful, kid.
Don't get ahead of yourself.
-This is perfect.
We were just thinking it'd
be a good idea to separate.
KIBA (VOICEOVER): What the hell?
He split in two!
-It's true, If we had taken
the full brunt of that attack,
it would have been bad.
-But now the real battle begins.
KIBA (VOICEOVER): Damn it.
[whimpering]
KIBA (VOICEOVER):
Yeah, I know, Akamaru.
Only one more chance
for Wolf Fang Over Fang.
The next shot will be our last.
[bark]
KIBA (VOICEOVER): This
time they're going down.
-Wolf Fang Over Fang.
It's no use hiding.
I told you.
We're not using our eyes.
We marked you earlier on.
So now we can track
you just by scent.
-Summoning jutsu!
Rashomon!
-Impressive Rashomon
is our greatest defense
for lord Orochimaru.
And for him to
dent it like that--
-But it doesn't matter.
[laughter]
-This is the end!
[whimper]
-Akamaru!
KIBA (VOICEOVER): No.
You were trying to protect me.
-He did it again!
Ugh!
My eyes!
KIBA (VOICEOVER): Damn it.
-This is worse
than the last time.
It's some sort of acid.
My eyeballs feel
like they're burning!
KIBA (VOICEOVER):
Where'd the other one go?
-Boo.
Looking for someone, kid?
[groaning]
-Go wash your eyes
in that river.
I'll take care of the rest.
A unique ability, I know.
Helps with assassination.
A sharp sense of smell
and a set of claws
aren't going to be
enough to beat me.
Face it.
You're in over your
head, little dog.
You know that he
network in our bodies
through which chakra
passes is deeply
interwoven with our
organs, do you not?
It's an intricate maze threaded
through the tissues that
make up our organs.
The cells that
make those tissues.
Even within each
individual protein,
the very building
blocks of our cells.
Once in stage two,
I'm able to use chakra
to dismantle and
reconstruct these cells
and proteins at will.
Breaking my body down
into tiny particles,
I seep into my opponent, then
return to my original form
inside their body.
KIBA (VOICEOVER): Akamaru.
Sorry, Akamaru.
We've always been a team,
together, wherever we went.
[barking]
-Good boy.
Yeah.
That'll do it.
Of course, it's lucky for
us that the people caught
in that trap had
an earth scroll.
And now we're going to be the
first ones to reach the tower.
[whimpering]
-Yeah.
Something just the little guy.
I have no idea.
Akamaru has the
ability to sniff out
the level of an enemy's chakra.
But, man.
I've never seen him this
scared by it before.
Whoever those ninja up ahead
are, they aren't normal guys.
-Now the seventh match.
Naruto Uzumaki and Kiba Inzuka.
-Wait a second.
Are you kidding me?
What's the puppy doing here?
He's just going
to get in the way.
-Deal with it!
I never go into to
battle without Akamaru!
[barking]
-All right.
Come on, Akamaru.
[barking]
-Take this!
[grunting]
[barking]
-He fell for it!
Naruto, if I were you,
I'd let Akamaru go.
[growling]
[roar]
-What the heck happened?
What was that thing you fed him?
How come all his
fur just turned red?
-Are you sure you want to
stick around to find out?
Let's go, Akamaru!
[barking]
-Beast Mimicry!
Man Beast Clones!
[growling]
-Let's finish this now.
On All Fours jutsu!
Now I gotcha.
Man Beast Ultimate Taijutsu!
Fang Over Fang!
[scream]
[whimper]
[barking]
-Akamaru.
[bark]
-Have a food pill.
[roar]
-OK.
Ninja Art.
Human Mimicry.
[bark]
[growling]
-Fang Over Fang!
But, I think this time
we're sunk, old friend.
-My cells are swimming
freely throughout your body.
I can even generate parts
that are solely yours.
In other words, we're
slowly fusing together.
We'll be sharing a body.
-Sharing a body?
-That's right.
I'm going to snuff out of
your life as only I can.
By eradicating all the cells in
your body from the inside out.
-I see.
In that case--
-Huh?
[groaning]
-What if I do this?
Then what happens?
-Suicide?
you're crazy!
-Time for you to die.
[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
Who is this guy?
What's with this Kekkai Genkai?
[grunt] I've never seen or
heard of anything like this.
Doesn't even matter how
many of me there are.
I can't even scratch the guy.
I don't know what the deal
is with the five dances,
but there is one
thing I do know.
I'll stop every one of 'em!
Next time-- to each
his own battle!