[theme music]
[singing in Japanese]
-This fog's so thick,
you can't see anything.
[sniffing]
-The bridge isn't far now.
Our destination's just
ahead-- The Land of Waves.
-(YELLING) Whoa!
It's huge!
-What?
Quiet!
I told you, no noise!
Why do you think we're
traveling like this, huh?
Cutting of the
engine and rowing,
moving through the dense
fog so they don't see us.
-Mr. Tazuna, before
we reach the pier,
I want to ask you something.
The men who are after
you, I need to know why.
If you don't tell
us, I'm afraid I'll
have to end this mission
when we drop you ashore.
-[grunts]
NARRATOR: The
Assassin of the Mist!
-I have no choice
but to tell you.
No, I want you to
know the truth.
Like you said, this
is beyond the scope
of the original mission.
The one who seeks my
life is a very short man
who casts a very long
and deadly shadow.
-A deadly shadow?
-[grunts]
-Hmmm.
Who is it?
-You know him-- at
least, I'm sure you've
heard his name before.
He's one of the wealthiest
men in the world--
the shipping magnet, Gato.
-Huh?
Gato?
Of Gato Transport?
He's a business leader.
Everyone knows him.
-Who?
Who?
What?
-Gato is a very powerful tycoon
from a famous company, that's
true.
But below the surface, with
the same ruthless methods
he uses to take over
businesses and nations,
he sells drugs and contraband
using gangs and ninja.
-[gunshot]
-[groan]
-It was one year
ago when Gato first
set his sight on
The Land of Waves.
He came to our island
and used his vast wealth
to take total control of
our transport and shipping.
Anyone who tried to stand in
his way simply disappeared.
In an island nation, a
man who controls the sea
controls everything-- finance,
government, our very lives.
But there's one thing
he fears-- the bridge.
When it is complete, it
will join us to the land,
and that will break his control.
I am the bridge builder.
-So that's it.
Since you're in
charge of the bridge,
you're standing in
this gangster's way.
-That means, those guys
we fought in the forest,
they were working for Gato.
-Ahh, Hmm.
-I don't understand.
If you knew he was dangerous,
knew he'd send ninja
to eliminate you, why did
you hide that from us?
-Because The Land of Waves is
a small, impoverished nation.
Even our nobles
have little money.
The common people who
are building this bridge,
they can't pay for an
A or B ranked mission.
It's too expensive.
If you end the mission
when you drop me ashore,
there will be no bridge.
They'll assassinate me
before I reach home.
But don't feel bad about that.
Of course, my sweet little
grandson will be upset.
He'll cry,
(CHILD-LIKE) "Grandad!
I want my Grandad!"
-[groaning]
-Oh, and my daughter will
condemn The Ninja of the Hidden
Leaves, denouncing and blaming
you for abandoning her father
and living her life in sorrow.
-[groaning]
-Oh, well.
It's not your fault.
Forget it.
-[groaning]
-Well, I guess we
have no other choice.
We'll have to keep guarding you.
-Oh, I'm very grateful.
I win.
-We're approaching the shore.
Tazuna, we've been
very fortunate.
No one has noticed us so far.
-Nice going.
-Yeah!
-That's as far as I go.
Good luck.
-Right.
Thank you for
taking such a risk.
-Just be careful.
-OK.
Take me to my home, and I mean
get me there in one piece.
-Right.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
The next ninja
they send won't
be chunin, They'll
be jonin-- elite ninja
with deadly skills.
Hmm.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Uggh!
I'm not letting Sasuke get
all the glory this time.
Believe it!
[grunting]
-Over there!
Hm.
It was just a mouse.
-(ANGRILY) Mouse?
Yeah, right!
Everyone can see
through your stupid act!
You're so obvious,
it's embarrassing!
-Naruto, those are kunai knives.
They're dangerous!
-[growling] Stop trying to scare
me, you scruffy little dwarf!
-Hey!
Is someone hiding over there?
No!
They're over there!
[grunting] Over there!
-That's it, Naruto!
-Ah!
[groaning] Wha--
Why'd you do that?
Someone really is following us.
I mean it!
-Yeah, right.
Quit lying and acting
like a dumb kid!
-[gasp] Naruto!
Look what you did!
-Ah!
A rabbit!
Ah!
Oh, I'm sorry little rabbit!
I'm sorry!
-All this fuss over a rodent?
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
That's a snow rabbit.
But the color-- they only
have white fur during winter,
when days are short and
there's little sunlight.
This rabbit was raised indoors
away from the light, which
could only be for one purpose--
a replacement technique.
So they're already here.
[crying]
ZABUZA MOMOCHI
(VOICEOVER): Hmmm.
No wonder the Demon Brothers
failed in their mission.
It's the copy ninja from the
village hidden in the leaves.
Kakashi, the Sharingan.
-Look out!
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
That must be--
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Here
it is-- my chance to shine.
Believe it!
I'm ready this time.
I'm not going to
lose out to Sasuke!
-Well, well, if it
isn't Zabuza Momochi--
rogue ninja from the
village hidden in the mist.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Rogue ninja?
Whatever.
Nothing's gonna stop me.
Ready?
Go!
-You're in the way.
Get back.
-But why?
-He's not like
those other ninja.
He's in a whole other league.
If he's our opponent,
I'll need this.
[gasps]
-This could be treacherous.
-Kakashi of the Sharingan
Eye-- Did I get that right?
It's too bad, huh?
But you'll have to
hand over the old man.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Uhh.
Sharingan.
What is that?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
What's he saying?
Does he have some special power?
ZABUZA MOMOCHI
(VOICEOVER): Sharingan.
-Now quick!
Manji formation!
Protect the bridge builder,
and stay out of this fight.
I taught you teamwork.
Now it's time to use it.
-Oh--
-I'm ready.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Ah!
His eye!
What is that?
-Well, looks like I get to
see the Sharingan in action.
This is an honor.
-Everyone keeps saying,
Sharingan, Sharingan.
Will someone please tell
me what Sharingan is?
-Sharingan.
A rare power that
resides in the eyes.
The user of this visual
jutsu, or doujutsu,
can instantly see and
comprehend any genjutsu,
taijutsu, and ninjutsu,
and reflect the attack back
on the attacker.
The Sharingan is a special,
rare form of doujutsu.
However, there's more to
the Sharingan than that.
A lot more.
-You got it right, boy.
But you only
scratched the surface.
The Sharingan can analyze
an opponent's technique,
and then copy it to
the smallest detail.
As for you, jonin, in
the assassination unit
of the hidden mist, we
had a standing order
to destroy you on sight.
Your profile was
in our bingo book.
It called you, "The man who
copied over 1,000 jutsu."
Kakashi, the copy ninja.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): What?
Is Kakashi Sensei
such a famous ninja?
-Wow, that's so cool!
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
Wait a minute.
The Sharingan is
a rare trait that
only occurs in a few
members of The Uchiha Clan.
My clan.
Could he be--
-Enough talking.
I need to exterminate
the old man, now.
[grunts]
-So, I'll have to eliminate
you first, eh, Kakashi?
So be it.
-He's over there!
-Standing on the water!
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER):
He's building up
a huge amount of chakra.
-Ninja art.
Hidden mist jutsu!
-He vanished!
-Sensei!
-He'll come after me first.
-But, who is he?
-Zabuza Momochi-- the
ex-leader of the Hidden Mist
Assassination Unit.
He's a master of the
silent killing technique.
-S-s-s-s-silent?
-As the name suggests, it
happens in an instant--
without sound or
warning of any kind.
It's so fast, you
pass from this life
without realizing
what has happened.
The Sharingan cannot
fully neutralize it,
so don't lower your guard.
[gasps]
-Well if we fail, we
only lose our lives.
-How can you say that?
-The mist is getting
thicker and thicker.
-The Land of Waves is
surrounded by ocean.
The swirling mists
are ever present.
-Sensei.
ZABUZA MOMOCHI
(OFFSCREEN): Eight points.
-What's that?
ZABUZA MOMOCHI (OFFSCREEN):
Larnyx, spine, lungs, liver,
jugular, subclavian
artery, kidneys, heart.
Now, which will
be my kill point?
SASUKE (VOICEOVER): What an
intense thirst for blood.
One shallow breath, one
tiny movement of the eye
is enough to bring
on instant death.
If it goes on like
this, I'll go insane.
The clash of two jonin
intent to kill-- I
never felt anything so chilling.
It's as if my own life
has been choked off.
No, I can't bear it!
I'd rather take my own life!
-Sasuke!
Calm down.
I'll protect you with my life.
All of you.
I will not allow
my comrades to die.
Trust me.
[gasps]
-I wouldn't be so sure.
It's over.
-Sensei!
Behind you!
-Die!
ZABUZA MOMOCHI (VOICEOVER):
The water clone jutsu.
It can't be.
Even in the mist.
He saw through my illusion
and copied it in an instant.
-Don't move.
Now it's over.
THEME SONG: Cultivate your
hunger before for you idealize.
Motivate your anger to
make them all realize.
Climbing the mountain,
never coming down.
Break into the contents,
never falling down.
My knee is still
shaking, like I was 12.
Sneaking out the classroom
by the back door.
A man railed at me twice
though, but I didn't care.
Waiting is wasting
for people like me.
Don't try to live so wise.
Don't cry cause you're so right.
Don't try with fakes
or fears, cause
you will hate
yourself in the end.
Don't try to live so wise, Don't
cry, cause you're so right.
Don't try with fakes
or fears, cause
you will hate
yourself in the end.
Don't try to live so wise.
Don't cry, cause
you're so right.
Don't try with--
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Oh no!
It's not over!
Kakashi Sensei fell
into Zabuza's trap!
I've got to escape.
He'll annihilate me for real!
Uggh!
This pain.
Hey, what am I doing?
I made up my mind, didn't I?
I swore I wouldn't run
away no matter what!
Next time-- "The Oath of Pain."
Nothing's going to stop me.
Believe it!