[theme music]
[running water]
-What's this?
Where does this water lead?
[yells]
Hey, what's the matter
with you, Naruto?
Snap out of it.
Come on.
Get a hold of yourself.
[laughter]
CHISHIMA: Naruto!
-Those kids are having
such a good time.
CHISHIMA: Naruto, hey!
Naruto!
-Huh?
Hey!
You jerk, let go-- This
is that lake from before.
-Hey, Naruto.
-Chishima, it's you.
Wait a sec.
So I guess it must
have been your voice I
heard calling out my name.
-How do you feel?
Are you all right?
-I should ask you that.
You ought to rest
with that injury.
-Don't worry.
It's not that serious.
We just have to find Lady Toki.
-You're right.
And where is Moso hiding?
We need him too.
-Looking for me?
-Moso.
-Lady Toki.
-Chishima, forgive me.
I'm sorry I had to deceive
you for such a long time.
-No.
Don't worry about that.
I had my suspicions
for a while now.
-You people know too many
of this land's dark secrets.
But you'll be
taking those secrets
to the grave when I send
you all to your doom.
-Finally showed us
your real face, huh?
-I am called Hoki,
a wandering ninja.
And no matter how you
may try to stop me,
I shall take over this once
peaceful land for myself.
Water style.
Water dragon jutsu.
-Chishima!
-Chishima, talk to me.
You gotta hang in there.
-So was I fast enough?
You're OK?
Thank goodness.
-Chishima!
Lady Toki, I remember.
There were so many wonderful
days spent together
at this lake playing here
with you and with Lord Sagi.
In those days, the Land of
Birds was so tranquil, so gentle
and warm.
With all your resolve, you can
again restore the Land of Birds
to the way it once was.
-Chishima.
-Come on.
Don't give up on me.
-Naruto, please.
I beg this of you.
Help Lady Toki.
Will you help my friend?
-Yes.
And if a Leaf Village
ninja promises something,
it means he'll never
rest till it's done.
-Then promise me.
Protect her.
Lady Toki means
everything to me.
-Hold on a second.
Then you have feelings for her.
-That ramen was so good.
-It was.
I'll treat you again some time.
-Oh, Naruto, thank you.
Goodbye.
-No, wait.
Chishima.
-No.
Chishima!
--[laughs] That fool was just
another convenient pawn.
Certainly nothing to
get so upset about.
-Shut up.
He wasn't a pawn.
This man loved the Land of
Birds with all his heart.
And he gave his life trying to
protect it from evil like you.
I'm finished listening to you.
You've said enough.
Now you'll pay.
-Oh, will I now?
Threaten me all you
want, but what exactly
are you going to do to stop me?
Water style.
Giant vortex jutsu.
So long.
-Man, you're persistent.
-Gentle fist.
-That was careless, cocky
ninja Kakashi Hatake.
If I can take you down, one
who possesses the Sharingan,
everyone will know of the
wandering ninja's power.
-What?
A clone?
-Sorry to disappoint
you, but I don't even
need to use the
Sharingan on you to win.
-It's this way.
-Naruto.
-If we follow this--
-Yes.
It will lead us to Naruto.
-Unfortunately, dear, I
cannot allow you to avenge
your beloved fallen comrade.
But out of sympathy,
I can send you
to where your father
and brother are.
-I don't care.
Just get on with it.
Do it quickly.
-You sure know when
to give up, don't you?
-What does it matter.
They're dead.
I'm the only one left.
My whole family is gone.
And now that I can't
even take my revenge,
there's no point to life, none.
-You're a courageous woman.
All right.
Then so be it.
I will grant your wish.
Prepare yourself.
-Naruto, wake up.
Save Toki.
Wake up and save
my little sister.
I entrusted her with the
future of the Land of Birds.
I left her my watch.
But Toki became obsessed with
her intense desire for revenge.
For her heart, it's
like time is stuck.
And as a mere soul,
I cannot change it.
So I bet of you, please
change it for me.
Push her time out of the
past and towards the future.
-What was that?
A vision?
-Goodbye.
What the--
-Hold it right there!
-What the--
-Naruto.
-You're not going
to believe this,
but I think I just met
your brother in a dream.
-You saw Sagi?
-And he told me something.
Your brother doesn't
want you to avenge
his and your father's death.
He said you should move on and
take care of this land instead.
-But--
-Not just for Sagi
but for Chishima too.
You gotta make the Land
of Birds great again.
You see?
Your life, it matters.
-Naruto.
-None of this will make
a bit of difference.
The two of you are going
to die here anyway.
-You're finished, Hoki.
You really think you'll
take over this land?
-What's this?
-No way.
A person who has an impure
heart, a heart that's
bent on revenge, can
never hope to govern.
Don't you get it?
The reason this was
such a wonderful place
was because Chishima, Sagi, and
Toki's hearts were connected.
They were one.
Even if you cheat your way
into a position of power,
you will never win over
the hearts of the people.
-Well, that's what you think.
-Fine, then.
Multi-shadow clone jutsu.
-You Leaf Village amateur.
No matter.
I'll gladly send you off to
meet the ones I've already
gotten rid of with my
multi-shadow clone jutsu.
-I hate to tell you, but it
ain't gonna be that easy.
-Go on and try me.
If you can even
find the real me.
-You're going down.
-Let's move.
-Aw, man.
Which of those guys is he?
Huh?
-Naruto, don't give up yet.
--[laughs] What idiot would
come straight to the front when
using shadow clones?
I was hoping you'd let me
have some fun, but oh, well.
Those who don't know
how to use their power
don't deserve to live.
-Don't get cocky.
I'm not finished
kicking your butt yet.
-You rat.
-Let's do it.
Naruto!
You want the real me?
Well, here I come.
Uzumaki Barrage!
I did it.
-Chishima.
Chishima, please don't leave me.
I need you.
Don't go.
You can't leave me here alone.
Open your eyes, I beg you.
-Lady Toki.
-Chishima!
You're all right.
-Lady Toki.
-Glad you made it, buddy.
-Naruto, I'm grateful.
-I was only trying to
complete my mission.
And besides, I had
to make sure that guy
pays for the crimes
her committed.
Right?
-You did.
-You know, I'm sure Sagi's
pretty happy right now too.
-That's right.
You met my elder brother.
-Sure did.
I saw Sagi in a dream.
But even if it was a dream,
it doesn't change the fact
that he asked me
to do something.
-What was it?
What did he ask you to do?
-Well, he said something
about how your time got stuck
and you needed a push.
-My time?
-Yeah.
He said that if you
forgot about revenge,
time would start moving forward.
-Thank you, Sagi.
-Hey.
-Huh?
-Naruto.
-Kakashi-sensei.
Neji, Tenten.
This stinks.
We don't get any bonus
now because of Moso.
The person who signs the
paychecks was the bad guy.
-It's not that bad.
-Yeah, it is.
-It looks like the
wandering ninja
are going to get a
pretty severe sentence.
-Good.
Now Toki will finally be able
to break this cycle of revenge.
[drumming]
-Hey, it's going to start.
-Everyone kneel before
the feudal lord.
-Oh.
-Oh, wow.
-My friends, I must
apologize to you
for falsely using my brother's
good name to deceive you,
and for not fulfilling
my duties as your daimyo.
I have done such wrong
that I should, perhaps,
relinquish my title
and pass it to another.
However, if somehow
you can forgive me,
I swear I will use my
position to reinvigorate
the Land of Birds for Owashi,
my late father, and Sagi,
my brother, and for
someone who loves
this land more than any other,
my dear friend Chishima.
-My lady.
-As long as I
shall live, I swear
I'll fight for the
sake of our land.
-She's doing a pretty
good job, isn't she?
-She's doing awesome.
-I am in full
agreement, Lady Toki.
And do you, the
people, also concur?
-Yes, sir.
-I'm humbled.
Thank you, Komi, for accepting
me as your new feudal lord.
Thank you all.
And a special thanks to
someone who taught me
what the true focus of my
life should be, a young ninja.
-You're embarrassing me.
-Please, travel safe on the
road back to your village.
-Thanks.
We will.
-Chishima, keep an eye on
Lady Toki now, will you?
-Thank you again, Naruto.
-Yes.
And you all must come back
and visit us again very soon.
-You got it.
But next time, I'm gonna
come here for a vacation.
-Goodbye.
-All right.
Goodbye.
Be well.
-See you around.
That Lady Toki, she was so nice
and downright gorgeous too,
wasn't she?
-I'm certain she'll
make the Land of Birds
as wonderful as it once was.
-Mm hm.
-But the way, Naruto, is it true
you ran into the ghost of Sagi?
-What, are you kidding
me or something?
Come on.
There's no such thing
as a ghost, Tenten.
I was just having a dream.
-Well, I'm not so
sure it was a dream.
-You what?
Wait, what are
you talking about?
-Naruto, do you remember
the very first time
we encountered the
cursed warrior?
-Yeah, sure.
-Mm.
The armor was empty
inside, right?
-Ah!
It's empty.
But that can't be.
U-- unless-- I remember.
But wasn't that just
some kind of trick,
like a string or a wire?
-No.
I definitely saw someone
or thing with my Byakugan.
-Hold on.
Now that you mention
it, at the time,
didn't you say there
was no sign of life?
-Yes.
I could see the
cursed warrior, but I
couldn't sense even
a flicker of life.
-A ghost, in other words.
-No way!
You're telling me
I was standing face
to face with a real, life ghost?
-Calm down, Naruto.
-No.
No way.
You're kidding me.
Please tell me this is
just a really bad joke!
[theme music]
-Pork.
-Chicken.
-Beef.
-Is this a guessing game?
-Sprouts.
-Spinach.
-Scallions.
-Oh, stir fried
beef and veggies.
-Egg.
-Nori.
-Seaweed.
-Um, a beef, vegetable,
and seaweed omelette?
-Pickled bamboo.
-Barbecued pork.
-Fish cake.
-I got it.
It's ramen.
-[buzz] Wrong.
-Sakura, you're so slow.
-Yeah, you should know by now.
-Miso pork ramen
with eggs on top.
Got it?
-How the heck would I get that?
-Next time.
Mix it, stretch it, boil it.
Burn, copper pot, burn.
[theme music]