[theme music]
-Kurenai-Sensei.
Asuma-Sensei.
Are you-- are you OK?
What happened?
-Naruto.
-There they are.
Hurry.
-The medical corps.
-We've got no time to lose here.
As soon as they've been
tended to get them back
to the village.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): What
in the world is going on?
-Don't worry about
the other prisoners.
Our primary objective
right now if Mizuki.
Got it?
-Right!
-We're close.
Aren't we, Tonton?
-Oink.
[sniffing]
-Here they come.
-[inaudible]!
-Oh, no.
It can't be!
Fujin and Raijin!
-Those two are Fujin and Raijin?
-Don't lower your guards
or we're done for.
-Hey, big brother.
Ginger pork or pork chops?
What will it be?
-Boy, I could go either way.
-All right, you two.
Where's Mizuki?
-Seems I'm rather
popular lately.
SHIZUNE (VOICEOVER): When
did he-- this isn't good.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER):
Just when things
were starting to quiet
down, this happens.
You've been a tough one to
wrangle with, Orochimaru.
[knocking]
-Reporting in, ma'am.
We've managed to get both
Krenai and Asuma to safety.
-Job well done.
Thank you.
I underestimated them.
Forgive me.
-Not at all.
I brought it on myself.
Let my guard down.
I wasn't expecting all of the
prisoners to have broken out.
-And if that weren't bad
enough, all the prison guards
were taken hostage.
What happened after
we were knocked out?
This wasn't any
random occurrence.
There was obvious
planning behind it.
They knew what they were doing.
-With that many
inmates running run
it was pandemonium in there.
He must have used
the chaos to escape.
Mizuki, that damn traitor.
[thud]
-[inaudible] Tsunade!
Come on, tell the truth!
Orochimaru's behind all this!
That's why you sent
Kurenai and Asuma, right?
-A lone inexperienced chunin
stole the secret scrolls?
He wouldn't actually be able
to do anything with them.
No, it would only make
sense if Orochimaru
were behind him, commanding
him, pulling the strings.
-Orochimaru.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): The
little brat was eavesdropping.
-Fine, forget I said anything.
-Let him go.
-Yes, ma'am.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I've gotta
pick up the trail somehow.
-And where are you off
to all by yourself?
-You already know
where I'm going.
I'm heading out to
get Sasuke back.
-Honestly.
At a time when we we're
running low on manpower, when
everyone in this village is
giving 110%, you want to-- ugh.
Here's the deal.
I've little doubt in my mind
that Orochimaru is tangled up
in this business somehow.
However-- this whole mess
with Sasuke and Orochimaru
has already risen way beyond
your ability to handle it.
It's too much for a genin.
You understand me?
I need you do the mission
you've been given.
[oinking]
What's wrong?
Is it Shizune?
-Hey, Tonton.
You're trying to
tell us something's
happened to Shizune, right?
[oinking]
I don't have a clue
what you're saying,
but she's gotten herself
into some kind of trouble,
hasn't she?
[oink]
That settles it.
Now I know what I have to do.
I'm gonna rescue
Shizune, then I'm
gonna find Orochimaru
in whatever
hole he's hiding himself in.
I'm gonna thrash that
guy like the rat he is,
and then I'm
bringing Sasuke back.
-Naruto, look--
-Come on, Tonton.
Lead the way!
-Naruto!
We need to deal with this fast.
-What's the problem?
-Kakashi.
-I, uh, picked these guys up on
the way back from my mission.
Lot of commotion around
here at the moment, huh?
-Yeah.
-So, what did
Naruto do this time?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): I know
it's not much to go on,
but I finally found
a link to Orochimaru.
-Just hold on.
I'm coming, Shizune!
The cavalry is on its way!
MAN (VOICEOVER): Naruto?
Where is he going
in such a hurry?
-Fujin, Raijin.
Time to head out.
-OK.
-Mizuki.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Whatever it
takes, I'll find you, Sasuke.
-Long time no see, Tsubaki.
-That lady captain sure
put up a fight, didn't she?
-No kidding.
After tangling with her
I'm starving to death.
[laughter]
I can't stop laughing.
Oh, wait.
I just did.
-The village hidden
in the leaves.
Been awhile since I
laid my eyes on it.
-Hey, big brother.
This rice is a little hard.
-It doesn't matter, dummy.
Food is food.
-Oh, right.
Boy, you're smart.
-What's this?
It's gotten all raggedy.
I think it's time
to buy a new one.
-You're right.
-What is it, Tsubaki?
What's wrong?
-I spotted a handful of
onbu out there earlier.
Why would they be in the
mountains away from everything?
-I see.
-You're not going to tell
me anything, are you?
You know, it's funny.
The Leaf Village, I mean.
It looks like it always did.
But while you were gone, Mizuki,
a lot of people were killed.
-Man, this soup is
fantastic, huh, big brother?
-Well, it's better than
what they gave us in prison.
-Are you leaving again?
-Yes.
-Please don't!
How can you go to him?
You know what kind
of man he is, Mizuki.
You mustn't.
[sobbing]
So many people lost their lives.
All because of Orochimaru.
Because of him the Leaf
Village is in shambles.
Even the Third.
If only you had
never gotten yourself
involved with that madman.
Then maybe you and I
would still be together.
-It'll be different
this time, Tsubaki.
Trust me.
I'm not going to let that
stupid little nine-tailed brat
much things up for me again.
And this time--
-That boy put his
life on the line
when Orochimaru tried to
destroy the hidden Leaf Village!
-The nine-tailed brat did?
That little snot.
-That's right.
He's not the monster
you made him out to be.
Please.
You have to abandon
this foolishness.
Don't you see?
It's over.
It's over and done with now.
Let it go.
-Oh, no.
This isn't over yet.
So the nine-tailed
brat's a hero now, huh?
What a laugh!
It never ceases to
amaze me how stupid
the people of this village are.
-Mizuki--
-Come here.
Soon all of Orochimaru's
power will be mine,
and then this village will
have a rude awakening.
They'll see.
With Orochimaru's power,
I'll be unstoppable.
And once the Leaf Village
is under my thumb,
we'll have the life
we've always dreamed of.
[cackling]
-Mizuki.
Mizuki!
Please!
This isn't you.
Where's that kind and
gentle man I used to know?
If you really love me, then--
give up this foolishness!
-Tsubaki.
-All right, then.
Guess I'll leave the rest
in your capable hands.
-Not so fast.
Here.
Another S-rank mission for you.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): Boy,
she's a real slave-driver.
-The Iruka squad has finished
rounding up all the inmates,
m'lady.
Oh, Kakashi.
I-- I beg your pardon.
-Not a problem, Iruka.
Good work.
-Looks like you and I won't be
getting a break anytime soon,
Iruka.
Summoning jutsu!
-What's up, sonny boy?
-Well, Iruka, I leave
the rest to you.
-Uh-- oh-- uh--
-Iruka, You have a mission,
and we haven't got much time.
-OK.
-Let's hurry.
We've taken too long as it is.
-Mizuki.
-Tonton.
What do you think?
They're here.
-Hold on.
It's me.
-Iruka-Sensei?
-Hey, Tonton.
[oinking]
So this is what I
was smelling, huh?
Thanks for all your
hard work here, Tonton.
I can track this now.
Why don't you head back?
You've earned yourself a break.
-Hey, Mizuki.
Weren't we supposed
to be hurrying?
-Yeah, yeah.
To Orochimaru's place.
-It's the nine-tailed brat.
-If you ever lay a hand on
my sensei, I'll kill you.
Take your best shot.
I'll give it back to
you a thousand fold!
[scream]
Sorry.
I kinda got carried away.
-I can't believe this.
That little
nine-tailed runt is--
-Do you think this
nine-tailed kid will be tasty?
-Yeah, sure.
Nine different kinds of tasty.
-Hey, sensei.
You didn't come out here
to drag me home, did you?
-Well, you wouldn't have come
back if I just asked you.
That's not really
your style, is it?
-Oh yeah, you got that right.
You know me pretty
well, don't you, sensei?
-Don't get carried away, OK?
The moment you let your guard
down is the moment trouble
will arrive.
-Wait a second.
-Is it them?
-Sure is.
And the stench of convicts
is growing heavier up ahead.
-All right, then.
What in the world
does this make?
-Smells like we're pretty close.
-Shizune!
Are you all right?
-Naruto--
-They've scattered
prisoner's garb everywhere
to throw me off the scent.
If I had to take a
guess I'd say they're
trying to buy some time.
-We almost Mizuki, but he
slipped through our fingers.
-Well, we're all just
glad that you're safe.
-Yeah.
-My men are still pursuing him.
We have to hurry.
-Right.
-They're close.
I'm getting the strong
smell of prisoners
hanging in the air around here.
-It's them, all right.
There's no question.
-All right.
Looks like it's almost go-time.
-But we're running
straight into a ravine.
The enemy could
attack us from above.
It would be safer
to make a detour
and get to higher ground.
-What are you talking about?
Our view is
completely wide open.
We're gonna be fine.
-They are trying to
buy time, remember?
We take a detour, we
might not catch them.
I don't believe it.
How can I have fallen
for such a trap?
-Stay on your guard, Naruto.
-It's not a dummy this time.
An enemy is near.
-A rock!
-Here we go.
-It's chow time!
-Naruto, watch your back.
-Shizune!
Hey, what's going on here?
Why is Shizune--
-Get away from her, Naruto.
That woman is an impostor.
-It's such a pleasure
to see you again.
Iruka, Naruto.
-Hey, Iruka-Sensei,
who is this joker?
-It's Mizuki, Naruto.
-Mizuki?
He looks a little different
than he used to, doesn't he?
-I'm not mistaken, am I?
You were that little loser
who couldn't pull off
a transformation jutsu, right?
-Are you trying to piss me off?
-What do you get think, Iruka?
I'm a new man, aren't I?
-It's true.
There's no comparison
with before.
-It's amazing what
being confined
to a dirty little prison
cell can do for your body,
don't you think?
I'm thankful for that, Iruka.
When did you realize it was me?
-When we found you hurt,
disguised as Shizune.
You said that your men
were still in pursuit.
The only way a subordinate
would leave their team leader
behind is if she had either
died or was on the verge of it.
Your injuries were minor.
-Straight out of the
textbook, huh, Iruka?
-And also-- you
didn't say a thing
when I suggested
we take a detour.
If you have a squad
in pursuit, you're
better off on higher ground
so you can scan ahead.
It was a clever game you were
playing, using those prisoner's
clothes not to buy time but to
draw us right into your trap.
-No way.
Your powers of analysis
are as good as ever.
It reminds me of the old days.
-Mizuki, abandon this
foolish path you're on.
-Please.
What could you possibly
know of the hardships
I've had to endure?
What are you two waiting for?
Crush them!
-Come on!
-Naruto, stop!
-Your fight is with me, Iruka!
-Naruto, get out of here!
-Don't worry, Iruka-Sensei!
I'll be fine!
-Naruto!
-Think you have the
leeway to look away?
-Run, Naruto!
-Darn it.
I'm not gonna lose.
Multi-shadow clone jutsu!
-Huh?
-Hey, wait a second.
-What the-
-That one-- and that one--
they all have the same face.
-One, two, three, four,
five, six-- hey, big brother,
I don't have enough
fingers to count them all.
-You dummy, Raijin.
You can use my fingers.
-See, Fujin, that's why
you are the smart one.
-What the heck is
wrong with those two?
-You want to get out of my way?
My business is with
Mizuki, not you.
-Did you hear that?
He said we were in
the way, big brother.
-But take a look.
Mizuki's too busy to
play with this kid now.
-Yeah, you're right.
He does seem busy, doesn't he?
-And anyway, if
we leave now we'll
miss out on the
big feast, brother.
-Oh my gosh.
That's right.
I forgot about the big feast.
-Big feast!
-These guys are kind of
throwing me for a loop.
Now focus, everybody.
Time for decisive action.
Let's do it!
-Kind of itches, huh, Fujin?
-Yeah, it itches.
-Huh?
My punches aren't having any
effect on these two idiots.
[music playing]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): [inaudible],
what's with these guys?
It's not just their size.
It's their power
and their strength.
None of my jutsu were
even making a dent!
Mizuki, you rat.
You're going down!
All right.
I don't have time
for you blockheads.
Come on.
Get it together, Naruto.
You've gotta find
a way around them!
Next time, a new squad.
Two people and a dog!
Uh-- a what?
[music playing]