[music playing]
[theme music]
[bell ringing]
[footsteps]
Uh, excuse me?
[bell ringing]
-Return of the morning mist.
[music playing]
[crying]
-Father and mother
shouldn't have died.
It didn't have to happen.
If only I'd been strong
enough, all of them
would still be alive.
My clan is destroyed.
[crying]
Damn it all.
[heavy breathing]
-That's enough for now.
Once I got a little
breakfast, I'm
going to get right
back to the grindstone.
Huh?
[music playing]
-Old man.
-Konohamaru.
What's up Konohamaru?
-Uh, not much, Naruto.
-I guess classes have started up
again over at the Academy, huh?
-Nah, not yet.
A bunch of the school
buildings got pretty messed up,
so all of the students are
helping to repair them.
-Ah, I've got you.
-What about you, Naruto?
You're still training, right?
-Yeah, sort of.
[music playing]
-What's up with you?
-Nothing.
What's up with you?
[in unison]
-So, um, huh?
-Hey, come on already.
What's the matter?
-Nothing's the matter.
What's wrong with you?
-Uh, never mind.
-I don't feel lonely or nothing.
-Huh?
-Lonely.
There's time for
stuff like that.
Everybody is working really
hard to rebuild the village.
-Konohamaru.
-Right now, I just want to do
whatever I can to help out.
So you'll have to
do enough training
for both of us, OK Naruto?
'Cause if you slack off, I'll
make it to Hokage before you.
-Ha!
You puny runt!
The next Hokage is standing
right in front of you.
Besides.
You've still got to make it
through the Academy first,
don't you?
Oh, that's right.
-Huh?
-Ah, there it is.
Here.
This is for you.
-A free meal at Ichiraku?
I can really have it?
-Yeah, don't worry about it.
I've got another one, anyway.
That little coupon is all yours.
-Oh wow.
Thank you, Naruto!
-Oh, hello there Konohamaru!
-Hey, good morning, guys!
-OK, I'm taking off.
Come on, lets' get to work!
-Mhm.
-Today we'll get to
work on the blackboards.
-I brought along some paint.
-Right!
Once I've had my
ramen from Ichiraku
I'll be ready for another
round of training.
[eagle cawing]
-Look at this.
[gasping]
-No!
Lord Kazekage.
They've been dead for awhile.
My guess?
Since before the Chunin Exams.
-I see now.
So that's what his game was.
Curse you, Orochimaru.
After the Kazekage was killed,
Orochimaru, or Kabuto, maybe,
assumed his identity.
We were careless.
[music playing]
-Sarutobi.
-You didn't think it
would be easy, did you?
Look who you were playing with,
one of the most renowned ninja
in all the five great
Shinobi nations.
You did very well, though.
Two of the five are
now out of the way.
-Shut your mouth.
I won't be patronized,
do you understand me?
I'll kill you.
-Forgive me.
I didn't wish to--
I'll grant you,
we didn't bring
down the village.
But let us not forget our
other objective, Sasuke.
You've done it.
Your leash is around his neck.
-And all that it
cost me were my arms,
and the entirety of my jutsu.
If I'd only gotten
hold of Itachi Uchiha
from the beginning, we
wouldn't be in this mess.
But it's too late now.
That dream has died.
Itachi is stronger than I am.
That is why I pulled myself
out of that organization.
-Kakashi.
The heck does he want?
-Breakfast, breakfast, oh boy!
Ready or not,
ramen, here I come!
[bell ringing]
-You know where he is?
-Yeah.
-Should be easy, then.
-Let's go.
-Oh, yes, that's it, that's it.
Oh baby, I'm telling you.
You've got to love
the Leaf Village.
The girls here are
off the charts.
-You're still playing
the buffoon, I see.
-Just doing a little research.
So, old man Homura,
and Koharu sensei.
What could you two scholarly
advisors want with me?
-Don't waste our time.
You know perfectly well
what this is all about.
-Come on, why the
long faces, guys?
From what I hear, talks
with the Sand Village
went off without a hitch.
-The Sand Village
has stated publicly
that Orochimaru was
responsible for all of this.
At any rate, they've offered
their complete surrender
to the Leaf Village.
So at the moment, their
betrayal is a moot point.
-For now we have no choice
but to accept their surrender
in order to shore up
our power in the region.
-That's correct.
However, the strength
of the Leaf Village
has just suffered
an enormous blow.
As things now stand,
our top priority
is preparing for the onslaught
we believe will come.
-We have no way of knowing when
one of the surrounding nations
might try to make a play.
Therefore, until the village
has regained its strength,
we've decided to gather the
top Shinobi from each squad.
And assemble an emergency
executive committee
to handle the situation.
But first.
We need a strong and
trustworthy leader.
It is more than just Orochimaru.
It is the seed of a
far greater struggle.
-Look, guys.
I don't know why you're going
to the trouble of explaining
all this to me.
But if you'll excuse me,
I've got to get back to work.
-I think you'll be interested
in what our plans are.
This village needs the
Fifth Hokage immediately.
-And yesterday, at
an emergency meeting
with the Lord of the Land
of Fire, it was decided.
We chose you, Jiraiya.
-Oh, I don't know.
It's not really up my alley.
-It has been decided.
Besides, if one of the renowned
Sannin is not suited, then
who else is?
-If you're so set on a
Sannin, there is another.
You're forgetting Tsunade.
-There's little doubt that
the child has the capability.
But it hardly matters.
No one even knows where she is.
-I'm sure I can dig her up.
You don't have a problem
with that, do you?
-But--
-Tsunade's got
the brains for it.
More than a loafer like me does.
What do you say?
-Very well, then.
We'll give it some thought.
But we'll send along three
members of the ANBU Black Ops
to accompany you on your search.
-You don't have to worry.
I'm not going to
make a run for it.
Besides, your men will
just get in the way.
Although, there is
one guy I wouldn't
mind having along for the ride.
I've stumbled across a very
interesting little egg.
-What?
This is so weird.
Sorry, kid.
No ticket, no ramen.
Those are the rules.
-No, no, no, no.
Wait a minute.
I just had one, I swear.
Where'd it go?
Man, don't tell me I gave
Konohamaru my last one.
[bell ringing]
-Come on in!
-Ah.
I want ramen!
-Hey guys.
You two seem to
be getting along.
-Ah.
Idiot.
Anko just asked me to pick up
some rice dumplings for her.
-What are you doing here,
aside from catching up
on your reading?
-I need to buy something
to put on a grave.
Plus I'm meeting somebody here.
I'm just waiting on Sasuke.
-Heh.
It's not like you to
be waiting on somebody.
Is it for Obito?
Be
-Obito?
-Yeah, kind of.
[music playing]
-Kakashi.
It's not like you
to show up early.
What gives?
-Well, sometimes I do.
[music playing]
-Let's eat somewhere else.
I don't have much
of a sweet tooth.
-Hm.
Is that so?
-Come on!
This is totally bizarre.
Where the heck did I
put that stupid thing?
[water flowing]
-You guys aren't from
around here, are you?
What are you doing
in this village?
-It's been a long
time, Asuma, Kurenai.
-The fact that
you know our names
must mean that you're a Shinobi,
formerly of the this village.
[bell ringing]
You're-- Heh.
Well, what do you know?
Itachi.
Itachi Uchiha.
[music playing]
-Are these friends
of yours, Itachi?
Well then.
I suppose I should
introduce myself.
Hope we can get
acquainted later.
The name's Kisame Hoshigake.
-Why should we wait til later?
When I can just wipe the
floor with you both now.
-Wow Itachi.
It looks like they hate
you as much in this village
as they do in mine.
-We know who you are, Kisame.
We've heard all about you.
You hail from the
Village of the Mist.
Suspected of espionage and
the murder of a feudal lord,
you're a rogue ninja
from the Land of Water,
wanted in every nation.
-You're a high level S-ranked
criminal, listed prominently
in the Bingo book.
Itachi, I gotta hand it to
you, the fact that you'd even
show your face in this
village, after what you did,
it takes some guts.
-I'm warning you two.
You don't want to
interfere with me.
It isn't my desire to kill you.
-You know, that's
pretty hilarious,
coming from a guy who
murdered his own people.
Now come on, out with it.
I know you didn't come
skulking in here, dressed
like that for no good reason.
What are you after?
[music playing]
-This guy is getting
on my nerves.
Can I kill him?
-Well I guess we're not going
anywhere without a fight.
Just try not to overdo it.
Your moves tend to stand out.
-They're as good as dead.
[music playing]
-I see.
Genjutsu.
[music playing]
-He's bearing down with
just the edge of his sword.
His strength is unreal.
-My massive blade shocks him.
[music playing]
It doesn't slide, it
cuts you to ribbons!
[music playing]
-It's about time, Kurenai.
-All right.
Let's end this.
-Genjutsu of that level
doesn't work on me.
-He used a kenjutsu reflection?
[music playing]
-Kurenai!
I wouldn't be looking
over there, if I were you.
-You live up to your reputation.
However, however this
is the end of the line.
For you, anyway.
[music playing]
-What?
Water style.
Water shock bomb jutsu.
He took up the same
jutsu that I did.
-Not that I'm
unhappy to see you,
but what are you doing here?
-Well, you know.
I asked you to take care
of those two earlier,
but I guess I got
a little worried.
-A shadow clone.
-Kakashe.
It's you.
-False alarm there, huh?
-Yeah, what happened there was,
I stuck in behind my headband
because I was so freaked
out it was going to fall out
of my pants or something
while I was working out
earlier this morning.
-Well, it all worked
out in the end.
Now go on, eat up, so
you can do your best.
-Huh?
-You've got more training
ahead of you, don't you?
-You bet I do!
I'm going to work my butt off!
-That's the spirit.
Here, have some more.
That one there is on the house.
Dig in.
-Oh man, thanks a bunch.
-Hey there, come on in.
-I had to see it
with my own eyes.
It looks like you do eat nothing
but ramen, huh, short stuff?
-Huh?
[mumbles]
[theme music]
-Itachi Uchiha.
He was the head of the
ANBU Black Ops at 13.
And single-handedly wiped
out the Uchiha clan.
I don't know why he suddenly
appeared out of the blue,
but I don't think
we'll be letting
him waltz out of here so easily.
Why have you come here?
What are you planning?
-Next time, eye to eye,
sharingan versus sharingan.
[theme music]