[theme music]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Tsunade's
Warning, Ninja No More!
[barking]
-'Atta boy, Akamaru.
You nailed it!
Now that's aerodynamic marking.
Now try it while spinning.
Watch your aim!
[barking]
KIBA: Ha ha!
Way to go!
-Is that any way to walk a dog?
No.
I think not.
I can't gather
specimens this way.
-Wow.
It must be so nice to have
something you're good at,
and that you love like
the three of you have.
SHINO: You will find your
strength someday too, Hinata.
-Yes, maybe I will.
-So, what is it?
There's something
you want to tell me?
-Oh-- uh-- well--
-Using the clues I've given
you, determine the quickest
route from your starting
point to the target.
Begin!
-Huh?
-Right.
OK, listen up.
I'm afraid that once
again, I'm going
to have to dismiss class early.
[cheering]
-But that problem
is your homework.
[groaning]
-Oh, man.
-Great, that means no
Taijutsu class today.
-Yeah, but we keep getting out
earlier, getting the whole day
off.
That can't be good, you know?
I mean, some time we're going
to have to learn all this stuff.
-You're such a goody goody,
isn't he, Konohamaru?
Huh?
What is it?
What's wrong?
Where are you going?
-Those are my
grandfather's things!
Where do you think
you're taking them?
-Honorable Grandson, we, uh--
KONOHAMARU: I said, where
are you taking them?
They belong to my grandfather!
-Uh, well, these things, they're
just in the way, you see?
So we thought it would be best
to put them somewhere safe.
-What do you mean,
just in the way?
You shouldn't even be
touching that stuff!
Who gave you permission?
-Well, we have to make
room for the next Hokage.
-Uh-- what?
-Yeah.
It's done.
The Fifth Hokage has
finally been chosen.
It's a big relief to
the whole village.
Now the one that's been chosen
is moving in, so we have to--
-No!
No way!
It's too soon for a new Hokage!
My grandfather was
everything to this village!
So poofy.
It reminds me of
my baby blanket.
Who are you, and what
are you doing here?
-What am I doing here?
Well, what are you doing
here, you pesky little runt?
-Who's a little runt?
I dare you to call
me that again!
-Oh, yeah?
So you're a glutton
for punishment, huh?
You're a pesky little runt.
-I'm warning you, if
you call me that again!
SHIZUNE: Lady Tsunade!
-Hm?
-You really should
be going in now.
The elders are waiting for you.
-Oink.
-Hm.
All right, Shizune.
I'm coming.
You watch your step, little boy.
-I wish you'd try
and behave nicely.
Because of course, I'm the
one everybody complains to.
TSUNADE: OK, OK.
-Huh?
I don't like being called
little boy, either!
Wah!
Hey, why don't you watch
where you're going?
-Why don't you watch
where you're standing?
-Is that you, Naruto?
What the-- Konohamaru,
is that you?
-Long time no see!
-Yeah!
You see an old lady around
here with a nasty temper?
Actually, she doesn't
look that old, but she is.
-I've seen her, all right.
-Huh?
Where is she?
-Who is she, anyway?
-Well, it's a long story.
Hm.
Gah!
I haven't got time
to tell you now!
I've gotta get up to
the infirmary pronto!
-The infirmary?
-Yeah, s supposed to be
some hot shot medical ninja.
Everyone's making such a big
deal about her being Hokage.
Has she forgotten what
she came here for?
-Hokage?
-Yeah, she's the Fifth Hokage.
You deaf?
Big deal.
All I care about is her doing
what she promised to do.
-I don't believe you.
-Huh?
-You're lying, Naruto!
It's not true!
-What's wrong with him?
-Seven.
There are seven birds within
50 meters of pillar number two.
What do you want, Tenten?
-Neji!
Hey, haven't you heard the news?
Lady Tsunade's returned.
It's really her.
Don't you want to see her?
-No.
Not really.
Not right now.
-Huh?
-Hm.
(VOICEOVER) There
were eight birds.
WOMAN: Listen
carefully, Tsunade.
We must send word do the feudal
lord that the Fifth Hokage has
officially arrived
in the village.
All the preparations
must begin at once
for the installation ceremony.
-Can't we just skip
the ceremonies?
They're such a bore.
WOMAN: Tsunade!
-OK, OK.
It comes with the job, I guess.
One of the perks
of being Hokage.
-Genma.
-Here.
-Aoba.
-Send out the word.
Everyone in the village
must be made aware
that in a few days from
now, we will officially
welcome the Fifth Hokage.
-OK.
-I hate you, Grandpa.
Why did you have to go and die?
A new Hokage?
-Oh, I hate all this.
My body's sore and stiff.
All I want is to
sit down and relax
with a nice, hot cup of tea.
-Yes, but Lady Tsun--
-Not so fast, grandma!
Before you start sucking down
some tea, isn't there something
you're forgetting about?
-What would that be?
-Come on, are you kidding me?
What about Kakashi-sensei
and Sasuke, and bushy brow?
-Oh, yeah.
I did forget about them.
-Well, if it isn't Naruto.
-Hm?
Shikamaru?
-What are you doing here?
Shouldn't you be somewhere
stuffing your face?
-How about you?
You're usually still
asleep this time of day.
-Very funny.
My dad asked me to come along
with him, but don't ask me why.
-Hm?
Hey, do they know each other?
-Greetings, Lady Tsunade.
It's been a long time.
-You're that kid
from the Nara family.
Hope you're still taking
good care of the deer.
I made a lot of good medicine
out of those antlers.
-Oh, yes.
The deer are fine.
-Who's the blonde girl?
And why is she talking to
my dad like she's his boss?
-Didn't you hear?
She's the Fifth Hokage.
-Huh?
-And she's no girl.
She's actually an
old lady in her 50's.
-Huh?
-I'll see you again
soon, no doubt.
-Yes, my lady.
-So long.
We're going to the infirmary.
I'll catch you later, Shikamaru.
I'll show you the killer
new technique I picked up.
-That's really the Fifth Hokage?
-Watch it, Shikamaru.
That woman is one
of the strongest
ninja you'll ever meet.
Don't let her good
looks fool you.
-Yeah?
-After all, there's
a reason she's
the only female among
the legendary Sannin.
-OK.
But I mean, a woman Hokage?
Not to sound
prejudiced or anything,
but is that's such a good idea?
[sigh]
-Come on.
You know what they're like.
You can never figure them out.
You never know where
you stand with them.
The smallest things could
put you on their bad side.
And always playing their
little mind games with you,
trying to get you to
do what they want.
They're just a big
pain, basically.
[sigh]
-Listen, Shikamaru.
-Hm?
-Keep in mind that without
women, you and I wouldn't even
exist.
And take my word for
it, they make men
better people than we'd
ever be without them.
Unlike us, even the
strongest of them
isn't afraid to be gentle
with the man she loves.
SHIKAMARU (VOICEOVER):
It's funny to hear
him talking like this,
tied to mom's apron
strings the way he is.
Ugh.
-Someday you'll understand
what I'm talking about.
Oh, uh, we'd better hurry up.
Let's finish up our
business here and get back.
You know how your mother will
chew us out if we're later.
Come on, Shikamaru.
-Well, if a woman has
made him a better person,
I'd hate to see what
he was like before.
-May I come in?
-Uh, who are you?
(VOICEOVER) Whoever she
is, she's beautiful.
-Sakura!
Sakura!
You'll never believe it!
She's gonna make
everything OK again!
Don't worry, Sasuke's
going to be all right now.
-Naruto.
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER):
Those flowers
weren't picked the same day.
Looks like she's been
visiting him for a while now.
-You must be the one
Guy-sensei told me about.
Oh, please, if you
can save Sasuke--
-Well, I'll see what I can do.
-Sasuke!
-Oh, Sasuke.
Sasuke!
-Hey, you're back.
Huh?
TSUNADE (VOICEOVER): Hm.
The little tough guy
has a soft spot, I see.
Huh?
-Come on.
You're not done.
TSUNADE: Disgraceful.
To be taken completely out
of the game by two low life
punks like that.
I thought you were
supposed to be the best.
-Sorry to disappoint you.
-OK, that's Kakashi-sensei.
Now just one more,
and you're all done!
-Rock Lee!
He's right next door.
Next door!
Lee!
Look who's here to see you.
It's Lady Tsunade.
[laughter]
-Is this one of
your students, Guy?
-Yes!
He's more than a student.
He's like a son.
-I see.
Naruto.
-Huh?
TSUNADE: Do you really have
time to be dawdling around here?
-You're right.
I almost forgot, I'm supposed
to meet Iruka-sensei.
-Better run along.
-Right.
I'll let you take it from here!
-All right.
IRUKA: Hey there, Naruto.
-Finally, Iruka-sensei.
Where ya been?
-I'm late.
Sorry.
It's all the preparations
for the Fifth Hokage.
-Well, OK.
Whatever.
MAN: There you go.
NARUTO: Ah!
This was worth waiting for.
-Naruto?
-Hm?
-You've sure come a
long way since the time
you were just a keep trying
to earn one of these.
-I'll say.
I'm glad you noticed.
Admit it, aren't you glad
you gave me this headband?
It looks pretty darn good
on me, don't you think?
-I wouldn't be so cocky.
You've still got
a long way to go.
Be careful that you
don't get a swelled head.
I want you to listen carefully.
The Leaf Village is
up against the wall.
We lost the Third
Hokage, as well as
many of our best shinobi.
Our strength's down
to less than half,
but even so, we still
have to carry through
with all the
missions we're given.
-Huh?
Why do you have to?
Turn 'em down if you
don't have the manpower.
IRUKA: Use your head, Naruto.
If we started turning
down missions,
it would be the same
thing as telling
the world that our
village is weak.
So everyone has to pitch
in, even the walking
wounded, like Kakashi-sensei.
-That's too bad.
You're up against it, all right.
-It concerns you too, hot shot.
You may be asked to
carry out missions too,
and to fight battles
you're not ready for yet.
-I'm ready.
But you can't expect me to
fight well on an empty stomach.
[laughter]
-I guess you haven't
changed that much.
-Hm?
-I know you'll do your best.
NARUTO: I'll take another bowl!
IRUKA: Whoa!
You're kidding?
TSUNADE: No one will
hold it against you
if you give up on
being a shinobi.
[gasp]
-Huh?
-Oink.
-But-- but you're not series.
You're exaggerating,
right, Lady Tsunade?
-His injuries have left
numerous bone fragments
embedded in his spinal column.
It's a miracle he can
still move at all.
He's physically
incapable of carrying out
the duties of a shinobi.
-This is some kind
of test, right?
You don't really mean that.
-Even if I were
able to operate--
-Don't listen to her, Lee!
That's not Lady Tsunade.
It's an impostor.
It's some kind of demon
that's transformed
itself to look like her.
Who are you?
What do you want?
-Oink.
[grunt]
-So I have no chance?
It is hopeless?
-No one but me could even
attempt the operation.
But even with my skills,
the risks would be enormous.
-What risks?
-The chances of it being
successful are 50-50 at best.
And if it should
fail-- he'll die.
[grunting]
ROCK LEE (VOICEOVER): I will
never give up, Guy-sensei.
I will be back,
stronger than ever!
This is horrible, Guy-sensei.
Why are you making me eat this?
-They're very rare Chinese
herbal medicine balls.
I'm told that eating 100 or
so should heal your injuries.
-Then I do not care
what they taste like.
I will eat them all.
Whatever it takes!
-I don't think they meant
all of them in one day.
TSUNADE: It's best if you
give up being a shinobi.
Find a different path.
-Lee.
Lee.
If I had known you
were going to do this,
I would have never
let you see him.
-Don't say that!
TSUNADE: I understand your pain.
Believe me, I get no
pleasure from this.
But he needs to know the
truth, and to know it now.
A choice has to be made.
Putting it off won't
make it any easier.
[theme music]
NARUTO: Stop this, Konohamaru!
Are you gonna come
out of there or not?
-Not!
-I'll buy you some ramen!
KONOHAMARU: Not hungry.
-Come on. you sure?
Not even with fried
pork and eggs on top?
KONOHAMARU: Shut up and go away!
-No kid's gonna talk
to me like that!
I don't care whose
grandson you are!
You get out of there right
now, or I'll drag you out!
Next time, The Will
of Fire Still Burns.
[theme music]