[music - Asian Kung-Fu
Generation, "Far Away"]
SASUKE: That proves that we
can't just trust appearances.
We have to come up with a way
of knowing that each of us
is who we say we are and
not just some impostor
using a transformation jutsu.
-Mhm.
-All right, then.
What do we do?
SASUKE: We need a password.
-Mm, what kind of password?
SASUKE: OK, listen
closely, because I only
want to say this once.
The question will be "When
does a ninja strike?"
And the response is "A ninja
waits until the time is right.
When the enemy sleeps
and drops his guard,
when his weapons lie forgotten
in the stillness of the night--
that is the moment for a
ninja to strike. " Got it?
-Whoa!
Ah!
I can't move!
Aaah!
Aaaaaah!
OROCHIMARU: You'd love to get
your hands on our Earth scroll,
wouldn't you?
[gasp]
-Well, when this is
all over, one of us
will have both scrolls--
and the other will be dead.
NARUTO: Ugh!
I can't believe it.
Is this really how it ends?
No way!
I can't just leave things
up in the air like that.
That's it!
I'm out of here, whether
slitherpuss likes it or not!
Shadow Clone jutsu!
Ya!
-It's no use-- I can't move.
-I expected you to be more of a
challenge-- how disappointing.
-(VOICEOVER): Move, Sasuke.
Move!
-(VOICEOVER): He overcame
the fear with pain.
So this prey is not so
helpless, after all.
-Uh ugh.
Aaah!
No!
Stay away!
OROCHIMARU: I sense your
fear and desperation.
-Ugh.
Uh ugh!
[sakura gasps]
OROCHIMARU: It's only natural--
the prey must never let down
its guard, not
even for a moment,
in the presence of its predator.
[evil laughter]
-NARUTO: It looks like
I came just in time.
-Uh uh.
-Naruto!
Oh, and by the way, what
was that password again?
-NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Naruto's
Counterattack-- Never Give In!
-OK, so anyway, what
is the password again?
-Forget it.
I know it's you.
You made it.
-Humph!
SASUKE: Naruto!
Get out of here!
What are you thinking?
You don't know what
you're up against.
Hurry!
Go now, while you still can!
-So Naruto, you managed
to escape from my friend.
Well done.
-(VOICEOVER): Hm, I get it.
So that wasn't just any old
random giant snake attack.
The snake was sent by her, or
it-- or whatever this demon is.
-(VOICEOVER): He doesn't get it.
He doesn't know what
he's dealing with.
What do I do?
NARUTO: OK, OK, I don't
know what's going on here,
but you've been picking on my
friends, and I don't like that.
So you'd just better
slither on back
into your hole,
Snake Lady, before I
make a pair of shoes out of you!
-Huh?
-(VOICEOVER): Little idiot!
He's just going to get
all three of us killed.
I've got to do
something-- but what?
-Uh, Sasuke.
-Humph!
-(VOICEOVER): It's no use.
There's only one way.
-You can have it.
-Hm?
-Huh?
-Uh.
-The scroll, right?
That's what you want.
All right, then.
Take it and leave us in peace.
-Huh?
-Mhm.
-What?
Sasuke, are you crazy or what?
We're going to just hand the
scroll over to the enemy?
No way!
What's wrong with you?
-Shut up, and stay out of it!
-What?
-Very wise, very sensible.
Sometimes the
helpless prey, if they
are to save their own skins,
realize that their only hope
is to distract the predator with
something even more precious.
-Take it.
[gasp]
-Stop playing the damn hero!
Just stay out of this
and leave it to me!
-Augh!
-Ah!
-Uh ugh.
You're a stupid fool!
You don't know
what you're doing!
-I may not know the password,
but I know who I am.
You're the one I'm
not so sure about.
How do we know you're
who you say you are?
-What do you mean?
It's him.
Don't be so stupid.
-What sort of nonsense is this?
It's me, you loser!
-Liar!
Liar!
You may look just like him,
you may sound just like him,
but there's no way
you're the Sasuke I know!
I don't care how
tough a fight you've
been through-- surrendering,
giving up the scroll--
when did Sasuke become a coward?
You keep saying I don't
understand what's going on,
but I do.
You've choked--
that's what it is.
-(CHUCKLING) Sad, but true.
Hahaha!
[gasp]
-It doesn't matter.
As far as the scroll
goes, I could simply
kill you and take it.
Ow.
-Huh.
Ah, let's see you try it!
-Don't!
Naruto, no!
-Ugh.
-(VOICEOVER): Forget Sasuke--
I'm going to have to do this
myself.
-Summoning jutsu.
[gasp]
-Naruto!
[birds chirping]
-That is no way
to treat a Buddha.
-What do you think?
It's some kind of
ninjutsu, isn't it?
-Well, or whatever
is, it's a problem.
Mm, just when things
were running so smoothly.
What a drag.
[birds chirping]
-We've got to report this.
Go get the proctor.
-Right.
[birds chirping]
-Mm-mm, nothing makes
dumplings go down
like a little sweet
red bean soup.
Ah, nice!
Om.
I guess it's about that time.
As soon as I finish
this little snack,
I'll see how the
kiddies are doing.
Mm, the quicker ones
will be finishing soon.
I suppose I'll just wait
and greet them at the tower.
There-- a perfect
Leaf Village symbol.
[giggling]
-Pardon, ma'am,
there's a problem.
-Huh?
What sort of problem?
-Corpses, ma'am-- three of them.
-Come on, I'm
trying to eat here.
-I think you'll
want to see them;
there's something
strange about them.
[gulp]
-Besides being dead?
-I went through their
belongings and found
their identification-- ninja
from the Hidden Grass Village.
All three of them
were registered
for the Chunin Exams.
They weren't just killed.
-All their faces-- they're gone.
-Yeah, there's nothing where
their faces used to be,
like they melted or something.
-(VOICEOVER): No doubt about it.
This is his jutsu.
Why is he here?
What's he doing at
the Chunin Exams?
-OK, I need photos of what
these three used to look like.
Where are their IDs?
-Right here, ma'am.
-(VOICEOVER): So this
is the face he stole.
Had it already happened when--
-OROCHIMARU: I was just
returning your knife.
-Why, thank you, Grass ninja.
-Uh, we've got big trouble!
-Huh?
-OK, get moving.
Tell Lord Hokage exactly
what's happened here.
And while you're at
it, tell Anbu Black Ops
they'd better get a couple of
convoys to the Forest of Death.
Meanwhile, I'm going to
head in after these guys.
Now go!
-Right!
-(VOICEOVER): He's come.
He's here in the
Hidden Leaf Village.
[wind blowing]
-OROCHIMARU: (CHUCKLING)
What a tasty little meal
you'll make for him.
Careful, he likes to
play with his food.
-Ahh!
Augh!
-Naruto!
-Augh!
Ow!
[heart beating]
-Ha ha.
Enough playing, finish him off.
[heart beating]
-Yeah?
Eat this!
-(VOICEOVER): But how?
It's impossible.
[yelling]
-Look at him-- he's gone nuts.
Whoa, where did he get that
kind of power all of a sudden?
-Ugh.
Yaaah!
Haa!
[screaming]
-Ehehuh ugh.
-That fire in his eyes,
there's no mistaking it.
-Whoa, is that Naruto?
-Oh, things have gotten
very interesting.
Now then, let's see how
well you do, Sasuke.
[heart beating]
-Sasuke!
[heart beating faster]
-Aaugh!
-This could be bad.
I've got to hurry and
pray I'm not too late.
-Hey kid, you're
not hurt, are you?
You scaredy cat!
-(VOICEOVER): Naruto.
-Hey.
-Yeah?
-You're not hurt are you?
Scaredy cat.
-Humph!
Sasuke!
Standing there frozen
like a frightened rabbit.
No way, you're not
the Sasuke I know.
Uh.
Augh!
[gasp]
-Hey!
Oh, man!
Disgusting!
Put me down before I yank
this tongue out of your head!
[yelling]
-(VOICEOVER): Extraordinary,
so the Nine-Tailed brat lives.
I see-- when your
anger is aroused,
some of the Nine-Tailed
Foxes' chakra is released.
What an interesting
childhood you must have had.
The spell that seals him within
you has appeared on your skin.
Five- pronged seal!
-Da!
Uh aah!
Ugh.
-Sasuke!
Hurry, do something!
-(VOICEOVER): For 12 years,
the seal has remained unbroken.
Soon, the demon's chakra and
the boys' will be as one.
But for now, he's
just in my way.
-(VOICEOVER): No way
he'll survive that fall.
-Hang on!
Sasuke, what's wrong with you?
Sasuke?
OK, say what you
like about Naruto--
that he's a pest, that
he gets in the way,
that he's just a kid.
But at least, he's--
he's doing something!
At least, he's no coward!
-Foolish little brother,
you can't kill me.
Your heat's not strong enough.
You're not strong enough.
Your life is too
precious to you.
So run.
That's right, run away and
live-- live with the shame.
-No!
[gasp]
-(VOICEOVER): Hm,
it's happened at last.
His Uchiha blood has
finally come to a boil.
-That's more like it.
-(VOICEOVER): I think I'll
play with him a little,
and learn the full
extent of his powers.
[evil laughter]
-No!
[music - Rythem, "Harmonia"]
-(VOICEOVER): I have seen my
own death if I fight this fight.
And to defeat my
brother, I must survive.
And yet, if I haven't the
courage to face this demon,
how can I ever hope to face him?
Calm down-- use your
eyes, trust your gift,
try to anticipate the attack.
Next time, "The Sharingan
Revived: Dragon-Flame Jutsu!"