[music - Asian Kung-Fu
Generation, "Far Away"]
-Withdraw now.
You know you were never
meant to be a ninja.
-[gasp]
-Who gave you the right to tell
her what she can or can't be?
Go on, tell this guy to
go jump in a lake, Hinata!
HINATA (VOICEOVER): Naruto!
-Hinata!
You just gonna stand
there and take that?
Do something!
You're driving me crazy!
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
You're right, Naruto.
Thank you.
NEJI (VOICEOVER): The look
in her eye has changed.
-If you don't forfeit the match,
you know what will happen.
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
No more hiding.
-Byakugan!
Defend yourself, my brother.
Hyah!
No!
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): "A
Failure Stands Tall!"
[heartbeat]
[heartbeat quickening]
[wet thud]
[cries out]
-So that's it, huh?
That's all there is to
the main branch's power?
[gasp]
-Wait!
What is going on?
I mean, I saw Hinata
hit Neji perfectly!
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
I'm not dead yet.
Hey!
-What's with this kid?
KURENAI (VOICEOVER):
It can't be.
HOKAGE (VOICEOVER):
So now I see why
he's called the most gifted one
to emerge from the Hyuga Clan.
[breathing hard]
-But-- you mean
all this time you--
-That's right.
I can see your chakra
points the whole time.
-Huh?
What is he talking about?
-On the chakra
network, there are
316 energy centers,
or chakra points,
and each are only about the
size of the head of a pin.
Hitting one directly
can affect chakra flow,
either halting it
or increasing it,
depending on how the attacker
strikes the chakra points.
Theoretically, doing
so allows a ninja
to gain complete control over
an opponent's chakra flow.
But these chakra points,
they're undetectable
even to my Sharingan eye.
-[gasp]
And even beyond his ability
to see the chakra points,
he can target them accurately,
even during intense battle.
NEJI: Hyah!
-Aaaahh!
[thud]
-Look, Hinata, I'm completely
out of your league,
and that won't change.
This is what separates the
elite from the failures.
[panting]
NEJI: You may not like
it, but it's a fact.
From the instant you said
you wouldn't run anymore,
your fate was sealed.
You were destined for failure.
And now you're consumed
with hopelessness.
Now this is your
last warning, Hinata.
Forfeit this match.
-I-- I-- [sobs]
-Hm?
-I never go back--
-Vo: Hinata!
-On my word.
-I'm not going to run away!
-Because that too is
my nindo, my ninja way.
-I had no idea that
Hinata's as tough as she is.
-She is a lot like you.
-Mm.
You know, come to think of it,
she is always watching you.
-Huh?
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Hinata.
-Bring it on.
[thud]
[cries out]
VO: She has reached her limit.
One more blow and she's done.
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): Neji's
hits to Hinata's chakra
points have completely
stopped her chakra flow.
That means she can no longer
send chakra into her opponent's
body to fight in the
Gentle Fist style.
This match is as good as over.
I never imagined there would
be someone this powerful here.
I'm afraid that even
as strong as Sasuke is,
he's no match for Neji.
MIGHT GUY (VOICEOVER): It
looks like Neji's gonna
win this match.
This girl just doesn't have
what it takes to bring him down.
-Whoa.
Did you see his eyes?
Do you think he's really
going to try to kill her?
He wouldn't!
-Doesn't it seem like the
difference in strength
makes it unfair?
He's just way too strong.
It's a mismatch.
Seriously.
-Nnngh!
Go, Hinata!
Yeah You can do it!
HINATA (VOICEOVER): Naruto!
NEJI (VOICEOVER): Strength
has come back into her eyes.
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
I've been watching you.
I've been watching you
closely for many years now.
I wonder why.
IRUKA: Next.
Naruto Uzamaki.
-This is a total
waste of time, Naruto.
-We always pay for
your screw-ups.
-Like I care.
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
Naruto, do your best.
-Transform!
HINATA (VOICEOVER): I
don't know why, but--
-[shouts]
My name is Naruto Uzumaki, and
I'm gonna beat every one of ya.
Believe it!
-Uh, can you say that
again a little louder?
Didn't quite catch you.
-You moron.
Are you trying to get everybody
in the place to hate our guts,
or what?
HINATA (VOICEOVER): When
I watch you, Naruto--
-On your feet, Naruto!
-Sorry, but you can
forget about being Hokage,
because I'm the top
dog around here.
HINATA (VOICEOVER): When I watch
you, I feel full of courage.
I feel that I can keep
going, that I can succeed.
That even I am worth something.
-Haaaa!
-Nnnnnaahh!
[cries out]
[gasp]
-Hinata!
-Hmmm.
[sobbing cough]
KURENAI (VOICEOVER): Hinata.
Hinata used to be a quitter, but
I can see that she's changed.
-Hut!
Hut!
-Come on, Hinata,
it's time to go home!
-Hut!
Hut!
KURENAI (VOICEOVER): She
put every ounce of her
being into her training.
I saw it with my own eyes.
-Hut!
Hut!
KURENAI (VOICEOVER):
But even so, she
continued to fail
all her missions.
She lost her nerve when
faced with real competition
and became easily discouraged.
But that's not the
Hinata I saw today.
I have never seen such a look
of-- of fierceness in her eyes
before.
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
Naruto, until now I
have always done the watching.
But now, finally, you're
the one watching me,
and I'll show you what I can do.
Naruto!
-Huh-ahh!
-[cries out]
[thud]
[gasp]
-You just don't get it, do you?
Your strikes were ineffective
from the very start.
You're finished.
-Vo: Hinata, you've done enough.
You lost the match,
but you've become
a new person in the process.
You did great.
-I want to change myself
into something better.
-It's too bad, but after
that blow to the heart,
Hinata is done.
-Since she's no longer able
to continue this match--
NARUTO: (SHOUTING) No!
-Huh?
-Don't stop this match!
SAKURA: Naruto!
What on Earth are you doing?
Hinata's had it!
You can see she's
unconscious, can't you?
-Mm.
-Huh?
-Uh?
-Ah!
[whimpering]
-What do you think you're doing?
If you continue to fight,
you're going to die.
HINATA (VOICEOVER):
It doesn't matter.
I'm not going to
let myself look bad.
Not now.
NEJI (VOICEOVER): Why
is she doing this?
HINATA (VOICEOVER): Not in front
of the person I admire most,
who's finally
seeing the real me.
-I'm far from finished.
NEJI: Give up the tough-guy act.
I can tell you're
barely standing.
You've been carrying
a very heavy burden,
having been born to the main
branch of the Hyuga Clan.
And you've cursed and blamed
yourself for being weak.
But look, people can't
change the way they are.
That's just how it is.
Just accept defeat and you
won't have to suffer anymore.
-No.
You're wrong, brother.
You've got it backwards.
You see, I can tell that
you're the one-- you're
suffering much more than I.
-I'm what?
HINATA: You're We
one who's all torn up
about the fate of the
main and side branches
of the Hyuga Clan.
[angry growl]
[shouts]
HAYATE: Neji, no!
The match is over!
Vo: Oh, man!
MIGHT GUY: Neji, get
a hold of yourself.
You promised me you wouldn't
let this whole head family
thing get you riled up.
-Why are you and the
other jonin butting in?
The head family gets
special treatment, huh?
[thunk]
[cries out]
-Hinata!
Hinata.
NARUTO: Hinata!
Hinata, you OK?
Hey!
-Naruto.
-Hm?
-I just-- I-- do you--
HINATA (VOICEOVER): Do
you think I changed?
Maybe a little?
-Hey, you.
Loser.
-Hm?
-I have two pieces
of advice for you.
First of all, if you intend
to call yourself a shinobi,
stop that stupid
cheering of yours.
It's disgraceful.
And second, once a
failure, always a failure.
You can't change that.
-We'll just see about that!
-Hmph.
[growls]
[gasp]
NARUTO: What are you doing?
ROCK LEE: Naruto, I get
where you are coming from,
believe me.
But the rules say all fighting
must be done officially
in a match.
The loser beating
the gifted genius
through sheer willpower--
now would that not
make for an exciting
match, even if I
am the one who is going
to have to fight Neji?
Of course, if you
ended up fighting him,
that is fine, too.
[growls]
-All right, fine.
You win, Lee.
ROCK LEE (VOICEOVER):
How was that, Guy-sensei?
MIGHT GUY (VOICEOVER):
Good one, Lee.
Nice going!
[choking]
KURENAI (VOICEOVER): Oh no.
She's going into cardiac arrest.
Was he really
trying to kill her?
-I wouldn't waste your
time glaring at me
when you really should
be taking care of her.
-(SHOUTING) Get a medic.
And hurry up!
We're coming!
She has no pulse!
-It's very serious.
She's got 10 minutes, at best.
Let's get her to the
emergency room now.
-Stand back.
-Hinata.
[panting]
-Because that too is
my nindo, my ninja way.
NARUTO: Hinata, I
give you my word.
I vow to win!
[music - Rythem, "Harmonia"]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER):
They say no one has ever
injured Gaara before.
He's strong as an ox
and has no weak points.
Yeah, right!
Bushy Brow is no match for him!
Except that he is!
He seems way faster than before.
What kind of crazy training
does Guy make him do?
Next time: "Gaara
versus Rock Lee:
The Power of Youth Explodes!"
Oh, wow-- I gotta get some
of that training for myself!