[music playing]
[theme music]
[groaning]
What's this?
Where in the world am I?
[groaning]
-That was a close.
Glad I got saved.
Of course I could have done
without the falling on my neck
part.
Look at that!
Awesome!
Man, that is humongous!
Wait.
Hold on here.
[panting]
What's that?
This is the toad, isn't it?
[screaming]
Let's see here.
(YELLING) There's no tail there!
[laughing]
I did it!
I didn't summon this or this!
(YELLING HAPPILY) It's
really a real toad!
He flies!
He jumps!
He lurks!
Chief Toad appears!
[laughing]
-Looks like he released the
chakra of the nine-tailed fox
all on his own this time.
But still, I certainly can't say
that he's proficient at it yet.
He over did it with
the chakra's power--
to have summoned
him of all things.
[laughing]
-I finally pulled it off!
-(YELLING) Why, you little snot!
[gasping]
[screaming]
-(YELLING) You little snot!
Just whose head do
you think you're
dancing around on top of anyway?
Well, let me tell you!
I am the wise and powerful
Lord Gamabunta, the Chief Toad,
and you're an idiot!
Now shut up!
[screaming]
[gasping]
-What is this guy?
He seemed cool, but
give me a break here!
[screaming]
-Just when I finally get to
breathe some fresh air again,
I find some weird kid
tap dancing on my head!
Hey, Jiraiya!
Where are you, Jiraiya?
Just what do you
think you're doing?
[yelling]
[groaning]
-Well, this doesn't look good.
Even I'm not able
to handle Gamabunta.
I mean, he's a real handful.
-(YELLING) Jiraiya!
Show yourself, you buffoon.
[groaning]
-It would be a pain in the
neck if he found me out,
so I better hightail it
out of here while I can.
-Hey, little snot.
-Uh, yeah?
-Where's Jiraiya hiding?
-Huh?
Who's this Jiraiya?
I don't know any--
[screaming]
-Don't play dumb.
I'm talking about
that [inaudible]
that calls himself
the Toad Sage.
Now, where is he?
Well?
[groaning]
-Man, he's scary.
-Look, I'm giving you an order,
and if you can follow it,
I'll even consider
making you my henchman.
(YELLING) So hurry
up and answer me!
-OK, OK.
If you're talking
about the pervy sage,
he's on the cliff up
there, Chief Toad.
-Up there?
-Um, can I ask you one
question, Sir Toad, sir?
-What is it?
-What business do you have
that pervy sage anyway?
-That's the very same question
I want to ask that pervert!
I mean, what in world does
that fool want with me?
Summoning me to a
dang place like this?
-Oh!
But, um--
-What now?
(LAUGHING)
-Well, actually,
the funny thing is
that I'm the one
who summoned you.
You see, I fell off
the cliff, and I
thought that maybe
you could rescue me.
So, thanks, boss!
[groaning]
[laughing]
-Give me a break.
What does a puny little kid
like you know about that?
There's no way a
little squirt like you
could have enough power to
summon up a being like me.
-Huh?
No, no, it's true!
It's true!
I mean, I really,
truly summoned you!
[laughing]
-(YELLNG) Knock it
off, you toad jerk!
-Huh?
-You've been talking down to
me and saying anything whatever
you want since you
first got here,
but I'm the one
who summoned you,
and that means I'm your master.
You have to start respecting
me and doing what I say.
You got that, Toad?
-(ANGRILY) Hmm.
What was that?
You've got some nerve.
Who do you think
you're talking to?
A meaningless little squirt
like you-- barely old
enough to stand,
and you dare to say
to Lord Gamabunta, the Chief
Toad, that you're his master?
That's it!
-Huh?
[screaming]
[crashing]
[gasping]
[screaming]
-Well.
It looks like he reached the
top, thanks to Gamabunta.
[screaming]
-Whoa.
That was awesome.
[laughing]
-I hate to tell you
this, you little snot.
But even if I were willing to
believe that you were actually
the one who summoned
me-- and trust me,
kid, that's a really,
really big if-- if you're
the kind of guy who could
fall off my back that easily,
then there's no way I could
ever accept you as my master.
You got it?
Hmm?
[groaning]
Now.
Since I'm back in the world
after such a very, very long
time, if Jiraiya doesn't need
me, I'm going for a walk.
NARUTO: No, wait!
-Listen, why don't you just
get out of here and go home?
Because it's clear you're
incapable of serving
as my henchman.
[laughing]
[music playing]
[groaning]
[screaming]
-What?
What do you suppose
you're doing now?
-(ANGRILY) Fine.
If making you respect me depends
on me staying on your back,
well then-- I'll just make
sure I don't get off your back
the rest of the
day, no matter what.
-What?
-That's right.
And when I do, then you'll have
no choice but to recognize me
as your undisputed master!
-(ANGRILY) You
really are a snot!
Fine, if that's what you
want, but don't think
I'm going to go easy on you.
[screaming]
-Must grip with chakra!
I don't have enough chakra!
Listen carefully, Chief Toad.
My name is Naruto Uzumaki.
I'm going to become
Akagi someday.
Don't forget that!
[screaming]
-(YELLING) I don't care!
[laughing]
-This is getting
pretty interesting.
[women giggling]
-Huh?
WOMAN: (PLAYFULLY) Stop it!
[laughing]
WOMAN: (PLAYFULLY) Quit it!
-Sorry, Naruto, I'd
love to help you,
but I'm afraid that I've got
far too much work to do here.
[laughing]
Research.
Yes, research.
[laughing]
[yelling]
-(YELLING) Get off!
[screaming]
-Welcome.
Come on in.
-I am going to eat until
I can't eat no more!
-Ha.
Those guys are eating
barbecue again.
Giving themselves a reward
for training so hard, I guess.
-Hey, I thought you were
told not to let Gaara out
of your sight, Kankuro.
-Oh, don't worry.
Even someone like
him wouldn't dare
to do anything in
broad daylight.
But about you--
that guy, Shikamaru,
or whatever his name
is-- he's the first guy
you're fighting, right?
Shouldn't you be
formulating a battle plan?
-Huh.
There's no way that I would lose
to a guy who's at that level.
No way.
KANKURO: You blew
it, didn't you?
-If you had taken the
exam one year earlier,
then you would have made
Chunin easily, right, Temari?
-Don't say that.
What?
What did you just say?
-I'm going to have
you three ninja--
the best from the
Hidden Sand Village--
participate in the
upcoming Chunin exam.
But the reason that
I'm having you do so
is not for you to
pass the Chunin exam.
We must use this
chance so that we're
able to crush the
Hidden Leaf Village.
-But why?
Why are we turning
on the Leaf Village?
Didn't we signed the Treaty
of Alliance with them?
-Yes, we did.
And that treaty is
the whole problem.
-I don't get it.
What do you mean?
-You Genin aren't aware of
all the details of this,
but when the Treaty of
Alliance was signed,
that idiot feudal Lord who rules
us used it as an opportunity
to force military
cutbacks on our village.
He also delegated to
the Hidden Leaf Village
matters that should
have been handled by us.
And even worse, he significantly
cut our village's budget
and slashed the
number of Shinobi.
When the head of our country is
weak, we-- the country's arms
and legs-- suffer.
And so we took the only
choice left to us--
improve the quality
of every Shinobi
to maintain our
military strength.
That's why Shinobi like
you were created, Gaara.
The land of wind's
very existence
is in danger-- more danger
than it's ever been in before.
But still, that
idiot fuedal Lord
and all his incompetent advisers
are too blind to see it.
So the Kazekage who
detected this weakening
of the might of
the Sand Village,
joined hands with
the Sound Village
to show our feudal
Lord his stupidity
by crushing the Hidden Leaf
village and restoring our own.
This needs to be done
to make that idiot
aware of the importance
of preparing for a crisis!
If any more time
passes, our Sand Village
will be completely
drained of its ability
to fight against
the Leaf Village.
This is our only chance.
Now, Gaara, this mission depends
entirely upon your skills.
-Yes.
-This path will certainly lead
to war with the Leaf Village.
-We'll be-- we'll be
going to war again?
We've spent so much time
and sacrificed so much
to achieve this alliance,
and now we're breaking it.
So many will die.
-But-- but Temari--
-Harden your heart.
This is the will
of Lord Kazekage.
[gasping]
-Lord Kazekage?
All Shinobi are simply
tools for fighting.
Accept that fact, and you'll see
that all the Treaty of Alliance
does is nothing more than
jeopardize our very existence.
This is an A-plus
ranked mission.
Make sure you succeed.
-OK.
-Yes.
[yawning]
-I'm bored.
The day sure goes by slowly when
you're not doing much anything.
-I guess.
[screaming]
-Ugh.
What an obstinate little squirt.
[screaming]
[groaning]
JIRAIYA: Oh, dear.
Look at that.
Seems like Naruto is in agony.
[laughing]
He must have exhausted
most of his chakra
when he used that summoning
jutsu to bring Gamabunta here.
WOMAN: Ooh!
Look at that!
Isn't that rainbow pretty?
WOMAN: Yeah!
It's gorgeous!
-Oh, yeah, I'll say.
It's all gorgeous.
[giggling]
WOMEN: Ooh.
KAZEKAGE: Good work, Baki.
-Thank you, Lord Kazekage.
I successfully moved
all three pawns
to the final rounds as planned.
KAZEKAGE: Hm.
And the pact with the Sound
Village has progressed as well?
BAKI: Yes, sir.
This scroll contains the details
of the Sound Village's plan.
KAZEKAGE: Is there
something else?
-Well.
-What?
Out with it.
-Yes, sir.
I was wondering if you
could position soldiers
near the border under the
pretext of a tactical exercise.
With just the four of us--
-The Hidden Leaf Village
isn't full of dimwits,
and the Anbu Black Ops
are active in that area.
-If we do what you
ask, they'll see
right through what
we're planning.
Everything we've worked
toward will be ruined.
-But with only our current
military capability--
-That's why I've sent
Gaara and the others.
The restoration of Sand Village
is glorious in your hands.
Now, go.
-Yes, sir.
-Hm.
[music playing]
-Just a little longer.
It's almost over.
Once that sun fully sets,
and I haven't fallen on,
then you're going to
be calling me master.
Ha!
-Never.
I didn't say I agreed
to your deal, did I?
-I don't care.
I'm not falling
off, no matter what.
[screaming]
-That Naruto.
He's already way past his limit.
I wouldn't be surprised if
he fell off any minute now.
-(VOICEOVER) I suppose that I
could simply ignore that snot,
but even the thought of
losing to him burns me up!
There's no way I'm going
to let that happen.
All right.
I'm going to bring an end
to this once and for all.
Hey, snot, what is your name?
What do they call you?
-(ANGRILY) My name!
I told you!
Naruto Uzumaki!
-Well, listen up,
Naruto Uzumaki,
I hope you won't hold it
against me if you die!
[screaming]
[yelling]
-Play fair, Gamabunta.
This is a matter of
pride for Naruto, too.
[gasping]
(YELLING) No!
(SADLY) That's where all those
pretty ladies come to hang out!
[screaming]
-No way!
I'm not falling off!
Not when I'm this
close to winning!
No!
[screaming]
-Huh?
-Incredible.
Even in the condition
he's in, the kid
is able to use more chakra.
Hm.
[screaming]
[gasping]
-I've got you.
Hold on!
[groaning]
[grunting]
[yelling]
[groaning]
[gasping]
[laughing]
-How do you like
that, Chief Toad?
I'm still on your back!
[laughing]
That's right!
I beat you!
[laughing]
[gasping]
-No!
If he falls like
that, he'll die!
-Hm.
Too bad for you, little snot.
And you almost made it, too.
-(VOICEOVER) Amazing.
He could hold out so long
against a tough opponent
like Gamabunta.
[laughing]
-Hm?
Naruto Uzumaki, huh?
You scandal, Jiraiya.
I am fully aware that this boy
summoned me all on his own.
He is courageous.
It's the first time
since the Fourth Hokage
that someone has dared
to climb on my head.
As may be expected
after that battle,
he looks completely
drained from energy.
I don't mind giving
him some of my power,
but I believe that taking
him to a place of healing
would be best.
[yelling]
WOMAN: What was that?
[theme music]
MAN: The hospital room.
Devoid of life.
The uninvited visitors.
The phantasms that
haunt a child's mind
appear in the
daylight the moment
when the forbidden
door is opened.
[door opening]
[child screaming]
And then he appears.
NARUTO: Next time-- Hospital
Besieged-- The Evil Hand
Revealed!
Who will be the next victim?
[theme music]