[theme song in Japanese]
KAKASHI (VOICEOVER): Effort
by itself does nothing.
Now watch.
We're going to show you
something called the Wall.
SAKURA NARRATING:
Sakura Blossoms.
-Your jutsu is indeed fast.
But ours is even
faster because it
travels at the speed of sound.
[retching]
-Lee, what's wrong?
-My-- my ear--
-Oh, I forgot to mention
this little gadget I wear.
You might be able
to dodge my blows,
but you can't get away from it.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): What trick
has he got up his sleeve now?
[laughter]
-I don't need to strike
you with my fists.
I can hit you with
the power of sound.
-Sound?
-What makes it possible
for the ear to hear things?
What is sound, really?
-Vibrations.
-Give the little lady a prize.
Yes, the vibration of
molecules in the air
creates a sound wave.
These vibrations are collected
by the ear, then directed
to your eardrum.
The human eardrum,
the tympanic membrane,
ruptures when exposed
to sound levels
in excess of 150 decibels.
Moreover, if the sound
is powerful enough
to upset the fluid within
the deepest inner ear canals,
it becomes impossible for
you to maintain your balance.
Feeling a little dizzy?
Nauseous?
That's right.
Best if you don't even try
to stand up for a while.
-You see, buddy, that
old-fashioned taijutsu stuff
won't work against us.
Not that you're not
pretty good at it.
It's just that,
what's the point?
Compared to our
jutsu that stuff's
totally yesterday's news.
See, I can manipulate ultrasonic
waves and air pressure.
I can do things you've
never even dreamed of.
ROCK LEE: Take this!
Primary Lotus!
-I can obliterate boulders, or
make the ground itself as soft
as a feather cushion.
Face it, little man.
You're up against the
jutsu of the future.
Ha, ha, ha, ha.
[grunting]
-Remember, this jutsu is to
be used only as a last resort,
and then only to protect
someone very precious to you.
-Right.
Only to protect someone
very precious to me.
-You've done real well.
I'll never get over how quickly
you were able to master it,
you lovable mop-top.
I'm proud of you, Lee.
-Now, then, little girl.
It's your turn!
-No!
No!
-What?
-Lee.
-Leaf Hurricane!
-Not quite as effective
as it was before, is it?
Still, it's impressive
that you can move at all.
We'll have to do something
about that Do you hear that?
This device amplifies the
vibrations of the impact,
transforming them
into a wave of sound.
-Lee, no.
-A sound wave I can
channel with my chakra,
focusing all its energy
on any target I desire.
-Stop it!
-All right, little man.
Time to end it.
-That's what you think.
-I'd almost forgotten you.
-These guys are scary.
I vote for getting out of here.
-Sasuke and Naruto
are out of it.
And Lee's not looking
too good, either.
It's just Sakura, all
alone against the three
of those guys.
Well, what do you want to do?
Ino?
-Why ask me, huh?
-Well, if we don't do
something soon, she's toast.
Are you cool with that?
You and her, you were
friends once, right?
-By the way, Ino--
-Well, what is it, Sakura?
Why do you look so down?
-It's just-- I heard that you--
-Come on.
What is it?
-Well, is it true what I heard?
You like Sasuke, too?
So I guess that means
we're rivals from now on.
INO (VOICEOVER):
Get a grip, Ino.
That's all ancient history.
-Well?
Ino?
So, like, what do
you want to do?
-Why do you keep asking me that?
What am I supposed to do?
You want me to go out there
and get myself killed?
INO (VOICEOVER): I mean,
that's all that would happen.
I'd just be in the
same fix she is.
What good would that do anybody?
-Catch these!
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): [inaudible].
My shuriken just bounced off.
-My, my, what soft
and shiny hair.
But you know what?
If you spent a little less time
shampooing and a little more
time practicing your jutsu
you might not be in this fix.
Hey, Zaku, I know
what would be fun.
Let's make Miss
Beauty Queen watch
while you finish
off that Sasuke guy.
-Why not?
Sounds like fun to me.
-You stay away from him.
-Don't even.
-Sakura--
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): It's no use.
I've got no strength left.
Way to go, Sakura.
You let everybody down again.
What good are you?
Even now, when the others
really need me, I cave.
How many times have
they saved my neck?
You'd think that
maybe, just this
once, when it's life or death--
you'd think that just maybe I
could come through.
-OK.
Let's do this.
-Man.
This thing's about
to get really ugly.
INO (VOICEOVER): What do I do?
What do I do?
-Come on.
It's pointless.
That won't work on me.
-It's not meant for you.
-What the?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
I've always considered
myself to be a true ninja.
I claim that I'm madly
in love with Sasuke.
And I'm always
lecturing Naruto, acting
like I know so much more.
But it's all empty words,
because they're always
in the lead.
And I watch them
from the background.
Why is that?
-Stay behind me!
-It's OK.
I've got you covered.
-OK.
No more Mr. Nice Guy.
-I'm not giving up.
I've still got this!
Sasuke!
Eat this!
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): No matter
what, they were always there,
those two.
Protecting me.
And Lee, you did more
than just say you like me.
You proved it.
-I will defend you with my life.
Take this!
Primary Lotus!
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
We're not even teammates
and you put your life
on the line for me.
All this time you've all
been teaching me something.
-Hey, Sakura.
-Sakura.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): It's about
time I learned the lesson.
OK.
No more caving.
Now it's my turn
to take the lead.
And all of you can watch
me from the background.
INO (VOICEOVER): Whoa.
Sakura!
-Sakura, be careful.
-Kin, finish her!
ZAKU (VOICEOVER): I
know that hand sign.
-A substitution jutsu.
ZAKU (VOICEOVER): You
think you can fool me
with that lame ninjutsu?
I'm on to you.
In fact, I'm way ahead of you.
-Kin, get out of the way!
-Pathetic.
Thanks for the present.
Hope you don't mind
if I return it!
Again with the hands?
Slicing Sound Wave!
What a surprise.
OK.
Where are you now?
You really want to
keep playing this?
Because I got news for you.
I'm not falling for it.
All right.
If you insist!
OK, so where are you
coming from next?
Huh?
No-- yeah.
This time it's really her!
What are you,
crazy or something?
Get off of me?
INO (VOICEOVER): Sakura.
[sobbing]
-Hey, aren't you the
one they're always
teasing because you've
got such a big forehead?
-Who are you?
-Who, me?
Oh, that's easy.
My name's Ino Yamanaka.
Who are you?
-My name's Sakura.
-Huh?
Hello!
I can't hear you.
Let's try that again, OK?
Who are you?
-My name is Sakura!
-That's better.
So this is the
famous forehead, huh?
Whoa.
It is kind of big.
So that's why you hide
it with your bangs?
That's dumb.
It just makes it worse.
Makes you look like a sheep dog.
So you're Sakura, huh?
-Uh-huh.
-Hey, you know what?
I've got something
special for you.
Come back here tomorrow, OK?
-Huh?
-Somebody get this
crazy girl off of me!
-There.
See?
What an improvement.
You look a lot better.
You can keep that ribbon.
-Oh.
Thanks.
But--
-Huh?
But what?
-My forehead.
-Oh, come on!
I'm telling you, the
more you try and hide it,
the bigger deal you make of it.
And your face isn't that bad.
Actually, it's a
pretty good face.
You just gotta be
more confident.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER): Confident.
-Hi, Ino!
-Hey, who's that you're with?
-Who's she?
-This is Sakura.
Go on.
Don't you wanna say hello?
-Hi.
-Get her off!
-Hey, everyone.
I've got something to tell you.
It's a secret.
You'll never guess who I like!
Not in a million years.
-How about you just tell us.
-Yeah.
Just please don't
say it's Sasuke.
-How did you know?
-Take a number.
Sasuke's, like, only the most
popular guy ever, that's all.
-He is?
Oh.
I guess that mans I've
got a lot of competition.
-Whoa, what a change.
Sakura's really come out
of her shell, hasn't she?
-Sometimes I wish
she'd get back in it.
-Hey, know what?
I just found out.
Sasuke likes girls
wit long hair.
-Well, is it true what I heard?
You like Sasuke too?
Guess that means we're
rivals from now on.
-Well, well.
I see someone's
grown her hair long.
Looks like I'm not the only one.
If you think being on
the same team as him
is gonna make him like
you, you're wrong!
-Face it, Ino.
I'm gonna win.
-Oh, you think so?
Sakura, I will never
let you beat me
no matter how hard you try.
-Sakura.
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
I'm-- I'm gonna win.
-Now you're gonna pay.
-Oh, man.
This is bad.
-Well, Ino?
SAKURA (VOICEOVER):
It's all on me.
There's no one else.
-Say so long, kid.
So what's this,
the second string?
-Ino.
-Surprised?
I swore I'd never let
you show me up, didn't I?
[theme song in Japanese]
SAKURA: This is Ino's fight now.
I've got to admit, she
and her team are tough.
When did they get to be so good?
They came to my rescue,
and maybe, with their help,
I can get Sasuke
out of this mess.
Next time, Battle
Formation-- Ino-Shika-Cho!
At least Sasuke's awake again,
but something's definitely not
right about him.