NARRATOR: 12 years ago, a nine
tailed fox suddenly appeared.
Its tails lashed out,
smashing mountains and sending
tidal waves crashing
to the shores.
The ninja rose up to
defend their villages.
-Hold the attack and wait
for the fourth Hokage!
-It's getting closer!
Don't let it near the village!
NARRATOR: One shinobi
faced the nine tailed fox
in mortal combat.
He sacrificed his life
to capture the beast
and seal it in a human body.
This ninja was known
as the Fourth Hokage.
[baby crying]
-[laughing]
-Naruto, come back here!
When I get my hands on you!
-You've crossed the
line this time, Naruto!
-[laughing]
-Give it up!
You're just bent
because you don't
have the guts to do what I do!
Do you?
Losers!
Wannabes!
You'll never catch
me! [laughing]
-Lord Hokage!
It's an emergency!
-I hope you're not bothering
me with some trivia.
And don't tell me
it's Naruto again.
-It is Naruto again!
He climbed onto the
great stone faces!
-He put graffiti
all over the Hokage.
-[sigh]
-Naruto!
-Hold on!
-[laughing]
-That was too easy.
-Oh yeah, Naruto?
-[screaming]
-Where'd you come
from, Iruka-sensei?
What are you doing here?
-No, what are you doing here?
You're supposed to be in class.
I'm at the end of
my rope, Naruto.
You failed the
graduation test last time
and the time before that.
Tomorrow, you've
got another chance,
and you're messing up again.
-Hmph!
Fine!
Because you missed
it, Naruto, everyone
will review the
transformation jutsu!
-Aww.
-All right, Sakura here.
Let's do it.
Transform!
-You transformed into me.
Good.
-Yes!
I did it!
-I kicked butt!
-Yes!
Sasuke, did you see that?
-Next, Sasuke Uchiha.
Uh, good.
Next, Naruto Uzumaki.
-This is a total
waste of time, Naruto.
-We always pay for
your screw-ups.
-Like I care.
-Naruto.
Do your best.
-Transform!
-Ooh. [giggle]
-Huh?
-[laughing] Gotcha!
That's my sexy jutsu!
-Cut the stupid tricks!
This is your last warning!
-This sucks.
Loser.
-You're not going home
until you've cleaned off
every single drop of paint.
-So what?
It's not like there's anyone
waiting at home for me!
-Naruto?
-What do you want now, sensei?
-Well, I was just thinking.
Maybe after you
clean this all up,
I could take you
out for some ramen.
The good stuff.
What do you think?
-Huh?
Now that's some
serious motivation!
I'll have this clean in no time!
Enter Naruto Uzumaki!
-Naruto.
-Hm?
-Why would you do that
to the Hokage faces?
I mean, you know who the
Hokage are, don't you?
-Course I do. [slurping]
Everybody knows.
They were the greatest
shinobi of their time, right?
The best of the best.
Undefeated ninja champs.
And the Fourth
Hokage's the one who
saved the village from
the nine tailed fox.
He was the most amazing.
-Then why did you--
-Because I'm going to be
greater than any of them.
Me.
Naruto.
The next Hokage!
A ninja legend!
Then everyone will have
to stop disrespecting me
and look up to me.
Believe it!
Uh, by the way, I kind of want
to ask a little favor, sensei.
-You want another bowl?
-Uh-uh.
I want to try on your headband.
Come on, please?
-Oh, this?
No way.
You can only wear
the Leaf headband
when you finally graduate from
the Academy and become a ninja.
You've got to pass
the test tomorrow.
-That is so uncool!
-Hey, is that why you
took off your goggles?
-I want another bowl!
-We will now start
the final exam.
When your name is called,
proceed to the testing room.
The final test will
be on the clone jutsu.
-Ugh, that's my worst technique!
Great!
I'm never gonna pass!
All right.
Get it together, Naruto.
You can do this.
Believe it.
Clone jutsu!
You fail!
-Iruka-sensei.
He's off, but his moves weren't
bad, and he did hang in there
and replicate.
This is his third
try, so you know
he really wants
to become a ninja.
We could cut him a
break and pass him.
-Mizuki-sensei,
the other students
created at least three
effective replications.
But Naruto could only
create one, and look at it.
It's pitiful.
I can't pass him.
-[growling]
[interposing voices]
-There.
You see him?
It's that boy.
I heard he's the
only one who failed.
-Hmph.
Well, it serves him right.
-Just imagine what would
happen if he became a ninja.
I mean, he's the boy who--
-Shh.
We're not allowed
to talk about that.
-Iruka, there's something
we need to talk about.
-Iruka-sensei's tough,
but he's not against you.
-Then why?
Why only me?
-He wants you to be
strong with all his heart,
but that will never happen
if he goes easy on you.
He's like you, you know?
No parents, no family.
-But this time, I really
wanted to graduate.
--[laughs] Then I guess
I have to tell you.
It's a secret, but I'm
going to let you in on it.
-A secret?
-Iruka.
-What is it, Lord Hokage?
-I know how you feel.
You grew up just like
Naruto, without knowing
the love of a mother and father.
The warmth of a family.
-It's getting closer!
Don't let it near the village!
-Let me go!
My mom and dad are still
fighting back there! [screams]
[knocking]
-Iruka-sensei, wake up.
-Huh?
-What?
What is it?
-You need to come to
Lord Hokage's right away.
It's Naruto.
He stole the sacred scroll.
-You mean the scroll of sealing?
No!
-Let's see.
The first one is
multi-shadow clone jutsu.
Ugh, not this again!
It's my worst jutsu!
-Lord Hokage, this
is not just a prank!
This is a serious crime!
-That scroll
contains secrets that
were sealed by the First Hokage!
Secrets known only
to our village!
-If it falls into
the wrong hands,
they could destroy our
entire way of life.
-All right.
Bring Naruto here at once.
-Sir!
-Where would he go?
-Now that I've told
everyone what Naruto did,
I can eliminate him.
They'll be glad he's gone.
And of course, I keep
the scroll for myself.
-[panting]
-It's all over.
-[laughing]
-Huh?
-Got me already.
Not bad.
You're quick, sensei.
I only had time to
learn one technique.
-He's been out here practicing.
I can tell how hard
he's been working.
-Listen, Iruka-sensei.
I'm going to show you
this amazing jutsu,
and you're going
to let me graduate.
Then everything will be OK!
That's the way it works, right?
Anyone who learns a jutsu
from this scroll passes!
-Huh?
Where'd you get that idea?
-Mizuki-sensei told me about it.
Believe it!
He told me where to find
the scroll, and this place.
-Huh?
Mizuki?
Huh?
Look out!
-I see you found
our little hideaway.
-So that's the way it is, huh?
I should've known.
-Naruto!
Give me the scroll, now!
-Wait a minute.
What's going on here?
-Naruto, don't let
Mizuki get the scroll!
It contains forbidden
jutsu that could
put this village
in great danger.
Mizuki used you to get
the scroll for himself,
for his own power!
-Naruto, Iruka's just
trying to scare you
because he doesn't want
you to have the scroll.
-Stop lying, Mizuki!
Don't let him trick you, Naruto!
--[laughing] Oh, I'll tell
you who's really lying,
-No, Mizuki!
-They've been lying to you
your whole life, Naruto,
since the decree 12 years ago.
-What decree?
-Everyone knows except you.
Iruka's trying to hide
it from you even now.
He'd do anything to shut me up.
-What is this decree?
Why does everyone
else know about it?
-Don't tell him!
It's forbidden!
-The decree is no
one can tell you
the nine tailed
fox is inside you.
The fox spirit that
killed Iruka's parents
and destroyed our village
has taken over your body.
You are the nine tailed fox.
-Stop it!
-They've all been sneaking
around hiding things from you
your whole life.
Didn't you think it was
strange how they treated you?
Like dirt, like they hated
you for just being alive!
-No!
No, no, no, no!
-Naruto!
-That's why you will never
be accepted in this village.
Even your beloved
sensei hates your guts!
HOKAGE (VOICEOVER): Iruka,
Naruto never had a mother
a father to care for him.
He's shut out of everything
and doesn't know why.
Most people won't
even look at him.
How would you feel if
everywhere you went,
people turned
their backs on you?
That's why he gets in trouble.
So people will notice him.
It may not show, but
he's always thinking
about the family
he doesn't have.
He's hurting inside.
-Die, Naruto!
-Naruto, get down!
-[groan]
-Why?
-Because we're the same.
When I lost my parents,
no one seemed to care.
They didn't have time for me.
They just forgot I was there.
My grades dropped.
I became the class clown.
I just wanted them to see
me and to know my name.
My schoolwork wasn't good
enough to get their attention,
so I did crazy things.
And then I had to pay for it.
It was hard.
I know that's how
you feel, Naruto.
You feel lonely and
it hurts inside,
and I could have been
there for you more.
I let you down.
I'm sorry.
No one should have
to suffer that much.
No one should be
alone like that.
-[laughing] Don't make me laugh!
Iruka always hated you!
He was orphaned because the nine
tailed fox killed his parents,
and that beast is
now inside you!
He'd say anything to
get the scroll from you.
-Naruto!
Naruto!
--[laughing] You know,
once he makes up his mind,
nothing can change it.
He's going to use the scroll
to take revenge on the village.
You saw that look in
his eye, didn't you?
Those are the eyes of a beast.
-No.
Naruto isn't like that!
-You're a joke.
As soon as I eliminate
Naruto and get the scroll,
I'll be back for you.
-[groaning] I won't let you.
-This is not good.
Mizuki has a big mouth.
He made Naruto feel so bad.
Worse than he's ever felt.
It could unleash the
power inside of him.
If Naruto keeps tampering
with the scroll,
the seal that locks the
fox spirit inside of him
could be broken, and the
beast could come out.
If that happens,
I fear for us all.
-Naruto, everything
Mizuki said was a lie!
Give me the scroll!
Hurry!
He's coming after
you to take it away!
[groan]
-It can't be.
How did you know?
Naruto, how did you know?
That it was me, and not Iruka?
-[laughing]
-Because I'm Iruka.
-You're a fool.
Why are you
protecting that freak?
He's the one that
wiped out your family.
-I don't care what you say.
You're not getting your
hands on that scroll.
-As if you could stop me.
Don't you get it?
Naruto is just like me.
-How's that?
-He wants the school for his
own power and his own vengeance.
That's how beasts are.
He'll pour all his rage into the
scroll and destroy everything.
-You're right.
-[gasp]
So it's true.
Iruka-sensei never
believed in me.
He thinks I'm some beast!
Some kind of freak!
-That is how beasts are.
But that's not who Naruto is.
He's nothing like that.
Naruto is one of a
kind, works hard,
puts his whole heart into it.
Sure, he messes up sometimes,
and everyone jumps on him.
But his suffering only
makes him stronger.
That's what separates
him from being a beast.
So you're wrong.
He's nothing like
the nine tailed fox.
He's Naruto Uzumaki of the
Village Hidden in the Leaves.
-Hmph!
You really believe that drivel?
Iruka, I was going to
save you for later,
but I changed my mind.
You're finished!
-So this is it.
-[grunt]
-Naruto!
-Not bad, for a little punk.
-If you ever lay a hand on
my sensei, I'll kill you!
-Such big words.
I can completely destroy
you with a single move.
-Take your best shot, fool.
I'll give it back to
you a thousand fold!
-Let's see you try!
Show me what you can
do, nine tailed fox!
-Shadow clone jutsu!
-Naruto.
Those aren't just illusions.
They're solid clones.
He's mastered an
extremely advanced jutsu.
-Huh?
Wha-- what is this?
[interposing voices]
-If you're not coming, then
we're going to come after you.
-[screams]
[punching]
-[groaning]
-Sorry.
I kind of got carried away.
You OK, Iruka-sensei?
-Yeah.
He's amazing.
He wants to surpass
all the Hokage.
And I'm starting to
believe he might do it.
Naruto, come here a minute.
I've got something
I want to give you.
[interposing voices]
-You're telling me no
one can find Naruto?
-Not a clue.
-This is bad news.
We've got to smoke
him out or something.
-There's no longer
any need to worry.
-Lord Hokage!
-The scroll's safe.
Naruto will be back soon.
-Sensei, how much longer?
-OK, you can open your eyes now.
Congratulations.
You graduate.
And to celebrate,
I have a surprise.
We're going out
for ramen tonight.
Huh?
-Iruka-sensei!
-Hey, that hurts!
Naruto.
This is only the beginning.
The road gets tougher
now that you're a ninja.
But if I told you that, I
guess it would ruin the moment,
so I'll tell you later.
Over ramen.
[music - akeboshi, "wind"]
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): Why
are you following me?
You want to become
the Fifth Hokage?
Listen up, you little shrimp.
I don't care if you are
the Hokage's grandson!
You can't just snap your
fingers and become a top ninja!
You'd better be ready,
squirt, because if you even
think about being a Hokage,
you'll have to beat me first.
Next time, My Name
is Konohamaru!