[theme music]
-This is a festival,
right ladies?
So let's get festive!
-Whoa there, fella.
You don't think you're
celebrating a little early?
-You handled it, didn't you?
-I did.
All the same, now that
the rain's letting up,
might as well cross
the finish line
and bring this farce to an end.
-Ha.
All right, all right.
Guess I'll go out
for a little run.
-All the way up there?
-Yep.
-That's pretty high.
How many steps are there anyway?
-I'm not really sure.
That's why they call these
stairs the Spirit Breaker.
-Heh.
They do, do they?
Piece of cake!
Just hang on!
Here we go!
-You're kidding.
How does he do it?
-Well, no one ever accused
that kid of not having energy.
MAN: Boss.
It seems that Idate's
headed this way after all.
-So he didn't run away.
You were right, boss.
-Of course I was.
I knew he had it in
him all the time.
Atta boy, Idate.
Keep coming.
You're almost there.
NARUTO (VOICEOVER): A Fierce
Battle of Rolling Thunder!
-Hey.
Just one thing.
-Huh?
I appreciate the
help, but don't think
this is gonna make me
trust you or anything.
-Yeah, yeah, whatever.
As if I cared.
-Hmph.
-You idiot!
You just said it yourself!
You still got one person
who believes in you, right?
-When you took the
Chunin exam, did they--
-Huh?
-What I mean is, was there a
tenth and final question that
came out of nowhere?
-Yeah.
It was weird, because the
whole point of the question
was whether you wanted
to answer it or not.
-Yeah.
Three years ago, I got
the same sort of question.
-All right.
Now for the 10th
and final question.
IDATE (VOICEOVER):
What could it be?
What could my big brother
have up his sleeve this time?
-This time, you're
not only competing
against all the
other Genin here,
but against the
rest of your squad.
[surprised whispering]
-That's right.
You're competing against
your own squadmates.
Whoever scores the lowest
in your squad will fail.
And the one who fails can never
again take the Chunin exams.
He or she remains
a Genin for life.
-What?
No way!
-To make us compete
against our own squad?
That goes against
every rule of--
-In here, I am the rules.
End of discussion.
If anyone wants to
withdraw, now's the time.
If you choose to withdraw, you
can try again later, right?
Of course, if one quits,
then all three squad members
will be disqualified.
However, you'll all still be
eligible to take the test again
in six months' time.
So then, what'll it be?
IDATE (VOICEOVER): A
one in three chance
of being thrown out for good.
I should be able
to beat those odds.
But still.
It means one of us is stuck
being a Genin for life.
MAN: Your comrades'
future versus your own.
A very tough decision
to have to make.
If it's too tough, quit now.
That's it?
Nobody else wants to leave?
All right then.
To you who've chosen to remain,
I have one thing to say.
You failed!
-What?
We've what?
-Failed?
What do you mean?
-You're penalizing us for
being confident enough to stay?
-So confident that
you'd sacrifice
the future of one
of your own squad.
None of you deserve
to become Chunin!
You're dismissed.
-Yeah, I see what you mean.
-So, what was the question
that he hit you guys with?
-Mm.
It's kinda hard to explain.
-Huh?
-It was complicated.
He explained it at the time,
but I didn't really get it.
-All I know is, I trusted
my brother and he failed me.
I trusted him, and it
ruined my life forever.
-Huh?
-I wasn't just gonna take it.
The least I could do was
make him explain himself.
-Ibiki, what was that all about?
-It was a classic double bluff.
A true shinobi would have seen
that and made the right choice.
-That was a dirty
trick, and you know it!
You taught us we're
supposed to accept
any challenge, no
matter the cost!
-Idate.
Is it really that hard
for you to accept?
-But the test, it--
it wasn't fair.
-I don't mean the test.
I mean that you'll
never be a ninja.
-If you're telling me I
have to quit, then I will.
But tell me why.
Why am I not good enough?
-Idate.
That is something you'll have
to figure out on your own.
-All this time, I still haven't
been able to figure it out.
-And that's when Aoi came
along and tricked you, right?
-That's right.
That's what he did.
-Unbelievable.
We made it.
-Right.
I'll take it the
rest of the way.
You can take a
break if you want.
-Huh?
Oh, now you don't
need me anymore?
-I have to do this.
I can't have you guys running
the whole race for me.
What's the point?
I have to win on my own two
feet, or else I haven't won.
-Hey, wait, Idate!
IDATE (VOICEOVER):
I can do this.
That medicine Sakura
gave me is working.
No.
No pain.
There's no pain.
Here we go.
I'm back in the race!
-I just have to cross this
bridge and I'm on O'uzu Island.
-Well then, get moving.
Idate's made it to the
Modoroki Shrine already.
-He what?
-Yes.
Looks like I may
have underestimated
that Genin a little bit.
-You incompetent--
didn't you tell me
you'd taken care of him?
-I thought I had.
But now's not the
time to discuss it.
Hurry up and cross the bridge.
-Some ninja.
You're worthless.
-Listen, you.
I'm here helping you
because I have to.
It's my duty.
But one more little crack like
that, I'll break you in half.
-OK.
Sorry.
-That's better.
Now get moving.
-Right!
-There he is.
I've almost caught him.
-Well, well.
What a surprise.
I have to admit, I never
thought you'd make it this far.
IDATE (VOICEOVER): That's the
Blade of the Thunder Spirit.
What are you doing?
No!
Stop it!
-Why bother even trying?
No one on Earth is a match
for the Blade of the Thunder
Spirit, the sword wielded by
the Second Hokage himself.
But then, you know all
about it, don't you, idate?
After all, you're the one who
stole it and brought it to me.
-You snake.
-Mud balls, huh?
What is this, a
playground fight?
-Sorry, but I didn't have
any kunai knives on me.
-Naruto?
-You're gonna need
more than an umbrella
to catch the next
ball I throw at ya.
Shadow Clone Jutsu!
-He's focusing all his chakra
into the palm of his hand.
-Here I go!
Get ready!
One more time!
[laughter]
-This couldn't be all there
is to it, now could it?
-Ninja Art, Senbon Shower!
I should have told you.
The Blade of Thunder
Spirit can cut anything.
It even cuts through
chakra as it it were water.
-Run, Naruto!
-I don't want to
underestimate you again.
This time I'll make
absolutely certain.
-Come on, what are you doing
wasting your time on him?
Your fight's with me, remember?
-Still at it, eh?
How touching.
Defending each other,
looking out for each other.
Pathetic nonsense.
Only a weakling needs
to depend on others.
Trusting other people
to give him the strength
he hasn't got for himself.
For a man like that, it's
always easiest to just run away.
Isn't that right, Idate?
I mean, isn't that what
you did after you stole
the Blade of the Thunder Spirit?
-There.
I can see it.
The Village Hidden in the Rain.
It's just up ahead.
-Aoi-sensei!
Aoi-sensei!
-Idate.
-Ibiki?
-Have you gone insane?
On your feet.
I'm taking you back
to the village.
-No!
-You little fool.
Do you have any idea
what you've done?
-You're always so strict, Ibiki.
Even towards your
poor little brother.
Actually, I'm glad
you showed up,
because you're just
the person I need.
-How?
What do you mean?
-The forbidden scroll can
only be decided by a Jonin.
So you see, both
brothers have a part
to play in betraying
the Leaf Village.
[groan]
[scream]
-Stop playing the hero, and just
tell me what the scroll says.
-Never.
-So you prefer death?
How about your brother?
-Whatever else he may
be, he's a shinobi.
He accepts death without fear.
-Oh, I have to disagree
with you, Ibiki.
Look at that face.
He's frightened half
out of his wits.
-No, don't kill me!
I've given up trying
to be a ninja!
I quit!
I don't want to die!
-Just decipher the scroll.
You don't really want to make
me kill your poor little brother
right before your eyes?
-What brother?
That coward?
-Ibiki--
-Doesn't matter to me
what you do to him.
Do what you want.
-So, loyalty to the village
above all things, eh?
You think you're
this great hero,
but in reality you're nothing
but a stupid pawn to them.
-Really?
Better a dead pawn
than a living traitor.
You're a sorry excuse for a man.
-I'll show you sorry!
[scream]
-Idate!
Get out of here.
Go on.
-What about you?
-I'll be along once
I've finished up here.
-Neither of you
is going anywhere!
-Ibiki!
-Go on!
Run!
-No!
I won't leave you!
-Get out!
You'll only be in my way here!
-You stay where you are.
-Get going!
-Incredible, isn't it?
That someone would
actually lay down his life
for the likes of you.
You could have hurried back to
the village and summoned help.
But that would have meant facing
up to your guilt, wouldn't it?
So instead you just ran away.
You didn't even have the
excuse that Ibiki was dead,
so there was nothing you could
do, because he was alive,
wasn't he?
-I have to give him credit
for that much, at least.
He not only survived the
torture and the fire,
but he even managed to get
back the forbidden scroll,
all without telling me
what I wanted to know.
What I really can't get
over is that he did it
all for your sake, his
worthless little brother.
Someone who betrayed his
own village, who's only ever
thought of himself.
Who trusts no one.
Not even your brother Ibiki.
Your own brother, who would
have given his life for you.
You don't even
trust him, do you?
You don't trust the
people in your own village
enough to go back to them
and admit what you've done.
You trust nobody.
And nobody trusts you.
You've learned
your lessons well.
I couldn't have asked
for a better student.
As a reward, Idate, I
will kill you quickly.
-Idate!
-Hey, guys!
Excellent timing.
-Don't sweat it, Naruto.
Just sit back and
leave this clown to me.
-This clown's tougher
than you think.
-It doesn't make any difference
how many of you there are.
You'll never defeat me.
I'm Aoi of the Rain,
and I wield the Blade
of the Thunder Spirit.
-Is that so?
Perfect.
The Blade of the Thunder
Spirit against my Chidori.
All right.
Let's find out which
one of them is stronger!
-Heh.
I see that the stories are true.
I'd always heard that the
last of the great Uchiha clan
was a hopeless loser
unworthy of his family name.
-Sasuke!
-Run, Sakura!
He'll show no mercy!
He'll kill us all!
Get away while you still can!
-No way!
-What?
-We'll never abandon you.
We have sworn to protect you.
You can trust us, Idate.
-Yes.
Well, then, back to the
matter at hand-- Idate
and his little friend.
Time to start your
journey-- to the next world.
-Take it back.
Take back what you said.
-What are you talking about?
-I'm warning you--
don't mess with me!
I'm Sasuke of the Leaf Village.
The last of the Uchiha!
[scream]
-Sasuke!
Get up, Sasuke!
Hurry!
-It's a long way to
the bottom of the sea.
-No, leave him alone!
-Idate!
Sakura!
No, Sakura!
[theme music]
NARUTO: OK, so now what
are we supposed to do?
This guy and his thunder
sword, or whatever it is,
are more than a match for my
Rasengan and Sasuke's Chidori.
We've used up our
whole bag of tricks!
Oh, well.
We'll just have to come up with
some news ones, that's all.
'Cause there's no
way we're giving up.
We've gotta find a
way to beat this guy.
But how?
Next time, The Last Leg!
A Final Act of Desperation!
[theme music]