[theme music]
[boom]
-What?
-What the--?
-Oh.
-An empty shell.
BOY (VOICEOVER):
Lee's hidden strength.
Forbidden secret jutsu.
-But how?
We didn't do it.
-It was when you closed
your eyes to pray.
-Huh?
-At that moment, Lee closed his
eyes too because of the pain.
That's when he did it.
[crash]
-Mm.
[grunts] Gaara.
-Huh?
Aa.
[evil laughter]
-Oh, know it's--
-So it's happened.
Just as I thought.
That look in his eyes.
It could only mean The demon
inside him has been awakened.
-Ah!
Yah!
Yah.
Uh.
[groans]
[grunts]
-Brantley!
-Oh.
[hollers] Uh!
-The poor kid is helpless.
He doesn't have anything left.
Gaara's just toying
with him now.
-I don't get it.
What's Lee doing
just standing there?
With his speed, he
should easily be
able to get out of the
way of those blasts.
Why doesn't he dodge them?
-For a very simple reason.
He can't dodge them.
-Huh?
Why is that?
-The Lotus is what you might
call a double-edged sword.
-Wha--?
What does that mean?
-You know that it's a
forbidden technique.
Why do you think that is?
-Well--
-The Lotus isn't
ninjutsu or genjutsu
It's taijutsu requiring
extreme physical effort.
The strain it puts on
the body is unimaginable.
No one can sustain it for long.
Right now, Lee is in so much
pain he can hardly move at all.
Isn't that right, Guy?
-But-- But that means--
-[grunts] [yells]
[music playing]
-Uh.
[cringing pain groan]
-No ninjutsu or genjutsu.
All he's got is taijutsu.
And not much of that.
-There's no way he can win this.
-Win?
He'll be lucky to survive.
-Lee.
-All right, you guys.
Keep it moving.
You want to run 200 more laps?
-[chuckles] Dummy.
Why bother?
You'll never be a ninja.
[kids laughing]
-Will too.
-There's no way a kid who
can't even do ninjutsu
can ever be a ninja.
-Yes, I can.
-Whatever.
I don't get why you're
even at this ninja academy
when you can't do
ninjutsu do genjutzu.
And you're even worse
than average at taijutsu.
It's idiotic.
-Hey, you know what everyone
here is calling you, don't you?
-Dork Lee!
Dork Lee!
-Hey, Lee.
Where you going?
Get back in line.
--[smugly chuckles] So that's
the no-talent overachiever
I've heard so much about.
-Yeah.
He kind of reminds
me of someone.
-Hm?
-Especially around the eyebrows.
-[chuckles]
-Rock Lee.
The dork with
nothing going for him
but a little lousy taijutsu.
-[screams]
-But you kept at it, didn't you?
You kept practicing your
little lousy taijutsu.
-394, 395, 396,
397, 398, 399, 400.
If I can't do 500 kicks,
then it's 2,000 squats.
404, 405, 406, 407,
408, 409, 410--
-Hm.
-411.
-Someone else is here.
-412, 413, 414, 415--
-I'll come back later.
-416, 417, 418--
[music playing]
[cicadas chirping]
-If I can not do 1,000 squats,
then at least 1,000 punches.
795, 796, 797, 798,
799-- [boxer breathing]
[music playing]
-He's still at it.
-If I cannot do 2,000 punches,
then I have to do 2,000 jump
ropes. [puncher's grunt]
-You focused everything
on your taijutsu,
training relentlessly, until--
-As of today, you are all Genin.
So now tell me, why
have you done it?
What are your goals?
Hm?
-Oh.
Me, me, Sensei.
Me.
-Yes.
Tenten.
-I want to be a great
and powerful ninja
to walk in the footsteps of the
legendary Kanoitchi Sunadai.
-I see.
And you.
Neji.
-I'd rather not say.
-How about me, Sensei?
I want to show I can
be a splendid ninja
as well even if I do not
have ninjutsu or genjutsu I
want to prove it
to the whole world.
-There's that the
look in his eye.
-Hm.
-What?
What is so funny?
You think I am joking?
I mean it.
I will be a splendid
ninja just by using
taijutsu and nothing else.
-It's painful to watch.
Why doesn't he give up?
-He should quit while he can.
It was just bad luck he
got Gaara as an opponent.
Huh?
Come on, Bushy Brow.
-Lee.
-Uh aa.
Aa.
-[attack cry]
-[groans] [moans]
-[yells] Not yet.
-Lee.
[sighs] This is stupid.
Why do you keep on
doing it to yourself?
Come on.
You're never going
to win against Neji
because he's--
well, he's a genius.
-A genius, huh?
What does that mean-- genius?
So I was not born with a
whole lot of natural talent.
Not gifted like Neji.
But I work hard and
I never give up.
That is my gift.
That is my ninja way.
-It doesn't change a thing.
-Huh?
-The sad fact is
you'll never beat me.
No matter how hard you work, no
matter how many times you try.
-That is not true
and you know it.
It is not true.
-True or not, you
didn't listen to them.
You, you never gave up.
-[screams] [grunts]
-[growling]
- [evil giggling] What good
do you think that'll do?
-I pity the kid.
Gaara will just toy with
him til he begs for mercy.
-Well, then, Gaara's
in for a long match
because that will never happen.
-Huh?
-Lee doesn't know
how to give up.
-[yells] [screams]
-Lee, will struggle on
long after the point
where anyone else
would have quit.
-If I cannot do 1,200
without a mistake,
then it is 2,000 kicks.
1,117, 1,118, 1,119, 1,100--
-Uh.
-[yells]
-Lee.
[chuckles] Taking
a break already?
-Huh?
[music playing]
-What is it, Guy Sensei?
If it is about my messing up
on the last assignment, anh,
I said I was sorry.
Anh.
-Lee, it's true you're different
from Neji and the others.
-Anh.
-You have no gift for
ninjutsu or genjutsu.
And your taijutsu needs work.
But, then again, you have a
gift that Neji doesn't have.
Not as flashy.
But perhaps even more important.
-You do not have to
make me feel better.
-You idiot.
You think I'd waste
my time with that?
No.
All I'm saying is that you
have the gift of perseverance.
And that's what makes
you a genius too.
-Uh?
Anh.
But is that true, Sensie?
I wonder.
Unh.
I use to think so.
I use to believe that if I just
trained harder than Neji, two
or three times harder, I would
make myself strong enough.
But now I am not so sure.
I do not know if I will ever
be able to work hard enough
to be real talent.
That is why I'm always
taking out Neji.
I keep thinking all of
my efforts will pay off.
But it is always the same.
I am no match for him at all.
Every time we have a ninja
mission, my legs begin shaking.
I do not know if I can take it.
Sometimes it seems like the
whole thing is pointless.
Like I am a loser and I
will always be a loser.
[sobs] I do not know what to do.
-You're right.
All the effort is pointless if
you don't believe in yourself.
You know, Lee.
We're a lot alike, you and I.
-You mean the eyebrows?
-No, I don't mean our eyebrows.
You see, I was a loser too once.
-What?
You were a loser?
-Oh, yes indeed.
But I made myself the equal
of any ninja, even Kakashi.
And I did it through effort.
You say you want to
show the world you
can be a splendid ninja
even if you don't have all
the gifts that others
are blessed with.
That's your nindo,
your ninja way, right?
Well, I think
that's a fine goal.
As fine a goal as
I've ever heard.
And one worth sticking to.
Don't let anything
steer you off the path
you've drawn for yourself.
Forge ahead to the end.
Stick to it, Lee.
Make me proud.
Be everything you can be.
Will you do that for me, Lee?
-Yes, sir.
[music playing]
- [pants heavily] Guy
Sensei, thank you.
Unh.
-He can't go on.
Make him quit before
he gets himself killed.
-Bushy Brow.
-Hm.
[wind whipping]
[speed zipping]
-Hm?
-What?
-He's still able to--
-Move like that?
[music playing]
-I will make you proud, Sensei.
I will forge ahead,
follow my path to the end,
and become the ninja
I know I can be.
-Lee's smiling.
He's running for his life.
But he's still smiling.
-Yes.
But now it's
Gaara's turn to run.
-Uh?
The Leaf Village
Lotus blooms twice.
-I've heard that
somewhere before.
Yeah.
Lee told me that.
[gonging]
-Sakura, The Lotus of the
Leaf Village blooms twice.
When we meet again, I will
have become a stronger ninja.
I promise.
-But-- No, Guy, you didn't.
-Yes, Kakashi, I did.
-So that Genin, that boy, is
able to open the Eight Inner
Gates and use the Hidden Lotus?
-Hidden Lotus?
-That's correct.
-Well, if that isn't
the most-- [grunts] OK.
So then how many of the Inner
Gates is he able to open now?
-Five Gates.
-OK.
What exactly are these
Eight Inner Gates
you're talking about?
And the Hidden Lotus?
-The Eight Gates are like
valves or chakra limiters
that must be opened if one is
to release the Hidden Lotus.
-I'm still not following.
-There are Gates along
the chakra network located
at those points
in the body where
the chakra is most
heavily concentrated.
Starting at the head,
they are the Gate
of Opening, the Gate of Rest,
of Life, of Pain, of Closing,
of Joy, of Shock, and
the Gate of Death.
These are what are called
the Eight Inner Gates.
Their purpose is to
limit the flow of chakra
through the body.
But the Lotus exerts tremendous
pressure on these limiters,
eventually forcing
the Gates open.
[explosive bursting]
-This releases the
restraints on the chakra.
The result being that
a person's strength
can be increased
tenfold or more.
-The Primary Lotus opens
only the First Gate--
[explosive bursting]
--the Gate of Opening,
releasing the brain's restraints
on the muscles, freeing a
person to bring forth its body
strength to it's full extent.
You'll see results.
-And, uh, Hidden Lotus?
-At the Second Gate,
the Gate of Rest,
one's strength is
increased further.
And at the Third Gate,
the Gate of Life,
one enters the Hidden Lotus.
-Wait a minute.
Just the Primary Lotus
almost destroyed him.
He could barely move.
What's going to happen to
him if he takes it farther?
-Exactly.
-Uh.
-By opening all Eight Gates,
you could attain power
beyond even the Hokages.
The only drawback is you die.
[gonging]
-[gasps]
-I don't know what this
boy means to you, Guy.
But I shouldn't have to
tell you that we never
bring our personal
feelings into play.
I wouldn't have thought
you were capable of this.
[cymbals crashing]
-You have no right.
-You know nothing about him.
[cymbals crashing]
-Nothing at all.
That boy has something
important to prove.
And he's determined to prove it
even at the cost of his life.
-I want to show I can
be a splendid ninja
as well even if I do not
have ninjutsu or genjutsu.
I want to prove it
to the whole world.
-And I am determined to
help him reach his goal.
Not for his sake.
But because that goal
is worth reaching.
-All right, Lee.
I'm going to be teaching
you a new technique.
So pay attention now.
-Yeah, yeah, yeah,
yeah. [cheers]
-OK, OK.
Enough of that.
-(LAUGHING) Yeah!
A new technique.
-(GROWLS) Lee!
I said pay attention.
-Ahyahah.
Right.
Pay attention.
Yes, sir.
-Let me first just
say one thing.
This technique is
even more forbidden
than the Primary Lotus.
It is not without danger.
But it will be your trump card.
-Ahp.
It will?
-But listen.
You can only use this forbidden
technique on one condition.
One very strict condition.
And that is--
-[pants] And that is--
[aero speeding]
-What?
-Um-um.
-I don't know what you think
you're planning right now.
But this match is over for you.
-You are right.
[thundering]
-It is over one way or another.
Neji.
Insoske .
And--
-I am not going to be the
only one to lose here.
Guy Sensei, please
let this work.
It is now or never.
[lightening striking]
-To protect and maintain
one's own ninja way.
-The Third Gate,
Gate of Life, open!
[music playing]
[theme music]
-I will show you
that hard work pays.
I would not have gotten
this far if it did not.
Neji, Soske, Narato,
if you can win,
so can I. You did not think
I had a chance, did you?
But you did not know I
had an ace in the hole.
I have been saving it
until just the right time.
And that time is now.
-Next time, the Fifth Gate.
A splendid ninja is born.
-It is now or never.
[gonging]