[music playing]
-Hey, you want to see it,
don't cha I'd say it's time.
-For what?
-Come on.
You know what I'm talking about.
Kakashi Sensei's real face.
--[screaming] What's
the matter with you?
-Please.
This is the lame.
You can count me out.
When we finish today's
mission, I'm outta here.
-Yeah, you're totally
right. (THINKING)
Who am I kidding.
[giggling] This sounds fun.
-What if he has lips, like a
blimp. (ECHOING) Like a blimp.
--[giggling] (THINKING)
Just one more little push.
Or maybe buck teeth.
(ECHOING) Buck teeth.
NARUTO: Gotta see, gotta know
Kakashi Sensei's true face.
KAKASHI SENSEI: Well, this
is out of the ordinary.
-Here, thanks for waiting.
The three of you
treating me to lunch?
I wouldn't be surprised
if it snowed on me.
-He fell for it.
-You know what I mean?
-Here, thanks for waiting.
The three of you
treating me to lunch?
I wouldn't be surprised
if it snowed on me today,
or something.
-He fell for it.
Is that the idea?
-Here, thanks for waiting.
-The three of you
treating me to lunch?
You're not going to drop a big
pile of snow on me are you,
or something like that?
No, I'm just being silly.
Oh!
-He fell for it.
-Well?
Come on.
You guys are up to
something, right?
-W-w-w-w-w-what?
Are you crazy?
-Kakashi Sensei, please.
You've just been
out of the hospital.
Now, uh, p-please.
Uh, why don't you
just go ahead and eat.
-Well, all right then.
I suppose I should just dig in.
-Thank you for waiting.
SAKURA: The roasted
pork is on us.
KAKASHI SENSEI: Mm-mm.
(THINKING) Boy, this looks good.
-[gulp]
-Hey, Sasuke.
What a coincidence!
-[yelling]
-Get out of the way, Ino-pig.
NARUTO: Aw, man,
I can't see squat.
-Ah, all done.
That was tasty.
-So fast?
Something wrong?
-[giggling] No.
Of course not.
What makes you say that?
-What the--
-Huh?
-OK, now I'm curious.
[cawing]
-That's it.
Nothing's going to stop
me from seeing that face.
-Yeah, but how?
You got any ideas?
-Don't you worry.
We'll see it one way or another.
-I'm asking you how,
you stupid little troll.
-All right, smarty pants.
How do you propose we do it?
-Well, we--
-We'll just have to tail
him around for the day.
He'll take off the
mask eventually.
-Oh, Sasuke, I swear,
you are so smart.
-Oh, whatever.
Good plan, captain obvious.
-I'm sorry.
What was that?
-Uh, never mind.
-[humming]
-What in the world is
Kakashi Sensei doing?
-It's so disappointing.
-He's onto us.
-Naruto, you idiot.
You blew our cover.
-Why the heck is it my fault?
-Wait, my favorite book
is going to be a movie?
I better order
tickets in advance.
-Hey, he's on the move.
-Let's go, before we lose him.
-Yeah, right.
-He' gone.
-Oh great.
He got away.
-Are you kidding?
Where did he vanish off to?
-Hey.
What are you three doing?
Do you guys need
me for something?
-Uh, no, not really.
-Hmm.
-Hey, how did he figure out
we were tailing him, huh?
-Maybe there were
just too many of us.
-Oh, please.
If you know how to
hide, it doesn't
matter how many
people there are.
Don't tell me you've forgotten
all of your Jutsu, Sakura.
-You're the one who forgets.
We should shadow him.
It'll be good practice.
But we should do
it solo this time.
-Yeah, I think so too.
We should totally ditch Naruto.
-Say what?
-Forlorn, Jinko fell on him.
I'm losing you.
And in doing so, I am lost.
-Huh?
What the?
-Ah.
Hmm?
-[nervous laughter] he got away.
-Just as clumsy as always.
-Why are you such an idiot?
[music playing]
-Aw, what is Kakashi
Sensei doing?
He hasn't even moved in ages.
Don't tell me!
[screaming]
-Ah.
Hmm?
-[nervous laughter]
[cawing]
-Ah.
Huh?
SAKURA: Sasuke, how did it go?
-I got tired of shadowing him.
-[sighs]
-Off we go.
-(THINKING) Our mission
is helping out at a farm.
-(THINKING) The mission
itself is no big deal.
-(THINKING) No matter what
happens, we're going to see it.
-(THINKING IN UNISON)
Kakashi Sensei's real face.
-What's with you guys today?
You seem ready for anything.
-Oh, we're ready all right.
-Hmm.
-All righty then.
Good to hear.
-So, I finally found
you, Kakashi Hatake.
Oh, Kakashi, it's
been a long time.
But my revenge is
finally at hand.
-Your revenge?
For what, boss?
-You fool!
Have you forgotten?
Well, I haven't.
It was three years
ago in the spring.
-No!
-There's no need
to be frightened.
-No!
-Our boss says he has something
he needs to talk to you about.
-Your boss?
-[laughing]
-Oh, I love you.
Marry me.
I beg of you.
-Wow, boss.
You're the man!
-Eww.
-Don't be shy now.
Embrace your
emotions, my flower,
and fly to my boss-- whoa!
-No, thanks.
-Don't worry, darling.
Even if you don't like what
you see, I'm filthy rich.
-I said no, OK?
-What?
How could you possibly
refuse me-- oh!
-No means no!
-But I arranged such
a romantic setting.
-What part of no
don't you understand?
KAKASHI SENSEI: I think this
has gone on long enough.
-Huh?
-Howdy do.
Look, it doesn't matter
how you slice it.
I don't think the
lady's interested.
Rejection hurts.
But what can you do?
-Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
-You got a lot of
nerve there, pal.
I don't think you grasp
who you're dealing with.
You're tangling with the
Moya triad, ninja trio
that strikes fear in
the hearts of children.
-Moya triad?
Never heard of you.
-Never heard of the Moya triad?
-You dare to mock us?
-Who do you think you are?
-Who, me?
The name's Kakashi Hatake.
I'm hardly worth mentioning.
-So why'd you even bother.
-No good scum.
-You'll live to regret this.
-You should know
better than to meddle
in a man's quest for love.
-Quest for love?
You mean stalking, don't you?
-Hold your tongue.
All right, boys, time to dance.
-Right.
-Four, three, two, one.
Hustle and bustle.
[screaming] [yelping]
-[neighing]
-Hey, come on, a
little help over here?
Seriously?
I'm pretty scared of heights.
-I'll take you back
to the village.
-Darling.
What are you-- are you just
going to leave us up here?
So anyway, that's
how it all went down.
-Don't gloat.
You're the one who lost.
-So now we're going to get
payback for three years ago.
[chuckling]
-The boss has only
gotten stronger.
He'll crush that chump into
dust if they go toe to toe.
The suspense is killing me.
Oh!
-You dingbat.
I'm not going to stick
my neck out like that.
-Huh?
-If I'm going to do this,
it will be from the shadows.
-That's pretty dirty.
[cawing]
-Oh, welcome.
My, my, my.
Welcome.
Welcome!
[giddy laughter]
-Oh, wow.
-That looks good.
-How lavish.
-Take your time.
[giggling] Enjoy
your meal, Kakashi.
For it will be your last.
I've added a tasteless
and odorless narcotic
to your food that brings
on uncontrollable hiccups.
Dig in, my friend, and
hiccup until you die.
A fitting end for
one such as you.
-Huh?
What's the matter with you guys?
No one's picking up
their chopsticks.
-Oh, it's nothing.
Don't wait on us,
Kakashi Sensei.
You go ahead and eat.
-Actually, I'm kind of
on a diet right now.
-(THINKING) So that's how
he wants to play it, huh?
Well I don't care what it takes.
That mask is coming off.
Oh no.
My hand slipped.
Whoa.
[screaming]
-Are you out of your mind?
-Sorry about that.
My hand just slipped.
-What do you mean
your hand slipped?
-Oh no.
All our cooking.
How could he do such a thing?
[moaning]
-OK, what's our next move, guys?
-Don't worry about it.
I think I have a plan.
-What kind of plan?
-Hmph.
-Not too shabby.
Way to come through Sasuke.
Who wouldn't take their
mask off in a hot spring.
-All right, you loser.
Zip your lip already.
-Oh.
--[evil laughter] Tonight you
breathe your last breath,
Kakashi.
I've coated this
blow dart with elixir
I concocted that brings on wild
and uncontrollable laughter.
-Huh?
[laughing madly]
-You'll die laughing!
A fitting end for
one such as you.
-Oh man, I wanted
to get a look too.
But with these hot springs,
I'm out of the loop.
I want to see.
Oh.
[gurgling]
NARUTO: What's the
holdup Kakashi Sensei?
KAKASHI SENSEI: One sec.
I'm coming.
-Hmm?
I gotta see this.
-This is it.
-Here we go.
-Oh, I can't see a thing.
-[giggling]
-Phew.
It is hot in here.
I'm just coming in for a minute.
-Gah!
You've got to be kidding.
-Now.
-Hmm?
What's up with you two?
Well, I'm getting in.
-[laughing madly]
-Ah!
-Oh!
-He escaped again.
-What's going on?
This is killing me.
-Just great.
What the heck was Kakashi
Sensei thinking back there?
Huh?
-[laughter]
-Oh man.
I'm completely flushed.
Hmm?
-Where did our clothes go?
[cawing]
-[laughing]
-Come back any time now.
-Thank you very much.
Safe journey to you.
-Come back any time.
Come back any time. [laughing]
-Curse you, Kakashi Hatake.
I will be your doom.
-It's a good thing
we brought along
a spare set of
clothes, huh boss?
-Yeah.
I wonder who took them, anyway.
KAKASHI SENSEI: All right.
You've all got jobs to do.
You'd best get to work.
Dismissed.
-I've about had it, guys.
I don't think my nerves can
handle much more of this.
-I'm getting pretty
fed up myself.
-Yeah, me too.
That makes three of us.
-All right then.
Desperate times call
for desperate measures.
-Desperate measures?
-Why are we dressed like this?
-Isn't it obvious?
We're posing as a
trio of rogue ninja.
-Where did you even
get these things?
-Uh, look, let's not get
bogged down in the details.
-Do you even have a plan?
-Ha!
Strip off the mask by
force if we have to.
-All right, Kakashi.
-Look!
-Huh?
-Hey, Kakashi Hatake!
What are the three of you up to?
-W-what are you talking about?
We're just three
wandering ninja.
It's not like we want to see
what's behind your mask or--
-You idiot.
Don't say any more
than you have to.
-That's my suit.
-Hey, boss, it looks
like you're not
the only one who wants to
get revenge on Kakashi.
Now's our chance.
-Let's do it!
-Right!
-Hold it right there.
[laughing] Kakashi, it's time
you pay for your transgress.
And the price is
death, delivered
in the form of
this elixir, which
will make you weep
uncontroll-- [screaming]
-That's funny.
I was just wondering
how long you fellows
were going to hide for.
You finally decide
to show yourselves.
-[whimpering]
-First things first, though.
Sasuke, Sakura, Naruto,
why on earth are you
dressed like that?
--[stuttering] Well,
the thing is--
-(THINKING) Oh boy.
We'd better come up
with something fast.
You fools!
You fell right into our trap.
We've known all along you
were targeting Kakashi Sensei.
-That's impossible.
Are you telling me
that our machinations
were exposed from
the very beginning?
-Of course.
This was all just a ruse
to lure you guys out.
And you fell for it,
hook, line, and sinker.
-So we were caught up in
your web of deception.
-Drat.
We underestimated them,
because they were kids.
-No one filled me
in on any of this.
-Nice work, Sakura.
-Well, I'm not sure I really
get what's going on around here.
But whatever.
-[whimpering]
-Please forgive us.
Forgive us.
-Words aren't going to help you.
-[whimpering and yelping]
-[neighing]
-This is just like three
years ago all over again.
We're swinging from a rope
like an oversized yo-yo.
You've got us all trussed
up in the same stupid rope--
-Hey, by the way,
who are you guys?
-And he doesn't even
remember who we are.
-Hey, Kakashi Sensei?
-Yeah?
-What are you hiding
under that mask?
-What?
You want to know
what's behind my mask?
-Yeah.
-You should have just said
so in the first place.
-So does that mean
you'll show us?
-Sure.
I don't mind.
-Huh?
-What's the big deal?
All right.
-(THINKING) Is it blimp lips?
-(THINKING) or buck teeth?
-(THINKING) or a tiny mouth?
-Behind this mask--
-(THINKING) behind that mask?
-Is another mask.
Pretty cool, huh?
-Huh!
-[laughing]
NARUTO: Are you
freaking kidding me?
What the hell kind
of ending is that?
[cawing]
[music playing]
NARUTO: I was born and
raised in the leaf village,
in the land of fire.
First name Naruto,
last name Uzumaki.
People have been
known to call me--
SAKURA: The knucklehead ninja.
NARUTO: I am not the
knucklehead ninja.
KAKASHI SENSEI: Why are
you talking like that?
NARUTO: We're
heading off to meet
with Boss Wasabi, aren't we?
I've got to learn how
to talk to him properly.
Next time, "Mission, Help and
Old Friend in the Land of Tea."
[music playing]