[AINS]
Lupisregina.
Do you have any idea
why I called for you?
No.
[AINS]
Hm. Tell me.
Have you heard about
the movements being made
by the monsters known
as the Giant of the East
and the Demon Snake of the West?
I have, but,
I didn't believe it worth
reporting to the Supreme One.
[AINS sighs]
So you knew?
--I did, but as I--
--[AINS] You fool!
[AINS] Why did you not
report it at once?
Was it your aim to
conceal the information?
No, I promise you!
I simply thought it was
beneath your notice.
[AINS] No more excuses.
I am disappointed in you.
[MOMONGA] She failed
at basic communication.
That's completely unacceptable.
Wait.
[AINS]
Lupisregina.
I'm curious.
Do you understand
why Carne Village
is valuable to Nazarick?
Well, yes.
You've used it previously
for experimentation.
And, um, there are lots
of fun toys there.
[AINS]
Ah, I see. My apologies.
The mistake here was mine.
I did not realize you thought
so little of the place.
Allow me to take back my words.
I should have not
called you a fool.
Forgive me.
Please say no more, my lord.
It was my fault
for being stupid.
[AINS]
Very well.
Now you know to be more
insightful in the future.
In the meantime, I will tell you
why that village is important.
[AINS] Carne Village has
some valuable inhabitants.
In particular, Nphirea
and his grandmother.
The two of them are in
the process of developing
a new potion for me.
[gasps] Right, I forgot!
Here. I was supposed to
give this to you, Lord Ains.
[AINS]
Oh?
A potion! A new one
Nphirea created
and asked me to pass on to you.
[AINS]
Excellent.
This potion is a prime
example of why Nphirea
and his grandmother
are so important.
[gasps]
[AINS] The potions of
this world are blue,
and, no matter how high
their quality may be,
they deteriorate over time.
By contrast, the potion
I know from Yggdrasil is red
and does not spoil.
[AINS] Nphirea is currently
trying to develop a potion
with similar properties
that does not rely
on any items or skills
from Yggdrasil.
However, the discovery
of a completely
different potion is certainly
an acceptable outcome, as well.
He is valuable enough
that I would have loved
to imprison him in
Nazarick and have him
perform his research here.
After all, knowledge is power.
Then, Lord, why not
do precisely that?
[AINS] Because earning his
trust and using his gratitude
to chain him will bring us
greater gain in the long term
than forcing him to
labor for us would.
I'm afraid there's
still one thing
I am too foolish and
ignorant to understand.
Forgive me for asking,
but why did you give
a red Yggdrasil potion
to the Britta woman
if they're so valuable?
[AINS]
Britta?
[MOMONGA]
Oh, right.
What do you mean? Explain.
Well, um...
Narberal's actually the
one who told me about it.
The incident she's referring
to occurred in E-Rantel.
Lord Ains gave a red potion
to an adventurer named Britta.
[AINS laughs]
[AINS] I'll admit,
it was a dangerous move.
However, the risk was
more than worth it
given what I stood to gain.
But... my lord.
I'd thought you
were acting simply
to replace that woman's potion.
[AINS] Did you truly
believe my motivation
would be so pedestrian?
[gasps] Of course
not--I'm sorry!
[AINS]
Nphirea.
I don't understand.
What about him, Lord?
[AINS]
Consider this.
When a person receives
a potion that they've
never seen before, what are
they most likely to do?
Oh, I know that one!
They'll ask somebody
for advice about it.
[AINS]
Correct!
As I had foreseen,
she went to the most skilled
and trusted potion maker
she knew, did she not?
And what happened as a result?
I came into contact
with Nphirea.
So that's why! I see now!
[AINS]
At last, you understand.
[MOMONGA]
They totally bought it!
That was such a
brilliant plan, Lord Ains!
Is that how you always
decide what to do--
by thinking three steps
ahead of everybody else?
[AINS]
Of course.
After all, I am the ruler of
the Great Tomb of Nazarick,
Ains Ooal Gown!
[AINS]
Lupisregina.
[gasps]
[AINS] The most important person
in that village is Nphirea.
Directly behind him
in value is Enri Emmot,
as his love for her is a
tether that keeps him there.
Last is Nphirea's
grandmother, Lizzy.
The others are
of no consequence,
but you must protect those
three at all cost.
[LUPISREGINA]
Right!
[AINS]
Now that you know my plans,
you won't make the
same mistake again.
Failure is unacceptable.
Understood?
Yes, my lord!
[AINS]
Good. Now go.
Do your duty and
don't disappoint me.
[LUPISREGINA]
Lord!
[NARBERAL]
Farewell, my lord.
[LUPISREGINA squeals]
Lord Ains is freaking amazing!
[NARBERAL]
Be quiet.
--[slap]
--[LUPISREGINA yelps]
Truly, Master.
You are amazing, but must
she behave like that?
It's embarrassing.
[AINS]
Let it go.
Aura, what do you know
about the Giant of the East
and the Demon Snake of the West?
My lord. I'm sorry,
but I know nothing.
I don't have any
information on monsters
called by those names.
I mean, I pretty much
combed those woods
for powerful enemies, but
everything there seemed weak.
[AINS] Something of Hamusuke's
level can hardly
be considered strong.
They would have
been easy to miss.
[AURA]
Shall I take care of them?
I'd be more than happy to.
If I send in a few of
my pets, it'll be easy!
[AINS]
Easy, perhaps, but boring.
I would like to see
the Giant of the East
and Demon Snake of
the West for myself.
And perhaps we can create
a test for Lupisregina
at the same time.
Huh?
[AURA]
We should be reaching the lair
of the Giant of the East
before much longer.
[AINS]
All right.
So, my lord.
Have you decided yet
how we shall dispose
of these creatures who
were foolish enough
to go against your wishes?
[AINS] Let us try
talking to them first.
[AURA]
Huh?
[AINS] If the Giant of
the East and Demon Snake
of the West are monsters that
did not exist in Yggdrasil,
I'd like to capture them.
Your kindness always
amazes me, Master.
[AINS]
It does?
However it might appear, Aura,
the truth is that I am
only kind to those
who are worthy of it.
Or those who are from
Nazarick, of course.
When it comes to
beings like Hamusuke,
I merely believe they
may have some worth
and so should not be wasted.
Seize every golden opportunity.
I hadn't realized Hamusuke
was really that valuable.
[AINS]
He is.
He has been a very
useful test subject.
[AURA] Are you talking
about the training
with the Lizard Men?
[AINS]
Yes.
I have him doing some
specialized conditioning
with a Death Knight.
I wish to find out if
they're capable of gaining
new skills or changing classes.
[MOMONGA] It's a long shot,
but if the Death Knight
could become a true warrior
class and learn martial arts,
it would greatly increase
Nazarick's power.
Still, it probably
won't be possible,
and I'm not sure about Hamusuke.
If we only had another
for comparison...
[AINS]
Ah.
Lord Ains, is something wrong?
[AINS]
Hm? No, it's nothing.
I was just lost in thought.
There's no need to worry.
That's good!
[MOMONGA]
She's so skinny.
Do kids just look smaller
now that my hands are so big?
[AURA yelps] What is it?
Did you need something?
[AINS] I was just thinking that
your waist is quite small.
Are you eating properly?
Yes. I am. Three meals a day.
On a regular schedule,
just as you instructed.
[AINS] Very good. Make sure
you continue to do so.
Right! I'll eat well
and fill out enough
to make old Shalltear blush!
[AINS] I suppose all of you
are bound to form
romantic attachments eventually.
Well, maybe, but it's still
way too early for me.
I'm only 70 years
old, after all.
[AINS]
Seventy? Oh, yes.
For a dark elf, that means
you're still only a child.
[AINS] So, tell me,
Aura, is there anyone
in Nazarick you like?
Do you have a "type"?
I love you the best out
of everybody, of course!
[AINS laughs]
That makes me happy.
Will you tell me yours now?
Who do you love
the most, Lord Ains?
[AINS]
Hm? I love you, too, Aura.
[gasps]
[MOMONGA] So, the children
are developing emotionally.
If there's a school for dark
elves, perhaps I should
consider sending
Aura and Mare there?
[AURA]
Um. Lord Ains!
[AINS]
Hm?
What's wrong?
That was quite loud.
Oh, um, I'm sorry.
[AINS]
There is no need to apologize.
Now, then. I've been
thinking about your future.
You have? Really?
[AINS] If ever we find a
dark elf colony or country,
let's visit it together.
What? Oh, of course.
That kind of future, yeah.
Absolutely. I'd be happy
to accompany you.
For right now, though.
We've almost reached
our destination.
[AINS]
All right.
Will you have the creatures
you brought along
stand at the ready nearby?
Yes!
Okay. Go, everyone!
[AINS]
This is laughable.
It seems they tried to copy
what you were building
with pathetic results.
Okay, here we are.
That should be their
nest up there.
[AINS] There are no
guards. How careless.
[AURA]
Smells terrible in here.
[AINS]
A gas trap maybe?
No, it could just as
easily be coincidence.
A bunch of footprints.
Judging by these,
I would say that
multiple creatures live here.
[AINS] Clearly, we can't expect
much intelligence from them.
I hope we can at least converse.
[OGRES growling, munching]
[AINS]
If I could have your attention.
Sorry to interrupt your meal.
[OGRES roar]
[AINS] As a welcoming committee,
they leave much to be desired.
[OGRE 04A]
Skeleton!
[OGRE 04B]
Skeleton! Enemy!
[AINS]
Aura, stand back.
[yells]
[AINS]
How filthy!
You not normal skeleton.
[AINS] Kindly refrain
from calling me that.
I am here to see your leader,
the Giant of the East.
Go. Inform him.
[AINS]
Well, I guess I could just wait.
Drat. I may have
overreacted a bit.
But its hand was just so dirty.
It was understandable.
A vile ogre tried to touch you.
You couldn't allow
that indignity!
[AINS]
That's reassuring, thank you.
You know, Punitto Moe once said,
"There are worse ideas
than punching people to
make them listen to you."
Or perhaps it was
Warrior Takemikazuchi?
[AURA]
Well, that settles it, then.
If the Supreme Beings
say so, it must be true.
[MOMONGA]
I don't know if those two
are the best examples.
[rumbling]
[AINS]
A troll.
So, "giant" is a bit of
a stretch in this case.
Although it isn't
a complete lie.
Is he similar in
strength to Hamusuke?
I believe they're
comparable, Lord Ains.
[AINS]
You are the Giant of the East?
In that case, I hope I am
correct in assuming you
are the Demon Snake of the West.
Yes. I'm referring to you,
the one hiding behind
an invisibility spell.
Concealing yourself
is pointless.
You may as well answer.
[AINS]
I see. You're a naga.
A type of snake,
I'll grant you that.
Still, the description
was misleading.
If you saw through my
invisibility so easily,
you're no normal skele--
Skeleton, why are you here?
[AINS]
I am not a skeleton.
Yet another
inaccurate description
I must see corrected.
Well, then, what are you?
Guu, the mighty ruler, feared
throughout the eastern forest,
will allow you to say your name.
[AURA, AINS]
Guu?
[AINS]
What an... interesting name.
Apologies for the
late introduction.
I should return the favor.
My name is Ains Ooal Gown.
[MONSTERS]
Huh?
[MONSTERS laugh]
Unlike me with my powerful name,
you have the name of a coward.
--Cowa--?!
--[AINS] Easy. Stay calm.
Please, mysterious undead.
These creatures believe long
names signify a lack of courage.
[AINS]
And what about you?
Do you believe me
to be a coward as well?
I don't think as they do.
I have a long name,
too, you see.
I am what you call the
Demon Snake of the West.
My name is Ryraryus
Spenia Ai Indarun.
So what business do you
have with us, weakling?
[AINS] I have ordered a
stronghold to be constructed
in the center of the forest
using golems and undead.
Do you know of it?
Of course I know, intruder!
If it weren't for this
gutless snake's whining,
we would have gone over there
and killed you already.
Now it looks like you
saved us the trouble.
[AINS]
Yes, so it would seem.
Which brings me to
the purpose of my visit.
I've come here because I would
like to negotiate with you.
If you wish to live,
submit yourselves to me.
As if I, the mighty
Guu would ever submit
to a poorly named weakling.
Guu! Be careful what you say.
I think first, I'll
make a meal of you.
Then I'll move on to
--the small one for dessert.
--[AINS laughs]
[AINS] You howl more than
a dog, you sack of flesh.
What was that?
[AINS]
I propose a duel.
Surely you, with your strong
name and boundless courage,
would be willing to
face one you believe
weak and cowardly.
If you're scared, however,
now is your chance to run.
I'll duel you, and there
will be nothing left
by the time I'm finished.
[AINS] Very well. Then let's
not waste any more time.
[GUU yells]
[GUU]
Huh?
[AINS]
Something wrong with your sword?
[BLUE TROLL 04A groans]
[AINS] Ah, yes. Trolls
can heal themselves.
[GUU cackles]
[AINS] The strong hold
the power of life and death
over the weak. However,
I found that distasteful.
He's too powerful.
We must work together
to defeat him!
Shut up!
[AINS] Some of us take
pride in our appearance.
I wish you wouldn't
wrinkle my clothes.
Now, are you finished
attacking me?
[GUU groans]
[growls, groans]
[AINS] Possessing a
so-called "cowardly name"
does not make one weak.
You may have a brain
the size of an acorn,
but surely you've
realized that by now.
[RYRARYUS hisses]
[AINS]
Aura! Don't let that one escape.
[groans]
Yes, Lord Ains.
What would you like me to do
with this weakling now?
You scrawny little brat.
I'm going to squeeze
you to death!
[AURA]
Hey!
You're obstructing my view
of Lord Ains' majestic form.
If you keep resisting,
I may accidentally
crush your throat.
[RYRARYUS groans]
[AINS]
Very good.
Now, take the creature away
from the fighting please.
I do not want him to
become collateral damage.
Right, you're comin' with me.
[AINS]
Now then. All healed up?
Let us continue
on with our duel.
I don't understand
how you're doing this.
Are you using magic?
[AINS]
Well, now. This is surprising.
Guu, the great king of
the forest and almighty
Giant of the East,
flinching in fear of a coward.
How can this be?
[AURA] He's obviously
quailing before you because
your name is a strong and
valiant one, Lord Ains,
while his not only
cowardly, but weird.
Right, snake?
Yes, that's right.
It's evidence of
Lord Ains Ooal Gown's
undeniable greatness.
[AINS] Indeed, that does
seem a viable explanation.
Damn you!
[AINS]
Silence, you filth.
[GUU groans]
[AINS] The trouble
with fighting a troll.
I could dice you
into tiny pieces,
and you'd likely still
be able to recover.
Though you do feel the pain.
My attacks don't have
any effect on you at all.
What the hell are you?
[AINS]
What am I? I am death.
And I have come for you.
Kill him now!
All of you! Go!
[AINS] I suppose I shouldn't
be surprised that someone
with such a cowardly name
would break his promise
of single combat.
It wouldn't do
for you to escape.
I've played around long enough.
Aura of Despair. Fifth Tier.
[RYRARYUS]
I'll submit to you!
I wish to serve you with
every ounce of my being.
It would be an honor
to do the bidding of one
with such a courageous name!
[AINS]
Ah. All right.
I did originally come
here for negotiations.
Have we collected data
on a troll zombie yet?
[AINS]
Hm.
A magic weapon?
It may be useful for
increasing the power
of an individual
from the village.
Do you have subordinates?
A troll would be nice.
I do have one, great lord.
[AINS]
Most excellent.
In that case, we can use
him as a substitute.
Although, it may be difficult.
You will bring your subordinate
and go to the building we are
constructing in the forest.
Aura, free him.
Are you sure, my lord?
[AINS] It will be fine.
If he betrays me--
No! I swear on my life
I would never consider
betraying someone of your power!
Only a fool would!
But I've seen the
terrifying coldness
that lurks in your gaze!
I know I'm nothing before you.
[AINS] Well, all right then.
Now leave, quickly.
And find me more subordinates.
That is my first order to you.
[RYRARYUS]
Yes!
[DEMIURGE] This seems
to be a menu, my lord.
[AINS]
I wanted to ask your opinion.
It would be a meal for
a human man and woman.
Perhaps a child as well.
Well, if Lord Ains is deigning
to offer humans a meal,
I believe they should eat
anything and everything
that is served,
without complaint.
However, I suspect that opinion
isn't what you're looking for.
If there is to be
a child present,
I would steer clear of
a dish like foie gras.
Also...
I would suggest something a bit
lighter and more refreshing.
[AINS] I see. That is
helpful. Thank you.
[DEMIURGE]
I am unworthy of your praise.
Lord Ains, if I may
be so bold as to ask--
do you plan to invite
guests to the holy place
of the Supreme Beings,
our Great Tomb of Nazarick?
[AINS]
Is there a problem with that?
[DEMIURGE]
Of course not.
Please forgive the implication.
Your will is all, my lord.
I live to obey.
[beeping]
[AINS]
Entoma.
[ENTOMA]
Yes, Lord Ains.
I have received a report
from Lupisregina.
[AINS]
Excellent.
It seems she's
passed the first test.
[ENTOMA] Also, she has requested
permission to enter battle.
[AINS]
Granted.
She is to do whatever
is necessary.
I want her to protect
those three with her life.
[clanging]
[gasps]
[NEMU]
What's wrong?
I don't know.
[AINS]
The monsters of the Great Forest
attack Carne Village.
At the main gate,
Jugem leads goblins, ogres,
and human vigilantes in
the defense of thier home.
Meanwhile, Enri and
Nphirea discover a troll
attempting to enter from
the rear of the city.
There's no hope for victory
if Jugem and the others
must fight on two fronts,
so Enri and Nphirea
risk their lives to buy time.
Chapter 5: "Two Leaders."
I am eager to see how
this might resolve.