[CHAMBERLAIN]
The region of Nazarick,
under the Sorcerer King
Ains Ooal Gown,
is hereby recognized
as a sovereign nation,
as well as a friend and
ally of the Empire,
by decree of Jircniv
Rune Farlord El Nix,
Emperor of Baharuth.
Furthermore,
the City of E-Rantel,
as well as the lands around it,
belong to Nazarick,
yet are currently held
by the Re-Estize Kingdom.
These lands should be returned
to their original owner at once.
Should this demand be refused,
the Empire will be proud
to aid Sorcerer King Gown
in the liberation
of his country.
[RAMPOSA] Our historians
have found no mention
of a country known as Nazarick.
Nor of an Ains Ooal Gown
who owned the land
surrounding E-Rantel.
There's not a shred of
legitimacy in this demand.
Then it would seem these
are the ravings of a lunatic.
As often as they invade,
it only makes sense
they would start
running out of reasons.
That could be the cause.
Now, that said,
I can't help but feel that I've
heard this name once before.
From the Chief
Warrior, I believe.
He is the same magic
caster who saved my life.
Of that I'm sure.
Oh, I see.
And afterwards, did he offer
to let you kiss his royal ring?
[NOBLES chuckle]
[UROVANA]
Control yourselves.
You stand before the king.
Well, I doubt we'll need to give
much attention to
one magic caster.
If you would permit me to speak.
Their claims are baseless,
their demands unreasonable.
We have no choice
but to go to war.
--[NOBLES gasp]
--[NOBLE 10F] Hear! Hear!
But then...
Chief Warrior Stronoff.
I would like for you to share
your opinion on the matter.
Your Grace.
In my humble opinion,
this war will not
be ended so easily
as the annual wars
that have preceded it.
Do you have a reason?
Yes.
It's because we'll be fighting
the great magic caster,
Ains Ooal Gown.
My king. How important
is E-Rantel?
I think, if possible, we should
cede it without resisting.
[gasps]
[laughs] A rare thing
to hear the Kingdom's
Chief Warrior speak
like a whipped pup.
Though the idea itself
is not without merit.
We could potentially
avoid a costly war
simply by ceding a single city.
It's a king's duty
to protect his people
from needless suffering.
Would a true king
not be willing to make
such an honorable sacrifice?
Before letting his
people suffer?
Well said indeed!
[BLUMRUSH] That land is under
direct control of the king.
If you think it right that he
give that land to the enemy,
then why not offer your own?
Chief Warrior, your
words invite needless
suspicion as to your allegiance.
[ROYAL 10E]
Yes, quite right. So they do!
The loyalty of my Chief Warrior
has been tested and proven.
It's beyond dispute.
This magic caster
must be strong enough
to warrant such words
I appreciate your counsel,
but I can't simply
cede E-Rantel.
A ruler cannot give up
his cities freely.
It's my duty to protect them.
Your Grace, forgive me for
speaking so foolishly.
[RAEVEN] War is inevitable.
Let's speak practically.
First, as this is a matter
of the defense of Re-Estize,
we all must prepare
to lend our aid.
But, Marquis Raeven,
only His Majesty--
That's enough. Just think.
If His Majesty's army
should fall,
why would the Empire stop
at taking E-Rantel?
Assisting his majesty in
the defense of the Kingdom
is the logical choice.
All of our lands
are at stake here.
Of course.
You only think about
your own gain.
I say it is the duty
of any noble to stand
with His Majesty in battle.
I concur.
My blade is the king's
to use as he sees fit.
[GAZEF] Since His Majesty
drove out Jaldabaoth,
the Royal Faction has grown
in strength considerably.
That's why it's essential
that he maintain his image
as a strong king. But...
Then it's agreed that
we shall go to war,
but we should delay
our formal response
for as long as we can.
[CHAMBERLAIN]
Yes, Your Grace.
I believe we can delay the war
for as long as two months.
While the Empire awaits
our declaration of war,
we'll gather our
troops in E-Rantel.
I'll go as well, of course.
And it would be my honor
to accompany you, Father.
That seems a bit
reckless, brother.
You're first in line to
inherit the crown, remember?
I should be the one--
No!
Ah--
Prince Barbro.
You're a valuable heir
to the throne,
as well as the fiancé
of my own dear daughter.
Shall I cower here
while my father fights?
[BOULLOPE] No, it's right for a
man to prove himself in battle.
I shall send my finest
soldiers with you.
I believe 4,000 will suffice.
Truly?
[BOULLOPE]
Is that acceptable, Your Grace?
Yes. By all means.
You have my thanks, Father!
I'll cleave the head
from El Nix's shoulders
and bring it to you on a plate!
[CHENEKO]
How charming!
[ROYALS laugh]
[RAEVEN growls]
That idiot prince!
He'll "cleave the head
from El Nix's shoulders."
Every last one of them's
a damn imbecile.
How can they not see the
danger our kingdom is in?
The nobles would rather fight
each other than the Empire.
Marquis Blumrush is
the worst of them.
He's selling the Kingdom's
secrets to the Empire.
Even the king himself.
At least he has compassion
for his people,
but he doesn't use
his head at all!
[sighs] If Prince Zanac doesn't
inherit the throne quickly,
this squabbling will never end.
The king knows that
as well as I do,
but he lacks the guts
to disinherit Barbro.
Damn! Such a foolish parent.
--[knocking]
--Huh?
Oopsies.
[RAEVEN]
Do come in.
[giggles]
Lee! My darling boy!
[laughs]
[baby talk]
What's this about? Huh, Lee?
[giggles]
[RAEVEN'S WIFE]
Dear.
Yes, what is it?
It's detrimental to
a child's development
to speak to them in such
a diminutive manner.
Ha! Rubbish!
I say that's nothing
but a baseless rumor.
[baby talk] Right, little Lee?
So tell me! What's going on?
Right now? Well, we're
about to have dinner!
[RAEVEN]
Oh, boy!
It's one of your
favorite foods, Papa!
[RAEVEN]
Wow! That makes me so happy!
So what is for dinner?
[RAEVEN'S WIFE]
It's Gabura fish meuniere .
I see.
[gasps] Little Lee?
What's wrong?
I wanted to be the
one who told you.
Oh. That's all Papa's fault!
I'm sorry, little Lee.
Why did you tell me?
[sighs]
[RAEVEN]
Sorry, little Lee.
Papa's so silly,
he already fogot!
Will you tell me
what we're eating?
[LEE]
Mm...
C'mon, why won't you tell me?
Papa's about to cry!
[LEE]
No! Don't cry, um...
It's that fish you like, Papa!
Oh, yeah? Wow! Papa's so happy!
Papa loves you.
And he wants to give his little
Lee the very best in life.
So he's gonna work
as hard as he can.
[RAEVEN] Everyone.
Thanks to your hard work,
preparations for
war are complete.
Now, we must discuss
our strategy
for the battle to come.
Three days ago,
the Emperor sent us
a missive stating
where his army will await us.
[BOULLOPE]
Is it not the same as always?
[RAEVEN] Yes, we'll fight
in the cursed fog
of the Katze Plains yet again.
Then can we assume that
they'll be employing
their usual tactics?
Unfortunately, Marquis Blumrush,
I don't believe that's likely.
I sent my subordinates, a team
of ex-Orichalcum adventurers,
to scout their army.
They reported seeing six
different coats-of-arms.
--[NOBLES gasp]
--[BLUMRUSH] So many!
[RAEVEN] For every two men
they brought last year,
they've brought another.
This is three-fourths
of their army.
In addition, we can
expect the magic caster
Ains Ooal Gown to
fight beside them.
Heh. A single magic caster
can't sway the results
of this battle, no matter
how strong he is.
Well, to be safe,
I think we should estimate
that he has the strength
of 5,000 footsoldiers.
--[NOBLES gasp]
--[LYTTON] What? Why so many?
I would equate the strength
of Chief Warrior Stronoff
to that of 1,000 soldiers.
If this caster has a
warrior like him on guard,
five times that
number seems right.
I trust the eyes
of the Chief Warrior.
I appreciate it.
Your Grace.
In regards to this so-called
Sorcerer King Gown.
It's said that he once
saved Carne Village
from a group of raiders.
We should send some
soldiers there to gather
information from the villagers.
I think we should give this
responsibility to the prince.
Marquis!
A fine idea, Marquis Boullope.
But, Father!
Go, my son. This is my command.
You are to travel
to Carne Village at once
and question the
people living there.
[BARBRO] If that is your
order, then I must obey.
[BOULLOPE] I have one more
question, Your Majesty.
Have you decided who
should lead our forces
in the battle to come?
I believe I would be the
most fitting candidate.
[ALL gasp]
Marquis Raeven.
Yes.
[RAMPOSA]
I shall leave it to you.
Your Majesty.
Marquis Raeven.
My troops will be in your care.
Tell me if you need anything.
You have my gratitude.
[RAMPOSA]
Any other matters to resolve?
Very well, then prepare
yourselves for battle.
[RAMPOSA grunts]
You handled that
well, Your Grace.
Good. Because it took
a lot out of me.
[chuckles]
My son is headstrong
and foolish.
He aches for battle,
but I can't stand
the thought of losing him.
I believe that Marquis Boullope
aims to protect him, too.
I believe this
as well. He's loyal.
There's no doubt in my mind
he wishes for Barbro
to inherit the crown.
I see. So then he
came up with the mission
because, if the prince
fought in this battle,
he'd have trouble
protecting him.
This battle could end us.
I should've dealt with
Baharuth long ago.
Before the nobles
split into factions
and started nipping
at each other's throats.
I wish only to leave a
good and strong kingdom
to the child who succeeds me.
I wonder. Is this not
my best chance?
My waning influence has resurged
in the wake of Jaldabaoth.
For the first time in decades,
we're a kingdom united.
Perhaps we'll win this battle
and earn a few years of peace.
Your Grace.
[door opens]
Marquis Raeven, I was
hoping you'd return.
I'm sorry for giving
you this burden.
Not at all. I'm honored
to do it, Your Grace.
And it would have been foolish
to allow Marquis Boullope
to lead our forces.
The only commands that one knows
are "attack" and "retreat."
Furthermore, if you'd
said you would command
the army yourself, the
Noble Faction would resist.
Many might have pulled
out their soldiers.
As such,
I turned out to be the only
viable candidate you had.
Although, I confess,
this will be exhausting.
I'd appreciate it if
Your Grace would allow me
to retire to my lands
for a few months--
once the war is
finally over, that is.
I should've asked you.
Please, I owe you this much.
There were plenty of
times that I've acted
without receiving
your permission.
And I feel that I could've taken
measures to prevent this.
Chief Warrior Stronoff.
Out of ignorance, I thought
you were a dishonorable man.
Now I understand
your good intentions.
You needn't apologize
for such a thing.
So raise your head, please.
[GAZEF] I must be made to
atone for my foolishness.
Or this guilt will never cease!
Well, if you insist.
Then atone by allowing
me to henceforth
call you Master Gazef
instead of Chief Warrior.
[gasps]
I never knew you well.
But I've always had
respect for you.
You have my thanks.
[RAEVEN] Now that we're
all on good terms.
I was hoping we might discuss
the Kingdom's future.
And how to win this war.
[GAZEF] How many of these
men will come back alive?
[GAZEF] Is it not the
duty of those who stand
on top to protect the people?
[GAZEF]
Ains Ooal Gown.
What could that man be thinking?
All I know is that he is not
a man I'd want to fight.
[gasps]
I take it the
adventurers have decided
to stay out of this battle?
Guess so.
With the exception
of Lockmeyer's group--
They all work for
Marquis Raeven now.
I see.
Hey, Lord Stronoff--
Just call me Gazef.
Well, Climb.
You allowed me to sneak up
behind you in plate armor.
Which tells me you're slacking.
Oh. My apologies, sir!
It's all right to relax
every now and then.
You noticed me from
across the street.
Of course, I did.
You were letting your presence
ooze out all over the place.
[GAZEF]
Climb.
When you're protecting
Princess Renner,
you should be aware
of such presences.
So that's what you're on about.
Listen, Climb.
Since you're usually
training on your own,
it can be difficult to sharpen
those kinds of senses.
Not all of your enemies'll
wanna come at you head-on
with a sword in hand.
Make sense?
[CLIMB]
As you say.
Gazef, thank you for
bringing this shortcoming
to my attention.
I'll train harder.
It's fine.
As the princess's guard,
you're one of my subordinates.
This is my fault.
I should've trained you more,
but I was worried the
nobles would see us.
Even now, I'm leaving
that duty to another.
There's no need for thanks.
So, hey. Are you two
free right now?
[GAZEF]
Tell me.
What were the two of you
doing over there?
[BRAIN] Oh, we went to pay
a visit to Momon of Darkness.
Did you now?
I hear that he recently
made E-Rantel his home.
[BRAIN]
Right.
We heard the same, so we
went back to his place
to see if he'd give
us some advice.
About Shalltear Bloodfallen,
the vampire.
On the same day and not
far from where I first
met that monster...
[BRAIN] ...Momon took
down a Honyopnyoko.
Honyopnyoko, huh?
I heard about that.
The thing sounded
incredibly dangerous.
I believe Momon defeated it
with a legendary magic item.
You did your research.
Apparently Momon was trying
to hunt down two vampires.
Which leads me to believe
that the one he didn't
take down was
Shalltear Bloodfallen.
Good guess.
So, what did he have to say?
Well. Not a lot.
He wasn't at home.
That's unfortunate.
He could've been helpful.
I'd like to speak with
this Momon myself someday.
Talk about an amazing view.
Yeah, it's none too
rough on the eyes.
[CLIMB]
Those are the Katze Plains.
We'll be fighting there soon.
[GAZEF]
They're less pleasant up close.
The undead wander
through that fog.
Those fields are
stained with blood.
[exhales]
[BRAIN] So, why'd you bring
us to such an isolated spot?
[gasps]
Is there a noble that you
need us to do away with?
[BOTH gasp]
[BRAIN]
Gazef. I owe you a lot.
I would do dirty work
for you in a heartbeat.
Well, I appreciate that. But no.
I didn't bring you here
to ask for something.
I just figured that,
before the battle,
it'd be nice to talk alone.
That's it?
For an army big-shot,
you've got a lot of free time.
By the way.
Hey, Climb. I had
a question for you.
[CLIMB]
Sir?
You're gonna stand out
with that armor of yours.
Have you considered
changing the color
before you head into battle?
[CLIMB]
I truly appreciate your concern.
But I can't do as you say.
If I fight well in armor
as conspicuous as this,
then my deeds will be noted,
and Princess Renner's
reputation will be improved.
For a goal like that,
I'm more than willing
to risk my life.
Also, Princess Renner
has requested
that I go into battle
without changing my armor.
I see. Then, do as you will.
I know you like
to worry, but don't.
I'll be right beside
Climb the whole battle.
Whatever danger he leaps into,
I'll pull him back out.
The Four Imperial
Knights are strong.
That said, you could
best any of them.
However, you should be wary.
Because if you come
before Ains Ooal Gown.
He will surely be
the end of you.
I'll keep an eye out.
He's really that powerful?
Yes.
Duly noted. Appreciate
the heads up.
[GAZEF] There's a pub I
like back at the capital.
We can celebrate there
once this war is over.
You mean once we've
sent those Imperials
running for the hills, right?
Oh, did you mean me as well?
[GAZEF]
It'll be my treat.
[BRAIN]
Say, Climb. Are you a drinker?
Frankly, I've never
actually had a drink.
That so?
Well, then this'll be
part of your training.
There'll be times when you're
socially obliged to drink.
I'd say you should get
drunk at least once
so you know how it feels.
That makes sense.
Then I'll accompany you both.
Well, after the fight,
the three of us should
meet here again.
So do your best to stay alive.
[CARVAIN] We pay our respects
to the Sorcerer King!
[AINS]
I appreciate your kind welcome.
Your Majesty.
I am known as
Sir Nimble Arc Dale Anoch.
It's my honor to serve
as your guide.
[AINS]
I'll be in your care then.
Forgive me for any trouble
I might cause you.
I'm General Carvain.
Pleasure to meet you.
First off, I would
like to thank you
for assisting my regiment.
We're honored to have
you fighting beside us.
[AINS] It was Emperor
Jircniv's request.
I'm glad I accepted.
By the way, I hear
you wish to signal
the battle's start
with one of my spells.
If that is the case,
might I bolster our ranks with
a portion of my own army?
That would be a great help
and honor, Your Grace.
However, we plan to
attack the Kingdom
as early as the day after next.
[AINS]
That won't be a problem.
Can you hear me, Shalltear?
Open a gate right behind me.
I have need of my soldiers.
[AINS]
This is my army!
Damn it. Marquis Raeven.
I should be the one to
inherit Father's crown.
But he sided with my brother.
I should be distinguishing
myself in battle,
but instead I've been
sent on a child's errand.
Hold on.
Could it be that Father
wants to stop me
from proving myself?
[CHENEKO]
Prince Barbro.
Are you feeling ill,
Your Highness?
No. I feel fine.
I'm thinking on our mission
and how best we
might complete it.
Have you any thoughts,
Baron Cheneko?
Not at this time, Highness.
I'll leave such weighty
matters to the future king.
You.
Yes, Your Highness?
What are you orders?
We need to hurry.
Let's double our pace
and reach Carne quickly.
This way,
we'll finish our job,
return tomorrow night,
and then we can
take a short nap.
And head to the Katze Plains
before the morning sun rises.
[KNIGHT 10A]
But out of our 5,000 soldiers,
4,500 are on foot.
At that pace,
some of them will
collapse from exhaustion.
That's an order I just gave you.
We must bring down
the Empire's army.
Defeat at the Katze Plains
is not an option.
Make them run.
Whip them if you must!
[KNIGHT 10A]
As you command.
[AINS] With the forces of
the Empire and Kingdom
about to clash,
5,000 royal troops arrive
at Carne Village.
This detachment is lead
by the first prince, Barbro.
After receiving
Lupisregina's report,
I watch over the town by
means of a magic mirror.
Against such an
overwhelming force,
the town's defenders
have no chance.
The village will surely
be forced to surrender.
Chapter 11: "Another Battle."
Wait. What in the world
just happened?!