[clanging]
You okay?
Yeah.
We have to get ready quickly.
Right!
[TOWN FOLK screaming]
[VILLAGER 05A]
Enri!
I'll take care of Nemu.
You do what you need to do!
Thanks, be safe!
But, Enri! I--
Nemu. Wait for me at
the safehouse, okay?
I have to fulfill my duties.
[ENRI]
Get going.
I've only just become
chief of the village.
It's like I'm being tested
by some evil god.
[thumping, rumbling]
[JUGEM]
All right, that'll have to do!
Go check your weapons!
Miss Enri.
Sorry I took so long.
How's Ms. Lizzy?
[NPHIREA]
Grandma's fine.
I took her to the
safehouse before I came.
Hey!
I'm gonna put your tribe
to work, too, Agu.
We're ready!
The Gigu tribe stands with you.
We'll repay our debt!
Agu, there's something
I'd like you guys to do
when the battle starts.
Throw these at
the largest enemies.
Say no more!
Us hobgoblins are very
good at throwing stuff.
So what're the odds
that this could be
the Giant of the East,
or Demon Snake of the West?
Well, we sure as hell
can't rule it out.
Gotcha.
I take it we'll be going
with Intruder Plan Two then?
That's right.
Look sharp!
We're seein' a lot of movement!
Yeah, they're definitely
comin' towards the village!
Warriors of the Carne Militia!
Prepare for battle!
[VIGILANTES]
Right!
I'm gonna do a quick run
through the village.
Just in case someone
missed the commotion.
You be careful, Miss Enri.
Yeah. You, too, Jugem.
[JUGEM]
Keep her safe, Nphi!
Leave it to me! Enri, c'mon!
[MONSTERS growling]
They're here!
Archers ready!
[JUGEM]
Enemy in range. Everyone, fire!
Let's give 'em hell!
[MONSTERS groaning]
Sounds like we hit 'em!
Yeah!
Prepare for wave two!
Ah--
Don't panic! Second wave!
Don't take us goblins lightly!
[groans]
Another volley!
Let loose!
[MONSTERS groan]
They'll break through soon.
Switch to melee weapons!
[rumbling]
[OGRE 05B grunts]
'Bout as smart as
a lump of bricks.
We made the right
side of the gate
more fragile on purpose!
[JUGEM] You just funneled
yourselves straight into hell.
[yells]
Attack!
Me smash!
I don't think so!
[groans]
At this rate, we'll
destroy them easily!
Long as they don't
have any magic.
[gasps]
[JUGEM]
What is that thing?
[CONA] A troll? But why
is it shaking like that?
[ALL gasp]
Jugem.
Do you think that's
the Giant of the East?
If it is him, then even with
all of us fighting together,
we might lose. Damn it.
Should we take
Miss Enri and retreat?
Yeah, she'll fight us, but--
[gasps]
No. We can't give up yet.
That's our last resort,
but right now, we fight.
Soldiers! The odds are
stacked against us.
But I don't wanna hear one
word about fallin' back.
Let your heroic
image strike fear
into the eyes of those
who stand against you!
[SOLDIERS yell]
Now go!
Time for us to teach this
Giant piece of garbage
not to mess with Chief Enri!
This side's clear as well.
[ENRI]
Looks like everyone got out.
[rumbling]
[BOTH gasp]
[NPHIREA, ENRI panting]
What was that?
I can't be certain,
but I think it was a troll.
A troll?
I know we have to hide,
but it smells awful here.
[NPHIREA] That actually
works to our advantage.
Trolls have an incredible
sense of smell.
But ogres have
a very strong odor.
Hopefully, that'll
conceal us for now.
Not good.
Trolls are powerful creatures.
Even one of them could turn
the tide of this battle.
You think so?
[TROLL 05A snorts]
He'll head for the gate.
All that blood and sweat
will attract him.
We should go. Jugem
needs to be warned.
That won't work.
If the troll reaches the battle,
our forces will be crushed.
What else can we do?
[gasps]
We have to keep it here, Nphi.
We don't have to beat it,
or even wound it.
We just have to buy some time.
Will you help me? Please?
I don't mind trying to fight it.
But uh, if it hits
me, that's that.
Thank you. I think
I have a plan.
First, we're gonna
make some fake ogres.
Me smell human. Tasty.
Ogre? Me smell one or two. Many.
[TROLL 05A groans]
[TROLL 05A]
That smell... so bad.
You trick me!
Human! Me eat.
Huh?
No run. Come here!
[BOTH yelling]
[groans]
[yells]
Hah!
[GUU yells]
[JUGEM] Strange. The troll's
wound isn't healing.
[yells]
[SOLDIERS gasp]
Hey!
This village belongs
to Miss Enri!
No chance in hell
I'm gonna let you
make a mess in here!
[ENRI panting]
I wonder if we were able
to buy them enough time.
If we lay out the cloth
the ogres slept on,
maybe the troll will
think ogres are here.
Maybe. It's a strong odor,
but a troll's nose is
a difficult thing to fool.
This could help.
But isn't that just
a bottle of medicine?
[NPHIREA]
Yeah, but it stinks enough
to confuse the nose
of a barghest.
If it hits the troll's nose,
its sense of smell should be
crippled for a bit.
That said, he should
figure it out
once he sees the fabric.
When that happens, we'll
have to get it to follow us.
I think it would catch up
to either of us eventually.
But if we can come up with
a way to take turns running...
[NPHIREA panting]
Enri!
[ENRI]
Leave it to me.
No way.
It can already tell the
difference between our smells?
Nphi!
[NPHIREA grunts]
Go! Run for it!
I'll try to buy you some time.
No way. Don't be
stupid, come with--!
It would catch us both!
Your best chance of survival
is to run while I distract it!
Reinforce armor!
[NPHIREA] Please. Let me
protect the girl I love.
Come at me, ya big
bastard. Acid Arrow!
[TROLL 05A grunts]
Hurry up, Enri!
See if the goblins
can send any help!
Try to be safe, okay?
Understood. You, too.
Whelp. Looks like
this is how I die.
You seem to be a bit wary of me.
Little do you know, you could
finish me off with one hit.
Hypnotism!
He's resistant to it?
[NPHIREA yells]
[gasps]
[NPHIREA groans]
[NPHIREA wretches]
Can't believe I'm still
alive. That's awesome.
I'm a little tougher
than I thought I was.
Acid Arrow!
[NPHIREA] I have to
buy as much time as I can.
Can't believe I
actually confessed.
[NPHIREA]
But... I don't wanna die
without knowing if Enri
feels the same way.
One last Acid Arrow!
[grunts]
Come on, we're almost there!
[ENRI]
Nphi!
[GOKOU]
Too far.
[KUUNEL]
Brother!
[gasps]
[LUPISREGINA]
Wow, this guy really
beat the piss out
of ya, didn't he?
You're lucky I showed up.
Heal.
[gasps]
Why don't'cha step back
to a safe distance?
[ENRI]
Nphi! I'm so glad you're okay.
I don't what I would do if--
We're safe now.
Hey, don't cry.
[ENRI]
Stupid.
So, I don't wanna spoil
the mood here, but--
[BOTH gasp]
[LUPISREGINA]
Whoa, that's a smell.
Kinda reminds me of hamburgers.
Anyway, I'm glad you
kids aren't dead.
And unless my ears deceive me,
the main battle went well, too.
[SOLDIERS cheering]
Those sound like victory cheers.
You hear that?
We really did it!
[LUPISREGINA]
Welp. My job is done here,
so I'm'a head home.
Oh, yeah. Nphi.
Lord Ains wanted to reward you
for creating that purple potion,
so he decided to invite you
to his home for dinner.
You better watch that
scrawny neck of yours.
Oh. I mean you should
look forward to it.
Thanks so much for everything!
Hey, Chief, n' brother Nphi.
We're gonna go let the
people at the safehouse
know the coast is clear.
Why don't you two relax
and take it easy for a while?
[ENRI]
We made it.
[NPHIREA]
Mm-hm.
[ENRI]
We got lucky.
[NPHIREA]
Mm-hm.
[ENRI] I never wanna go through
something like this again.
[NPHIREA]
Mm.
[SOLDIERS laughing]
I haven't thought about
what this means before,
but I know that I never
want you to leave me, Nphi.
Really?
I wonder if that means
I'm in love with you.
I can't tell you what
it means, but, uh,
I'd be happy if you were.
[VILLAGER 05B]
Angle looks good so far!
Perfect! Good job.
So what do you think about
the troll's magic greatsword?
Well, I've only sparred with it,
but I've gotten used to the
weight and center of balance,
so I can use it as well
as my old sword now.
Tell ya what.
I've never seen that
kinda troll before.
It was kinda weird
how that fight went.
How so?
Well, it couldn't heal.
Then there's the
way it was moving.
And when I scored a cut...
It just didn't feel right.
And it barely reacted.
It was like it was already dead.
Dead, but still moving.
Like a zombie?
Can't say for sure.
It might've just been
a different species of troll.
You think I look okay?
You look lovely, Enri.
[gasps] Thank you.
Hope I didn't keep ya waiting!
Ow!
Please excuse her behavior.
My name's Yuri Alpha.
I'm a maid of Lord Ains.
I have come to escort
Lord Nphirea, Lady Enri,
and Lady Nemu to his home.
[squeals]
Oh, wow.
[MAIDS]
Welcome, honored guests.
[gasps, laughs]
So cool, so cool, so cool!
Nemu! Don't be rude, come back!
Lord Gown! Your house
is so amazing!
[AINS]
You find it that impressive?
No, you're right.
My home truly is
amazing, isn't it?
I sure think so!
Did you build this place
yourself, Lord Gown?
[AINS laughs]
That's right!
My friends and I
designed it ourselves.
That's so awesome!
Your friends must be just
as amazing as you are!
[AINS laughs]
Sorry, Lord Gown.
My sister means well.
She just doesn't know
much about etiquette.
[AINS]
No need for apologies.
Tell me, young Nemu.
Would you care for a tour
of the house that I--
that my friends and I built?
[NEMU]
Yeah! I wanna see it!
[AINS laughs]
Then see it you shall!
Come, I'll show you around.
I hope my little
sister doesn't end up
causing any trouble
to Lord Gown.
I don't think you need to worry.
Lord Gown seems like a
very patient person to me.
Yes, that's correct.
There's no cause for you
to feel nervous, milady.
Please, drink.
Thanks! I'm
completely reassured!
[laughs nervously]
[NPHIREA]
Uh...
So sweet.
Yeah...
That's probably because of
all the sugar cubes you used.
Sweets are pretty hard to
come by back at the village.
You know, I might find
a way to change that
if I'm able to learn
spice magic someday.
Try your best to learn it!
[NPHIREA]
Uh. Yeah. Sure.
Thank you so much for
bringing me here!
This place is the best.
It's so clean and shiny!
Lord Gown.
Please let me apologize if
my sister was rude in any way.
[AINS]
No. Please allow me to apologize
for taking so long.
[ENRI] Not at all!
Thanks for showing her.
[AINS]
Of course.
Now, before we discuss the
success of Nphirea's potion,
why don't the three of you eat?
What's on this evening's menu?
For this evening's dinner,
our appetizer shall
be piercing lobster,
drizzled with a
noatun fish velouté.
For your next appetizer,
we'll be serving
a pan-sizzled Visofnir
rooster foie gras.
Then we'll move on
to a cream soup
made with Alfheim
yam and chestnuts.
After that, we'll be
serving the main course
for the evening.
A marbled steak,
hewn from the Ancient Frost
Dragon of Jotunheim.
Then, for your dessert.
A compote of the
golden apples of Idunn,
drizzled with yogurt.
These will be
accompanied, of course,
by a golden tea ice cream.
In regards to your
after-meal drink,
coffee may not be
to everyone's liking,
so we've prepared pitchers
of iced Roulesh Peach Water.
And that's tonight's menu.
[ENRI]
Did she just cast a spell?
If there's to be
a child present,
I would steer clear--
[AINS]
We have a child present.
So perhaps we should
steer clear of foie gras.
I think something light and
refreshing might be better.
Ah, in that case, I can
have the chefs substitute
a scallop salad served with
a plum confit dressing.
[AINS] I see. That should
be better, don't you think?
Oh, yeah, we like
salad just fine,
thank you for asking.
[AINS]
Then let's begin.
Although I will not be
eating with you tonight.
I hope that won't
stop the three of you
from eating all you wish.
Please enjoy this
meal as a family.
[muttering] I'll have to add one
more name to Lupisregina's list.
Huh? What did you say?
I couldn't hear you.
[AINS] Oh. It's nothing
important, Nemu.
Please, follow me.
Right!
Uh--
I just realized
I can't beat him.
Well, not that I ever had
a chance of competing.
Lord Gown's on a
completely different level.
He's not the kind of
guy I'd fall for.
But you are, Nphi.
[gasps]
[NPHIREA]
Let's go.
[ENRI]
Sure.
[AINS] Our visit to the capital
of the Baharuth Empire
revealed it to be
a vibrant city.
It seems the young
emperor, Jircniv,
is quick to toss aside
the incompetent.
He has also been known
to hire commoners
if they possess
sufficient skill.
After completing a small errand,
I visit the Adventurer's Guild
in the guise of
Momon of Darkness.
Presented with an easy job,
I make the decision to take it.
Chapter 6:
"Invitation to Death."
You are all fools for
undertaking this mission.