[AURA] Our challengers
tonight are a band
of four foolish human
adventurers that dared
to infiltrate the
Great Tomb of Nazarick!
And against them,
we have the Supreme One.
He's the illustrious overlord
of the Great Tomb of Nazarick!
The King of Death itself,
Lord Ains Ooal Gown!
And his corner man--
or rather, lady--
is the overseer of the
floor guardians, Albedo!
This is my fault.
I wanted the money
and got too greedy.
What, are you kidding me?
If the rest of us
weren't just as greedy,
then we wouldn't be here.
That's right--we all
decided to take on
this job together.
Comes with the territory.
Sometimes a gig
goes south, right?
I'm not hopeful, but let's
try to talk this through.
Might be worth a shot.
I must offer you my most
sincere apologies.
Master Ains Ooal, uh...
[AINS]
Ains Ooal Gown.
[HEKKERAN] Yes, of course.
Master Ains Ooal Gown.
I am deeply sorry
for any displeasure
that our intrusion
has caused you.
If you might show us your mercy,
I would gladly pay
any price you ask.
We have plenty of gold to offer.
[AINS] I'm afraid that your
perspective is flawed.
After all, if you were to
find maggots in your food,
you wouldn't ask what
they had to offer--
you'd crush them
dead on the spot.
Although in that case,
the maggots themselves
are blameless.
You, on the other hand, knew
full well what you were doing.
You invaded my home to
satisfy your petty greed.
That makes you
lower than a maggot.
Please, just let me explain.
There's a reason why--
[AINS]
Silence!
Do not compound
your transgressions
with obvious lies.
What if we were given
permission to be here?
[AINS]
That's impossible.
Who could have given you
permission, other than myself?
I assure you, it happened.
[AINS]
You're bluffing. Buying time.
Making a fool of me.
But, fine. I'll entertain
your little story.
Since you are so
confident, tell me.
Who gave you
permission to be here?
It could only be one person.
Surely you must know him.
[AINS]
"Person?"
Or rather, monster,
and a giant one at that.
I only spoke to him
for a moment,
so I'm afraid he didn't
give me his name.
[AINS]
A giant, you say?
Can you elaborate?
What did he look like?
His body was real shiny.
[AINS]
Shiny, huh?
[AINS] All right then.
And what did he say to you?
One thing first.
I want you to promise
we can leave here in peace.
[AINS] If what you claim
is true and you really were
granted entrance by
a comrade of mine,
then yes,
I shall allow you to
leave here unharmed.
[HEKKERAN]
Comrade.
[AINS] What did he say
to you? Every last word.
He said "if you go to the
Great Tomb of Nazarick,
give Ains my regards."
That was the last I saw of him.
[AINS] "Ains"? "Give Ains
my regards," he said?
Uh-huh.
[AINS laughs]
[GROUP gasps]
[AINS] I got my hopes up
for a moment, but if I stop
to think logically, your story
didn't hold up from the start.
[AINS growls]
Scum! All of you!
You lie to me, in my home,
the place that I built
with my comrades!
Dragging your filthy boots
across its sacred grounds!
And then you taunt me
with the false words
of a friend you never met!
An insult to my
memories of them!
I'll kill you!
[AINS yells]
[AINS]
Well, those are my feelings.
But in truth, I can
scarcely blame you.
Your life hangs in
the balance, after all.
I'm sure you would say
anything to survive.
And frankly, if I were to
indulge in this wrath of mine,
it would be selfish.
Albedo! Aura!
As well as any other
Guardians who can hear me.
I order you to cover your ears!
[gasps]
[AINS sighs]
[AINS] Although I'm
standing here right now,
I was opposed to the plan of
luring thieves into Nazarick.
Still, I accepted it because
I value Demiurge's judgement
and he insisted that it was
the best course of action
for us moving forward.
Well, it's fine.
I'm done complaining.
It's time to dispose
of you vermin!
[SHALLTEAR squeals]
--[SHALLTEAR] Hey! Cocytus!
--[AINS] Listen up!
[AINS] You can stop
covering your ears now!
[HEKKERAN gasps]
[AINS]
Let's proceed, shall we?
If you won't attack,
then I will!
[AINS yells]
Martial Art! Twin Blade Strike!
Magic Arrow!
Lesser Dexterity!
[AINS]
Child's play.
He can nullify it?
He's too fast.
[AINS grunts]
Try this one!
[AINS]
Mm?
Now, Flash!
Here goes Lesser Strength!
[HEKKERAN] I won't miss again!
Twin Blade Strike!
[AINS] Melee combat has its
charm, but it's not very showy.
Also, for all my strength,
I find myself at a disadvantage
against a party with good
coordination like yours.
From now on, we're
going to play my game.
[AINS]
Come at me. If you dare!
He's a magic caster?
He can't be!
The guy's strong enough
with a sword, isn't he?
I hope that doesn't mean
he's even stronger with magic.
He's not. I just checked.
He must be trying
to trick us somehow.
[AINS] Hm. And where do you
get that impression?
I'm not sensing any
magic power from you at all.
[AINS]
Oh, you used detection magic.
My apologies. Try again.
[gasps, wretches]
[AINS]
I know I'm not exactly handsome,
but vomiting at the sight
of me is a bit rude.
[IMINA]
What did he just do?
Everyone, run away!
If we fight him, we'll all die!
I've never seen power
like this before!
It's impossible! Impossible!
[ARCHE sobs]
This is a nightmare!
We're not dead yet!
Quick, help her!
[ROBERDYCK]
Lion's Heart.
I mean it. He can
crush us like insects.
I felt it myself.
When he took off that
ring a moment ago,
my knees nearly
gave out beneath me.
[HEKKERAN] Yeah, but I
checked out the surroundings
and we can't run away.
[AINS]
Don't want to fight?
Perhaps this will motivate you.
Touch of Undeath.
What kind of magic is that?
I don't know. Never
heard of it before!
Stay away!
[AINS]
You first, then.
[IMINA gasps]
[HEKKERAN grunts]
[yells]
He's right behind you!
Fight me , you son of a bitch!
Here goes!
Martial Art! Limit Breaker!
Physical Boost!
Dull Pain! Iron Fist!
Twin Blade Strike at full power!
[gasps]
[HEKKERAN]
Blades don't work!
He has some kind of resistance!
[AINS]
Nonsense.
You're giving yourself
far too much credit.
The truth of the matter
is that attacks
from weaklings like you
aren't strong enough
to even scratch me.
That goes for the rest
of your friends, too.
That can't be true.
This is a trick!
Keep thinking!
His power, what is its source?
Why did he change his combat
strategy all of a sudden?
He must have a
weakness somewhere!
We'll find it!
[AINS]
You think I'm deceiving you?
How hurtful. Paralysis.
[screams]
[HEKKERAN gags, sighs]
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
Run away.
[AINS] All it took was
a simple Paralysis spell
and he's down for the count.
I guess Touch of Undeath
may have been a bit overkill.
[IMINA]
You idiot!
[AINS]
Hm?
[IMINA]
I'm useless in this fight
and he went after me first.
You should've run away
while you had the chance!
Now look what happened!
[AINS] He risked his own
life to protect you.
The man deserves
a little respect.
I know that already!
Hekkeran's a great leader,
a better one than I deserve!
But he's still an idiot.
Just like you!
You both lost your cool
and made a huge mistake!
[AINS]
What are you talking about?
Take that spell off of him.
If we don't return to our
camp within a set time,
the strongest man in the world
will storm this place
looking for us.
[AINS]
Lying again?
[ARCHE]
It's not a lie!
Our ally is the
adventurer, Momon.
He's Adamantite class.
[AINS]
Oh, Momon.
Right. The truth is, he and I...
Well, never mind.
Let's just say that you won't
be able to depend on him.
Sorry.
[gasps]
[AINS]
That said, shall we continue?
[ROBERDYCK]
Arche, get ready to run.
[ARCHE gasps]
If you cast "Fly," at least
you'll have a chance to escape.
We'll buy you time, though,
I'm afraid it may only
be a few seconds.
[AINS]
What an amusing turn of events.
Yes, by all means,
leave your allies behind.
See what happens.
[growls]
[ROBERDYCK]
Take this. We'll survive.
Just go! Your sisters
still need you!
We don't have time to
stand around and argue!
Leave us here and we'll
figure something out!
[ARCHE]
I can't!
Listen to Imina.
We'll defeat Ains
and follow you soon.
We're not so weak.
When we're done,
you can buy us all
a round of drinks.
Have faith in us.
If you don't come back,
I'll never forgive you.
Fly.
[AINS] You may be filthy
thieves, but you seem
to look out for
your own at least.
[ROBERDYCK]
She is our comrade, after all.
[IMINA]
That's right.
If your friends were in danger,
wouldn't you do the same
to protect them?
[AINS]
That I would.
"Greater love hath
no man than this,
that a man lay down his
life for his friends."
Ah, was that the gospel
of Mark or John?
We'll take responsibility
for our crimes,
but if your comrades
taught you any compassion,
then honor our sacrifice
and spare our friend's life.
That's all we ask.
[AINS] Liars such as
yourself deserve no mercy,
but I'm feeling sentimental,
so I shall grant
the girl a kindness.
Shalltear!
[AINS] I want you to teach that
girl the meaning of despair.
Punish her by striking
terror into her heart.
Let her come to realize
that she has no hope
of ever returning home.
Then, kill her mercifully,
so that she does not
suffer any more.
[SHALLTEAR]
As you wish, Lord Ains.
A splendid plan!
[ROBERDYCK]
You monster!
You order her killed,
then have the audacity
to call it "mercy?"
[AINS]
I assure you.
For those who dare to
march into Nazarick,
death is not a punishment, but
a release from true suffering.
As you'll soon see.
[gasps]
Don't give up on me!
Of course not!
[yells]
They're not coming.
It's just me now.
--Why did I go? Why?
--[BATS clicking]
[gasps]
I think that's enough
hide and seek.
[AINS]
Futile, but good effort.
[AINS] Aura, take these
two to the Large Hole.
Goshokukochuuo says he's
running out of nesting room.
[AURA] Uh-- If it's
all right, Lord Ains.
Might I ask Mare
to do it instead?
He'll do a fine job.
[AINS]
It's all the same to me.
Very well, my lord.
I'm sure he'll be delighted.
[ROBERDYCK]
I would ask you one question.
If death is a mercy
then what manner of fate
awaits me here?
[AINS] Hm. I would like to
experiment on the nature
of your power as a
religious magic caster.
For example, if I altered
your memory to replace
the god you worship
with another,
would your power still function?
If so, then what is
the value of your faith?
And what is the purpose
of knowing that?
[AINS] If you think
I'm trying to confirm
the existence of God, I assure
you, it's nothing so trite.
My only goal is to find
new sources of power
to strengthen myself
and my allies.
To strengthen my nation.
I don't believe that
I am the only chosen one
in this world, so I dare
not rest on my laurels.
[ARCHE grunts]
[ARCHE]
Is this a barrier?
[SHALLTEAR]
More like a wall.
[ARCHE grunts]
[SHALLTEAR] It seems you've yet
to understand your situation.
What you see before you
is the sixth floor
of the Great Tomb of Nazarick.
In other words, we're
underground right now.
[ARCHE]
Underground?
[SHALLTEAR] Mm-hm. Knowing
that, will you still run?
Is there any point?
A fair question, but no.
[sighs] I see.
[yells]
Can't blame you for trying,
but we're done here.
[SHALLTEAR]
Well, you're done at least.
I'm just getting
to the good part.
Though I am a bit
disappointed you didn't
break down into tears for me.
Don't worry, I'll be quick.
Why, you'll hardly feel
a thing when I kill you!
You have Lord Ains to thank
for such a generous mercy.
But first...
[ARCHE gasps]
A bit salty, huh?
[whimpers]
[gasps]
[SHALLTEAR cackles]
[AINS]
Impressive work.
Not only did you
subdue the intruders,
you did so with precious
little expenditure.
I feel confident leaving you
in charge of our defense.
You're too kind, my lord.
[ENTOMA with ARCHE'S voice]
Excuse me, Lord Ains.
It is time for Lady Aura
and Lord Mare to depart.
[AINS]
Very well, I'll see them off.
Surely you can't be happy
to hear that thief's
voice again.
[AINS] On the contrary,
I'm quite pleased.
I was the one who
suggested she take
the girl's voice
in the first place.
Which reminds me. Entoma?
[ENTOMA]
Lord?
[AINS] What did you do with
the rest of her body parts?
Did you ensure they
were put to good use?
[ARCHE] To the best of
my ability, Lord Ains.
To summarize, her head
was given to one
of the Silk Hat demons,
and her arms were divided
amongst the Deadman Struggle.
Lord Demiurge requested
her skin, and the rest
of her remains were fed
to Grant's children.
In the end, I believe
every last piece of her
was useful in some way.
[AINS]
Good. I'm pleased to hear it.
It is the responsibility
of the hunter to use
every part of its
prey without waste.
This is how we respect the dead.
I miss Arche.
When was she coming
home again, sis?
Should be real soon.
I can't wait!
[KUUDERIKA]
Me either!
[UREIRIKA] We're going
to live somewhere new
after she comes back, right?
[KUUDERIKA]
I hope so!
[UREIRIKA]
It's so late! Wish she'd hurry.
[KUUDERIKA]
I know, huh?
[UREIRIKA] I'm gonna have
her read me a story!
[KUUDERIKA] And I'm gonna
have her sleep in my bed!
No fair, that's cheating!
What? You're cheating, too!
[BOTH giggle]
It's fine.
'Cause if we all live together,
then we can just take turns!
[KUUDERIKA]
Mm-hm! Together with you.
And together with Arche.
[JIRCNIV]
None of the Workers survived?
[VASSALS gasp]
So soon, too.
--[VASSAL 08D] Then what's next?
--[VASSAL 08C] Don't know.
Very well then. Now
we know the strength
of this Ains Ooal Gown.
Those were high capable teams,
so he's not to be trifled with.
He's a true threat.
[FLUDER] You have grown
to be a fine leader.
I've served under six
generations of emperors,
and even amongst
this kingdom's finest,
your talents are extraordinary.
I have raised you
like my own son
and tried to instill
all of my wisdom,
and yet this time, I--
[JIRCNIV]
Old man?
You must excuse me,
Your Majesty.
I was lost in thought.
Pay me no heed.
No, on the contrary.
Even if you're getting
on in years a bit.
I still value your
every word. Truly.
Thank you for your kindness.
I shall endeavor to be
ever worthy of such favor.
As for the Workers, we need
to clean up the pieces.
Taking the head
of one foolish noble
should settle things nicely.
Was that the idea?
Just as you say, Your Majesty.
And the people in this
room are the only ones
who know the truth of it.
Although, to be safe,
I suppose we--
[rumbling]
What is this?
Are we under attack?
[EMPIRE KNIGHT 08A]
Your Majesty! A dragon!
A dragon has landed
in the inner gardern!
[EMPIRE KNIGHT 08B]
What the hell is going on here?
[VASSAL 08A] It's not from
the Council State, is it?
[VASSAL 08B] Why did the
Royal Air Guard let it through?
[VASSAL 08C] Lord Paradyne,
do you have any clue
what this is about?
Unfortunately, it's not
a dragon I'm familiar with.
But it seems to have dark
elves riding on its back.
[BAZIWOOD]
He's just walking up to them.
I dunno if that's smart.
[EMPIRE KNIGHT 08A]
Your Majesty, please take cover.
They landed on our roof.
Clearly, no place is safe.
[EMPIRE KNIGHT 08A]
Even so--
[AURA]
Everyone, can you hear me?
My name is Aura Bella
Fiora and this is Mare.
Lord Ains Ooal Gown sent us.
[AURA] The Great Tomb
of Nazarick, which Lord Ains
calls his home, was
recently invaded by some
unsavory sorts,
sent by your emperor!
This has put him in a bad mood!
If no one comes to apologize
for this offense,
he will reduce your
country to ash!
[gasps]
And as proof,
we'll start by eliminating
everyone here.
Mare.
'Kay, here we go!
[yelping]
[KNIGHTS screaming]
[VASSALS gasping, murmuring]
[AINS] Emperor Jirkniv
receives my message
and opts wisely to
respond by apologizing
for the Workers'
trespass in person.
Jirkniv is considered a genius
compared to the emperors
who preceeded him.
He wishes to see Nazarick
with his own eyes.
And, perhaps, to win me over.
Before, he sent trespassers,
but now, he comes as a guest.
I'll be sure to
welcome him accordingly.
Chapter 9: "War of Words."
Dance as I tug your strings.