Our war should begin shortly,
if I'm not mistaken?
[gasps]
[BAZIWOOD]
Hey, kid.
His Majesty was
asking you a question.
You still with us?
Uh. Oh! Please excuse me, Lord!
Yes, I believe our
last advisory warning
was sent to Re-Estize
just recently.
I was wondering...
Majesty, why did
you ask for help
from that creepy undead guy?
The Re-Estize forces are
of no real threat to us.
And you told him to use
his most powerful magic,
right off the bat?
Kinda overkill.
You just want him
to put on a show?
Is that it?
[JIRCNIV] Eventually, we'll
need to form an alliance
against Ains Ooal Gown.
But no one will bite
until they understand
how dangerous he is.
Think. Even that dark
elf girl can wipe out
over 100 imperial knights
in the blink of an eye.
From what I've seen
of her master,
that's just the start.
Frankly, if that man killed
3,000 soldiers with one spell,
it wouldn't surprise me.
Three thousand?
I can't imagine!
That's horrifying!
The Demon Gods, or even,
the Thirteen Heroes couldn't
do something like that.
True enough, but I think
we should assume
the worst in this situation.
It does present us with a
unique opportunity, though.
We'll get to see a demonstration
of his power, firsthand.
Then we'll have more of an idea
of how we might defeat him.
If we can't best him
with strength,
we shall do so with ingenuity.
[BOULLOPE] I'm certain they
received the final warning.
The war should've
started already,
but the Empire's
just standing there.
Also, there's still no
word from Prince Barbro?
No, sir.
He should have arrived at
Carne Village yesterday.
I have no idea what
could've happened.
No matter, we'll make do.
We 70,000 soldiers
of the royal army
shall change
formation and march!
Let us be the frontline
and first to deal a blow
against the dogs of the Empire!
Heh!
The Empire only has 60,000
troops, Your Highness.
I think, with our 240,000,
we'll wrap this up
and have them begging
for quarter soon.
[MEN laughing]
Perhaps we should
take this opportunity
to invade the their territory.
[MEN]
Ah!
Well, I have duties to
fulfill back with my unit.
I'll leave the details of this
slaughter to you fine gentlemen.
[MEN laugh]
I'm not certain I share
your confidence exactly,
but it is reassuring.
[RAEVEN]
Still not moving, huh?
In previous years,
they would mount
their attack when the final
warning had been issued.
[GAZEF]
They're waiting for something,
but I don't know what.
Whatever they're planning,
I hope we can settle
this matter quickly.
I noticed you're
wielding the legendary
Razor Edge, "whose enchanted
blade can cut through
armor like butter" they say.
[GAZEF grunts]
[RAEVEN]
Ah, and I see the intent.
By donning the four
treasures of Re-Estize,
you have become a symbol
of the Kingdom, itself.
A living treasure.
I'm not worthy of such praise.
I owe everything to our king,
who bestowed such an honor
on a mere commoner like me.
That's true.
But His Majesty
trusts you completely.
The course of action that
he took with Prince Barbro
is evidence of that.
Huh?
In other words.
His Majesty believes
that this Ains Ooal Gown
you're so wary of must be
every bit as deadly as you say.
Perhaps His Majesty was
selfish in sending
his child away from this battle.
In the past, I certainly
would have resented him
for such a decision.
But I was foolish enough
to aim for the throne then.
I know better now.
Because, I understand
how His Majesty feels.
And frankly, if it were my son,
I wouldn't want him
fighting in a war, either.
Indeed. No surprise.
I hear that you're quite
the doting father.
[laughs] Like any other.
A father, busy with work,
but always promising his son
he'll spend more time
playing with him.
Maybe after this
little war is over.
Though I fear
that Prince Barbro
will fail to appreciate
his father's thoughts.
Feels a bit tragic, doesn't it?
Look there.
Seems they're moving,
at long last.
[KNIGHT 12A whimpering]
[KNIGHTS murmur]
Master Gown.
That's him?
The magic caster who could
bring our land to ruin?
The mighty Ains Ooal Gown?
Listen, sir.
I recommend you call your team
of ex-adventurers quickly.
We need their expertise.
[BORIS]
Marquis Raeven!
Something terrible
is about to happen.
Did you feel it, too?
[SOLDIERS gasp, murmur]
[RAMPOSA gasps]
What now?
I can scarcely
comprehend that power,
let alone hope to defeat it!
I'm going to return to my unit!
Protect the king, Master Gazef--
I fear we must order a retreat!
Indeed.
And I must insist that
we do so immediately.
I concur.
Disgraceful though it may be,
it seems we've no choice.
Marquis Raeven. Good luck.
[RAEVEN]
You as well, Master Gazef.
[AINS]
No response.
[MOMONGA] In Yggdrasil,
players casting super-tier magic
are the first ones targeted.
But no one is stopping me,
they're all just
staring dumbfounded.
I guess that means
there are no Players
in the Kingdom's army.
In that case, acting as
a decoy is pointless.
[AINS]
Yes.
Now the festival of
destruction can begin.
[MOMONGA]
A lot of people are about to die
by my hand, but I feel nothing.
[BOULLOPE]
Forward march, men!
[MOMONGA] All I want is to
see what this magic can do,
and to make Nazarick
even stronger.
[AINS] I make this tribute
to Dark Fertility.
Ia! Shub-Niggurath!
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[BOULLOPE groaning]
[KNIGHTS gasp]
[NIMBLE whimpering]
[AINS] Is something the
matter, Master Nimble?
I was merely stunned
by the power
of your spell just now!
It was terrifyingly effective.
To think, that 70,000 people...
[AINS laughs]
Did I say something wrong?
[AINS] I'm not offended,
if that's your concern.
But you praised the
effectiveness of my spell.
I find that amusing.
Why is that?
[AINS] Because the magic I cast
was only a means to an end.
A prelude to the carnage
you are about to behold.
Uh.
[AINS]
After a tribute is offered
to the goddess of
dark fertility,
she responds by sending
some of her Thousand Young.
They're rather adorable
kids, as you'll see.
[KNIGHTS gasp]
[SOLDIERS murmur]
[NIMBLE whimpers]
[AINS] And now I show you
the face of despair.
[AINS laughs] Splendid!
Looks like a new record!
I believe I may be
the first to summon
five of them at once.
A pity all the sacrifices that
made this moment possible
can't share it with me.
Uhm, congratulations
on your summoning.
I'd expect nothing
less, my lord.
[AINS]
Why thank you, Mare.
Congratulations, Your Grace.
[AINS]
How kind of you!
[KNIGHTS whimpering]
[AINS] I know our objective
was to show off my strength
to other countries,
and I do believe we have
accomplished that, but still,
it seems like a waste
to send away the children
before they can play.
Especially after you
set a new record.
[AINS] Hm... Yes, let's
have a little fun.
Hunt them down, little goats.
Do your wicked mother proud.
[THOUSAND YOUNG bleating]
[AINS]
But there are three, or rather,
four people who
you must not kill.
Run wild, but spare
them your wrath.
[bleeting]
There's no way.
This can't be real.
[SOLDIER 12B]
Huh?
Come on. It's a trick--
it has to be!
--[THOUSAND YOUNG bleeting]
--[SOLDIERS screaming]
Everyone, ready your spears!
Did you hear what
I said, damn it?
Don't just stand there!
Ready your spears!
[BLUMRUSH screams]
[RAEVEN]
Retreat! Run for your lives!
Marquis Raeven, you need
to get out of here, too!
I'm ready! Follow my lead!
I knew he was dangerous,
but this is insane!
Never mind us,
someone this powerful
could tear the
whole world apart!
[RAEVEN]
No, I can't think like that.
We'll come up with something.
We have to protect our
future from this monster.
I think it's chasing
us! Be careful!
[BORIS]
Damn it. We gotta take a stand.
Everyone, cast your spells!
[GORAN]
Reinforce Armor!
[LUNDQVIST]
All right, Lesser Strength!
Marquis. We'll do what we can!
Hopefully we'll draw it away!
[LOCKMEYER] I don't know how
this'll go, so keep running
and don't look back, Marquis!
Thank you all!
[BORIS]
Now. To battle!
--[GORAN, LOCKMEYER yell]
--[LUNDQVIST] Fireball!
[BORIS]
Impenetrable Fortress!
--[crashing]
--[THOUSAND YOUNG bleating]
[KNIGHT 12A]
This is nothing but a slaughter.
[AINS]
Let's end this farce.
[gasps]
[KNIGHTS gasp]
[AINS]
Now, applaud.
[KNIGHTS, NIMBLE gasp]
[AINS]
My power is sublime!
Should it not be celebrated?
[clapping]
[giggles]
[nervous laughter]
[THOUSAND YOUNG bleeting]
[KNIGHTS laughing]
[KNIGHT 12A]
Hurrah! Hail the Sorcerer King!
[KNIGHTS screaming]
Don't run away!
[AINS] If I recall,
in our original plan,
you were to launch your
attack after I cast my spell.
And yet it seems that your
troops have fled instead.
Don't worry,
I'm not blaming you.
After all, I would feel bad
for the emperor if his men
leapt into the fray and
got trampled to death
by the creatures I summoned.
So, this time, I'll be happy
to do your part as well.
Mare, please guard
the camp in my absence.
[MARE]
Yes! Of course, Lord Ains!
Leave everything to me!
Hey. Haven't you killed
enough people today?
Are you a man or demon?
[AINS]
Make no mistake. I am undead.
That is all.
[NIMBLE whimpers]
[AINS] All that's left is
to do a little cleanup.
Fortunately, it seems
I've found my target.
[VICE-CHIEF 12A] Your Majesty!
We have to get out of here!
[RAMPOSA] I will stay.
You may retreat without me.
But, Your Majesty, why?
My Lord! So few guards.
Where did they all go?
Probably ran away in terror
with everyone else.
There is nothing you can
do here, Your Majesty!
Let's return to E-Rantel.
Today's a lost cause.
Plan for next time!
Let the Chief Warrior
hold them at bay!
If there's truly
nothing I'm able
to accomplish here, then...
...I'll go. What's
the next step?
Those creatures seem
to chase down horses.
You there! Take the
king on your back!
Sir!
And the rest of you?
We'll try to make
a distraction.
I'll lead our horses in
the opposite direction
of your retreat.
I'll be a decoy as well.
Although, I don't know if those
monsters have eyes or not.
If they do, my armor
makes a fine target.
[sighs] In that case, I guess
I'd better stick around, too.
I'm grateful.
Do your best.
Of course.
I can't believe
it's come to this.
Please, return to
E-Rantel safely, men.
I will grant you
any reward you wish.
I'll look forward to it!
I thank you, but my
life has been saved
by Princess Renner.
I ask no reward.
I don't need
anything for myself,
but I'm friends
with this nice kid.
He seems to get along
great with your daughter,
so it'd make my day if
those two could get married.
Uh--!
[RAMPOSA laughs]
A rather audacious
request, I must admit!
Please tell him
you're just joking!
Well, no promises,
but perhaps we can begin
by granting this friend
of yours a noble title.
I give you my support.
That settles it,
better make it out
of this alive, little noble!
I'm counting on you!
Your Majesty.
Let us meet again in E-Rantel.
[RAMPOSA]
Hm.
--[SOLDIERS screaming]
--[THOUSAND YOUNG bleeting]
[GAZEF] Beyond this point
lies His Majesty's camp.
I won't let you pass!
[sighs]
Martial Art: Sense Weakness.
[GAZEF] There's nothing.
Possibility Sense!
Come, monster! I have no fear!
[gasps]
Now!
[yells]
[panting]
[GAZEF screams]
[GAZEF grunts]
[yells]
[GAZEF] The beast doesn't find
me worthy of its attention.
Huh?
Master Ains Ooal Gown.
Huh. So that's it.
Seems you're not human.
[CLIMB]
Lord Stronoff!
Glad to see you're safe.
Someone is up there.
Guess I must be a
magnet for monsters.
This'll be the third impossibly
powerful being I've met.
No matter the enemy,
I will not run away!
[AINS]
You look well, Master Stronoff.
[GAZEF]
Indeed I am.
As for you. I'm
not quite certain.
If you've lost your humanity
since the last time we met,
I offer you my
sympathies instead.
[AINS laughs] I assure you,
I haven't changed a bit.
[AINS]
Still, it's been far too long.
I feel the weight of
that now. Tell me.
What was your purpose in
reaching out to me here?
Surely you don't hope
simply to reminisce
in the midst of a battle.
[AINS]
You get straight to the point.
And as I don't like
beating around the bush,
I shall return the favor.
I want you to join me.
[gasps]
[BOTH gasp]
[AINS]
If you become my subordinate,
I shall grant you this.
[ALL gasp]
[AINS]
Do you understand now?
[GAZEF]
You've stopped them.
And easily, no less.
[AINS]
Consider it a momentary pause.
Your answer will determine
what happens next.
That is to say, if you
refuse my generous offer,
I will give a different
order to these children.
And I expect you can guess
what that order might be.
[AINS]
What do you say, Gazef Stronoff?
Will you come to my side or not?
I refuse. I am the
sword of the king.
I owe His Majesty too much.
I cannot turn my back on him.
[AINS] Even if many lives
will be lost as a result
of your decision?
Surely you understand the
weight of what you're saying.
You're a man who risked his
life to save Carne Village.
Now, when countless other
lives hang in the balance,
you will allow them to be lost?
[AINS] I never took you
for such a fool. Pity.
[AINS]
What is this?
Forgive me.
I know I'm still indebted
to you, Master Gown.
But I must challenge
you to a duel!
[AINS] Seventy thousand lives
are snuffed out in an instant,
and the beasts I summoned will
crush countless more underfoot.
In times such as these,
I wonder if this undead vessel
has stripped me of all mercy.
But I still respect strength,
and I see it in the eyes
of the warrior before me.
Gazef Stronoff,
I accept your request.
Chapter 13: "Player vs Player."
This world, and
every person in it,
will soon know of my strength!