[ARCHE] The more I look at it,
the stranger it seems.
I can't tell what era
these ruins are from
or what culture built them.
That's a good sign.
It means we're that
much more likely
to run into something
interesting inside.
Think that's guaranteed.
Although there's also the chance
that a terrifying
undead lurks in there.
[ARCHE]
Still. I'm a bit excited.
[IMINA]
Same here.
I wanna know why
this tomb was built.
And what kinda person
got buried inside it.
Yeah.
There's nothin'
quite as exciting
as exploring a total unknown.
What would excite me is
if it were full of money.
[GROUP laughs]
--[HEKKERAN] Yeah, me, too!
--[ARCHE] What?
Well, I'm sure this'll
be our best job yet.
[HEKKERAN] Once the four
teams have signaled
that they're in position,
we'll all move in at once.
Each team will explore one
of the smaller mausoleums.
After that, we'll all meet up
at the larger one in the center.
[GRINGHAM]
Good.
[ERYA]
Simple enough.
[PARPATRA]
That works for me.
[THIEF 7A] That was one
short-lived invisibility spell.
It lasted as long
as needed. Now come.
No traps as of yet.
Continual Light.
And Continual Light.
[GRINGHAM] Hm. I've not
seen such a crest before.
Have any of you?
[CASTER 7A]
No, don't think I have.
[PRIEST 7A] Doesn't look
like a Re-Estize sigil.
[WARRIOR 7A]
Oh, by the way, Gringham.
You can start acting normal now.
There's nobody else around here.
True.
Man, that crap's exhausting!
I feel so stupid, talking like
some kind of white knight.
[CASTER 7A]
The other groups bought it,
but you can relax
now that it's just us.
Nah, I'd better keep it up.
If I let myself slip
out of character now,
I'll have a hell of a time
getting back into it later.
I always talk like that
when I'm on the job.
Tricks people into thinking
I'm more talented than I am
and worth more money.
[GROUP laughs]
Now then. Into the fray, men.
[GROUP]
Right!
[THIEF 7A] This banner is
woven from precious metals.
Amazing.
I bet this would fetch a
pretty good price on its own.
[THIEF 7A]
Should we go ahead and take it?
[GRINGHAM] It's far too unwieldy
to carry through the ruin,
and besides, we haven't
fully explored this room yet.
[BOTH grunting]
[GROUP gasps]
[GROUP panting]
Hey, Gringham. What kept you?
My apologies for
making you wait.
We didn't actually decide
on a rendezvous time,
so you're good.
Tell me.
Was there treasure in the
mausoleum your team explored?
It was chock full of it.
We're excited. Parpatra
says his was, too.
I'm glad to hear that.
It seems this ruin has
riches enough for all.
[HEKKERAN] Doesn't look like
we'll have any trouble
accessing the
lower floors, but...
This place reeks of death.
Yeah, that's my worry.
It's a stench I remember from
my time on the Katze Plains.
I have a proposal
for the other teams.
[WORKERS]
Huh?
I and the rest of
Green Leaf will go back out
and look for any
secret entrances.
I think it's fairly
likely there are
other ways to get inside.
The elder makes a valid point.
If providence wills it,
he may find a safe
passage that leads
directly to the
center of the tomb.
But I must say.
My team will be taking
a loss, so in exchange,
we'd like to have a share
of any treasure you find.
Let's see... About ten percent
from each team should do.
And if there's a route
to the lower levels,
how about my team takes
the first crack at it?
We have no qualms with that.
Neither do we.
I myself half a minor objection.
Sharing ten percent of my
treasure isn't a problem. But--
Great! I'm glad everyone agrees.
Good luck down there!
And be careful.
Oftentimes, the most valuable
treasures are booby trapped,
so feel free to
leave them for us!
Tch.
All right then. I guess
we'd better get to it.
[ARCHE]
Rober.
Do you sense any undead
magic from these corpses?
No. They're not a threat.
Good.
This ruin is like none
I've ever seen before.
I wouldn't be
surprised if the place
was more than 600 years old.
If it's that ancient,
we'll find more than gold.
Can we move this along please?
I don't know about the rest
of you, but personally,
I would like to hunt
down some monsters.
[WORKERS gasp]
C'mon, is somebody pullin'
our legs, or what?
[THIEF 7A]
These are the tomb's defenders?
[IMINA] They might as well have
sent a swarm of bugs at us.
[WORKERS laugh]
[WARRIOR 7A]
This is too easy!
We could fight these
things blindfolded.
[THIEF 7A]
All right then.
I guess that rules out
the idea that this place
is ruled by some great monster.
Or if it is, then the thing
must be a complete idiot.
I've never felt this
underestimated before.
These foes are beneath me.
Fine. Then I shall strike first.
[grunts]
We must not become careless.
Steel yourselves
for the possibility
of a powerful undead foe.
And push forward with
the greatest care.
[AINS]
So. They've made their entrance.
[LEADER 7A] That they have.
They may be Workers,
but they're our comrades
till the job is finished.
I hope they all
make it back safely.
Do you think they'll
run into any trouble?
[AINS]
Does death count as trouble?
Huh?
[AINS]
Oh, uh!
[AINS clears throat]
[AINS] I mean, they should have
resolve in the face of death.
These ruins are a new discovery.
Who knows what lurks within?
It's important to balance
hope with pragmatism.
Oh, I see what you mean now.
Thank you for the
sage advice, sir.
[AINS]
Of course.
Now if you're taking the
first watch, I should rest.
Right! Take all the
time you'd like.
[AINS sighs]
All right, Nabe. No, Narberal.
I shall return to Nazarick now.
I'll send Pandora's
Actor in my place.
I trust you to handle
any problems here.
Thank you, my lord.
I won't fail.
[AINS]
Then, I leave it to you.
[NABE]
Right.
Greetings, my lord.
Welcome home.
[AINS]
It's good to be back.
The intruders should
be entering now,
just as we planned.
Are we fully prepared
to welcome them?
Everything is ready, sire.
I'm certain that
our guests will enjoy
what we have in store for them.
[AINS]
Very good.
I look forward to seeing
your hospitality at work.
You can watch from here.
[AINS]
Hm. And so it begins.
Don't even let one of
them leave unscathed.
[ALBEDO]
As you say, my lord.
For the crime of entering
the Supreme Being's abode,
these imbecilic thieves
must be punished
in the harshest of ways.
Also, before they're
all torn to bits.
Have you chosen which
group you'd like to use
as rodents for the
testing of the sword?
[AINS]
Ah, yes.
[HEKKERAN]
Whelp.
This job's goin' a lot
smoother than expected.
That first encounter
was almost too easy.
Shh.
[HEKKERAN]
That's a bother.
[ARCHE] Two of those
skeletons are mages.
They can use first tier magic.
If we don't take them out fast,
they could be a problem.
But skeletons are tough
to snipe with arrows.
Let me handle this.
Now. Turn Undead!
Nice work. You took 'em all out!
[THIEF 7B]
I feel like we're gonna lose out
on a lot of treasure.
We're getting priority
on tomorrow's foray,
so it won't be a
complete loss for us.
Besides, if you ask me,
it's dangerous
to be the first group to
explore an unknown dungeon.
Best to let someone
else take that risk.
That's a very
pragmatic approach.
[PARPATRA]
Hm?
Well then. So much for that.
What do you think
we should do now?
They don't outnumber us.
Maybe we can manage.
Gotta say, with the
shape this tomb's in,
these maids have
really been slacking.
[GUARDIANS growl]
[PRIEST 7B, WARRIOR 7B gasp]
[ENTOMA]
We should kill them.
They need to die.
It isn't enough
to simply kill them.
We should do it in the most
painful way imaginable.
[YURI]
Yes. Yes.
We planned to kill them
from the start, remember?
Though I am pleased to see
everyone so motivated.
[WORKERS gasp]
[YURI]
Gentlemen.
I'm afraid circumstances
prevent us from being able
to butcher you with
our own hands.
Which is a shame.
Allow me to introduce the foe
you'll be facing in our stead.
Nazarick Old Guard,
arise. To war.
Say what?
A pincer attack?
No. It looks like they truly
plan to stay out of it.
[armor clinking]
[gasps]
[THIEF 7B]
Magic weapons.
Isn't this an honor.
To think you'd
summon so many mighty
undead just for us.
Tough break.
It would appear that
we've encountered
the most powerful
beings in the ruin.
Seems I'm right.
Which means that, unfortunately,
my efforts to avoid danger
have put us in the thick of it.
So why don't we just run for it?
Look at those things.
They'll tear us apart.
We lost any chance of escape
as soon as they pincered
us. Push forward.
Yes, I suppose that is
the best chance you have.
Best of luck, gentlemen.
All right. Please begin.
[swords clanging]
Wow, they're bad.
I thought they would
put up more of a fight.
Lord Cocytus thought
the same thing.
[PARPATRA grunts]
[ENTOMA] I'd hoped we'd get
to see at least a bit of a show
before they died.
[WARRIOR 7B grunts, groans]
[LUPISREGINA]
Uh-oh.
He's a goner. No dodgin' that.
[WARRIOR 7B groans]
[YURI]
You'd best get to work, Priest.
Can't you see that your warrior
needs healing right now?
[CZ]
He's already dead.
Which means their party's
frontline has been destroyed.
[groans]
What the hell is this?
[THIEF 7A groans]
[ENTOMA] Oh. Their thief
has gone down, too.
Seems like the
battle's been decided.
[yells]
[ENTOMA]
He looks delicious.
Restrain yourself.
Remember, our instructions
are to take the ones
who are no longer able
to fight as prisoners.
[PARPATRA screams]
Right. Heal whoever's
still breathing
and send them to
the torture chamber.
As for the dead:
I'll include them in
my report to Lord Ains.
There's no way we can
beat those monsters!
God's blessings can only
protect us from so much evil!
Have we gained any ground yet?
No! They're still
right on our tails!
[THIEF 7A]
Damn it!
Hey! I found a door!
[WARRIOR 7A]
This piece of shit tomb!
[BOTH gasp]
[GRINGHAM]
Anyone here?
[THIEF 7A]
Yeah, I am.
[GRINGHAM]
Where are the others?
[THIEF 7A] What the hell
happened back there?
[GRINGHAM]
We got teleported.
C'mon, let's ditch this
place while we can.
[crunch]
[KYOUHUKOU] That window
of opportunity has passed.
[GRINGHAM]
Who's there?
[KYOUHUKOU]
I am known as Kyouhukou.
It is I who guards this area
by decree of Lord Ains.
[THIEF 7A, GRINGHAM gasp]
What the hell are you?
[KYOUHUKOU] Hm. Shall I
introduce myself once again?
No, please forgive me.
I misspoke.
I'll be blunt. I'd
like to make a deal.
I-If you would but release
us from this place,
we'd be willing to give you
anything you ask
for in exchange.
[KYOUHUKOU]
Oh. A trade.
I am most thankful,
but if we're being blunt
then I should confess
my reservations.
"Thankful"?
[KYOUHUKOU] The problem
is that what I desire
is already in my possession,
and I quite doubt
that you can offer me
something better.
[BOTH gasp]
[KYOUHUKOU] I am thankful for
you because my family and I
have grown weary of cannibalism,
and your arrival here
means that, for the
first time in many years,
we can enjoy a civilized meal.
[yelps]
[KYOUHUKOU] It's a shame that
there aren't more of you.
Please do your best
to nourish my family.
[BOTH yell]
No, damn it, no!
I don't wanna die here!
[KYOUHUKOU]
You're a spirited one.
Lend my children your strength.
[WARRIOR 7A grunts]
[clicking]
[NEURONIST]
Awake already, are you?
[WARRIOR 7A yelps]
[NEURONIST] I'd ask if you slept
well, but what's the point?
[NEURONIST] You seem to be
stiffening up everywhere
except the part
that counts, dear.
[WARRIOR 7A yelping]
[NEURONIST]
Anyway.
As you might've noticed,
you've been captured.
This is the Great
Tomb of Nazarick.
The illustrious home of the last
of the 41 Supreme
Beings. Lord Momo--!
Oh, um. I meant
to say, Lord Ains.
But let me tell you,
he's a great leader
and a wonderful man.
[WARRIOR 7A whimpers]
He's just incredible!
Say, you can keep
a secret, can't you?
All right, then
between you and me,
if he were to call me to
his bed, I wouldn't mind
letting him be the first
to taste this cookie.
That stupid brat Shalltear,
and the piss-ugly
overseer Albedo
are both aiming
for his heart, too.
But I'm much more attractive
than either of them.
You agree, don't you, darling?
[WARRIOR 7A whimpers]
Oh, yeah. Right.
My name is Neuronist and I'm
the Great Tomb of Nazarick's
Special Intelligence Collector.
Though, there are those
who call me a torturer.
[WARRIOR 7A whimpers]
The supreme one who brought me
into existence suffered from
an excruciating condition
known as "kidney stones."
So to honor their suffering,
I thought we might start
with this little toy of mine.
[WARRIOR 7A yelping, whimpering]
[NEURONIST] We'll be spending
a great deal of time together.
If you're crying about
this little thing,
then wait till you
see what's next.
[WARRIOR 7A screams]
Why have you stopped walking?
Move on, or else.
[gasps] I'm sorry, but...
I hear something.
--Interesting.
--[swords clanging]
Finally come to
face me you have,
foolish intruder.
And you are?
[HAMUSUKE] Someone instructed
to greet the intruders
with tail and fang, I am.
To see if my training has
been successful this is.
But slaying you I doubt
will prove much.
What kind of a
magic beast is that?
My apologies, Master,
but I've never seen
such a creature.
Tch. You worthless imbecile.
Now then.
Told I've been,
it's not a problem
if I should slay you
in this duel of ours.
So to the death
this fight will be!
Oh.
The others you see have
come only to observe
and score our battle.
So rest assured that interfere
in our fight they shall not.
Ill-equipped for battle
those elves seem.
Shall I wait while they prepare?
[ERYA]
There's no need for that.
I'll face you alone.
Then to meet your god, prepare.
Hamusuke I am called.
Declare your name
as well, warrior.
I see no point in
telling a beast my name.
[HAMUSUKE]
If to give your name you refuse,
then erase you from
memory I shall.
For die here you will
as a nameless fool!
Now. Martial Art Shukuchi Kai.
[ERYA yells]
You damn rodent!
Fine. Ability boost.
And then Greater Ability Boost!
Huh.
Keep at a distance until
I understand the abilities
of my opponent,
I think they said.
But also, as a warrior,
I was told to fight,
and warriors must be brave.
Close combat it shall be.
Strike me down
if you can, human.
Don't underestimate me!
So close!
[ERYA grunts]
--[HAMUSUKE] As expected.
--[ERYA] You idiots!
[HAMUSUKE]
A match for my tail you are not.
Do something!
Cast a healing spell!
Don't just stand there,
get on with it!
Can't you see I'm injured?
Middle Cure Wounds.
[ERYA] Not enough. Cast
enhancement magic on me.
All of you!
There's a massive difference
in physical strength
between humans and magic beasts.
But with this, I can
bridge the gap.
Mind I would not if you
chose to attack as a team,
for a better challenge
you might then provide.
Far from your grasp is victory,
but should you fight
together, we could have
a praise-worthy battle.
[growls] Shukuchi Kai!
[HAMUSUKE]
Slashing Strike!
[grunts]
[screams]
You! Heal me! Do it!
[ALL giggle]
Why? Are you--?
Find enjoyment in the
suffering of others I do not,
so end this now I shall.
--Huh?
--[HAMSUKE] Bye.
Master Zaryusu, did
you see what I did?
Indeed, I saw.
Slashing Strike. Good.
You used a martial art.
Most excited to hear that I am,
and continue to train until I
become Warrior Hamusuke I shall.
[ZARYUSU]
Hm?
What are they doing?
Strange it seems.
Is that how elves
mourn their dead?
[ZARYUSU]
Don't know.
[IMINA]
How'd we get here?
I guess that was a magic
trap we stepped on?
[HEKKERAN]
All I remember is the ground
lighting up beneath our feet.
This place seems different
from the others.
[ARCHE]
I know of a similar building.
The Empire's colosseum.
Yeah. This is pretty similar.
So would that lead to the arena?
[HEKKERAN]
Looks right.
And if we were teleported here,
that can only mean one thing.
What?
We were teleported
to the surface.
Good. Then let's escape with
Fly Magic while we ca--
[AURA yells]
Our challengers tonight
are a band of four
foolish human adventurers
that dared to infiltrate
the Great Tomb of Nazarick!
And against them,
we have the Supreme One.
He's the illustrious overlord
of the Great Tomb of Nazarick!
The King of Death itself.
His name is Lord Ains Ooal Gown!
[AINS] Every second these
thieves draw breath,
they defile Nazarick
with their mortal taint.
I should erase their every atom,
but when life gives
you test subjects,
you find ways to experiment.
Wait. Thier leader, Hekkeran,
claims he recieved
permission to come here.
Did he speak with
one of my comrads?
No... That's impossible.
Chapter 8: "A Handful of Hope."
You will atone for your
arrogance with death!