[BARBRO]
How dare they march me out
to the middle of
nowhere like this!
Carne Village is scarcely
worthy of my attention.
But I won't let them
rob me of my glory.
I'll wrap things up
in short order,
then march straight to the
Katze Plains for battle.
Wait. Maybe this
place isn't useless!
I might be able
to use the villagers
to negotiate with Gown.
If he backs out of the war,
the Empire will retreat
without so much as a skirmish.
This is my chance to prove
that I'm worthy of the throne.
That I'm the only choice!
No, even better.
I'll draft the
villagers as soldiers
and march them
before Gown himself.
If he ends up killing them,
he'll show what
kind of man he is.
All his support will be lost.
A splendid plan. Just perfect.
[AGU]
Hello, Chief, we've returned.
[GOBLIN 11A]
Greetings, Chief.
[GOBLIN 11B]
Greetings.
Yeah, greetings to
you, too. Nice work.
So, what are you up
to right now, Chief?
I'm preparing for winter.
Making sure we have enough
supplies for everyone.
You have the firewood
under control.
Tell us if you need
anything else. 'Kay, Chief?
[forced laughter]
Oh, hello, Chief!
Keep up the good work, Chief!
[forced laughter]
Well, if it isn't the chief!
Have you spoken to the
new villagers joining us?
[ENRI] If one more person
calls me "Chief,"
I am going to scream!
We need to check on
the dried grass.
Try to hang in there till
we're done with our inventory.
Considering that so many
people think I can crush
a barghest with my bare hands,
I suppose the least I can do
is take stock of our
supplies properly.
But, Chief, you...
I mean, Enri--
You're pretty tough!
[KAIJALI]
What?!
[OGRES gasp]
Wow, so it is true!
You are strong enough
to crush a barghest,
just like everyone says!
[gasps]
Chief so strong.
Chief so great.
I knew you could do it, sis!
[sighs]
[laughs] After that,
the ogres all wanted
to arm-wrestle you, too.
Okay, enough.
Ah-- I'm sorry.
[gasps] You smell really
nice! What is that?
Just something I cooked up.
I'm glad you like it, though.
I haven't made much
cologne before.
Wow!
It'll sell for a
fortune in the city!
I mean, maybe, but that's
not really why I...
What's this pose?
You wanna wrestle?
Here we go!
[yelps]
[JUGEM]
Bad news, Miss Enri!
[BOTH gasp]
[JUGEM]
Oh, sorry for the interruption.
It's an emergency.
[AINS] The royal army
came to Carne Village?
[LUPISREGINA]
Yes, my lord.
The first prince, Barbro,
suddenly appeared at their gates
with 5,000 soldiers.
[AINS]
To what end?
[LUPISREGINA] He claims he's
here to question villagers
who have come into
contact with you.
But I believe his true intention
is to hold the village hostage
in hopes you'll surrender
before the battle
with the Empire starts.
[AINS] The royal army
may not be strong,
but 5,000 soldiers
is overwhelming.
Carne's goblins and ogres
won't be enough
to turn them away.
How are they responding to this?
It seems that the
villagers are just trying
to buy time right now.
[CHENEKO] I have come as
a vassal of the first prince
of Re-Estize, Barbro Andrean
Ield Ryle Vaiself!
We have a matter of great
importance to discuss!
Open this gate immediately!
[ENRI] I'm sorry, but there's
cow dung everywhere inside here.
We can't possibly let a prince
visit until we clean it up!
[CHENEKO]
What?!
Enri is holding them
off at the gate.
In the meantime, the goblins
and ogres are hiding.
Oh, no! I've got
dung on my hands!
I'll wash them and come back!
[AINS] She seems to be
handling this well.
[MOMONGA] I wonder if
Demiurge planned for this?
I'll just have
to act like I knew
it would happen or something.
Either way, the village
itself isn't a big deal.
I just don't want
anyone finding out
about our potion experiments.
[AINS] Lupisregina, continue
to monitor the village
and tell me every last detail.
There are four people
you must protect.
You know who they are.
Of course, my lord.
[CHENEKO] We have heard word
that you're connected
to the rebel forces
of Ains Ooal Gown!
If you will not cooperate,
that must be the case!
If these accusations are false,
prove it and open the gate!
[BARBRO]
Hah.
Enough of this. They've given
us all the proof we need.
Burn this place to the ground!
Please, my lord!
If we're forced to kill
this many civilians,
surely our morale
will suffer for it.
Tch. Fine. Then
strike the tower.
Burn it down and they'll
get the message.
Now no one will die.
That good enough?
--[VILLAGERS gasp]
--Oh, no.
[VILLAGER 11B]
Why?
[VILLAGER 11C]
Are they going to kill us?
This village wouldn't
have survived
if it wasn't for
Lord Gown's help.
I'm not going to betray him,
no matter the cost.
This prince is our enemy!
I'll fight 'em if I have to!
[VILLAGER 11B]
Count me in!
If they wanna start
somethin' with us,
we'll hit 'em right back!
[ENRI]
Nemu.
[JUGEM] Miss Enri.
Gotta make a call on this.
[ENRI]
All right, everyone.
We have enough
villagers gathered here.
Let's take a vote
while we still can.
[VILLAGERS grunt]
Who thinks we should meet
the prince's demands?
In that case, even though
it may cost us our lives,
who thinks we should resist
the kingdom's forces?
[VILLAGERS]
Yeah!
Seems you all agree.
We will prepare for battle.
Let us pay back our debt
to Lord Ains Ooal Gown!
All right. We need
a plan, quick.
[JUGEM]
Your courage is admirable.
But let's be frank.
Us old men are the only ones
who should be
risking their lives.
We'd like to have the women
and children evacuate,
but it's too late for that.
The prince's forces have already
gathered at the back gate.
We'll make it work.
Just open up the front gate,
and launch a quick,
concentrated attack.
They might see through
that plan, but as long
as our strike is strong enough,
they'll have no choice
but to gather their forces.
If you have any objections,
make 'em quick.
[ENRI]
I think it's settled, then.
One question.
Where will they go?
Into the Great Forest of Tob.
Agu and Miss Britta
know the area,
so they can lead
everyone to safety.
They'll be able to
survive for some time.
'Least till the soldiers leave.
I accept.
Be quick. But be careful, too.
And listen up.
Nphirea and Miss Enri
are going with you.
[ENRI, NPHIREA gasp]
No, I have to stay and--
You be safe! We still need you!
We'll be all right.
Come back soon!
Watch over those kids for us.
[VILLAGER 11H]
You got this, Chief.
[VILLAGER 11I]
Don't worry.
[VILLAGER 11J]
It's not over.
[VILLAGER 11K]
Stay strong.
Enri. Listen. This isn't
our battle to fight.
Our job will be to rebuild.
It's not right.
And remember. We still
have one last hope.
We've stayed loyal to Lord Gown.
He may save us in time.
He has already.
You still have that summoning
horn he gave you a while back?
That summons goblins?
Yeah. Right here.
[JUGEM] It may be tempting,
but don't use it now.
You'll just lead them
to slaughter. Don't worry.
If we die here, take that horn,
and summon new goblins
to help rebuild the village.
Will they be okay?
I understand.
[BARBRO]
I don't have much time.
How will I know who to question?
Damn it. I should have
brought an inquisitor.
Torture would settle
this quickly.
They're finally letting us in?
[CHENEKO]
All units, forward!
[roars]
[KNIGHTS yell]
[BARBRO]
What?
[roars]
[yelps] Hold on.
Why is an ogre here?
--[OGRE 04A grunting]
--[KNIGHTS screaming]
[yelps]
Draw swords!
[KNIGHTS screaming]
Shouldn't we be firing arrows?
What's going on?
We'd like to, my lord, but I
fear we'd hit our own men.
Bah!
What's this?
That was a surprise,
but no need to worry.
That's likely all they've got.
Surely Marquis Boullope's
elite soldiers
can handle five ogres.
That we can, my lord.
One thing troubles me.
Ogres are monsters--
they lack intelligence.
But this is clearly a
tactic on someone's part.
They may have a cunning
leader in there.
Agreed.
Better to proceed with caution
until we find out more.
What?
Look at that!
They've trampled
all over our flag!
This isn't a village--
it's an enemy stronghold!
Burn it to the ground!
Gather those we sent
to the back gate!
Unleash a volley of
fire over these walls!
We'll hunt down the villagers
and kill every last one!
[ENRI]
Good. It looks like
Jugem's diversion was a success.
All of the soldiers have
moved to the front gate.
[AGU]
Let's go!
Ready? Just follow my lead.
[ENRI] Right. 'Kay, guys,
it's time to go.
They're here.
Come on, hurry!
We just have to make
it to the forest!
I'll try to buy you some time!
You'll be killed!
[NPHIREA]
Just trust me!
[ENRI]
I can't let this happen.
Goblins. Please, help us.
[horn blows]
She used it.
Huh?
[LUPISREGINA]
[AINS]
Huh?!
[JUGEM yells]
[KNIGHT 11B grunts]
[JUGEM]
Goblin's Single Blow!
[KNIGHTS groan]
[groans]
[roars]
[panting]
[JUGEM] Miss Enri must be
safe in the forest by now.
We've hardly put a dent in them.
[horn blows]
They sent for help?
But what army would aid them?
[gasps]
[JUGEM] Reinforcements are here!
Retreat to the back!
[BOTH panting]
[GOBLIN STRATEGIST 11A]
Well, hello, gentleman.
You have done well to protect
General Enri thus far,
but henceforth, you may entrust
this little operation to me,
the great goblin strategist!
I vow to you, not a single life
will be lost on my watch!
Anything less would
be an embarrassment!
Complete victory shall be mine!
[MOMONGA]
What the hell is going on?
There's gotta be over
1,000 of these guys!
This is bonkers!
Um, my lord?
That horn I heard before
the goblins showed up
was a magic item, wasn't it?
[AINS] The horn. Ah, yes,
of course, the horn.
It was so insignificant to me,
I forgot I had given it
to that human woman as a gift.
[gasps]
[MOMONGA] That's the only
logical explanation, I guess.
But the Horn of
the Goblin General
isn't supposed
to be that badass.
It's just some garbage
item that summons
a few low-level goblins.
Not like, a whole army.
[BARBRO]
What the hell is happening?
[KNIGHT 11A]
My lord. We must retreat!
You think we can't
handle some goblins?
Stop wasting time and fight!
Listen. This isn't
just a handful of troops
we're dealing with.
It's an overwhelming force.
Please give the
order to withdraw!
Use your head for once!
If this army's as
strong as you say,
what if they invade E-Rantel?
It would be our fault!
Then we shall do
our best, my lord.
All right, take the
V formation! Ready?
Attack!
[KNIGHTS yell]
[GOBLIN HIC LEADER 11A] We are
the Goblin Heavy Infantry Corps.
In the name of the
Honorable General Enri,
we shall crush your paltry
forces beneath our boots!
[KNIGHTS yell]
[GOBLIN PKS LEADER 11A] We are
the Goblin Paladin-Knight Squad!
In the name of the
Honorable General Enri,
we shall fell the wicked
and prove our valor!
[GOBLIN BRC LEADER 11A] We are
the Goblin Beast Rider Corps!
In the name of the Honorable
General Enri, we race forth!
[KNIGHTS groaning]
[GOBLIN LC LEADER 11A] We are
the Goblin Lowgbowman Corps!
In the name of the
Honorable General Enri,
we shall rain vengeance
from the skies above!
[KNIGHTS scream]
[GOBLIN MSC LEADER 11A] We are
the Goblin Magic Support Corps!
In the name of the
Honorable General Enri,
we shall strengthen our
allies, weaken our foes
and sow destruction with
every measure of our guile!
[GOBLIN MBS LEADER 11A]
We are the Goblin Magic
Bombardment Squad!
In the name of the
Honorable General Enri,
we shall wield the flames
of chaos and prove our worth
as the strongest force
in the Goblin Army!
[KNIGHTS scream]
[JUGEM]
Miss Enri!
--[CONA] There you are!
--Hey! I'm so glad you're safe!
[GOBLIN STRATEGIST 11A]
Honorable General Enri,
the valiant troops you see
before you are yours to command.
Five thousand of the finest
soldiers of every variety.
Suitable, for a leader
of your prowess.
My lord, give the word.
Let's retreat.
[ASSASSIN SQUAD 11A]
Not a chance.
We are the Goblin
Assassin Squad
who walk among the shadows.
In the name of the
Honorable General Enri,
we shall seize
your final breath.
[REDCAP GOBLIN 11A] I am one
of the Thirteen Redcaps,
the goblin elite guard
tasked with defending
the Honorable General Enri.
Though it appears my services
aren't needed here.
Protect His Majesty!
Pull back immediately!
Too late, punk.
[BARBRO, CHENEKO gasp]
[MOMONGA]
Hm.
The first horn summoned goblins
just like it did in Yggdrasil,
so I don't see why
changing worlds would make
this horn act differently.
Everything else has
been the same.
Maybe the item always
had a hidden effect
and I just didn't know about it.
It's called the Horn
of the Goblin General.
That could be a clue.
Like, it normally
summons weak goblins,
but if you meet
certain conditions,
it summons a whole army?
Might have to do with the
skills of the summoner.
[MARE]
Um, Lord Ains?
[AINS]
Hm?
Did you give her that magic horn
because you knew
this would happen?
And you knew the villagers would
be loyal to you, even then?
[AINS]
Oh, uh, yeah.
[MARE]
I... I'm sorry.
I'm no good at putting
it into words,
but you really are
amazing, Lord Ains!
[AINS]
Well, of course.
[panting]
[REDCAP GOBLIN 11A]
Why did we let him escape?
[ASSASSIN SQUAD 11A]
It was an order
from the Goblin Strategist.
He said that General Enri won't
have any room for negotiation
if we take the prince's
head in our first battle.
[REDCAP GOBLIN 11A]
Hmph. Fair enough, I guess.
[BARBRO] It's absurd!
How could we lose to goblins?
Damn it! Damn it! Damn it!
Hey there, buddy!
You're looking glum.
You wanna play with me?
Who goes there?
You sure are testy.
I'm Lupisregina.
One of the maids
that serves Lord Ains.
What did you say?
That was pretty rough, huh?
Summoning those goblins
out of the blue like that
is practically cheating.
I gotta admit, even I
let out a little yelp
when I saw that go down.
Who knew Enny had
it in her, huh?
[laughs]
All right, that's enough.
What do you want from me?
C'mon, Mister Grumpy,
I think you know
the answer to that
one without asking.
Huh?
I came here to murder
you, of course.
Yeah right. And how do
you intend to do that?
Do you realize who
you're dealing with?
I'm Prince Barbro Andrean
Ield Ryle Vaiself!
Yeah.
I wouldn't be here
if you were some guy.
But even a prince
is still just a human.
Hold on.
[LUPISREGINA]
I'm afraid Lord Ains Ooal Gown
doesn't have a place
for you in his plans.
And since you're less
than garbage to him,
that means you're
better off dead.
You get it?
[gasps] You mean it.
You're planning to kill me!
Ooh! I like that face!
This might not be
so boring after all!
Maybe I was a little
harsh before--
I've changed my opinion of you!
Oh, yeah?
[LUPISREGINA]
So, I was thinking.
If you're gonna
fight to the death,
then I gotta pick out the right
enemies for the job, y'know?
Are you ready? Ta-dah!
You probably hate
goblins right now,
so I had Lord Ains summon
some choice ones for you.
[yelps]
[swords clanging]
[KNIGHTS screaming]
[CHENEKO screams]
[BARBRO yelps]
My powers don't measure
up to Solution's,
but beggars can't be choosers
and I do have my charms.
[chuckles]
[AINS]
In response to Jirniv's request,
I release a mighty spell
to signal the battle's start.
Super tier magic:
Tribute to Dark Fertility!
Ia! Shub-Niggurath!
I wonder what kind of result
it will yield in this world.
There are those who see
the magic circles around me
and know enough to flee,
but they are far too late.
Chapter 12: "Massacre."
Now, let us begin!