Me... humanity's savior...?
Nonsense...! I have chosen the
path of the mad scientist...!
I vie for chaos
and destruction!
Dude, you're freaking me out...
We shall be recommencing
Operation Wyrd
without further delay.
'Kay, but you know Mr. Braun's
gonna lose his shit, right?
Then let him!
Wait! I told you before...
this is too risky.
"Too risky"?
This afternoon you
couldn't wait to begin.
When did you say?
You already sent it, didn't you?
Yes... The experiment
has indeed taken place...
I've no doubt that
the events of the past
have been altered
in certain details.
No kiddin'?
You mean we really made the
jump to another world-line?
Near as I can tell.
This would also explain why
your memories of earlier today
differ so significantly
from mine.
Oh yeah. You mean that
whole lottery-number-thing
you were talking
about before?
That's the one.
So... Then why are
you the only one
who remembers us
sending that D-mail?
According to Titor...
I might have an
unprecedented skill...
The only way I'll know is
for us to change the past
enough to shift
the world-line again.
What's the skill?
When a world-line splits off,
and memories
which are inconsistent
with the new reality get
erased... mine are not.
I call it "Reading Steiner."
Check it!
Well, nothing in the
sent messages folder...
But it does look like a D-mail
hit the inbox five days ago!
So it worked.
Whaddya think? Did I win?!
If you had won,
you wouldn't be asking me.
We sent a D-mail five
days into the past,
telling Daru the
position of the cards
in his match with Faris.
So he should've won.
Hey, Mayuri...
This might sound like
kind of a dumb question,
but when I went up against
Faris the other day, did I...
Sorry, what was that...? Kicked
my butt...? Yeah... 'Course...
Sure, thanks... You, too.
Daru got the message all right,
but it didn't seem
to change the past.
It should've,
though, shouldn't it?
He knew where the cards were.
I guess the
world-line doesn't jump
for every little incidental
thing that runs interference.
I feel like we need to find a
more objective way of analyzing
whether or not we've gone
through that kind of shift.
Really?
Wait a sec!
That doesn't mean I agree
with what you're doing!
I'm just saying...! Hey...
Why do you think you've been
able to retain your memories
after a jump, while all of
ours are getting overwritten?
You already know the
answer--it's my Reading Steiner!
If you're genuinely
curious as to how it works,
perhaps you should be the
one to send out our next D-mail.
I don't want to.
Still worried about
a time paradox?
Changing the past, just...
just feels... unfair.
For better or for worse,
the eighteen years
I've lived up until now
have made me who I am today.
There may have been bad times,
but they've been mine--just
as much as the good times.
In other words...
You're a scientist... A mad one!
What?! Where did
you get that?!
You've no qualms about
sitting back and letting others
hurl themselves headlong into
the unknown, obviously...
That is rather the attitude
that sets mad scientists apart.
Whatever!
That said, in all seriousness--
Anyway... if we want to
perfect the D-mail system,
we're going to have to--
We're going to have to
conduct more experim--
Moeka?
Shut up!
Can I?
You are a tenacious one,
Shining Finger...
Home again,
home again--jiggity jig! Haha!
Those crepes hit the spot, yeah?
Yeah.
Do you ever
actually go to class?
I'm awaiting my compatriot.
Hey! What'd I tell you
about spookin' my kid?
I didn't do the least
little thing to her!
Come on, Nae...
Let's go inside before
this loser freaks you out
any more than he already has.
Good morning!
Yay! It's Mayuri!
Too-too-roo!
Brought you something!
Wow, my favorite!
And Okarin gets one, too!
Whaaaaaaasup!
Oh, good morning, Suzuha!
Good morning, part-time girl!
Well? Spill it! How'd it
go with Mr. You-know-who?
What do you mean?
Time-travel, goofball...!
D'y'ever get a hold
of Titor or what?
Uhh, he and I did
end up corresponding,
in fact, but I'm not exactly
sure if I believe him anymore.
What the in hell...?!
Why would you doubt him?!
Um... Explain to me why
you're so worked up about it?
I think somebody just outed
herself as a Titor fangirl.
Yeah, as if!
Too-too-roo!
It's Kurisu everyone!
Good morning, you guys.
So, she gave ya the ol'
stink-eye yet again, huh?
What's her problem, anyway?
People fighting
really gets me down.
Uh... Hey, I'm sure it's
just a misunderstanding.
Thank you.
Nothing too complicated,
Shining Finger.
Make it simple enough
that we'll know whether
or not the past
has been changed.
"I got this cell
phone four days ago,
but I don't like it...
So I want to tell the
past me not to purchase it."
I get it...
If you see Moeka and she's
got a different cell phone,
you'll that know it worked...
You did tell her
to stay "simple."
Indeed...! Take your
places, everyone!
Ready!
All right! Initialize the
Phone Wave (Real Name--!
Wow, it's perfect...!
Why the melon?
I just... wanted to
apologize to you for getting
the numbers all mixed up when
I bought that ticket for you...
Do you think you can forgive me?
Oh... Yeah... Course
I can... No problem.
And... my callow apprentice...
owning up to this slight misstep
has bolstered your powers.
Heh. Well thanks,
I'll get out of your hair now.
Oh, are you leaving already?
I figured you were in the
middle of something, so...
Anyway, good luck with it!
You wanna come back sometime
and try on my cosplay?
I don't know about that...
I'm not really into that
sort of thing, you know?
Aw, I understand.
That's too bad, though.
You'd look super-cute in them...
I'll see you later!
'Kay...! Later, Ruka!
Kid's a gem.
I don't have to ask
this time... I felt it...
How...? How'd it change...?
All this kinda blows my
mind sometimes, ya know?...
Something's different,
but...? Wait...!
Where's Shining Finger?!
She was just here!
What are you on about?
Just ignore him.
That's what I do.
Did Ruka...
happen to stop by...?
My Ruka...? Nope.
Why do you ask?
What about Moeka, then?!
Has she been here today?
I don't think so...
Do I know her?
Kiryuu Moeka! The one
I call Shining Finger.
Okarin... I don't
know who you mean!
Who is this chick?
It's not just Mayuri, Okabe...
I've never heard of her, either.
Oh God...!
We sent another
D-mail, didn't we!
We did...? What's
different this time?
Did we alter the
past so thoroughly
that Moeka's very
existence was negated......?!
Impossible...!
I still have her
earlier messages,
so at least she was alive as
of then, but what about now...?
She messaged me right back.
That's very much in character...
So she's still here...
Let me get this straight...
The girl that you were asking
about... Shining Finger...
She sent herself a D-mail...
and changed the past in that...
she never made her
initial visit to the lab?
In so many words, yes.
So... your ability
to remember conflicting
memories after a jump...
Your "Reading Steiner,"
I think you called it?
That name is ridiculous,
by the way, I mean...
Come on--it's
just word-salad.
Thank you so much for
that unsolicited opinion
from the peanut gallery.
I have to ask you something,
and I'm hoping you don't
take it the wrong way.
You're not, like,
pulling our leg, are you?
Okay, I'm ready!
We can talk about this later.
See you tomorrow!
I know what I remember.
But...Could I be...?
Seriously, how do the boys sleep
in there? Buncha savages...
I guess that's what hackers
and mad scientists do!
Hey, know what?!
We should get together
some night and have
ourselves a big sleepover!
No guys, and you
got yourself a deal...
Better yet... why don't we
have one in my hotel room.
We can do that?!
Why not?
Oh, I can't wait--it's
gonna be so fun!
Hey, Ruka! Too-too-roo!
Whoa, really?
Blasphemy!
You made the pilgrimage here
without your sacred blade?!
I... I thought that...
You stop being a grumpy-butt!
Ruka's my extra-special guest,
so I want everyone
here to behave!
You are still okay with me
dressing you up... right?!
Uh, sure... I guess...?!
Of course you are,
my darling Ruka!
It's too late to
turn back now...!
Y'know, maybe this isn't...!
Now... let's get you out
of those clothes, yeah?
You're gonna be so pretty!
Oh, oh! Watch the hands!
Watch the hands!
I'll put it on, I swear!
Just let me dress myself, okay?
I can't do this
if you're looking!
You'll need help!
No, wait! Please
don't take that off!
I'm begging you...!
It's like yuri
times infinity...
That stammering blossom
is Mars, not Venus.
Yeah, but ya know...?
That's even hotter!
Ta-da!
He's Kirari from
the game Rai-Net!
It fits perfectly!
You look adorable!
I've never been so
embarrassed before...
Don't be embarrassed...!
You're the prettiest boy
these goofballs have ever seen!
Balls or not, man...
I would so hit that...!
What do you think, Okarin?
Let's see here...
Code Red...!
The Organization's attacking me
with mind-blowingly
adorable cosplay!
Curves and colors eating
through my corpus callosum!
Uh... are you going to
be all right, Kyouma...?
Oh give it a rest,
you big drama queen.
Hey, Kurisu's here!
Too-too-roo!
Behold the pervert, undressing
the poor dear with her eyes...
No I'm not!
This moment gets
better and better...!
Well, what do you think...?
Looks pretty cute, huh!
Yeah...! I could never pull
off an outfit like that!
Well... Um, I usually
wear more clothing...
Okay, are you ready for
the next cosplay outfit?
Mayuri...!
I have a confession...!
I didn't actually come
here to play dress up...
I stopped by to ask
the members of the Future Gadget
Lab for a really big favor!
Wait, so you're not really
here to play dress up with me?
I tried to tell
you on the phone,
but you sounded so excited, I
couldn't bear to disappoint you.
I guess I did kinda
get carried away...
So, what pray
tell is this favor?
Okay... Don't be mad.
There's someone in the past
I've gotta send a really
important text message to!
Huh?!
Sorry...
Remember how I brought you
that watermelon yesterday,
to make up for the ticket...?
We sent another
D-mail, didn't we!
Hold up... What's
different this time?
Did we alter the
past so thoroughly
that Moeka's very
existence was negated...?!
Impossible...!
I didn't mean to eavesdrop!
I was about to knock right
when you said that stuff...!
It's okay...
Why don't you just tell us what
message you wanna send back.
Okay... I, uh...
I think I was
meant to be a girl!
Huh?!
For as far back
as I can remember,
I've always felt awkward
about the way I look...
I don't think it'd be a problem
if the parts of me you see...
y'know... matched
the parts you can't.
Wait... What...?
Time out for a sec...
Why is the cute girl talking
about not liking how she looks?
Hmph. Alas, my poor
assistant--allow me
to shatter that candy-coated
bubble of naiveté around you.
Naiveté?
Our dear Rukako isn't a
female... Quite the opposite.
How dumb d'you
think I am? Come on.
Oh, it's the truth...
I believe any scientist worth
her salt would be conducting
some field research
right about now.
Someone this cute
can't possibly be a boy...
Sorry... I'll just--
How ya doin' there?
Look, this isn't a joke!
I'm totally serious
about wanting to be a girl!
Please let me do it!
Here's the thing...
I fail to see how
sending a text message
into the past can change
a Y chromosome into an X.
I've already got
an idea, though,
I heard that if you eat a lot
of meat when you're pregnant,
you end up having
a baby boy...
And if you eat lots of veggies,
you have a girl instead.
Maybe if she knew that...
So... you want to
message your mom
and have her
double-down on the salad?
Yeah...If you'll let me.
So be it... Your request
shall be summarily granted.
Oh Kyouma, thank you so much!
This is so exciting!
I hope it works!
Me too!
As hot as it would be,
I don't know if changing
someone's gender is smart.
Some old wives' tale
about food isn't going
to change whatever
gender he happens to be.
He's right, Daru.
There's absolutely no
evidence to support it.
If sending a D-mail
makes him feel better,
what's the harm in
letting him try it?
All right... Forswear your
life among the mundanes
and consent to become our
newest lab member--Double-O Six!
Yes!
Now... let us
begin without delay!
You're seventeen years old
this year, if I'm not mistaken?
Oh... Uh-huh!
As I thought...
That means you came
into the world in 1993...
Why's it matter
when Ruka was born?
And someone remind
me, what year it was
when cell phones started
to be popular in Japan?
Looks like it was '96,
and we're talking
bare-bones telephony.
Messaging wasn't 'til later.
So what we're saying
is that we shouldn't
just assume anything.
Rukako's mother might
not have had a cell phone
in the early '90s when
she was pregnant with him.
Wait, you mean he won't
be able to send a D-mail?
Oh no...
We could tweak the
Phone Wave to do mind control...
Yeah, I see you using that
power for good, Harem Boy.
Oh yeah......!
I can totally picture it...
Faris at my command...
I've got it.
My brilliance is
frightening even to me!
If you've got
something, just spill it.
If cell phones
are off the menu,
let's try sending
it to a pager!
Let see here...
"Pagers were miniature
receivers to which
one could send signals
through the telephone.
They enjoyed widespread
use in the 1990s,
but were antiquated by the
advent of cellular phones."
Pagers, huh?
So that's what
they looked like...!
Quaint technology...
I take it you're familiar
with it, Christina?
That's still not my name--
and I'm just
reading what's here.
Well, I hope you're ready
for your first assignment,
zero-zero-six!
It pertains to your wish!
Ascertain if your
mother had a pager,
and then ascertain the
number of said pager!
I'm on it!
Good news, Kyouma!
She totally had one!
Still remembered
the number, too!
Excellent work, Double-O Six!
Have you decided what
you're going to say?
Yes!
I hope she already knows she's
expecting when she gets this...
I figured information stored
in a pager was limited,
so the message shouldn't
be too complicated...
I think it was a good idea
to keep the message
as short as we can...
Now we just need to
convert it into digits.
Monkey wrench.
Conversion's burning through
more numbers than
I thought it would.
Huh?
Looks like we can only
transmit enough numbers
for 24 characters at a time,
which means we're
four over the limit.
Fine... Observe...
Turning it into
numbers, we get...
Are you ready to send
your D-mail, Ruka?
Yes!
You're positive this
is a good idea, huh?
It's perfectly safe.
Different... but
I remember everything...!
Does that mean...?!
I don't know anyone
who would go out in that.
Sure! Why not?
It's comfy enough.
In fact, I think you'd look
really cute in this, Ruka!
Who, me...? Uh...
Dude or not?
Oh, real nice...! Keep your
eyes on the face, Mister!
Uh... I was doing research.
Now what...?
I can't ask if Ruka's a girl...
The poor thing would
probably faint...
I guess... the text didn't work.
Dude...?! Stop...
Why are you such a
creeper all of a sudden,
with the weird smile?
You're grossing me out.
Yeah, bad Okarin!
That skeeziness from
Daru wouldn't surprise me,
but I expect better from you!
Hey, who're you calling skeezy?!
I'm just a
red-blooded young man!
Call it what you want!
I've seen your hard drive!
Oooooh, yeah.
Something... Something
has changed from before.
We're on a
different world-line.
The question is... what?