You're on Earth...
Seventy-million years
ago, give or take.
Mayuri?
You were brought here
by a time machine,
but you probably won't
remember that yet.
I don't understand...
It's crazy, you know.
I've chased after you through
so many mixed-up world lines
that I don't even remember how
far back it was I lost count.
Please, I...
'Course, the "you"
I followed here is just one of
a whole bunch of
different versions.
You're the original, though.
That much I know.
The Mayuri that found you
is just one of a
bunch of versions, too.
But I sure I'm the
original version of me.
I learned that the hard way.
The important thing is,
I have a feeling we're
both going to die here.
The good news is, the stuff
that makes us who we are
will pass down to the versions
of us seventy-million
years from now.
So... It's okay.
Okarin!
Kurisu's mostly finished
setting everything up
and she says you
should come take a look.
Even awesome-er, though,
my cosplay is almost done. Huh?
Earth to Okarin...
Hey, hold this a
second for me, will you?
Like that, yeah.
Like this?
Yep-yep...
Nice and stretched out.
Try to think like
you're a clothesline.
Awww. What a pretty ribbon.
I know right? Ah!
You should totally try this on!
It's okay, I have other
outfits I can compete in.
It is kind of cute...
Got the cosplay bug?
Please. Don't even go there...
Like I'd ever traipse
around in public wearing...
Finished!
Yay...! Mayushii takes
home the gold! I beat you...
This was a race...?
Oh dear...
You cleaned our clock, huh?
But we're not far behind.
Matter of fact, we're done...
We've got our leaper, folks.
Oh, wow...
Definitely looks like something
an evil genius' bunker
would have in the armory, huh?
Hmmm... So it works kinda
like the Phone Wave...
Except it comes with a headset?
It may not be a
masterpiece of design...
But this puppy is
able to transport
a person's memory to
any point in the past...
Particularly now that
we've got access to the LHC.
And what does the
LHC have to do with it?
Well... To put it simply,
it's acting as a compressor.
See, our machine more or
less reads the neural patterns
that comprise one's memory and
converts them into terabytes.
Three-point-two-four
terabytes, to be exact.
The Phone Wave can only
move thirty-six bytes
of data at a time, so terabytes
are totally out of bounds.
With the LHC, however, we can
generate a black hole that'll
defrag the neural data to a
size the Phone Wave can manage.
Basically, once the
data is compressed
we can send it just
like we would a D-mail.
So it's like putting your
old quilt into a vacuum bag
before shovin' it
into the closet?
Well, not exactly,
but close enough, I guess...
You've got the basic idea.
Anyway, we send it to
your phone in the past
like we do with D-mail...
It goes through...
then gets unraveled by the
broad spectrum signal...
And the neural
patterns comprising
your present state of
memory are overlaid
onto the neural pattern
unique to your past self.
We can only send data back in
48 hour increments, though...
Push that window any
further and the copy signal
will find nothing to match up
with in your past brain...
The developmental gap between
the two versions of
yourself will be too great.
And then there's the
other glaring issue...
What?
Unlike our D-mail experiments,
this isn't something we can
run without a test subject.
Specifically a human being.
Believe me, I really wish
that weren't the case,
but it's the only surefire way
to verify memory transference.
Proxies just aren't enough.
Wait, so you're saying
one of us has to volunteer
to be the first chimpanzee
in space...? Yeah, not it.
Okabe...? Give me your
opinion on all of this.
I want to know what you
think about it, not Hououin.
Daru.
Yo-yo.
Am I to understand that
you've yet to puzzle out
how we're connected to SERN?
Uh-huh. But we can
be reasonably sure
they haven't
sniffed out our trail.
I'm inclined to agree
with Daru's assessment...
If they were wise to us,
we'd have seen some
indication of it by now.
If we've really found
a way to conquer time...
I have to know.
Um... Maybe we can send a
gel-nana back to the past
to see if it changes into how
it was when I bought it...?
Sweetie, think about
what you're asking, okay...?
Bananas don't have memories.
And ours aren't worth risking.
I think it fair to say we're
out of our depth here...
I vote we, go public
with our findings
and let someone else
sort out the ethics.
Um... I second that.
If that's what everyone wants,
that's what we'll go with.
That's what I want!
I second it, too!
Do we know what kind of
pizza Hashida's ordered?
No idea.
Well, it's not a big deal.
Salad pretty much goes
with whatever. Let's see...
Hold on.
Now what?
You are making a salad...?
That's right... Grapefruit
salad, to be precise.
Then why in the name
of all that's holy
am I looking at ground beef?
C'mon, you don't like
to mix it up a little?
Grapefruit's like the
equivalent of black anyway:
it goes with everything.
Excuse me...
Have you eaten one?
Oh and since when did you
become such a connoisseur?
Look, they have these things
called "prepared" salads
designed to save a busy woman
like you the trouble of--
No thanks, those are
basically boxes of foliage...
You've seriously got to
loosen up and learn how
to make your own fun
sometime. I swear...
Ah! Cilantro! Perfection!
It's me... It appears
the sleeper agent
is going in for a checkmate...
Backup requested to keep
her out of the kitchen--
I can't believe
you're joking around.
I gotta say,
I didn't think you'd be
taking this all so well.
I'm kinda surprised.
I thought you'd be
climbing the walls
to leap through time once
we figured out the mechanics.
That bother you?
It is what it is.
Ever read any Martin
Heidegger... or, try to?
He thought that
humans were... temporal.
Just so you know,
I'm glad we're turning this
thing over to someone else...
Really... I mean, I think all
of us are, but me in particular.
Is it okay if we invite
Ruka and Faris to the party,
'cause we kinda already did...
When did this become a party?
This sounds weird...
But I get the impression
Mayuri's more
relieved than all of us.
Maybe you're right...
I think out of the group,
she had the keenest
focus on the big picture.
We couldn't see the
forest for the trees.
When do we go public?
The sooner the better,
as far as I'm concerned.
Just give me a heads up;
I want to let my mom know.
Oh, hell...
Dad's going to find out
I made a time machine...
I don't even want to imagine
the kind of temper
tantrum he's gonna pitch...
It'll probably be a big enough
deal that we'll have to put
Aomori on the back-burner,
for a while at least.
I wouldn't worry too much.
As a lab member you
are entitled to
my protection in times
of impending crisis.
Oh, sure I am...
Provided I submit to
your evil will, right?
Provided that you
keep in contact.
Uh... Well, I... I mean, sure...
Oh...! I... Uh...
Uh... Wait, hold on you...
Owww...! What are you doing?!
You're so out of character
all of a sudden I'm forced
to conclude you've been stricken
with some kind of fever!
What...?
Look, I... it's not like
I was serious or anything;
I was just trying to avoid
an awkward situation
by being courteous.
Liar, liar. Pants on fire.
What is your problem?!
How the hell do you
expect a girl to act
when you keep
flying off the handle?
And then you babble about
"keeping in touch"
like you care...
Stop throwing me curve balls!
I'm sorry, which
one of us is supposed
to be flying off the handle...?
Don't make this more
complicated than it is already:
you're my assistant.
Yeah, well there aren't
any words for what you are.
Really? 'Cause you just
hurled a slew of them at me!
You know what: I thought
of one. "Impossible."
Hey. Soup's on.
Thanks for waiting on us...
You have the
manners of a baboon.
What? It was gettin' cold.
Thanks for the variety,
too, I might add.
There's like a plethora
of good stuff here, dude.
Moron...!
All these are
smothered in olives,
which you damn-well
know I hate!
This is exactly why I'm
making a salad fit for royalty.
Give me a sec to toss
all the bits together
and we'll have proper noms.
You let her buy produce?!
I tried to stop her but
she wouldn't see reason!
Damn it...!
Are you or are you not
pledged to protect our lives?!
Don't lose heart,
my harried friend;
we're not done-for just yet...
Bear in mind,
that apple pie fiasco may
well have been an accident...
The rare miss of a gourmand...
Damn it, I forgot
to buy radishes.
Oh well, shallots'll do.
Okay... If I survive this meal,
I'm going to write a
letter of apology
to everyone I've ever wronged.
I'm back!
We're saved...!
Mayuri, darling, could you
scuttle into the kitchen--
Hey! Wassup, party people...?
Wowza, something in here
smells almost edible...
Did you guys
order some pizza...?
'Cause I got
chicken tenders, too.
I thought you knew better
than to have her around.
I happen to be a
member of this lab...
Mind telling us all
what you're doing here?
I'm a lab member, too.
What's happening?
Not a clue.
Did something happen between
the two of you or what?
No... She just gets off leveling
bizarre accusations at me.
Like when she tells people
I'm a mole for SERN...
Well, hey, if the
shoe fits... Wear it.
What gives you the right
to say crap like that...?
You don't even know me!
Keep talkin'... I know
how this goes down.
Huh?
Trust me, lady...
The things you're gonna do...
Let's just say I'm more of
an expert on what's behind
that whole innocent girl
act than you are.
Wait, what?
I'm sorry,
could you maybe run that by
me again without the crazy?
Uh-oh... Um, are you
guys gonna fight?
Clear a path, please,
oh sensitive one...
It appears the only remedy
for this awkward turn
of events is the intercession
of yours truly... Zombie!
I did not raise an
insolent back-biter!
You didn't raise
me at all, freak.
If you intend to don the
appellation "mad scientist"
you must first subdue your--
I have no intention
of donning it.
Part-timer!
You can point your finger
at me all you want, Okabe.
If you ignore my warning,
whatever happens is on you.
I... don't deny
that you warned me...
Hey! Slow down a sec!
Don't tell me you
actually believed her?!
No, it's a bit more
complicated than that...
You sure didn't
put up an argument.
Well... Perhaps I...
Perhaps you shoulda
just let 'em cat fight.
If you'd like to jump in
and help me contain this,
you are more than welcome!
Umm...
Please stop fighting...
I really hate it
when people fight.
Sweetie...
Uh... For the record,
I'm not a big fan of it myself.
I don't mean to be all weird...
I just want you to like each
other as much as I like you.
Weigh your options carefully.
Is it a virus or a link...?
Only one way to know.
But of course, therein
lies your dilemma:
the cost of knowing may
be forfeiture of dessert!
Like I always say:
when in doubt come at the
enemy with all you've got!
Like a rat in a trap...!
Three viruses and
no help in sight...
Not one to be
ungracious in triumph,
however, admit defeat now
and I'll concede the cherry.
Poor gal's got no game face.
You're being mean
to her, Okarin.
Law of the jungle, my dear.
Hate not the player;
hate the game.
In case you were wondering,
the cards nesting up there
in the corner are all links.
He's not half as shrewd a player
as he'd like everyone to
believe, take my word for it.
Ah-ha!
Whoa. Good call.
Damn you...!
Underlings are not supposed
to rat-out their superiors!
Oh, nice move, chief...
Calling someone "underling"
totally inspires loyalty.
Yeah, well...
I'm not thanking you.
Oh, here.
Let me give you a hand.
Aww... Thanks,
sweetie--actually,
if you wouldn't mind
making tea, that'd be great.
You're a doll.
You know I really
can't thank you enough.
What for?
Trying as hard as you are
to get along with
Suzuha for my sake, silly.
Ah... Well, sad
to say I don't think
it's done a whole lot of good...
But what you said earlier about
us all liking each other...
We spend so much time
in this room together
it'd be a waste if
we couldn't get along.
Okabe and I had a
little chat about you.
About how while we're
all fumbling in the dark,
you always seem to
see what's important.
You know, Okabe never
seems more himself
than when the topic of
conversation is you...
It's kinda creepy to
tell you the truth.
Aww, that's not a very
nice thing to say you know.
Sorry! It's the truth.
I call shenanigans...!
You accepted outside help...!
Your victory was
a deus ex machina!
Ergo that cake is a lie!
I was gonna give you
the cherry, but nah...
I will marshal my forces
for round two, rest assured.
Savor that cherry,
callow upstart;
it may well be your last!
Why don't you handle this one?
I can manage the tea.
Okarin...
What on earth are you doing?
Heh! It's dark.
I couldn't find a flashlight.
Just be careful;
that's Future Gadget
Numero Six you're holding
and it has... nostalgic value.
Huh... Plus it's nice and shiny!
You having fun?
Oh yeah, you bet I am...
The pizza was super tasty.
Suzuha and Kurisu
are getting along...
Hmph. Peachy.
We have a whole bunch of new
lab members now, you know...
I've been thinking lately
about some of the things
we could really use around here.
Is that a fact?
Oh yeah... We need, uh...
Well, new dishes. More chairs...
Have patience, my dove...
Give it a little time.
Once we've gone public
with our discoveries
somebody's bound to
pay us handsomely...
Then I'll set you loose
in a department store.
Wait, so... You'll let
me get more chairs?
And new dishes, of course...
Which will just
be the beginning...
Think even bigger.
Can we get a new microwave...?!
I majorly miss not being able
to heat up my chicken tenders...
Mayhap I'll take
it under advisement.
It's funny how much
things have changed.
I mean, just a few months ago
you were always
so sad, you know?
The lab was quiet and lonely.
It was pretty much just
you and your computer.
Then Daru came along...
And Makise, too...
Ruka came on board...
Then Suzuha...
Moeka... And Faris...
Even Mr. Braun and
Nae are like family now.
I suppose so.
The place is
getting so crowded...
It's kinda goofy for me
to still be your hostage.
Hey, guys!
Come back in...!
Somethin's going
on with the trains.
Developments on the metro:
a terrorist bomb threat
called in to local authorities
just moments ago has
shut down every line. Repeat:
Every line, traveling
to or away fr--
This terrorist crap is so...
Ugh... I mean, come on.
Jeez, I better check in at home.
Hey, uh...
This soiree was
supposed to be about
celebrating your time
machine, wasn't it?
Yeah, sort of...
Kinda funny you would
ask 'bout that now...
How deep have you
hacked into SERN?
Well we're pretty
much done digging.
Hit the mother
lode a while back.
What are you talking about?!
I'm talkin' about being
directly connected.
Oh god... There's no...!
I... I've gotta get home.
Huh? Suzu...?
Alrighty, then...
That was subtle.
You got money
for a cab, Mayuri?
Uhm.. Not really, no.
Oh no. I just wound you!
Don't tell me you're
broken... So not fair...
I've taken extra good
care of you and everything.
Oh god...
Please don't...
What... the hell...?
Don't move. Let's see
those hands in the air.
What are you doing?
Wait, you... You?!
Your time machine is
now the property of SERN.
Hold on...!
You can't just storm--
Makise Kurisu...
Okabe Rintarou...
Hashida Itaru...
You'll be coming with us.
And Mayuri?
I'm sorry.
The little one isn't needed.
Please, no...
I'm begging you.
For FB... For... For...
Oh, god... Mayuri!
Please, no...
What is this?
What the hell is this?!