We undo that D-mail...
You'll be...You'll
be murdered.
Ah, there you are.
Don't stay up here so
long you draw the ire
of Uncle Heat Stroke.
Says the guy who's
always sprawled out
on the roof like a cat.
It's cloudy today anyway.
Hey, d'you find Mayuri...?
Daru said he didn't see
her at all at Comima.
Yeah... I saw her afterward.
Ah...
Hey... Okabe?
What's up?
Never mind, then...
Hey...
It's starting to rain.
Where the hell did
this come from?!
You could have mentioned the
rain a little sooner, y'know...
For cryin' out loud,
I'm soaked to the bone.
I'm no meteorologist.
You were the one
staring up at the clou--
You're such a perv!
Hey, it's not like I was
trying to ogle you, okay?!
Your penchant for sheer clothing
can hardly be held against me.
Guess I forgot what a
typical male you can be!
Ha! As if I'd go to any undue
trouble to catch a glimpse
of your scrawny a--
Finish that thought and
I'll smack you so hard,
your cerebral neocortex
will be pudding!
Yeah, you'd like
that--wouldn't you, Zombie!
Hey, get outta my face!
Was that... always there?
I must've snagged
it on something
while I was looking for you...
God, you're klutzy.
Because I used my points on
intelligence, not dexterity.
Sure ya did...
Whatever gets you
through the night, dark elf.
Give it here...
I keep a sewing kit on me--
I can get it fixed
up for you in a jiff.
Quite the hausfrau.
Spare me the smirk.
I get it, I'm a girl so I'm
good at home-ec stuff--
blah... Just gimme
the damn coat.
As you've probably noticed,
it's kinda dark in here,
so don't expect needlework
worthy of Athena...
I'd say what color
thread I'm using,
'cept that I can't even tell.
Your choices, quote-unquote,
are black, red, and pink.
I'm just praying that
I don't get the pink...
Ah! Don't try anything!
Oh, don't worry.
I'm pretty sure a coat-rack
would prove more arous--
What part of "brain
pudding" didn't you get?!
Hmph. You're a
piece of work...
Where'd you even go
that you managed to
rip it like this, anyway?
Let me see...
I went to the lab...
The laundromat...
Took a walk... Last of all...
I made a trip to your
fancy hotel.
My hotel...? How come?
I didn't have much choice...
You wouldn't reply to my
messages... or answer my calls.
Wait, were you...
worried about me--?
I'd be remiss if I didn't
keep tabs on my assistant...
Can't have you running amok.
Aren't you done sewing yet?
Hold your horses. Catch!
It's still soggy!
Just put it on.
Who wants to see
the scrawny body
of a mad scientist with
pudding for a brain?!
It happened right here...
didn't it?
This is where...
where you found me...
How... do you know that...?
I didn't know.
I only suspected...
But now that we're here,
I'm having these feelings...
So you... you
remember being...?!
Yeah... I can remember
it happening...
But the memories I have
are so hazy...It's Like...
I dunno... Like I'm looking
at myself through a fog.
They're not just of... that.
I remember you... How hard
this all has been...
You want to save
Mayuri so badly...
You're so lonely and hurt...
and you just keep trying...
You live it again, and again...
but in the end,
she always dies...
How many times have I watched
as you howled her name...
I've seen how hard you've
been fighting for her.
You get this look on your
face and when you do,
I realize how... how
irreplaceable Mayuri is to you.
Nobody's ever... I've never
been that person to anybody.
You're so determined...
It made me want to help you...
I couldn't let you
face this by yourself.
Okabe... I want
you to save her.
Mayuri has to live.
And you're the one who
has to make it happen.
How can you say that...?
If I return to that
world-line... you will die!
If that's... what it
takes... so be it.
There's only one way
to make this work.
You know that better
than anyone.
So what, then...?!
I just abandon you...?
It can't be helped, can it...?
I've been trying
since yesterday...
I've wracked my brain...
looking for some
magic solution...
something that
would save us both.
But there isn't one...
Everything led to the
same conclusion...
She continues on the
original line... and I end.
Okabe, wait!
You won't die... I'm not
going to let you... I refuse!
I can't throw you away
...not even for Mayuri...!
What was the point of
this repetitious hell...
if I have to lose
someone either way?
Someone I...I...!
No more running...
This is what I want...
Going back won't change that!
Goddamn it!
Time-leaping isn't
going to work...!
You'll never get
past the 1% barrier!
But how can we know for
sure unless we try it?!
All that's gonna happen is that
you'll watch Mayuri die again!
Don't go back...
Seeing her die is gonna
break you, Okabe!
It won't, though...
How could it?
Do you know how many times
I've watched her die now?
Dozens. Easily.
Again... and again, and again
and again and again...!
No matter how many
times I have to watch it
to save you, it's not
going to break me--!
Did you hear what
you just said to me...?
Our friend... is dying
and you don't care...
I know you don't
really mean that!
If losing Mayuri doesn't
hurt you anymore...
Then... your heart
is already broken.
Please, just stop...
It's destroying you.
Yeah... you're right.
Has for a while.
What's happening is awful...
but I can barely feel it.
I'm numb to it...
How did I get here?
I've waited to go back,
all so I could note her
precise time of death.
Now, her dying is... nothing
more than a puzzle to be solved.
I can always...
just give it another go...
Try it again... Ad infinitum...
Please, Okabe... Save her...
If you let her die...
you're going to regret it for
the rest of your life...!
Losing her for good
is going to end you!
You know that I'm right!
Think of all the things
you've done to keep her alive!
If you give up now,
then what was it for?!
If you let her go... the
Okabe that I know is dead.
Dammit...! If I save
Mayuri's life... then you--!
I'll just go back...!
To the initial world line where
the first D-mail was never sent!
I think that's
what's best for you!
What's best for both of us!
We've argued so many times
these last twenty days...
Gone at it like cats
and dogs, even...
But we've shared
our problems, too.
Kurisu's the one I relied
on when things got rough.
I came to her with
this over and over...
and she always believed in me.
She's a scientific genius.
Published at the age of 18...
She can be stubborn as a mule...
And proud... and nosy...
There's a world of ideas
dancing in her eyes...
And her theories... god, how
they always hold me spellbound.
I remember every
word she said...
Every moment...
we spent together...
I've called her
so many things...
But never the words
in my heart.
Kurisu...
I just don't know...
how to save you.
I'm sorry...
Thank you...
Nobody's ever... wanted
to have me around so much.
Why did that girl turn
out to be you...?
Why couldn't it have
been somebody else?!
You know...
there's a lot about
changing world-lines that
we aren't sure of.
Maybe when you...
blip out of existence
in this world-line...
you just trade places with
their Okabe or something...
You could, for all we
know, right...?
It doesn't matter...
You'll be gone.
That's what I'm saying...
maybe I won't be.
Even if I am dead in
the original world-line...
that doesn't necessarily
mean I'll be dead here, too!
There are infinite lines...
What if each one
has its own me...?
And maybe all of our
minds are connected,
forming the Kurisu you know.
That would be...
wonderful, wouldn't it?
Getting to be in so
many times and places.
Always with a similar
quest for truth...
always with a desire to make
a difference in the world...
always with the same
love for... someone...
Many stars, shining
in their own space...
but just one constellation...
That would be a
beautiful truth.
Okabe... Please don't think
of this as letting me die.
Even if the
world-line changes...
and I'm gone... so long as
you remember me...
I'll still be right there...
With you.
I couldn't forget you...
Not even if I tried.
There's not a person I care
for in this whole world...
like I do for you.
Uh... You don't...
I mean it.
What are you trying...
to tell me...?!
Kurisu... I love you.
Huh?!
How do you feel about me?
How do I feel?!
I have to know... just for this
moment... what I was to you.
You really want to know...?
Yeah.
Don't look, okay?
Close your eyes...
What for?
Just close 'em!
There was... a scientific
rationale for that.
Because... certain
important memories,
including but not limited
to one's first kiss,
are stored in the hippocampus--
which makes 'em harder
to forget... So I figured--
There's just one problem.
You're assuming that
was my first kiss.
Kissing your pillow
doesn't count, virgin!
You would know, wouldn't you...
Nevertheless, I will
admit my first kiss
lacked that romantic
je ne sais quoi...
Either way... my hippocampus
didn't get that one...
Let's try it again.
Huh?
I can't risk forgetting
this... Not for anything...
I mean, I guess that's
logical... And it's just a kiss.
It feels... like time
is passing so quickly...
Damn you, Einstein...
Your science is crowding
in on our kiss...
He was right, Okabe...
The passage of time
depends entirely
on where you're standing...
Relativity Theory...
It's so romantic... but
it's just so tragic, too...
This is it.
It's not to late
to call the others.
A big goodbye with everyone
would hurt too much.
But if it's just you...
then I can't wait to be outta
here and back in the U.S.
It's a joke.
I brought you something...
A memento.
What the hell...?
Hey, that happens to be version
2.67 you're sneering at.
It's still impractical...
But I suppose it's the
thought that counts.
Okay...
Kurisu--?
Oh, yeah.
Got you something. Catch!
You know you
throw like a girl.
Go get it, smartass.
Yeah, yeah...
Okabe...
It hurts me to say it... but
you're gonna have it rough.
It'll be a world where no
one else remembers me...
Only you... And you'll
have to shoulder it alone.
You care about people,
more than you know...
Losing them gnaws at you.
I'm sorry.
But... knowing you care
means so much to me.
Maybe when you're
up in the lab...
or drinking your soda...
or just walking through town...
Or maybe even
during... a kiss...
Not every single time...
Just once in a while...
I hope that you'll
think of me...
'Cause I'll be right
there with you...
Even if we're worlds away...
know that I'm
still in your heart.
Okabe... Okabe... Okabe...!
Heads up...!
I think I found it!
This is the droid we're
looking for, right?!
If we erase that line...
Then mission accomplished.
Okarin... You feel okay?
Why wouldn't I?
Finally...! The ultimate moment
of Operation Verdandi is nigh!
Victory is ours for the taking!
Despite their vile
machinations... we held fast...
we stayed true to our
convictions... and persevered!
We have survived the
Battle of Ragnarok!
To my comrades-in-arms...
who fought and
bled for this victory...
You have my gratitude!
And I promise...
I will never... forget you!
What awaits us now... is the
future she would have wanted...!
A world not hamstrung
by their tyranny!
All of this... will
never have happened!
Kurisu...
Forgive me...
Okabe!
You wanna know...
how I feel...?
Kurisu!
Okabe...! You should know
by now that I'm in l--
Mayuri...
Who is lab member
zero-zero-four?
Zero-zero-four...?
Hmmm...
Oh! A trick question.
There isn't one.
Behold...! The way is
clear! We're free...!
I, the mad scientist
Hououin Kyouma,
have triumphed over a
two-fold assault by SERN
and the Organization by
twisting the very fundamentals
of time and space!
The world as we know it
has been put to rights...
and a future of
chaos awaits us...!
This, my friends... is
the choice of Stein's Gate!
It's okay... Just be yourself.
Whaddya mean...?! This is me!
How else should I deliver
a victory speech?!
You don't have to pretend to
be Hououin Kyouma for me.
The bad stuff isn't
gonna happen to me now.
I can tell... you can
cry now if you want...
Go ahead.
We took apart the Phone Wave.
If we hadn't built it...
I'd never have met her.
But... it came at too
high of a price...
Too many people had to suffer...
Hououin Kyouma's
consigned to the past.
As are the tools
of his mania.
Life isn't about do-overs...
For good or ill,
you get one chance.
This is for the best...
Isn't it... Kurisu?
Hello?
Huh...? Wait, who is this...?
I'm your what now...?!
Okarin, huh?
Yeah--lemme get 'em.
Hey, Okarin! Phone!
It's some crazy chick!
Go ahead.
Please, get to the roof of
the Radio Building A-SAP!
Huh? Who is this?!
Listen! I came here from 2036!
I'm Hashida Itaru's
daughter, Amane Suzuha!
Suzuha?! But--! What are
you doing here...?!
How is SERN still a
threat in your timeline?!
I'll explain when you get
here, but you have to hurry!
I need you to prevent
World War III!