Seriously...
World War Three?
Let me put it into
perspective for you:
that's upwards of 5.7
billion human lives snuffed out
by the year 2036.
And it all starts with this.
But... what is "this?"
Totally a mech...
Please tell me it transforms.
It's a time machine, Daru.
Sorry?
You're familiar with it...
That's good, Uncle...
Very good... I can
get to the point.
We're gonna run interference.
I refuse.
Okarin...
I've been jumping from
world-line to world-line
for weeks.
I've run interference...
So many times I'm barely
myself anymore...
The only way I was able to
land back onto this world-line
was by allowing Kurisu to die.
And now you're asking me
to go another round...?!
I refuse!
What are you talking about?
Kurisu...? Oh...
You mean the scientist
chick who got, like,
stabbed or whatever at the
Radio Building the other day?
Rintarou... Hear me out...
What if I told you the
circumstances
of her death on the
afternoon of July 28th, 2010
play directly into what
kicked off the war...?
That the reason I'm here,
is to see to it she survives?
I'm listening.
I don't have a clue
how it all dovetails...
All I know is I've
been entrusted
with an important mission...
Rescue Makise Kurisu and
shift things to a world-line
beyond the divergence barrier;
free of the attractor field...
A little place we
call Stein's Gate!
I don't believe it...
You actually hatched this
plan yourself...
By that I mean you will...
With dad...
Though you're the first
to admit it's pure conjecture...
Push comes to shove,
it's possible this is
all wishful thinking...
Even if a Stein's Gate
world-line exists,
the odds of us reaching
one are slim to none.
Odds be damned,
though: I'm all in...
As you always like to remind us:
nothing ventured,
nothing gained, right...?
If a future without World War
Three is worth the risk to you.
Take my hand.
Um... Okay to be honest,
I don't think I understood very
much of what just got said...
But...
This friend of yours...
This Makise Kurisu...?
Sounds to me like she's
worth taking a chance, right?
I, say you should go for it!
Face it, chief.
It's your cuppa tea...
All this World War Three
stuff seems, well...
No offense, you understand,
but tailor-made for your
special brand of crazy.
I do this for her, no
one else... Got it?
Whatever gets you there.
Climb aboard!
It can actually carry two?
Well, yeah... Like
this puppy's inventor
would've have skimped on
installing a backseat...
Be careful.
Leave your cell
phone here.
We'd all be screwed five
ways from Tuesday if it
crossed signals with the one
your past self'll be carrying.
Watch it for me?
Good luck, guys.
Nice, uh... set up you got.
Thanks... Works like a charm;
I've already stopped off
at 1975 and 2000...
She's running low on fuel,
though... That's the thing...
You've got to watch the
indicators like a hawk.
Wait. So we can not only go
backward in time, but forward?
I should hope so...
What the in hell'd be the
point if we couldn't?
I see... This one must come
from a different world line
than its twin...
Have a seat... I'm setting
coordinates for the day of,
just shy of twelve o'clock...
I don't dare go back any further
because I can't
change our position.
If we stir up trouble
at the Radio Building
it might throw Kurisu's
movements out of whack.
We're about to pull an
ungodly amount of Gs here,
so you might want
to prepare yourself.
Okarin...
What are these?
They come with the territory.
Little beads of time...
Kinda pretty, huh?
Come on.
Sorry. I, uh... just need to
let my stomach settle a bit...
Somebody's a wuss...
Hurry it up!
'Kay, critical point:
avoid running into your
past self at all costs...
We could have a major paradox
on our hands otherwise...
How long do you
think this'll take?
Uh... Well... Maybe twenty
minutes, give or take?
Alright, I'm going to stay
here and prep the time machine
for our return trip, and you do
what you can to save Makise.
Wish me luck.
July 28th...
The day I found
Kurisu on the floor,
soaked in her own blood...
Mayuri and I had come to
see Dr. Nakabachi's lecture
and were waiting
for it to start
when we heard a sound
on the roof...
That's right.
This must be when Mayuri
heads to the vending machines
on the seventh floor.
Is anything not
an emergency?
I'm sorry. I know
sometimes it's not,
but this one counts for sure.
Better play it safe. I'll take
the far stairs back to eight.
I don't believe it...!
A metal Oopa!
And that's good?
You bet it is!
Should be safe now...
Oh, I'm sorry.
Ku... Kurisu...
Um... have we met before?
No... This is too much...
I don't... think
I know you... do I?
Kurisu...
Look, whoever--
What is your trauma...?
Don't rush to help me
or anything...
I, uh...
I'm just... Here to see...
Your attention, please.
Doctor Nakabachi's
conference is about
to begin in the 8th
floor lecture hall.
All interested are welcome.
At least finish a sentence!
Printed on the handouts
there in front of you
is more or less the
hard blueprint
for one of mankind's
oldest ambitions...
Of course,
the theoretical scaffolding
begs some explanation.
As I'm sure you're aware,
mainstream science currently
boasts something like
In the brief I was given,
they said you'd be able to pick
her out instantly. Is that true?
Yeah.
Right. Bear in mind, though...
It's probably a bad idea
to take her off site.
We don't know who
kills her or why.
And in the event
that her death
is a fixed point
on the timeline,
we don't want things
getting more complicated.
I learned that the
hard way with Mayuri.
Doctor!
Save your questions...
I have none, sir...!
I throw down the gauntlet as
to your "theory's" authorship!
Do you take us all for
babes in the wilderness...?!
Please! World lines?
Kerr Black Holes...?
Any moment now, this is
where she'll end up...
What on earth
am I going to do?
Wait! What if she's
killed somewhere else
and dragged here...?
Damn it! I hadn't
thought of that!
There she is...
This is where it happens...
What is that she's reading...?
Time machines...?!
Is that why so much
is riding on this?
Stupid kids...
What in the hell
do you want?
Look, please... I just want
you to read this... 'kay Dad?
"Dad?!"
Nakabachi's her dad?!
Look, I... I'm just trying
to bury the hatchet...
It's been years...
Too damn long...
I want you in my life again.
Don't tell me her
father's the one who...!
I put on my thinking cap,
as you like to say, and well...
I'm now convinced that
you were right all along.
I wanted your opinion
on the theory.
If this paper gets accepted...
you can lord it over
all the stuffed shirts
who laughed you out
of the academy.
I did not get "laughed out!"...
I turned my back
on their politics
to pursue my
researches unfettered!
Sorry...
This isn't half bad.
Really?! 'Cause I was
thinking, maybe,
if you were okay
with the idea,
we could publish it under
both our names.
I mean, after all,
you're the one who inspired
me to write it--
Don't be ridiculous...
Go home.
What?
If this paper sees the light of
day, it'll do so under my name.
Excuse me?! That's
called stealing!
I knew you could be cruel, but
I never thought you'd stoop to--
Shut up!
You dare call me a thief?!
Bitch! What makes you think
you're so much better than me?!
A daughter's got no goddamn
right to outshine her father!
Every second you're
out there whoring
to make a name for yourself,
you trample my reputation
as a genius of the age!
You were my heckler,
weren't you...?
Heh... I see... You were in
cahoots to make nattering
ol' Nakabachi shit the bed
during what should've been
his moment of glory...
Well, You succeeded.
But success comes at
a price.
Dad, no!
Stand your ground;
protect her!
Where's your heckling now...?
Come on, let's hear it!
Son of bitch...
Dad, this is crazy...!
Please stop!
So I'm crazy...?! I'll show
you crazy!!!
Look out!
You're an idiot...
A DNA fluke...!
You're not as smart as me...!
My name belongs in the annals
of history... You're nothing!
Daddy, please...
If it hadn't been for you...
I wouldn't be the academic
laughing stock I am now!
Stop!!!
Oh god...
Oh my god...!
Look at that... Poetic
justice all around, I'd say.
I'm sorry... I didn't mean...
What...?
I didn't mean to
drag you into this...
I just wanted him to...
To acknowledge me...
Kurisu...
I'm so scared. I... I... don't
want to die... I'm not ready...
This wasn't...
wasn't supposed to...
No... oh god...
Please no!
Neat-o! They're already back!
Okarin!
Whoa. Dude...! What the
hell happened to you?!
He's gonna be alright...
It's, just... a little
bit complicated...
I'm responsible for
her death...
I'm responsible for her death...
Okarin...
Walk it off...
Look, I know you're in shock,
but you've got to
pick yourself up...
We've got enough
fuel for one more trip
and now we know how
things play out, so--
No! I won't do it...!
I won't put myself
through that again!
Whatever I do,
Kurisu will always die...
Okarin, it's your phone.
A text?
Open it.
I shouldn't...
Just do it.
It says to turn on the news.
Seriously?
Despite the cargo bay fire,
Dr. Nakabachi's plane
managed to land safely
within the borders of
the former Soviet Union,
to which he'd recently defected.
Fate was certainly
smiling on me...
If this guy hadn't set off
the onboard metal detectors...
My thesis would've
been barbequed.
That's my metal oopa!
I know it is...! See look!
I wrote my name on the side
right after Okarin
bought it for me!
No, I see. It's just,
why's it in Russia?
That thesis of his...
That's what starts
World War Three.
It basically
sparks an arms race,
only the goal is which country
can build a time machine first.
Take first place
and win the world...
That's how it starts, but things
get hostile pretty quick...
Then war... Then people are
getting killed in droves.
The lives of 5.7 billion
people are at stake here...
Save Makise Kurisu... and
you save every one of them.
I can't do it.
Things'll end up just
as they did with Mayuri.
No matter what
I did, she died...
There's no point...
It's all the same.
No! You only tried once!
You can't say that!
Once?! ...Are you mad?
I tried dozens of times!
And every time, I failed!
Believe me, I know...
You may not think I do, but
I know how cruel time can be...
We like to imagine we can
bend it to suit us, but...
This was bound to happen.
It was stupid of me to play
along... I'm sorry, but...
I'm... I'm just done...
Let time have it's way.
Since when have you
been the type of person
who's "just done"?
You're not fooling me.
You've never given up
on anything, ever...
Remember when I couldn't bring
myself to say bye to grandma...?
You went to her
grave every day for me
until I was ready
to do it myself.
You never got mad
and you never quit...
And because of that I was
finally able to let her go.
So, no... I'm not letting
you throw in the towel.
Listen, a video file
should've turned up
in your inbox on July 28th.
That's right... I'd forgotten...
It should be viewable now...
You had to fail saving her
once before it would unlock,
so to speak.
What the hell are you
talking about?!
I apologize...
I know it was a lot
to put you through,
but things had to be this way...
The whole point was
for you to see that file.
Is that...?
Hale and well met...
Old friend.
Is that you?!
That you're able to
open this means
you've seen firsthand
what became of Makise
and failed to prevent it.
I feel for you. I really do.
That said, the pain you're going
through right now is necessary.
I daren't deny you-- us--
the bitter inspiration
it represents.
Without it, you cannot hope
to carve out your destiny.
Now we can marshal our
resources properly.
I hereby charge you with the
task of reaching Stein's Gate...
To do so, two conditions
are absolutely essential:
one, you must destroy
Nakabachi's ill-gotten
time travel thesis before it
crosses into Russia's borders...
Second, you must
rescue our beloved Kurisu.
But how?! I've tried--
I'm fully aware
that the grisly nature
of her death appears be set
in stone due to its position
within the so-called alpha
attractor field. However...
I'll just come right out with
it: it is possible to save her.
You're simply going
about it the wrong way.
Listen carefully: you must
not--I repeat, not--
alter any detail surrounding
her death as witnessed by you.
That is, the version of
yourself prior to the botched
rescue attempt that allowed you
to view this video file...
To do so would alter the
past too drastically.
Think of your experiences
immediately following
the first D-mail:
the three weeks you spent
jumping through time
were instigated by that text.
It's what gave you
a history with her...
Your desperate, bitterly
ineffective bids to save Mayuri.
The countless sacrifices...
The terrible Rubicons crossed.
All of that must
stay in your head.
The period spent adrift in time
constitutes your unique reality.
It must not be distorted.
To do so would be tantamount
to a betrayal of who you are.
I know that to label Kurisu's
death as traumatic is
the epitome of understatement.
Believe me, I do.
The memory of seeing her
life ebb away as I held her
in my arms haunts me still.
But the pain it wrought can be
wrought in turn to greater ends.
It what's brings you
to yourself.
So trick yourself.
Save her without changing the
apparent fact of her death.
Convince your past self that
she's well and truly dead,
even though she lives.
Keep the past to all intents
and purposes where it is.
That's what will get
us to Stein's Gate.
Of course...!
I don't think I get it.
That goes for both of us.
I've every faith
that you understand.
Incidentally, the time
machine's model is Type C204.
I doubt I need tell you
what the C stands for.
It's for Christina...
The target world line's
charming little nickname
comes care of me as well;
which is to say,
it comes from you.
Care to guess its significance?
There's none
Bingo.
There's none.
And to further
please our whimsy...
Operation Skuld will be the
name we assign to this mission.
Forge of yesterday whatever
you must to save the future...
without detectably altering the
past as you understood them.
Okabe Rintarou sees Makise
lying dead on the ground
in a pool of her
own blood.
Keep the past, for all intents
and purposes, where it is.
Deceive yourself in every last
detail... Deceive the world.
Do this, and victory
is assured.
Best of luck to you, old
friend. El... Psy... Congroo.
Okay. Trippy...
You have any idea what your
future self is tellin' you?
Oh wow... You get
really suave.
"Operation Skuld..."
"El Psy Congroo..."
Do I never grow out of the
cloak and dagger act?
I'll be as barking mad
then as I am now.
Yeah, but is that so bad?...
Ah to hell with it...
If Stein's Gate so decrees, then
so am I compelled to behave.
Hououin Kyouma accepts
the challenge...!
With gusto!
Deception is my forte...
Let the world beware!
Oh ho. I think the Okabe we
all know and love is back...
Uh-huh... Good thing, too...
The Okarin who just broods
all day isn't nearly as fun.
Hear me...
privileged companions...
Time is ours... Hououin Kyouma's
mind recognizes no limit...
Neither does his reach!
Heave anchor...!
This ship of fools
is about to embark!