Your time machine's
now the property of SERN.
Hold on...!
You can't just storm--
Makise Kurisu...
Okabe Rintarou...
Hashida Itaru...
You'll be coming with us.
And Mayuri?
I'm sorry.
The little one isn't needed.
Please, no...
I'm begging you.
For FB... For... For...
Oh, god... Mayuri!
Please, no...
What the hell is this?!!
Stand up, slowly...
Okabe...! Please......!
She's gonna kill
you if you don't!
I swear ... on my life...
you will pay...!
The big-screen...
Down in the shop...
It's on right now.
Do it! Now!
Are you sure?!
Just start the time-leap!
But... We don't even
know if it's gonna work!
Goddammit, Do as I say!
Okabe!
Please work!
Mayuri's grandma died
when we were young...
To Mayuri... it's like
time itself had stopped.
She visited the grave
every day... without fail...
rain or shine...
for the next six months.
She would just stand there...
her grandma's
pocket watch in hand...
she'd gaze patiently
into the sky...
As if... as if the woman
was coming back for her soon.
And one day... she almost did.
The sun broke
through the clouds...
Mayuri was swathed in light.
She reached into
the sky... unafraid.
At that moment... I knew
I was about to lose her.
Mayuri!
Okarin...?
I'm not letting them take you!
You're my hostage,
do you hear me...?
You can't escape
a mad scientist,
so don't even bother
trying...! Please!
In my panic...
I blurted out the first
thing that came to mind.
A line from some
scenery-chewing bad guy...
care of a TV show
we'd grown up on...
'Kay...
Better stay, then...
Since I'm your hostage and all.
You're gonna have to wait
for me... 'Kay, Grammy?
Hey guys, you know what?
Looks pretty cute, huh!
I've got to get her into
cosplay one of these days.
I give you permission
to hug my oopa cushion...
Is your head all empty or what?
What's with you?
Did you doze off
just now or something?
What time is it...?
Huh?
What time?!
Hey, chill...
It's almost five o'clock...
We're going
shopping, remember?
Shopping? But I...
I'll be a bro and
order the pizzas, yeah?
Knock yourself out...
but no Hawaiian, okay?
Too much going on there.
I hear ya.
the time-leap succeeded...
It's earlier today...
You ready?
Huh? Where's Mayuri?!
I need to know where she is!
Jeez. Calm down with
the shouting already.
Mayuri headed out
a few minutes ago.
She went to invite Ruka
to the party, remember?
Um, you going solo?
The press conference
is cancelled!
Wait, cancelled...?
Just like that?
Something up, dude?
Executive decision...!
We're done for today...!
Just... go home, all right?!
What's wrong with you?
I told you to leave...!
Okay...?! So just do it!
Hell was that about...?
He was fine until his
cell phone went off.
His cell phone...
Too-too-roo!
This is Mayushii...!
Actually, it's my phone,
so leave me a message, okay?
I'll call ya back!
I don't see any discernible
change in the world-line...
This is different than D-mail...
I've really gone back
to 5 p.m. this afternoon.
Clackety-clack...!
Look, Mommy--it's
the bullet train!
That's a whole different kind...
The bullet-trains
are white, honey.
After this... Mayuri brings
Suzuha to the lab... and then...
Do I go to the police...?
No, they'll toss me
into the drunk tank,
or a straightjacket...
Who's gonna
believe me...?! God...!
I only have three hours
left to save her...!
Mayuri!
Oh...! Okabe...!
I mean... Hey, Kyouma--!
Tell me that
Mayuri's still here!
I... I'm sorry...
She's already left...
How long ago?! I need to know.
Uh... about half an
hour ago, I think...?
She said she was
heading back to the lab...
Hasn't she shown up yet?
Um... thanks, by the way...
It was really nice
of you to invite me
to your party later, buuut...
I don't think I'll be able to--
Did she mention stopping
anywhere on the way?!
She... did say something
about that... But she...
Look, if she comes back ,
you have her call me at once!
It's life or death!
Yeah... Okay...
If the world-line
hasn't shifted,
Mayuri's actions will lead
her to the same fate...
She's going to die again
unless I can change things...!
Where the hell is she...?!
Hello!. You've reached
Faris's cell-phone!
Leave a meow-ssage,
and I'll call you ba--
Damn it, why the
hell can't I find you?
Mayuri--thank God!
Nope. Sorry.
No, really it's... fine...
I told you we're
done for today...
I need you to leave at--
Not till you answer my question.
Did you time-leap back
here from the future?
Yes or no?
How'd you figure it out?
You answered your
phone and flipped out.
I just connected the dots...
Something happened,
didn't it...? Something bad.
Yeah... But there's no
time to explain right now...
Just run... Please.
Sure. Okay. Where am
I supposed to run to?
Anywhere...
Get yourself as far away
from the lab as possible...
It doesn't matter.
You're so explaining later.
Deal... Get Daru out, too.
All right... Hey.
Yeah?
Don't do anything too crazy.
Perish the thought.
What are the odds, huh?
How do I get to
Ochanomizu? I've got no--
Have you seen Mayuri?!
Dial back on the caffeine...
But yeah, she just invited
me to the party tonight.
Where was she?!
Hang a right at the corner--
Hey...! At least tell me
where Ochanomizu is at!
I'm supposed to take
Nae shopping later,
but Sir Cue Ball
didn't give me a map!
Just ask a policeman!
Keep Nae out as
late as you can!
Do not go back to the shop!
What are you on about?
I'll explain everything later!
Thank God...
Mayuri!
Okarin, look...! It's the
first star of the night!
Hey, What are you doing?!
We're not going back
to the lab tonight!
But... what about the party?
It's canceled...! I've
already told the others!
Huh......? How come?
I'll explain later!
But I just invited Suzuha,
and Daru said he was gonna
order some pizzas, rememb--?
Dammit! Just do as I say!
Please don't yell.
I'm sorry.
I don't understand... all the
science stuff that you do...
but I can usually tell what's
going on in your head, anyway...
And right now,
I feel like I don't
understand anything at all.
I guess you... kinda
time-leapt after all, huh?
Yes I did.
It's not as though
I wanted to...
Okay...? It was something
I had no choice over.
We have to go now.
I promise I'll explain all this.
Yeah... I'm sorry...
Guess you just startled
me a little bit, that's all...
Don't apologize...
You've done nothing wrong.
Lotta folks here, huh...
Guess It's to be
expected with rush hour.
Oh yeah... but then how come
the platforms are all empty?
Developments on the metro:
a terrorist bomb threat
called in to local
authorities just moments ago
has shut down every line.
Still no clue when the trains'll
be up and running again...
Shut down by the bomb threat...!
Of course the trains
aren't running!
Is that bad?
We need to get to the
subway as quickly as we c--!
Okabe Rintarou, yes...?
Something the matter?
You're coming with us.
Why're you just standing in the
middle of the damn walkway?!
Run!
Get out of here, Mayuri!
Whatever you do,
don't stop running!
Why are they chasing us?!
Okarin!
Don't worry about me...!
Just keep running!
Reporting that Shiina Mayuri
has been neutralized...
There was no problem...
Okabe Rintarou has
been apprehended.
The mission is complete.
Mayuri!
I won't let you do this
to her--do you hear me...?!
I'm going to save you, Mayuri!
I swear it...!
On my life!
Wait, cancelled...?
Just like that?
Something up, dude?
Yes... You see...
I have it on good authority
that Mr. Braun's
in a vile mood today, and he's
likely to take it out on us.
Lemme guess. You managed
to piss him off again?
I dunno... I guess...
But what about Mayuri?
Look, I plan to
tell her about it...
The point is, you guys need
to get out of here ASAP.
And no, this isn't
my idea of a joke.
I didn't play that
off very well...
They have to at least suspect
I was being dishonest...
Not that it matters
either way, I suppose...
So long as they
clear out of the lab,
they can think whatever
the hell they like.
Too-too-roo!
This is Mayushii...!
Actually, it's my phone,
so leave me a message, okay?
Looking for her
takes too much time!
If I don't find her, and soon,
this is going to pan
out the same way...!
Hello?
Rukako--hey!.
It's me...! Okabe!
Oh! Okabe...
I mean, hey, Kyouma--!
Is she there?!
Huh?
Is she still there?!
Mayuri...?
Yeah, she is, but...
she's heading out right now--
No, stop her...! Order her
to stay put until I get there!
Don't let her out of your sight!
But, I think she's just
going back to the lab--
Listen, I am begging
you to stop her!
Uh, okay...! Wait up, Mayuri!
Huh...?
Clackety-clack...!
Look, Mommy--it's
the bullet train!
That's a whole different kind...
The bullet-trains
are white, honey.
Mayuri!
Heya, Okarin! Too-too-roo!
You didn't have
to run here, silly...
I was just gonna pop over
to Fubuki's to fix her outfit
before I head back to the lab.
Fubuki...? Your
cosplay friend...?
Yeah! She texted me that one
of the hems I did came undone,
so I'm gonna re-stitch it.
I'll be super-quick!
That's why I couldn't
track you down before!
And I'll go straight over to
the lab when I'm finished...!
I wouldn't miss a second
of that party for anything!
Look, about the party...
I had to go ahead and
canc--I had to postpone it.
Awww...! How come?!
The lab is off-limits to us
for the foreseeable future...
It's out of my control.
That's a let-down...
I know. And I'm sorry.
But for right now, I need
you to come with me--Alright?
But Fubuki's hem--
It's just gonna
have to wait...
This is really important, okay?
Um, is something
the matter, Kyouma...?
Yeah... But we're
gonna get it sorted out.
On a trip.
Huh...?! You mean, just
the two of you on a trip...?!
Oh, my, that's sudden...!
Wow... I guess I can
help Fubuki tomorrow,
but this is really random...
Where are we gonna go?
It's a surprise. Come on.
Don't want to miss our train.
Yeah but, I haven't even packed
an overnight bag or anything,
and won't I need some money--
I'll deal with all that on
the way. Now... shall we?
Uh...! Kay! I'm
coming--wait for me!
Uh... Hey...!
Yeah...?
Have a good time.
'Kay...! See ya soon, Ruka!
Aren't we taking the train...
'cause the station
is over there.
Taking the subway.
Okie-dokie then.
It's been a long time since
you led me somewhere
by the hand like this...
You used to do it a bunch.
Yeah.
Change of plans.
Huh?
All clear... On three.
Just Kurisu...
Oh no. I just wound you!
Don't tell me you're broken.
So not fair...I've taken extra
good care of you and everything.
It sure is crowded in here, huh.
The Soubu Line
is shut down, so...
Oh...! Is it really?
I didn't know.
Uh-huh.
I heard somebody
say in passing that
there'd been some
kind of bomb threat.
That's just horrible.
Okarin...?
Listen... There's a bunch of
stuff I wanna ask you about,
but I know you already
have so much on your mind.
So pretty please...
just promise me you'll explain
all this when it's over, okay?
I will.
I promise you.
I'm sorry.
Huh?
I know I'm not useful
like the others...
And I'm sorry.
Just you wait...
We'll have that party.
Yeah.
Someday.
Someday...
I know it.
Mayuri--surprise!
I didn't...
I didn't mean to...
I just wanted...
to surprise Mayuri.
I didn't know I was
gonna fall down...
You're not going to die...
I don't care...
what it takes...!
I swear it!