Is this...?
You know what it is.
I'm a time traveler;
specifically from the year 2036.
Dear god...
We've met online a
few times, you and me...
I post as John Titor.
By the year 2036...
SERN has taken complete
control of the world.
Their word is law.
Democracy is
nothing but a memory.
People sleepwalk through their
lives completely devoid of hope.
Opposition is treason;
treason is death.
I was a member of the
anti-SERN resistance.
On the run, day and night,
living in the hit
squads' crosshairs...
I realized they couldn't
be defeated in my time.
So I bet my only chip--
the secret time-machine
my father had left me.
That's why I'm here.
I need to prevent that future.
Then all those things John Titor
was posting online were true?
Yeah... Much as
I wish they weren't.
But SERN's a
research organization--
it doesn't have a standing
army or anything like that...
I tried asking Titor about
it online a bunch of times
and I never got
a straight answer.
Hold on...
So that was you posting
under the nom de web
"Chestnut Rice
and Kamehame-ha"?!
Hey, she laid her
cards out on the table...
So the least I can do
is reciprocate, right...?
I hid my posts in plain sight...
Attributing them all
to Hououin Kyouma--!
Yeah, we know that.
Once SERN builds
a time-machine,
they're the ones who're
calling all the shots...
With that kind of
power at their disposal,
it doesn't take long for
them to decide the world needs
to bend to their liking,
for our own good, of course.
And one person did
more than anyone else
to bring SERN's
machine to fruition...
"The mother of time-travel,"
they call her... Makise Kurisu.
Are you saying I'm
some kind of traitor...?!
I would never help them...!
I don't know where you
got your information,
but it's obviously wrong!
It's true in 2036.
Is that why you've always
been so hateful around me?
What about my
future self, then?
Later in life, you're going
to become an infamous terrorist.
A what?!
More like an anti-SERN
freedom-fighter, actually.
Oh, also... you
two should know...
By the time I leave in 2036,
both of you are dead.
Time for me to go.
Wait a sec...!
You can't just drop
a bombshell like that
and blithely sashay
back to the future!
The future's a dead-end...
I'm heading to an
earlier point in time...
Back to the year 1975.
Why nineteen seventy-five?
SERN is only able to
build their time-machine
because they get their hands
on a working version of one
from Akihabara and then
improve on that technology.
Our Phone Wave, you mean?
Mhmm.
They managed to set up a
worldwide monitoring system
to alert them to the emergence
of any viable research
in the field of time-travel.
I hate to lay this at
your doorstep, Okabe...
but that first D-mail you
sent probably caught their eye.
You mean the one I sent in
front of the Radio Building?
That's the one...
But if we can just
delete that message
from their system altogether
before anyone over at
SERN bothers to read it...
...we'll change... the future.
We'll toss life as we
know it onto a world-line
where their time-travel
ambitions never pan out!
Will making that jump
help us save Mayuri's life?!
We can hope.
Then what are we waiting for?!
Let's go back in your machine
and hack their database --!
We'll need to find an
IBN 5100 to pull that off.
Wait, so... is that why...?
My mission was to
travel back to 1975,
obtain an IBN 5100, and
make sure that it got to you...
That's was all.
But I let myself get distracted,
and spent too much
time looking for my dad...
I should've left
this year way earlier.
What's going on?!
Oh my god.
Something's broken...!
Not good...!
Do we run?!
One of us is about to...!
Sneak out of here as
soon as they're distracted!
Is someone in there...?
Who are you?!
Foolish man...!
Can you not see I'm
clearly in the midst
of a foiling an
Organization plot...?!
This'll send their ranks
tumbling like so many dominoes!
I recommend you forget what
you've seen here tonight...!
Now if you'll excuse me...!
What the hell?!
Get back here!
C'mon--let's go!
Hurry it up!
Look--I don't know what
happens later, okay?!
But right now we're on the same
side--so just trust me, dammit!
Okabe!
You're sure you weren't
followed...?! Come on, then.
So now what? We can't
exactly go back there...
I can't believe the
time machine is broken...
Did crashing into
the roof do it?
Hey, I didn't crash. I
miscalculated the coordinates
and... well, kind of
materialized mid-roof...
Semantics aside, though:
no... it wasn't broken
when I got here.
What happened, then?
Remember that
thunderstorm we had...?
I think that
could have done it.
Maybe the lightning,
or the rain...
Hell, probably both.
It's my fault.
If I hadn't stopped you
from leaving that night...
Wait--I can use the Phone Wave!
Yeah, but you can only go back
as far as 48 hours
with it, remember?
Right, of course--that was
more than two days ago.
Heya, Okarin!
And Kurisu and
Suzuha make three!
I cancelled the party tonight!
Why haven't you
both gone home?!
Uh, she told me she wanted to
un-cancel the party, so yeah.
Don't be grumpy! Look at
the tasty snacks we picked up!
I told you to leave for today!
I'm sorry, honey.
We're just dealing
with some important stuff
right now, that's all.
Can I help?
Just call it a day.
I'll pay you back for
all the snacks and stuff...
We'll have a party
later on--I promise you.
Okay, then...
But only if you promise me
that you're gonna be safe...!
'Cause I get all
worried about you.
We'll be all right...
You have my word.
Alright! See ya later, then!
See ya.
I hear they even
stopped the trains.
You serious?
We have got to get the
time-machine operational again.
Here's the plan...
Okabe jumps back
to five hours ago,
when the lab first had
time-leap functionality...
Then you jump back again
to the full 48-hour maximum,
to 2 p.m. on the 11th...
Everyone clear?
Sounds like that's as much time
as we're going to
have to work with.
I just hope that it
ends up being enough.
Whatever it takes to
get that time-machine up
and running again, that's
what we do--understood...?
I'll keep reliving those
two days 'till it works!
This isn't about
saving the world.
Not for me. Not anymore.
This is about Mayuri!
Okabe?
Something the matter?
Get the lab members
up here on the double.
There's something
you all need to see.
It ain't a blue box...
but it's still damn cool.
Can you fix it?
Hey, future-girl--what do
you know about this thing?
I just used it--I don't know
what's under the hood...
My dad's the one
who put it together.
We can't possibly
fix a time machine
from 2036 with the
current technology--
How will we know unless we try?!
Just repair it, Daru!
You have 48 hours...!
You're the only
one who can do it!
Why 48 hours?
Because... it's just
more of a challenge!
Look, if you can
do it in two days,
I'll give you whatever
you ask for, okay?
I'm in! I want a day-long date
with Faris if I pull it off!
Fine. I'll make that
happen somehow.
Hah...! Oh yeah, right.
I can make it
happen...! I swear!
You want this pretty bad.
Damn right I do... Now fix it.
Then let's earn that date!
Oh!
There's something
you gotta do.
You gotta bring us an IBN 5100
when it works again, okay?
Ooh! And an animation
cell of this pose, from...
the 1975 mahou series
"Radical Girl Omit-chan"!
Don't get greedy!
Want me to stay
here and help out?
A good idea, but no...
We need you to
get back to the lab
and finish up construction
on the time-leap machine...
That way, if we miss
our two-day deadline--
Okarin, wait...!
You're forgetting
something really important...!
We gotta help
Suzuha find her dad!
Don't worry about it, Mayuri--
Don't say that...!
I know you used the time-machine
'cause you're on a mission,
but you wanna see
your dad, don'tcha?
You've never even met him!
I really wanna make it happen
for you if I possibly can!
You know your father's
online handle, don't you?
That was just a code-name...
I don't know his real one.
So where did you get Amane?
Got it from my mom...
All I've got to go on
is this one clue...
a pin he used to wear.
Okay, I remember
you saying your dad
was somewhere in Akihabara
this year... Never fear!
'Cause Detective Mayuri
always gets her man!
Find him or not...
She's a good egg.
What's the verdict?
Well, I could be talking
outta my butt here...
but based on what I've been
able to scope out so far,
the insides remind me a lot of
how the Phone Wave operates.
So then, you might be able to
get it working again after all?!
I've been wondering
'bout your dad, y'know...
if maybe he's
somebody close to us.
I mean, he had enough
info on us to know where
we were and what we were up
to when it all went down...
Maybe... He didn't tell
me anything in-person...
All I have is the information
he left for me in his will...
My dad and I never actually
met though, so there's that.
He was conducting his
own time-travel research,
apart from whatever it
was SERN was up to...
trying to undo some
of what they'd done.
Pulling this off is the best way
I know of to honor his memory.
Man... That really
sucks, Suzuha...
But hey, don't
worry about it!
I'll get this all fixed up,
and you're in like Flynn!
And I'm gonna keep looking for
your old man while you're off
doing your time traveling thing.
You just come
back to us, okay?
Oh, and if you could get
me that cel on the down-low...
that'd be cool...
I absolutely loathe
making this stuff...
C'mon, Future
Gadget Lab founder...
Think you ought've invented
a robot to do this by now?
Coffee's an assistant's
sacred duty.
Future Gadget the Second...
New R&amp;D Prototype...
Alpha test number
two-point-six-seven.
Or "Bamboo-Copter
Cam," for short.
On account of the
closed-circuit digital camera
we put in the base.
This is actually practical...!
We could use it to
conduct an aerial search--!
Sadly, the camera
lacks its own gyrometer,
and the spinning footage
is nausea-inducing.
That seems like it's
a pretty basic problem
for version two-point-six-seven.
Ah, but that's the
only one... You see...
Daru tends to name
things on a whim
without much concern
for logic or convention.
Where's Daru?
Still there. Probably
gonna pull an all-nighter.
The Divergence Meter...
You should be the
one to keep this.
It's only fair,
considering you're the one
who built it in the first place.
Remember, the big
picture changes
if the tubes ever reflect a
number bigger than one-point-oh.
And since you're the only one
with the Reading
Steiner ability,
you're the only one who
can track the changes.
Did my future self
hand that over
to you right before he died?
Nu-uh. I've never even laid
eyes on future-Okabe...
Too risky... seeing as how
you're one of the founders
of the resistance
group I'm a part of.
Me, spearhead the resistance?
Surely you jest.
First I let Mayuri die
through no fault of her own...
and then I go tilting at
windmills like a goddamn fool?!
How can you say that?!
What's foolish about wanting
to save the world from tyranny?!
Isn't that a goal
worth dying over?!
Uh... how's it hanging?
I'mma bust out some questions,
yo, so holla at ya boooooy...!
Wordtoyamutha!
Sorry. I don't speak jive.
Well that was
nice and awkward...
I've a button that
I want you to ID...
Have you seen this before?
Or, if you don't
recognize it, then...
perhaps you know
someone who would...?
Nah, it isn't
ringing any bells...
Sorry... I wish I had
something I could tell you.
I can't believe you
said "wordtoyamutha"
to this guy, you freak...
Look, if you remember...
please don't hesitate to call.
Maybe the pin simply
doesn't exist yet...
There's nothing to say
it couldn't be made
in the near future.
Yeah, I guess...
Well... it's okay, maybe it
just wasn't meant to be, y'know?
Hey, at least we tried.
So you're throwing in the towel?
Just like that?
With a full day left?!
Why are you getting s--?
Listen!
Saving Mayuri's life is
my absolute top priority...!
But, you are a lab member
and I intend to help you out!
Dammit, that's just what
friends do for one another!
But if you've already given up,
then what's the
point of even trying?!
Hey, you don't
have to yell about it.
Huh...?
Wow.
Sorry.
Attention, Attention!
What in the... nine hells...?
There was a kidnapping
yesterday--right near here!
The kidnapper was wearing a pin
just like the one on my fliers!
If you could give it a
look it'd be a big help!
Okarin! You're here!
Lookie what I made!
Colorful...
Fliers are a pretty
good idea, huh...?
I was thinking about
everything real hard...
and then it just
kinda hit me! Ooh!
And that's when I grabbed
my markers and got to work!
I think I'll call it
"Operation Attention!
Someone Got Kidnapped."
Advertising a bogus kidnapping
might be takin'
things overboard...
What are you going to do
when the police take
notice of this little--?
Never mind...! Time to go!
How come?
You! Miss...! stop!
I'm sorry, Okarin...
From this moment on,
how 'bout you run all your
plans by me first, yeah?
Just to be safe side...
Huh?
What's with the kung-fu?
Never hurts to be
prepared, that's all.
I'm glad I found you guys.
I got some terrible
news out there...
Go on...
When I went to buy lunch...
I overheard two of the
shop clerks gossiping.
I'm sorry, Suzuha,
but I think your dad might
have kidnapped somebody!
Wait... what...?
What's so funny, huh?
How goes it?
Take a soda break?
This is not my soda of choice
and it's room temperature,
but it's gonna be gone
in like thirty seconds, bro.
Well? Do you think
you can get it working?
Should have it done by tomorrow.
Check this guy out!
We're gonna have time to spare!
Daru's a cheetah when
it comes to tech jobs.
He's so unassuming, I'd never
have known he was a bad-ass.
Don't judge a book by its cover.
Guess you're right.
Lesson learned.
Wanna hop in and
lend a hand, Suzuha...?
The heat in the time-machine
might be oppressive,
but it's nothing
that couldn't be fixed
by stripping down to
our unmentionables...
Why're you such a creeper?!
Wow, Suzuha and Daru make
a pretty good match, huh!
Huh...?! How do you
mean? Predator-prey?
I don't know how
I mean it. But they just do.
What's going on?
Oh, it's nothing... Mayuri's
just being inscrutable again.
I know you gotta
go back to 1975,
but I'm gonna worry
about you a lot...!
And if that time-machine
could hold two people,
I would totally
be going with you!
No offense, but how's
that going to help ?
How can you ask that, silly?!
I'd hold her hand real tight...
and tell her stuff like,
"Don't be scared,
'cause your friend
Mayuri is here for you,
and we're in this thing
together, come rain or shine!"
Listen... There's
something I need to say...
and the chance might
not come up later, so...
If that's how you
feel, go ahead.
Thanks so much... You guys
have really gone to bat for me.
When I first came
back to this time,
I didn't know a single person
around here, you know...?
This place might
be walk in the park
compared to where I'm from...
but to me, it was
still as scary as hell.
But now, just get a load
of all the awesome people
here than I can call friend.
Traveling back to this
period was a good idea...
This was... the most
fun I've ever had.
I'm glad I got this
time to be with you guys,
even if it wasn't for long...
Being a member of the Future
Gadget Lab... it was nice.
Yeah, it was...
It's up to you.
You're the only
chance we've got...
Promise me you'll keep
the world the way it is now.
I promise...
Yes?
Yeah, is this the
"wordtoyamutha" guy?"
You're the street vendor, right?
I just wanted you to know.
Last night, I met
a guy who wanted
a pin like you
were asking about.
You're telling me
you found her father?!
I'll meet you in
the alley in fifteen.