[VICTIM]
If that is all, Lord Ains.
I will take my leave
and return to my duties
in the Great Tomb.
[AINS]
Outstanding work, Victim.
Keep the first floor of
Nazarick safe until we return.
[VICTIM]
With my life, if needed.
[AINS]
Gate.
Hm.
[AURA] Sorry the place
is so shabby, Lord Ains.
When I heard you
would be coming,
I kinda panicked and
turned it into a rush job.
[AINS]
There is no need to apologize.
You built this place for me
out of love and devotion.
In my eyes, it is on par
with even Nazarick.
Thanks!
[AINS]
That being said,
I have to ask: what is that?
[DEMIURGE]
Plain though it may be,
it seemed only right to
prepare a throne for you.
[AINS]
And the bones?
[DEMIURGE]
We assembled the best parts
of various animals.
Griffons, wyverns, and the like.
[AINS]
That's not what I... Nevermind.
[MOMONGA]
I don't care what he says,
those are human skulls.
I can't sit on that!
[AINS]
Shalltear.
I promised you
punishment, didn't I?
This is the perfect
time to administer it.
Your humiliation.
Get down on your
hands and knees.
[pants]
[growls]
Brilliant, my lord. I'm in awe!
[AINS]
Sorry, Demiurge, the throne
will go to waste for now.
It could never
compare to this, Lord.
A Guardian as your throne?
Truly, such a seat is
worthy of the Supreme One,
for it could be
claimed by no other!
This is inspired!
I never would have
thought of it!
[AINS]
Is that so?
[ALBEDO] Lord Ains. May I
be excused from the room?
I will only be a moment.
[AINS]
If you must. Go on.
[ALBEDO]
Thank you very much.
--[ALBEDO growling, screaming]
--[crashing]
I am refreshed,
and ready to serve.
[AINS]
Uh. Great!
[ALBEDO]
Ah yes, Aura.
I'm afraid when I left I
accidently bumped into the wall.
It appears to have been damaged.
Could you fix it up
for me, later?
Sorry for the inconvenience.
No biggie.
[SHALLTEAR panting]
[AINS]
Hm. Shalltear, is this too much?
If so, I could...
It is not too much
at all, my lord!
I take it as the grandest
of rewards, in fact!
Uh--
[MOMONGA] No. I should see
this punishment through.
My... lord....
[MOMONGA]
Besides,
Shalltear's slip-up was a
direct result of my failure.
If I have to suffer through this
in order to punish
myself, so be it.
Still, Peroronicino.
Just how kinky did
you make this chick?
[SHALLTEAR moans]
[AINS]
All right, down to business.
Do you think we effectively
scared the hell out of them?
We were so awesome
it almost scared me!
Without a doubt, Ains my lord.
Their faces were riddled
with delicious fear.
[AINS]
Very good.
Then I suppose we can
call the first stage
of Coctyus' demonstration
a success.
We've set the stage
perfectly for him.
Now.
Why don't we see
how the Lizard Men
are spending their time?
[AINS]
Utterly wasting it.
Save for the Chiefs.
Hm. I don't see the white lizard
or the one with
the magic weapon.
He said his name
was Zaryusu, right?
[AINS]
Ah, yes. I believe you're right.
Maybe he's inside
one of the houses.
[AINS]
It's quite possible.
The Mirror of Remote Viewing
can't offer a view indoors.
At least, not normally.
However, using magic,
I can create a sensory organ.
Then, by linking the two,
we should be able to...
[gasps]
[AINS grunts]
[DEMIURGE]
I can't abide these Lizard Men!
[MARE] Were they wrestling?
I don't get it.
[SHALLTEAR] Repulsive!
They should be punished...
[MARE]
Why are we so angry?
--Wait, were they...?
--[AURA] Totally gross!
--Oh. Oh . Wow.
--No one wants to see that!
[ALBEDO]
One of these days...
[AINS] Well, they are about
to die. In these situations,
the instinct to preserve
the species kicks in.
If movies are to be
believed at least. Hmph!
[DEMIURGE]
Yes, it's only natural.
[ALBEDO]
This much can be forgiven.
[AURA]
Right? Totally fine!
Leave it to Lord Ains
to know what's up.
[AINS]
All of you, quiet!
[GUARDIANS gasp]
[AINS] That took the wind
right out of my sails.
[MOMONGA]
Oh, crap!
Was that too soon
for Aura and Mare?
What am I supposed to tell them
if they ask where
babies come from?
Turn to Albedo? No, bad idea.
Demiurge? He would
explain it clinically.
Solid choice.
Shalltear?
Huh. Actually, that doesn't
sound as bad as I thought.
Whatever. That's a
problem for future Ains.
[AINS clears throat] Aura, since
we have yet to see any activity
from them at this stage,
it is highly unlikely
that we will run into
whoever attacked Shalltear.
But a slim chance
is still a chance.
Be vigilant and mind
your surroundings.
[AURA]
Right!
[AINS]
If there is an Yggdrasil player
on the Lizard Men's
side we will give them
one chance to ally with us.
If they refuse,
we must destroy them
to keep information
from getting out.
[ZARYUSU, SHASURYU]
That monstrosity is Cocytus?
[COCYTUS]
Listen carefully.
Do not hold back,
no matter what happens.
Lord Ains is watching, and only
your best will satisfy him.
But, before we start...
Ice pillars!
[COCYTUS] I accept all of you
as honorable warriors,
so please forgive any affront
my next statement might cause.
Beyond this gate
lies your death.
Should you choose
to step beyond it,
know that it will be your last.
How 'bout that?
Monster with manners.
You should stay back, for now.
In fact, go back to the village.
[WARRIOR 5A]
Wha--? No!
Let us fight with you,
Chief Shasuryu!
It's not cowardly to withdraw!
Nor is living!
[WARRIOR 5B]
Then let us--
But some of us don't
have that option!
You would not accept
us as your Chiefs
if we refused to fight.
In fact, I hope you would
cut us down yourselves.
But we want to fight!
Please, don't rob
us of the honor!
Let us old timers have this.
You'll all get your
chance at honor someday.
Sorry to keep you
waiting, Cocytus!
For the ancestors!
[LIZARD MEN yell]
[COCYTUS]
I hate to do this to warriors,
but I must reduce
your numbers quickly.
[COCYTUS]
Frost Aura!
Hm... Seems about right.
[COCYTUS]
Ranged weapons won't hurt me.
All the Guardians of Nazarick
have acquired items
or skills that grant
us full resistance.
[KYUKU yells]
[COCYTUS]
God Slaying Emperor Blade!
Martial Art.
Iron Natural Weapon.
Iron Skin!
[groans]
[COCYTUS] Not bad at all.
The sword, I mean.
[pants]
[groans]
[COCYTUS]
You're just in the way.
[ZARYUSU yells]
Maximize Magic!
Mass Slight Cure Wounds.
[gasps]
[COCYTUS grunts]
[grunts] Damn.
[COCYTUS] You still
have the will to fight?
Then I shall return this to you.
[COCYTUS] That's getting
annoying. Piercing Icicles!
[groans]
[yelling]
[gasps]
[panting]
[COCYTUS] Amazing.
Lord Ains predicted this.
That the two of you
would last till the end.
And sure enough,
here you are. Be proud.
How are you holding up
over there, brother?
Bad, I'm afraid. The pain
is still throbbing.
But don't worry, I got
a few more swings in me.
All right. Then that'll
have to be enough.
That last spell really
took it out of me,
my magic power is drained.
One more cast and I'll pass out.
You always did push yourself
too hard, brother.
But, all the same.
As long as I have a drop
of blood left to give,
Frost Pain and I won't give up!
[COCYTUS]
That was a fine war cry.
You always did have
a way with words, brother.
We will meet our death together.
Now, come.
Let's not keep our guest
waiting any longer.
[COCYTUS]
I am in no rush.
Far be it from me to
get between brothers
saying their goodbyes.
[COCYTUS] Prepare yourselves.
No, forgive me.
You were prepared for death
long before we crossed blades.
May I have your names
before we finish?
Shasuryu Shasha.
Zaryusu Shasha.
[COCYTUS] I shall
remember you as warriors.
As long as I live,
you will not be forgotten.
Also, I must
apologize yet again.
Normally, I would face
you with a weapon
in each hand, but you
are not strong enough
for me to draw them.
It would be an insult
to go all out.
To both of you.
That's a damn shame, isn't it?
It sure is. Let's go!
I'm on it. Earth Bind!
[COCYTUS]
My defense cannot be penetrated
by one whose magic
level is inferior.
Don't waste your time!
[ZARYUSU]
Icy Burst!
[ZARYUSU yells]
[SHASURYU yells]
[COCYTUS]
Want to take me by surprise?
Then don't scream
like a banshee!
[COCYTUS] Hm? Blood? You did
all of that for this?
[COCYTUS]
Magnificent.
I'm sorry.
I have a skill that
temporarily negates any attack
from weak magic weapons.
Unfortunately for you,
that means, as long
as it's activated,
your effort was
meaningless at best.
[COCYTUS]
Well fought!
[blow lands]
[AINS] Cocytus, you fought
admirably today.
[COCYTUS]
And I always will, Lord.
[AINS] That being said,
giving them the stick
is no longer permitted.
You must lead them
only by the carrot.
It must not be
a reign of terror.
[COCYTUS]
I understand, Supreme One.
[AINS]
Very good.
Lift your heads, Guardians,
and hear my words.
The rule over the
Lizard Men villages
is assigned to Cocytus.
If he ever requests
your support,
assist him to the
best of your ability.
[COCYTUS]
Lord Ains.
If I may, what do you intend
to do with the bodies
of those Lizard Men?
[AINS]
Could you be more specific?
[COCYTUS]
Sorry.
The one called Zaryusu
and his brother Shasuryu.
[AINS] Ah, yes. Let's
recover their bodies.
I would like to see the kind
of undead they would make
if they were not
created using my skill.
[COCYTUS]
I think we can do better.
[AINS]
What's on your mind?
[COCYTUS]
I admit they were weak.
But I also cannot deny they
possessed the brilliance
of true warriors.
I truly believe they
have the potential
to become stronger
than we assume,
if given the chance.
Unless I'm mistaken,
you have yet to conduct
any more experiments
with resurrection.
What if you were
to use them for that?
[MOMONGA] The brilliance
of warriors, is it?
[AINS]
I see.
They're too precious
to waste, then?
Is there anyone
who can represent
the Lizard Men villages?
[COCYTUS]
There was one who did not
participate in the fighting.
The white female lizard
with powerful druidic magic.
[MOMONGA]
That one? Interesting.
[AINS]
All right.
How long will it take
to bring her before me?
[COCYTUS]
Forgive me.
I had assumed you
would ask that.
She is already waiting
in the next room.
[AINS]
Well done. I'm pleased, Cocytus.
Your judgement was
right on the mark.
Please, show the female in now.
[COCYTUS]
Lord.
[AINS]
Tell me your name.
[CRUSCH]
Of course.
Whatever you wish,
Lord Ains Ooal Gown.
Supreme ruler of death.
I am priest and
guide to the tribes.
Crusch Lulu.
[AINS]
Thanks for coming.
Of course, my lord.
Please, accept the absolute
allegiance of my people.
We will serve you
without resistance.
[AINS]
Hm.
[gasps]
[AINS]
Now that that's done.
I have a special
request for you.
If there is anything this
humble servant can do,
you have but to ask it,
Lord. I'm listening.
[AINS] This isn't an order.
More a "favor."
Accept it, and I will
return Zaryusu to life.
Is that possible?
[AINS]
Life and death are nothing more
than states of being.
To move someone between the two
is a simple matter
to one such as I.
I see. Then, what is
it that you desire?
How can this slave serve you?
Do you wish to
partake of my body?
[growls]
[AINS]
No. Not exactly.
[AINS clears throat] Nothing
like that. It's quite simple.
I want you to keep an eye
on your fellow tribesman.
Make sure there are none
who would betray me.
There are no such
Lizard Men, I assure you.
[AINS] I am not foolish
enough to believe that.
Not even for a second.
[AINS] I'm offering you
a miracle, Crusch Lulu.
But I cannot wait
for you to decide
where your loyalties truly lie.
Seize this moment
and do as I ask,
or lose the chance forever.
What is most important
to you now?
I want you to think hard on
that while I present my offer.
Then I expect an answer.
I want you to
covertly keep watch
on your fellow Lizard Men
from the inside.
I will cast a special
magic spell on Zaryusu
when I revive him.
If at any point I feel
that you have betrayed me,
the spell will
kill him instantly.
And I'll make sure
you see it happen.
Spying on your people
is a small price to pay
to have the love of your
life back, wouldn't you say?
[MOMONGA] Too bad that spell
doesn't really exist.
[AINS]
Time's up, Crusch Lulu.
What is your decision?
[AINS whispers] Even if
she declines, do nothing.
[AINS]
Well? I'm done waiting.
Make your choice.
[CRUSCH muffled]
Zaryusu. Zaryusu!
[CRUSCH]
Come back.
Please. Open your eyes!
Zaryusu?
Zaryusu!
[garbled speach] Crusch?
Why are you...?
Is this the afterlife?
Were you killed by that monster?
[AINS] You're alive, but the
confusion will last for a while.
Apparently you've lost
some levels, as well.
I guess I can reason that
little has changed
from Yggdrasil.
[gasps]
[ZARYUSU]
Wh-What in the...?
[AINS] Zaryusu Shasha, first,
allow me to congratulate you
on your resurrection.
What? Resurrection?
You can bring the
dead back to life?
Truly, your power
cannot be rivaled.
[ZARYUSU]
Great One.
I humbly pledge my
eternal allegiance to you.
[AINS]
Very good.
In the name of Ains Ooal Gown,
I accept your fidelity.
All we ask in return,
is to prosper.
[AINS]
Is that it? Fear not.
I can definitely promise
prosperity to all under my rule.
I offer my thanks.
[AINS]
Your speech is still faltering.
A little rest
should remedy that.
Take some time to recover,
then speak with Cocytus
about what is to follow.
[ZARYUSU]
Just a moment, Lord.
[AINS]
Hm?
What about Zenberu
and my brother?
[AINS] Their bodies
should still be around.
[ZARYUSU]
Please, Great One.
May I ask you to bring
them back, as well?
[AINS] I don't see what
I would gain from it.
Then, why did you
only resurrect me?
Zenberu and my
brother are strong.
I'm certain that they could
be of great use to you.
[AINS]
I see.
Safeguard their bodies.
I'll consider your request.
Aura, time to go.
Right!
Could I play with the
Hydra sometime, my lord?
We managed to survive.
Some more than others.
[ZARYUSU sighs]
You'll be fine, love. I swear.
Just try to focus on recovering.
We can worry about
everything else
when you have
your strength back.
[ZARYUSU]
Yeah.
As long as I can
rest in your arms.
[AINS] Sebas and Solution
continue to collect information
in the capital of Re-Estize.
Working with extreme caution,
they seek to uncover
the identity of those
who attacked Shalltear.
But they have yet to
find even a shadow.
The days seem peaceful
on the surface,
at least until Sebas
meets a certain girl
on a dimly lit street.
Chapter Six: "Those Who Pick Up,
Those Who Are Picked Up".
Miracles do not happen to
those who merely pray.