[ZENBERU]
I'm only saying this once!
If I don't make it out
of this duel in one piece,
this guy's the new
chief, understand?
[LIZARD MAN 3A]
He can't be serious!
And if anyone's got
a problem with it,
I'd be happy to rip
their head off.
[LIZARD MEN gasp]
Don't you dare hold back.
I don't want there to be
any doubt how I rank
against Frost Pain's new master.
Very well, then.
One last thing.
If I should die today...
Yeah, yeah.
I'll make sure your
female leaves unharmed.
She isn't mine.
Not yet, at least.
[gasps]
Heh, You're really making
a bid for her, huh?
That walking shrub must
be one hell of a female
to catch your eye.
Extremely so. Yes.
[yelps]
Well, then, perhaps
I'll rip that bush off
and see for myself
if I win this thing.
[ZARYUSU] Bad move.
Now there's no way I'll lose.
You're really head over
heels for her, aren'tcha?
Yes, from the moment we met.
[CRUSCH whines]
Ha! Then beat me
and prove it to her!
That's exactly what
I intend to do.
[yells]
[BOTH grunting]
[gasps]
[ZARYUSU grunts]
[yelling]
Ha, ha! Few have
survived that one.
So, you're a Monk.
If I were you,
I'd use Frost Pain's special
ability before it's too late.
Yes, another bearer
of the weapon
defeated me long ago.
These wounds are a memento
from our great battle.
I'm stronger than I was then.
If you keep holding back,
you're through.
Sorry, I don't intend
to use it on you.
Tch. What, you think
I'm not good enough?
After trading blows with me,
you should know that
that isn't this case.
Sorry, I went too far.
You didn't deserve
such disrespect.
But don't expect me
to show you mercy!
[ZENBERU]
Iron Skin!
[LIZARD MEN cheer]
[ZENBERU, ZARYUSU grunting]
[yells]
[BOTH panting]
Dammit all.
Enough, I've lost.
[sighs]
[CRUSCH]
Are you okay?
Just relax, I'll heal you up.
Middle Cure Wounds.
Tryin' to make me jealous?
It's working.
Any chance I could get
some heals, white stuff?
Sure thing.
That was a whole
new level of hurt.
Feels like I'm frozen
clear to the bone.
Thank Frost Pain.
It carries a chill
within the blade.
And delivers a small
amount of cold damage
to anyone who strikes
or is struck by it.
So, just block and your opponent
does all the work for you.
Here I thought it was just
like any other hunk of ice
if you didn't use its special
ability. Guess I was naive.
Now that I've proven my strength
to you and your tribe,
could we finally
get down to business?
Not yet.
There's something
we must do, first.
To prepare.
These annoying talks are easier
when you're drunk off your ass.
Let's get started!
You cannot be serious!
Perfect timing, plant monster!
So, finished yet?
Broadly speaking,
What are we going to do?
[ZENBERU]
Huh? We're gonna fight 'em!
What did you expect?
You really are brutish,
you know that?
Aw, cut it out.
You're gonna make me blush.
So, this a fight we can win?
I don't know. That sky herald.
Do you remember what it said
when it appeared to you?
No, I was taking a nap.
"Offer up your
pitiful resistance,
so that the Great One may
take delight in your failure."
That's galling.
Cocky bastards are lookin'
down on us from the start.
Yes.
Our foe holds us
in complete contempt.
Their force must be as
large as their ego.
Even so, we'll take their hubris
and ram it down their throats.
Yeah! Now you're talkin'.
But, even if we give their
pride a good thrashing,
what's the point if we die?
I'll choose life over a
needless death every time.
Even if it's a life
bound in chains.
Listen to them celebrating.
[ZARYUSU] Do you think
we'd be allowed to do this
if we were under their rule?
[CRUSCH]
There's a chance that we could.
Right?
[ZARYUSU]
I'm not sure.
I doubt that a being who
would enjoy watching us die
has any concept of mercy,
or even cares to know it.
True enough.
What I'm trying to say,
though, is don't get killed.
I won't.
I'm still waiting on
your answer, after all.
[gasps]
At last, we're nearing
the front line.
[ZARYUSU]
Yeah, the sky herald said
that Razor Tail would be first.
Those from the other tribes
are probably already there.
This battle will be legendary!
Welcome back, little brother.
Good news?
Indeed.
My trip went even better
than I could have hoped.
You'll see.
[SHASURYU] What's the deal with
the creepy plant creature?
She's the love of my life.
[CRUSCH gasps]
I hope to marry, after the--
[yelps]
There, ya see?
I told ya you'd knock that
arrow one of these days.
It was just a matter of
finding the right female.
Now then.
I'm chief of the
Green Claw tribe.
Shasuryu Shasha.
Your timing couldn't
be more perfect--
our scouts have just returned.
I have a feeling their
report will be interesting.
[SUKYU] The enemy's
stronghold is in the forest.
Their entire force is
roughly 5,000 strong.
Made of mostly zombies
and skeletons.
Unfortunately, we weren't
able to locate
this "Great One" of theirs.
So.
Our force numbers roughly 1,300.
They outnumber us
by over three to one.
We just have to take on
three or four of 'em each,
right? Sounds easy to me.
[ALL but ZENBERU groan]
First, we need to make
a proper chain of command.
Perhaps we could form
brigades centered around
each of the chiefs.
No.
We should have a separate unit,
consisting of only the chiefs.
[SHASURYU]
Hm.
Traveler want to make unit
of elite warriors, yes?
That's right.
The enemy's numbers are great.
Taking out their leader
may be the only way to win.
And if he's protected
by stronger foes,
it will take our
strongest to do the job.
But, won't that leave our side
without commanders, too?
True.
Then we'll have the
elite unit issue orders
to the head hunters
from the rear,
and coordinate things
as the situation demands.
[CHIEFS]
Mm.
We have four days
until the enemy strikes.
Make sure no one wastes
a single moment.
[COCYTUS]
Message.
Attention all forces. Advance!
[AINS]
Report.
Has Cocytus begun the
attack on their village?
[ALBEDO] Yes. According
to Entoma's report,
nothing on the field has
exceeded your expectations.
As you ordered, Lord Ains,
Cocytus is remaining
at the command post,
and they are attacking with only
the forces they have been given.
[AINS]
I see.
It isn't the outcome
I was hoping for,
but we may yet get
something out of it.
Ah--
It begins.
Everyone!
We've been preparing
for this moment!
We know, the enemy is great.
But there is nothing
to be afraid of!
For the first time in history,
we have ceased to be
separate tribes.
Through this alliance,
all Lizard Men are now one!
I know our ancestor spirits
are proud of what they see.
And they will protect us!
For them, we will
send these bastards
back to the grave!
[LIZARD MEN yell]
To victory!
[LIZARD MEN cheer]
They're using the cavalry
to flank our line
so they can surround
and crush them.
Then it's time for us to make
our first play, as well,
don't you think?
[HEAD GREEN CLAW HUNTER]
Shoot them!
[LIZARD MEN screaming]
[ZENBERU] Are they thumbin'
their noses at us?
[SHASURYU] I can't make
sense of their strategy.
Is it possible they're acting
without a commander?
If so, they must think they
can win by numbers alone.
Bastards are mocking us.
Still, we should
reduce their force
as much as possible before
they make their next big play.
Tch. I hate waiting around.
[KYUKU]
Patience, Zenberu.
We'll reveal the elite
unit once their leader
graces us with his presence,
then you'll have all the
action you can handle and more.
[gasps]
[CRUSCH]
Incredible.
Summoning swamp elementals
that fast isn't easy.
We can do truly amazing
things working together.
Indeed.
After that last war,
all we did was exchange
bits of information.
Once this battle's behind us,
there are many things
I would like to try.
[CRUSCH]
I couldn't agree more.
[COCYTUS] I underestimated
the Lizard Men's morale.
They're resilient.
[COCYTUS]
Message.
Demiurge.
[DEMIURGE]
Hello, my friend.
Why are you messaging me?
Aren't you in the
middle of a campaign?
[COCYTUS]
Actually...
[DEMIURGE]
I see.
Still, that doesn't explain
why you reached out to me.
[COCYTUS]
I need advice.
If this defeat were mine
alone, I could accept it.
But, if this continues,
I will disgrace the Supreme One,
and that cannot happen.
[DEMIURGE] Are you sure
Lord Ains wanted you to win?
[COCYTUS] I'm not sure
what you mean by that.
Think about it.
Why did Lord Ains raise an army
of such low-level
servants for you?
It's possible that
this was a test.
Perhaps he wished for you
to think for yourself.
To gather intelligence
on the enemy
and adjust your strategy
to ensure victory.
This could be a plan
to promote your awareness.
[COCYTUS]
Hm...
Additionally, Nazarick and
Lord Ains were never mentioned.
And you were forbidden from
joining in the battle yourself.
--Which would mean...
--[beeping]
[COCYTUS]
Hm. Demiurge?
[DEMIURGE]
I'm sorry, Cocytus.
Something urgent has come up
that I must attend to.
I wish you victory.
[COCYTUS] It's too late to
find out anything useful here.
I have no choice but
to send in the reserves.
[COCYTUS]
Elder Lich Iguva.
I have a task for you. Advance!
Show the Lizard Men your might!
[yells]
[HEAD GREEN CLAW WARRIOR]
Okay, get the seriously wounded
back to the village!
The rest of you, follow us!
We're taking the fight--
[LIZARD MEN yell]
Retreat!
That one isn't like
the other rabble.
Head back and tell
the chiefs about this!
We'll make sure
you aren't roasted!
[WARRIOR 3A]
Just don't take too long!
Running won't save you, pests.
I will ensure His victory.
Ha!
[WARRIOR 3A screams]
[WARRIOR 3B screams]
[HEAD GREEN CLAW
WARRIOR screams]
It looks like we're up
this time, that's for sure.
Yeah. That one is
far more powerful.
Perhaps the commander
we've been waiting for.
Even if it isn't, it's obvious
he's their ace in reserve.
Agreed.
But how are we supposed
to get close enough?
The range of his spells
has to be at least 100 meters.
You're right. There is a way.
Zaryusu?
[IGUVA]
Fools.
That slow moving beast
will succumb to my hellfire
long before it
closes the distance!
Insufferable brute!
[gasps] Why won't it stop?
Why does it keep coming?
[ZARYUSU]
Icy Burst!
Thank you, Rororo.
Impossible!
[ZARYUSU]
Icy Burst!
Shoot as many as you like!
I'll counter every last one!
Then I'll have to
switch things up a bit.
Try blocking this! Lightning!
Move, I'll handle this!
Resistance Massive Unleash!
Nice save!
[laughs] That was too easy.
Very well. Summon Undead four!
[IGUVA] I am an Elder Lich
in service to the Great One.
You can't win!
If you bow your heads.
I will make sure your
deaths are painless.
[ZARYUSU]
I think I speak for all of us.
Go to hell!
You ingrate!
That was your last
chance at mercy.
Your suffering will be such
that in the end
you'll beg for death!
Not if we send you
back to the pit
you crawled out of!
Take care of him, Zaryusu!
Succumb to fear. Terror!
[CRUSCH]
Lion's Heart!
You're okay!
Pestiferous harpy.
Lightning strike!
[CRUSCH screams]
Crusch, no!
--[IGUVA] Light--
--Too slow!
Magic won't help you this close!
Don't underestimate me,
Lizard Man!
Last one! You're clear, Zaryusu!
I'll just be over here.
[ZARYUSU groans]
I'll help. Middle Cure Wounds!
You won't best me!
[IGUVA] How dare you look
down on me like this!
[ZARYUSU]
An AOE spell at this range? No!
Icy Burst!
[ZARYUSU grunting]
[IGUVA] Ha. Cold doesn't
work on me, simpleton.
You were only hurting yourself.
Once I find your frozen corpse,
I'll feed it to the bugs.
[yells]
[screams]
Damn you.
I am a servant created
by the Great One himself!
I refuse to fall
to a filthy reptile!
I will feel your bones
crush in my hands!
Now, die, Lizard Man!
[ZARYUSU]
Rororo. Zenberu. Crusch.
[ZARYUSU growls]
Impossible! How are you moving?
Tell me how!
[ZARYUSU]
You're... finished!
Please. Forgive me, Lord Ains.
[LIZARD MEN cheer]
[LIZARD MAN 3K]
The traveler did it!
[ENTOMA]
'Scuse me, Lord Cocytus.
Lord Ains has requested
your presence at once.
[COCYTUS]
Understood, thank you.
[COCYTUS] Nicely done.
But, it was truly a close one.
[AINS] The Lizard Men
successfully survive the horde
of undead that was
sent against them
and celebrate their
unexpected victory.
Meanwhile, the defeated Cocytus
in summoned back to Nazarick
to explain his defeat
before his master.
Ains does not blame the
apologetic floor guardian
for his loss.
[AINS] Chapter 4:
"Army of Death".
What will you gain
from this experience.