[MESSENGER 1A]
I am herald to the Great One,
sent to deliver a message.
Henceforth, death's
gaze is upon you!
The Great One has
mobilized an army
to destroy your pitiful race!
Nevertheless,
you have graciously
been granted time to organize
whatever desperate resistance
your people can pull together.
Eight days from now,
destruction shall descend
upon this land,
and claim your clan as the
second offering of death
among the lake's tribes.
The second?
[MESSENGER 1A]
Offer your pathetic resistance,
so that the Great One may
take delight in your failure,
as his minions cut you down.
Death comes in eight days!
Do not forget!
[HEAD GREEN CLAW PRIESTESS] We
all saw those malevolent clouds.
That was likely
fourth tier magic.
The spell is "Control Cloud."
Fourth tier magic, huh?
It takes a truly powerful
magic caster to use
spells of that magnitude,
even I can only manage
as high as second tier.
We should evacuate
with all due haste.
Are you really suggesting
we run away without
putting up a fight?
That thing said
we have eight days.
We still have time.
Let's see what the
enemy does until then.
[SHASURYU]
Hm...
Huh?
Well, between
running or fighting,
I choose fighting.
You're nothing but a
lowly traveler, Zaryusu.
You're lucky to be sitting here.
Shut your mouth or lose your--!
[TRIBE gasps]
Anyone with knowledge is welcome
to participate in
this meeting, understood?
It would be unwise
not to listen to him.
[ELDER 2B] Chief Shasuryu,
you shouldn't be giving him
special treatment just
because he's your brother.
Failing to heed the words
of the educated is an act
of the foolish and prideful.
And no warrior would
disregard the opinion
of he who holds Frost Pain.
[ELDERS grunt]
[SHASURYU]
Hm. So, why should we fight?
Because it's our only choice.
Can we win?
Of course we can!
No. Not if things stay
the same as they are now.
What are you talking about?
I believe this foe is confident
because he is aware
of our lack of forces.
If that is the case,
we need to throw
his reckoning off.
Now.
Do you remember
our most recent war?
'Course we do.
[HEAD GREEN CLAW PRIESTESS]
There's no way we could forget.
This marsh was the
home to seven tribes.
There was our tribe, Green Claw.
The skilled hunters
of Small Fang.
Razor Tail, whose
defenses were legendary.
The war-loving Dragon Tusk.
The moderate Yellow Speckle.
The great fighters
of Sharp Edge.
And Red Eye with their
priestly abilities.
Then the food shortage struck.
All seven tribes ended up
competing with each other
for what little there was.
Until, finally,
it turned into an all out war,
and we made an alliance
with Small Fang and Razor Tail
against Yellow Speckle
and Sharp Edge.
The three of us claimed victory,
and the two defeated tribes
were absorbed into Dragon Tusk,
who stayed out of the fighting.
And why does that matter?
That thing said this village
would be the "second."
Which must mean he
intends to destroy
all of the tribes in order.
You're suggesting
we join forces again.
But is eight days long enough
to mount a meaningful defense?
I'm fairly certain
our former allies,
Small Fang and
Razor Tail will form
an alliance with us once again.
Let there be no mistake.
What I'm suggesting
entails all the tribes.
Brother. We need
to form an alliance
with Dragon Tusk and Red Eye.
We can't!
Dragon Tusk now consists
of the survivors from the two
tribes we beat in the last war.
There can be no
alliance between us.
Plus, we have no
interaction with Red Eye.
This seems impossible.
A five-tribe union. I'm for it.
Who will be the envoy
to these two tribes?
I volunteer.
Even though you're a traveler?
That's right.
If they refuse to listen
because I'm a traveler,
then they're on their own.
[SHASURYU]
Hm...
I insist you take
the chief's seal.
[TRIBE gasps, murmurs]
I am honored.
[gasps]
Hello, brother.
[SHASURYU]
Hm?
[ZARYUSU]
Rororo!
I've always believed
that you should've
become chief instead of me.
If that would've
happened, I never
could have traveled,
which means I wouldn't know
how to farm fish
for the village.
But why do you say
such things now?
[SHASURYU]
You could have learned
those farming practices
here as well.
The bright young men like
yourself should be in charge.
Be the ones who shoulder
the weight of a village.
[ZARYUSU]
Brother...
Tell me.
Are tribe alliances
really all you're after?
[gasps] What does that mean?
What are you implying?
It's hard to overlook
some of the similarities
between now and the past war,
such as diminishing
tribe skirmishes and our
increased population.
That's enough.
You shouldn't say anything else.
Just as I thought.
There's no other way.
Not if we want to avoid
a repeat of the last war.
What are you planning
to do with them
if the other tribes refuse
to make an alliance with us?
If I can't persuade them,
we'll attack.
You'd actually kill
our fellow kinsmen?
That I would.
I do understand. It's the
survival of the tribe.
But what happens
if the man in charge
doesn't consider
that possibility?
Rororo!
Time to head out.
Tell me, brother.
What will the count be?
Ten from warrior class,
12 hunters,
three high-priests, 70 males,
100 females, and the children.
I would say.
Good to know.
If it comes down to it,
I should be able to use those
numbers as bargaining tools.
[SHASURYU chuckles]
It's sure gotten big.
Yeah, but he was a lot
smaller than this
when I found him.
[SHASURYU]
Ha! That's hard to believe.
The first time you brought
him to the village,
I'd thought he was already
too big to handle.
Do you remember that?
Don't do anything crazy!
Come back safely!
Don't worry.
I will carry this plan
through to perfection
and then come home.
Just sit tight.
See you soon.
[door clatters]
[DEMIURGE]
Hm.
It has been far too long,
Assistant Butler.
Oh, hey.
It has been a long time,
Lord Demiurge.
Is Lord Ains in there by chance?
'Fraid not.
He's visiting the human
village for several days.
However, Lady Albedo is inside.
That's too bad.
Isn't it strange, Eclair,
for an assistant butler
such as yourself
to be here without your boss?
Lord Sebas is away on business,
so I must work twice as
hard to make up for him.
That's why I just
finished making
specific arrangements
with Lady Albedo.
I guess you're right.
Now that he's gone,
Nahzareek's ninth floor
is safe in your more than
capable flippers, eh?
Correct!
I treat this extra work
as preparation for when
I'm finally calling the shots,
and ruling the Great
Tomb of Nazarick.
Right you are.
Keep at it, little guy.
After all, your creator,
Lady Ankoro Mocchi Mochi,
did design you to act that way.
So then.
How exactly are you planning
on achieving that goal?
[ECLAIR]
By cleaning, of course.
I dare say there's
no one in Nazarick half
as thorough at cleaning as me!
After I'm done
with the restroom,
it's safe to eat off both
the floor and the toilet!
[gasps] Truly outstanding!
I'm Zaryusu Shasha
of the Green Claw tribe!
I wish to speak to the
tribal chief of Red Eye!
Zaryusu Shasha of Green Claw,
the one who holds the tribe
together will see you now.
Huh. I wonder why
it's not the chief.
Right through here.
[ELDER 2C] The one who holds the
tribe together has requested
to speak with you one-on-one.
I am Zaryusu Shasha
of the Green Claw tribe.
I bring an urgent request.
[CRUSCH]
Come in.
Thank you for coming today.
[gasping]
[CRUSCH chuckles]
Even the bearer of Frost Pain,
one of the Four Great
Treasures appears
to find my body bizarre-looking.
Uh, is something the matter?
[squeals]
[gasps]
[yelps] Please, excuse me.
Think nothing of it.
I am the acting chief
of the Red Eye tribe.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
My name is Crusch Lulu.
[ZARYUSU grunts]
Now, may I ask what
brought a member
of the Green Claw tribe
over to our village?
Please marry me.
U-Uh...
Huh?
M-Marry you?
That isn't the reason
I came here, mind you.
I realize it's probably
confusing that I didn't
settle that matter first before
offering up such a proposal.
But I cannot ignore such
strong feelings of love.
Love?
But, we... Huh?
A-Again, excuse my rudeness.
Feel free to give me an answer
once we get to know
each other better.
Know each other?
Uh--
[CRUSCH] It comes as
quite a surprise to me
that you're not afraid of my
white body, like others are.
You see, every now
and then an albino,
such as myself, is born
into the Red Eye tribe.
They always exhibit an
aptitude for some talent,
and in my case that talent
turned out to be
priestly powers.
That's the reason
we always end up
second in command
under the tribal chief.
As white as the snow
blanketing yonder mountains.
[gasps]
Beautiful color.
What did you say?
[growls]
[ZARYUSU grunts]
[BOTH panting]
Why would you touch me
without asking first?
I've fallen in love with you.
And odds are, we could
both get ourselves killed
in this upcoming battle.
I don't want any regrets.
I'm at a loss.
The bearer of Frost Pain
is actually prepared to die?
Did you see the monster
that delivered the message?
I did.
That horrible creature
emitted screams
that rattled the mind,
neutralizing almost any attack
by non-enchanted weapons.
Terrifying indeed.
Last time I encountered it,
I had no choice but to flee.
We druids can help with that.
We possess the
power to temporarily
imbue swords with magic.
Are you able to ward against
mental attacks as well?
Most priests can, in fact,
bolster one's resistance.
However, protecting the mind
from confusion is different.
I'm the only one who can do so.
[gasps]
What number did it
say your tribe was?
It said we were fourth in line.
I see.
Tell me, what are you
planning to do about it?
Uh...
I'm going to be
straight with you.
[ZARYUSU]
If the Red Eye tribe evacuates,
will you be able to
carry on your lifestyle
in a strange location?
[CRUSCH]
It would be difficult.
[ZARYUSU] So then, if all
five tribes in the area
were to evacuate at once.
What would happen?
What if we couldn't
find enough food?
What if the fish we
depend on grew scarce?
Would we end up killing
each other off this time?
You don't mean
that fighting a battle
we may not win
would be a better...
Indeed.
I'm taking into
account depopulation,
including the other tribes.
Crusch Lulu,
Green Claw requests an alliance
with the Red Eye tribe.
Please think this through.
If you were to refuse us,
we'd have to challenge
your tribe to battle first.
To prevent a tribe
from running away
and establishing a
numerical superiority
in a new land, correct?
My hope is, if we
form an alliance,
and are then defeated,
that once we settle
in a new land
the chances of intertribal
warfare are decreased.
Uh?
We won't be separate tribes.
Instead, we'll be
allies who bravely
fought alongside each other.
That makes sense.
I have to know.
Red Eye abstained from fighting
during the last battle.
How did your people
manage to not starve?
Do I really have to
answer that question?
I need to know.
Was it priestly power?
Or by some other means
you've kept hidden from us?
It may prove to be
our salvation.
Definitely not.
[gasps]
It won't be our salvation.
What we engaged in
back then was cannibalism.
We fed on the meat
of our fallen friends.
[gasps]
At that time,
our tribe found itself
in a dire situation due
to the shortage of food
and unwillingness
to fight for it.
But then, one day,
our chief came to the
village with food.
Bright red fresh meat.
I'm not going to lie to you,
we were vaguely aware
of where it came from.
Because, whenever the
chief brought us meat,
it was always after he expelled
families from the village
for breaking our laws.
We all simply closed our eyes
and ate the only food we had.
In order to survive.
But yet, it wasn't
as though we could
live like that forever.
The pent-up frustration
soon came to a head,
and manifested into
the form of mutiny.
As the second most
powerful leader in the tribe,
I became the banner
they rallied to.
And we rose in revolt
against the chief.
The fighting divided
the village in two,
but we managed to
secure a victory
thanks to our greater numbers.
The chief refused to back down
even at the very end.
He was on the verge of death
after countless wounds.
And at the moment he was
struck by a fatal blow,
he looked into
my eyes and smiled.
It was a genuine, sweet
smile without any anger.
Through the death of the chief.
Our tribe was brought
back together.
And with our new
decrease in numbers,
came the great gift of recovery
from our dwindling
food situation.
But our rebellion was
in the wrong, wasn't it?
The chief faced reality,
and found the only logical way
through our grave circumstance.
I can't ever shake
those thoughts.
We're neither omniscient
nor omnipotent.
Who knows. I might have
done the same thing you did.
Crusch, you don't
need my solace.
There are no right answers.
We all live with regrets.
And now, the only
thing left to do
is just keep walking.
Even as we afflict
woe unto our feet.
You, too must keep walking.
At least, that's what I think.
I apologize for my disgrace.
I see no disgrace in you.
What's more, do I
look like someone
who's foolish enough
to judge others?
When they're doing their best
to move on from their past,
and being tormented
by old actions?
Your soul is beautiful.
[gasps]
You have a way with words.
Let me ask again.
Which policy will
Red Eye adopt this time?
We had a tribal meeting
and decided to evacuate.
Really?
Are your feelings
the same, Crusch Lulu.
After talking with me today?
It is your decision to make.
The previous chief smiled
at you during his death,
meaning he was leaving the
tribe's future in your hands.
If true, it is time
to fulfil that calling.
I have but one question.
How many do you plan on
letting escape as refugees?
Well...
One hundred of the females
and 70 males, 12 hunters,
ten warriors, three priests,
and the children.
And what about the rest?
If we fail, they will die.
I see how it is.
Let me make one thing clear.
We're not fighting this
battle just to die.
We're fighting to claim victory!
I was hoping to hear
you say such things.
The Red Eye will fight
beside Green Claw.
I'll make sure the
chief's last smile
was not meaningless.
This alliance will ensure
that the Red Eye tribe
have enough survivors
to carry on.
[ZARYUSU]
I'm grateful.
[yawns]
[CRUSCH]
Good morning.
Uh, yeah. 'Morning.
Looks like you were able
to bring the tribe around
without any issues.
[CRUSCH] I'm grateful that you
stayed up so late last night
talking them through it.
Our warriors should be equipped
and ready to leave
within the day.
The evacuees will be
gone soon, too.
Zaryusu. What are you
planning to do?
I'll be heading over to the
Dragon Tusk tribe next.
So, question. What's
with the getup?
Does it look bad on me?
Would you like me to say
that it looks good?
I will.
[CRUSCH]
You're so silly.
This is how I protect my
fair skin from sunlight.
Are you planning
on coming with me?
[CRUSCH] If I'm not mistaken,
the Dragon Tusk
have the greatest force
of arms within the tribes.
Right.
But we haven't dealt
with them in a while
so things may have changed.
[CRUSCH] Then I think it's best
if I accompany you there.
It's dangerous.
[CRUSCH] Is there anywhere
around here that isn't?
Huh. You're right,
of course. Sorry.
Crusch Lulu, I'll gladly
accept your help.
Thank you.
[CRUSCH]
Sounds good to me, Zaryusu.
I'll do what I can.
[ENTOMA] These are the
teleportation scrolls
I was instructed to deliver,
and the "Message"
scrolls as well.
Lord Ains informed me
they were constructed
from parchment that
we obtained through
the grand efforts
of Lord Demiurge.
He said we should
report back to him
if we have any problems
using them correctly.
[COCYTUS]
I see. Understood.
So, once again, Demiurge
has overshadowed me.
[ENTOMA]
There's more.
[COCYTUS]
Hm?
[ENTOMA] We have been
directed to stay put
and monitor the
outcome of the battle
with the Lizard Men
from this location only.
[COCYTUS]
I understand.
Your orders are to
see this fight through,
and deliver an absolute
victory for the Supreme One!
Don't let me down!
I'm Zaryusu Shasha.
I've come here on behalf
of the Green Claw tribe.
I wish to speak with your chief.
[CRUSCH] I am acting chief
of the Red Eye tribe,
Crusch Lulu.
I am also here to meet
with your chief.
[ZENBERU]
Possessor of Frost Pain!
What a pleasant surprise.
[ZENBERU]
Whoa.
Didn't realize the Red Eye
were led by a plant monster.
Don't be ridiculous!
Oh, please, learn to
take a joke, will ya?
I am the Dragon Tusk chief
you seek, Zenberu Gugu.
Call me Zenberu.
Feel free to call me
Zaryusu. Now let's get--
[ZENBERU] I can already guess
why you traveled this far.
However, our tribe only
trusts those who are strong.
Show me that you are.
[AINS] Zaryusu and Crusch
visit the village of the Dragon
Tusk tribe to seek an alliance.
However, the tribe chief,
Zenberu, declares that he
will only follow someone
stronger than himself and
proposes a one-on-one duel.
Meanwhile, the razor tail tribe,
the first of the Lizard
Man clans marked for death,
prepares itself for
battle under
Shasuryu's direction.
Chapter 3:
"Lizard men gathering"
Finally, the signal for battle.