[ZANAC] People of the proud
Kingdom of Re-Estize!
These devils do not
deserve our fear!
As long as I have this blade,
no monster will harm you!
[TOWNSPEOPLE cheer]
[MAN 13A]
Where'd all the people go?
Think they're hiding
in their houses?
[MAN 13B]
No. Look at the doors.
Poor bastards were probably
dragged somewhere.
Iron and copper adventurers,
stay here and search
through the houses!
The rest of you, spread out
and form a defensive line.
They'll be here soon.
Here we go.
[SOLDIER 13A]
An Overeating?
Gazer Devils... Hellhounds, too.
[SOLDIER 13A]
No! Stay with the group!
[SOLDIERS gasp, yell]
[gasps]
[AINS]
Toss me!
[AINS grunts]
[AINS yells]
[AINS] I think you've
had enough snacks.
[AINS]
Such paltry foes.
Fear not.
I am Momon, the adventurer.
And Jaldabaoth will
fall just as easily!
[AINS]
But, while I deal with him,
I need you to keep the
citizens beyond the wall safe.
I'm counting on you.
It's started.
Yeah.
I just hope they can
distract them long enough
for us to find and
rescue the prisoners.
Well,
Renner had mentioned
the warehouses.
That seems as good a place
as any to start looking.
Shalltear Bloodfallen.
She's actually here!
[gasps]
Go ahead. I'll buy
as much time as I can.
Don't wait for me.
What are you and your friends
doing in the capital?
[SHALLTEAR] What makes you
think I owe a human
any kind of explanation?
Poor thing.
Are you the only one
that made it this far?
You sound disappointed.
What's the matter?
Weren't you waiting for me?
[SHALLTEAR]
For you? Why would I?
[BRAIN]
Oh, I get it.
I was so insignificant,
you don't remember me, right?
[SHALLTEAR] Would you
like to die, little man?
I can help, but first,
I think I'll have you
prostrate and lick my boots.
Yes, that's exactly what
I need to improve my mood!
Sorry, but that's not happening.
Round two. Here we go.
[SHALLTEAR sighs]
What a hassle.
I guess you can't sense
how much stronger I am.
Oh, I can.
I'll die, but at least
I'll buy Climb
the time he needs.
And I'll go out my way.
With sword in hand.
[BRAIN]
Thanks for showing me the way.
My dear friends.
[yells]
Four-Fold. Slash of light.
[SHALLTEAR]
You aimed for it?
[laughs]
[SHALLTEAR] At least you
pass for a nail clipper.
S'quite the compliment.
I'll gladly take it.
My swordsmanship, my life's work
wasn't the massive waste
I thought it was.
In some small way,
I actually touched that
unreachable height!
[SHALLTEAR]
Poor crazy boy,
let me put you
out of your misery.
[SHALLTEAR] Even though
the Supreme One is close,
I can't sense his presence.
That detection blocking
ring really makes it hard
to stalk my beloved.
[SHALLTEAR]
Insolent ant!
I refuse to let a measly human
escape from me unharmed.
Time Accelerator!
[SHALLTEAR]
Is that...?
[DEMIURGE]
You are strong, indeed!
[EVILEYE gasps]
[EVILEYE]
We severely underestimated
the forces of Jaldabaoth.
[AINS]
You two handle the newcomers.
Let's get to it, Demi-- Demon!
[AINS yells]
I'll take three and you'll
handle the other two.
That should be enough
to subdue them.
[EVILEYE]
I don't mind taking three.
You'll take two.
There's no point
arguing with me.
[EVILEYE]
My, what a stubborn one.
[NARBERAL] I'll let you
decide who will fight me.
[YURI]
My name is Alpha. This is Delta.
[EVILEYE] Introductions?
How courteous of you.
My name is Evileye.
I'll be the last
thing you ever see.
[ALL panting]
What are you doing?
I told you to go on ahead!
[CLIMB]
Well, we just--
Whoa, whoa, whoa, back up a bit.
What's with you and
that lady in white?
You look like you'd
seen a specter.
Why isn't she chasing me?
Is this some kinda
lover's quarrel?
She's a monster who
could give Sebas
a run for his money!
[gasps]
Wait, and you--
Attacked her? Sure did.
I even managed to cut
off her fingernail.
Holy crap.
I cut it off and lived
to tell about it.
That's awesome!
Way to go Brain,
I'm proud of you.
You've done something
special, really.
Special! Yes!
Right. That's what it is.
Well, I'm not sitting around
to see if she'll chase us.
Let's go.
Martial Art!
Dark Blade, Mega Impact!
Floating Swords, do your work!
There's just no end to them!
What now, evil boss?
[LAKYUS]
Not good.
The priests are running
low on magic power.
[GAZEF]
Six Fold Slash of Light!
Run 'em through!
My Lord Stronoff,
this is a crisis!
Shouldn't you be
guarding the castle?
--[SOLDIERS gasp]
--[MAN 13A] His Majesty?
[MAN 13B]
King Ramposa!
[MAN 13C]
What is he doing here?
His Majesty asked of me:
"Which do you protect?
The castle or the crown?"
There's only one answer!
We swore to protect the King
and uphold his kingdom.
So, an attack on his people
is an attack on him!
Attack!
[SOLDIERS yell]
I'm glad you're here.
Think you could help
me with something?
Of course.
[GAGARAN]
Not without us!
It'll take more than death to
keep this warrior from battle.
This Ninja is ready to get back
into the fray
as well, evil boss.
Gagaran! Tia!
[GAGARAN] Just lyin' around
was makin' me soft.
We're ready to fight.
There's no way.
Always happy to have you along.
[SOLDIERS gasp]
Let's go!
[TINA, GAZEF, TIA, GAGARAN]
Yes, ma'am!
[EVILEYE]
Shard Buckshot!
[YURI yells]
[EVILEYE]
Not again!
[YURI yells]
[EVILEYE grunts]
[CZ] Not that you need it,
but, I'll cover you.
[EVILEYE]
Sand Field All!
Damn.
Monsters aren't supposed
to team up like this.
It isn't fair!
[EVILEYE gasps]
What the...?
Crystal Wall!
[YURI yells]
[EVILEYE]
Fa jin?
Impressive.
I've never met anything immune
to negative energy before.
You must have every
resistance there is.
Looks like Lord Momon
is still in the fight.
In that case, I'll buy him
as much time as I can.
[AINS]
You're sure this room is secure?
[DEMIURGE]
I've seen to it.
There's no one who can listen in
on our conversation, my lord.
[AINS]
All right.
Tell me everything
about your plan.
Of course, but first,
allow me to thank you
for indulging me, my lord.
I'm rather eager to share
the results of my design.
Overall, there are four
merits to the series
of plans I have devised.
[MOMONGA]
Four? I don't know a single one!
[AINS] Hm. Here I thought
there were three.
I think this may be the
first time I've bested you
in a contest of wits, Lord!
[AINS] Oh, you always
have the better of me.
You are too modest.
I'm flattered.
[AINS]
No, really.
Now, why don't you tell
me about these merits?
Right.
The first one is that we are
claiming all the materials
within the surrounding
storehouses.
[AINS]
Hm.
[MOMONGA]
Fantastic!
Now we don't have to worry about
being low on funds for a while.
Secondly, this incident
allows us to cover
our attack on Eight Fingers,
as you instructed us to do.
[AINS] Now that you mention it,
you said your goal
was to recover a powerful item?
[DEMIURGE]
See for yourself.
The magic within is
called "Armageddon Evil."
Tenth Tier magic.
Almost "god" level.
[AINS] As I recall,
it summons a horde of demons.
My creator, Lord Ulbert,
also crafted this item.
Shall we use it here?
[AINS] I have one better.
I think you'll like it.
[AINS] It's Ulbert's
prototype of the same item.
It should work, all the same.
You may use it
for your purposes.
Lord.
I couldn't possibly use
such a personal treasure.
[AINS]
Oh?
Then I shall gift
it to you, Demiurge.
Though,
Ulbert might be
embarrassed that I've kept
his failed creation
around for so long.
Do with it as you see fit.
Such an honor.
[DEMIURGE]
I'm most grateful.
[AINS]
Stop that. Really.
Consider it thanks for
your fierce loyalty.
The Great Ones created us.
It is only right we are loyal,
and that we continuously
demonstrate it until
we meet our end.
Nonetheless, for to
once again address me,
a servant, with such charity,
and to reward me with
such a precious gift...
I can only repay you
by humbly offering
an even deeper
devotion to your will.
[AINS grunts] I look forward
to it. Now, continue.
I wish to know the
rest of your plan.
With that narrative in place,
Jaldabaoth has attacked
the Eight Fingers bases
looking for this item.
Which just happened
to give him control
of the capital's
warehouse district.
And of course,
this item will be "found"
in the warehouse that serves
as Eight Fingers'
base of operations.
[AINS]
Obviously. Tell me the merit.
Right.
We have captured all the
humans that were trapped
within the wall of the flame.
The majority of them are already
being taken to Nazarick,
where I think they could be
put to all kinds of uses.
[AINS] Regardless of their
age or gender, I'm assuming?
[DEMIURGE]
Of course.
[MOMONGA] Ever since I
ended up in this body,
I haven't felt a sense of
affinity for the human race.
Not a single death or suffering
we've inflicted has
pained my heart.
If it benefitted Nazarick,
I didn't care.
But, even so.
[AINS]
Listen carefully.
See that those who haven't
dishonored the Great Tomb
or myself are given
painless deaths.
Only the guilty shall suffer.
How benevolent, my lord.
It shall be as you wish.
[AINS]
Back on topic.
You still have one more
merit to reveal.
Yes, Lord.
When everything
is said and done,
all the city's woes will be
laid at Jaldabaoth's feet.
[AINS] In other words,
you're establishing yourself
as a notorious demon.
[MOMONGA]
He's using this to increase
Momon's reputation. Nice.
[AINS]
That makes sense. I'm convinced.
So, is there something
in particular
you need me to help with?
All you have to do is
drive me out of the city,
and there should be
no problem, Lord.
I will do everything in my power
to serve you as your foil.
And I promise to put on one
hell of a show in the process.
[LUPISREGINA]
Wow, that little girl
has some serious moves.
What'd she say her name was?
I don't know, she's a rodent.
Why would I care what
other rodents call her?
[SOLUTION] I believe she
is Evileye, of Blue Rose.
She was listed in the
information Sebas collected.
Ah, right. Lord Ains
mentioned that.
[LUPISREGINA]
Narberal, honey,
I think your mind's
starting to go.
I'm sure none of you remember
the humans you've met.
[SOLUTION]
It was no problem for me.
I pay close attention
to proper names.
[LUPISREGINA]
Every one!
I actually get along
pretty well with them, too.
[ENTOMA]
No problems, either.
Uh...
[SOLUTION, ENTOMA, LUPISREGINA]
[ENTOMA] An earthquake.
Feels like one of Mare's.
[NARBERAL]
Is this some kind of sign?
[SOLUTION]
That's right.
Okay, Narberal, time for
you to get some bruises.
[LUPISREGINA] It needs to look
real, but I'll try to go gentle.
Sorry about this.
Don't worry about me.
This is our job.
[MAN 13D]
It's the devil!
He's coming back for us!
Remain calm. We're
here to help you!
They took my child,
please, we have to hurry!
[MAN 13E]
Yeah, my wife, too!
[WOMAN 13B]
I have a three-year-old son,
do you know if anyone's see him?
Looks like the princess
was right on the money.
Sure enough, those
bastards split up
the families when
they took them.
[grunts]
Can you keep fighting?
Don't worry, that won't
be a problem.
Lord Momon!
[AINS]
That was actually fun.
How can I describe it?
"Real," perhaps?
Yes. I'm really
getting to fight!
[DEMIURGE] I am pleased
that you're pleased.
Now, I'll take this seriously.
[AINS]
Come at me, then! I'm waiting!
[AINS grunts]
[gasps]
[AINS yells]
[DEMIURGE] Aspect of the
Devil: Hellfire Mantle!
[AINS yells]
[AINS] You must have
boosted your power.
How else could you melt
a weapon of this level?
[DEMIURGE]
How else, indeed.
[AINS]
The flames of hell?
[DEMIURGE]
What's wrong?
You wanted a true fire
to test you, right?
So I'll give you one that
sears the very soul!
[AINS]
Frost Pain Modified!
[DEMIURGE]
What's that?
It's much like that
spear you used earlier.
[AINS]
Icy Burst!
[DEMIURGE]
You truly are strong, warrior.
[AINS]
As are you.
It's like watching gods at play.
[DEMIURGE]
I have a proposal for you.
I will withdraw, now.
Shall we call this
the end of our battle?
Of course not!
[AINS]
Very well.
[DEMIURGE]
This woman seems clueless.
I can't fathom
why you would bring
someone so unintelligent,
Mr. Momon.
Think hard for a moment
and you might understand.
I'll give you a clue.
I have my demon
hordes standing by
to assault the entire capital.
You would take...
the city hostage?
[DEMIURGE] Now then,
we will leave, as agreed.
Sadly, we were unable
to retrieve the item,
but there's always
next time, Momon.
[AINS]
Till then.
[EVILEYE squeals]
You did it! You won!
You're incredible, Mr. Momon!
[AINS] Er, could you give
me some space, miss?
[EVILEYE]
Aw, don't be bashful.
[GAGARAN]
Hey! Shorty's still kickin'!
You guys.
Go on, Lord.
Declare our victory!
[AINS]
I don't know.
As the most distinguished
warrior of this battle,
it is your duty!
Come on, don't be shy!
[AINS] I suppose you're
right. Very well, then.
[AINS yells]
[EVILEYE]
Lord Momon is victorious!
[SOLDIERS cheer]
[EVILEYE]
I see.
You're really going back
to E-Rantel, then?
I'd very much like
to accompany you, but...
[AINS]
Don't worry about it.
You have done us and the
kingdom a great service.
[AINS]
Mm.
His Majesty would have liked
to thank you personally,
but he must oversee
relief efforts.
[AINS] That's quite
all right, Marquis Raeven.
I'm grateful for
all you've done.
Not at all.
I hope we can continue
our good relations,
moving forward.
[AINS] Members of
Blue Rose, as a fellow
adamantite class adventurer,
I hope I can look to you
the next time
something comes up.
As do we.
[AINS]
Farewell.
He turned you down, huh?
Not at all.
That's just the
kind of man he is.
As of now, you are all
servants to our great Master,
the Supreme One and
Overlord of death!
Give yourselves a hand!
[EIGHT FINGERS EXEC 6A]
Don't be absurd, brat.
We'll start things off
by inviting you all
to a fun new place!
Fun. Yes, that's
what we'll call it.
[HILMA]
No, please, wait!
Hilma!
You don't mean me, do you?
I did everything
you asked of me!
Don't let it have me.
I can't take it anymore!
Whoa. What did you do to her?
I might have taken her
into Kyouhukou's room
and had him eat her from
the inside out a couple times.
Oh, that figures, and then
you used healing magic
to make her fresh as a daisy.
It's only natural that she'd
be more submissive after that.
Okay, lady.
We need you to buy some
time with the others
until we're sure they'll
do as they're told.
Can you do that for us?
[HILMA] Uh-huh! Of course I can!
Just leave them to me!
[EIGHT FINGERS EXEC 6A]
No, you wouldn't!
With that done, we've officially
taken over half
the country. Nice!
[CLIMB] All those under your
protection wish to express
their gratitude,
Princess Renner.
My. I would sure
like to see them.
You mustn't!
I'm sorry to decline
your kind feelings,
but it's for the best.
Well, I suppose
it can't be helped.
[BRAIN]
I'll be.
Rigrit kicked your ass too, huh?
[EVILEYE]
Buzz off.
[TIA]
Kicked it bad.
[TINA]
She cried.
This sure takes me back.
[EVILEYE]
Don't lump me in with you!
In addition to that old lady,
I had these fools to deal with!
Hey, Evileye.
Somethin's been buggin'
me since Momon left.
Why didn't you just create
a portal to E-Rantel?
I mean, you could've gone
with him as you pleased
and never looked back, amirite?
No way, did you
just realize that?
[EVILEYE wails]
[PESTONYA] I'd like to
introduce the newest maid
to join Nazarick.
I'm Tuareninya. It's a
pleasure to meet you.
Is there any sort of
training you'd like me
to focus on with her,
Lord Sebas? Woof.
There's no need
for special treatment.
Just aim for the same
passing grade as any maid.
That said. Tuare is only human.
Please keep her training
geared with that in mind,
Lady Pestonya.
I understand perfectly!
Being a maid is a temporary
assignment for her.
I'm not sure what
you mean by that.
Only that she'll be
quitting once she's married.
Uh, woof.
It's good to have
you back, Lord Ains.
What is your bidding?
[FLUDER] I've looked
into this Ains Ooal Gown
fellow as you requested.
If such a man truly exists.
I'd say that his caliber
of magic would rival my own.
Perhaps even surpass it.
Interesting.
Is that why you seem
so pleased, old man?
[FLUDER]
Naturally, my lord.
It takes all manner of oracles
to gaze into the abyss.
But, to find a
true magical peer.
If possible, I would like to
meet him personally, my lord.
I would also like you
to collect information
on an adamantite
class adventurer
known as the
Raven-Black Hero, Momon.
Think you could help me
with that, old man?
[FLUDER]
Of course I can, my emperor.