Welcome back to the
Magician's Guild, Lord Sebas.
Always a pleasure.
I'd like to see the
spell and cantrips list,
if you please.
[REP 6A]
As you wish. One moment.
I'm not sure I understand this
"Floating Board" spell.
Would you explain its
function and general uses?
Of course. The
Floating Board spell.
A first-tier conjuration
of a glowing board.
It floats and is easy to move.
Very useful for
transporting items.
Often used in public
work projects.
[SEBAS]
I see.
Then, I would like to purchase
one such magic scroll.
If none are available,
please make one.
[REP 6A] We appreciate
your business, as always.
That will be one gold and
ten silver coins, please.
Go, Shadow Demon.
Deliver this message for me.
Tell Solution I'm
looking around the city
and will return
later than normal.
Now then.
I think I'll head
over there today.
[DOG barks]
[SEBAS]
Shadow Demon, go!
Please remove your hand,
you have my attention.
[SEBAS] Are you in need
of some assistance?
If that is the case,
then simply ask.
[MAN 6A]
Hey, old timer.
Where the hell did
you blow in from?
Well?
What the crap? Let go of me!
I'm assuming you
know this woman?
She's one of my employees.
What of it?
[SEBAS]
So, she's human.
Yet you've forced,
or at least allowed,
extreme violence upon her.
And where were you
planning to take her
while she was in that sack?
To the temple. She's very sick.
[MAN 6A groans]
In that case, you wouldn't mind
if I decided to take
her in your stead.
Wait!
Legally speaking,
she belongs to us!
If you take her away,
it would be kidnapping!
And a proper looking
butler like you
shouldn't get mixed
up in trouble
behind his master's back, right?
A valid point.
Do you want me to
help you, miss?
Do you want me to help or not?
[cackles]
[inaudible whimpering]
[SEBAS]
I'm not inclined to help those
who choose prayer over action.
They waste their
lives wilting away,
like flowers waiting for
the rain to sustain them.
However, you are
fighting to stay alive.
So, let go of your
fear and be at peace.
As of this moment,
you are under my
steadfast protection.
Like hell she is!
I never agreed to that!
[SEBAS]
"Like hell," you say?
An immoral blob like
you has the gall
to imply that my words
don't have merit?
No.
Good. Then we shall
take our leave of you.
[MAN 6A]
Wait!
[SEBAS]
Is there something else?
[MAN 6A]
No.
It's just, if you take her,
I won't last through the night.
I'm in deep with
Eight Fingers, man.
You know what that means?
[laughs]
[MAN 6A] They control this
entire kingdom from the shadows.
I'm begging you.
Put her down, walk away,
and pretend this didn't happen.
[SEBAS]
I couldn't possibly do that.
[MAN 6A]
Have a heart, old man!
They'll kill me! Slowly!
[TOUCHME] Because saving
a person who's in trouble
is always the right thing to do.
Holy hell. Are these
all platinum?
[SEBAS] Take that and hire
an adventurer or something.
It should be more than
enough to flee the country
and live comfortably with.
If you run as fast as you can,
perhaps you'll live long
enough to use it all.
[SOLUTION]
Welcome back. Lord Sebas.
How-- If I may ask,
what the hell is that?
I found her.
[SOLUTION]
I see.
I doubt you meant it
as a gift for me,
so what do you
intend to do with it?
A good question.
For now, I think I will have
you tend to her wounds for me.
Heal it? Seriously?
Could you not have left it at
a temple for such treatment?
[SEBAS]
I could have.
Imagine, me, of all people
not realizing such a thing.
I will dispose
of it, if you wish.
[SEBAS] No. I have already
brought her this far.
It would be a waste
not to think of
some effective use for her.
[SEBAS] If you don't mind,
I would like you to start
by assessing her
physical condition.
[SOLUTION]
Very well, Lord Sebas.
Right away.
I'll leave you to it then.
I won't keep you waiting.
How could I act so foolishly?
"Saving a person
who's in trouble
is always the
right thing to do."
That philosophy was also
the motto of my creator,
Lord TouchMe.
He lived and breathed justice.
Perhaps, that is the reason
I endeavor to do the same.
Though, it could yet
prove to be a curse.
[knocking]
[SEBAS]
How is our guest?
It has three venereal
diseases, including Syphilis.
Several cracked ribs
and broken fingers,
and the tendons in its
right arm and left leg
have been torn.
Upper and lower front
teeth were removed.
It also has an anal fissure.
There's the possibility
it is addicted
to some kind of drug.
In addition, there are
multiple bruises
and lacerations across--
Can she be treated?
Easily.
[SEBAS]
Then please see to it.
That is not my specialty, Lord.
Lady Pestonya's healing magic
would be better suited by far.
[SEBAS] Solution, you have
the necessary healing scrolls
in your possession, yes?
Then use one of them on her.
But, Lord Sebas, those
scrolls were graciously
provided by the Supreme One
to serve his purposes.
Would it not be
sinful to waste one
on lowly human scum?
That is an order.
As you wish, Lord Sebas.
Forgive me if I'm being
too forward, but...
Would restoring its
physical state be sufficient
for you to engage in
whatever "activities"
you have planned?
[SEBAS]
Once her treatment is complete,
draw a hot bath
to clean her up.
Make her comfortable.
I'll buy something
for supper, in the meantime.
If I may, sir.
Tending that woman's
mental state will involve
much more than we're capable of.
Perhaps we should
call Lord Ains--
This is not something Lord Ains
needs to be bothered
with. Am I clear?
[SOLUTION] I would have
understood Sebas' intentions
if he had agreed to
make you my plaything.
Once you were fully
recovered, of course.
We still have time before
he returns, though.
More than enough to see
how flavorful you are.
It looks like the healing magic
did its job perfectly.
How are you feeling, young lady?
I'm sure you're hungry.
Eat. Before it gets cold.
[SEBAS]
Here.
As long as you're here,
you are free from
any kind of danger.
When you wake, you'll
still be in this bed.
You have my guarantee,
as head butler of the Pleiades.
[faint stammering]
[TUARE whispers]
Th-Thank you... very... much.
[SEBAS]
Please, think nothing of it.
Now that I have taken you in,
I will ensure your safety
to the best of my ability.
[TUARE] Why didn't
anyone try to help me?
They cannot hurt you now.
[sobbing]
[SEBAS]
You're all right.
[TUARE]
I-I'm s-sorry.
[SEBAS]
Please, don't concern yourself.
For a man such as myself,
it is an honor
to be the shoulder
a woman can lean on.
[TUARE] But it's so clean.
I would hate to get it dirty.
[gasps]
[SEBAS]
Here. Take it.
A handkerchief that goes unused
is a thing to be
mourned. After all,
it exists so you
may dry your tears
and keep moving forward.
Now then, you should
get some rest.
When you are ready, we will
discuss what comes next.
What do you mean, "comes next"?
I'm sure staying in the capital
is out of the question.
Is there anywhere
else you can go?
Unfortunate.
But, expected.
Is it all right if I
ask for your name?
I... My name is Tuare, sir.
A fine name indeed.
Oh, yes, forgive me.
I haven't told you
mine yet, have I?
My creator blessed me
with the name Sebas Tian.
But, please, feel free to
call me Sebas from now on.
Okay.
[SEBAS]
Something the matter?
I have to ask.
What are you ultimately planning
to do with that woman?
Her name is Tuare.
Its name?
Lord Sebas.
I do not know the reasons
you had for bringing
that thing into this house,
but it received those injuries
from being exposed to
certain types of people.
Whoever did this to it
will be very displeased
when they find out
it's still alive.
They'll come looking.
If, and I do mean
if that happens,
then I will deal
with it accordingly.
For now, I want you to
wait and see what happens
for a little while.
Or can't you do that, Solution?
[BRAIN]
Gazef.
I developed the God Flash and
Field so I could beat you.
And if I combine
the two of them,
I will.
Blade Technique, Whistling Wind!
How? There's no way!
--[yells]
--[SHALLTEAR yawns]
What's wrong?
Are you tired already?
That sharp little
clipper of yours
did wonders for my nails.
Perhaps I should block
with the other hand.
[gasps]
[BRAIN screams]
[BRAIN gasps, pants]
Where am I?
[GAZEF]
You look awful.
Gazef? Am I still dreaming?
[GAZEF]
Where did we meet again?
The championship of the
royal matches, right?
I barely managed
to win that bout.
It was the closest
match of my life.
From my first day to now.
I know you.
Unglaus. Brain Unglaus?
Gazef. Stronoff.
Talk to me.
What the hell happened?
I found out how
weak I really am.
And it's not just me.
It's all of us, Gazef.
We're all nothing.
Our skill with the
sword amounts to garbage
in the face of monsters.
Just because we're human.
An inferior race.
Goes without saying.
Every warrior should understand
their own limitations.
But a monster's strength
is a height to work toward.
That's why you fight.
Close the gap.
Reach those new heights.
[BRAIN]
You're wrong!
The level I'm talking
about can't be reached.
No matter how hard we fight,
or how far we manage
to push ourselves,
the human race won't
see those heights.
That's the truth,
plain and simple.
You saw something that extreme?
[BRAIN]
Yes. I did.
A summit of strength that
humans will never climb up to.
No, what I saw wasn't
even a "height."
I was so utterly
lacking in ability,
that it was just a game!
It was almost funny.
[BRAIN]
Heed me.
Pursuing strength through
the sword is a fool's errand.
In the face of true
strength, rubbish!
[BRAIN] I'm glad I got
to see you one last time.
Now I can die.
Hey, that's enough!
Sit down. Eat something.
And then, move on.
[SOLDIER 6A gasps, grunts]
Huh?
[TINA]
Everything is ready here.
[TIA]
Flawless.
[EVILEYE]
I know. I was watching you.
I'm moving to the next location.
[EVILEYE]
This won't be worth the trip
if we don't catch the
biggest fish possible.
We should move in
to attack as well.
What about them?
Probably goofing around
since they're just watching.
[EVILEYE]
The hell they are.
They're lying in wait
near the village
in case of emergency.
Anyway, I'm off.
You two continue
according to plan.
Wont' do much,
but it should buy us
what little time we'll need.
If we can't strike a blow
that will turn things
'round, this is futile.
Lovely, it burns so well!
I hope the people of the village
can get away from it in time.
[GAGARAN] I'd be just as wary
of the smoke as the fire.
Remember, we're burning the
plant that diabolical drug
Black Dust is made from.
Breathe lightly.
What now?
We burning a different
site than this?
That's the plan.
We have to strike where we can.
If we aren't vigilant,
Black Dust will spread
across the kingdom just
like this wild fire.
Problem is they have
so many outposts
for cultivating the
drug, you could cover
half the map with them.
Eight Fingers really is
a gigantic organization.
Terrifying, right?
An underworld
syndicate so large,
they could undermine a nation.
[TINA] We finished everything
as planned, fiendish leader.
And we left no evidence
of our identity.
[LAKYUS] Tia. Tina.
Did you find anything?
[TINA]
Not at all.
[TIA]
Nothing valuable.
Ugh. I hope shorty
had better luck.
[EVILEYE]
I've returned.
Happy hunting, Evileye?
[EVILEYE]
Eh. You tell me. Catch.
What is this?
Code, maybe?
[EVILEYE]
Probably.
This could be the
lead on Eight Fingers
we've been waiting for.
[EIGHT FINGERS EXEC 6A]
I bring this meeting to order.
There are several
items on the agenda,
but one requires
urgent attention.
Hilma?
Yes, yes. Well.
Word has it one of your
cultivation facilities
came under attack by a
group of unknown assailants.
[HILMA]
It was. Hell of a mess, that.
It was a village
where we produced
the drug en masse.
Won't be cheap to replace.
This loss could put
a bit of a squeeze
on our distribution and sales.
[EIGHT FINGERS EXEC 6A]
And you have no information
on the attackers?
None at all.
They left nothing for us
to find.Of course,
the flawless execution could
be the key to their identity.
[ZERO] Hey. Why don't
you bring us in on it?
[HILMA]
Hm?
Your group of
nobodies is worthless.
They can't protect jack.
Think I'll pass, thanks.
I can't afford to let
you know the location
of all my sites now, can I?
[COCCO DOLL]
In that case,
I'd like to take you
up on that offer.
Sure about that, Cocco Doll?
Last I checked,
your purse was light.
[COCCO DOLL]
Don't worry, Zero, darling.
True, the slave
trade is hurting,
especially after the Golden
Princess prohibited it,
but I have a nest
egg in my coop.
Ah. What you mean is you have
something major going down.
I'm in.
[COCCO DOLL]
Lovely!
I've had a bit of problem
come up with a woman
who was scheduled
to be disposed of.
I'm afraid it will take
more than my perfectly
manicured hands to deal with it.
I need some excessive force
to keep my business
up, understood?
[ZERO] That's what the
Six Arms does best.
We'll protect your property.
And if things get hairy,
we'll handle it with a smile.
[AINS] Renner, the third
princess of the kingdom of
Re-Estize, knows that her
country is continuing
to weaken. Powerless to act
on her own, Princess Renner
can only depend upon
her loyal soldier, Climb,
and the adamantite team
known as Blue Rose.
To protect the people from Eight
Fingers, the group that controls
the underworld, the greatest
adventurers begin to move.
Chapter 7: "Blue roses".
No matter the era, the weak
are always the victims.