To our glorious victory!
And to the ancestor spirits!
I fought Frost Pain.
Even knew about that
fancy ability it has.
"Icy Burst," you mean.
The ability's strong
but has limited uses.
Even me knew that.
[SHASURYU]
Hm.
Yeah.
Okay, but did you know the
weapon also has the power
to protect its user from the
most extreme cold possible?
It's not without
its drawbacks, though.
Drawback or no,
that do-or-die maneuver
wouldn't have worked without
Frost Pain's protection.
He's an amazing warrior.
Yeah. Proud to call him brother.
You did well, too.
Thanks for having his back.
[ZENBERU]
So, it's back to life as usual?
[SHASURYU]
Doubtful.
It's far more likely that we've
pissed off this "Great One"
and they'll decide to
attack us personally.
Then why isn't your
brother living it up
with the rest of us?
Last I checked,
he was still asleep.
He and Crusch were
pretty exhausted.
We should let them rest
for a while longer.
Heh. Don't be an idiot.
We both know rest ain't
what's happening in that tent.
Don't make a nuisance
of yourself, y'hear?
[gasps]
[ZARYUSU gasps]
Hey, how's the baby makin'?
[CRUSCH, ZARYUSU yelp]
[AINS] Thank you for
assembling so swiftly,
my faithful Guardians.
We have much to cover.
Victim, come forward.
[AINS] Take a moment
to introduce yourself
to the others.
[VICTIM] It's a pleasure to
meet all of you. I am Victim.
[AINS] Though you guard
the Eighth floor,
that is not the reason
I've called you here.
We have yet to identify
Shalltear's powerful assailant.
I doubt we have seen
the last of them,
and must consider
future incidents.
Therefore, to protect all
of the Guardians, myself,
and Nazarick. I must
use a powerful skill
that is only invoked
by your death.
I am sorry.
Though, I will bring you
back to life right away,
I hope you can forgive me.
[VICTIM] Do not let it
bother you, Lord Ains.
Death is my purpose.
What I was born for.
If dying would be of use
to a Supreme Being
and the Tomb as a whole,
nothing would give
me greater joy.
[AINS] There is a motto our
members often lived by.
I'm reminded of it now.
"Greater love hath
no man than this,
that he lay down his life
for his friends."
Truly a sublime expression.
One that I believe
fits you perfectly.
I am grateful for your love.
[VICTIM] Your words are
more than I deserve.
[AINS]
Next up, Demiurge
Lord?
[AINS]
First, allow me to honor you.
You always answer
my calls with haste.
You are too generous, Lord.
It is expected of me,
just as it is for all
of your humble servants.
[AINS]
Indeed.
I've inspected the sheepskin
parchment you provided.
It is evident they will stand
up to use as low-tier scrolls.
Can I count on a
stable supply of it?
[DEMIURGE] Yes. That will
not be a problem, Lord.
I have acquired an
ample number of them.
[AINS]
I see.
What is the name of the beasts
you've been harvesting?
Their name? Ah.
Would "Abelion Sheep" suffice?
The skin is similar.
As is their role
in your conquest.
[AINS]
"Sheep," huh? Interesting.
[MOMONGA] So, the beasts
are actually chimeras,
or, rather, a subspecies.
In Yggdrasil, chimeras
had the head of a lion
and a goat, and their
tails were snakes.
He must think that
a beast with sheep
mixed in is something different.
I think "Abelion Goat"
would be better,
but very well.
Continue your work.
Now. Shalltear.
[gasps] Yes, Lord?
[AINS] Regarding the
splinter in your soul.
Please. Master.
I can't reconcile
the shame of my sin
with the honor of my
position as Guardian.
I beg of you, punish me
for the reprehensible
monster that I am!
[AINS] All right. I will
settle on one later.
Lastly, Cocytus.
[COCYTUS growls]
[AINS]
You ended in defeat.
[COCYTUS]
Yes, Lord.
I am terribly sorry
for my offense.
I have dishonored
Nazarick. I was foo--
Cocytus!
Look your Master in the eye
when begging forgiveness!
[COCYTUS]
Of course. Sorry.
[AINS] I'm curious. Why do
you think you were beaten?
[COCYTUS]
Lord Ains.
I cannot begin to atone
for losing the army
you entrusted to me.
[AINS] Enough. Let me make
this perfectly clear.
I don't intend to punish you
harshly for this defeat.
[COCYTUS]
Uh?
[AINS] The reason being
that everyone makes mistakes.
I don't care who they are.
That goes for me, as well.
[GUARDIANS gasp]
[AINS] That being said,
I would like to know
how you could have won.
[COCYTUS] I should have
acted more cautiously.
I underestimated the
Lizard Men's resourcefulness.
[AINS]
Yes, you did.
Never underrate someone,
no matter how weak they are.
Is there anything else?
[COCYTUS] I think I may have
had insufficient information.
The enemy's strength,
the topography.
I realize that, without
considering such factors,
my chance of victory
was lowered regardless.
[AINS]
Mm.
[COCYTUS] Uh... A lack of
commanders was also a problem.
Since my soldiers
were low-level undead,
I should have placed those
with the ability
to lead in as needed.
[AINS]
Anything else?
[COCYTUS]
Apologies, my lord.
That is all I can think
of for the moment.
[AINS] Outstanding!
Except for the Elder Lich,
our losses were inconsequential.
Their demise has
absolutely no effect
on Nazarick's power.
And considering what
one of my Guardian's
has learned from this,
I'd say we've gained.
[COCYTUS] Your benevolence
knows no bounds, my lord--
[AINS] Hold on. The fact
remains that you lost.
For that you must be punished.
[AINS]
Cocytus!
You will personally
mop up that sludge
by exterminating the Lizard Men!
And, this time, you will
rely on no one but yourself.
[COCYTUS gasps]
Fantastic idea, my lord!
He will expunge his sin
and the Lizard Men
in one fell swoop! You truly
are a Supreme Being!
[COCYTUS]
Lord Ains.
[AURA, MARE]
Huh?
[COCYTUS]
I must humbly make a request.
Please, Lord. Hear me out!
You have brought
defeat and disgrace
to the glory of Nazarick,
and now dare to
petition our master?
You forget your place, worm!
Insolence!
[AINS]
It's fine, Albedo!
You've surprised me, Cocytus,
and piqued my interest.
Lift your head and
make your request.
[COCYTUS gulps]
[AINS]
Don't keep me waiting.
I simply wish to know your mind.
Speak up, and let
it be known to all.
[COCYTUS] I am against
exterminating the Lizard Men.
I beg you, Lord Ains,
show them mercy!
The nerve of you!
Do you realize
you're challenging
the Supreme One's will?
[AINS] Albedo! Do not get
in the middle of this.
I beg your pardon.
Please, forgive me.
[AINS]
I am intrigued.
You must have a
pretty good reason
for making this request.
Something that will benefit
the Great Tomb of Nazarick
and its denizens.
Tell me what it is.
[COCYTUS]
Yes, Lord.
There is a chance
that valiant warriors
will appear among
the Lizard Men tribes.
It is my judgement,
that it would be
far more beneficial to have them
pledge their loyalty
to Nazarick.
Make them our subordinates.
[AINS] That is indeed
a convincing proposal.
If we were to use the
Lizard Man corpses
to create undead, I'm not
convinced they would be
much stronger than if
we used human corpses.
As such,
I see no reason to insist on
using them for that purpose.
[COCYTUS]
In that case--
[AINS]
However!
It would be more
cost-effective to use undead
created by me than to leave
the Lizard Men alive
and rule over them.
[COCYTUS]
Oh...
[AINS] If you can think
of any other benefits,
now is the time to voice them.
[COCYTUS]
Well...
[AINS]
How about it, Cocytus?
[COCYTUS]
Uh...
[AINS]
If you have nothing more,
then you won't mind
exterminating them, yes?
I see. That's too bad.
[DEMIURGE]
Lord Ains?
[AINS]
Hm. Speak, Demiurge.
Lord.
Instead of zombies, what if
we used the Lizard Men
in a governability experiment?
[AINS]
Hm. Interesting. Continue.
Yes.
The time will likely come
when we will be handling
different races simultaneously.
Why not practice?
We could use the
Lizard Men to that end.
Work out the kinks, and find
a means, other than fear,
to govern with for
when the time comes.
[AINS]
A terrific suggestion, Demiurge!
Thank you very much.
[AINS] We will then accept
Demiurge's proposal,
and shift from exterminating
the Lizard Men
to occupying them.
[GUARDIANS]
Lord!
[AINS]
Demiurge. I am impressed.
I appreciate the praise, Lord,
but I'm sure you
were already aware
of my proposal before
I even thought of it.
You were simply waiting
for Cocytus, yes?
[AINS chuckles]
You give me far too much credit.
All I wanted
was for him to display
his own thinking,
no matter what
it might have been.
Listen well, my Guardians!
Orders are not infallible law
that you must blindly
obey and carry out.
You must carefully consider
them before you act!
Always aim for the greatest
benefit to Nazarick!
[GUARDIANS]
We will!
[AINS]
Consequently, we must change
your punishment, Cocytus.
You will govern the Lizard Men,
and instill everlasting
loyalty towards Nazarick
within their hearts. Rule
through fear is forbidden.
[COCYTUS]
As you wish, Lord.
I swear on my life to
live up to the great mercy
you have shown me. Even if
it takes me an eternity.
[AINS] It's time to
move out, my Guardians!
I want one team as a decoy,
and another to flaunt our
power to the Lizard Men.
We'll put on one hell of a show.
Albedo, make ready our soldiers.
Activate Gargantua, as well.
By your command, Lord.
About the decoy.
I'm assuming that
someone has enjoyed
peeking on us lately.
So, you're sending out
this dummy unit,
to keep our true intentions
hidden for the time being?
[AINS]
That is correct.
[ALBEDO]
Very good, Lord.
[AINS] All right!
It's time to get moving!
[COCYTUS]
Demiurge, you have my gratitude.
[DEMIURGE] Please. There's
no need for that, Cocytus.
For, you see, this is
probably the outcome
Lord Ains wanted all along.
[AURA, MARE]
Huh?
You mean everything
that's transpired
has done so according
to his design?
I should've known
that was the case!
But, if so, does that,
well, I mean...
I could be wrong about this,
but, did Lord Ains assume
that Cocytus would
lose from the get go?
Not so much "lose," perhaps.
He may have been hoping
Cocytus would probe
the Lizard Men's strength
and ask for reinforcements,
rather than blindly
follow his orders.
Well, that's our
Lord Ains for you!
Ten steps ahead of the rest.
No wonder he assumed
the role of guild master
for the Supreme Ones!
Truly, no one was more
deserving of the throne!
[AINS groans]
[AINS giggles]
[MOMONGA sighs]
[MOMONGA]
That was freakin' epic!
Cocytus totally took
me by surprise.
In Yggdrasil, if you do anything
you don't have the skills
for, you're screwed.
But if Cocytus can gain
tactics and strategies
from this experience,
that just goes to prove
that everyone has a massive
potential for growth!
However, growth means change.
If my Guardians' skills
can change over time,
who's to say their loyalties
can't do the same?
Oh... That's a scary thought!
I wonder if there's
anyone around
who can teach me kingcraft.
[AINS] I suppose it's
about time I got ready
to move out, as well.
[AINS]
Hm?
[AINS sniffs]
There's a floral scent.
Have they been sprinkling
perfume onto my bed sheets?
Perhaps this is what
the wealthy are used to.
If so, I should
keep that in mind.
It could come in handy
when pretending to be rich.
[ZARYUSU]
I knew this might happen, but,
not this soon.
[CRUSCH gasps]
Look at them.
[ZARYUSU gasps]
Impossible.
[ZENBERU]
I noticed it, too.
Every one of them is
covered in magic equipment.
A mythical, undead army.
How'd the wind get
cold so suddenly?
I don't believe it.
[ZARYUSU]
Hm?
The only thing that could
change the air like this
is "Control Weather."
Sixth-tier magic.
You're sure about that?
Ah. So, this must be the
power of the "Great One"
we keep hearing about.
[SHASURYU]
Remain calm!
Don't let fear rule you,
brave warriors.
The ancestors are watching.
Don't think or do anything
that would cause them
to hang their heads in shame.
What do ya think?
They're making their move.
But it doesn't look like
battle preparations.
[ZENBERU]
Then what's the point of this?
Huh?
[LIZARD MEN gasp]
Is that the ruler of death?
What is that, Crusch?
I don't know. It's
completely new to me.
[LIZARD MEN gasp]
Everyone, to higher ground!
[ZENBERU]
I'm guessing we can be sure
this is the "Great One"
after that little display.
[ZARYUSU]
Most likely.
Well, I'm sold.
We don't stand a chance
against this thing.
Might as well be dung beetles
from where he's standing.
Am I hallucinating?
[ZARYUSU]
What is that thing?
[LIZARD MEN scream]
Hold on.
[ZARYUSU]
Is this a Royal procession?
[MESSENGER 4A] We carry a
decree from the Great One.
Our glorious master wishes
to converse with you.
[MESSENGER 4B]
Let your delegate step forward
and receive your judgement.
[MESSENGER 4C]
Know that time wasted
is displeasing to the Great One.
Do so at your own peril.
[gasps] He used
all those monsters
just so he could invite
us to speak with him?
That's crazy.
My brother.
Will you walk with me?
[ZARYUSU]
Hm!
[gasps]
[CRUSCH]
Zaryusu.
Don't worry. I'll be back.
You better be.
Thanks for this.
I would never let you
go alone, brother.
Besides, they might take a
single delegate as an insult.
And, if he decides to
make an example of us,
our newly formed tribe will
only have lost one leader,
and a lowly traveler.
I'm fine with that.
I'm Shasuryu Shasha,
representative of
the Lizard Men!
This is our mightiest warrior,
as well as the one
I call brother.
Zaryusu Shasha!
[AINS]
Hm.
Pathetic, as expected.
Demiurge, please teach
these lower life-forms
the proper posture to
adopt before our Master.
Prostrate yourselves!
Do not resist!
[SHASURYU, ZARYUSU grunting]
Lord Ains. I believe they
are ready to listen now.
[AINS]
Good work. Lift up their heads.
You are permitted to gaze
upon the Great One.
[BOTH gasp]
[AINS] I am the master of
the Great Tomb of Nazarick.
Ains Ooal Gown.
First, I shall express
my gratitude to you
for assisting in my experiment.
Now, onto the main subject.
Your race will
fall under my rule.
[gasps]
[AINS]
However,
I am sure that you do not wish
to come under the
rule of someone
against whom you have so
recently achieved victory.
Thus, in four hours,
I will attack again.
The attacker will be one
of my most trusted aids,
Cocytus, on his own.
If you are able to prevail
against him, as well,
then I promise to leave
your people alone
in peace from this day forward.
We surrender--
[AINS] I prefer you fight
instead of giving up
without trying.
That would displease me.
He's toying with us.
[AINS]
My business here is done.
You have four hours.
I suggest you use them well.
[SHASURYU] If I may ask,
will this ice melt away?
[AINS] Mm. That's right.
Fear not, I simply did not want
to dirty myself with your mud.
I will dispel my
magic's effect later.
[BOTH gasp]
[AINS]
Farewell, Lizard Men. Gate!
Till next time, if you live.
See ya!
Try not to get killed out there.
Um, please, take care
of yourselves, I guess.
[VICTIM]
I bid you farewell.
You are now free to move.
[chuckles]
Do try to enjoy your
last few hours, okay?
Curse all of them!
[SUKYU]
Feels like a ritual sacrifice.
So, what's the plan?
We'll call every warrior class
Lizard Men to arms, at once.
With all of us, we just might...
Could I ask that it
just be five of us?
If their goal is to demonstrate
their overwhelming power,
they are unlikely
to kill us all.
Especially if they
want to rule us.
If that's the case, we will
need a central figure
for the survivors
to rally around.
A sound argument.
Yes.
But... Who stay?
It won't be me. I'd
rather go down fighting.
Then that's what we'll do.
And Crusch will
lead the survivors.
Just a minute!
I'm fighting, too!
Zaryusu, why are you
willing to be a martyr now?
Because our people have been
given a chance at living.
[CRUSCH growls]
I'll let the two of you
work this thing out.
See you all in four hours.
Crusch. Understand.
There's no way that I could!
We could still win, after all!
My powers could keep you alive
until we grasp victory!
I refuse to let the female
I love die like that.
[gasps]
Would you please
grant this foolish male
his dying wish?
That's not fair.
Sorry.
You know, you'll
probably die out there.
Yeah.
And you're asking me to sit back
and watch it happen,
after we've become
so attached to one another?
Yeah.
I'm so happy we met, Zaryusu.
But also, sad.
[gasps]
Huh?
Impregnate me!
[AINS] The Lizard Men have
come into direct contact
with the overwhelming
power of Nazarick.
For the sake of their species,
the warriors step forward
to the final battle.
Cocytus, the guardian
of the 5th floor,
is their one and only opponent.
In this last ditch battle,
he overwhelms them
with terrifying ease.
Chapter 5: "The freezing god".
The miracle is upon you.