[SEBAS] I will have to offer
my gratitude to Lord Ains.
I did not expect this level
of support from the Tomb.
Yes, command of this
operation will fall to me.
If you have any objection
to the supreme one's decision,
voice it now, please.
[SEBAS]
No, of course not.
[DEMIURGE]
Then I hope you are not under
any mistaken impressions.
We've assembled to cull
Eight Fingers from existence.
They've spit in the collective
faces of the supreme ones
with their brazen actions
and must be dealt
with accordingly.
I understand perfectly.
Rescuing Tuare is insignificant
next to avenging Ains Ool Goan.
Now that that's clear,
please know that I also hope
for Tuare's safe return.
Should the poor thing perish,
I doubt her body could withstand
the intense strain
of resurrection.
How kind of you to say so.
Do you have a plan for
finding Eight Fingers?
There's no need for such a plan.
I've already
attained information
on seven of their bases.
Sorry, Sebas, but you
do not need to know.
The success of our plan relies
on compartmentalizing
certain components.
Once Tuare is safe,
you will return with her
to Nazarick, and leave
the rest to us.
I understand.
[DEMIURGE] Solution, back up
Sebas for the time being.
[SOLUTION]
Very well, Lord Demiurge.
What I'm about to tell you
is a matter of great
importance. Entoma?
[ENTOMA]
Acknowledged.
Killing this person
is strictly forbidden.
Understood, Shalltear?
Oh, ha, ha!
Poke fun at the vampire,
why dontcha? Jerk.
[DEMIURGE]
What is it, Shadow Demon?
Excellent.
It appears we now have
one more Eight Fingers base
to attack tonight.
Mare.
You and Entomah will focus
on the new location.
Um. Kay, I'll do my best
not to disappoint you.
This is a grand opportunity.
Use this mission
to show Lord Ains
your unwavering
devotion and love.
Failure is forbidden.
See that you provide results
that will wipe the slate clean
of any mistakes, understood?
So, uh, what about me?
Sorry, but you'll
have to stand down.
I'm concerned you'll lose
yourself to your Blood Frenzy.
You know what, I am not
even mad about it.
Not one little bit!
Now, then. Phase two
of plan "Gehenna."
It's a tad complex,
so do pay attention.
That mythril must've
cost a pretty copper.
You sure you wanna dye it?
It does mean a lot since
Renner gave it to me,
but it just stands out too much.
However, it's virtually silent.
So, I think it's perfect
for infiltrating.
All captains, gather 'round!
We're going to go over the plan!
Ah!
[LAKYUS]
All right.
This operation's goal
is to raid eight buildings
in Eight Finger's possession
and take control of them.
But we only have seven squads.
Once we've taken control
of our assigned buildings,
everyone here will head
for the last location,
so don't dawdle.
In other words, it's
first come first served!
I'm sure you're all
aware of our enemy's
overwhelming strength.
Don't let your guards down.
[BRAIN] The squads look
fairly competent.
Even the Marquis' men.
They're a full group of former
orichalcum class adventurers.
Name's Lockmeyer.
Nice to meet you.
[GAGARAN]
Hey, virgin!
[CLIMB] Miss Gagaran.
Is something wrong?
You tell me, kid.
Thought you might be nervous
and figured a playful
pat on your tight little
tushie would loosen ya up.
You must be Brain Unglaus.
I guess you'll do.
I'm glad I passed the test.
She was measuring me up,
trying to figure out
whether I was a warrior she
can entrust with you or not.
Is that true, Gagaran?
Absolutely not!
If you died tonight, I wouldn't
lose any sleep over it.
But with him there,
things'll be easier.
I wouldn't be so
certain of that.
There are monsters in this world
you couldn't even fathom.
Huh. So you're the prudent type.
I'm not totally adverse
to a man like that.
How about a little
one-on-one in the sack?
I think I'll pass.
The pressure might crush me.
You're probably right.
That's too bad.
Watch yourself out there, okay?
Uh, yes ma'am!
[BRAIN]
She's a nice lady.
[CLIMB] Everyone in
Blue Rose is just as kind.
Well, time to get going.
Right.
[LOCKMEYER]
Wait, hold on, it's me!
I just got back! So jumpy.
I scouted the place
with invisibility magic.
There's a young woman being
held captive in a prison cell.
and about five people who look
like they fit the description
of Six Arms members.
Five of them?
Sucks for us, but it
might be a good thing.
If Six Arms is gathered here,
then the other locations
should fall without much
of an effort on our part.
What are we gonna do?
[CLIMB] It's going to be
impossible to take this place
without significant force.
Let's fall back.
Fine with me. Let's...
[CLIMB]
No way.
What a coincidence,
running into you
here of all places.
Lord Sebas, what are
doing around here
at this hour?
As it happens,
the woman I mentioned
rescuing has been taken
by Eight Fingers.
I was instructed to meet
them at this location.
[CLIMB]
Then she must be...
Can you tell me more
about the woman you saw
in the prison cell?
That's good to know.
Having most of Six Arms here
will make my job
a fair bit easier.
Does that mean...
you're willing to help us?
I know it's a lot to ask,
but we really need you.
I'd be happy to.
Even If you weren't here,
my duty would be unchanged.
I will deal with
the Six Arms members
and provide you cover.
You have our thanks, Lord Sebas.
I will go in through
the front entrance.
While I'm keeping their
attention away from you,
I would appreciate if you
would rescue Tuare for me.
You can count on it.
What should those
without stealth do?
If it's just the three of us,
our magic caster should be
able to make us invisible
long enough to get
past the front.
[BRAIN] I was more concerned
with the others.
Their armor is so noisy they
couldn't sneak past the dead.
I swear, we'll bring
Tuare back safely.
I would be much obliged, Climb.
[MAN 11A] Right on schedule.
They're waiting.
[SEBAS]
Hm?
[MAN 11B]
The main event.
[MAN 11C]
Better put up a good fight!
Aren't there supposed
to be five of you left?
[EDSTROM]
We're more than enough
even for one of your strength.
Though, I didn't think the
one who beat Succulent
would be someone of your age.
[MALMVIST]
That just proves he's worthless.
Not only did he fail, he failed
in front of Cocco Doll,
a client.
He's embarrassed
us beyond words.
[PESHURIAN] Well, he insisted
that he was beaten
by Brain Unglaus,
not an old man.
[DAVERNOCH] Either way,
this imprudent butler
had the audacity to
start all this trouble.
so he will die first.
Look up there.
[MALMVIST] Some of our Noble
patrons like a little
entertainment with their dinner.
We'll torture you for a while,
then finish you off just
in time for dessert.
Is that Zero fellow watching
from there, as well?
Why, yes, he is in fact.
[EDSTROM]
What was that about, old man?
Trying to challenge our leader?
[SEBAS]
Pay it no mind.
Where is she?
What have you done
with young Tuare?
What if I said she was dead?
From what I've seen,
I doubt you would be that kind.
[DAVERNOCH cackles]
Got me there.
Even in life, I lacked mercy.
Lucky for her, she's meant
to be a gift for Cocco Doll.
She's safely secure until then.
Then I won't keep
you or your patrons
waiting any longer.
Attack me all at once,
and you might last ten seconds.
You're either insane or
have a death wish, human.
He's probably never met someone
who was truly strong before.
[MALMVIST] Either way,
I'm happy to oblige him.
Malmvist of the Thousand Kills.
[EDSTROM]
Of the Dancing Scimitar.
I am Edstrom.
[PESHURIAN]
Peshurian of the Spatial Slash.
[DAVERNOCH]
And Davernoch the Undead King.
Is that so? You poor fool.
That title is far
beyond your reach.
[yelling]
There's only one
person who can claim
to be the Ruler of Death.
And you couldn't
fathom his power.
Your deserved far worse
than a quick death
for your arrogance.
Did you manage to
find Zero, Solution?
He does not appear
to be here, my lord.
[SEBAS] Hm. Then I have another
ten seconds to spare.
[LOCKMEYER]
Here it is.
[bell rings]
Are you Tuare?
[gasps]
[HILMA]
What is going on?
Excuse me, little girl?
[HILMA]
Or boy?
What brings you here
at this hour, little one?
I'm trying to find the
most important person
in the mansion.
Is that you, lady?
No, I...
Actually. Yes, I am.
Now could you tell me
how you got in?
[sighs] Thank goodness,
I thought I screwed up.
[door opens]
--[gasps]
--[MARE] Uh.
I need you to come
with me now, okay?
[screams]
You broke it!
Stop! That hurts!
Let go! Please, let me go!
There's no time, lady.
We're late enough as it is.
I'll let you handle
things from here.
[ENTOMA]
'Kay!
[ENTOMA] Get that stuff home
as quickly as you can!
It will be of great use to us!
[ENTOMA]
There's still some left!
Whoopsie daisy.
[ENTOMA]
Mm!
Nothing beats well-muscled
man meat when you're dieting.
Hey, you.
What kind of meat makes
a creepy crunch like that?
[ENTOMA]
Human.
Down to the bone.
How interesting.
I didn't think Eight Fingers
kept monsters around.
This'll be fun.
[ENTOMA]
Actually, could we pretend like
we never saw each other?
I'm in a hurry.
[GAGARAN]
No can do.
I'm one of the top
adventurers in the Kingdom.
I can't catch a man-eating
monster in the act
and just let it go.
Sorry, creepy.
[ENTOMA]
This is so much trouble.
Still, you're strong.
Maybe I'll preserve you
for a midnight snack.
[GAGARAN yells]
Come on! I'm gettin'
bored here!
[ENTOMA] Oh! You're quick
with that hammer!
Whoosh whoosh!
I'll crush you!
[ENTOMA]
Ah.
You dare to soil the uniform
my creator gave me?
I will end you.
[GAGARAN]
What was that?
[ENTOMA]
Hard Armor Bug!
I'm an entomancer, see?
I summon all kinds of fun
little insects, like this one.
[ENTOMA]
Blade bug!
[ENTOMA] And then I put
them to work for me.
I'll kill you now.
I really didn't want to,
just so you know.
But you're in my way!
Finally taking this seriously?
Good, bring it on!
[GAGARAN yells]
[gasps]
Thanks for the save, Tia.
[ENTOMA]
Ninja skills?
So, your blood does
in fact flow red.
What a surprise.
Of course it does,
what did you expect?
I just thought it
would be blue by now,
like some kind of cool power up.
It could happen.
[GAGARAN]
I didn't change races.
[TIA]
All right, then a class change.
[ENTOMA]
Are you done wasting my time?
Spider Talisman!
Shadow Clone Technique!
[ENTOMA]
Hard Bullet Bugs!
[gasps]
Adamantine Shield Technique!
[yells]
What's with her?
She defended without
looking at me!
Wide field of view?
It's something else, but I
can't put my finger on it.
This is bad.
I don't think we have the
slightest chance of winning.
[ENTOMA]
I don't need these bugs anymore.
Come on, it's your turn!
[ENTOMA]
Oopsie!
I thought I'd eaten my fill
earlier, but I'm hungry again.
These two morsels should
really hit the spot.
[ENTOMA yells]
Flame Burst!
[gasps]
[ENTOMA]
Thunderbird Talisman!
This is so gross.
I can't stand
things that slither!
--[TIA screams]
--Tia!
[ENTOMA]
Thunderbird Swarm Talisman!
[TIA groans]
[GAGARAN]
No!
[ENTOMA]
Explosive Talisman!
[TIA yells]
[ENTOMA]
Sharp Cutting Talisman!
Piercing Wind Attack!
[GAGARAN]
Tia!
Creepy punk!
[ENTOMA]
I had planned to eat you first,
but she looks tasty
on top of filling,
so I guess I'll spoil
myself just this once.
[EVILEYE]
Don't get any closer to her!
[ENTOMA]
Who are you?
[EVILEYE]
Back at you.
Is a man-eating monster
in a maid uniform
some kind of sick joke?
I can't imagine
anyone would be happy
with something like you
attending to them.
You smell of blood
and cockroaches.
[ENTOMA]
What did you say?
[TIA]
Evileye.
[EVILEYE]
Good grief, you're hopeless.
You need to size up your
opponent next time!
This one is stronger
than you two.
That said. I'm
stronger than her.
You picked on the wrong
girls, worm breath.
Time to swat you!
[ENTOMA]
No one would be happy
to have me attend to them?
How dare you.
None of you will
leave here alive!
[EVILEYE] What a foolish
attack. Reverse Gravity!
[yelps]
[EVILEYE]
You're in the way!
Heal Tia's wounds or something!
[EVILEYE]
Are you with that Demon God?
In that case. Vermin Bane!
[ENTOMA]
Huh?
[ENTOMA screams]
[TIA]
What did you use?
[EVILEYE]
Insecticide magic.
A spell of my own design.
I call it "Vermin Bane."
[TIA]
Her face is melting.
[EVILEYE] You're kidding.
It was a mask all along?
[ENTOMA whimpering]
[TIA]
A Lip Bug!
It devours the vocal chords
of its human victims
and perfectly imitates
their voice.
[ENTOMA]
How dare you. How dare you!
[GAGARAN]
You sound a lot more endearing
like that, y'know?
I think I prefer
your voice this way!
[ENTOMA]
Damn humans!
[EVILEYE]
Vermin Bane!
[ENTOMA]
That cursed spell.
You're the only one I need
to fear. If I kill you,
everything else will
go down like a simple job,
and I can feast!
Paralysis Technique!
[ENTOMA grunts]
[GAGARAN yells]
[EVILEYE]
Crystal Lance!
Vermin Bane!
[ENTOMA grunts]
[EVILEYE gasps]
This is different. Crystal Wall!
[ENTOMA grunts]
Did you hear the
sound that made?
Her little outfit
is as heavy as my armor.
How's that possible?
[ENTOMA] That stingy spell
of yours is getting annoying!
What now, boss?
[EVILEYE] Attack her with
full force and wear her down.
Now that's the type of
plan I can get behind.
Give me the chance,
and I'll squash her!
[GAGARAN yells]
[EVILEYE]
Acid Splash!
[ENTOMA]
Explosive Talisman!
[TIA]
Adamantine Shield Technique!
[EVILEYE]
Vermin Bane!
[GAGARAN panting]
We did it.
[ENTOMA grunting]
[TIA]
I'll finish her.
[EVILEYE]
Right.
[TIA gasps]
[EVILEYE gasps]
[DEMIURGE] I'd appreciate it
if you stopped there, ladies.
[GAGARAN] Hey is he...
Is he like you, Evileye?
[DEMIURGE]
Are you all right?
I will handle things
from here on out.
Please, head back,
heal up, rest a bit.
[EVILEYE]
Leave.
That is a monster
among monsters.
What are you gonna do, shorty?
[EVILEYE]
Don't worry.
Once I've bought you
enough time to escape,
I'll get away using
teleportation magic.
[DEMIURGE]
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Shall we get started?
[EVILEYE]
Go! Now!
[DEMIURGE] It would grieve me
to part so soon after meeting,
so I'll block
all teleportation.
Dimensional Lock.
[EVILEYE]
Maximize Magic! Shard Buckshot!
Nullification?
[DEMIURGE]
Hellfire Wall!
[EVILEYE gasps]
[EVILEYE growls]
[DEMIURGE]
My deepest condolences.
I didn't think that level
of flame would kill them.
I assumed they were
at least as strong as you.
Why would you team up with them?
If that did them in,
they were obviously weaklings.
[EVILEYE]
Don't you dare call them that!
[DEMIURGE]
Aspect of the Devil: Demon Arm.
[EVILEYE gasps]
[EVILEYE]
Translocation Damage!
Penetrate Maximize Magic!
Crystal Dagger!
[EVILEYE] It went right through
his defenses, and nothing?
[DEMIURGE] Aspect of the
Devil: Razor Sharp Claws!
[EVILEYE] I can't get away
while carrying their bodies.
Which means...
So be it. Let's do this!
[EVILEYE gasps]
[DEMIURGE gasps]
[AINS]
Evening.
So which one of you
will be my foe?
[AINS] A powerful, masked
demon known as Jaldabaoth
suddenly appeared
in the royal capital.
Evileye, a member of Blue Rose,
realizes she is outmatched
and prepares to die.
However, the reinforcement
hired by Marquis Raeven
arrives just in time.
An adamantite adventurer,
the black-helmed Momon.
Chapter Twelve: "The Final
Battle of the Disturbance."
What in the world are
you trying to do?