[BLACK SCRIPTURE CAPTAIN]
Oh, is that a Rubik's cube?
Haven't seen one in ages.
I could always get one side,
but anything past that was
a true test of patience.
Of course. That's the point.
Another trial from
the Six Great Gods.
In six centuries,
few have passed it.
So, what's so dire
that it called for
a gathering of all the officers?
You got the report,
same as the rest of us.
[ZESSHI]
Didn't read it.
[sighs]
[ZESSHI] It's easier to ask
someone who knows the situation.
Your last mission
was to subjugate
the Catastrophe
Dragon Lord, right?
I'm assuming seventh seat,
Thousand Leagues Astrologer's
prediction was faulty.
We ran into trouble.
A powerful vampire.
It murdered Cedran
and Beaumarchais,
and severely injured
Lady Kaire, so we retreated.
Myriad Barrier and
Divine Chain, dead, huh?
We just can't keep
the ninth seat filled.
So. Who do you
think is stronger?
Me or that blood sucker?
You are, of course.
I see. That's disappointing.
I thought it might
be able to defeat me.
Come to think of it,
I heard the Sunlit Scripture
was wiped out, too.
It was.
A caster named Ains Ooal Gown
has claimed responsibility.
But we can't confirm it
since no bodies
were left behind.
I see. So, he's strong?
Hard to say.
The Sunlit's Captain lost
to the Blue Rose once.
Of course Nigun was
outdone by those harpies.
Why is a strong man
so hard to find, Captain?
It doesn't matter if he's
hideous, inside or out.
He could even be
inhuman for all I care.
Best me, and his seed
is all I would require.
Our legacy would be a child
of unmatched strength.
Oh, they would make
Mommy proud someday.
[footsteps]
[RIGRIT]
It's been a long time, Tsa.
What's wrong?
Did you forget your manners
while you've been stuck in here?
[laughs] Apologies, Rigrit.
I was merely
trembling with emotion
at seeing my old friend again.
Friends, are we?
The only friend I knew
wore that armor.
'Course, it's been empty
for over 200 years.
[PLATINUM DRAGON LORD]
And I've been apologizing
ever since, but you
never let it go.
Traveling in this body
is out of the
question, I'm afraid.
[RIGRIT]
Hmph.
[PLATINUM DRAGON LORD]
So...
Still clinging to the
adventurer's lifestyle, I see.
No, I'm retired now.
I had that crybaby, Inberun
take my place in Blue Rose.
'Course, she wouldn't
do it willingly,
so I made a bet
with the little imp.
If I beat her, she had
to do whatever I said.
Spanked her real good, too.
[laughs]
You're probably the only human
in existence who could do so.
Well, don't praise me too much,
my friends helped out.
And, that crybaby
may be a tough cookie,
but there are tougher out there.
Like you, for example.
If you hadn't constrained
yourself, I have no doubt
you'd be the most powerful
being in the world by now.
[PLATINUM DRAGON LORD]
Hm... I'm not so sure.
There is a power in motion
to corrupt the world once again.
An aftershock of the last one.
Is this "power" simply reckless
and refusing to work
alongside the world?
No. It is evil,
plain and simple.
[RIGRIT]
I see.
My old friend, I hate to do this
after you've given up
being an adventurer,
but may I ask a favor?
I suppose.
I'd like you to
gather information
on items that can
rival Guild Weapons.
Or rather,
special items from Yggdrasil.
[PLATINUM DRAGON LORD]
By the way,
what happened to your ring?
I doubt there's anyone
who could have
taken it from you.
I passed it on to the youngster.
That's an item that
transcends human bounds.
I would rather it not fall
into incapable hands.
But,
if you feel confident
in your decision,
then that's good enough for me.
[BOULLOPE]
Listen!
It's high time we kick the
Empire out of our borders
and take the fight
to them, for once!
[NOBLEMAN 1A]
I couldn't agree more.
Constantly fighting off their
invasions is not only tiresome,
but a waste of good coin.
Those imperial dogs
need to learn
that Re-Estize has
fangs of its own,
and we aren't afraid
to bite back.
[NOBLEMAN 1C] You couldn't
be more right, Count.
We must strike swiftly!
If our strength declines,
Baharuth will throw
everything they have at us.
The nobles know nothing of war.
All they care about
is their pockets.
But as long as those
pockets run deep,
we can keep the Empire in check.
We appease the nobles
to keep the Kingdom united.
Right.
[RAMPOSA]
Be that as it may.
I deeply regret my
inability to defend you
from their scheming.
I should have done better.
Fifty soldiers
were insufficient.
You needed more
men and armaments.
Please, forgive me
for my failure.
[gasps] I was glad to do it.
My duty is to protect King and
country no matter the odds.
Thank you.
Oh!
Renner!
Hello, Father! Chief warrior!
Princess, wait!
[RENNER] The nobles certainly
kept you in there for a while.
Indeed.
I had a wonderful
thought earlier.
I've been eagerly waiting
to speak with you about it,
but your meeting seemed
to go on forever.
Well, I'm here now.
Tell me all about it, my dear.
I would love to, Father,
but I'm afraid it's
time for my stroll.
I can't miss it.
Climb and I were just on
our way to wander for a bit.
I see. Then, don't
let me keep you.
But, please, come by
my room when you're done
so we can talk.
As you wish.
Let's be off, Climb.
Excuse us, sir.
About Master Ains Ooal Gown.
I would like to speak
with him directly,
so I might thank him for saving
my most loyal attendant.
Would you make that
happen for me, Gazef?
As benevolent as he is,
I think those words
alone would do.
I'll be sure to pass them along.
Master Ains!
Sorry to keep you waiting, I am!
Bring you the giant
basilisk, I have!
Drive it to you, I shall,
for a loyal servant, Hamsuke is!
[AINS] Its size is impressive,
but if Hamusuke
can cause it to flee,
it's level certainly isn't.
[NARBERAL]
My lor--Mr. Momon.
There's no need to lower
yourself. Let me fry it.
[AINS]
Entertaining as that might be,
your magic would
hit Hamusuke, too.
[NARBERAL]
Right.
[AINS grunts]
[AINS]
Hmph. Pathetic.
[HAMUSUKE]
Not at all!
Truly impressive, it was!
I agree, Mr. Momon.
[AINS]
Nabe.
I'll have you report back
to the adventurer's guild.
Take Hamusuke with you.
As you wish, sir.
What are you
going to do, Master?
[AINS]
Nazarick requires my attention.
[MARE]
W-Welcome back, my lord.
[AINS]
Mm.
[MARE]
Your ring. Thanks again.
[AINS] Mm. Well done, Mare.
Is Albedo out?
[MARE]
No, she's here.
Actually, she said she
would be in your room
until you returned.
She hasn't left all day.
[AINS]
I see.
She may have a secret report
or other urgent matter.
I should go at once.
Welcome home, Lord Ains.
I've been waiting for you.
[ALBEDO sighs]
Would you like some
dinner, my lord?
A hot, relaxing bath?
Or, perhaps, to have me?
Take your pick.
[AINS sputters]
[AINS]
What are you doing, Albedo?
Newlywed roleplaying, my Lord.
You had a long day of
hard work away from home.
Then, finally, you return,
and find your blushing bride,
ready to please you.
Appealing scenario, yes?
[MOMONGA]
Seriously?
This is why she didn't
go out today? ERP?
Wait, who cares about the why?
Oh, I've never even
gone out with a woman,
let alone married one.
What does she expect me to say?
How would a charming prince,
a ladies' man, react?
[AINS]
It was quite appealing... baby?
[gasps] I'm glad
you think so, Lord.
[giggles]
[AINS grunts]
[gasps]
[AINS]
What's wrong?
I've really messed up.
Ordinarily, roleplay etiquette
dictates that a new bride
greet her husband dressed
in nothing but an apron
for the final showdown.
Say the word,
and I will correct
my mistake at once.
Uh...
[ALBEDO]
Of course, I'll happily change
for your viewing pleasure, Lord!
[MOMONGA]
Albedo and the other NPCs
that my friends created are
like our children, in a sense.
I couldn't do
anything uncalled for
to those who are dear
to me. Besides...
Albedo is like this
because I changed
her original settings.
[AINS clears throat]
This was fun,
but it's time we
stopped goofing around.
All the data we've
gathered recently
isn't going to review itself.
Oh. As you wish,
Lord. Let's begin.
[AINS]
This is the world map we managed
to acquire from E-Rantel.
That's all?
[AINS]
I understand your discontent.
It's sketchy, and only details
human nations around this area.
But getting anything
more would prove
too difficult at present.
[ALBEDO]
Understood, my lord.
I will make copies,
and distribute them to
the other guardians at once.
[AINS]
Before you do,
I'll familiarize you
with the key points.
This is the Great
Tomb of Nazarick,
and the large forest
to the north
is the Great Forest of Tob.
How is the dummy
Nazarick progressing?
Well. Precisely on schedule.
[ELDER LICH 1A]
Hold on! That's no good.
[AURA] Hi! Which team are
you from, little guy?
Team "U." Number three,
Lady Aura.
Let's see, Team U...
Storage warehouse inventory.
Ah, found you!
'Kay, talk to me, impy.
[IMP 1A] There's a problem
with the wood's diameter.
[BUKUBUKU]
Lunch time! Take a break!
Sure, whatever you say,
Lady Bukubuku Chagama!
Sorry, impy, but my
wonderful creator says
take a break and
I'm doing just that.
Could you come back in an hour?
Very well, my lady.
[giggles]
Pestonya! What's on the menu?
[PESTONYA]
I have prepared a hamburger
just as you
requested, Lady Aura.
With two pickles and
fries on the side
with the skin intact,
and a cola for your drink.
Uh--woof!
Time to eat! Time to eat!
[gasps]
[AURA]
Get in my belly!
Tasty!
The Grade A,
100 percent ground beef
certainly hits the spot,
but beef and pork
might be even better!
I think three patties like
that should do the trick.
Then I'll relay that to
the head chef immediately.
Woof!
[AURA]
Awesome. Thanks.
It's great to hear
Lady Bukubuku
Chagama's voice again.
[AINS]
I see.
I should have guessed she'd
take a liking to that watch.
It's adorable.
And, to be honest,
I can't blame her.
Not only does she get to hear
the voice a supreme being,
but it just so happens to
belong to her birth mother.
For a Guardian, there could
be no greater reward.
Other than being
your servant, of course.
Being here by your side is
an honor none of us deserve.
[AINS]
Mm. Y-Yes. Now, as I was saying.
West of the mountains
is the Re-Estize Kingdom.
Here's the capital.
Sebas is there
collecting data for me.
Any word?
[ALBEDO] He is making
regular reports, my Lord.
However,
Shalltear's assailant
remains a mystery to us.
We have yet to find any leads.
[AINS] I see. Have Sebas
double his efforts.
On the other side
of the mountains,
to the east, is the
Baharuth Empire.
They attack
Re-Estize constantly.
E-Rantel, which serves
as Momon's home base,
becomes a military
outpost in times of war.
And to the south,
beyond the forest,
is the Slane Theocracy.
They're the ones who
attacked Carne Village.
Pitiful humans.
If we're lucky, they'll
kill themselves for us.
[AINS] Additionally,
several races of demi-humans
have formed a nation
to the north.
The Argland Council State.
From what I've been
able to gather,
they're led by as many
as five or seven dragons.
So, they are in this world.
[AINS] The Holy Kingdom lies
to the southwest of Re-Estize,
and in the wilderness
next to that,
demi-humans of all kinds engage
in disputes almost daily.
Isn't that where you
sent Demiurge, my lord?
[AINS]
Yes.
He's conducting experiments
in parchment production.
With a supply of
high-quality parchment,
we could make as many scrolls
as we would ever need.
I believe that covers it.
Which of these nations do you
feel we should be wary of?
I would say the Slane Theocracy.
Challenging you may have
blown up in their face before,
but they're foolish
and prideful.
For all we know, they are
already plotting their revenge.
[AINS]
Hm...
[MOMONGA]
She could be right about that.
[gasps] Begging
your pardon, Lord.
But, until we know more,
we should be wary
of every nation.
[AINS]
Uh, yes, of course.
And, even if the countries
of this world aren't a threat,
there are individuals
who could surprise us.
How is Shalltear doing?
There doesn't appear
to by any problems
with her physical recovery.
But, I'm afraid her
psychological health
is another matter entirely.
[SHALLTEAR gulping]
[SHALLTEAR]
Ah!
Ugh. This barely has
me drunk at all.
[PIKI] Given your
resistance to poisons,
this may be a futile endeavor.
[yells]
[PIKI] But, what do I know?
You did chug it down.
Why not retire for
the day, my lady?
No, I don't wanna go back yet.
[PIKI]
Very well.
[door opens]
[PIKI]
Welcome.
Yo, Piki!
[PIKI]
What can I get for you?
The us'.
[PIKI]
Very good, Mr. Eclair.
My original cocktail,
a Nazarick.
For you, my lady.
To perk you up!
Ah--
[PIKI] Perhaps you should keep
your flippers to yourself.
Terribly sorry.
It won't happen again.
Ah. If it isn't the
assistant butler Eclair.
Something the matter?
Not to be rude, but you
don't look well, miss.
Oh, you know, no big.
I just managed to fail
in the worst way possible.
That's why I'm
escaping into alcohol.
Like any godforsaken
floor guardian should.
[ECLAIR]
Hm?
[PIKI]
No idea.
[whines] Ains, my lord,
how could I do that to you?
[ALBEDO]
The fact that she lost control
and turned against you is
only compounded by the fact
that she tried to kill you.
She's sick with guilt.
[AINS] She only lost control
because I failed to anticipate
the existence of world
level items here.
It wasn't her fault.
I've told her that
countless times by now.
[MOMONGA] I guess even
resurrection can't completely
erase the effects of
a world level item.
I would hate to
speak out of turn,
but I'd like to suggest
a means to cure her.
[AINS]
Go ahead.
The world turns on
reward and penalty.
If you were to punish
Shalltear, my lord,
her sense of guilt will fade.
Fault or no,
it would be a mercy.
[MOMONGA]
I'm glad she's here.
I'm just a simple office worker.
I never would have
figured that out.
[AINS]
All right. I'll consider it.
Please, forgive me for
overstepping my bounds, lord.
[AINS]
You did no such thing.
Suggestions like that
are precisely why
you are Nazarick's
guardian supervisor.
I am pleased.
[ALBEDO]
Then so am I.
[AINS]
Hm. Now then.
I believe Cocytus
wished to see me?
Yes. He's waiting
in the Throne Room.
Shall we go, my lord?
[AINS]
Cocytus, is it ready?
[COCYTUS] Yes. Everything
is as you requested.
I will depart as soon as I have
your blessing, Lord Ains.
[AINS]
Mm. You have it.
I leave you in charge
of everything.
[COCYTUS]
As a guardian and a warrior,
it is an unexpected delight
to be given command
of Nazarick's first
war in this world.
I will serve you well,
Overlord. This I swear.
[AINS]
Excellent.
I have no doubt you will live up
to all my expectations.
[COCYTUS]
Excuse me.
[AINS] Be sure to keep
in regular contact
with him, Albedo.
As you wish, my lord.
[AINS]
Now then.
Momon still has some
guild quests to complete.
I'll be in E-Rantel for a while.
Please be careful!
Whoever possesses the world
item that took control
of Shalltear may be waiting
to attack you out in the open.
[AINS] Hmph! If they do, I will
crush them or die trying.
Still, be at ease, Albedo.
If they show themselves,
my priority is to withdraw.
At least until I've learned
everything I can about them.
[MOMONGA] There's no doubt
that items from Yggdrasil,
even the most powerful ones,
exist in this world.
Which means there's
every possibility
that whoever attacked Shalltear
is another player, like me.
I should assume the
worst-case scenario,
and refrain from any actions
that might antagonize them.
Very well then.
I will keep watch over
the Great Tomb of Nazarick
in your absence, my lord.
When you return, it will be
exactly as you
left it or better.
It's my wifely duty.
Uh...
[ZARYUSU] This is hardly a place
for the chief to be seen,
don't you think?
Zaryusu.
[ZARYUSU] Brother, are you...
eyeing my crop?
[SHASURYU]
Please.
I just came by to see if the
fish had gotten any bigger.
[ZARYUSU]
So, you don't want to eat them.
[SHASURYU growls]
They're good.
Way more fat on them than
the ones you catch fishing.
That so?
[ZARYUSU] When they hit
your tongue, that prime,
greasy goodness
fills your mouth,
and when you bite into them?
Oh, they melt!
My sister-in-law was right.
Your tail gives
you away, brother.
[SHASURYU]
What? Come on!
My own wife is talking
behind my back?
It's just a stupid
twitch! Nothing more!
If you ever knock that arrow,
you'll know exactly how I feel.
It will never happen,
you know that.
Why not? Because of
that damn mark?
[ZARYUSU] I left the tribe
to travel the world.
Our laws are clear.
My knowledge is respected,
but I'll always be an outsider
in our people's eyes.
The elders, you mean.
Y'know... This, uh,
what'd you call it?
[ZARYUSU]
A fish farm?
[SHASURYU]
Yeah. It's great!
No one in the tribe's
ever done anything like it.
I couldn't have made it
without you, brother.
All I've done is
drool over them.
Come on, I know that
you spoke to everyone
on my behalf.
Once they get a little larger,
I'll make sure you get
the pick of the lot.
[SHASURYU] Huh. Don't keep
me waiting too long.
--[CHILDREN giggling]
--[splashing]
[BOTH gasp]
Hide the children in the huts!
If you aren't a warrior,
get in your homes now!
[MESSENGER 1A]
Weak ones!
I am herald to the Great One,
sent to deliver a message.
Listen and heed my words.
Henceforth, death's
gaze is upon you!
[AINS] After receiving the
death sentence from Lord Ains
messengers, the Lizard Men
of the Green Claw tribe
decide to fight. Even though
they face an enemy
with overwhelming power. Putting
into motion his proposed plan
to form an alliance
among the Lizard Men,
Zaryusu leaves for the
villages of the Red Eye
and Dragon Tusk tribes.
Chapter 2: "Departure".
Everything in order to survive.