(Wind blowing)
Are you kidding me?!
What's up with this school?
It's friggin' huge!
"Kyokusei Dormitory"...
Where the heck is this place?
The sun's going down!
(Crows cawing)
I'm tired... I'm cold...
And this dried squid ain't
gonna cut it anymore.
Ugh...
There sure are a lot
of pompous‐looking
buildings around here.
I have no idea what they
could all be for...
Well, this school looks like
it's got plenty of cash.
All the facilities are awesome.
So, maybe my dorm will be
all fancy‐schmancy, too.
I can't wait!
(Cawing)
(Ominous music)
(More cawing)
Guess not...
(Opening Song)
(Door creaks)
Hello?
Smoke?
Something's on fire!
(Clatter)
(Loud bang)
A‐an earthquake?
Uh!
(Numerous animal sounds)
Usako! Kamosuke! Shikanoshin!
[GIRL]
Stop, stop running!
Please!
[FEMALE VOICE]
Hey, Room No. 116!
You cannot bring wild game
into the dorms.
You do that again,
I will skin you alive!
I swear to God!
[GIRL] I'm sorry!
[SOMA]
Ooohhh...
[FEMALE VOICE]
Oh, and Room No. 208:
You turned an empty room into
a smoker again, didn't you?
How about I hang you upside‐down
and flavorize you!
How'd ya like that?
[RED‐HAIRED STUDENT]
Yeah, yeah, I'm sorry.
And you, Room. No. 205!
If you've trashed your
room again, I'll gut you
and feed you to the hogs!
I know! I know! I'm sorry!
But these morons won't
stop fighting in my room!
(Arguing in background)
You wanna throw down, bro?
Fine by me, dude!
You're Soma Yukihira,
the transfer student
looking to move in, yes?
I am the dorm mother for
this establishment...
Fumio. Or Miss Daimidou... Hmph.
Or the "Holy Mother
of Kyokusei".
You can call me that.
I'm surrounded by
nut‐jobs again!
Okay, young man...
What ingredients have
you prepared for us?
Huh? Ingredients for what?
Uh! What else?!
[FUMIO]
For the famous Kyokusei
Entrance Exam, of course!
"1: Those who wish to
board here must create a dish.
Residency will only be
granted if said dish's
flavor is acceptable.
2: Judging will be by
the dorm supervisor.
And 3: Applicants may bring
any ingredients they wish."
How was I supposed
to know that?!
I didn't bring any
ingredients with me!
Then you've lost
by default.
Unless you show what
you can do, you have
no place here.
Huh?! So what
about tonight?
You will be sleeping outside.
You've gotta be
kidding me!
Do you know how cold it gets
out there in April?!
Come on, lady! I'm about
to fall over from
hunger and exhaustion!
Hmph. Oh, well aren't you
pathetic? You can eat.
We've got some leftovers
in the kitchen, but
it's a mish‐mash.
Huh?
Guess today is
just not your day.
[SOMA]
Ah! Can I use the
leftovers for the test?
What's that?
I'm gonna do this
"test" of yours.
Where's the kitchen?
Hm...
Woah...
Oh my god!
I never would've
guessed you'd have
a kitchen like this!
[FUMIO]
If there's one thing
I hate, it's cocky kids
with inflated egos.
I mean you have no idea
how many students' dishes
I've tasted in my life.
Do you really think you'll
impress me with some slop
you just throw together?
[SOMA]
There are some vegetables,
onions and whatnot.
Eggs...
Bread crumbs...
And lots of spices.
I got this...
Mm‐hmm. I think this
oughta be enough.
Hm?
What is he thinkin'?!
Ms. Fumio Daimido,
Kyokusei Dorm Mother...
give me a few minutes!
There should've only been
a scrap or two of ground pork
and beef lying around.
[FUMIO]
How could this be?
How did he make such
a thick Hamburg steak?
Hmph. I used the rest of your
canned mackerel to make...
a "Mackerel burger"!
Canned mackerel?!
[SOMA]
I added onions and breadcrumbs
to the egg,
then mixed it with
the mackerel,
added pepper, and lightly
salted it.
I fried that up, creating a
flaky mackerel‐burger steak.
Then, I added ponzu
to the leftover mackerel liquid
and thickened it up
with some potato starch
to make a simple,
refreshing sauce.
Given the timeframe;
I call it: Yukihira Brand
"Use What You've Got"...
Holy Mackerel Burger!
What's this?
Impossible.
A "Hamburg steak" made from
canned mackerel...
This should be horrendous
and inedible.
Haahmmm...
MM!
OH!
AH!
Mmmm...
It's so thick that if
he'd told me he used just
meat, I'd believe it.
And it's fried up so
flaky and soft!
Well, what's with
this egg soup?
Ah! Where is all this
flavor coming from?!
It's the quality of the
fish stock that makes
a soup's flavor.
This rich taste is
proof that he used a
high‐quality stock!
(Crash)
Hey boy, how on earth
did you make this?
We have no seaweed
or fish flakes
nothing that could have been
used to create a fish stock!
Well, about that...
I happened to have
something on hand.
(Flick)
[FUMIO]
Squid?!
You mean you used that
thing to make your stock?!
[SOMA]
Dried squid is pure umami.
Soak it for a while in
some boiling water,
add some salt,
and you'll get a richly
flavored soup stock.
The perfect start
for many dishes.
(Slurping)
This kid is something else.
For him to make food of
this caliber using only
those ingredients...
is remarkable.
Such a soothing taste...
Ahh! It warms both
the body and the soul.
Mackerel and squid...
These fruits of the
sea combine to create a
delicious, salty flavor.
It reminds me of my youth! Ooh!
(Waves crashing)
Uh, aren't you kinda
cold in that...
Fumio?
No, come on...
Kou, you know what I
really want to do right now...
Don't you, too?
Fumio! U‐um,
yeah, well uh...
Um...
(Sigh)
(Annoyed sigh)
Making a girl say it
is just... cruel.
Come here...
[FUMIO]
Come closer to me.
(Awkward gasps)
I just want you to...
I want you to warm me up.
[KOU]
(Heavy breathing)
Hm.
I beg you...
Ahh...
Aagghh...
(Frantic screams)
Gimme some‐a that sugar...
Whoa! Hey!
Get away from me!
(Sigh)
My reactions to the taste of
so many of his "new dishes"
have left me utterly exhausted.
(Cackle)
[MEGUMI]
Soma, that jerk‐wad!
He treats me like some kind
of experimental lab rat.
Ahh...
That right, Mr. Ducky?
Soma's a real pain
in the butt, huh?
[FUMIO]
Ahem! Very well!
Uuuh!
You may live in the dorm!
Huh?!
Hm!
You're welcome!
Your room is No. 303.
Here.
Oh, yes!
Doing so much with such
limited ingredients...
Looks like we have an
interesting new resident.
Soma Yukihira, hm?
[MEGUMI]
Ahh... Ever since I got here,
this is the only place where
I've been able to relax.
Ms. Fumio CAN be
a bit terrifying,
but at least there aren't
any strict teachers or Soma.
[SOMA]
Guess I'll start things
off with a hot bath!
Hm?
(Gasp)
Hm.
Uh!
(Fearful whimper)
(Terrified scream)
Oh. I see he's already
making some friends.
I'll have to tell him
the bath schedule.
[FUMIO]
Oh... What's
going on there?
(Owl hooting)
Man, that bath felt good.
(Exhale)
Heh. This is my first time
away from the only home
I've ever known for 15 years.
[SOMA]
'Kay! Here's your
liver and onions!
Can I get a meat‐and‐tofu
plate, please?
Say, uh... And I'd like
to have the daily special.
Right, you got it!
One meat‐and‐tofu! One daily!
It's so quiet...
Hello! Young transfer student!
Guh! Huh?!
Who are you and what are
you doing up there?!
Come on, there's
a welcome party.
[ZENJI]
I already told you...
I am extremely busy trying to
study for my written exam!
If you want to have a party,
do it in someone else's room!
Why do you guys always
insist on coming in here?
What choice do we have?
You have the only room
that can fit us all.
Hey, do not
sit on my bed!
And not to mention
how sparkly clean it is!
Because I just finished
straightening it up!
Oh yeah, there was crap
all over the place, huh?
[ZENJI]
Because you two
destroyed the place!
Dude, you need to get some
more chairs up in here.
No, I don't!
Hmph.
[AOKI]
Whoops!
[ZENJI]
Ah! My books again!
[AOKI]
Sorry bro.
(Shy whimpers)
Listen here, sweetheart.
A true lady never exposes her
goodies 'til she gets married.
I'm sorry, Mom.
But nobody is going to
make me his bride now!
It's pretty crazy, Megumi...
I can't believe we
ended up in the same dorm.
Isn't it though.
Hmm! You mean to tell me
that you actually passed
the entrance exam on
your very first try.
Sort of.
I'm just glad that
it worked out.
That's incredible...
Not very many people
have cleared the test
in just one shot.
[SOMA]
Huh? How'd it
go with you?
Um... So‐so,
I guess you might say.
Ah?
I‐I can't say it.
I can't say it took me
three months to get in!
Hey. You want
some of this?
Oh? Ah, thank you.
Sure.
(Sniff)
Huh?
[SOMA]
It's so cloudy...
And the bottle has
a handwritten label.
Yeah it's some "special"
juice I made from rice.
Drink up.
Uh‐huh...
(Festivities continue)
[SOMA]
So, it's okay to make all this
racket this late at night?
[RYOKO]
It's fine. The dorm is
in the middle of a forest.
[SOMA]
Yeah, but still...
I mean, won't the dorm
mother get mad and‐
Guh!
[FUMIO, LOUDSPEAKER]
Hey! You kids!
There's stewed amberjack
and daikon down here.
Come and get it!
Whoo! All
right, dude!
Love you, Gramma!
(Both laugh)
They're going
down?!
I'm sure they'll be back
before Ms. Fumio
starts yammering
on about The Ten.
"The Ten"?
Get away from her!
Do you know who
you just touched?
Not really.
This is none other than
the top student in the
Middle‐School Division
and the youngest member
in history ever seated at the
table for the Council of Ten...
this is Erina Nakiri!
[SOMA]
The Ten...
What is "The Council
of Ten" exactly?
Huh? Are you
asking for real?
What? You seriously came
here not knowing anything
about the Tohtsuki Academy?
Zenji, will you
please fill him in?
Why's it always
gotta be ME?
Oh stop your
complaining.
Can you just help
the new guy out?
All right, fine.
The Tohtsuki Council of Ten...
It's a committee made up
of the ten highest‐ranked
students on campus.
At Tohtsuki, students settle
most of their issues through
self‐governance,
and all items are decided by a
mutual consensus of the Ten.
It is the highest
decision‐making body on campus.
In terms of school
organization, they're
right below the director.
Which means, even the
teachers have to follow
the decisions made by The Ten.
It is said that decades ago
the rooms at Kyokusei
were always full,
and that most members of
The Ten often came from here.
There was even a time when
Kyokusei residents held every
single one of the council seats.
Hm?
And Ms. Fumio can
really get going
on and on about it, too.
Huh?
And I take it Erina Nakiri
is one of The Ten, huh?
(Door opens)
Uh!
[BOTH]
Back with
deliciousness, dudes!
[ISSHIKI]
Hello, Young
Soma Yukihira.
Welcome. It's nice to meet you.
We're glad you're with us.
I am Satoshi Isshiki,
a 2nd‐year.
Please call me
"Isshiki"
Will do.
Well. Isn't this just lovely.
I am simply delighted we
have acquired a new student.
We must share the
bloom of our youth!
Nothing on Earth could
make me happier!
Now listen to me:
We are adolescents
living under
the same roof,
sharing our joys
and sorrows!
This student life is
a blossoming spring!
I entered this dormitory
enamored with that concept.
Let us embrace one another
and rejoice in our resplendent
dorm‐life existence!
That's real nice and all,
but can you please stop
comin' to get us by creeping
around in the attic?
Doesn't sit right
with you?
Hmm... I suppose I could
use this contraption.
[ISSHIKI]
When I do, Megumi Tadokoro
is always quick to respond.
Uh, well, do I have to...?
[MEGUMI](Scared whimpers)
[ISSHIKI](Creepy whisper)
Megumi. Are you asleep?
I'm having a little
fun over here.
(Continued whimpering)
But I'm all alone...
And I have so much
WONDERFUL food to share.
Scamper on over if
you're still awake. M'kay?
I promise I'll... make
it worth your while.
If I don't, then
you'll just keep
calling me, won't you?
He'll eventually give up
if you just ignore him, okay?
You need to stand
your ground, girl.
But it does totally suck
whenever he does that.
It's probably
pretty nice up there.
What is going on?
My dorm‐mates are a bunch
of weirdos and freaks.
I'm pretty sure that you'll
have no problem blending in.
'Kay then, does everyone
have a drink in hand?
[ISSHIKI]
Then here is to
Soma's success...
and to the glory
of Kyokusei...
[ISSHIKI]
Cheers!
[ALL]
(Festivities continue)
What is this magical
"rice juice"?!
This is like the best
stuff in the universe!
I think I could drink
this all night long!
Yep he's fitting in,
no problem.
[ZENJI]
♪I will be reborn♪
♪I will live right
here and now♪
♪I'll transcend the sky♪
♪The sky up above
the clouds♪
Hungry! We need more food!
(Crazy laugh)
[SHUN]
So, I guess I should bring
out what I made today.
Huh?
[SHUN]
Smoked cheese and
three kinds of jerky.
Ah, I can't get enough
of that smoky flavor!
Shun, my man, you
can do no wrong!
Uuuh‐huh.
[AOKI]
Dig in, dudes!
It's an assortment of
fried vegetables, all taken
from the garden out back.
Oh man, this stuff
is delicious!
HAHAHAH!
I know, totally
awesome, right?!
The fried shrimp
I served last week
was way better
than this, bro.
Whatever!
You've got the
weakest taste buds of
anybody here, dude.
Bring it on, hoss!
Bro! Don't push me!
[SATO]
Get outta my face!
[ZENJI]
AAGH! What is with
you meatheads?!
If you're a chef, then prove
it with your cooking, bro!
No problem, dude! Just
gimme eight minutes, holmes.
Oh, come on!
This is how we end up always
making way too much food
and leaving the
kitchen a disaster!
[BOTH]
Shut up, you wild‐game
hose beast!
(Annoyed groan)
[AOKI]
You stink like animals!
[SATO]
The whole floor
around your room does!
It's like a petting zoo!
Anyone who says something
like that
obviously does not
appreciate the freshness
that my wildlife brings.
[YUKI]
Just give me about an hour...
[RYOKO]
You're going to go
strangle something
this late at night?!
[MEGUMI]
Come on, Yuki,
please calm down!
Oho, wait a second.
I've got a brand‐new
dish I was able
to make earlier today.
Way to go, Soma! That's
what I'm talking about.
Give it here!
Oh, my bad, it turned
out to be revolting.
BLEEEGH! THAT'S NASTY, BRO!
(CACKLE)
(Sato gagging)
[SOMA]
Sorry, sorry.
(Gagging continues)
(Group laughing)
[SATO]
I think I'm dying, bro!
[ISSHIKI]
Bing! Bang!
POW!
Aw yeah,
there it is!
Bang! Ping!
It was only a matter
of time before
"He's Naked and Wearing
his Apron of Illusion"!
(Raucous laughter)
[SOMA]
Nice!
(Echoing laughter)
Hehe. Times may continue
to change in this life,
but two things will
always stay the same:
One is the laughter
of students...
Hmm. And the other one...
(Ending song begins)
is how the stars will
always gather beneath
the brightly lit moon.
(Owl hooting)
(Light snoring)
(Snoring)
Uhaahhhhh...
(Light snoring)
[ISSHIKI]
Ah... Tonight sure
was dandy fun, yes?
I would like to
welcome you again, Soma.
I'm glad you're here.
Nah, the pleasure's all mine.
Are we already
out of food?
Ah, well we do have
some mackerel fillets.
I shall make
something TASTY!
You're going to the kitchen
like that, aren't you?
(Dramatic violin music)
[ISSHIKI]
Well, it's ready.
Enjoy...
Mackerel pan‐fried
in Chinese pepper.
Ehehe!
[SOMA]
Don't mind if I do!
This is TOO delicious!
It makes perfect use of
seasonal spring ingredients.
He made an extremely
delicate dish in a short
amount of time!
This is on a whole different
level than the other
people here.
Sure, he's a sophomore,
but is that all it
takes here for someone
to learn to make
something like THIS?
[ISSHIKI]
By the way, Young Soma...
Uh!
My attention is aroused.
You said something interesting
at the opening ceremony.
Aiming for the top spot
here at Tohtsuki
may not be as
easy as you think.
Allow me the indulgence
of re‐introducing myself:
[ISSHIKI]
From the Tohtsuki Council
of Ten...
Uhh.
[ISSHIKI]
I am Chair No. 7...
Satoshi Isshiki.
Now then...
I would like to try
YOUR food, next.
(Nervous inhale)
Come and show me...
how you express yourself...
through your cooking.
[FUMIO]
Next time on Food Wars,
it's the fifth course:
"The Ice Queen and
the Spring Storm"
Time to eat up!
[OLD FUMIO]
Give me some of
that sugar, baby!