[SEKIMORI]
Anyone who is unable to complete
their dishes in an hour
will be summarily expelled
from the academy.
(Frantic cooking)
(Hectic scarfing)
This is never
going to end!
This is insane...
Fifty servings!
[MEGUMI]
Sorry for the wait.
[ATHLETE]
That look a long time,
little girl!
Whoa! Delicious!
More! I want more!
I'm glad they seem
to like it so much.
This has just the
right amount of fat!
The rice is nice
and fluffy!
I'm gonna need more of this
yumminess!
Don't stop the food
from comin' out !
Yeah!
I've GOT to work harder!
(Opening Song)
(Humming)
AHH!
Gaah!
[SOMA]
Oh, sorry.
Ahh!
(Gasp)
Huh?
Watch where you're going!
Ah! Hmph!
Are you okay, Erina?
You didn't hurt anything,
did you?
Don't touch me!
I can stand up
on my own, okay!
I don't believe this.
I let my guard down,
thinking I was alone.
And it had to be HIM
of all people.
Please don't tell me
he heard me...
So how are you?
I heard you humming. You must
be in good spirits today.
What are you
talking about?!
I was doing no
such thing!
Dammit.
He DID hear me!
I understand why
you'd feel festive.
We're at a nice hotel
with a hot springs.
I brought some cards for playing
hanafuda and poker tonight
if you wanna join us.
I am not feeling festive!
And you and I
are not the same!
I know that everyone calls this
the "training camp from hell,"
but to me, it's just a
tedious empty ceremony.
But however... I do wonder how
long it'll take you to fail.
Being able to watch that would
be mildly entertaining for me.
(Sigh)
Well that's not nice...
for someone humming and singing.
Urrgh!
Miss Erina!
Hm?
I'm sorry I'm late!
It took a little time
trying to find my‐
S‐Soma Yukihira!
What in God's name do you
think you are doing in here?!
Oh, I... just laid Erina
on the floor...
Huh?!
(Evil snicker)
Wha...
HUH?!
I know what you're doing!
Don't say things like that!
Don't be like that.
You sounded like
you enjoyed it.
What?!
Omigod! Do not listen
to a word he says!
Get out of here.
Just go away and
take your stupid bath!
All right,
all right, fine.
♪I'm gonna get myself all
squeaky clean! Splish! splash!♪
Are you sure you're really
all right, Miss Erina?
I'm fine, Hisako.
You should probably take your
bath before the crowd comes.
Yes Ma'am...
Oh, and I was able to get these
from the front desk clerk.
Playing cards!
I don't ever play such
frivolous games!
Um...
Huh? Okay.
But, uh, what
about earlier?
[ERINA]
Say, Hisako... I wonder if they
have some playing cards here.
Huh?
You know, cards
to play games with.
Uh. You want to play
cards while we're here?
It only takes
two people, right?
Well... SOME games.
I'll go ask at the front desk.
So I got you
some cards.
I said no such thing.
Um... are you sure
nothing's the matter?
Nothing at all!
Uhh...
Good grief!
What'd I do to her anyway, huh?
She's needs to adjust
that attitude of hers.
Well, whatever.
At least I get to take a bath.
The first soak is all mine!
Ah‐wha...
Oh? I see the first
one's already here?
Doing a little stretching
in the bath is part of my daily
routine to quiet the mind.
[NARRATOR]
At that instant,
Soma had a thought:
I'm scared!
Which was quite unusual for him.
(Both laughing)
[NARRATOR]
But, it lasted only a moment.
Man! You know I was
kinda hoping I'd be
the first one in here,
but I guess I was
wrong, wasn't I?!
Hahaha! My apologies.
Well, you are the first
one of the students,
so can be satisfied with that.
Hm... It would seem that we
have discovered someone
with some talent...
That would make it
two years in a row now,
wouldn't it?
Last year, too?
That's right, and we always
hold the 50‐serving challenge
in different hotel
kitchens simultaneously.
That way it's
clear to see who's
the first to finish.
And each year, I'm usually out
of the bath before the students
ever show up.
But last year...
there was another
who came in here having
finished up this quickly.
[GIN]
He's the current No. 7 chair
on the Tohtsuki Council of Ten.
[SOMA]
You gotta be
kidding me.
He seemed like he was
an unusually strong
and unique character.
That's Isshiki all right...
Hm...
Hold on.
That means...
she made her fifty servings
faster than me?
Now that's a surprise!
Now clearing the challenge first
isn't all we are judging on.
but it definitely
shows us your skills.
(Annoyed grunt)
Thank you
very much.
[CLERK] Yes Ma'am.
Ah, Hisako!
Hang on a second.
I brought some cards for playing
hanafuda and poker tonight if
you wanna join us.
Nevermind,
I don't need those.
O‐okay...
[GIN]
Erina Nakiri...
Granddaughter of the director
of the Tohtsuki Academy.
Known as "The God Tongue."
She's driven the Academy's
top instructors since
she was just a baby.
It's okay.
(Cheers)
[GIN]
She would eat only the most
refined baby foods.
As a child, she tasted
multiple varieties of salt...
blindfolded.
From Kagawa Prefecture.
(Gasps)
From Ishikawa Prefecture.
(More gasps)
This one is from
Kochi Prefecture.
(Even more gasps)
[GIN]
She could determine where
they came from by taste.
There are endless stories
that prove her abilities.
She is the "God Tongue."
And the fact she became the
youngest member of The Ten
shows that her talents are
backed up by genuine skill.
If all goes as planned, she'll
become a culinary monster,
the greatest masterpiece in
Tohtsuki Academy's history.
[GIN]
But... for now she's
just raw material.
Tohtsuki is an inhuman,
demonic realm
where those of talent are
gathered only to eat one
another.
It's a long way down
at this academy.
Sharpen your fangs, kid,
'cause you're gonna need them!
Yes Sir!
Soma Yukihira!
You may have be able
to beat me this round,
but next time will be
a different story‐ AAGH!
[TAKUMI]
Ch‐Chef Dojima!
Well, I've been long enough.
See ya. Good luck.
[GIN]
For what it's worth, your
stay here has just begun.
Make sure to take good care
of your body while your here.
Try to do your
best tomorrow, okay?
Thank you. I plan on it.
(Takumi stammering)
Do you have any idea who
you were talking to?!
Well yeah. Chef Gin Dojima.
How can you possibly...
Wait you already
know that?!
What're you doing just
happily shaking his hand
like it's nothing?!
[SOMA]
Huh?
[GIN]
Yukihira?
I've heard that name
somewhere before...
(Chatter)
[YUKI]
Man, I'm freakin' exhausted
after that 50‐course challenge!
I can't believe we were all
able to make it through.
This is gonna go on
for another four whole days?
The name "training camp
from Hell" was no joke.
Still, now that we're getting to
relax,
it kinda makes you
want to get back out there
and do it again, right?
You brought
your little ducky?
Oh! Hehehe.
Well, I thought that I'd
let him go on a trip too.
Uhh...
Oh My...
So, uh...What's going on?
[YUKI]
Looks like the
dumplings are ready.
Aren't they,
Lady Ryoko. OW!
Perfectly plump and
tender and ready to eat!
Oh, not you too.
Don't stare
at me like that!
(Squeak)
Oh! He IS on a trip.
Huh?!
I swear. You guy are the worst.
Ahhhh...
Okay, girls...
What do you say
we get going?
Time to get back to
our 800‐a‐night suite
of pure opulence!
(Aahing)
Yahoo!
Ahah! Why don't you
try it too, Megumi?
I dunno...
This place is so upscale
I'm not sure if I can
handle a bed that soft!
(Intense giggling)
Yuki, that's not
very ladylike.
I know it's nice and all,
but still...
[ZENJI]
Hey, guys...
Oh, hey there,
Zenji.
You look like
you lost weight.
Have I really?
Then please listen to my
tired, withered body.
Let's just call it a night.
We need to rest for
tomorrow's challenge.
[AOKI and SATO]
Knock knock! Who's
ready to party?!
It's time to let loose!
Why do you knuckle‐draggers
always get together in MY room?!
All right!
What're we doing?
What're we doing?!
A 100‐round game of
Rich Man, Poor Man!
(Both laugh)
Alright, you asked for it!
It's go time!
(Snoring)
[SHUN]
They lasted 2 minutes,
51 seconds.
[RYOKO]
The day caught up
with them all at once.
[SHUN]
I guess we'll just leave 'em
till it's lights out.
You're not getting
tired yet, Megumi?
I guess you always go
to bed pretty early
so that you'll be ready
for the next day, huh?
Yeah well...
It's kinda weird, isn't it?
I'm exhausted, but I'm
not that sleepy, y'know.
Well, it was a
pretty stressful day,
that's for sure?
It certainly was,
too much so at times,
but I'm not sure that's it.
I mean, I'm always so nervous
during our class lessons...
And if I mess something up,
I get really flustered
about what I should do.
But today, you were
there to support me, Soma.
You're welcome, Ma'am!
I feel kinda like...
Like maybe with you I've been
getting just a little
bit more confident.
The whole thing is getting
my heart pounding.
[MEGUMI]
Ah!
But wait! It's only because
Soma told me everything
that I was supposed to do.
I'm not trying to say that
I'm great or anything!
You guys know I
wouldn't do that! Right?
No, you got
it all wrong.
If you hadn't gotten all
of those ingredients,
we couldn't have
made our perfect dish.
And you were able
to prepare 'em flawlessly.
When you put your mind to it,
just look at what you can do.
You should be more confident
in yourself, okay?
Mm‐hmm.
Sixteen whole cups!
Hm.
AHahaha!
[SOMA]
High‐speed revolution!
[RYOKO]
Ooh! I want to try that!
There is it!
There it is!
Let me try.
Let me try!
[MEGUMI]
I want to spend more
time with everyone.
I want to get better
at cooking.
I'll do my best.
[KOJIRO]
You are out.
(Extended muscly groan)
Good morning.
I'm Kojiro Shinomiya
from Tohtsuki's 79th.
Today's cooking challenge
will be to make
a dish of my choosing.
You should all have
your recettes.
This is bullcrap! We had
to get Chef Shinomiya?
I heard this guy sent more than
30 people home yesterday.
Plus, the theme he has us
making today is a recipe
he thought of himself.
[NARRATOR]
A terrine with nine
types of vegetables.
The multitude of vegetables
gives it a beautiful, vibrant
appearance.
Each of the nine varieties
requires different preparation
and heating techniques.
None of the vegetables' flavors
can be overpowering or
underwhelming.
And weaving those flavors
together is an extremely
difficult task.
To give you a chance,
I've chosen one of my
relatively easier recettes.
Unless you would prefer
a more difficult dish.
Man, I wanna punch this
guy's face in the face.
What's a "Recette"?
It means "recipe."
Ah!
[KOJIRO]
Also...
in this challenge, you will not
work in pairs.
(Gasp)
[KOJIRO]
You'll each make
your own dish.
Any exchange of tips
or information is
strictly forbidden.
Behind you, stacked in the
back of the kitchen, are all the
ingredients you may choose from.
Also, let me give you
a piece of advice:
It would be sensible of you...
to consider everyone
around you as an enemy.
(Shocked murmurs)
[KOJIRO]
You have three hours.
Now then...
Begin.
(Frantic screams)
Hey! Get off me!
Shut the hell up!
I'll kill you!
Get outta my way!
Ah!
(Whimpering)
[MEGUMI]
Everyone is out for blood.
The tension level in here is
even higher than yesterday.
But I can't get intimidated.
I can do this!
(Grunting)
Good.
Good!
Um, uh... This one!
[MEGUMI]
I'm getting started
pretty late, though.
Let see, if there's
any cauliflower...
Uh... no.... uh... ugh...
They're all in
pretty bad shape.
The only ones left have
started oxidizing and
their color is muddied!
If I try to cook
them like this,
they'll foam up and the color
will get even worse,
making the terrine lose
its visual appeal!
Wh‐what should I do?
I'll ask Soma!
Uh!
Any exchange of tips
or information is
strictly forbidden.
No, Megumi.
You cannot rely on
Soma for everything.
But what am I going to do?!
How am I going to fix this?
I have to do this on my own!
What can preserve the
cauliflower's color?
That's it!
[SCHOOLBOY]
Hey, um, isn't that a bit
different from the recette?
Oh, I guess it
is different.
Hey, you two.
Huh?
I told you not to exchange
any tips or information.
Did you not hear me?
No, no! That's not
what we were doing,
Chef, I promise!
That's right, Sir! He was
telling me I made a little
mistake, that's all.
Thank you for giving me an
example of what a tip is.
You two need to leave.
Get out of the kitchen.
Right now.
Hmm...
(Scared chatter)
Do it again!
(Groaning)
Ah.
Lousy... you're done.
C‐come on! I can do better.
Gimme another chance.
Chef, please let me
make it again!
Do you have
the ingredients?
Uh!
[KOJIRO]
You have neither the
ingredients nor the time.
If you're telling me you can
make it regardless,
well then, young man, you are
a better chef than I am.
(Disheartened sigh)
You are out.
Bye bye.
(Sobbing)
I'm Soma Yukihira.
Huh...
You pass.
Oh!
All done!
My nine‐vegetable terrine!
And just in time.
Just look at you.
You're the last one.
Um, I'm Megumi Tadokoro.
It's an honor.
[KOJIRO]
Megumi Tadokoro...
You're out.
(Gasp)
Everyone, that
concludes the challenge.
Those of you who did pass,
prepare for your afternoon
sessions.
U‐um!
Um, Sir.
Can you please tell me what
was wrong, um, with my dish?
Well. Your cauliflower
was a little off,
so you used wine vinegar
to boil it, is that correct?
Vinegar acts as a bleaching
agent, so it preserved
the color nicely.
The aftertaste of the vinegar
accentuated the sweetness
of the cauliflower.
The vegetables' sweetness
and the slight acidity
of the vinegar
created a perfect match,
flavor‐wise.
S‐so then, why, Sir?
Who said you were free to
stray from the recette?
Huh?!
This menu item is
intended to let one enjoy
the harmony of the
vegetables' sweetness.
Was there anything in
the recette that said to
accentuate the acidity? Hmm?
What you made was
a different dish altogether.
If you put out a dish not
to my standards, then of
course you're going to fail.
Are you satisfied?
Well I am not
very satisfied.
That was totally out
of her control.
Because you had produce
in there that had
already turned bad.
[SOMA]
Throughout these challenges,
we're being treated as
if we're your employees, right?
That being said, responsibility
for inventory control lies at
the top, with you.
Seriously... that fault
lies with the chef...
You little brat.
Do you understand who
you're talking to?
Well?!
It seems you do not,
so I'll tell you this:
I purposefully included some
substandard cauliflower...
to reduce the number
of those who pass!
(Gasps)
[KOJIRO]
Cauliflower is an ingredient
that has multiple pitfalls.
It's prone to oxidation,
bruises easily, and is
difficult to cook.
Those who lost their cool
and failed to be a decent
judge of quality
have all been
effectively purged...
As well as all the
dolts who hesitated and
didn't secure product.
Well yeah... that is
exactly why Megumi came
up with a great idea
to make up for lost
time and instead of‐
Be quiet! I am the
master chef here!
You do not have the authority to
try to question my decisions.
I cannot allow some peon
to butcher my dish.
(Grunt)
Listen here,
you little pissant.
If you're going to keep
fighting me on this,
I will use my rights
as head chef
to cut you loose
along with your girlfriend?
(gasp)
What'd you say?!
Soma, that's enough!
I'm going to be just fine...
He's just going to make it so
that you're expelled as well.
'Kay? I should just go...
What?! How can you
say that right now?
Soma, it's fine.
Please, I don't want
you to worry.
I'm good. I'll be okay.
Everything will be fine.
Um, excuse me, Chef.
There's just
one more thing.
What is it,
Monsieur Yukihira?
Do you have
another complaint?
[SOMA]
Well, not so much a
complaint as a question.
Does that rule at Tohtsuki
still apply after a student
has already graduated?
What are you talking about?
I'm challenging you.
(Gasp)
(Swish)
If I beat you in a
Food War challenge,
will you take back your
decision to expel Megumi?
(Ending Song)
[SHUN]
Next time on Food Wars,
the eleventh course...
"The Magician That
Came From the East"
You gonna be okay, Zenji?
[YUKI]
(Improvised theme)
Doo‐doodoo‐
doodoodoo‐doo‐DOO!