(Man whimpering)
[IKUMI]
So...
are you gonna do
it with me?
I know you want to.
Come on.
(Gulp)
Just do it with me...
[IKUMI]
A Food War.
Dah!
Mmm...
(Opening Song)
(Snoring)
[ISSHIKI]
Good morning, Young Soma.
I could use
a bit of help.
Could you get dressed
and come on over?
Dude.
I stayed up way
too late last night.
I'm super tired.
Ask someone else
to help out.
Oh come on, don't say that!
You have got to
stop doing that!
(Yuki laughs)
I see he woke you up, too.
[SOMA]
Yes, he did.
So, what are we supposed
to help him with?
We're collecting vegetables
from our field.
That's awesome.
We even grow our
own stuff here?
(Laughs)
Well, delicious food starts
with only the best ingredients.
That's our dorm's motto.
[SOMA]
Woah.
[YUKI]
That's how Shun gets wood for
making his smoked dishes.
[YUKI]
Ryoko's specialty is making
meals with malted rice,
so she has her own
workshop just for that.
(Caw)
As for me,
I want to breed a
"Kyokusei Chicken"
equal to the French
Poulet de Bresse.
And I let them run
free range of course.
That's cool.
[YUKI]
And then...
Isshiki's main area
of operation...
...is here!
This plot grows dozens of
different vegetables.
[SOMA]
Woahoho...
...oooooh...
Hm?!
Hup!
Good morning!
Hello Soma. Hello Yuki.
[BOTH] Guuh...
[ISSHIKI]
A bit of hard work
in the morning
helps soothe the spirits.
Let us all sweat together.
What'd he just say?!
Knowing different strains of
ingredients and how they grow
is part of learning
how to cook.
This is known as Kyokusei Field.
But truthfully, it might as
well be called "Isshiki Field".
So...
[MEGUMI]
Ah, Soma!
Huh?
[SOMA]
Oh! Megumi came out too.
Look! These are the vegetables
Isshiki grew in the garden.
Don't they look amazing?
You know what Megumi...
That outfit
oddly suits you.
Yep. Megumi is Kyokusei's
breath of fresh air.
Hm?
Here, take a bite of this.
[SOMA]
Oh, thanks.
WOW!
It's so plump and sweet!
I'd love to stock up on
these for our restaurant!
This is a quality
product here.
Yes, well I may have spent
too much time on them.
Because, unfortunately,
I haven't really been
going to class.
I think he's got his
priorities messed up...
Morning, everyone!
[YUKI] It's perfect!
[MEGUMI] (Laugh) Wow!
[RYOKO]
Isn't it though?
[SOMA]
Whoa! This is incredible!
[MEGUMI]
Soma, you haven't
stopped eating.
[SOMA]
Yeah, so what?
Hey, guys! It's time
for breakfast!
[YUKI] Work sure
gets you hungry.
[SOMA] My back hurts!
Oh. You made all this
for us, Megumi?
Yep. I'm sure
everybody's hungry.
Help yourselves.
[RYOKO] Wow!
[ISSHIKI]
Looks delectable.
I see it's your special
three‐variety onigiri.
This is FANTASTIC!
Onigiri after working
in the garden!
It's time to
stuff my face!
Wow! It's delicious!
You used a salt
and green onion sauce.
The sauce was added to the
flash‐boiled chicken tenders
and it coats the onigiri's
exterior, too!
The saltiness of it
really stirs the appetite!
Doing physical work always
makes me want something savory.
And this is seaweed, huh?
It is a staple of onigiri.
You boiled seaweed in sweet
soy sauce and added cheese!
That's right! A little cheese
actually goes very nicely
with the rich sweetness
of the seaweed.
Okay then, what is
this last one?!
[SOMA]
Oh man! This garlic flavor is
so great I can't even stand it!
As you can see, it's just
some garlic‐marinated pork.
Huh?!
[MEGUMI]
When I saw you use honey
in our class the other day...
It inspired me.
So I tried changing
it up in my own way.
I boiled some pork belly,
then steeped it in a
mixture of garlic, miso,
sake, and honey.
It goes great with rice,
so I chopped it finely
and put it in an onigiri.
Whoa...
Oh!
[MEGUMI]
There's barley
and green tea, too,
so don't be shy.
(Everyone gasps)
Now this is the true appeal
of Megumi's cooking.
It soothes the heart
of whoever eats it.
The chicken isn't dried out,
and the pork belly is
perfectly tender.
They're all made with such
thought and consideration.
Glad you like it...
Why can't you ever manage to
cook like this in our class?
AHH!
I freak out.
I, uh... I've always
had stage fright.
When I get really nervous,
my mind goes blank
and I just mess up
everything in the kitchen.
Yeah, well that's
too bad.
[ISSHIKI]
You need to relax more
in the kitchen, Megumi.
[YUKI]
Totally.
The more calm you are,
the better it turns out.
Just does.
[MEGUMI]
Hehe. I don't know...
[SOMA]
Huh? A "research society"?
[YUKI]
Yup! There are lots
of them at Tohtsuki,
researching every
theme related to cooking.
It's fun.
Each group gets
together after class
and works on
developing new menus.
Or participates in
cooking contests that
are outside of school.
They're a lot like
club activities,
much like a regular
school would have.
I'm a member of
the Regional Cuisine
Research Society.
Huh...?
[SOMA]
You weren't kidding.
Japanese, Western,
Russian, Chinese,
haute cuisine, vegetarian,
vegan, dairy free...
Huh! They even have fermented
and preserved foods.
Boxed lunches at
train stations?!
"Rice Bowl
Research Society"?
That could be good
for the restaurant...
Let's go check it out.
Huh?
[SOMA]
Come on, Megumi!
Oh, dear...
Huh...
Sorry, but you guys
should just beat it.
Bowl‐club's on
its last days.
We are doomed
to get shut down.
[BOTH]
Huh?!
[KANICHI]
Soma and Megumi, was it?
I am Kanichi.
I run things around here.
Um, are you
doing okay, buddy?
You seem like you're kinda
down in the dumps.
(Sobbing)
Feel free to laugh.
I couldn't even
protect Bowl‐club.
Look... a recipe book.
Hm?
Looks like menus that
Bowl‐Club members
have come up with.
Let's see...
They have high‐end items
and off‐the‐wall stuff.
With all their own unique spin.
These recipes look
pretty interesting!
Why the heck are you
guys being shut down?
Huh?!
You mean you actually get it?!
Ahh!
You really do,
don't you?!
He's crying!
[KANICHI]
The rice bowl's beauty
is they're FAST,
TASTY, and CHEAP!
They're pure manliness
encapsulated in a single bowl!
It's manly food for men
doing manly things!
And as a man with
manly cravings,
I will not die until
I've thoroughly mastered
every last one of them!
He's a little off,
isn't he?
Yeah, a bit too
intense for me.
My poor Bowl‐club...
If only it weren't
for Erina Nakiri!
Erina?
That's right.
This is how she does
things around here.
First off, she'll suggest that
the Council cut the budget
or take space away from
groups she doesn't like.
She'll force the
motion through.
She grinds people down
till they've just got
one option left...
You know what that is...
A Food War.
[KANICHI]
And in exchange for accepting a
Food War challenge,
she makes a bunch of
outrageous demands,
till in the end she gets
exactly what she wants.
It's how she keeps gaining
more and more power!
As soon as the other members of
Bowl‐club learned we were up
against Erina, they...
They all friggin' quit!
This guy must not
have many friends.
M'k... so you're going to
have to face off with Erina?
Well...
(Door slides open)
[ALL]
Hm?
Wha‐?! Hey!
You're absolutely right,
Miss Mito.
It's going to be faster to tear
everything down than remodel it.
Oh? Then go ahead.
What do you think you're
doing?! What is this?!
[IKUMI]
What else? I'm making a
preliminary inspection.
You already know how this is
going to play out, don't you?
Uh! Uhhh!
It's just like
Miss Erina said:
No matter how
you dress it up,
a rice bowl is a second‐rate
dish. Simple, lowbrow cooking.
[IKUMI]
You are not needed
here at Tohtsuki.
Got it?
(Chuckles)
But if you think that
you can actually beat me,
(Whimpering)
well that would be
whole different story.
You follow me,
Mr. Club Captain?
(Jiggle)
Your entire club
isn't needed here.
Dammit, Meat‐Meat.
[MEGUMI]
Ah!
What the‐?!
My name's not "Meat‐Meat".
Never call me that again.
Don't tell me...
that's who he'll
face in the food war!
Sounds like it. Who is she?
That's Ikumi Mito...
the butcher and chef
nicknamed "The Meat Master."
She's made top grades
since middle school,
and is so good, especially
with meat, that she's gotten
nothing but straight A's.
Her intimate knowledge
of meat is as good as it
gets here at the Academy!
When it comes to the power
of meat other ingredients
pale in comparison!
No matter what dish you think
you can prattle together...
it will never match the luster
of my top‐quality meat.
Bein' happy about how
much your ingredients cost...
is a disgrace
in my opinion.
Huh?
What's that?
[SOMA]
Kanichi...
About this Food War...
Would you please let
me battle it for you?
Why would you bother to
interfere if you're not
even a member‐ Uh?
[IKUMI]
It's you. The transfer idiot
from the opening ceremony.
I must say I've been wanting
to have words with you. Hmph.
You must be very confident
in your skills
if you're going to suddenly
take on someone else's
fight for them.
Or very stupid.
Lets go with your specialty.
We wouldn't want you
to be without your meat.
Either way, I'm gonna win.
I don't think so.
And whenever I do beat you...
you will have to
leave Tohtsuki Academy.
(Gasp)
Yeah.
Y'know, if you don't
have what it takes,
then maybe you shouldn't
be mouthing off.
I'm in.
What?
In exchange,
if I win...
Well, let's see here...
You'll have to
join Bowl‐club.
H‐Huh?!
[OTHERS]
HUH?!
Yeah, that's right...
You'll contribute to the growth
of rice bowl culture.
Sorry if it isn't
really your thing.
You honestly think
you can defeat me?
Hehehe.
(Clap clap)
Attention, everyone.
That'll be all for today.
Alright. I will allow your
request for the Food War theme.
The main ingredient will
be meat, and we'll be
making rice bowls!
The battle will take
place in three days.
Why'd you do that?
Are you crazy?!
Well, thinking expensive
meat is everything
is an insult to mom‐and‐pop
diners everywhere.
But more than anything,
it'd be a shame to
see this place go.
You're the coolest!
But, uh, Soma,
do you have some sorta
plan for winning?
Guess I better think of one.
Oh dear God!
[IKUMI]
I am grateful to Erina for
entrusting me with this.
I will teach that
uppity transfer punk the
pleasures of the flesh.
[KANICHI]
A bit to the right.
A little more.
Yeah, yeah, That's it.
[YUKI]
Soma's such a big doofus!
What was he thinking?!
The whole stinkin' school
is talking about this!
This could go bad! Hmph.
Yuki, settle down.
I'll try to help out
as much as I can.
But there's not a lot of time
until they have their battle.
So then...
How will you tackle this,
Young Soma?
[KANICHI]
Okay. Here goes...
I've been giving this
a lot of thought.
Meat‐Meat is a specialist
in meat, especially beef.
So, I think we should stay clear
of that particular protein.
For example, a
chicken‐and‐egg rice bowl.
That would be within
the battle theme,
but it will still make our
dish different from hers.
That makes sense.
Something outside the box, huh?
Megumi, is there a type
of rice bowl you like?
Uh yeah, I don't know if you
could call it a rice bowl,
it's not really
meat, but, uh...
I love scallops...
grilling them!
And as soon as
they open up...
I pour in a bit of melted
butter and soy sauce.
Then I'll put those on a bed
of fluffy hot rice and it's
absolutely scrumptious!
Well that's a pity.
You could've done
a seafood rice bowl.
But unfortunately
that doesn't count
as a challenge meat...
Okay, okay.
The rules are the rules.
Please don't
start crying again.
You have no idea how
formidable Meat‐Meat can be!
Listen, If she brings out
some of her A5 beef,
we're done for!
"A5"? Guess that's good?
It's from a ranking system.
And A5 is the highest
quality of beef.
Correctamundo!
When a cow is broken down,
the cuts are ranked
on fat‐to‐meat ratio...
[KANICHI]
There are three rankings,
A to C.
Marbling, firmness,
and texture...
The brilliance of the
meat's fattiness!
All these determine a cut of
beef's Marbling Standard!
These are ranked from 1 to 5.
(Bell ringing)
Meat that has been given
top ranking by these
two standards...
is classified as A5!
I once ate one of her steaks
at an Academy function.
Oh man... it was
a whole other level...
It was almost as
if you could...
drink it!
Drink it?!
Yes!
The moment I bit it...
the flavor took on
a life of its own.
It slid softly
down my throat!
If something like this
were offered in a restaurant,
the cash would be flying
out of your wallet!
Also... and this is very
important to remember:
Ingredients must be
prepared by the chef.
After all, chefs should be
skilled in food prep, too.
The Mito family turned their
wholesale meat business
into a massive company,
and have cornered the market
on beef production.
Their expertise is
undeniably the best the
industry has to offer.
They have money!
They have facilities!
They have distribution routes!
They have everything!
And that's why Meat‐Meat has
such badass meat dishes.
He just depressed himself
with his own story...
But can you really beat
such incredible meat?
I mean, what are you
going to do, Soma?
[SOMA]
You know...
Hm?
I think I got it...
we should do a rice
beef bowl too.
Huh?!
Are you nuts?
Did you not just
hear what I said?
When it comes
to meat, she is‐
You said it yourself,
Kanichi:
Rice bowls are fast,
tasty, and cheap.
Hm!
Her beef will make
a mockery of that.
We want bowls
to be respected,
we have to win with a menu
using affordable beef.
And we're not gonna use any
weird top‐quality ingredients.
That's not part of
a rice bowl's appeal.
Yeah. Sometimes, even when
a man's convictions are
tested, he must stand tall.
[SOMA] Yeah, well, I'm gonna go
pick up some things.
[KANICHI] Prove to the world
that he is not‐
Do you, like,
have a budget?
I'll take whatever
you have left over.
Uh, well...
not so much
(Coin drops)
[MEGUMI]
Huh?
[SOMA]
That's it?
(Frantic panting)
I'll just have to take it
out of my account!
That's all I have left?!
[ATM]
Your account is now empty.
[JOICHIRO]
I'll wire you some money for
expenses every now and then.
[SOMA]
"Every now and then"?
So I guess that means
never again.
(Sigh)
This whole thing
could be a bad idea.
[KANICHI]
Oof!
Huh?
These are our best
collected recipes.
There might be somethin'
in here you can use.
Here you go,
there's these, too.
[KANICHI]
Oh, thank you!
Set that pile over here.
Okay, guys!
Shall we get to it?
[SOMA]
Order up! Give it a try.
I used beef instead of pork to
make a "beef cutlet" rice bowl.
I tweaked Bowl‐club's recipe,
using a mixture of chicken
and quail eggs to give it
a richer taste.
Ahhh...!
That's not bad.
But, it's not enough.
When you put it in your
mouth, you want a reaction.
With Meat‐Meat's food...
it hits your tongue with a bang!
"With a bang," huh?
Then we need some fat!
(Sizzling)
[SOMA]
This is my
"sukiyaki rice bowl,"
cooked in sugar and beef fat
with a raw egg dropped in.
Om.
Haaahh...!
[KANICHI]
Nah, still not enough!
There's no
refinement to it!
[SOMA]
Then I'll reduce the
beef fat, and instead‐
[MEGUMI]
Um, how about this recipe?
[SOMA]
Okay!
[MEGUMI]
He's so sad, he's
turned white again!
Splash some water him
and snap him out of it!
Nyah!
[SOMA]
We've tried all of Bowl‐club's
best recipes.
I've even tweaked them
in every way I know how.
[MEGUMI]
Hey Soma.
Why don't you try
taking a little break?
Once you're all recharged,
you might get another
idea like you did in class.
I mean, I'd say it's
worth a shot, right?
Don'tcha think?
Ah.
Like using honey
to make the meat
more tender, huh?
Guh!
Megumi!
Uh!
Wh‐what'd I do?
You are a genius,
you know that?!
You've saved us!
It's been in front
of us the whole time!
It is ALL about
the cheap meat!
Kanichi! Do we have any more
steak cutlets lying around here?
I'll take Sirloin or rump.
I have an idea!
Uh!
You need steak cuts?
[SOMA]
Slice the steak into
a grid pattern...
then pound it
to spread it out!
Next, cover it with
minced onions on both
sides and let it sit.
Remove the onions,
and season the meat
with salt and pepper.
Cook the meat, melting a pat
of butter along with it.
Then caramelize some
onions by cooking them
in the leftover juices.
Why onions?
[SOMA]
Then, spread the cooked
onions on top of the meat,
and it's done.
That's...
it's Chaliapin Steak!
When opera singer Feodor
Chaliapin came to Japan,
he was suffering
from a toothache.
He told his hosts that he
needed very tender steak,
and this is what
the chef came up with.
You can't get this overseas!
It's a unique style of steak
found only in Japan!
Well, give it a taste, you two.
Hm.
Yeah...
(Echoing)
Ahhh...
So light and fluffy...
[KANICHI]
It's so tender!
I mean, it's just
falling apart.
And with every delicious
bite I take, it...
[BOTH]
...melts in my mouth!
(Cows mooing)
The onions contain
enzymes that help break down
the meat's protein.
The exact same as
pineapples and honey.
That's how the meat is able
to get this tender.
[MEGUMI]
Haahhh...
You'd never think this
was cheap cut.
The flavor is so full
and robust!
And it goes great paired
with rice.
But, will this really...
Can it do it?
Can we beat her meat?!
(Ending Song)
[IKUMI]
I will be using fillets
of Kuroge Wagyu.
The quality is, of course, A5.
And well...
I have aged it for over
a month at this point...
giving it the most intense
flavor possible in a steak.
[IKUMI]
It is an A5 beyond any other A5.
I will make sure
to draw out every
drop of flavor.
That pathetic
"Bowl‐club" will be
crushed in an instant.
Oh, I'm looking forward to it.
Well, if you'll
excuse me.
To think, an opportunity would
come up this quickly...
Soma Yukihira...
The time has come for you to
leave Tohtsuki Academy.
(Sinister laugh)
[IKUMI]
Next time on Food Wars,
it's the seventh course.
"The Silent Bowl,
the Eloquent Bowl"
Have a taste.
[KANICHI]
That's what I call
a skirt steak!