[SOMA]
All right!
Fluffy souffle omelets,
cooked up hot and fresh!
No one's touched the ones
I already put out!
Aw man! Now they've all fallen!
Crap! At a buffet, there's no
guarantee the food you put out
will get eaten right way.
That's way different from what
I'm used to at our shop.
The food gets to the
customers quickly and at just
the right temperature.
But here at the buffet...
it's up to the customers to
decide what to eat, and when.
The key to a souffle's texture
is eating it right after it's
made!
Otherwise, it deflates before
anyone has a chance to eat it!
I can keep putting them
out all I want,
but if they collapse before
the customers eat them,
it won't make any difference!
This is bad!
And what's worse...
I'm right next to the
"Queen of Eggs Benedict!"
I'm looking like an amateur!
[GIN]
Erina Nakiri!
You've served two hundred!
Soma Yukihira,
it seems you get it.
For a buffet, nothing's more
important than appearance
and flavor retention.
Put simply, you chose the
absolute worst dish to make
for this challenge.
I guess this is where
we must say goodbye.
Feel free to gaze at my
incredible creation until time
runs out. (Laugh)
(Opening Song)
[GIN]
The main ingredient is eggs.
Dishes must gain the approval
of both the producers and our
skilled staff.
Also, guests must eat at least
200 plates within two hours.
The standard for
passing isn't easy.
This, truly, is the
most crucial stage.
It is a genuine fight to
survive!
Dammit!
I haven't gotten a single
customer since the 150th plate!
We have more!
Over here, no pushing
to the front please.
[GUEST 1]
What is that?
[GUEST 2]
She said there's more!
Ever since her
first customer,
she's gotten
more and more busy.
She's even started poaching
people from other tables!
Those can't be normal eggs.
To think, her dish could hold
such a powerful a secret...
(Shiver)
This... This isn't a raw egg!
The "whites" are a gelée of
diluted seawater.
The "yolk" is salmon roe that's
been firmed up with gelatin!
Huh? At first glance,
this looks like
a hard‐boiled egg...
But the "whites" are a
mousse of white asparagus,
and the yolks were used as a
base for a hollandaise sauce.
Balancing the richness
of the eggs
with the slight bitterness
of the asparagus is exquisite!
[WAITRESS]
So then, what's this
egg gonna be?
I'm so glad you
asked that...
Watch!
She stabbed it!
It's a milkshake you
drink with a straw.
[ALICE]
I emptied the shells,
then mixed eggs, milk, and
caramel to create a drink that
is piped back into the shell.
I‐it's delicious!
It's so smooth, with a
lingering aftertaste.
It's like she's recreated
a brisk morning!
There you go! All together...
it's eggs prepared in three
of its most glorious forms.
This dish is astonishing!
Each egg opens the door to an
unexpected world!
On a single plate...
The ocean...
the forest...
the plains...
the deliciousness of all three
are condensed right here!
[GIRL 1]
I wanna try that!
[GUY 1] Me, too!
[GIRL 2]
And me! Me! Me!
[GIRL 3]
Me, too, please!
Is that girl for real?!
At this pace,
She'll end up clearing
more than 300 plates, easy!
[GIN]
Takumi Aldini! You've
served two hundred!
Yes! Hm?
Soma!
Man, what is he doing?!
[GIN]
Megumi Tadokoro!
You've served two hundred!
(Sigh)
What's with Soma?!
Guh... Lack of sleep has
caught up with me.
Miss Erina's over there taking
all the customers away from me.
I'm done for!
Calm down... Calm down...
[JOICHIRO]
We have two more guests!
Soma, get them some appetizers
and hot towels.
Table 3 needs to be bussed.
And get Table 4 their check.
Ugh! You can't just say
that all at once!
The appetizers, appetizers...
Uh, wait. Huh?
How do I prep those?
My mind's all over the place.
What do I do?
I don't remember
how to do anything!
Ow!
What was that for?!
Listen up, Soma.
If you're ever freaking
out in the kitchen,
you need to start over.
Just picture what you need to
do and attack it one thing at a
time until it's all done.
(Chuckle)
Aw, isn't this a shame...
Well that's just the
difference between your
skill level and mine.
Oh, I'm sure you've
figured that out.
Um. Huh?
No way. Is he asleep?
There's about 30 minutes left.
Just get the customers
attention.
Cooking an omelet on one side
takes less than a minute.
Then, cover and cook for
a minute and a half.
With this number of burners...
Ingredients and
preparation time...
What are you
babbling about?
It's gonna be tight!
Don't tell me...
He's going to try to
200 dishes in a half hour!
That is ridiculous!
'Kay!
[GIN]
There's not much time left.
Looks pretty hopeless
out there.
So, what're you gonna do,
Soma Yukihira?
First, just one.
Get just one customer.
And work from there...
Woah! These
look awesome!
I wanna eat 'em all!
I hear they're called
"Eggs Benedict."
Ah!
Huh?
C'mon over here!
Young lady, feast
your eyes on this!
I'm gonna cast a
magic spell on these eggs!
Mmmm...
Smells good!
Order up!
(Giggling)
It's like jello!
It's great!
It melted just like soft,
fluffy foam!
So are you some sort
of food wizard?
Just like magic, right?
Huh? What's this?
Looks like a
regular omelet.
Even if he can rope in a
customer or two,
at this point,
it won't be enough.
Order up!
Ohh!
(Fluffy moans)
Oh my God?!
It tastes like an omelet,
but the texture is like a softly
enchanted dessert souffle!
Yeah! I was
just gonna say
that the outside is cooked
while the inside is
still fluffy like foam!
so when you press it with
a spoon, it just bounces back!
It's so springy!
What's all this then?
Hey, let's take a
look over here.
Please, help yourselves!
Dig in!
All right, I've got customers.
I can't let this
chance slip by!
He still has over
100 plates to go.
[ERINA]
And there are only
30 minutes left.
It's impossible.
The real fight
begins NOW!
Eeek!
Yeah!
[GIN]
You've served two hundred!
You've served two‐hundred!
Oh, my, what a shame.
I've used up all my
ingredients that I
prepared for today.
I never thought so many people
would be brave enough to try
a dish so innovative.
M'kay. You can call
it quits then.
Thank you very much, Sir!
(Alice humming)
Toodle‐loo.
I don't believe it!
She's already finished?
That tramp cleared
380 friggin' plates!
Now I don't have anything to do.
Maybe I could peep in
on Her Majesty's table.
Come to think of it...
I wonder what happened to him.
Mister Soma Yukihira.
Cover up the pans,
and while they're cooking,
get the next round of
ingredients ready.
He's fast!
This kid's got
some skills!
All right...
Whip up the egg whites,
then add fresh cream, salt,
and pepper to the yolks.
Taste test... Good!
They should be about done.
(Beep)
Garnish...
Special tomato sauce
and parsley...
Order up!
Wooaahh!
Hey, the food at
the next table
looks pretty awesome.
Let's go
take a look!
My customers!
[SENA]
Even though he's taking
on that much work,
his cooking pace is
getting faster.
Each time he
finishes a round,
his technique
actually improves.
He's refining it on the fly.
This is so good!
It melts in your mouth!
I am loving this.
How can it
be so fluffy?
He's fast.
And attracting more
and more of a crowd.
Word is spreading
around the floor.
Great for this style
of contest. I love
"live cooking."
[GIN]
Raw ingredients are
brought to the table.
Chefs and cooks
prepare everything
in front of the customer.
This increases the anticipation,
creating excitement as
ingredients are transformed
into a completed dish.
Woah!
Awesome! He keeps
making more and more!
Look how fast he is!
He's cool...
[GIN]
Soma is capturing the
hearts of the audience...
by putting on an elaborate
demonstration of skills.
By using his talents and
highlighting the cooking
experience,
he's turning the
tables around...
Hmph!
[GIN]
Ryoko Sakaki!
You've served two hundred!
(Sigh)
[GIN]
Yuki Yoshino!
You've served two hundred!
I did it.
[AOKI and SATO]
Yeah!
RAAAAR!
We rocked it, bro!
I wonder how
Takumi is doing.
[GIN]
There are five minutes
remaining.
Soma...
Come on, Soma!
Impressive!
[GIN]
Soma Yukihira!
You've served two hundred!
(Buzzer)
[GIN]
That's it!
Utensils down!
(Sighs and moans)
Oh whatever.
Don't even give me that look.
Just barely making it
is nothing to brag about.
That was a shocker!
I didn't think you had
a chance to even
get past eight plates.
Although still, using showy
tactics did seem a bit cheap.
Huh?
That was some
surge of momentum,
wouldn't you say?
Yes. He understood the most
important aspect, which was to
quickly assess the situation.
Mm‐hmm. And most importantly...
it's key to have
a clear idea in mind.
One will need to have a
strong knowledge in service,
so as to anticipate the
needs of a hotel breakfast
presented buffet style.
There is one more thing:
An ability needed when faced
with the whims of a kitchen,
where the unexpected is
almost sure to happen...
The skill to adapt. When a major
blow has been dealt to your
menu, you must move forward.
And he did that perfectly.
He's a bit unrefined,
but he's an interesting
specimen.
On the other hand...
What about Nakiri's
four hundred and seven?
[SENA]
Erina Nakiri was the
only student to clear
the 400‐plate mark.
And then there was the girl who
used all her ingredients,
serving 380 plates.
But if you
rely on gimmicky
cooking like that,
you'll never make
it to the top.
What you need is an approach
that's built on the latest
advances in cooking theory.
For example, cooking
that's revolutionary.
Mine!
I should really
introduce myself...
My name is Alice Nakiri.
That's a name with far more
prestige than any of you.
Remember it well.
Alice... Nakiri?
Nakiri?!
Yes.
She is my
unfortunate cousin.
I lived in the same mansion as
her till I turned five.
Huh?
[ALICE]
Ah, perfect timing!
Hey... Why don't you
tell Soma here
about my privileged
culinary background?
Oh, well, uh...
Mistress Alice happens
to be Miss Erina's cousin.
I already unveiled
that revelation!
Oh...
Never mind!
I'll tell him myself!
My father is sentimental.
He chose my mother's
hometown in Denmark
as the prime location
for his innovative company,
Nakiri International.
You may've heard of it.
There they research cutting‐edge
cooking techniques based
on molecular gastronomy,
with the study of mechanisms
of taste and smell, and even
cerebral physiology.
It's a top‐notch research
center, unlike any culinary
facility on Earth.
I stayed there till
I was 14 years old.
And then, I came
to Tohtsuki Academy...
To face my dear sweet cousin,
and ultimately take her place
as the queen of the school!
Right... As if I could lose
to some silly novelty chef
with "cutting edge" methods.
But it's cute that you
allow yourself to have
such a big dream.
Gah! 'Course
you'd say that!
You've always
been that way!
When I was three, you'd steal
all my favorite toys.
When I was four, I spent
all day making a cake.
Remember what you said?!
It's stinks.
[ALICE]
I mean who does that?!
And I will never forget what
you did when I was five!
Oh shut up, none of that has
anything to do with anything!
And as for you,
Mister Big Deal,
Soma Yukihira.
You sure talked
a lot of talk at
opening ceremony...
But the days when people
can get by on nothing but
showmanship are at an end.
As proof of that, you were
down to the wire for a challenge
that only required 200 plates.
HAHAHAHA!
Right, I was totally
getting worried!
I almost didn't make
it outta there.
I really messed that
up, didn't I?
But hey...
I gained the kinda experience
that comes from messing up.
You're really annoying.
Whatever, I'm not going
to lose to any of you!
I'm looking forward to
beating you all and taking
the top spot at the Academy.
Yeah, you don't say. I feel like
I've heard that one before.
I'm sure you have.
Well, till next time!
[TAKUMI and MEGUMI]
Soma!
Ohmigosh! I was so
worried about you!
You had no game plan
whatsoever, did you?!
Oh, uh, sorry?
[GIN]
Attention, everyone
who cleared 200 plates:
Get some rest because,
your next challenge will
take place in four hours.
He's kidding,
right?!
No... No, no, no, no!
That gives us just
over three hours to sleep!
I like training camp.
This is fun.
[SCHOOLGIRL]
It isn't over yet!
Uh! I can't take
it anymore!
My legs won't
even move!
I just wanna
lie down...
I'm so exhausted.
What is this? I don't
know what we're doing here,
but I don't like it.
Well there's nothing
written in the
camp itinerary.
Huh? Wait just a minute!
This pattern is
looking familiar...
Don't tell me we have to
stay up all night again!
[GIN]
Very well...
It seems you're all here.
Please! Not this again!
Just a few words
before we get started.
So far, 352 students
have failed,
leaving 628 remaining.
Though it may seem cruel,
this is a taste of what
it's really like to be
a working chef.
You must keep your cool in
unfamiliar situations,
always retaining a "dialogue"
with your ingredients.
If you become a chef in the
real world, you'll face far
greater pressures than this.
There will be nights where
you will have to endure
anxiety and indecision,
while dealing with
various situations.
Being a chef is like
living in a wasteland,
and having to brave the storms
and trials all by yourself.
The longer you endure it, the
more difficult it becomes...
and you can lose sight
of your goal.
Even when you've reached
the summit, you may very
well forget the way back.
However!
I want you to remember this:
Know that there were
comrades here at Tohtsuki,
who left tracks in that
wasteland with you.
You traversed it together.
And that fact should comfort
you when you one day
set foot on your own.
From the bottom of my
heart, I wish you the
best as you fight on.
Now then, let's begin the
final segment of this training
camp's program.
Dude!
Why do they hate
us so much?!
Welcome!
The final act is to congratulate
you on completing your training,
and offer you this humble meal.
(Ending Song Begins)
Please enjoy
a full‐course dinner
served up by our highly
esteemed graduates.
To all of the 628 who
remain standing with us,
You've cleared the challenges
of this camp! Congrats!
Enjoy your dinner everyone!
(Cheers)
For real?! No friggin way, bro!
[SATO] There's nothin'
"humble" about this!
No way. This is
something no one else
in the world but us
will get to eat!
What a day to
be aliv‐
He's kicked
the bucket!
Please, have a
seat, My Ladies.
Thank you very much.
(Squeals)
Fantastic!
So... good... yum!
There's no need
to cry, Yuki.
Cooking school?
Why would I need to go
to someplace like that?
This is dumb.
Payin' some yahoo to teach
me to cook is just stupid.
Are you doin' okay
over there?
Yeah... I'm good.
I was just thinking,
this school is more interesting
than I thought it would be.
Huh? What d'ya mean?
Oh uh... don't
worry about it.
C'mon, let's eat.
Sure!
[SENA] This is a
very exciting year.
So the matter we
discussed...
Yes. I am looking
forward to it.
The grand stage
where a select few
will battle with
everything they have....
The coming Fall Selection.
[AOKI and SATO]
Next time on Food Wars,
back with deliciousness, dudes!
[AOKI]
Got a problem with that, bro?!
[SATO]
Whatever, dude!
[AOKI and Sato]
"The Man Called 'Carnage'"
It's friggin' delicious, holmes!
[SOMA]
I'm gonna go see a chef
that's better than I am!
[ERINA]
BAAAAAA!