Megumi Tadokoro...
you will be the lead chef.
[GIN]
Soma, you'll act as
sous‐chef and support her.
Gah!
[GIN]
This Food War...
(Screaming)
will now begin!
[GOTODA]
A chou farci!
[GIN]
The Legume Magician!
Megumi. Soma. Your turn.
Yes, Sir!
Um, thank you.
Ooh...
Look at this...
[HINAKO]
A terrine!
I have made you all
a "rainbow terrine,"
using seven vegetables.
How nice. You made seven
differently colored pate...
arranging them in stripes
like a beautiful rainbow.
Now come to think of it,
The challenge in Kojiro's
class was a terrine.
How very interesting.
Well, looky here.
You copied my recette...
A nine‐vegetable terrine...
Why've you done
this to yourself?
Ah! Uh! No, I certainly
didn't want to copy it.
I wanted everyone to
experience my own personal
approach to the recette.
That's it, I promise!
[GOTODA]
Well now.
Let's see what this little
flower has made for us.
[SEKIMORI]
Hmm...
Megumi Tadokoro...
You have failed.
Why is she
still here?
She'll bring down
Tohtsuki's status.
I mean she's always
at the very bottom.
Go home,
country bumpkin.
You ain't got no talent.
[KOJIRO]
Megumi Tadokoro...
You're out.
Monsieur Yukihira...
if you lose, you and Megumi
will both be sent home.
(Whimper)
(Opening Song)
It's delish!
Yes it is!
Wonderful!
Mmmmm...
Huh?
[SEKIMORI]
Potatoes, carrots, zucchini,
and other vegetables were worked
into pate
to create the layers,
treated to bring out each
vegetable's individual profile.
You did well, accomplishing
so much in the limited
time allotted.
[GOTODA]
There are two different sauces.
One is a sweet‐and‐sour,
citrus‐based gelee.
The other is a cool,
refreshing green sauce
made of a shiso‐based paste
infused with various herbs.
Delightful!
Having us eat the terrine
with citrus and shiso
is a most enticing impression.
MMM! The combination
of the sauteed zucchini
mingled with the herb sauce...
It's so refreshing.
Mph! The citrus also pairs
nicely with the sweetness
of the tomato.
This seven‐layered pate
combined with the two sauces
lets us enjoy 14 different
exquisite flavors each
expertly showcased!
Quite provocative,
isn't it?
Mm‐hmm, these vibrant colorful
stripes are pleasing to the eye
as well as the palate.
A very well made dish,
I must say.
Okay, Megumi,
you used sundried
tomatoes, didn't you?
Um, yes, I did!
Y'see back in my
hometown, we take all
the summer vegetables
we've gathered and
dry them in the sun,
preserving them so we can eat
them during the winter.
[MEGUMI]
I used to help my Mom
in the kitchen every day.
And she showed me how
to do it in the oven.
I loved cooking with her.
You cut cherry
tomatoes in half,
sprinkle them
with rock salt,
then slow roast them in the
oven at 120 degrees.
That brings out their
sweetness and gives them
a different texture!
I thought it would be
a fun change to enhance
the terrine nicely.
Mm. Tomatoes are known to
contain the compound glutamine,
which is an umami component.
It is concentrated when
the tomato is dried,
and the sweetness on the tongue
is intensified greatly.
[GIN]
Kojiro's nine‐vegetable terrine
lets one taste the lively
flavors of fresh vegetables...
But this recette has a special,
splendid flavor that comes from
using a preserved ingredient.
[GIN]
While both are basically
the same menu item,
a vegetable terrine,
we have a fine, fresh flavor
vs. a full‐bodied umami.
Two completely
different approaches.
A taste that truly
warms the heart...
It's like it's brimming with
Megumi's sweet tenderness.
Yes. If Kojiro is
the Legume Magician,
then young Megumi is...
someone that presents the
bounty of nature in her own
modest way:
a Legume Gnome!
(Squeaky voice)
Hi there!
No, that's not it at all!
Sweet Megumi is a
conjurer of happiness!
She is the Legume Spirit
of Fortune!
Hellooo...
No. I disagree...
It's more like she's come
from a land of snow,
blessing us with a
bounty of vegetables...
A Legume Snow Queen!
Haha!
It's not winter, so I'd
say that doesn't really
make any sense!
Then she should be known
as a Legume Gnome!
She MUST be a
spirit of fortune!
I think she's
a snow queen.
Why does she have to be
some sort of weird creature?
[GOTODA] A gnome!
[HINAKO] A spirit of fortune!
[SEKIMORI]
A snow queen!
[MEGUMI]
It's like a dream.
I've failed over
and over again,
lost all confidence,
and have been
hopeless at school...
but these graduates who I've
looked up to for so long...
they actually...
They like my food!
(Chuckle)
(Laugh)
[GIN]
Very well, let's proceed
to the judgment.
Each judge will receive
one of these coins.
With it, you will
cast your vote.
For Kojiro...
or Megumi.
Cast your vote for whoever's
dish was more successful.
Alright, I'll go first.
Up until now,
I've been so afraid
of being expelled
that I've been
running in circles.
But now, finally,
I feel like I really want to
stay in school and succeed.
For the first time, I've
truly embraced my own cooking.
Please, please...
I don't want this
to be over yet!
Nice to meet ya!
Can't believe we ended
up in the same dorm...
[SOMA]
All right! Let's go, Megumi!
I want to... I want to
stay at the academy!
Hey, Soma, why don't you
try taking a little break?
(Sobbing)
You're incredible, Soma!
Thank the
friggin' cosmos!
I'm so glad to be
paired with you again!
You're welcome, Ma'am!
There's so much more cooking
I want to do with everyone,
with Soma!
So please, God!
Please let me stay!
(Gasp)
Heh! All that hard
work for nothing.
The difference in
skills is clear.
Kojiro was able to score a
rather substantial victory.
I‐I... couldn't do it.
Um, Megumi.
I'm sorry...
I didn't really
help much.
But don't give up! You're
a really great chef.
Trust me, that was a
fantastic dish you made.
No...
No, Soma, you didn't
do anything wrong.
Nah, nah, it's fine.
We should work
together again, Megumi.
Great! I'm countin' on you!
Here we go, Megumi!
Hey hey! Who do you think I am?
I am the number‐two guy at the
"Japanese Eatery Yukihira"!
Now, because of me,
Soma is expelled, too.
I'm sorry!
There's no need. I did
this because I wanted to.
You don't owe me anything.
(Gasp)
The only drawback is you
can't do it by yourself.
I'm gonna support you with
everything I know! Okay!
I'm sorry!
(Sobbing)
[KOJIRO]
Well, there's no
reason to feel down.
After all this obviously
was bound to happen to you.
Alright, I have an
early day tomorrow,
so if you'll excuse me,
I'm going to turn in.
Been a real treat.
(Clank)
Huh?
What do you think
you're doing, Chef Dojima?
[KOJIRO]
Um, the challenge
is already over.
Well, not quite yet.
I believe that I would
like to weigh in on this
contest as well.
So I am going to cast a vote.
Huh?
Seriously? After all that,
NOW you're going to get
involved with this?
Come on. What is
there to weigh in on?
You're not a judge
in this contest.
The votes were cast.
It's over.
Do you really not get it?
[GIN]
The answer to
your questions...
is right there in the
food Megumi has made.
Hmm...
Kojiro...
You've hit a plateau,
haven't you?
(Gasp)
[HINAKO] (Cackle)
You think you're
so cool, Kojiro!
(Thud)
Ow...
(Sobbing)
[GOTODA]
Hinako,
I know you're sad, but there's
reason for you to cry, my dear.
We have to see him off
with a smile.
But, I...
I didn't know he was
leaving us straight away,
and to France at that!
Yeah, you know...
I'm surprised too.
But you're serious, aren't you?
I am. And if I don't
learn in France,
my cooking will never
be complete.
I will train there,
open my own restaurant,
and win the Brousse‐Poiret.
[GOTODA]
The Brousse‐Poiret?
If you do, you'll be the first
Japanese to achieve that feat.
Still, I'm sure you can‐
But Kojiro, you're
so anti‐social,
there's no way you'll
make any friends!
You know you're going to just
fight with the staff‐
Whatever!
(Grunting)
[MIZUHARA]
For sure.
You are all
worthless!
[OLDER KOJIRO]
A Japanese person opening
a restaurant in France...
That was an unbelievably
difficult task.
While still in school, I saved
up by earning prize money
from winning various
cooking contests.
Then, I was eventually
able to make it to France.
I studied there for six years,
finally opening my own
restaurant, "SHINO'S,"
in the mecca of fine dining.
[CUSTOMER]
I'm quite shocked.
For you to be a chef owner
at such a young age...
The food was impeccable.
Thank you very much, Sir.
I loved it.
I was on cloud 9,
having opened my
own restaurant.
What is he doing here?
[KOJIRO]
But I overlooked one small
point of contention...
Hey! Who was it?!
Who changed the
sauce's recette?!
This is the preferred
method here in Paris.
I'd say your flavors are a bit
too oriental for our clients'
tastes, Monsieur Shinomiya.
Grr...
A Japanese
wouldn't
understand.
You're a long way
from home, garcon.
Backlash for being an
outsider...
Other chefs being
jealous of my youth...
Wanna eat at Shino's?
Oh, I dunno.
I haven't heard very
good things about it.
Let's try somewhere else.
Oh, o‐okay.
There was one problem
after another,
and the clientele
slowly began to dwindle.
If you keep coming in
late on your payments,
I won't be able to deal
with you anymore, alright?
All of my ambitions...
were falling away!
There's no place for slackers
in my kitchen. Get out!
The one person I could
trust was myself.
The staff became my enemy.
[KOJIRO]
Atrocious!
Finish this miroir off
per my instructions.
Do not stray from my recette.
Um, if I may, Chef,
I find it quiet appetizing
when done this way.
And in terms of efficiency
and cost percentage‐
I told you what I want.
If you don't like it, get out.
Ah! Yes of course, Chef!
[KOJIRO]
I pushed myself...
MM!
Oh wow!
Delicious!
And I pushed myself...
The treatment of
the vegetables
has an essence of
Japanese cuisine.
And yet, it doesn't stray from
the methods of French cooking.
Dear Lord, this is the
work of a magician!
A magician indeed!
He's the Legume Magician!
And having pushed
myself to my limits...
I made it to the top.
[GIN]
I have a feeling...
you're already aware
of it, aren't you?
Now that you've finally
won that award,
you're clueless as to
which direction to take.
[GIN]
Having reached that apex,
you've become unable to take
even a single step forward.
For a chef, a plateau is
the same as going backwards.
The reason you didn't make
one of your specialties
for this challenge
is that you didn't
want us to know
your cooking has stagnated!
Shut up!
What the hell do
you think you know?!
You're nothing but
a glorified resort chef
employed by your old school!
How dare you question me?!
Then try a bite.
Huh!
[GIN]
Try Megumi's cooking.
Mm... Why should I bother?
Do it.
Ha! It isn't cooked right.
The plating is off, and the
pate hasn't set properly.
Christ, are you getting senile?
Mph...
Hm!
And yet...
Why?! Why is it tugging
at my heart like this?
There's something else to it.
[KOJIRO]
The dish is crude,
But the way each
ingredient was treated
shows careful consideration
for the diner.
It's enough to relax
a soul that has been
strained and troubled.
This flavor...
it... reminds me...
[MOTHER]
Kojiro!
Boy, you were fightin'
again, weren't ya?
You went sayin' some
bullheaded nonsense to
your friends again, I bet!
Hm?!
Well, yeah!
I can't stand 'em.
I'm fine being on my own.
I don't care if nobody
gets me here!
Uh!
Oh sweetheart...
You're always flyin' off
the handle like this.
Makes it hard to
keep friends.
The truth is,
you're a kind boy.
Your momma knows that.
Uh... Um, Mom!
Now let's hurry
back and eat.
I'm makin' your favorite
for dinner tonight.
That okay with you?
Yeah...
[MOTHER](Laugh)
Look over there,
there's a rainbow!
It's pretty,
huh, Kojiro?
Yeah.
Hehehe! Thank goodness!
Right?
[KOJIRO]
This...
This tastes like...
like a mother's love.
(Clank)
(Sniff)
Uh!
Okay, dimwit.
Ah! Yes?!
That spice you added
to the pate...
It was allspice,
wasn't it?
Ah! Um, it was!
Well I would say it was
used to offset the smell
of the chicken liver.
It's a blend of cinnamon,
and cloves, and nutmeg,
and it's used throughout
the world in a wide
variety of cuisines.
Maybe... But that's not
the only reason, is it?
Uh, um! No, uh, right.
Huh?
Well I know you've
all been judging
since yesterday, right?
And I know you've
had to eat a lot
of different foods.
So, I thought that
you might be...
Well allspice aids in digestion
and might do you some good.
Oh!
I‐I wanted to give you something
that would be gentle
on your stomachs
and might help
settle your tummies.
You really are so
thoughtful and sweet!
You sure are...
I'm overcome knowing your
beauty extends to the kitchen.
Meaning that she's just
your type, right?
Do not say things
like that, Chef Mizuhara!
Though clumsy,
it resonates.
That's the kind
of food she's made.
[GIN]
Even while taking on
this challenge,
Megumi kept the interests
of the diner close to heart.
I would say that
that's an important
aspect to consider...
if you want to move
beyond the summit.
Uh!
Chef Dojima had me
from the start, didn't he?
I get it. For a long time now,
I haven't considered
the faces of my customers,
nor the voices of my staff...
I've cooked all alone.
Hyaa!
There! Now the
votes are even.
In other words,
the battle is a draw.
Allow me to settle
this Food War challenge
once and for all.
Alright, if you do
really think it's a draw,
Then I believe Megumi
should return to her same
status as before this Food War.
(Sigh)
This whole fiasco
has been preposterous.
It's just ridiculous.
Ahh!
Fine, I'll cooperate
with your wishes.
She survives
for one more day,
in her own
unfortunate way.
Ugh...
[KOJIRO]
Soma Yukihira, huh?
Hm.
Someone isn't being a very
nice person, now is he?
AH! You see! This is
what I'm talking about!
Um, uh...
Oh, no... But I...
[GIN]
Megumi...
Huh?
Your food is like a warm
embrace for those honored
enough to try it.
It's hospitality...
And it is the essence
of your cooking.
That is a
powerful weapon.
Hone it well while
you're at Tohtsuki Academy!
Consider these three coins as an
investment in both your futures.
Looks like we were able
to make it through, huh?
(Gasp)
Not too bad! We did it!
(Whimper)
(Sobbing)
So Kojiro's plateau
was the result of his
own resourcefulness?
That what
you're saying?
Yes...
Kojiro has always been
able to move forward
by removing everything he
has considered unnecessary.
Then, he reached the summit,
before he'd fully matured
as an chef owner.
For a chef to continue
to reach new heights,
it takes an insatiable desire
to absorb knowledge from all
sources.
[GIN]
Perhaps he will get
that back tonight.
So this Food War saved two of
our promising chefs at once.
You are quite the
educator, my friend.
Ha! You flatter me.
Man, it sure has gotten
pretty late, hasn't it?
(Phone vibrates)
Ah! I have, like, a
million missed calls
from Yuki and everybody!
Well there wasn't any
reception underground.
You should probably go
and talk to them.
I'll be right behind you.
Okay!
Uh, hey, Soma...
Thank you so much
back there!
I mean it. I'll never forget
what you've sacrificed for me!
Everyone's worried about you.
Get going.
Mm‐hmm!
He beat me...
And I...
I lost...
Dammit.
Soma Yukihira
truly intended to win,
all by himself.
That's another trait
a chef needs.
Much like Kojiro
when he was younger,
pledging to win that award and
setting out on his journey.
(Ending Song)
I'm ba‐
WAAGH!
Jerk face!
[YUKI]
Just how reckless
can you be, you idiot?!
I was so worried
about you two!
When I'd heard you'd challenged
an alum to a battle, I thought
you'd both be expelled!
Yuki, you need
to calm down!
If it wasn't for Soma, I
would've been expelled for sure!
Oh, that right?
So I guess that means...
AHHH! Ryoko!
Um, could you please
not cry all over me?
But I am really glad
you both made it.
I really am, you guys.
How are you even
standing up, Soma?
I feel like I got
run over by a truck.
Hey Soma, what happened
to your right hand?
You all right?
AGGHH!
(Laughing)
Don't worry about it.
Yo, Soma!
You made it, bro!
Sweet, dude!
All right!
Tonight, we're gonna have the
hanafuda cards championship!
Huh? Right now?
Why do you have to use
my room?! I hate you guys!
Because it's so clean!
Hm!
(Sobbing)
[GIN]
Next time on Food Wars...
Aahhhh...
the thirteenth course:
Uuhhh...
"Eggs Before the Dawn"
Go ahead and try some.
[MIZUHARA]
Aim for completion.