[ALICE]
In other words, I'm sure you
figured out...
one of us is gonna
go on to become the
next member of The Ten.
[URARA]
The top contestants from
each block will earn
the right to move on
and compete in the
actual tournament event!
That means just eight finalists!
28 points!
31 points!
6 points!
[MEGUMI]
No way...
All those dishes
were really well done!
[URARA]
Nao Sadatsuka has 84 points!
So, Hisako Arato's score is...
92 points!
(Cheering)
This is so insane!
That's why Miss Erina has
chosen her to be her aide!
[URARA]
And now, Miyoko Hojo
takes the stage!
What will her score be?
There we have it!
87 points!
She overtakes Nao Sadatsuka
to grab the second spot!
A boluo‐curry fried rice
rich with the aroma of spices
and pineapple
that linger in my mouth.
Oh god! I love just
thinking about it...
I can still taste the sweetness
of the fruit mixed with the
saltiness of the fried rice!
It's reminiscent of sweet
and sour pork, which also
uses pineapple.
To finish it off,
she hollowed‐out a pineapple and
then placed the rice inside.
Then, she re‐covered it
and baked it in the oven.
She was even careful to salt
the areas the rice would come
in contact with
so as to not become
overly sweet.
By doing that, she was allowing
the fragrance to come out
and not diminish the rice's
moisture in any way.
[ORIE]
This was another step
forward in the history
of Chinese cooking.
[ANDO]
She demonstrated
unparalleled talent.
And it manifested in the form of
someone with the skill to have
tamed the dragon's heat...
The Iron Dragon Girl!
True to form for the daughter
and heir to Chinatown's
leading restaurant!
It was a striking blow
to everyone, enough to
feel great shame!
Incredible! I never thought
curry could be made to
make you feel that way!
[AOKI]
OH! Hurry up!
Judging's about to start!
[SATO]
Oh man! Looks like things are
in high gear over here too!
Yeah!
You can cut the tension
with a knife.
Sure is quiet
in here.
[SATO] HUH?!
[AOKI] Zero points?!
What the heck?!
How can you get
zero points?!
Hmph.
(Cheering)
[URARA]
86 points!
Oh wow! Talk about an
attack from behind!
Yuki Yoshino was able to
capture the third spot!
Right now, Hisako Arato
dominates the top spot
with 92 points.
Coming up in second place
is contestant Miyoko Hojo,
with Yuki Yoshino in third
and Nao Sadatsuka in fourth.
[KITA]
I tell ya what, girl!
Your wild game curry was
a masterpiece, far exceeding
my expectations today.
I'm glad. Thank you for
the compliment, sir!
[KITA]
You made that stock with
fried duck fat and spices.
The fat imparted a duck flavor
to all the ingredients.
Normally, that would give it a
gamey smell, but...
this scent is so inviting!
It's brimming with the aroma
of the wild!
And the finishing touch is
unreal!
You topped it with
a duck cutlet!
You've used turmeric
and other spices to
perfectly mask the smell
and give it an
orange‐like scent.
Oh and speaking of that,
duck a l'orange is a classic
French dish, is it not?
Yes! I mixed in the fruit
and it's rind to the sauce.
It really matches that special
garam masala, doesn't it?
Ah, yes.
Fall is indeed the season
for wild game hunting...
Still, acquiring meat
of this quality for use
in the Selection
would require a direct line
to a wild game hunter.
Young lady, I invite you
to the next meeting of
my culinary club!
Huh, really?!
That's so kind of you!
[KITA] (Laughs)
Think nothin' of it!
Even her adorableness is
whetting the appetite.
[FUMIO]
Yuki, the innocence of
your smile draws everyone
into your orbit.
And your food is a straight
and honest shot to the heart.
You're just like...
the Little Red Riding Hood of
the Wild Forest!
The wait is over!
Next up is the must‐see
competition of...
The Aldini brothers!
First is the youngest
Aldini‐ Isami!
Looks like it's my turn.
Good luck...
[ISAMI]
Please, judges, eat
while it's still hot.
Oh, what is this?
Did he make us a curry calzone?
The Italian Calzone.
Pizza dough that
has been folded
and stuffed with a
variety of ingredients.
In Italy it can be
either baked or fried,
depending upon the region.
Usually you find this
sort of pizza dish
filled with
mozzarella cheese and
other ingredients.
But that's just the... OHH!
It's filled with curry!
Making this indeed an
Italian‐style curry bread!
Well look at this!
This is by far a
different approach
from what we've
seen thus far.
Interesting!
Well, let's try a bite!
Ohohoho!
I‐is there tomato in this?
The depth and juiciness
of the tomato permeates
the entire curry!
You are correct, ma'am.
The only liquid used in that
curry was from tomatoes.
No. You used only tomatoes,
with no added water to your
innovative dish?
Yes. I laid all the tomatoes
in a pot and applied heat,
which released all the
moisture I could need.
I added a special spice
blend suited for the
acidity of the juice
to bring out the umami
of the tomato, producing
a deep, rich curry.
The dough was baked using our
house‐made grape yeast starter.
[ANDO]
The surface is nice and crispy.
The texture becomes sweet
the more you chew.
It produces the perfect harmony
with the depth of the curry!
This is splendid!
Uniting the Japanese
idea of curry bread
to make a new kind
of Italian cuisine!
(Crowd oohs and aahs)
The only thing anyone ever
thought about Isami Aldini...
was that he was most likely
just riding the coattails
of his older brother.
But that's not true.
He has chosen to head
down uncharted territory
all on his own...
He's an explorer
of flavor horizons!
I am going to beat my brother.
Once and for all!
[URARA]
And Isami scores...
87 points!
He's in second place!
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
He's tied with Miyoko!
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
Looks like Nao is kicked out of
the running for the finals.
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
What is she laughing for?
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
Maybe she's in
shock or something.
Big Sister Miss Hisako!
It is a dead heat!
It's only fitting that
competition be fierce at
an event this big!
Now then, moving forward,
is Takumi Aldini!
Buon appetito.
Oh, the next dish
is pasta, is it?
Two Italian dishes competing
back to back.
[ORIE]
There's bacon, green peppers,
mushrooms...
This is like
Spaghetti Neapolitan,
but with curry sauce instead
of traditional tomato sauce,
and the pasta is closer to
a fettuccine cut as well.
Aside from that, nothing
really pops out as
significant. Hmm.
That calzone earlier was
so unique and flavorful
that this doesn't appear
very promising for‐
What in God's name is causing
this amazing depth of flavor?!
It's like a lightning
bolt to the senses!
[ANDO]
The stock uses beef shank
and chicken carcass,
with fennel and green cardamom
added as aromatics.
This splendid curry sauce
tantalizes the nose!
It binds itself perfectly to
these wide‐cut noodles!
Is there soy sauce
in this dish?!
It's not... It's tamari!
[ANDO]
It's produced mainly
in the Tokai region.
The flavor is more concentrated
than normal soy sauce,
and it's known for being
uniquely sweet and mellow.
I'm getting something else.
The smoothness of some
cheese embedded inside!
Allow me to explain.
Please look at the noodles'
cross‐section.
Oh! What is this treat?
The pasta has three layers!
The surface layers are flavored
with turmeric,
while the middle layer is softly
filled with the exquisiteness of
parmesan cheese.
I see...
The mixture of tamari
and parmesan
create an unusual
richness of bold flavor!
I don't understand.
When you added cheese,
the heat from boiling
the noodles would have‐
That's why he went
with three layers!
Sandwiched by outer layers,
the cheese inside would seep
into the pasta!
[ANDO]
The tamari reinforces the depth
of flavor in the curry sauce.
The richness of the
parmesan cheese spreads
perfectly on the tongue
and drives the point home.
The technique of steeping soft
cheeses in soy sauce is well
known,
but to think parmesan
cheese and tamari would
go so well together!
It is like a whole new
genre of cooking.
Bringing forth Italian and
Japanese styles with curry
as its heroic vessel.
[ORIE]
Takumi Aldini...
The Man who Carves out
new Flavor Horizons!
(Cheering)
[GUY]
Don't get me wrong.
They're both talented,
but I think Takumi has
a little more finesse.
I would like to request
that YOU make our main
dish tonight, Takumi.
Is that ok?
[ISAMI]
I can cook too, you know!
Isami! Why did you alter a
dish that was already completed?
[FATHER]
You muddled the flavors.
Do you want our customers
to lose faith in us?!
(Sobbing)
Brother, I'm sorry.
I ruined your cooking.
I didn't mean to. I promise.
I was just trying to show
that I knew how to cook too.
I didn't want to
be a burden to him.
The mezzaluna:
The knife named
after the half‐moon.
It suits us perfectly,
don't you think?
When two halves come together,
it forms something complete.
To be Aldini means the two of
us side‐by‐side, Isami!
I'm trying to get better
as a chef so that you
can grow with me.
Then one day, our
restaurant is sure to be
the best establishment
in all of Italy!
Buon giorno!
And welcome to Trattoria Aldini!
Ciao, Aldini brothers!
Looking forward to
some great food!
Countin' on you!
[ISAMI]
Usually he's more laid back,
but when he puts on his chef's
jacket, it's like he's a
different person.
Once again, I couldn't
keep up with him.
Yeah. Sure enough,
my brother is incredible.
[URARA]
Takumi Aldini scores 90 points!
Grazie!
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
Someone else was able
to score in the 90s!
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
Oh, man!
He even beat Miyoko!
(Whimper)
B Block is reaching
the final stretch.
Remaining chefs,
will you pl‐
Here you go!
What is she doing?!
Don't ever interrupt
Urara's commentary!
Don't make me hurt you!
I was kind of getting
tired of waiting.
(Gasps)
Wh‐wh‐what the heck
am I looking at?!
[SCHOOLGIRL]
What IS that?!
[SCHOOLBOY]
Is that really food?
I put my very soul into this.
Well, please eat up and enjoy!
The twins on this
package are supposed
to be us, yeah?
How... nostalgic...
This photo is from
1990...something.
Don't tell people
how old we are!
[BOTH]
Yeah, we have got
to change this box.
[URARA]
What? Um, this dish
looks so strange?
Can this really
be considered curry?
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
Is that spiral thingy edible?
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
The sauce is a weird
green color too.
There doesn't seem to be any
roux present in that dish.
Um... you don't know what
you're talking about.
Make no mistake:
Everything on that
plate is curry.
(Grunts)
What's going on?
The judges have
been so talkative,
but now they're totally
frozen all of a sudden.
Um... What's it?
So what's it like?
Is it any good?
How do I even
try to describe
this masterpiece?
Hot and cold, the ingredients
are infused so well...
These seasoned culinary figures
are at a loss for words!
Does that mean the dish is
beyond their comprehension
or understanding?
[KITA]
This curry sauce has
been made into a foam,
and is slightly warm.
Melting away elegantly
on the tongue.
Oh... This beautiful tomato
mousse is refreshingly cool and
pairs with it perfectly.
I added spices as well as
sodium alginate to harden it.
I made the mousse
using turmeric
and the powder of frozen and
pulverized foie gras.
The white in the middle
is a puree of
potato and six kinds of cheese.
And of course,
I flash‐froze it as well,
So it melts the moment
it touches the tongue.
If your mouth becomes too cold,
please have some of the spiced
pie crust.
It's been flavored with
coriander and other spices
to give the tongue
a tantalizing break.
Thermal sense:
It's a school of thought in
molecular gastronomy
where elements are used
in varying temperatures.
This dish incorporates
that concept.
Uh... so then...
what do you say?
Does it taste good or what?
Of course! Perfect!
I can't...
I don't have the words to
describe its pure deliciousness!
I just can't...
I'm at a loss for words.
[SCHOOLBOY]
It's so good even the food
critic can't describe it?!
It uses spices as its base,
but contends with alternating
textures and temperatures.
This dish redefines the field
of traditional cooking!
Yes. She could be called...
The Global Innovator!
(Giggle)
[URARA]
95 points!
In a surprising upset,
Alice Nakiri leaps to the
top, overthrowing Hisako!
Oh, I didn't get 100?
That's unexpected.
Still...
Y'see that? I beat you,
Little Miss Helper.
Don't call me,
"Little Miss Helper"?!
[SCHOOLBOY]
Awesome! All the judges
gave her 19 points!
[SCHOOLGIRL]
That's practically perfect!
Impossible!
Gourmands of such renown.
Haven't seen scores
like this in long time!
[URARA]
Alice Nakiri takes first place!
Followed by Arato
and then Takumi,
And tied for fourth place,
we have Hojo and Isami.
Only four contestants
from B Block will be
allowed to move on.
There will be a runoff vote
for the two contestants
now in fourth.
(Crowd cheers)
But they still put out
some interesting dishes,
only fitting for
the final contenders.
Yes... Hard to say one
is better than the other.
It's been a passionately
heated battle this year.
Now, let's move on
to the voting.
[MEGUMI]
Excuse me...
Huh?
Uh...
Please, I haven't...
presented... my curry.
She did the
suspended cutting.
(Surprised and annoyed murmurs)
Grr! And after I'd built them
up to the grand finale!
I‐I'm sorry!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
All right!
Now it's Megumi's turn!
Megumi!
Oh my gosh!
What're you guys
doing here?
We left the fishin' to all
the young'uns just for today.
We wanted to watch you shine
bright and make us all proud!
Oh, that is just too much.
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
Check out her crowd. Those are
some pretty rough‐lookin' dudes.
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
Who the heck IS
this girl, anyway?
[URARA]
Okay, Miss Tadokoro, if we could
get on with the tasting.
Go get 'em, Megumi!
You go stick 'em in the craw!
(Agreeing)
Um, please! I want to help
my family's restaurant!
Please help, sir!
Please, help me!
Please, help me, sir!
A monkfish DOBUJIRU
curry, sir.
"Dobujiru"... a hotpot with
monkfish as the main ingredient.
Indeed. It's a dish passed down
by fishermen in the Ibaraki and
Fukushima prefectures.
Monkfish in curry?
Just what is this
girl thinking?
Oh wow!
So this is pure heaven.
THIS is what monkfish
cooking is about.
[KITA]
The main trait of dobujiru
is that it takes monkfish liver
and slowly cooks it
down in a frying pan.
Miso and sake are added to the
liver to create the flavor base.
This thoughtful young lady
added spices to make a
spectacular "liver curry miso."
My body's free!
I could get addicted
to something like this!
To think, these spices
would be such a match
for the richness of liver!
It's like a warm glow within...
After all the food we've eaten,
you can feel it even more.
I mean, there's a
personal touch to this dish.
Ingredients include the
monkfish's flesh, its skin,
and fins and...
Hm? What's this?
Kogiku pumpkin,
Tachikawa burdock root,
and Akasuji daikon!
Um, it is!
All those vegetables are
grown in my hometown.
I tried various ways
of bringing out their flavor,
but curry is overpowering and
didn't match the sweetness and
bitterness of the vegetables,
so I was very worried
about what to do.
But in a dobujiru using
monkfish liver,
not only is the flavor
of the spices drawn out,
but it acts as a kind of
bridge to the naturalness
of the vegetables.
I wanted to make something
where you could taste
AND smells where I was born.
That's the kind of curry
I wanted to make!
[MOTHER]
Huh? Megumi
really made this?
[HOSTESS]
Yes! If she worked here,
no one could come close to her!
[MOTHER]
Apparently, there's a
world famous cooking school
stationed in Tokyo.
You think you
might wanna go
there, sweetie?
They say a bunch of
its graduates are
working all over the world.
[MEGUMI]
Yes, but...
Mom, I...
In the future, I was
gonna help out around the inn.
Well if in the end
you decide you still want
to work here that'll be fine.
And actually, that would
make me real happy.
But first, I'd like for
you to go out just once
to see what the big,
wide world has to offer.
Y'understand?
What the heck?!
You tellin' me Megumi's
cooking's only in the 10s?
I told ya, it's the judges five
scores all together that
make a perfect hundred!
Way to go! That's our
shining star right there!
Take this... It'll
bring you good luck
at school, darlin'.
[FISHERMAN]
Tokyo, huh?
We're gonna miss ya 'round here.
But look...
there aint many of us
that're better than you,
ya got that, kiddo?
[OLD CHEF]
Do your best, Megumi!
[FISHERMAN]
Megumi might be the
greatest up‐and‐comer
this town's ever had!
[MOTHER on phone]
Megumi, how's school goin'?
Mother, uh... it's uh...
It's going great.
My classes are so much fun.
You do know that you're
really talented, right?
Are you going in for some
cooking practice, Megumi?
We'll go with you
if you want.
Oh, thank you!
But I thought it would be best
if I study by myself tonight.
(Sobbing)
Here we are, Megumi,
your day is here.
It's time to leave your
tiny, tiny garden...
and spread your wings.
[URARA]
Megumi Tadokoro
scores 88 points!
4th place!
She leaps into 4th place!
(Crowd cheers)
(Chuckling)
Miyoko Hojo is out
of the running!
What an upset!
Megumi, you did it!
(Chanting)
Megumi! Megumi! Megumi! Megumi!
[MIYOKO]
I thought I had what
it takes to win.
And that princess had nothing.
But it looks like she has
everything she needs.
[NATSUME]
Uh yeah. This is bad.
How could I give points
for a dish like this?
Um... okay...
but, um, what about
the student's score?
Are you hard of hearing?
I said the dish was bad.
WAHH! Oh so,
the total score is...
19 points.
[SHUN]
Natsume Sendawara gave
zero points again.
She's judged more
than 10 contestants
and hasn't given a
single point.
Even though everything
looked delicious, huh?
It's crazy... it's like
a graveyard, dude!
A‐Block's judges seem to be
pretty tough on these guys!
Please, uh, the next contestant!
Ryo Kurokiba,
if you would be so kind!
It's your turn.
[ALICE]
Next time, on the twenty‐third
course of Food Wars...
Darnit, Ryo, say something!
[RYO]
Uhh...
[ALICE]
"The Unfolding Individual
Competition"
I'll be the one
to reach the top!
Uh, isn't this
a bit much?
Nah, not at all. Nothing's
too much for our girl!