Well, the train
is right on time.
I guess I'll be goin'.
Megumi...
I can't believe you're
leaving your mother and I.
It seems like you only
now just turned 13.
(Sob)
Grandpa...
you don't need
to worry about me.
Sure enough!
Your food is, like,
the best we've ever
had 'round here!
I just know you'll make
it in the big city!
[MEGUMI]
Yeah...
[MOTHER]
I hope you'll be able
to get settled.
Take this...
It'll bring you good
luck at school darlin'.
(Gasp)
Ah... Thank you.
Oh my gosh we're gonna miss
you so much, Megumi!
[GRANDMA]
That Megumi, she is
such a sweet girl.
(Train horn blows)
Thanks, everyone.
I just know I'll become
a great chef some day,
then I'll come back home!
(Thud)
(Boom)
EEEEE!
(Birds chirping)
Uh...
Megumi Tadokoro...
at the very beginning
of my first year
of high school...
is on the edge of a cliff!
(Opening Song)
(Orchestral music)
[URARA]
We now present our
academic insignia.
And our new freshman
representative...
Erina Nakiri.
[ERINA]
Thank you.
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
Ah, Miss Erina,
she's smokin' as always!
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
She's beautiful and
top of her class.
She's the perfect woman!
If I could just go out with
her one time, I'd die happy.
You crazy?! She would
either kill you
or you would end up getting
thrown out of freakin' school!
Yeah! She's the granddaughter
of the Don who's like
the mafia boss of
the food world!
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
Yeah, but still...
(Sigh)
[URARA]
And now, we will have
our ceremonial address.
The Academy's director...
Ngh!
(Crowd gasps)
[URARA]
Master Senzaemon Nakiri!
Hmm.
(Scared screams)
OH‐MY‐GA‐GA!
That man rules fine cuisine!
I mean, he has Japan's entire
food industry under his thumb!
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
He's more terrifying
than a mafia Don!
He's the Devil!
The Devil of Cooking!
I welcome you...
You have reached the
high school division.
Congratulations.
(Oohs and aahs)
For three years,
you have learned the basics
of food preparation,
while attending our
middle school division.
You have furthered your
knowledge of ingredients.
[SENZAEMON]
You have undertaken numerous
drills in which you have
had to prepare dishes...
You have heard a wide
variety of lectures,
such as cooking theory,
nutrition,
public health,
cultivation,
and managing a
restaurant business.
Now, as you stand at the
precipice of the rest
of your cooking lives...
you will be facing challenges
not just of technique
or knowledge...
But your resolve to see if you
can live as a professional chef!
And that means ninety‐nine
percent of you...
will sacrifice yourselves
to the cooking gods...
to unveil those
who move on!
(Cackle)
He said sacrifice!
That sounds like it's goin'
to be pretty hardcore.
Uh‐huh... Sure hope so.
(Nervous whimper)
Last year we started with 812
high school division freshmen.
And the number that was
allowed to proceed on...
was just 76!
The mediocre and the inept
are cast aside without mercy.
Out of a thousand freshmen
only one hundred will
remain to advance,
and you will be able to
count on one hand those
who reach graduation.
The odds are not
in your favor...
But you...
You can make it happen!
(Excited gasps)
Study hard. Cook hard.
Mm‐hm.
(Inspirational music)
Best of luck to you!
(Crowd murmurs)
[ERINA]
The source of the Tohtsuki
brand's strength
is that it educates
a select few chosen
through fierce competition.
If you can make it
to graduation,
you'll attain a lifetime of
stardom in the cooking world.
But be that as it may...
I feel sorry for everyone that
is in the same class as I am...
because from the moment
you were born,
you were fated to battle
for merely second place.
Only one will reach
the summit of the Academy
and reign supreme over the
Japanese culinary world:
me, Erina Nakiri.
[URARA]
And finally, I would
like to introduce a
new transfer student.
Hm.
Someone must've passed
through a different reviewer.
[ERINA]
Soma Yukihira...
(Erina screaming)
Go away! Get away from me!
(Angels laugh)
Stay away, you little freaks!
(Grunt)
Burns me up just to
even think about it.
[SOMA] Uh, well,
[ERINA]
Well, no matter.
sorry to be all up here
I'll never set eyes
in the spotlight and everything.
on that pig ever again.
[SOMA]
(Nervous laugh)
[URARA]
Never mind that, just hurry
up and introduce yourself!
Hm...
[SOMA]
Okay...
I'll make this
short and sweet.
Hm?
I'm sure you all
need to study.
HUHHH?!
So um, my name's
Soma Yukihira.
And, well, to be honest it's an
honor to attend this school...
as a stepping stone
in my career.
(Murmurs)
[SOMA]
Now sure, my transfer
was kinda unexpected...
but I still don't plan on losing
to a bunch of wannabes
who've never even stood
in front of a customer before.
(Angry whispers)
I mean, c'mon, am I right?
Anyway, since I'm here
and everything...
I might as well
take the top spot.
Mm?!
Wuh! Ah!
[STUDENT]
Is he serious?
Alrighty then...
See a few of you at graduation!
[SCHOOLBOY 7]
Oh you think so, huh!
[SCHOOLBOY 8]
Oh whatever! Eat it!
[SCHOOLBOY 9]
Go to hell, you son of a bitch!
[SCHOOLBOY 10]
You don't know
what you're talking about,
you A‐HOLE!
(Angry yelling)
(Sigh)
Glad I got through that...
Huh?
Oh!
It's you!
Uh, it was
"Erina," right?
(Angry gasp)
I sure was nervous
up there!
When I was a kid,
getting awards always
made me uncomfortable.
So how'd you think I did?
It wasn't weird, right?
How the hell is this
happening right now?!
What is this! What are you
doing at this school?!
Well, I mean, uh...
I got a notice that I passed, I
figured I might as well show up.
Ah!
That's absurd.
I thought I didn't
make it in.
You said my food
was disgusting.
If something's delicious,
you should just
own up and say it.
S'cuse me?!
[ERINA]
This is all wrong.
I failed him.
There's no way
he can be here!
Is it delicious or not?
Say it!
Disgusting!
WHA‐?!
Ngh...
I'll make myself clear:
I do not approve
of this decision.
Not of you, and not of
your peasant cooking!
Uh!
This is obviously
some sort of mistake
and you've been accepted
by a clerical error.
Hm.
"Take the top spot," will you?
Don't make me laugh.
[ERINA]
All the students who've advanced
from the middle school division
have learned cutting‐edge
gastro techniques!
You don't have the nearly
enough training for this.
There's no way you can
measure up to them.
Have fun trying
to play catch‐up!
Middle school
training, huh?
Uh!
Yes, that's right.
I was three years old
the first time
I held a chef's knife...
[SOMA]
My dad taught me.
And I've spent the last
12 years in the kitchen!
Uh!
I won't let you
call my food
"disgusting".
Slandering our restaurant's
name is unacceptable!
Just you wait,
Erina Nakiri.
I'm gonna make that
mouth of yours...
say my food is delicious!
I'll show you what
my cooking's all about!
Hm.
Hehehe.
Wow, that transfer student
was something else, huh?
Mm‐hmm. It might just
take that kind of
attitude to graduate.
And snag the top
spot at the Academy.
That's a good point!
We'll just have to kill
it, too, won't we?!
Right, Megumi?
Uh... Where'd she go?
Uhh...
It's hopeless.
I'm sure to be the first one
on the chopping block!
[MEGUMI]
I was dead last in the high
school advancement exams,
and now I've gotten
my final warning!
No, I cannot give up.
I can't disappoint everyone
back home who got me here.
I have to focus, I'm on the
verge of flunking out...
I have to keep to myself and
not rile people up like that
crazy transfer student!
Okay! I'll make sure not to go
anywhere near that guy!
[AIDE]
Students, as of today
we'll be splitting into
separate classrooms
for our lectures.
(Menacing growls)
[AIDE]
You'll be cooking
(Soma whistles)
in these assigned pairs.
Everyone understand?
(Whimper)
Hello!
Eek!
Wah! Why?!
[ERINA]
L.I.C.K.
(Classroom chatter)
[SOMA]
Oh man...
I don't think I've had someone
try to teach me how to cook
since I was just a little kid.
Look at this frickin' jerk.
Jackass.
That transfer student sure
talked a lot of crap at the
ceremony.
Sure did. Hope he falls
on his dumb face.
Anyway... so you're name
is Megumi, right?
(Nervous sounds)
What are you doing?
Is that some sort of pre‐cooking
ritual or something?
Ah! Um... well, uh...
I thought that maybe it would
help me not be so nervous.
You're nervous?
What for?
Uhh.
(Sigh)
Well because...
if I end up with one
more failing grade,
then I'm gonna be expelled.
Okay...
Isn't this like
an elite school?
How were you even
able to get in?
UGH!
AHH!
Just when I was trying
to keep my head down,
I had to get paired up
with him of all people.
This is so not fair.
Well, my name's
Soma Yukihira.
But you can just
call me "Soma."
Nice to meet ya!
Ohh...
Okay... I'm Megumi.
(Ominous growl)
[MEGUMI]
Th‐the other people's
eyes feel like daggers.
Does he not even notice?
[TEACHER]
Pay attention.
[STUDENTS]
Huh?
Good morning...
Time to learn,
my young apprentis.
[OTHER STUDENTS]
Good morning, Master Chef!
A‐apple... "Apple n' tea"?
That is Chef
Laurent Chapelle!
Ze moment you step foot
in ze kitchen,
you are responsible for
producing extraordinary food.
Regardless of your
gastronomic experience
nor your pedigree in life.
My class rules are very strict.
Any dish zat is not an A
will be viewed as an E.
And zat, my friends,
is a failure.
(Megumi squeaks)
Uhuhuh...
Are you kidding me?
I cannot believe my bad luck!
Why is my first class
with Chapelle?!
[SOMA]
That guy's kinda
scary, huh?
He's famous
the world over
for being incredibly
strict even for Tohtsuki's!
[MEGUMI]
Last year, he failed his
entire class of 50 students,
and 18 of those flunked out
just because of his lectures!
He's been given the nickname
"The Chef Who Never Smiles."
Oh yeah?
(Nervous mumbling)
[CHAPELLE]
Apprentis, today's menu item is
boeuf bourguignon.
It is a staple of the
traditional French cuisine.
I've put ze recipe on ze
whiteboard for you to follow.
You have two hours
to prepare it.
Present your dishes once
they're complete.
[CHAPELLE]
Now then: Let's begin.
Everyone, commence à cuire!
Whoa, what'd he just say,
that's not appropriate.
(Sigh)
I guess we'll
just have to try.
Calm down, take it
step by step...
Soma seems so confident.
He's gotta be a
good cook, right?
"Boofa... buffa..." What the?
EEK! Soma, have you ever
made this dish before?
Never. Not once.
(Gasp)
(Whimper)
Sounds like it's basically
stewed beef with bacon,
am I right?
I'm sure we'll be
just fine.
I'll go take
a look‐see.
I am so freakin' dead.
(Soma whistles)
(Growling)
(Sizzling)
Sauté the mushrooms in butter
and add them to the pot...
Then, just let it
simmer over low heat.
Take the meat out
in 40 minutes.
in 39 minutes!
TAKE THE MEAT OUT
IN 38 MINUTES!
Megumi, check
it out.
Ah!
There must be like a thousand
seasonings in here!
Ah...
Ah... Kinda feeling
like an idiot
being the only one
who's freaking out.
Oh, I guess I really need to
start plating, don't I?
(Maniacal laughs)
(Casual whistling)
Huh?
Uh...
Hey, Megumi.
Did you open the lid?
Uh? No, I didn't.
I mean, it still has to simmer
for 20 more minutes, right?
Hm?
Hehehe.
Uh!
(Boiling)
[BOTH]
Huh?
[MEGUMI]
Uh! What the heck
is that in there?
It's salt.
Ah! Omigod!
[MEGUMI]
Wh‐what do we do?
There's no way we can
use this meat anymore!
It'll take over an hour,
the meat needs more
time to get tender,
and for it to soak up
all the flavors.
Then it's gonna need to
simmer for another 30 minutes
for the flavors to blend
within the sauce!
(Heavy ticking)
[MEGUMI]
And we've only got
30 minutes left!
But if we presented
this over‐salted mess
to Master Chapelle,
he'll fail us out
of school for sure!
Ahh!
(Dramatic piano music)
[MEGUMI]
No...
Everyone, I'm sorry.
I guess I'm
coming back home!
(Sobbing)
[SOMA]
I brought the backup
ingredients.
Huh?
Well, wanna get started?
Huh? What? But, Soma...
There's no way we'll be
able to get this done in time.
That teacher said some pretty
smart things today, huh?
[SOMA]
We may be students,
but above all, we're CHEFS!
Ah?
So!
No matter what,
the food must go out!
[SOMA]
Help me.
Ah! O‐okay!
(Sheen)
Here ya go! Salt, pepper,
and Bouquet Garni!
I'm on it!
[STUDENT 1]
Hehe. That big‐mouth
transfer student
seems to be having himself
a little trouble, doesn't he?
Sure is. Those two are
bound to get flunked now.
Uh‐huh.
Mmm...
You get an A.
[BOTH]
Yes!
[CHAPELLE]
Next team.
Shouldn't be too long till
another team is finished.
All we have left is
the sauce. Let's get to it.
[SOMA]
Chef Chapelle...
We're ready for tasting.
Huh?
(Shocked gasps)
Order up!
How in the...?
Hm?!
Huh?
It's perfectly tender...
dare I say,
fork‐tender, even.
How is this
happening?!
That's impossible!
There's no way they
had time to simmer!
It seems that
the two of you had
somewhat of an
accident earlier.
How were you able
to finish on time?
Hehe. By incorporating
some honey...
I rubbed it on the meat
before simmering,
adding some to the
seasoning, as well.
Did you?
Honey contains protease...
an enzyme zat breaks down ze
proteins at a faster rate.
[CHAPELLE]
You used it on the tough,
rib‐cut roast
to make it tender
in a short amount of time.
But, Soma, how in the world did
you know you could use honey
to make that happen?
A while back,
I read in a cookbook
that pineapple juice can
work as a tenderizer.
But I was pretty
young at the time.
And I wasn't going to be able to
just go out and buy a pineapple.
So I tried out a bunch of
things to see if they would
have the same effect.
And guess what I found...
Honey! It keeps well,
and is super easy to use.
(Gasp)
[SOMA]
You'll understand
if you try a bite.
Here.
Uh!
(Gasp)
Bzzzzz. Bzzzzz.
Ahhhh!
AHHHHH!
I'm gonna melt!
HAAHHH!
So syrupy!
Aah! C'est merveilleux!
Ahh...
[STUDENTS]
Professor Chapelle...
He's smiling!
[CHAPELLE]
Chefs Soma and Megumi...
Ah...
However...
Uh?
It is a shame I do not have
ze auzority to give you two
a higher grade than an A.
For the dish was perfection.
Whaa!
Ha! You are welcome!
Uh...
So that transfer student's
food is...
...better than ours was?!
What the‐?!
[BOTH]
Guh!
Uh? Ah! Geh!
Hey!
Our sauce is burnt!
Wha‐?! Oh, no! Ah!
GAH!
(Both scream)
Hmm...
You have failed.
(Groan)
(Thud)
(Classroom chatter)
(Laughing)
That was a cinch,
wasn't it, my brother?
Of course.
Just like always.
If only we'd been in
the same class...
I wanted to crush
that transfer student.
Soma...
Megumi, good
work today.
Um...
No, thank you
for all your help.
It is all thanks to you
that I... that I...
Nah, nah, it's fine.
We should work
together again, Megumi.
Okay!
I think I may have
been paired up
with someone
really talented.
Someone special.
Ehehehe.
By the way,
now that the two of us
have gotten acquainted,
you wanna try one of
my new dishes?
Oh! Are you sure?...
I would love to try it!
(Glop glop)
[SOMA]
Here...
Huh? I don't...
(Distant cackle)
It's honey‐coated
dried squid.
MM!
BLEEGGHH!
Ah!
AH!
AHHHH!
The squid and honey
combination is so offensive
in so many ways,
it's as if my entire body
is being violated!
[MEGUMI]
NOOOO!
(Ending Song)
(Oohs and aahs)
[SCHOOLGIRL 1]
Ah! That's Miss Erina!
[SCHOOLGIRL 2]
Omigosh, is she trying
a new dish again?
[SCHOOLGIRL 3]
Ahhh?! I would love to taste it!
I don't care what it is!
[HISAKO]
Miss Erina!
Please, Miss Erina!
[ERINA]
What are you
going on about?
Chef Chapelle's class
has just posted
his highest grade
of the day so far.
[HISAKO]
It was that transfer student:
Soma Yukihira!
ERRGH!
UH!
I'll tell you
just once...
(Demonic voice)
Do not mention that name
in front of me ever again!
I‐I'm sorry,
it won't happen again!
Grr!
(Cheeky laugh)
[ERINA]
The one blot on my otherwise
pristine record...
I will not stand for this...
I'll make sure I get rid of
him as quickly as possible!
That I will!
[SOMA]
Oh! And there's peanut
butter‐flavored squid.
(Cowering)
Plus I have all sorts of other
experiments for you to try...
(Evil laugh)
Somebody help me!
Get me away from this guy!
[MEGUMI]
Next time on Food Wars.
F‐f‐fourth course:
"Sacred Mother of Kyokusei"
Bon appétit!
[SOMA]
Oh, oh, oh!
Try THIS one next...
(Sheepish scream)
(Sinister laugh)