This is too delicious!
It makes perfect use of
seasonal spring ingredients.
He made an extremely
delicate dish in a short
amount of time!
This is on a whole different
level than the other
people here.
Allow me the indulgence
of re‐introducing myself:
[ISSHIKI]
From the Tohtsuki Council
of Ten...
Uhh.
[ISSHIKI]
I am Chair No. 7...
Satoshi Isshiki.
So, that means...
you're on the council of Ten?
Now then...
I would like to try
YOUR food, next.
(Nervous inhale)
[ISSHIKI]
I'm curious as to
what you will prepare.
Come and show me...
how you express yourself...
through your cooking.
(Nervous exhale)
[SOMA]
I think I'm beginning
to understand...
why my dad sent me here.
Hmph!
Huh?
(Swish)
Order up!
(Opening Song)
(Owl hooting)
(Heavy snoring)
[SOMA]
His dish. A peppered mackerel.
With a puree...
So I'm guessing your
family's restaurant...
is in traditional
fine dining?
Interesting. Why would
you think that?
Because peppered mackerel
is normally found on
that type of menu.
Plus, you can't learn to
prepare this kind of thing
at just any old restaurant.
(Laugh)
[SOMA]
That mackerel, cooked up
flaky and delicate...
And the surprising choice
to make the spring cabbage
the base of the puree...
Still, the silky smoothness
is a perfect match
for the mackerel.
Mackerel's in season now,
and paired with spring cabbage,
the palatability of each
heightens the other.
It's just like a
gorgeous spring day!
Mackerel...
Yes!
Yukihira's No. 20
from our secret menu!
"Yukihira"?
That's the name of
our family restaurant.
[SOMA]
I will use mackerel as
the ingredient, too.
It's one of our most
popular dishes.
And just like your dish,
mine will have a spring
theme as well.
Ahmm... Uhh?
Buh! I fell asleep...
[RYOKO]
Oh, gosh! I think I drank
too much special rice juice!
(Sizzling)
[BOTH]
Hm?
[YUKI]
Huh? Soma's cooking?
[RYOKO]
Um... Maybe he's
still hungry.
No, it's a
cooking battle.
Oh, Shun, you were
awake this whole time?
Wait! They're
really facing off?!
How'd this happen?!
Beats me.
But it was Isshiki..
He was the one who
threw down the gauntlet.
[GIRLS]
Uh!
[YUKI]
Um, shouldn't we be talking
about someone's lack of clothes?
[RYOKO]
I don't know. It'd be a
shame to ruin the mood.
[YUKI]
I guess.
(Sizzling)
Order up!
[SOMA]
Yukihira secret menu
No. 20: revamped!
Mackerel onigiri chazuke!
Now it really should
be done using salmon,
but I wanted to make
a slightly different
version using mackerel.
There's enough for
everybody, so please
dig in, guys!
Ah! Thank you very much!
Okay, so what do
we have here?
[SOMA]
Salted seaweed tea.
It's bold, but its
lightly salted flavor
should finish out
the meal perfectly.
GAH!
If you cook up
something like this,
you're gonna
make us all hungry!
Got that right.
[ISSHIKI]
Okay, it looks like simple,
normal ochazuke.
This dish would be served at
any cheap family eatery.
Unless...
Don't mind if I do!
Eat it, everyone!
[BOTH]
This is looking good.
(Slurp)
(Heartbeat)
Mm! Mmm...
Mmmmmm...
Delicious!
The mackerel is perfectly juicy,
but the skin is still
nice and crispy!
[YUKI]
The flavor pops out
with every bite!
This kind of texture
wouldn't be possible by
simply broiling it.
How did he do this?
[ISSHIKI]
Poele...
Hm?
This mackerel was cooked
using the poele method.
Po...e...le?
Why are YOU acting
so surprised, too?!
Uh, I'm just not sure
what "poele" is...
Huh?!
It's time to learn, kids:
Poele is a French method
used to cook protein.
It is a style of saute.
[ISSHIKI]
Olive oil is poured on
top of the protein,
basting it if you will, giving
it a consistent browning.
Would you mind telling me,
Young Soma?
Where did you happen to learn
your French cooking techniques?
From my dad. He's my mentor.
He taught me how
to cook like this.
He said it's perfect for making
fish nice and crispy.
[SOMA]
The crunchiness goes great
on a bed of rice,
or you can add seaweed tea
to give it a whole different
texture.
It all depends on what
you're trying to do.
Hm...
So, it appears your father
has studied French cuisine?
I'm not sure, I couldn't really
tell you anything about that...
But it sure seems like
he's studied in several
different countries, though.
I can see that.
[ISSHIKI]
Who could've imagined
onigiri done in
a French fashion?
He's bound by neither genre
nor nationality...
This cooking is so free!
And poele was the perfect
choice, given the thickness of
the fish's skin.
Ideal for both salmon and
mackerel.
Young Soma made that
determination in an instant,
and arranged his menu
accordingly.
The pure white of the rice
is like newly fallen snow!
And amidst it, the mackerel
flavor is so pronounced...
It is the essence
of spring itself!
With this dish,
he has expressed
the very moment
of spring's awakening!
(Blowing)
Mm... Mm!
(Slurping)
Mmm...
(More slurping)
(Aggresive scarfing)
Ah...
(Twinkling)
(Choral music)
(Leaves rustling)
(Birds chirping)
Mm! AHH!
AAHHH!
Mmmmaaahh!
Bloom!
You're welcome!
So beautiful...
A magical greeting
to the season...
Well done!
You too, my man.
I really like what you did...
It felt just like spring.
Thank you for your
scrumptious competition.
Mm. Ah... Huh?
Huh?!
What the heck?
What's goin' on?
Uh! Uhhh...
Hoh...
(Light snoring)
[YUKI]
Zenji? Zenji! Zenji!
Hey.
He's not waking up, is he?
Doesn't look
like it.
(Aoki and Sato groan)
Okay, time to go!
We'll definitely clean
up next time, dude.
Totally, next time
for sure, bro‐chinski.
(Yuki hums)
(Megumi whimpers)
(Yawn)
[MEGUMI]
Okay, so why did
Isshiki decide
that he wanted to do a
cooking battle tonight?
Beats me. Who ever knows
what he's thinking?
There's really no point in
wondering what a freak‐a‐zoid
like him is thinking anyway.
[AOKI]
So sleepy!
[YUKI]
Well, goodnight,
Megumi.
[MEGUMI]
Yeah, goodnight.
[ISSHIKI]
Well, Young Soma,
With these festivities,
you are officially
one of us here at Kyokusei.
(Yawn)
If you have any concerns,
do not hesitate to ask.
In that case...
How does someone
join the Ten?
Hm?
(Laugh)
[ISSHIKI]
Oh, yes!
You ARE out to take
the top spot
at the Academy,
aren't you?
So I must ask you then...
what keeps you so motivated?
[SOMA]
The truth is, my dad and I are
kind of at odds at the moment.
Unless I can become
a member of The Ten,
he won't acknowledge
what I can do.
That battle we just had
may have been a draw, but...
If I do end up
beating you...
would that make me
the new Tohtsuki No. 7?
Heh.
This is wonderful!
WHA?!
You have such powerful
ambition, Young Soma!
[ISSHIKI]
I'm so ridiculously
moved right now!
That's exactly what
it takes for a student
to thrive here at Kyokusei!
Uh... Okay...
(Gleeful yelling)
[ISSHIKI]
Alas, we must postpone that
discussion for another day.
It's getting
pretty late.
We should probably get
some rest, okay?
Yeah... I guess
you're right.
Take the top spot
at Tohtsuki, huh?
I believe the true weight
of those words will
soon become clear.
[SOMA]
So, um, my name's Soma Yukihira.
And well, to be honest it's an
honor to attend this school.
As a stepping stone
in my career.
I might as well
take the top spot.
Young Soma, you will
come to learn...
at this school,
cooking is everything.
[ERINA]
Your main ingredient
will be eggs.
Make me one proper dish.
Those whose plate impresses
me may transfer.
All others will be forever
banned from the Academy.
Shut up and give me
that bowl, you idiot!
DISGUSTING!
I'll make myself clear:
I do not approve
of this decision.
Not of you and not of
your peasant cooking!
"Take the top spot," will you?
Don't make me laugh.
[ERINA]
All the students who've advanced
from the middle school division
have learned cutting‐edge
gastro techniques!
You don't have nearly
enough training for this.
There's no way you
can measure up to them.
Have fun trying
to play catch up!
(Long laugh)
Mmmm...
I'm gonna ferment...
Uh. Huh? Hey, Bonnie.
(Oinking)
Hm?
(Quacking)
Heavy!
(Yawn)
Hi there, guys...
Good Morning.
GAH! They always,
ALWAYS mess up my room!
I'm gonna tell em like it is,
no more, not ever, I am done
with those mouth‐breathers!
AGHH!
[AOKI]
'Sup?
[SATO]
How's it going?
[BOTH]
Huh?
(Yawn)
What is it?
What's going on?
(Upbeat music)
[SOMA]
We put it off last night...
But now, with your
No. 7 seat on the line...
Satoshi Isshiki...
I challenge you!
(Music ends abruptly)
(Tap Tap Tap)
(Groans and yawns)
Hm!
Hm?
Hello?
[SATO]
We should it.
[YUKI]
I'm so freakin' starving!
[AOKI]
Hey, Gramma, you done yet?
Stop complaining and wait
patiently, you big ol' babies!
[ISSHIKI]
I'm sorry, Young Soma.
I failed to explain
things well.
HM?!
[ISSHIKI]
About how challenges work
here at Tohtsuki Academy.
(Crowd cheering)
[SCHOOLGIRL]
Good luck!
Dosukoi! Hah!
[GODABAYASHI]
We of the Chanko Stew Society
have a long and noble history,
stretching back to the
Academy's very founding.
And yet, Erina Nakiri,
you wish to demolish it.
In order to build
what exactly?!
A cooking annex
for my personal use.
My fifth kitchen
has gotten a wee bit
crowded for my taste‐
How dare you!
That grand
historic building
is home to a long
passion for eating
fostered by the students
of Tohtsuki Academy!
It's not for you
to toss aside!
How can you even
call yourself a chef?!
[SUMO 1]
Yeah, that's right!
Miss Erina...
(Sigh)
Trying to imitate the recipes
of those senior students,
while also squandering
away your budget...
Is that YOUR grand idea
of "passion"?
Uh?!
These past
few years,
you've contributed
little of value.
A society that
merely praises its
past accomplishments
isn't needed
here at Tohtsuki.
You are always quick to
flaunt your authority...
Someone needs to put
you in your place!
If I beat you, you will step
down from the council!
I challenge you!
Let's go Erina Nakiri!
And if I win, construction
continues as planned.
Ready, Godabayashi?
Let the battle begin.
[ISSHIKI]
Here at the Academy,
there's a system
for resolving disputes
between students.
And it involves following
a few specific rules.
[ISSHIKI]
You may challenge me for
the No. 7 seat if you wish,
but the guidelines state that
you must offer something
of corresponding value.
What would be considered
"corresponding value"?
For something to the level
of losing my council seat...
Even you being expelled
wouldn't be adequate.
Guh! Why not?!
That's right.
That's how much weight
the Council of Ten carries.
[FUMIO]
After all,
they're the highest
decision‐making body on campus.
Not even the teachers can
go against a ruling made
by the Council of Ten.
In the past, residents from
this very dorm would join the
prestigious Ten every year.
It was truly the Golden Age
of Kyokusei's dormitory.
By comparison, you're all
just pathetic losers.
Aww, Ms. Fumio, you
don't really mean that.
I guess that
would be that...
You could battle me only
if I accepted the challenge,
and to be honest I would not
prefer you leaving the school.
Put simply... this challenge
is not going to happen.
Are you serious?
But I've been up since 5 in
the morning all ready to go!
In any case,
going for the No. 7 seat...
...is too ambitious!
They'd probably
think you were
some kinda idiot.
[ISSHIKI]
And it's not like you can
just challenge people on a whim.
Hm?
There are three things you
need to challenge someone.
First off: You need authorized
officials to declare the
challenge valid.
Second: An odd number of judges.
And third: The agreement of both
parties as to the conditions of
the challenge.
Only then will things
start to come together.
Oh man, that seems like
a lotta hassle.
[ISSHIKI]
However, the upside is...
When the conditions are met,
you are free to battle anyone
who attends the school.
(Light gasp)
[ISSHIKI]
"Any and all challengers must be
put down through cooking."
That is Tohtsuki's traditional,
one‐on‐one battle mantra.
And it has become known as:
"Food War"!
[JUDGE 1]
A judgment has been reached!
In this Food War,
the victor is Erina Nakiri!
(Crowd cheers)
No... What the hell?!
How can this be?
[GODABAYASHI]
But the... Stew Society...
What is the matter
with you people?
What was wrong with
my lobster hotpot, huh?
Uwaahh...
Ah...
(Bubbles churning)
Ahh...
(Railroad alarm)
(Stampeding footsteps)
(Growling)
[ERINA]
Godabayashi...
your dish fails on 27 points.
First, there's the lobster.
You blanched it for
two seconds far too long.
Ehh!
[ERINA]
Next, the oysters produced
a slight off‐flavor that
affected the whole dish.
Guh! Shut up!
As for how the vegetables
were treated‐
Shut your mouth!
Do you really think
what you made
is that much better
than mine?
I have been perfecting
that dish for weeks,
just for this challenge!
[JUDGE]
Hakkeyoi!
AH! Ooooh!
[ERINA]
Well, Godabayashi?
Huh?!
What do you say to my
langoustine ravioli?
[GODABAYASHI]
The ravioli is steamed
light and fluffy,
while the langoustine inside is
plump and bursting with flavor.
Mm!
(Struggling)
[GODABAYASHI]
The sheer delicacy of it
is like being at the mercy
of a champion yokozuna!
This is a different
dimension of flavor!
It's immaculate!
Uuhhh. Uhh.
(Groaning)
It's me. I won.
Huh?
[ERINA]
Take it down.
AHH! NO!
She's so heartless!
This...
This is truly the granddaughter
of the Demon of Food?!
Hmm. I'll be seeing you.
(Crowd cheers)
[SOMA]
"Food Wars," huh?
Okay then. I was kinda hoping
to challenge Erina Nakiri...
Uh. There's no way you
could ever beat her, Soma.
(Satoshi chuckles)
I look forward to seeing
how things play out.
I am certain he will achieve
some impressive victories.
After all, he was able to
cook to a draw against me,
the No. 7 seat.
I'm sure you see it too,
don't you, Shun?
Tch. Too early
to tell.
You don't seem to be
taking this very seriously.
[SHUN]
You didn't even serve
your specialty.
That dish you made is the
definition of playing it safe.
Don't be silly, my friend.
I put a great deal of effort
into making that dish special.
Yeah... I'm not
buying it.
Young Soma...
when I ate your food,
I had a revelation:
[ISSHIKI]
You might be a little
green right now...
But you are going
to be the catalyst
that will bring the academy's
Food Wars to flourish!
(Ending Song)
(Distant crowd cheering)
[HISAKO]
That was an excellent
performance, Miss Erina.
[ERINA]
Eh...
Defeating that toad
is nothing to brag about.
The entire ordeal
was a disappointment.
The Tohtsuki Academy
is in search of nothing
less than perfection.
Give me the list of
the next targets.
Uh! M‐ma'am!
It's right here!
[IKUMI]
Miss Erina.
Hm?
[IKUMI]
Would you allow me to go next?
There's really no need
for you to waste your time
going after these low‐life
imbeciles yourself.
I would like to
handle them for you.
Oh, would you?
Now that sounds
promising.
But well, you do know what
that entails, don't you?
(Shink)
They don't call me the
"Meat Master" for nothing.
[IKUMI]
And I'll protect that title...
You can bet on that.
I will serve up
a flawless victory.
(Giggle)
[ISSHIKI]
Next time on Food Wars...
Oh, it's already
the sixth course, huh?
"The Meat Aggressor"
Just wonderful!
[ERINA]
You want some?
[HISAKO]
You know I do!