[AOKI] Zero points!
[SATO] Zero points!
[AOKI]
Zero points again?!
[SATO]
Is zero the only score
Natsume Sendawara know?!
[AOKI]
Maybe her machine's,
like, broken or somethin'!
[SATO]
Alice Nakiri's gothy
servant‐dude, huh?
What kind of food is
this weirdo gonna make?
Apparently he had some huge
lines at the camp's 200‐dish
breakfast challenge.
[NATSUME]
Ah, yes. That's the young man
who was preparing lobster.
He acted like a different person
when he was cooking earlier.
[KODA]
Ohhh! The contrast of the
fiery red of the lobster
against the bright yellow of the
saffron rice is quite beautiful.
And it's been expertly treated
so that the legs and the
antennae pose no danger.
How thoughtful.
This presentation has a
grace and refinement to it.
It's difficult to find
this outside of the fine
dining experience.
Yeah. Several restaurants
serve lobster curry within
their repertoire.
A seafood curry is nothing
special to write home about.
(Gasp)
Forest...
Deep forest...
What is this?
What is this aroma?
Whoa! That's the first time
she's taken a second bite!
[SCHOOLGIRL]
It must be pretty incredible!
[SCHOOLBOY]
I know, right?!
(Sligh moan)
[YUA]
The A‐Block Competition
continues.
Ryo Kurokiba's lobster dish
is currently being tasted.
(Moaning)
Aaahhhh...
The sauce is americaine,
but its origin is French.
It's rich with fish stock
and butter, and it also has
savory vegetables.
But the core of this deep,
woody fragrance...
it actually seems to be
coming from...
Cognac!
That's a top‐quality brandy.
It's made in the region around
the western French city of
Cognac, correct?
Smells enticing!
Brandy is infused with
the scent of wooden casks
when left to age
creating this aroma.
That would explain
why this curry dish...
has such a rich fragrance
of cedar and sandalwood
emitting from it.
You are correct in that.
However, I used a top‐shelf
Napoleon cognac.
This was to deepen the scent
of the curry and bring out the
pureness of the others flavors.
To think, the aroma of cognac
could enhance curry so greatly!
This is the perfect accentuation
to French lobster curry!
This is the first time the
judges have reacted!
That guy's curry must be
some kind of amazing!
[ALICE]
It's been a while, Erina.
Let me introduce you.
I have my very own aide now.
You have an aide?
I do! I found him
in Northern Europe.
So he's like some
kind of pet puppy?
No! Okay, be a
good boy and speak.
Hey.
Well he must be
skilled enough
for Alice to have
put her trust in him.
Well. It's about time our
dishes start to receive a
proper judgment.
Yeah, okay.
But is that really it?
Seems like there should be more
to the dish.
[NATSUME]
Um, well, it wasn't a bad dish.
I may actually give it a score.
Your score will be‐
Hmm...
Huh? Oh... Just a sec...
Oh, there it is...
Huh?
Not just yet!
It's still too soon for
you to stop eatin'!
Um, was it really necessary
to go through all that?
Well...
What're these for?
It would seem that these are
filled with cognac as well.
There's still a part of the dish
you haven't enjoyed yet.
The tomalley nestled deep inside
the lobster head!
You must take this dropper,
put a couple of drops into the
shell and then slurp it up.
That's the most satisfying
way to eat this dish.
You want me to "slurp it"?
How could you even suggest
we do something so vulgar?
At least serve it once
you've split the shell.
Why are you holding back,
my dear?
Excuse me?
I can tell by just
looking at you.
I can see your true colors.
The truth is you want
to scarf it down right now
in all of its
dirty glory!
Once you've swallowed the
tomalley with the cognac,
try stuffing your mouths with
the roux and saffron rice again.
It'll be so sinfully delicious
it'll make what you just
ate look like nothing.
More delicious?
(Slurping)
The delicious seafood flavor
explodes in your mouth,
blending with the rich,
woody aroma!
So... sensual...
My consciousness...
It's flying away!
(Cosmic moans)
[YUA]
Ryo Kurokiba scores 93 points!
[SCHOOLBOY 1] Awesome!
[SCHOOLBOY 2] He totally
just took the lead!
[SCHOOLGIRL]
I don't believe it!
[SCHOOLBOY 3]
93 points?!
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
I thought for sure
Akira would sweep A‐Block!
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
No joke!
He just came outta nowhere!
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
This guy is one heck
of a dark horse!
[SCHOOLBOY 3]
This really shakes things up!
For as long as
I can remember,
I have been endlessly
driving toward this fate...
to fight on the Food War stage!
(Bar revelry)
This academy is
a disappointment!
[SCHOOLGIRL]
Can you believe that score?!
[SCHOOLBOY]
How could someone just come
in and jump that far ahead?
[RYO]
Well, that's that.
They gave
him a 93?
Heh! That was a grand
surprise, wasn't it?
At his young age,
70 or 80 points
should've been the most he could
have gotten in this competition.
Th‐that completely
blindsided me.
I never expected such
an incredible dish!
I need to calm down.
Will, the, uh, next contestant
please come forward now?
Ooh!
Wait, this is...
Go ahead and eat
it up, everyone.
Allow me to present
to you my curry dish...
Dongpo pork curry bowl!
Dongpo pork...
It's pork belly simmered
in soy sauce
and other delectable
ingredients.
Just look! The sultriness
of this ravishing meat!
It's glistening
with juices!
The pork belly has been cut
so that it has three
distinct layers,
alternating between
lean meat and fatty meat.
What's most notable is
the dish wobbles simply by
tapping the bowl gently.
It takes an incredible
sense of temperature
control to achieve that!
In some regions this
masterpiece is lovingly
called "Three‐layer meat."
(Sniff)
We are now entering
the realm of the senses.
My tongue is rejoicing before
I've even taken a bite!
It looks like her
dish has made a good
impression on them.
Thatta way to take it
to 'em, Meat‐Meat!
That is awesome, Meat‐Meat!
The meat has been cut
into thick cubes,
and it has most certainly
absorbed the umami of the soup!
I want to grab that meat and
tear a big ol' bite into it!
I can't even imagine what
it would taste like.
Uh! W‐wait a moment...
I still haven't recovered
from the shock of that
lobster curry.
To have it followed up
by a dish like this...
What's the matter?
Take yourself a great
big bite of meat.
Taste the pleasure of the
highest‐quality pork around.
Mpphh!
MEAT!
AAAHHHH!
The moment you bite into it,
the pork's juices spill
out like an untamed waterfall
of velvety smoothness!
The distinctive smell
of pork belly skin
is masked by the aroma
of the spices...
So that the tongue is
hit by the sweetness of the
fat and richness of the curry.
It's a mind‐scrambler!
I parboiled the shank,
pan‐frying the surface to a
savory finish.
Simmering it in soy
and oyster sauce, Shaoshing rice
wine and other flavors.
My aromatic spices were a blend
of star anise, a little ginger,
and Sichuan pepper.
But I don't get it.
The pork is cut so thick!
Why is it so easy to eat
with a mere spoon?
I see! It's all in the rice!
The rice has been mixed with
a little bit of rock salt,
and teng jiao
you flavoring oil!
The numbing sensation and
refreshing scent of ten jiao you
makes this oil set
one's heart to racing!
It makes you crave the sweetness
of the fat, which allows
the cycle to continue.
This bowl dish has
created a chain of vicious,
delicious wickedness!
Um, okay guys, there are
still other dishes needing
to be judged,
so please eat
in moderation, please.
I don't think so!
You want us to eat
in moderation?!
Talk all you want, but there's
no way I'm not finishing this!
Ikumi Mito...
When she entered Tohtsuki,
she had a sense for meat‐based
cuisine far above ze others,
but her attention toward other
ingredients was lacking.
However, her cooking has
clearly evolved.
[KODA]
The fat and the smoothness of
the curry make a harmonious
combination.
Aaahhh! Such a glorious
sense of euphoria!
[MINATOZAKA]
There's no better way
of properly tasting this dish
without a skin‐on pork belly.
The destructive force of
this dish is proof enough!
She's truly
the Meat Master!
No, she's more
than that...
Oh, meat!
She's The Meat General!
Thick juicy meat!
[YUA]
Ikumi Mito scores 86 points!
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
There it is!
She's in the running!
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
She went straight to 2nd place!
Damn it! I wasn't even able
to get up to 90 points.
Meat‐Meat! That looked
SO amazing! You got me
wanting to try it.
Well, you kinda gave
me a helping hand with
the idea for it.
Huh?
Rice bowls should be
a meal summarized
in one bowl, right?
Haha! You really
get it, huh?
[KANICHI]
WAAAHHH! Meat‐Meat,
you're the meatiest!
Oh my gosh, thank goodness!
At least it's finally become
more of a competition.
Let's keep things
moving forward!
Next up is Ryoko Sakaki.
I hope you enjoy my dish...
This is everything
I have to offer.
This one looks kinda normal
compared to all the others.
It certainly doesn't
have much impact compared
to that last dish.
Alright this could either be
an Indian dal or a bean curry.
It's very similar to
Indian channa masala.
But why is it so thick?
Because it's natto!
Stickiness and umami
intertwine on the tongue!
Has natto ever been
this delectable?
It can't be...
this is no normal natto.
Now don't tell me
this is actually‐
[RYOKO]
It's natto that was
finished on coals.
In other words,
it's char‐fired natto.
I kept charcoal burning
in the basement,
preserving the optimal
temperature and humidity.
Then I spread the natto
spores over soybeans,
fermenting them over
dozens of hours.
I nurtured it over the course
of the summer vacation.
She used charcoal to
slowly age the natto,
and by doing so, she made
the flavor especially strong.
Because that doesn't kill
the bacteria, it keeps natto's
ammonia odor in check.
But that's not all!
There's something else in there.
What is this umami that
reverberates on the tongue
like a deep bass?
I added soy sauce koji
to help bring out more flavor.
Soy sauce koji?!
Soy sauce mixed with
malted rice.
Then it's fermented at room
temperature for weeks to make
a flavoring agent.
Okay then.
So that black stuff
she's been carrying around
is soy sauce koji!
And that sticky stuff
was the natto!
Soy sauce koji's umami
component, glutamic acid,
is more than ten times stronger
than that of salt koji!
So zat's how she was able
to increase ze flavor
without it being overpowered
by ze strength of ze curry.
A splendid dish, one making use
of the secrets of fermentation.
Thick Japanese‐style curry...
It's so well suited to the
stickiness of the natto!
The generous topping of
diced green onions is
exquisite as well!
It perfectly brings together
the power of the soybeans.
I want to call this girl
"Big Sis"...
No, I shall refer to her as,
"Elder Sister"!
[STUDENTS and JUDGES]
Soy! Soy! Soy! Soy!
[YUA]
Ryoko Sakaki gets 86 points!
She is now tied with Ikumi Mito!
Way to stick it
to the man, Ryoko!
You're moving up
to 2nd place!
[SOMA]
Hey, Ryoko, you make some
pretty interesting stuff.
Let me have some
of that next time!
Okay. Sure thing!
Things are heating up!
Who's up next?
Oh jeez, it's him?
[ZENJI]
I guess most of the people
at this venue don't expect
much of me.
Come on, Zenji!
You GOT this!
Do it to it!
Zenji... Good luck!
Time to get real.
I'm about to stir
things up a bit.
Okay, go ahead.
Uh... Um... Uh!
Just calm down.
I'm Madoka Enomoto!
I'm in the Miyazato Seminar
group along with Zenji!
Zenji Marui!
Next contestant
is Zenji Marui!
Please present your‐ Uh!
It's white!
The roux, the ingredients,
everything is white!
[KODA]
These are udon noodles,
and they're infused with cumin.
In other words,
it's a curry udon done in your
own unique style, correct?
Yes sir. It's a
white pottage curry udon.
Interesting. It is
quite a beautiful‐looking
dish to behold.
If Ryo's dish was a kaleidoscope
of bright and shining colors,
that would make this a
spring that has fallen silent.
Well, then...
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
I bet it won't
get a great score.
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
That Zenji guy practically
collapsed at the training camp.
Hm!
(Slurps and yummy grunts)
Um, hello there?
Would someone care to comment on
the present dish at this time?
Uh, hello?
Hey! Please don't
ignore me, you guys!
[SCHOOLBOY]
Look! They totally
can't stop eating it!
A soft poached egg,
creamy mashed potatoes,
and melted cheese...
On top of all that
decadent goodness,
sits a delicate roux in the
style of a truly classic
vichyssoise!
Yes. Vichyssoise soup:
It's a chilled pottage
made mostly from potatoes,
pureed leaks, and fresh cream.
It is said to have been created
back in 1917 by a man
named Louis Diat,
head chef at ze luxurious
Ritz‐Carlton hotel.
It looks quite creamy and
heavy,
but the chopsticks are
able to move through it
with such delicate ease.
That would be because of the
supremely lightweight noodles
and coriander powder.
A mellowness reminiscent of
citrus fruits and select spices
that give it a hint of heat.
They're a perfect match for
the cumin‐infused noodles,
with each complementing
each other!
Such unbelievable pleasure!
I used dill as a
cornerstone ingredient
to top the Vichyssoise.
I combined that with the
dill's seeds and seedlings
in a pan roast.
Creating an extremely
aromatic soup.
How did you come up with
something resembling
modern tsukemen
based on the vichyssoise
of over 100 years ago?!
This is a splendid dish!
Zenji!
Way to go, my homie!
Oh, Zenji!
Uh‐huh. This is the
greatest venue possible
for Zenji to show off his
wonderful talent.
[MIYAZATO]
Miyamoto Seminars researches
and analyzes classic literature
regarding fine dining.
Even though he's a freshman,
Zenji could be considered
an ace among my students.
[ZENJI]
My cooking sense is
nothing remarkable.
Also, I'm weaker than
the average person.
That's exactly why I set
out to acquire knowledge:
so that an average guy like me
could devour the geniuses!
This is why we call
our little Zenji:
the Great Professor of Taste!
[YUA]
Zenji Marui gets 88 points!
He easily takes the
2nd‐place spot!
(Cheering)
Way to go, Zenji!
Awesome, buddy!
Ahh!
Look Professor!
Professor, please look!
Zenji's in 2nd place
right now! (Giggles)
Yes, yes. I know Madoka.
And the high scores
keep on coming.
We're on a roll! But can
this momentum keep going?
Next up is Shun Ibusaki‐ Aahh!
Judging solely by the
strong aroma...
this might be the most
powerful dish yet!
[SHUN]
This is my special
smoked curry.
Please, take a bite.
[SATO]
The toppings are smoked bacon,
smoked potato,
and smoked egg?!
You can't go around
just smoking anything
and everything!
I mean, come on!
But it smells delicious!
In the end, the theme is CURRY.
This reckless smoking seems
like he's out to destroy the
aroma of the spices.
(Smoky squeals)
The spices in play are:
ground cinnamon, ground cumin,
cardamom‐and‐clove,
mixed into a heady blend.
He also added apple
bits that were slowly
cooked over smoke chips.
I see! That's how he managed to
elevate the flavor of the spices
instead of overpowering them!
Yes! These smoke chips
are the optimal way
to make use of the
coarse‐ground spices.
Prior to them being smoked,
the spices were cured
in a Saumur.
Giving a solid curry flavor.
Even from just the toppings,
you'll experience
a distinct taste.
Your choice of toppings
are excellent.
The egg really locks
in the umami flavor!
Being soft‐boiled, the yolk is
perfectly viscous and oozes out!
But wait, how was he
able to do that?
All the ingredients have
stayed perfectly aligned.
How did he get them to stay
so cohesive without shifting?
Ahhh!
That's it! I get it now!
The salt that he added
to the spices has also
been regaled in smoke!
How does one go
about smoking salt?!
But wouldn't that change the
flavor of the curry in the dish?
[SHUN]
By the way, rather than ordinary
salt, I used seaweed salt.
Seaweed, which contains
a lot of sodium,
is dried and then
dissolved in water.
The top layer is scooped out
and boiled to create salt.
That's what gives it such
a rounded, mellow flavor.
He was able to harmonize the
curry using smoked salt!
[KODA]
A formidable young
man, indeed.
He had an idea of showcasing
the flavors smoking can
produce,
and it was
perfectly realized.
[MINATOZAKA]
Though young, he is
able to manipulate
smoking techniques
with precision!
[MINATOZAKA]
Young man, you are...
The Prince of Smoke!
[YUA]
88 points!
Shun Ibusaki is
now tied for 2nd!
Wow, both of these guys
are something else!
I've never seen a tie
quite like this!
You've finally
shown people your true
colors, haven't you?
Oh yeah? Like
you're the one to
be pointing fingers.
You've been the
secretive type since
I've known you.
Maybe a little.
(Whimpering)
[SCHOOLBOY]
Ms. Natsume is starting to look
a little weak in
the knees down there.
That's awesome!
Three of the top
five finalists
are representing
Kyosukei, dude!
Whoa... Wait,
hold on a second.
Only four can move on
to the finals, right?
But what about if
the scores are tied?
If this order remains unchanged
by the tournament's conclusion,
the five judges must
cast run‐off ballots
to break the tie.
However...
Ah. Ze judges are still
holding back, eh?
[YUA]
The next contestant
is Akira Hayama!
(Cheers)
Don't worry, Soma,
I made enough curry
for you to try as well.
Oh! Well, what
a coincidence.
I did the same.
So we'll taste
and compare, then?
Let's do it.
[OWNER]
Here you go. Thanks!
Huh? Um, this is not really
what I was looking for‐
Yeah well it's yours,
now get lost.
I'm busy over here,
little girl.
[JUN]
Huh? But...
(Sniff)
That spice is
only about 30% pure.
Huh?
It's mixed with
an inferior product
with a weak aroma.
Look here, you little
garbage boy...
You don't know what you're
talking about alright‐
Oh, I know alright.
I happen to have a very
special sense of smell.
Are you Chinese?
No, you're Japanese,
aren't you?
Huh?
This is no place
for little kids
to come sight‐seeing.
Um, well, I'm 26,
so, uh...
Huh?!
Akira Hayama has been named
a candidate to win this
year's Selection!
Finally, it's his turn!
His dish would appear to be a
fish‐head curry.
It's a marvelous dish
wherein the entire head
is used in order to‐
Huh?
What's this?
What's happening?
This looks so small!
This isn't a fish‐head
curry at all.
This dough covering the
ramekin, acting as a lid...
It's naan, isn't it?
Use your spoon and
push the naan inside
the ramekin while you eat.
It's still hot,
so be careful.
(Swift explosion)
The aroma!
It's like an explosion!
[SOMA]
Next time, on the twenty‐fourth
and final course of Food Wars...
"The Warriors' Banquet"
Order up!
[SOMA]
Ah, uh...
You're welcome!