[KOJIRO]
I am the Master Chef here!
You do not have the authority to
try to question my decisions.
I cannot allow some peon
to butcher my dish.
[KOJIRO]
Megumi Tadokoro...
You're out.
(Grunt)
I'm challenging you.
If I beat you in a
Food War challenge,
will you take back your
decision to expel Megumi?
A Food War?
Ha! That brings back memories.
What is that
idiot transfer
student thinking?
He's going up against
a graduate, a former
seat No. 1 at that!
Totally, and Chef Shinomiya is
a beast who fights on the front
lines of the culinary world!
A Food War against
a graduate chef.
It's not unheard of,
but a Food War requires the
consent of both parties.
Correct?
Sorry, I'm in no mood to
take on a challenge.
You can carry on all you want,
but Megumi Tadokoro's
expulsion is going to‐
[GIN]
Easy now, don't be so hasty.
It looks like things have
gotten rather exciting,
haven't they?
Oh!
Chef Dojima.
(Whimper)
(Opening Song)
[GIN]
Hmm. I see.
Oh! Her dish is so well done.
How can you not agree with that?
Something like this totally
deserves a passing grade.
Kojiro, why are you
so stubborn?!
You are a pig‐headed fool!
And a complete narcissist!
A show‐off dum dum!
Shut your mouth, Hinako.
I‐I‐I‐I'm sorry.
(Pained groans)
[HINAKO] He's a meanie...
[KOJIRO] Chef Dojima,
this challenge was supposed
to have been left only to me.
[GIN]
Of course, Kojiro.
I have no qualms with the
parameters of your test
or your criteria for judgment.
But at the very least,
this girl tried to cope
with the situation at hand.
Don't you believe that
her grit leaves some
room for consideration?
No, I do not.
Not in the slightest.
Well I think it DOES
leave some room!
Well, looks like there's
no way of avoiding it,
we have too many votes.
These guys...
It is decided.
I will manage this
unofficial Food War.
Or, rather, this offsite match.
Huh?
[GIN]
However, we cannot disrupt
the training camp's
programming...
so you two will battle
against Kojiro
once the afternoon's
challenges have concluded.
[KOJIRO]
Hold on...
Now wait just a minute!
Why do I have to take
part in this‐
Because, Kojiro... I said so.
Uggh...
Aggh...
Very well then.
I will go along with this
whimsical idea of yours.
Okay, Soma,
if you win, I'll take
back her expulsion.
However...
If you lose, you and Megumi
will both be sent home.
[GIN]
Then, it's settled.
I invite you to the basement
of the hotel annex this evening.
You two will show
me what you've got.
Uh...
Well... we just might
be able to turn this
thing around, won't we?
But first things first,
we need to take care of business
at the afternoon challenge.
(Angry squeal)
Gah!
Soma, you idiot!
Why would you go and
confront him like that?!
I don't believe you!
You already passed
the stupid test!
(Sobbing)
Come on, Soma, just let
me fail on my own...
(Crying)
Megumi...
I can't let you fail
on your own, you'll mess
that up too! (Laugh)
Do you have to make
fun of me right now?!
Come on, get up.
We don't want to be late
for the afternoon challenge.
You're always
helping me.
And now I've gotten
you involved in THIS.
How can I...
How can I ever
make it up to you?
There's no need.
I did this because I wanted to.
You don't owe me
anything, m'kay?
Also, the reason I challenged
him should be obvious.
[SOMA]
Megumi, this journey was not
meant to end for you here.
[RYOKO]
Well?
[YUKI]
Nothing. She wasn't
in her room, either.
She's not answering
her phone.
This is not like her.
I wonder if something bad
happened in class.
All teams should've
finished their afternoon
challenges by now.
Don't tell me...
Her name wasn't on the list
of those who failed today.
Why don't we ask
someone who was in
the same challenge?
Oh, yeah! Soma
would've been
with her, right?
Where is he anyway?
Yeah, I haven't
seen that
dude either.
Huh...
Let's see here...
Those two started
a Food War
when they were
involved with Bowl‐club.
Actually, Soma was
responsible for that.
[ALL]
I've got a bad
feeling about this!
Heh, heh, heh, heh, heh...
[GIN]
Tohtsuki Resort's hotel annex
won't be used in this year's
training camp.
So here, in the 1st‐floor
basement kitchen...
...there will be no
distractions.
Huh?!
So, um, why are all these
graduates in here with us?
They've come here to
act as our judges.
(Groans)
[GIN]
Hinako's judgment would seem to
be rather biased, however.
An unofficial Food War right in
the middle of training camp.
On top of that, a graduate
vs. a freshman student...
I wonder what Mr. Chapelle
would think about this.
He'd tear us a new one.
Not in the good way.
If he found out,
I'd make a run for it.
And blame everything
on Kojiro.
Uh, I can hear you, Mizuhara!
May I have everyone's attention.
We'll now begin
our offsite match.
You'll use these leftover
vegetables to make your
dishes for the challenge.
You're free to make
whatever you like,
but have vegetables
be the main component.
Time limit is set at two hours.
[MEGUMI]
I'm the one who caused
this Food War...
There's no way I can let Soma
get expelled because of me!
I have to at least make sure
I don't hold him back!
Also, there will be
one more condition...
Megumi Tadokoro...
you will be the lead chef.
Uhn!
Huh?!
You'll decide the
recipe on your own.
Soma, you'll act as
sous‐chef and support her.
Gah!
This Food War...
will now begin!
AHHHHH!
Chef Dojima!
I am the one who
wanted this Food War!
So why would I not
be the one to‐
I brought together a
challenge that otherwise
would never have happened.
You will accept the
conditions I've set.
I know but, sir‐!
Soma!
Let's say Megumi survives
thanks to YOUR cooking.
What merit is
there in that?
It does nothing to
show us what she's got.
(Gasp)
[GIN]
Sooner or later,
she will just end up failing
some other challenge.
She cannot continue
to rely on you.
At Tohtsuki Academy,
you must show your worth
by your own hands.
You must prove if you
should remain here.
And prove it yourself.
Tonight, right now,
at this cooking station...
Megumi,
YOU are the chef.
[KOJIRO]
Chef Dojima...
I've already decided
what I'll make.
Would it be okay
with you if I begin?
[GIN]
Yes, feel free.
Heh.
Huh?
(Whimpering)
[KOJIRO]
Hmph! I kinda feel
bad for you, kid.
How so?
You have the world
crashing down on you.
And your fate is resting
solely in the hands
of a petrified dimwit.
(Groan)
Can you believe what
that wretched man
just said about her?
Kojiro Shinomiya
is a horrible person.
And that's precisely why
he's never been able
to keep a girl
for very long.
Shut up over there!
Hinako, when did you
get out of your ropes?
Good luck,
my tiny sweet Megumi!
Don't you listen to that
arrogant horse's ass!
[KOJIRO]
Shut up!
[MEGUMI]
Chef Kojiro Shinomiya...
After graduating from Tohtsuki,
he went to France on his own
and opened up a
restaurant in Paris,
the fiercest battleground
for fine dining.
How am I to fight a man
like that with MY recipe?
I have to calm down.
I have to be brave...
But I...
I'm drawing a blank.
I can't stop shaking.
I can't think of anything.
Ah! Megumi!
Incidentally...
you will not be
helping her with
her recipe either.
You are nothing more
than her sous‐chef.
Got it? She's the
one in charge.
[GIN]
You thought Megumi was worthy
of moving on, didn't you?
If you're saying you don't
really believe that...
Then you should leave now...
Withdraw from the challenge.
I'm not going to do that,
because I am a chef.
A proper chef would never run
away from the kitchen.
Hmph!
(Heavy breathing)
It's happening,
just like always.
I'm blanking.
I can't do it!
I've only made it this far
because of Soma.
[SOMA]
Hey, Megumi...
I'm just...
Put your hands together.
Your hands! Do it!
Ah!
Uh.
Huh?
That really hurt...
[SOMA]
I learned that
from back home.
It's how I was taught
to get my mind right.
The only drawback is you
can't do it by yourself.
Ah!
It stings, But...
I stopped shaking.
The first thing you need
to do is just calm down.
Then focus only on
what you want to make.
But...
But Chef Shinomiya's
going to make French
cuisine.
He's a master.
If I don't make something
special to beat that...
you're going to
get expelled, Soma!
[SOMA]
It's like my
dad said...
Huh?
"Cooking is about taking
everything that is in
your heart and soul
and putting onto a plate."
[SOMA]
So for now,
you need to forget
about what the other
guy's making.
Yes but...
But my cooking is just‐
That onigiri of yours
I ate out in the fields...
It was incredible.
[SOMA]
Don't overthink this.
Just make the kind of food
YOU would want to eat.
That'll be enough.
The kind of food that I'D eat?
[KOJIRO]
Well, this is... interesting.
She hasn't even bothered to
start cooking anything yet.
Your little friend isn't
really all there, is she?
Why don't you wait till AFTER
you've tasted her food
before talking trash about her?
Hmph!
Soma!
Yeah?
I'm ready... I've decided!
I know what I'm making.
[HINAKO]
What are you
doing, Kojiro?!
This is abuse!
Untie me! Untie me!
[KOJIRO]
If you don't shut
your trap right now,
I am going to
tape your mouth shut!
Oh, well at least
something worked.
[YUKI]
He challenged a graduate
to a Food War?!
Uh‐huh. That's totally
what a guy in their
class said.
But why?! How did
things come to that?
It looks like Megumi
was going to be chopped,
so Soma stepped in.
They were gonna
expel her?!
Oh, no!
[YUKI]
I can't deal with this!
(Sobbing)
[RYOKO]
Yuki, calm down.
[MEGUMI]
So, that's the dish
I thought I'd make.
Hmph!
Interesting!
Uh? Really?
You like it?
That's great!
Oh, um, but the
ingredients...
There will need to be
a lot of prep work
and it will have to
be done very quickly.
I don't know if we
can pull it off...
Hey hey! Who do
you think I am?
(Swish)
I am the number‐two guy at the
"Japanese Eatery Yukihira"!
Well it's really just the two of
us, y'know, me and my dad.
(Laughs)
I'm gonna support you with
everything I know! Okay!
For one day only,
"Eatery Megumi Tadokoro",
is open!
Woo! Yeah!
[SOMA]
All right, Chef Megumi!
You ready to do this?
I am!
[MEGUMI]
I'll do the tomatoes.
Soma, you prep the
rest of the ingredients.
[SOMA]
Got it!
[HINAKO]
Oh, Chef Kojiro!
What do you want, Hinako?
A Japanese eatery
is a dokoro,
and her name
is Tadokoro,
It kinda has a nice
restaraunty ring
to it, doesn't it?
Erk! Somebody get
her out of here!
(Screaming)
Oh, come on!
If I think about trying to
beat Chef Kojiro Shinomiya,
I'll get all worked up
and even more nervous.
I just have to concentrate
on my own cooking.
Because right now,
I'm the chef!
WAAHH!
I should've cut the
shoulder first thing!
Now the whole cooking order
is going to be off!
Here are the cuts.
I've removed all
the connective tissue.
So, should I get on the chicken
liver or the backfat next?
U‐um, the liver, if you don't
mind. That would be great.
[SOMA]
Comin' up!
Hey, Soma! How's the bake mold
coming along over there?
All done. I just need
to add in the paté.
I'll be finished with
the sautéed vegetables
in about 12 seconds.
Uh! Thanks so much!
Incredible!
He keeps turning out
the pre‐prepped ingredients
exactly when I need them.
This the consistency
you're looking for?
Mm‐hmm!
Even though he's the only
one person supporting me...
my cooking speed
is so much faster!
I can't believe how
quick we're moving.
Are you seeing this?
He's supporting her
by anticipating what
she'll be doing next,
thus making sure that
the two of them are
working on the same page.
What's more, he only
focuses on what's needed.
He's not in Megumi's way,
he's showing a great
deal of sensitivity.
[SEKIMORI]
Who is he again?
Soma Yukihira?
Ah yes, this year's
sole transfer student.
He works at
a local diner.
It seems he's built his body
of knowledge on the job.
Still, he wouldn't have moves
like that just by helping
at the family restaurant.
No matter how you look at it,
his skills are far beyond those
of most Tohtsuki's students.
All right, everyone,
prepare your dishes!
We need to begin
plating, Soma!
Gotcha!
(Tick)
[GIN]
Now then, we'll
start the judging.
We'll start with Kojiro.
Present your dish!
[MEGUIMI]
The cooking of a top graduate
from Tohtsuki Academy...
I'm sure we're going to see
something pretty special.
Man, I've been looking
forward to this.
Yes.
Hmm...
Huh?
[GOTODA]
A chou farci!
This is quite an unexpected
surprise from you.
It's a local dish of the
Auvergne region.
[SEKIMORI]
Meat and vegetables
are minced and stuffed
into cabbage leaves
which are rolled and steamed.
Similar to the cabbage rolls
of many other cuisines.
It's a staple of local cooking,
most often prepared
in French households.
This must be kind of a let down
for him, don't you think?
Kojiro usually only makes
pretentious food, but this‐ OH!
Wait a minute...
Don't I get a
serving as well?
You don't get one.
You can share
with Mizuhara.
[GOTODA]
Well then...
Oh my goodness!
The aroma of the herbs
simply whets the appetite!
Ah!
(Squealing)
Ahhhh!
This... is... magnifique!!
Um...
this filling...
It isn't the pork roast
and onions used in a
normal chou farci.
It's a farci made
from local duck!
He sliced the breast meat open
and stuffed with morel
mushrooms, asparagus,
and foie gras,
all sautéed in beef fat to give
them depth of flavor.
What's more, the breast meat,
butter, and cream were
blended into a mousse,
inserted and then steamed!
AhHhH!
This mousse lingers
on the tongue.
And then everything dissolves,
and the rich flavors spread
throughout the mouth.
It's so delicate.
What I find most
impressive about this,
is the type of cabbage
that surrounds it.
Savoy cabbage:
This ingredient, called
chirimen cabbage in Japan,
has a strong grassy
scent when raw,
but when cooked, it takes
on a sublime sweetness.
Blanchir...
Blanching.
Vapeur...
Steaming.
This was cooked using
various processes,
each the perfect
complement to the
highlights of the dish.
The result is a delicate
sweetness that elevates the
flavors of everything else.
It's as if a spell had
been cast on it.
[GIN]
As soon as he graduated from
Tohtsuki, Kojiro went to
France, alone...
And after a few years honing
his skills, he opened a
restaurant in Paris,
becoming an chef owner.
While French cuisine tends to
emphasize meat dishes,
Kojiro's cooking cast a new
light on legumes.
He paved new ground...
and created a shockwave
to gourmands throughout
the country.
In time, the Parisian
connoisseurs of haute cuisine
came to respect the chef
who had come from Japan.
And they began to call him...
The Legume Magician!
He is the worst! I hate him...
But it IS delicious!
His heightened creativity has
transformed what is a simple
regional dish.
He's elevated it to where
it could be served in a
fine dining establishment.
The duck mousse dissolves
in the mouth,
and the sweetness of the
cabbage that surrounds it...
Uhh! it embraces the palate,
and then the entire body!
It's as if a kind of flavor
sorcery has possessed the
tongue and freed the soul!
This is...
...magic!
Yes...
Indeed!
[GIN]
It is the work of the Magician
that Came From the East...
[ALL]
Legume Magic!
Cabbage Red!
Ahahah!
Cabbage Blue!
Uh!
CABBAGE PINK!
Yes!
[ALL]
Magical Cabbage!
[SEKIMORI]
Magic, magic, magic, MAGIC!
(Ending Song)
Ahh... I feel
so satisfied!
That's our little Kojiro!
[SEKIMORI]
Indeed. The work of
the Legume Magician.
Well, what about you, Mizuhara?
Did it meet your approval?
Oh dear God.
If I could just make myself
forget it was you who made it
then it would be perfect.
Aw... well I do
apologize for that.
That was rather unexpected,
Kojiro. I must say.
I thought for sure we would be
getting one of the specialties
from your restaurant in Paris.
Hm! Oh, come on, Chef Dojima,
that would be just cruel.
I mean, I'm going up
against mere students.
Don't you think that being
in my presence is already
humiliating enough
for these poor dumb bastards?
How modest of him.
I might just have
to beat him so hard
he will never be
able to cook again.
This up‐and‐coming chef
opened his own restaurant
in the best district of
Paris, the battleground
of fine dining,
and has continued to
wage culinary war.
He has an overwhelming
sense of pride,
that he could never lose to a
student.
But if anyone were up
for the challenge...
[GIN]
Megumi. Soma. Your turn.
Yes, Sir!
Um. Thank you.
This is it...
It's time for our food
to be judged.
You ready to go, Megumi?
Unh?
[SOMA]
Megumi?
I made this food using
everything I had.
To offer it up for
someone to judge...
It's just...
It's just so daunting!
What will they say?
What if they don't like it?
What if they say it's awful?!
Even WITH Soma's help!
Ah! Uh! Waaahhh!
It'll be okay.
Go on.
Hm?
Ohh...
Look at this...
(Gasp)
[HINAKO]
A terrine!
[KOJIRO]
Next time on Food Wars,
the twelfth course!
"The Memory of a Single Dish"
You are all expelled.
[HINAKO]
Yes!
[ALL]
Magical Cabbage!
[GIN]
Woo!