[NARRATOR]
Fried chicken...
With rising plumes of steam...
and spices that tickle
the nose...
The plump texture of the meat...
and the hot juices that
run down one's chin...
This is the comfort food that
continues to grace Japanese
tables everywhere.
And now, the decisive battle
over it, one fought with knives
and skewers, is about to begin.
Sumire‐dori Shopping District‐
the Summer Battle
for Fried Chicken!
[SOMA]
Let's go check out the enemy!
(Obnoxious laugh)
I mean, it's not like YOU
could ever make something
this delicious.
[SOMA]
What would you say if
our shopping area can make a
fried chicken more delicious
than yours...
Mozuya would be
totally disgraced!
You sure do talk a big
game there, little boy.
But talking's a lot easier
than cooking, isn't it?
What are you
gonna do, punk?
What is the ideal way for
someone to eat fried chicken?
Uhh...
Well it's gotta be when
it's piping hot fresh
right out of the fryer,
of course‐
That's right!
But you see,
Mozuya's dishes don't
necessarily represent that.
Huh? Meaning what exactly?
The takeout boxes that they send
home with their customers
are closed off in order
to keep the heat from escaping.
Those are made assuming
they'll be eaten when
the customer gets home
and not right away when they're
bought at the franchise.
Their customers aren't
opening them up and eating them
in the middle of the station.
Makes sense.
There's no food court
area at the station,
so the only option
they have is takeout.
However, our shopping area
doesn't have that mentality!
After all, that's one of
the reasons you come here,
to snack and walk around.
Chomping down on fresh
hot fried goodness...
And that, my friends, is when
fried chicken is at its best!
Plus we've got plenty
of starving school kids
that need something quick,
easy, and portable.
That's brilliant!
We don't have to fight
on their terms at all.
We will offer fresh hot,
ready‐made food for takeout.
We can use this location
to its full advantage!
Exactly right!
The keyword is...
"Fried chicken for
eating and walking"!
I'm feeling pretty good
about our chances.
Yeah!
[TOMITA]
Woohoo! YEAH!
WOOOOOOHOO! Now you
got me all fired up!
I'm on it! I'm going to make a
new exciting dish as well!
Huh?
'Cause after all,
I am a lunchtime expert.
With everyone's help,
we'll take those suckers down!
All right, people!
Let's do this thang!
Yeah, good luck with
that, Mr. Tomita.
[KINU]
The All‐Japan Fried Chicken
Championship!
We've won the gold medal
three years in a row, folks.
Because we're Mozuya!
Step on up and get
yourself the best‐fried
chicken in all the land!
Um, excuse me, Miss Kinu.
We've received the invoice from
the consultant for this month.
[KINU]
Maybe I should just be done with
that four‐eyed dweeb for good.
I can't keep paying all
his ridiculous fees anyway.
Are you okay, Ma'am?
Nothing that
concerns you!
As long as Mozuya has its
secret marinade, we're all set.
True, we are now set up in this
impregnable chicken fortress
thanks to that dork...
But this fortress is now mine!
All right! Let's get ready
for another day
of sucking the delicious
dinero out of the city!
Mwahahaha!
[SOMA]
A package so you
can eat it on the spot.
Then add some toothpicks...
Something like this, maybe?
You plan on
reusing milk cartons?
Ohh!
Elementary and
middle‐school kids
seem to like to eat
fried chicken, so...
I've got one flavored
with curry powder
and another with some
gooey grated cheese
melted all over it.
[SOMA]
What do you think?
Delicious!
Both the curry and the cheese
are great! But, uh...
I feel like Mozuya's chicken
was still more satisfying in
taste and texture.
So, um... well...
I don't think this quite
measures up yet.
Oh, alright...
Putting it in a package
and having you eat
it with toothpicks
makes the serving
size feel small.
It pales to the in‐your‐face
meatiness of Mozuya's.
And the flavorings are only
concentrated on the surface.
We've gotta bring out the
quality of the ingredients
throughout.
Ah! What about if we
tried putting the fried
chicken on a stick?
You could eat it with one
hand and not be messy!
Uhhh... chicken‐on‐a‐stick
is a pretty common concept.
It doesn't really
scream that it's
something different.
Oh... Okay...
We need packaging that's not
only new and unique,
BUT will also be able
to draw out more flavors.
There has got to be some idea
out there to solve both problems
at the same time.
Got it!
I've got a bunch of
notebooks
where I wrote
recipes down as a kid.
They're in my room.
He's going to his room?
Soma's room...
Ah! It's just the two of us!
I‐I have to try and say
something! Uh, uh...
U‐um, Ms. Meat!
Whattayou want?!
Um, um... Are...
How are you enjoying
the curriculum so far?
Huh?
Ah! N‐no!
I wanted to ask what
Soma is like at school,
and ended up saying
something that sounds like
it's from a letter from
a middle‐school teacher!
I'm such a hopeless wreck.
Soma please come and save me.
Just relax...
This girl has known Soma
since middle school...
Uh, well...
They're childhood friends?
How are you...
um...
Why am I getting so mad?!
Recover, recover!
Um, you must be incredible
too, Meat‐Meat.
To think, you're in the
strictest cooking school
in all of Japan.
There's nothing
remotely special
about me at all...
It's not really
a big deal.
A lot of worthless
punks go there.
I mean real
good‐for‐nothing bastards
whose level is
nowhere close to mine!
Just thinking about
it makes my blood boil!
I swear, some of 'em are
absolutely worthless!
Get bowled over by
Bowl‐club, baby!
O‐oh...
Still...
Soma's at least... a little
better than most of them.
Sorta...
Oh no!
Please don't tell me
this girl likes Soma?
I have no chance.
Uh! Meat‐Meat!
Oh, sorry! Are you okay
under there, Meat‐Meat?
What the hell are you doing?!
You're such an idiot!
I said I was sorry, okay?
DAMMIT! AAHHHH!
Or maybe I'm just
imagining things...
This is by far the juiciest
of any of them yet!
That's right!
Mozuya uses all breast meat
which is low in calories
and has very little fat content.
True, that does make
it a bit more popular
with the diet crowd,
But if you want the
knockout punch of
fresh‐fried taste...
You've gotta use thigh meat
to get the juices!
[MAYU]
Yes! It's the perfect size
and it's so succulent!
Even at Western fried
chicken places...
drumsticks are by far the most
popular pick with the kids.
So using dark meat will get
the students drooling
and wanting more!
Nice! You ARE
the Meat Master!
Cut it out.
"Meat Master"?
Oh! Because she's
Ms. Meat‐Meat.
We're going to need
a really special marinade
for our chicken.
Let's use a base
of soy sauce and
Ichimi‐pepper seasoning.
And, to get the right
batter, we should try
using some cornstarch.
Ah! Yeah I don't
have any of that.
I can go buy some for us.
Be right back.
[SOMA] Thanks!
We didn't have
anything at first,
but now they're coming up
with idea after idea.
I knew those two were great,
but this is amazing!
[IKUMI]
All right. Looks like our
flavors are now coming together.
Yeah. Now to figure out how we
want people to eat our food.
[TOMITA]
Soma!
What's going on, Mr. Tomita?
With this I needed to sneak
in through the back entrance.
Sneak in?
I've finally discovered it!
The perfect dish for the
concept of walking and eating!
This radical dish captures
all the knowledge of
Tomita‐ya Boxed Lunches!
Here is it! Behold!
A fried chicken onigiri!
People already
sell this, you know?
They make them
in convenience stores.
AhhhhHHHH!
I'm so embarrassed!
Such a waste of space.
I thought it was
a hit for sure...
I mean, fried chicken
and rice is the ultimate
combination. Right?
Something new with impact...
Something easy to carry...
and that elevates the flavor.
You, sir, are a genius,
Mr. Tomita!
Huh? You think so?
Um. No, not that.
But that over there!
It's gonna work!
We can pull this off!
We'll roll this thing out...
Tomorrow night!
[TOMITA]
Hey! Open up!
I need to print
something out, FAST!
[IKUMMI]
Yes, chicken thigh meat.
I need you to get things
ready right away.
Ship it to the Todo Meat Market.
It's in the Sumire‐dori
Shopping District,
I'm gonna it need there
it by 5:00 am.
Hey, what are you drawing
over there, sis?
Ah! I totally need your
help with this, Hiro!
This will be a surprise attack.
Before dinnertime,
when the daily feeding
frenzy is at its peak,
We will invade the
enemy's stronghold...
and there will be no chance for
them to fight back!
[MAYU]
In kindergarten,
Soma started making his
own disgusting lunches
and feeding them to his friends,
making them burst into tears.
Not a lot's changed since then.
[KINU]
Now then...
It'll be dinnertime soon,
when things really get moving.
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
Our club activities
were tough today.
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
I know right.
I was starving and
I still had like
an hour left to go.
What is that?
What are those boys holding?
Is that fried chicken?
No, it couldn't be.
No fried chicken could
possibly make you want to
buy it more than Mozuya!
No worries, no worries.
Welcome! Come and get some!
[KINU]
How about getting some fried
chicken from MozuyaaaaaUhhh?
Huh?
What the hell is going on here?!
What's with all these people
walking around the station,
holding that damn cone
full of crap?!
You, girl, what're our
sales looking like?!
Oh, uh... Well, I e‐mailed you
my report, just like always.
And they were good,
they were solid right?
Actually, Ma'am,
for the past two days,
they've been down about 20%.
Why didn't you tell me?!
You girls are giving
proper customer service,
aren't you?
I've seen you slacking off
with your little "breaks"!
[CUSTOMER]
Excuse me.
Ohh? Yes, yes. Welcome!
Is this the fried chicken place
with the "Sumire Mark" on it?
I‐I believe you mean
the shopping area in
front of the station.
[CUSTOMER]
Oh, really?
[GUY]
The shopping area, huh?
Thanks very much.
Hey, sweetie, should we
get some Mozuya for dinner?
Huh? I wanna eat Sumire
fried chicken!
Works for me.
Let's do it!
[GIRL]
Yaay!
Customers are passing us by!
This is unacceptable!
Ma'am, I think maybe you should
report it to your contact.
I don't need some kid
to help us, you idiot?!
I wanna see what's goin' on
at Sumire‐dori with my own
eyes!
This place was a ghost
town three days ago.
How is this even possible?!
[GUY 1]
I'd like one, please.
[GUY 2]
Oooh me too.
And me!
One for me too, son.
I think I'll take three.
You got it! One minute, please.
I need another batch!
Understood!
Working on it now.
This original marinade is
mainly soy sauce and ichimi
pepper seasoning,
We added big chunks
of thigh meat to soak
throughout the day.
I'm done with the
batter, too!
Fantastic!
Man, this smells so good
I can't stand it!
I wanna eat some now!
Next, we take it from
the oil and let the heat
slowly work its way through...
Then fry it again to make
a crispy exterior.
Finally, we add lettuce
leaves and herbs,
and tuck it in a special,
lightly pan‐fried wrap.
We top that with chili
sauce that uses Thai fish
sauce for a secret surprise,
Finishing with coarse
black pepper...
Order up!
"Sumire Mark
fried chicken roll"!
Whoa! This is stuffed
with so much goodness!
[GIRL]
It's still sizzling!
This looks yummy!
Oh, the meat
is so plump!
[WOMAN]
Some parts are nice and crispy,
and others are moist
from absorbing the sauce...
Meat juices mixed with the
pepper and vegetables...
So many flavors all
coming together!
[ALL]
IT'S DELISH!
This is incredible!
Another one for me, please!
I'll take two!
Three for me!
Mom, I wanna eat one!
Coming right up! Huh?
Mr. Tomita! I'll be
back in just a minute.
Huh?! Hey! Where are ya going?!
Just what's in that wrap?
A crepe?
Something like
they use for tacos?
I've never seen that!
Well, if it isn't the
lovely lady who said
I was in over my head.
Why are you not
standing proudly in line
like everyone else?
When... When did
you start planning this...
this strategy?
Three days ago.
Three days?!
The hardware store gave
us the cooking equipment.
The sheet metal place
made the Sumire Mark
branding iron for us.
The ingredients are from
the butcher and grocer.
The printing shop made
the flyers and paper
sleeves for us to use.
We got everything ready here
in this shopping district...
in just one night.
I got your ice‐cold beer
here! Perfect to go with your
hot fried chicken rolls!
We're having a sale on taiyaki!
Cold ramune over here!
Two‐for‐one!
We've got some exciting
new menu items people!
Come and try our brand
new dessert for free!
[GIRL]
It's like a festival!
[MAN 1]
This fried chicken
is so good!
[MAN 2]
I'll take one of those!
[KINU]
Fried chicken.
Unbelievable.
This little waste of space
was the driving force
in breathing life back
into all of Sumire‐dori!
I underestimated him.
The twerp is a
master strategist.
In the blink of an eye,
he set up a battle formation
that completely
surrounded Mozuya.
Just like the "one‐night
castle" constructed by
Hideoyoshi!
What was it you said?
We have no sense
of identity
or competitiveness
and it's only natural
we fall to ruin?
Something like that,
right?
[SOMA]
But you're mistaken.
Our shopping area...
Is like nothing else!
Shut up, you twit!
What's so friggin' special
about your fried chicken?!
Sooner or later, Mozuya
is going to crush you‐
[BOY]
Well don't say that...
What?
Unless you're gonna
try some, Grandma.
It's, like, crazy delish.
Where are your parents,
young man?
And who are you calling
"Grandma"?!
Oh, that's right.
Last time we met,
you let me try a sample.
Care to have a taste
of our fried chicken?
It's really tasty.
Order up!
(Fresh‐fried moans)
This wrap...
It uses rice flour!
Dear Lord...
It's like a... banh xeo!
[NARRATOR]
Banh xeo: a Vietnamese
batter‐based delight.
The batter uses rice flour,
water, and coconut milk.
It is lightly fried and stuffed
with ingredients such as pork,
shrimp, and bean sprouts.
It's so simple!
The concept of this dish is
piping‐hot white rice combined
with juicy fried chicken!
He reinterpreted the
ultimate family meal.
Packaging it so that it makes
it easy to eat while walking,
while still showcasing
its original flavors!
Students coming home from
afterschool activities...
Mothers in a hurry to get
dinner ready...
A place for commuters
to relax...
The peaceful murmur
of city streets...
It fits so well...
The atmosphere of this place
awakens the senses.
Profit... Earnings...
The two most
important ingredients
to any fine cuisine!
[P.A.]
In this final battle,
at the bottom of the ninth,
two outs, full count.
Here's the wind up...
and the delivery!
HOLY MOLY!
He scores!
This is...
the taste of youth!
You're welcome!
[SOMA]
You were awesome, Meat‐Meat.
Big time.
Man. That marinade was
perfect. You really nailed it!
I want you to keep teaching
me cool stuff like that, okay?
Um, yeah, okay,
if I'm not too busy.
She... She must be really nice.
This is the last night
I get to spend with Soma.
I wonder if he notices.
Mayumi...
Say, uh, would you
like to maybe, uh...
Y‐yeah?
...would you like to work
part‐time with Tomita?
Huh?!
It's going to take
a lot of hard work
to get that fried
chicken roll famous!
I'm worried about him
being on his own.
And I won't be able to help out
very much.
Um. Oh, I don't know. I've never
worked a part‐time job before!
There must be someone
more suited than me.
You've got a strong sense of
responsibility,
so I'm betting I could
trust you with this.
Huh?
[SOMA]
Back in middle school,
you used to work late doing
things for the student council.
Even in elementary school,
you never skipped your turn
to water the flowerbeds.
I'd feel better knowing
you were here keeping an
eye on things.
[MAYUMI]
I thought Soma was someone
so very far away from me...
But he noticed me?
Well, I don't wanna force you‐
I'll try to do my best!
Really?! Great!
I'll be back in town to air‐out
the shop every once in a while,
and then we can hang out more.
I'll even cook for ya!
Yeah, sure!
Ahhhhhh!
Uh... What's wrong, Meat‐Meat?
Nothing at all.
Ah, youth.
I've never felt so satisfied!
Show 'em the wrap!
The hot new fried chicken roll.
I'm sure you want to know
all about it.
One, two...
An unbelievable score
of 20 out of 10!
[EIZAN]
Sales have been plummeting
the past three days.
'Kay then... Can you explain?
What exactly is
happening at Mozuya?
[SOMA] (Stretch)
Man, so much for
a relaxing vacation.
That was over so fast!
What the hell?
What do you want?
You're Soma Yukihira, right?
Come with me.
Hello there.
So, who are you?
I hear you've created a
new fried chicken roll.
And that it's a
rather interesting dish.
I'm the one who oversaw
Mozuya's expansion into Kanto.
And it's not
just Mozuya.
Since my middle
school year,
I've consulted for
over 500 restaurants,
bringing in record‐breaking
profits for every single
one of them.
I've been told it was
you who got the shopping
arcade back on its feet.
My strategy is ruined
because of your play.
And? You want to take
me out or something?
No.
I want you to work for me.
Do so, and you
will never need to
look for a job again.
I've got my eye on being the
successor to my family
restaurant back home.
I have no interest in being
anybody's pet monkey, okay?
Hmph. Well I didn't actually
think you'd go for it.
Not with you reputation.
Huh?
A talented chef shut within
his own little box...
who feels satisfaction simply
by the pride in his work.
It's just a tiny little
shop, isn't that right?
Has being born into such
a modest household hindered
your culinary ambitions?
Well?
You sure do talk a big game...
But you're not even a real chef,
I mean how can you even‐?
Not true.
I am the one whom all chefs
look up to and aspire to be.
I'm standing on a far
greater stage than you.
Soma Yukihira, I'm
letting you know.
You've been chosen to compete
at the Fall Selection.
However, I wouldn't get
too excited if I were you.
Being selected means these
antics of yours are over.
No one is going to
blemish my career.
In the culinary world,
I go by a nickname...
You've heard of me, I'm sure.
I am the Alchemist!
Tohtsuki Council of Ten...
Seat No. 9, Etsuya Eizan!
There is no greater
stage than this,
and I look forward
to crushing you.
[MAYU]
Next time, on Tomita‐style
Boxed Lunches...
I mean, on Food Wars,
it's the nineteenth course!
"The Chosen One"
It's delicious, Soma!
I'll do my best
at work today!
Ahheehehehe!