[YOUNG SOMA] Hey Pops!
One day... I'll be a master chef
and beat you!
[JOICHIRO] Really? You don't
say.
Well good luck with all that.
[YOUNG SOMA] 'kay! Let's do it!
It's a food battle!
[JOICHIRO] It's been 490 battles
since then, huh.
[JOICHIRO] Listen up, Soma:
Don't go losing to anyone,
until you've lost to me again.
&lt;gulp&gt;
&lt;attack&gt;
[JOICHIRO] Oh dear god.
Mine is way more foul and
offensive than yours, my boy!
[URARA] Megumi Tadokoro has 88
points.
That's 4th place.
She's headed to the finals!
&lt;cheer/roar&gt;
[URARA] In 3rd place with
90 points is Takumi Aldini.
[URARA] Ranking in at 2nd place
with 92 points is Hisako Arato.
[URARA] And in 1st place with 95
points is Alice Nakiri.
[URARA] Congratulations!
You are the chosen candidates
from B Block!
[URARA] Now then, how is A Block
doing?
&lt;milling around,
surprised/concerned&gt;
[SOMA] The aroma...
It's like an explosion!
[SOMA] This... is Akira's curry!
[BOTH] Hohhhhhh!!!!!!!
&lt;OM gasp&gt;
[SCHOOLBOY A] The aroma
is coming off so strong!
[SCHOOLGIRL A]
It's even reaching up here in
the rafters!
[AOKI]
My nostrils sting so bad
it's like they're bein' stabbed
with aroma knives!
[SATO] It's so pungent it's
seeping into my brain!
[MINATOZAKA] Beneath the lid is
a sublime curry
infused with an incredible
amount
of the fish collar's umami!
[SCHOOLGIRL B] Oh wow, it smells
so good!
[SCHOOLBOY B] Amazing! Man, I
wanna eat that!
[JUN] Go, Akira!
&lt;CM nervous sounds, gulp&gt;
[MINATOZAKA] I'm gonna have to
dunk this naan
into the curry and gobble it up.
[MINATOZAKA] HrRrrrrrrr!!! I
have no words!
[ZENJI] This is known as pie
crust soup...
It follows the method of Paul
Bocuse,
leading chef in French cuisine.
It's said to be inspired by the
lidded bowl of Japanese Kaiseki
cuisine.
[SHUN] The scent of the
ingredients
are concentrated when covered.
When the lid is removed...
a burst of aromatics is released
into the air..
[IKUMI] Fragrances are Akira
secret weapons.
He's used their unbridled power
to launch a direct attack on the
judges!
[KODA] The spices are: fennel
and lemongrass...
and cinnamon too.
But there's more in there...
There's something
tying them all together.
What is it? What is the source
of this powerful aroma?
[NATSUME] It's holy basil!
And he's using it while it's
still fresh!
[SOMA] "Holy basil"?
[MINATOZAKA] This herb is deeply
regarded as Holy
in areas of Southern Asia.
If you smell it, a sensation of
sweetness
will surge through your body.
[KODA] In the traditional Indian
medicine
known as Ayurveda...
it's considered an enigmatic
miracle cure
for whatever illness you may
be carrying at the time.
[NATSUME] How did he get a‐hold
of this?
Fresh high‐quality holy basil is
rare.
and it's hard to find it here in
Japan.
[AKIRA] Yes. Those in the Shiomi
Seminars
have spent the last year growing
it.
[NATSUME] EhEhhhh!
[AKIRA] Our cultivation
method... is a trade secret.
[NATSUME] Professor Jun Shiomi,
a leading authority on spices.
[JUN] Wha‐wha‐wha?
[SOMA] True enough, it has a
powerful aroma
that's very... intoxicating.
But that's not all he's done.
There's something that makes you
wanna eat more and more...
[SOMA] Is that yogurt?
[AKIRA] You are correct... Soma.
[AKIRA] Y'see. One mistake with
holy basil
and it overpowers everything
else in your dish.
Yogurt can help mellow the
flavor
and blend it with the rest.
[CHAPELLE] What's more...
Curcumin is also good for
digestion.
And it has the ability to remove
toxins from the liver.
But when it's ingested with
yogurt ‐
it has the ability to produce
even greater effects for one's
overall well being.
[JUN] He even considered the
health benefits!
Do it, Akira! Use that big brain
of yours!
[NATSUME] To think, there's a
chef in this country
who can properly use holy
basil...
[NATSUME] Akira Hayama!
[NATSUME] Won't you be mine?
You're too delicious to be true.
&lt;react&gt;
[NATSUME] Just think a moment
and name your asking price.
100 million?
200?
I'll pay however much you
require of‐ Uh?!
[AKIRA] No thank you...
I fight for Jun Shiomi.
&lt;gasp&gt;
[JUN] Oh...?
[AKIRA] Appreciate the offer,
though.
[NATSUME] Hmmmm! Such a glorious
young man!
If I didn't want him already, I
want him now!
[MINATOZAKA] Mmmmm!!
Each bite sends a bolt of umami
straight to the brain!
Like laser beams of YUM‐YUM!
[KODA] I've never encountered
something so "sharp" yet so
delicious!
[NATSUME] This dish is perfect.
It has reached the pinnacle of
modern‐day curry.
[YUA] Um... so then, judges...
What is your final verdict? Your
scores, please.
[YUUKI] You guys!
[BOTH] Uhh?
So what was the final score?
[YUUKI] &lt;heaving for breath&gt;
We'll tell you later.
How are things here?
[TAKUMI] What about Soma?
What score did he get?!
[ISAMI] Calm down, Takumi.
Looks like he hasn't presented
yet.
[TAKUMI] &lt;growl&gt;
[YUA] Shun Hayama's score is...
There we have it!
[YUA] 94 points, putting him
straight into 1st place!
[JUN] Way to go,
Akiraaaaaaaaa!!!
[RYO] 2nd place, huh?
I think the Mistress will
be upset with that.
Well, I'll just try to do better
in the finals.
[IKUMI] Ehh! Guess I'm out...
[KANICHI] MEAT MEAT!
You got robbed out there!
But it's okay!
[MEGUMI] Poor Ryoko
[SATO] Hey, look!
TWO judges gave him a perfect
20!
[AOKI] Akira Hayama is one
fearsome dude!
[SATOSHI] A perfect 20, which
not even Alice Nakiri was able
to achieve...
That was a sight to see.
[ERINA] Oh uh Isshiki!
Why are you in here?
What about B Block's judging?
&lt;laugh&gt; I asked the others
to kindly clean up for me.
[FUMIO] My, that was a heck of a
battle over there.
[ERINA] Oh my God!
Unauthorized personnel
aren't allowed in here.
[FUMIO] There, there. I'm askin'
you as a dorm mother.
[ERINA]
That is totally irrelevant!
[SATOSHI] You came to A‐Block
cause you were curious about
Soma too, weren't you?
[ERINA] ERK! That's ridiculous!
[YUA] All right. Let's keep this
competition moving.
Soma Yukihira will present next.
[ERINA] Uh!
[YUA] Please serve your dish.
[MEGUMI] Soma... What kind of
dish did you make?
[SOMA] Here.
For you, enjoy Akira.
[AKIRA] What's with that smug
face of yours?
[AKIRA] Barely a month ago,
this guy didn't even know about
karipatta, a basic spice.
So why is he now grinning after
having eaten my curry?
[SOMA] &lt;laugh&gt; Yeah.. I just
thought why not y'know.
And I went with whatever came to
mind.
[AKIRA] Wait this is...
an omelet!
[SCHOOLBOY C] Huh?
[SCHOOLBOY D] Didn't that
transfer student
make that at the training camp?
[SOMA] Order up.
Another aroma Bomb...
[ERINA] Uhnh!
[SOMA] Comin atcha!
[MINATOZAKA] Whoa! Inside of
that omelet is risotto!
[NATSUME] The aroma that had
been sealed inside...
is exploding all over the place!
&lt;yells, screams&gt;
[SCHOOLBOY E] On the heels of
Akira's dish...
[SCHOOLBOY F] It's another huge
explosion of aroma!
[AKIRA] You came up with the
same idea.
[SOMA] Looks to be that way,
huh?
So far, at least.
[SOMA] It's hot, so watch
yourself.
[SOMA] May I present...
Yukihira curry risotto rice
omelet!
[IKUMI] The risotto he's stuffed
in the middle
is bright and sweetly
glistening!
The filling is like a rice bowl
coated with top‐quality sauce.
[RYOKO] &lt;hand love&gt;Incredible!
Such a full‐bodied, mellow
aroma!
Makes you smile without even
realizing it.
[KODA] My anticipation is right
up there with Akira's curry.
Here we go...
&lt;blow/inhale/blow&gt;
[NATSUME]
[STUDENTS] &lt;ohhs and whoaahs&gt;
[MINATOZAKA] Hmmm...
&lt;gulp&gt;
&lt;raging blowed&gt;
[MINATOZAKA] So powerful!
[KODA] It's a raging blow of
flavor!
[IKUMI] &lt;CT&gt; Yes!
[MEGUMI] HaAhhhhhh!
d[KODA] He made a rich bouillon
using chicken carcass and beef
tendon...
The flavor of onions and ground
beef
pan‐fried in butter extends to
the rice itself.
[MINATOZAKA] The creaminess of
the risotto
and the soft‐cooked fried egg
form the perfect combination.
Ahhh!!!I feel like I'm about to
collapse!
[NATSUME] This sauce delivers
the finishing gut punch.
It uses oyster sauce as a base,
with an accent of pure honey.
It's rich, but with a mellow
acidity that comes through.
Through the sauce and the
risotto,
he was able to create two layers
of flavor!
[KODA] Just amazing.
The impact of Akira's curry
came from its lack of pungency.
But this is like a secondary
explosion of aroma!
The inner and outer smells
intermingle in waves,
tantalizing the diner!
[AKIRA] But there's more to this
depth of flavor...
It's savory with a hint of
bitterness.
Cumin and cardamom...
And clove to stimulate the
tongue...
[AKIRA] I can make out bits and
pieces of it,
but those are only the surface
flavors.
What is this richness that has
bound with the spices?
I've got it!
[AKIRA] Mango!
Mango chutney.
[NATSUME] Mango chutney, you
say?!
That's enough to create such
levels of alluring flavor?
[ISAMI] Mango Chutney, is that
paste‐like stuff.
Am I right?
[TAKUMI] Yeah.
You grind up and simmer spices
and other fruits and vegetables.
Then you turn it into a
condiment.
[JUN] Different parts of Asia,
have created combinations,
in a wide variety of styles,
using either sweet or spicy, or
adding in herbs like mint.
[SOMA] This mango chutney
is my own homemade blend.
All I did was add this to the
rice and let it simmer.
[SOMA] I used mango as the focal
point,
to bind the flavors of the other
spices
and give the dish that much more
depth.
[SOMA] Put simply, "applied
spice techniques."
[ZENJI] In India, which is its
country of origin...
Chutney is simply a garnish.
It's also considered medicinal
in some parts.
This is the Japanese method.
[IKUMI] Huh...
[RYOKO] I had no idea.
[CHAPELLE] This is a most
unusual
cooking method for its place of
origin.
But having said that...
[KODA] This dish would be
difficult
to add any more fats or animal
products to it...
[MINATOZAKA] It's added a
dramatic dimension of flavor!
[ERINA] Soma Yukihira...
[ERINA] His prior use of eggs
was a disaster. Uh.
[SATOSHI] At the training camp,
his omelets almost caused him to
flunk out.
Then, his risotto battle against
his father was a failure.
[SATOSHI] He brought in the
combined
techniques of those two
experiences.
[ERINA] His father?
[SATOSHI] Through all his
failures...
zero against 490 wins...
he hasn't let a single lesson go
by the wayside.
[FUMIO] Heh.... Come to think of
it, he's a good listener.
That could be taken as hard
persistence.
If he loses, he's not willing to
let that be.
That darn Soma...
He puts on a cool face,
but he hates losing
more than anything.
[ERINA] UhUhhh...
[SOMA] But hey... I gained the
experience
that comes from messing up.
[ERINA] That's simply making
excuses for yourself!
For a chef, failure is
unacceptable!
&lt;react&gt;
[MINATOZAKA] It's delicious
through and through,
the result of some hard work.
What's more, the aftertaste
is so crisp and clean!
That must be thanks to the
chutney.
[NATSUME] Still, Akira's pie
dish
had a more luxurious aroma.
[JUDGE B] Yes, However...
When the sauce and the rice come
together
the resulting depth is profound!
[KODA] Akira's curry revolved
around holy basil,
likening it to a spear piercing
through your very soul.
This curry attacks in waves...
In successive assaults on your
taste‐buds!
[CHAPELLE] They both have
their own scented weapons,
different styles they're using
in all‐out warfare!
[SOMA] &lt;growls&gt;
[AKIRA] &lt;snarls&gt;
[JUN] Ahhhhh!!!
[AKIRA] &lt;thrust effort&gt;
[SOMA] Hyehh! HYAHHH!
[SOMA] Ehhh! AH!
[AKIRA] Hahhhhhhhh!!! Huh?
[BOTH] Hyeehhhhh!!!
[CHAPELLE] This is a fight
between two warriors
aiming for the top spot at
Totsuki!
&lt;whoaas and ohhs&gt;
[SCHOOLBOY F]
Whoa. Look at that.
They're givin' him
great reviews!
[SCHOOLBOY E] Don't tell me that
transfer student's gonna beat
Akira Hayama!
[YUA] Well then, judges...if
you're ready...
please mark your final scores
[YUA] 18!
19!
18!
[YUA] For a total of...
[YUA] 93 points!
[YUA] Soma ties for second
place!
And that is your final tally!
[YUUKI] What?! Come on!
[MEGUMI] One point off?
[ISAMI] He got 93 points!
[TAKUMI] Oh my God.
[ZENJI] 2nd place?
[RYO] We're tied...
It's you and me... Soma.
[ALICE] &lt;giggle&gt;
[SCHOOLBOY B] Good, that
transfer student
wasn't able to take the top
spot.
[SCHOOLBOY H] Akira's like the
essence of curry.
[AKIRA] &lt;react&gt;
[RYOKO] Wait...
Take a look at those scores!
[IKUMI] Out of the five
judges...
three of them preferred Soma's
dish to Akira's.
[IKUMI] And that means...
If they were to fight... under
Food War regulations...
[MINATOZAKA] What is wrong with
you!?
How can you not understand
the remarkable work of art that
curry was?
He had the skills to put Holy
basil in a dish!
[KODA] Nonsense.
If you recall the theme is curry
cuisine.
We are not here to judge
simply on their choice of
spices.
It's important to feel satisfied
by a single plate.
[NATSUME] Unless you are dead,
Akira won on that point as well!
[JUDGE A] But it was
Young Soma's dish
that made me want to eat it over
and over again.
[MINATOZAKA] Oh shut up, you
minor character! [JUDGES]
ERK!
[KODA] Don't let your emotions
cloud your opinion!
[MINATOZAKA] Anyone who lacks a
diverse frame
of reference has no business
talking about fine dining!
[KODA] You have no business
being a judge!
[MINATOZAKA]
Oh shut your fat mustache!
[YUA] Stop it please!
Everyone just needs to
settle down and relax!
[KODA] Why don't you go back
to your computer where you
belong!?
[MINATOZAKA] What was that, you
go to hell!
[IKUMI] Why are they
still arguing?
I mean isn't Akira still
in 1st place?
[RYOKO] I think so.
[EIZAN] Well at least
he made it this far.
I look forward to the finals...
Soma Yukihira.
[JUN] Oh, Akira! You were
amazing out there!
You're incredible!
[CHAPELLE] There are but two
outcomes at the finals:
win or lose. Hmmm...
[CHAPELLE] If those two are to
be
pitted against one another...
Which one of them will end up
coming out on top?
&lt;laughter&gt;
[SENZAEMON] And so the 92nd
era...
The Golden Age, eh?
&lt;big evil laugh&gt;
[YUUKI] Gather 'round folks...
To the Fall Selection's
theatrics!
To its crazy conclusion,
we celebrate the results
AND all our hard work. Let's
partay!
[ALL] Cheers!
[ALL]
ME‐GU‐MI!
ME‐GU‐MI! ME‐GU‐MI!
[FISHERMAN A] That was some
mighty fine cooking, Megumi!
[FISHERMAN C] At this rate,
you might win this whole food
competition!
[MEGUMI] Huhh?! Wait, just calm
down you guys! [ALL] laughs
[MIYOKO] Megumi Tadokoro.
[MEGUMI] Huh? Hey Miyoko.
[MIYOKO] It kinda looks like...
I misunderstood the talent you
have.
Impressive. I'll be rooting for
you.
[MIYOKO] If you run into any
more trouble,
you just let me know.
[MEGUMI] Thank you very much,
Miyoko!
[YUUKI] I toldja! I knew how
truly awesome
you were this whole time,
Megumi.
[MEGUMI] Come on, Yuuki!
[YUUKI] Don't worry my talent
friend.
I'm gonna have a whole squad
ready to cheer you on at the
finals!
[MEGUMI] That would be great!
[FISHERMAN A] Come over here,
Megumi!
Let's get a picture with the
guys, okay?!
[YUUKI] They're calling for you.
Get over there girl.
[FUMIO] Well done Yuuki.
[YUUKI] Ms. Fumio you're just
the greatest!
Thank you for all your support
today!
Things are going to get really
busy 'round here.
I've gotta make a banner for
Megumi that screams awesomeness!
Ms. Fumio will you help me put
together some..
[FUMIO] Tonight I'm treating
my sweet girl to
her favorite dish.
That was some good cooking.
You did all right out there.
&lt;sobs, crying&gt;
&lt;sniffles&gt;
[IKUMI] That's some super
high‐quality duck you got there!
[YUUKI] You can tell
just by looking at it?
That's a pretty neat trick.
[TAKUMI] Ah!
I didn't realize Koji can work
like that too?
[ISAMI] I had no idea you could
do that.
[RYOKO] Yeah well you just gotta
know when to use it.
[AOKI] Still, I never thought
Zenji
would have his own cheering
section!
[SATO] Yeah. That gives him a
whole new level of cool...
[ZENJI] And yet, once again
the party is being held
in MY freakin' bedroom.
[SATOSHI] You two, please make
sure that you eat your fill.
[TAKUMI] Uh, okay.
We're very grateful for the
invitation, Isshiki.
[IKUMI] We've got a guy waggling
around in nothing but an apron.
Why isn't anyone
talking about this?
[RYOKO] Say, where is Shun
hiding away tonight?
[YUUKI] Hmm? I bet he's holed up
in his room
feeling sorry for himself.
He may not let it show,
but I think he was pretty upset.
Jeez, I swear.
Maybe I should go drag him out
here.
[SATOSHI] It's two weeks
until the final tournament
is upon us.
This will be a battle between
the students currently
considered to be
the fiercest of Totsuki's
1st‐years!
[TAKUMI] Now listen to me, Soma!
If you go losing before you face
ME,
you're gonna pay!
Yeah yeah...
that's fine by me.
[SOME ]Bring it on!
[TAKUMI] Oh I'm bringin' it.
&lt;drunken laughter...
barely conscious moans&gt;
[AKIRA] Hey, Jun.
Getting drunk by yourself
and passing out is even more sad
than usual.
&lt;nasal exhale&gt;
[AKIRA] I guess it is
what it is.
[JUN] You know what Akira...?
You might just change the
culinary world forever.
&lt;Hmm&gt;
[AKIRA] &lt;Hmm&gt; Jun. I am going to
win the finals first.
[AKIRA] You found a place for
me...
[AKIRA] I'm winning this for
you...
[ALICE] What the heck?
What's your deal, Erina?
Come on Gimme a break! Come out
with me tonight!
Your cousin just got through the
preliminaries
with the top score out of
everyone from both blocks!
[ALICE] You have a DUTY to
celebrate.
You think so too, don't you Ryo?
[RYO] I'm fine with whatever she
decides.
[ALICE] Whuuuaaghhh!!! Dangit,
Ryo!
What's wrong with you!
You're supposed to be on my
side!
[RYO] Okay... really
sorry about that.
[ERINA] I'm afraid I have some
paperwork to take care of
tonight.
I'll have to celebrate with you
another time.
[ALICE] Ooh?! If you say so.
I'll let you off the hook for
tonight.
I'll be back tomorrow.
Let's go, Ryo.
[ERINA]
[RYO] Sure.
[ERINA] Congrats on getting
through the prelims, Alice.
You too, Ryo.
[RYO] Thank you.
[HISAKO] I'm sorry, Miss Erina.
I know you said you were very
busy tonight, but I tried.
[ERINA] It couldn't be helped.
It's Alice, after all.
[ERINA] Congratulations to you,
too, Hisako. [HISAKO] Oh?
[ERINA] I thought it only
fitting that you would make it
through
but just the same it still makes
me very proud.
[HISAKO] Okay!
I'll work to get even better,
and I WILL win! Don't you worry!
[NAO] HeeHeeHeeHee!
That's my "Big Sis" Miss Hisako!
Heeheeheehee!
ACK!
&lt;sigh&gt;
[ERINA] The aroma that came from
that dish...
[ERINA] That amazing... Aroma!
[ERINA] AhAhhhhhhhhhh!!!!!!!!!
&lt;OM inhale&gt;
[SOMA] How ya like me now?
How ya like me now?
[ERINA] Get away from me!
[SOMA] You wanna take a bite!
[SOMA]
You know you wanna try it!
[ERINA] It's disgusting!
[ERINA] Uhhnn!!! [ERINA]
[ERINA] Soma Yukihira...
[MEGUMI] Hey, Soma!
[SOMA] Hmm?
[SOMA] Oh uh hey there Megumi.
What's goin' on?
[MEGUMI] Um...
I thought you seemed a little
down.
You want to talk about it?
[SOMA] I'm doing fine.
More importantly Megumi,
they say you used ingredients
from your hometown to make a
curry!
[MEGUMI] It's not a big deal.
[SOMA] That's totally amazing!
[MEGUMI] You know, it still
doesn't feel quite real to me...
Six months ago, they were gonna
kick me out.
[SOMA] Oh, yeah. Man,
that first lesson seems so long
ago.
That was the first time you and
I worked together, huh?
[MEGUMI] Everything... I've done
is thanks to you.
It's because of you I've been
able to come this far.
You are a good friend.
[SOMA] Nah, you've always
had what it took right
from the start Megumi.
[SOMA] Your cooking really is
top notch.
[SOMA] It's like, it really
warms you up inside...
[SOMA] Kinda like love.
&lt;inhale, tittering&gt;
[SOMA] Ah!
[MEGUMI] EhHeeHee!
Thank you very much Soma.
That makes me really happy.
[IKUMI] What are those
two talking about
all alone out there?
And why am I creeping around
in the shadows watching them?
[YUUKI] Well, well.
Isn't this an
interesting development?
[IKUMI] Ohhhh?!
[RYOKO] It certainly is.
[MEGUMI] You really did great,
Soma.
To be able to go toe‐to‐toe with
Akira...
I mean...he's the curry
specialist...
[SOMA] Hmmmm... He still managed
to get
a one‐point lead on me though.
I really went in there expecting
to win this thing.
Honestly I wanted to get a
perfect score
from all five of the judges.
[MEGUMI] You were aiming high,
weren't you?
[SOMA] Akira used spices I'd
never even heard of
to make an unreal dish.
How is that even possible?
[SOMA] There's so much more
I wanna learn about cooking.
About different ingredients,
different methods...
I want to learn from people who
already know how.
[SOMA] Then put all that into my
next dish.
[SOMA] I want... I need to get
stronger!
[YUUKI] Come on! It's time for
round two you guys!
[SATOSHI] I'm not done...not
yet.
This night is just getting
started!
[IKUMI] &lt;scream!&gt;
[SATOSHI] It's Boomerang time!
[AOKI] Yeah... All right:
Isshiki's Third Form front and
center!
[SATO] That is one tiny little
speedo!
[FUMIO] &lt;hums the closing theme&gt;
[ZENJI] Come on, Shun! Get on
that bottle like you mean it!
You love rice juice!
[SHUN] You're freaking me out
Zenji.
[TAKUMI] Okay Soma! Just you
wait
I will utterly annihilate you at
final competition.
[RYOKO] I think this guy might
have some problems.
[ISAMI] I usually just leave him
alone
whenever he gets all worked up
in a tizzy like this.
[YUUKI] You're his brother you
should take care of him!
[SATO] This meat is some top
quality stuff, bro!
Eat up!
[AOKI] Don't mind if I do!
[IKUMI] Oh hell no! [BOTH] Huh?
[IKUMI] If you dunk that
delicious meat in that nasty
sauce...
you will massacre its delicate
natural flavors!
[IKUMI] You're spittin' directly
in that poor meat's face!
I‐I'm sorry, Miss Meat Meat!
Have mercy!
[MEAT MEAT] Don't call me "Meat
Meat," you piece of crap!
[MEAT MEAT] There is only one
person on this earth
who is allowed to say Meat Meat
to me.
[MEAT MEAT] Agh oh my god
now you've got me saying it,
too!
[AOKI] Whaaaauuughhhhh!!!!
Agggghhhh!
&lt;back breaking&gt;
[SOMA] All right now. We need
something
to liven things up around here.
[RYOKO] I think he's going make
something gross again!
[YUUKI] No, please don't do this
to us Soma?!
[MEGUMI] No, Soma.
You don't have to make
anything, it's okay!
[SOMA] Too late. It's already
made.
[SOMA] Time to eat up.
[MEGUMI] Ummph!
[SOMA] Octopus tentacles in
yogurt sauce.
[MEGUMI] NOOOOO!
It's horrible!!!!
[ALL] Thanks for the food!