(Light snoring)
Really? He's sleeping?
How can he be asleep
at a time like this?!
There it is!
Done!
That aroma...
(Murmurs)
Hey, look!
Check out his pot!
That's rice!
He's boiled vegetables and
spices in with the rice!
[AKIRA]
That pot of yours...
I see you've added a paste of
apples, bananas, and carrots.
Interesting. It will give the
rice a thickness, making it
into a kind of risotto.
Well done, Akira!
You can smell all that
just standing there?
You've got yourself
a great sniffer.
No. There's another
hidden element.
The aromatic spices that he's
using aren't all that unique...
so what's making
this aroma so complex?
The truth is,
I was experimenting
till early morning.
I was trying to really
concentrate on the aroma
and kinda fell asleep
in the middle of it all.
Nothing fazes you,
does it?
You just keep
on watching...
for when my dish really
starts to come together.
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
Man, look at that redneck.
She's barely even
trying to cook down there.
I swear, she pisses me off!
You don't belong here!
Go back where came from!
[AOKI]
What was that?
What'd you dill weeds just
spew outta your mouths?!
Got something to say,
say it to me!
AAHHHH!
[FUMIO]
That's enough!
Just leave the punks be.
But, Miss Fumio,
they deserve it!
They're talking so friggin' loud
Megumi's gonna hear!
Just cheer those two
on as much as you can, boys.
Alright, then.
We understand.
Megumi! Yuki! Good luck!
Yeah!
[AOKI and SATO]
Cook that food's butt!
This should just
about take care of
all the prep work.
Now I have to get to
work on the protein.
Ah!
Do you know what is the
greatest burden in the kitchen?
A fool not paying attention...
who doesn't know
their surroundings
and gets in the way!
Oh, okay! I'm very sorry!
I'll be more careful.
Oooohh...
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
Miyoko finally added her spice!
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
Now that it's got
a strong aroma,
she's adding it to the
egg and stir‐fried rice!
Look at that!
He's awesome, too!
[SCHOOLBOY 4]
He cut that pasta so fast!
[SCHOOLBOY 5]
Such technique! To think,
he could take a mezzaluna,
which is mainly used for dicing,
and slice noodles so perfectly!
Check out his brother
behind him. What kind
of dough is that?!
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
Oh, I can't take my eyes
off either of them!
Looks like Megumi's
holdin' her own, bro!
Totally, dude. Let's see some
of her awesome technique!
[AOKI]
Ah! Uhh...
AHHH!
Dude...
Megumi Tadokoro...
After the rumors I heard
about your Food War
with Chef Shinomiya,
I thought you had what it took
to go up against a man,
but I overestimated you.
(Shocked gasps)
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
Look at that!
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
She's using monkfish?!
How is she gonna
prepare THAT?!
(Chuckle)
[ORIE]
What does that girl
think she's doing?
Slicing the meat
while it hangs.
Yes, I already know that.
The skin of the
monkfish is covered with
a gelatinous substance,
so it's hard to prepare on
a cutting board.
She's using the traditional
method to break it down.
But still...
Because it's hangin'
in mid‐air
without a stable surface,
it takes a special skill to be
able to cut it properly.
[SATO]
For her to choose such a tough
fish to prepare at a major
event like this is pretty bold!
Order up!
[MEGUMI]
Up till now, I've done
nothing but rely on Soma,
who always stays positive
in any challenge.
I know Soma is
nowhere nearby...
but I know he's fighting too!
I don't know if I can do this
properly on my own, but...
Soma, please, give me some
of your strength and bravery!
[SOMA]
I learned that
from back home.
It's how I was taught
to get my mind right.
The only drawback is you
can't do it by yourself.
Okay!
[OLD CHEF]
I'm so sorry.
Our suspended‐cut monkfish
is a specialty,
And I would like to keep it
up for the entertainment
of our customers, but...
my body just can't
provide the strength
it takes.
Don't force yourself.
You've worked real hard
for a long time.
[MOTHER]
It's more show
than anything.
You don't have
to do this anymore.
[FISHERMAN]
What was that?!
You want me to teach ya
suspended cutting?
What the hell
you talkin' bout?
There's no way a woman,
a kid, could do it!
Um, please! I want to help
my family's restaurant!
Please help, sir!
Please help me!
Please help me, sir!
Please, sir!
Alright...
If you promise not to do
any whinin' about it,
I'll teach ya how to do it.
But listen up!
Don't you dare say it's
hard work or you wanna
take a break for a while.
I will throw ya
right out on your butt!
[FISHERMAN]
No, no, no!
That ain't how it's done!
Quit makin' me
repeat myself!
You ready to tell me
you can't do it?
Go on, just quit.
Give up!
Uh‐uh!
(Amazed exclamations)
Can we...
keep it... going now?
Incredible!
Oh, sweetie.
Suspended cutting!
Oh, man! She friggin'
broke it down!
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
A whole monkfish,
all by herself!
What on Earth does
that girl intend to make?
Aw yeah,
there she goes!
Now this is
Megumi's true skill!
You two better run off
and go cheer for Ryoko and
everyone else from Kyosukei!
Gotcha!
Leave it to us!
[FUMIO]
Yes, that's the spirit.
You've got my respect, girl.
After all, you ARE a
member of Kyokusei.
All right! I've got
some tricks of my own!
[URARA]
We'll soon be out of time!
Everyone, please get your
dishes ready!
[URARA]
Five!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One!
(Ding ding ding)
[URARA]
Time is up!
(Cheering)
A little longer...
Just a little longer,
Hisako Arato!
Soon, the moment will
come where I beat you,
and Miss Erina will
only notice me!
I will be hers
and hers alone.
Time to become hideous...
(Cackle)
[URARA]
Now then, it's time for
judgment to begin!
And your guide will be ME,
Urara Kawashima!
Cutesy!
You're the cutest
thing ever, Urara!
(Girls growling)
[URARA]
We have five judges,
each of whom can award
20 points!
In other words, food will be
judged on a scale, with 100
being a perfect score.
Only the contestants with
the top‐four scores will
move on to the finals.
Just four of us?
Now our first contestant!
Judges, please
begin the testing!
Well, well...
Mmm! Most delicious!
[FUMIO]
Osaji Kita...
Organizer of the Kita
Gastronomy Club,
which only the most elite of
the cultural and business worlds
are allowed to become members.
The power of money brings
all the world's delicacies
to that man's table.
[FUMIO]
Over there is Shingo Ando.
He's an author and essayist
that holds sway over all
culinary culture.
Lord knows how many restaurants
he's shut down with a
stroke of his pen.
This dish uses
achari murgh spices,
a dish representative of
northern India, as a base.
[KITA]
The splendid fragrance of the
chat masala is used to increase
the acidity profile.
[KITA]
What's more, the meat
was prepared in a
chicken tikka style
rather than as a
chicken marsala.
Having been deboned,
it's tender enough to
eat with a spoon.
It's a well
thought‐out dish,
one that's considerate
of the diner.
[KITA]
Now THAT is a student
of Tohtsuki, my friends!
Why, thank you very much.
And now for the score, please!
Let's see it!
[SCHOOLBOY]
The maximum score per judge
is 20 points, not 10, right?
[SCHOOLGIRL]
But they praised him so much!
My dish is only good
for a measly 33 points?!
What's that supposed to be?!
Watch yourself!
Who the hell
do you think we are?!
Every day we critique
chefs with a lot more
tricks up their sleeves
than you could
possible imagine!
This was prepared well,
but it's still on the
level of a mere student.
And listen here.
You should be ecstatic if you
were to reach even 50 points.
I see. The Sendawara
sisters aren't the only
sharks in the tank.
[TAKUMI]
All five of them have spent
years indulging in the finest
of cuisines.
They have a completely
different standard when
it comes to taste.
[URARA]
28 points!
31 points!
6 points!
No way... All those dishes
were really well done!
Are you kidding me? No one's
even reached 40 points yet.
The string of harsh reviews
continues!
Now then, our next dish is...
UUUGGHH!
That reeks!
[ORIE]
What is that stench?!
Ingest...
It's the Nao
Sadatsuka's special...
(Terrified screams)
pitch‐black Laksa curry!
(Disgusted outcries)
It smells like
sewer water!
[URARA]
It's Hell on Earth!
Death has assailed us
here at this venue!
I can't imagine something
like THIS at an event meant to
celebrate the finest of cuisine!
[URARA]
It's killin' me!
Yeah. I thought
something like this
might happen.
I'm glad I came prepared
with some protection.
Laksa. A dish from Southeast
Asia that uses a noodle with a
unique, "slippery" mouthfeel.
The darkness of the broth
is from squid ink.
[KITA]
This commanding stench
that turns the nose...
Please no!
It's kusaya.
I knew it!
Why in the hell would you use
something like that in a CURRY,
you twisted heathen?!
Kusaya...
A dish famous on
the Izu Islands.
The same saltwater used to
steep fish for years or
even decades,
a fermenting liquid known
as "kusaya broth,"
is used as a brine for
blueback fish such as sardines
that are then left
to dry in the sun.
It really stinks!
On top of that,
it's my own special blend.
I chose to use flying fish
and mahi‐mahi.
It uses a kusaya broth
I brewed oh‐so carefully.
You get a zero,
you little devil child!
I've eaten some
strange foodstuff in
my time, but this...
Uh, Miss Orie,
you're trying it?!
Merely to fulfill my
responsibility
as a sponsor of this
competition.
The harsh acidity mixed with
that foul, fishy odor...
It smells like an unwashed
toilet!
I‐it's delicious?
[ORIE]
But it stinks!
It really stinks!
But it's so delicious!
Even though it stinks!
Wh‐wh‐what's going on?
She says that it stinks,
but she keeps going back
in for more!
The flavor reminds me of kapi,
a fermented shrimp paste.
By using ingredients far
stronger than those in kapi,
she creates a depth of flavor
comparable to laksa,
which uses fish stock
as its base.
It all makes horrible,
wonderful sense!
The seafood flavor spreads
across the tongue!
It's delicious!
The more you chew it,
the more this "stink"
grows into a good thing!
She's used spices
like lemongrass,
as well as coconut milk,
to give the dish some
added flavor!
Having kusaya as the
star ingredient
actually makes the curry
that much more enchanting!
Nao Sadatsuka
is an expert in
simmered dishes.
She's a wealth of
knowledge regarding
dried fish
as well as other
dried goods that are
hard to work with.
(Cackle)
[ISSHIKI]
Her cooking room gives off
a sinister air,
one that would send children
crying to their mothers.
The odor emitting from it
has been known to cause
quite a commotion.
And thus, the reason
for her nickname...
"The Boiling Witch"!
True aesthetics are rare
in most food. One must
dig deeper to find them.
The essence of fine cuisine
is hidden in the grotesque.
Such creativity!
This is the first page
in a new book on curry!
It's nasty... It's stinky,
I love it!
I can't stop myself!
(Pungent moan)
I'm a slave to its stench!
(Cackle)
[URARA]
Um, there we have it!
84 points!
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
That's the first time
someone's cleared fifty!
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
I can't believe it
was her who did it!
[SCHOOLBOY 3]
She's in first place for now!
Aah... I would like
Miss Erina to partake in
my delectable curry.
Well, while we're
airing out the venue,
let's go ahead and continue.
Will the next student
please come forward?
I've waited for this...
to utterly defeat
and humiliate you
in front of everyone,
Hisako Arato.
[OFFICIAL]
Alright.
This battle is being recognized
as an official Food War!
Do either of you have any
objections to the rules?
So we're clear, Hisako.
If I win this battle,
you will hand over your prized
role as Miss Erina's assistant.
Of course, Nao.
And if I win,
from now on...
you won't get within 50 meters
of my treasured Miss Erina!
Being at her side
to bask in her glow...
while being subjected
to her verbal cruelties
is my dream!
Oh all the foul obscenities
that would pour forth from
her godlike tongue...
(Sinister laugh)
But we have already
battled for that privilege.
I have beaten you.
And quite decisively.
Yes...
But since that time...
I've had to view her divinity
through binoculars...
and have resorted to
sending my beautiful angel
just 30 sad letters a day.
I should have made that
off‐limits as well.
But if I publicly annihilate you
at this Fall Selection,
Miss Erina may well have a
change of heart.
She will let me
walk by her side
forever more.
[SCHOOLBOY 1]
Look! Miss Erina's
assistant is next!
[SCHOOLBOY 2]
I bet she'll put out
an awesome dish!
[HISAKO]
Please enjoy.
[ORIE]
The roux looks watery
and lacking thickness.
This looks more akin
to a soup curry.
This meat is mutton,
is it not?
[KITA]
Though from the same
animal, it has a
stronger smell than lamb,
but the spices should
mask the odor.
[ORIE]
Odor!
(Cackle)
The effects of my cooking
still linger on, don't they?
That, my dear, is my curse!
My curse upon you, Hisako!
Well, I guess we should
give this dish a try.
This is...
OH!
Is everything okay over
there, Mister Ando?
Uh...
What?
Wh‐what?!
This from Ando,
the man who actually
mutters unintelligibly,
actin' like some
uprooted, withered tree.
I don't know what's going on,
but now you're starting
to sound like someone
in a kung fu movie!
[ANDO]
This unique aroma... It's...
Fuuwaaa...
Angelica! Rehmannia!
Lovage! And peony!
This dish uses the four
main ingredients
of Chinese herbal medicine
as its main base!
It's the Four Pillars of
Herbalism!
When devoured all at once,
the Four Pillars
do great things.
They can instantly bring
people back from the grips
of death's hands!
[KITA]
Of course!
She must have infused them
along with the spices!
Yes. That's her
specialty after all.
Hisako Arato: the Expert
of Medicinal Cooking!
[ALICE]
It's a discipline
based in Eastern medicine.
The combination of techniques
creating nourishing food
infused with natural drugs and
herbs used in Chinese remedies.
A fusion of food, medicine,
and pharmacology...
My original spice
mixture contains
ginger, star anise, and a
dash of fennel thrown in.
I added that to four more
medicinal ingredients.
I boiled those spices about
an hour earlier to draw
out their medicinal properties.
And then, I added the
vegetables and mutton and
let them simmer until moist
and the flavors seeped in.
Shaoxing rice wine and coriander
elevated the aroma profile.
Ahh...
Come to think of it,
curry and medicinal foods
have a lot in common with
each other, don't they?
[KITA]
Kyo‐o is turmeric.
Dai‐i‐kyo is star anise.
Sho‐i‐kyo is fennel.
All these spices are
absolutely essential in
making a great curry!
So that was her goal here.
A blending of curry
and medicinal cooking!
My brand of medicinal cooking:
brings forth a
"Four‐Pillar Mutton Curry"!
Ah! I can feel it! It's true!
The energy from this medicinal
meal is racing through my body!
AHHH!
It's superb!
The flavor of the mutton is
heightened by the spices,
and the vegetables have
absorbed the roux,
becoming sweet and
velvety smooth!
Thanks to the Four Pillars,
the body feels warmed the
second you take a bite!
Definitely. Medicinal food
is said to aid the kidneys
and lend strength...
as well as rid the
body of toxins.
[KITA]
It's the perfect balance of
flavor and aroma!
This is incredibly well done!
It not somethin' you'd expect
a student to prepare!
This is divine singularity.
Eating this curry makes
the last dish look like
a simple indulgence.
AHHH!
I‐it can't be...
I thought my dark curry
and my wickedness had made
slaves of the judges!
Here you go, Ms. Nao.
Once you eat some,
you will soon understand
the stark difference in
level between you and me!
Hesitation... Chaos...
THAT is the essence
of my cooking, and yet...
It's all being washed away.
I'm being cleansed!
Stop it!
My family has had a long
relationship with Chinese
medicine.
I've incorporated all
that into my cooking,
so that I could help Miss Erina,
who has been forced into
hardship from such a young age.
That is the source of my
medicinal cooking.
In the palaces of
ancient China,
emperors were assigned a
medical diet called
"gastric health,"
which was the introduction
of medicinal food.
To me, Miss Erina is the only
empress I will serve.
Nao Sadatsuka, your
cooking shows you only
think of yourself to impress.
You have no right to
serve the divine Miss Erina!
Stay far away.
And get up.
So then, Hisako Arato's
score is...
92 points!
(Cheering)
This is so insane!
That's why Miss Erina has
chosen her to be her aide!
That's over 90 points!
[SCHOOLBOY 4] She easily
beat Sadatsuka's score!
(Laughing)
My Big Sister, Miss Hisako!
[URARA]
Now this is a match to watch!
Big Brother...
I really want
to beat you.
You think you can handle
something like that?
Hmph!
I'll give you a shot,
Little Brother.
[URARA]
The Aldini Brothers!
[AKIRA]
Next time, on the twenty‐second
course of Food Wars...
It will be me who
rises to the top.
"That Which Transcends
the Norm"
Smells good, doesn't it?
[HISAKO]
Princess Erina,
I shall protect you!
My sweet Hisako.