[alarm beeps]
[HOTARO groans]
[TOMOE]
"Hey, Little Bro.
How are you?
I'm still in Varanasi.
Congrats on passing!
Sorry this is late.
I hear you ended up going
to Kami High, my alma mater!
Now that you're
officially in high school,
let me give you
some sisterly advice.
Join the Classic Lit Club.
It's one of the oldest
clubs the school has,
and I was in it
my whole time there.
From what I've been told,
it doesn't have a
single member right now!
If no one new joins this year,
the Executive Committee
will do away with it!
As one of the veterans,
I couldn't bear
to see that happen.
Please, Hotaro.
Join the Classic Lit club,
and help keep the legacy alive.
My adolescent
memories are at stake!
It's not like you have
anything better to do, right?
Sincerely, your sister, Tomoe."
[BOY 2A]
1, 2, 3,4 !
[HOTARO] It's been a month since
we saved the Classic Lit Club.
I'm starting to feel at home in
the Earth Science prep room.
When I get bored after school,
it's the first place I go.
I never expected to
feel that way in there,
but I'm not complaining.
[ERU]
Want some?
I brought some snacks from home.
You're welcome to
whatever you want.
Thank you.
[HOTARO] It's not that I
ever disliked spending time
with other people.
As long as they weren't the kind
who wore me out or anything.
It's pointless.
Yeah, is life
like a dull pencil?
What? What are you
talking about?
Was that supposed to be a joke?
Yeah, sorry.
Look. I'm not in the
mood for jokes now!
'Kay, fine then.
I said it's pointless!
What?
[ERU] All the time we've
been wasting in here
after school every day,
doing absolutely
nothing productive!
[HOTARO] I don't have
a problem with that.
But is there something
specific you want to do
with your time in
the Classic Lit Club?
Yeah, there is.
Oh?
But... That's more
of a personal matter.
[HOTARO]
She's said that before.
Right now I'm talking
about something different.
If we're going
to be a legit club,
we need some good activities.
[HOTARO]
That's pointless.
Wait, hear me out.
Let's submit an anthology
to the cultural festival!
Seriously?
Yep.
Let's not.
Sounds like a ton of work.
No, we have to
have an anthology!
Look, if you really want to
participate in the festival,
there are much
easier ways to do it.
Like concessions.
Kami High's cultural festival
has never allowed students
to sell concessions.
Anyway, they'll give us
a budget for an anthology,
and our advising teacher has
requested that we create one.
Also, it's been a
tradition for this club
to create one for the festival
for the past four decades.
They don't want to break that.
Well then, why didn't you
mention all that sooner?
That means we have to do it.
Great!
So what is this anthology
supposed to contain, anyway?
I have no idea!
Are you kidding me?
Yeah, sorry.
I thought that you and I
could look into it together.
I figured if there
were any anthologies
from previous years lying
around, we could start there.
Why don't we
search for them?
I give up.
[ERU]
Maybe they're in the library.
Let's check it out!
[ERU] Why are you
still sitting there?
You're coming with me.
Get up.
[HOTARO]
I'm not in the mood for this.
It's Friday, which means that
it's her shift on library duty.
Well, well. It's Oreki.
Long time no see.
Can't say I've missed you.
Hey, Ibara.
Nice to see you, too.
This is the sacred
realm of knowledge.
Your presence here
defiles all that.
Oh, yeah?
I'm floored they'd leave
you in charge of books.
Do you even know how to read?
You haven't changed at all.
If you came to insult me,
then you should just leave.
'Scuse me.
[SATOSHI]
Hey, Hotaro! How's it going?
Looks like you two
are as close as always.
Seems about right for the cutest
couple in middle school!
Ridiculous.
Don't be disgusting.
I'd rather date a slug
than this lowlife.
Out of your league.
Over the line, Fukube!
And you've got a lot
of nerve making a joke
when you're well
aware how I feel.
Ah, I'm sorry, Mayaka.
Hurt your feelings?
Do you even care
that you're pouring salt
into my wounds? Not cool.
Seriously. Have a heart, okay?
I don't understand
what's going on here.
She's had an
enormous crush on him
ever since middle school.
Oh!
[SATOSHI]
Ahem.
Chitanda, I'd like you
to meet Mayaka Ibara.
We all went to Kaburaya
Middle School together.
Nice to meet you!
[SATOSHI]
Mayaka, this is Eru Chitanda.
She's president of
the Classic Lit club,
which I joined recently.
Yes, indeed.
It's a real pleasure
to meet you.
So anyway, what brings
you two to the library?
Oh, right, I almost forgot!
So, uh, Ibara...
I was wondering if you
might be able to help us.
[MAYAKA]
I'll try.
Does the library happen to
have any old club anthologies?
Like Classic Lit Club, maybe?
Let me see.
I don't think so, actually.
At least not out here,
but maybe in the back.
Oh, okay.
So why are you
looking for them?
We've decided our
club should make one
for the culture festival.
So we wanted to look at past
anthologies to get some ideas.
Oh, yeah?
Are we gonna
present it at Kanyasai?
I can't believe
Hotaro agreed to that.
I was pressured into it,
as a matter of fact.
"Kanyasai?"
Abbreviation.
Kamiyama High Cultural Festival.
Is this another one
of those terms
you make up and try to coin?
No, for real!
That's what everyone
here in the school calls it,
not just me! Right?
Yeah, "Kanyasai" is what
they call it in Manga Club.
"Kanya"?
Wait, how do they
spell that, anyway?
I have no idea.
I've asked around but I
haven't gotten an answer.
I bet it started as,
Kamiyama High Bunkasai,
then shortened to, Kamiyama-sai.
Kaynama-sai. Kanyasai.
That's my hypothesis,
but who knows?
[MAYAKA]
Anyway, Chitanda.
There might be some
old anthologies
back in the storage stacks.
But the librarian is
in a meeting right now,
and we can't get back
there unless she unlocks it.
I think her meeting will be
done in about 30 minutes or so.
Wanna wait?
What should we do?
We should wait.
[MAYAKA] You could always
leave and come back.
[HOTARO]
Yeah, yeah.
Wait! Hotaro, hold up!
Hey, Mayaka.
You should tell these guys the
story that you told me earlier.
[MAYAKA]
Huh?!
[groans]
Hmph. Okay, fine.
Oreki. Do you feel like
using your tiny brain
for once in your life?
[HOTARO]
Nope.
What story are
you going to tell?
[SATOSHI] It's called the "Most
Favored Book of Disfavor."
[ERU] "The Most Favored
Book of Disfavor"?
[SATOSHI]
It's quite a peculiar tale.
No matter how I slice it,
it doesn't seem to add up.
It's got Mayaka and me
pretty much stumped.
Please, tell us
all of the details!
[MAYAKA] I report here
for duty every Friday
after school, you know?
And every week,
the same book gets returned,
like clockwork.
Today makes five weeks in a row.
That, in and of itself,
is kinda weird, right?
This is the book.
[ERU]
Wow, what a gorgeous book!
[HOTARO]
It's huge.
[ERU]
Is it okay if I look inside?
[MAYAKA]
Go ahead.
Oreki, you should see this.
[ERU] It's about the
school's history, huh?
I can't believe how dense it is.
This would be a
lot of work to read.
It's not weird for someone
to check this out every week.
They'd never finish.
You've obviously never borrowed
from the school's library.
The check-out period
here is a full two weeks,
instead of just one.
So why would someone need to
get it more often than that?
Nevertheless,
someone always does,
and turns it in every week, too.
[ERU] Do you have a
record of the borrowers?
Yeah, of course!
The checkout list
is in the front cover.
See?
[ERU]
Huh? Oreki, this is odd!
Each Friday, a different
person checks this book out,
but they always bring
it back that same day!
[MAYAKA]
Exactly.
This giant book has been
checked out and returned
every Friday, for
five weeks in a row now.
Even the times are consistent.
All five kids have come
to get it during lunch
and returned it after school.
[SATOSHI]
What do you think?
You're curious, right?
Yes.
I just... I have to know!
Let's try to figure
this out, Oreki.
You want to?
[HOTARO] Damn you, Satoshi.
You knew this would happen
when you stopped me
from leaving, didn't you?
I mean, you did such a great job
solving that
locked door mystery.
And then there was that strange
business with the secret club.
Wait, what are
you talking about?
She would be referring
to a rather provocative
facet of Hotaro, here.
Stop, you're making
it sound dirty!
In any case,
this is curious, right?
[HOTARO]
No, it's not.
Yes, it is!
Is not!
Enough!
Be quiet. Both of you.
[ERU]
Right.
[HOTARO]
Sorry.
I got reckless.
Any further refusal could
result in a careless waste
of precious energy.
That can't happen.
With that in mind...
Yeah, all right.
I guess I will
think about it, okay?
Great!
Fukube...
Has Oreki ever been
smart in his life?
No, not like us.
But he does have a knack
for solving problems,
which can come
in handy sometimes.
Hey, don't talk about
me like I'm not here.
[HOTARO]
For five weeks straight,
different people have
checked this book out,
and returned it
a few hours later.
Lesser minds might shrug
it off as a coincidence,
but Chitanda wouldn't be
content with that answer.
The truth isn't
what matters here.
What's important is satisfying
her burning curiosity.
Now, then...
Borrowing the book
at lunch hour,
then returning it after
school doesn't allow
sufficient time to read it.
If they didn't want
to lug around such a tome,
they could just read it in the
library without borrowing it.
Conclusion: this book
is not being utilized
for literary purposes at all.
They're not reading it.
What does that mean?
If a book's not
being used for reading,
what other purpose
could it serve?
If you stack them up,
they make decent pillows.
They make good
shields in combat, too.
Are you ever serious
about anything?
He's right; these people
can't be reading it,
so what could they
be doing with that book?
[SATOSHI] Well Chitanda,
what do you think?
Let me see.
Someone could use them
as weights in a workout.
[HOTARO]
You guys are no help at all.
[HOTARO] Is Chitanda really as
smart as everyone claims she is?
She seems like a
total doofus to me.
Let's try something else.
What does it mean
that a different person
borrows this book every week?
Well, from the names, we can
guess that they're all girls.
This brings up
two possibilities:
The girls have no connection.
It's en vogue to have this
book on Friday afternoons,
so they've all checked it
out on different occasions
by coincidence.
Or, the five of them
use the book together,
as a group, and
they each take turns
being the one to borrow
it every Friday.
"En vogue," huh?
For fortunetelling!
Right, like...
This book will be your
lucky charm on Friday,
so take it with you!
If you check it out
during your lunch period,
and return it after school,
your boyfriend will
plant a kiss on you!
Heck yeah!
Astounding.
That's the dumbest
thing I've ever heard.
I'm just brainstorming here.
[HOTARO] All they have in
common is that they're girls
and second years, though
all in different classes.
Why would the fact
that they're all girls
have anything to
do with this book?
Who knows, it might not.
Think about it:
If you randomly selected five
students from this school,
there's a pretty decent chance
they would all be female.
It's also pretty common
for members of the same sex
to stick together.
Well, what if they're using
it for some kind of code?
Like if they return it facing
up, it has a particular meaning.
Face down, then it
means something else?
[MAYAKA] I don't think that
would be a very effective
code at all.
[MAYAKA]
You see?
[SATOSHI]
She's right.
Any face-up, face-down code
would be lost in there.
Hmm...
Well, no matter
how hard he thinks,
Oreki's not gonna figure it out.
After all, Fukube and I racked
our brains and couldn't get it.
Hey, what's wrong?
It has a peculiar smell.
Wait, it does?
I don't smell anything.
[ERU]
I swear, it stinks.
There's some sort of acrid odor.
It's like paint thinner.
It's unmistakable.
[HOTARO]
Is she a dog?
Well, if Chitanda insists
she smells something strange
on that thing, then
it's worth looking into,
don't you think?
[HOTARO]
What could that mean?
Hotaro, if you've
cracked it open,
then you gotta say so.
Huh? Did you get it?
Calm down.
Maybe, but I'm not sure.
Hey, Chitanda, you
wanna get some exercise?
There's a lead I want
you to investigate.
Let's get right on it!
[HOTARO]
No, I'm not going this time.
It's just you.
Just me? Don't you need to go?
Well, I, uh...
Yeah, good job, Chitanda!
Hotaro has got no right
to use you like that!
He's at his best
when you're the one
taking advantage of him!
I'm not using anyone!
[ERU]
Oh, no, it's not like that.
I just figured we'd
investigate together.
Right. That makes sense.
What are you waiting
for then, huh?
Let's get going!
Thank you so much for coming.
We're honored to serve you.
We have prepared two
fine menus for you tonight.
Which one would you prefer?
[FEMALE GIGGLING VOICE]
[MALE GIGGLING VOICE]
[GIGGLING VOICES]
I recommend...
this dish for you.
[SATOSHI] This might end up
costing you more than you think.
Are you okay?
Let's go.
After all, gym class
got rained out today.
So I think I have exactly
enough energy to spare.
Great!
What kind of guy your age
has such a deficit of energy?
Shut up.
All right, come on, then.
[ERU]
Right.
[MAYAKA]
Hold on.
I'm going with you.
I'm kinda curious.
Fukube, would you watch
the desk till I get back?
[SATOSHI]
Huh?
[MAYAKA]
I mean, I can't just walk away
from my library duty, right?
[HOTARO]
You hold down the fort. Later.
Don't have too much fun.
So where are you taking us
to investigate now, Oreki?
[HOTARO]
To check out the art room.
Whoa, all the way over there?
Yep, it's far,
which is why I didn't want
to go in the first place.
You have to be the laziest
person I have ever met.
[ERU]
What's in the art room?
[HOTARO] First let's set
a few things straight.
I'm willing to bet
none of those girls
would have time to get any use
out of that book on a break.
It's too enormous for that.
Which means that they could
only really do anything
with it during class time.
What are the only
classes made up
of students who are
in the same year,
but in different homerooms?
Gym and all of the fine
arts subjects, right?
[HOTARO]
Yep.
So every week before class,
those five girls
have each taken turns
to come borrow the book.
I still don't understand
the timing, though.
I mean, they could check it out
for two weeks if they wanted.
[HOTARO]
The book is huge,
so they probably
just want it for class
rather than lug it around.
[MAYAKA]
Oh, that makes sense.
[ERU gasps]
[MAYAKA]
What is it?
It's the same smell
as the book!
Seriously?
Look in the room
and you'll see why.
[HOTARO] There's the answer
to your little mystery.
The second-year combined
D, E, and F classes
are just using it
in art as a prop
when they model for
portrait painting.
The book's binding makes it
an ideal, picturesque motif.
It was the smell
of paint. Not thinner.
How did you figure it out?
Huh? What do you mean?
It came to me, I guess.
I just got lucky.
[SATOSHI]
Wow, nicely done, my friend!
Students using it
as a prop for art class
is the last thing I ever
would have imagined.
I still don't
know how you did it.
You're just... weird.
No, I'm not.
I'm probably the most normal
person at this school.
Well... That's a bit strong.
Still, that's some
really impressive
detective work, Oreki.
I'm completely
fascinated by what goes on
inside that head of yours.
"Fascinated"?
Yes!
I'd just love to
crack open your skull
and pick your brain
sometime, you know?
That sounds like
a horror movie to me.
Plus, to an honor
student like you,
it's not that
remarkable of a brain.
[MAYAKA] Oh, yeah?
You're an honor student?
Let me put it this way:
We haven't had midterms yet,
but I'm sure when we do,
Chitanda's gonna be
at the top of our class!
No way.
It doesn't matter
how good my grades are.
That can't compare
at all to his raw ability.
Taking little clues and
piecing them together
into a lead that actually
pans out is just incredible.
[SATOSHI]
Huh...
[HOTARO]
Well, on that note...
Her senses of smell
and hearing fascinate me.
They're what solved
this mystery and the last.
Oreki might even...
be able to...
Hmm?
Uh... Oh! Uh... Nothing.
Anyway...
I had fun with this, even
though I missed the best part.
What about you?
[ERU]
Yeah, I had a blast!
The afternoon flew by
before I knew it!
I spent hours gripping over it
and I still couldn't
even get close!
It's so frustrating!
[SATOSHI] Didn't I tell you
he could come in handy
once in a while?
I can't stand the thought
of being outdone by Oreki!
My stupid life is
over now. Finished!
[SATOSHI] Come on,
it's not that bad!
[HOTARO]
It's odd.
Something just
doesn't feel right.
I can't ever see myself acting
like they are right now.
Why is that?
Is there something
wrong with me?
[SATOSHI]
Yeah, I know what you mean.
Once he's got the scent,
there's a brilliant flash,
and in an instant
he knows everything!
[ERU]
Oreki, you can't leave yet!
[HOTARO]
Why not?
Oh, right. The anthologies.
Yeah, we have to wait
till the librarian gets back.
Hotaro does kind of
zone out sometimes, huh?
Not just sometimes.
He's always out to lunch.
[ITOIGAWA] Ibara, thank you
for watching the desk for me.
You're free to go now.
[MAYAKA]
Oh, good.
It was my pleasure,
Miss Itoigawa.
Ma'am. My name is
Satoshi Fukube.
We're from the Classic Lit Club,
and we hoped you
might be able to help us.
Where could we find
the old anthologies?
Classic Lit? Anthologies?
You're in the
Classic Literature Club?
Well, unfortunately,
we don't currently have
any of the back-numbered
issues anywhere in the stacks.
[SATOSHI]
Are you sure about that?
If they were here, son,
trust me, I would know.
Now, if you'll
excuse me, I'm busy.
Huh. Well, thank you anyway.
I guess we're out
of luck, Chitanda.
This is a big problem.
We'll find them soon enough.
[MAYAKA]
So, Oreki.
Was it frustrating
not being able
to solve a problem for once?
Not really.
[MAYAKA]
Whatever.
[ERU] That's that, then.
We should go home.
I did learn something
helpful today, though.
Yeah, what's that?
Nothing.
It's a personal matter.
Oh, that again, huh?
Yeah.
Knowing Oreki, it might
be possible after all.
[phone ringing]
Hello? This is Oreki.
[ERU]
Good morning. Um, it's Chitanda.
Chitanda?
[ERU] Yeah, um, I'm
sorry if I woke you up.
Did I?
[HOTARO]
Oh, no.
I thought it might be
my sister or something.
[yawns]
So why are you
calling on a Sunday?
[ERU]
I'm sorry.
But I'd like to see you
today, if that's possible.
There's something I really
want to talk to you about.
[HOTARO]
She's late.
Hi. Thank you for waiting.
I rushed right over.
[HOTARO]
Uh-huh.
So, was there something
you wanted to talk about?
[ERU]
Huh?
I'm just curious as
to why you wanted
to meet me here at
this weird coffee shop.
You're the one who
recommended this place,
not me, Oreki.
[HOTARO]
Later.
[ERU]
Huh? No, please don't go.
[HOTARO] It's my precious
Sunday to do nothing.
I won't waste it sitting
in this place with you,
playing these games.
Look, I'm sorry!
It's just that...
I'm really nervous, okay?
What is there to be
so nervous about?
Are you about to
make a confession?
Tell me that you love me?
There may be something I'd
like to confess to you, yes.
[HOTARO]
Huh?
[ERU]
Next time:
"The Circumstances of the
Classic Lit Club's Scion."