[HOTARO]
Oreki residence.
[ERU]
Good morning. It's Chitanda.
Sorry to bother you
on a day off.
[HOTARO]
It's fine.
[ERU]
I know it's short notice,
but do you have any plans
for the day after tomorrow?
[HOTARO]
No.
[ERU]
Fantastic!
Listen, I know it's kind
of rude to ask you this
out of the blue, so no pressure,
but I was wondering, well, if--
You'd be willing to
carry my parasol.
Your what? Parasol?
[ERU]
That's right.
I'm not sure what you mean.
[ERU]
Oh. Sorry.
I didn't explain that
very clearly, did I?
Let me try again.
The shrine near my house
is hosting a Dolls' Festival
the day after tomorrow
and we need help.
Dolls' Festival?
But it's already April.
[ERU]
Ah, yes, I know.
This shrine goes by
the old calendar.
I'm only asking because
one of the parasol holders
had a freak accident
and can't do it.
They can't find anyone
who fits into his costume,
but you guys are the same size.
Wait...
You mean someone
holds it for them?
[ERU]
Yes.
It would mean the world to me
if you could help us out.
All right. I'll do it.
[ERU] You mean it?! I can't
thank you enough for this!
I just have to stand
next to them, right?
[ERU] Well, no, you have
to walk alongside them.
Walk with all the
dolls, you mean?
[ERU]
Yes, that's right.
[HOTARO]
So the dolls can walk?
[ERU]
Yes.
[HOTARO]
Are the dolls--
[ERU]
Oreki, please!
I'd appreciate it if you'd stop
saying "dolls" so much.
This is embarrassing
enough for me as it is.
They're not really
dolls, are they?
[ERU]
No.
It's Mizunashi Shrine's
Living Doll Festival.
The dolls are just
girls in costumes.
[HOTARO]
Oh.
[ERU] I've been participating
as one of the living dolls
for the past few years.
[HOTARO]
Head upstream along the brook
and take the Chokyu bridge
past the cherry tree.
Wow. That cherry tree.
It's blooming out of season.
[HOTARO] Did Chitanda really not
know there was construction?
Excuse me, mister.
Is it okay if I
ride across here?
Yeah, you're fine.
We're about to
start working, though.
You won't be able
to cross back.
[HOTARO]
Thanks.
Anyone here?
Hey, Hanai.
Where should I put these?
[HANAI] Oh, over in the hall,
if you don't mind.
[SONO]
Right.
[HOTARO]
'Scuse me.
[HANAI]
Who are you?
[HOTARO]
Hello, my name is Hotaro Oreki.
I'm supposed to be
carrying a parasol.
Hmm...
I guess Chitanda
didn't tell you about me?
I was asked to be a
replacement parasol-bearer.
Oh, you came to
take Hazawa's place?
I'm sorry about that.
Come right on in.
[FUKIYA] Hey, Hanai,
who's in charge of the saké?
[HANAI] I gave it to
Nakatake 'cause it rhymed.
[FUKIYA]
Hey, Nakatake, are we good?
We're good. It's on the way.
Never mind that. What about
the business this afternoon?
[FUKIYA]
I delegated it to the maid.
[HANAI]
Will that work?
Hey. Where are
the spare banners?
[KONARI]
In the hall.
[SONO]
Gotcha.
[HANAI]
So, Oreki.
Yes?
You're going to be
carrying a parasol
for Chitanda's daughter,
is that right?
As far as I know, yes.
[ASSISTANT 22A]
Hanai, sir! Telephone for you.
The newspaper.
Geez, for the love of--
[HOTARO]
I can't relax in here.
[YOSHIDA]
Nakatake!
What's going on with the saké?
They told me that
it'll be here at 1:00.
Are you a moron?!
The parade is over at 12:30!
1:00 is way too late!
Have them move it up!
[NAKATAKE]
Right away, sir.
[YOSHIDA]
For crying out loud.
Oh.
Uh... yes?
Who are you?
Oh, you must be that kid
Chitanda recommended.
[HOTARO]
Oh. Yes.
My name is Oreki.
Thanks a lot for
coming all the way here
to help us out.
We're shorthanded, but still...
Shame we had to bother
an outsider to carry
a damn parasol.
We appreciate your help,
young man.
Sincerely.
It's my pleasure, sir.
I'm sorry that a stranger
like me has to intrude.
I'll try my very best to
keep out of everyone's way.
If I do anything to offend,
please let me know immediately.
You sure are a
stalwart young man.
[HOTARO] First time
I've ever been called that.
[YOSHIDA]
Oreki, was it?
You just relax here
until we send for you.
[HANAI] What about the
parishioner representatives?
[FUKIYA]
Got it covered.
The kids?
The living dolls?
They need more time.
Fine.
Tanimoto, is the Chokyu
bridge good to go?
[TANIMOTO] Murai is
in charge of that now, sir.
[HANAI] Well, do you know if
they've halted construction,
at least?
[TANIMOTO]
Yes.
He assured me he
would take care of it.
Actually, they resumed
construction a little while ago.
[ALL gasp]
What did you say?
[HOTARO]
Hm?
Tanimoto!
You did follow up, didn't you?
[TANIMOTO] Well...
I reminded Murai about it.
[HANAI]
Oreki.
Are you positive about this?
[HOTARO]
Yes.
Sono!
[SONO]
Yes, sir?
[YOSHIDA] I hate to do this, but
take the truck and go make sure.
[SONO]
Yes, sir.
[YOSHIDA]
Tanimoto.
[TANIMOTO]
Yes, sir?
[YOSHIDA]
Call Murai.
Scratch that, get Nakagawa
Construction on the phone.
[TANIMOTO]
Yes, sir.
Will that cover it, Hanai?
What's the problem
with construction?
The procession is set
to cross Chokyu bridge.
[HOTARO]
Oh.
I really hope you're
mistaken about this one, kid.
[HOTARO]
What's he glaring at me for?
[footsteps]
It's true!
They've resumed construction!
[BOTH gasp]
Tanimoto! This falls on you!
No, there has to be some
kind of misunderstanding!
I'm positive that Murai called
the construction office earlier!
He specifically told them
not to start working today.
[HANAI]
Then why did they?
[TANIMOTO] I do know they got
a call the day before yesterday
to go ahead as planned, though,
so maybe that's why.
[HANAI]
From whom?
[TANIMOTO]
Well, I didn't ask them that.
I didn't think it mattered.
[SONO] The workers told
me a similar story just now.
Never mind the reason.
We have to deal
with this immediately.
[FUKIYA] There's gotta be a way
to get them to halt construction
before the parade.
[HANAI]
It's too late for that.
The TV crew is already
here and set up to shoot.
Plus, if someone
gets hurt, we're liable.
We'd better find
a way to reroute
and avoid it altogether.
[SONO] What if they
took the same route,
but doubled back instead
of crossing the river?
They could just stay
on the east bank.
[FUKIYA] That's great for
the people on the east side,
but what about all the folks
gathered on the west?
No dolls for them?
[TANIMOTO] Then what if they
go down to the bridge and back,
then cross over here and
then go up the west side?
[HANAI] Walking twice the
length of the current route
is out of the question.
[SONO] Then what about going
halfway to the bridge and back,
then crossing over
to the west side?
[HANAI] I refuse to do something
that ridiculous on live TV.
[SONO] So then what
do you propose we do?
[KONARI] We could have them
cross over at the Toji bridge.
If they cross
at the Toji bridge,
then back via Kaya bridge,
it only ends up being slightly
longer than the original route.
[ALL sigh]
[HANAI]
I don't know.
[FUKIYA]
I'm not sure about it either.
[MAID 22A]
Excuse me.
Is there someone here
by the name of Oreki?
Yes. That's me. What is it?
[MAID 22A] Chitanda's daughter
asked me to come get you.
[FUKIYA]
What does she want?
[SONO]
Who knows?
[ERU]
Oreki, is that you?
Yeah.
[ERU]
Sorry I can't come out and talk.
I'm not quite finished
getting dressed.
[HOTARO]
That is Chitanda, isn't it?
[ERU] I called you back
here to find out what's up.
Something has gone kind
of haywire, hasn't it?
[HOTARO]
Yeah.
[ERU]
Is it anything serious?
[HOTARO]
Yes, it is.
[ERU]
I see.
Can you fill me in
as much as possible?
There's not much time,
so talk fast.
[HOTARO] There's an
issue at Chokyu bridge.
So it's been proposed that we
cross at Toji bridge instead.
But not everyone agrees.
Are you listening?
[ERU]
Yes, I am.
When the others heard that,
for some odd reason they started
acting weird and scowling.
That's all.
[ERU] I must say, that was
an excellent retelling.
[HOTARO]
Thanks.
[ERU] Oreki, can I ask you to
relay a message for me?
[HOTARO]
Sure.
[ERU] I will speak to the other
shrine's priest about this
right away.
I am also going
to have my father
call the parishioner
representative.
Please tell them that.
So is that the whole message?
[ERU] Don't worry,
they will understand.
[HOTARO]
That's all she told me.
[ALL sigh]
[HANAI]
Okay, then that's what we'll do.
All right, everyone,
we'll take a detour
across the Toji bridge.
What are you waiting for?!
Start getting things
ready to go!
[ALL]
Right!
[HANAI]
Yes, Toji bridge. Did I stutter?
We already talked with Takahashi
in the traffic division!
[NAKATAKE]
Hey, Hanai,
the cameraman wants to know
where he should shoot from.
So, um, weren't you originally
slated to take over here?
Yeah, but I couldn't
fit into the costume.
[HOTARO]
Oh. I guess not.
Besides, this kind of
procession is a rare sight.
I came back home just for this.
If I'm in the parade,
I can't see it, right?
[HOTARO]
That's true.
[KONARI]
And, the finishing touch.
Well, what do you think?
Kinda sad, huh?
That's for sure.
[CROWD chattering]
[CROWD gasps]
It's freezing.
[HOTARO]
Oh, isn't that...?
I think that's Irisu.
[CROWD gasps]
[HOTARO]
Wow...
Aw, crap.
[HOTARO]
Not good...
This is not good!
[HOTARO] I'm rethinking
this entire thing.
What is the matter with me?
[HOTARO] My philosophy
of energy conservation
has encountered a deadly threat.
[HOTARO]
I can't see Chitanda.
I can't see how she looks.
I just... I have to know.
If I could see her
from the front...
Dressed up so beautifully...
Looking down so demurely...
What would happen then?
[SATOSHI]
Hotaro!
Man, that was fantastic!
Chitanda and Irisu's elegance
was absolutely unmatched!
[MAYAKA] They were so
gorgeous, weren't they?
[SATOSHI] Where are Chitanda
and the other dolls now?
[HOTARO]
Main building.
They said something about
purging their impurity.
By the way, buddy,
that outfit did not suit you
at all, just saying.
Man, shut up.
For real, it was
wasted on you.
Fine, keep running your mouths.
I'm gonna go get another
one of these things.
Oreki, I wanted to thank you.
Yeah, for what?
For the Valentine's thing.
I haven't had a chance
to tell you until now.
Sure.
How's it been going since?
[MAYAKA]
Well, not too bad.
[HOTARO]
That's good.
I snapped at him
for that, you know.
It's not very often that
I really lay into him.
Mm-hmm. I heard.
Oh. Hey, there, Irisu.
Oh. Hello, Oreki.
Weren't you the emperor doll?
[IRISU]
That's a long story.
And speaking of those, I heard
about the Chokyu bridge.
[IRISU] A lot of it sounds a
bit suspect, if you ask me.
What do you think?
Huh... Uh...
I guess it does, sure,
but I don't know.
[IRISU]
I see.
I thought you'd be
the first person
to try his hand at
solving the mystery.
Don't do that, please.
[IRISU]
Oreki.
In that situation, I had
a specific role to play.
And in this one,
I'm just the emperor doll.
And since I have no
stake in any of this,
I won't mislead you.
Oh.
[CROWD chattering]
[footsteps]
Oh, Oreki.
Oreki!
What? What's wrong?
Today was just awful!
I've been forced to hold
it in this whole time!
Yeah, you're a real trooper.
I couldn't.
Not that, silly,
the Chokyu bridge!
The business with
Nakagawa Construction!
Oh, okay, right.
[ERU]
I've been obsessing about it,
but since I had a part
to play, I couldn't let on.
I was dying to ask
about it the whole time.
What I mean is--
You just have to know, huh?
That's right!
You must have drawn up
some conclusion
about everything that happened.
Well, yeah, I do
have a suspect in mind.
Oh, good, so do I.
Why don't we write it down
and reveal our theories
to each other at the same time?
That's fine with me,
but write on what?
[ERU giggling]
Here.
[HOTARO giggling]
[ERU]
Okay, good to go?
Ready, set, reveal!
Oh, Konari's son
does have brown hair,
as a matter of fact.
We're thinking
of the same person?
Yes.
I'm curious:
why did you suspect him?
[HOTARO] First of all,
it seems pretty clear
that they got a call saying
to come to work today, right?
[ERU]
Yes, I believe so.
[HOTARO] Okay, then who would
have made that phone call?
Everyone was running around
like crazy here today.
There was only one person
who seemed totally sure
we wouldn't be able to
cross the Chokyu bridge.
[ERU] And you're saying
that was Konari's son?
[HOTARO]
Yeah.
He helped me get
into my costume.
He told me that
he came back home
just for this, and he said
that this kind of procession
is a rare sight to see.
[ERU]
Did he really?
[HOTARO] Yeah, and I
thought that was weird.
They do this every year, right?
If he's from here,
why would this procession
be so rare to him?
[ERU] You're right,
that's an odd thing to say.
[HOTARO] However, a "rare sight"
did happen today.
Do you know what it was?
[ERU] Well, for one,
they altered the route.
Doing that took us
to the Toji bridge.
Oh, the cherry tree!
Yes, and it was
blooming out of season.
We'd only get to see
it by taking the route
we ended up with.
The spectacle of a
parade of living dolls
passing under cherry blossoms?
That is what I'd call a
"rare sight to see."
That's a frivolous motive.
[HOTARO]
I wouldn't call it that.
Um, Oreki?
But who knows what
he was really thinking.
Why did you suspect him too?
Well, I know him.
And he's...
Konari's son is the only
person around here
who would put so many people
through all that stress
without thinking twice
about their feelings.
[HOTARO]
That makes sense.
[ERU] But couple that
with your theory,
and I am totally convinced.
[HOTARO]
What do you mean?
[ERU] Apparently, his lifelong
dream is to be a photographer.
He is going to vocational school
to study it, as far as I know.
[HOTARO]
Ah, so that's why.
I'm sure he just wanted to get
a photo of such a "rare sight."
Could be.
[ERU]
Hey, Oreki.
Remember in my dressing
room when I mentioned
contacting the other
shrine's priest?
Yeah.
That was what finally calmed
all the chaos, you know.
It may seem kind of trivial,
but hear me out, would you?
'Kay.
[ERU] A long time ago,
this area was divided
into two halves:
north and south.
The north half was our village,
and the south was another.
There were lots of disputes
over water and territory.
And though that
was so long ago,
for a solemn ritual like this,
crossing over without permission
would be a major source
of contention, even now.
[HOTARO]
Ah, so that was a big deal.
[ERU] They wanted to let
them know ahead of time,
but there aren't many
people who even know
what channels to use
to make that call.
[HOTARO] And that's
where you stepped in.
[ERU] Once I talked
to the other side,
we were free to go that far
south with peace of mind.
[HOTARO]
I see.
No wonder Satoshi calls
your family "prestigious."
I wouldn't go that far.
It's fascinating.
All I did was act as a liaison
between the north
and south sides
of a little community
north of Kamiyama.
I don't think it's something
grandiose or monumental,
but I wouldn't dismiss it
as insignificant, either.
[HOTARO]
Interesting.
You may have a point there.
[ERU] If I manage
to get into college,
I'm still gonna come
back here eventually.
No matter where life
takes me, in the end,
my place will always be here.
I love this place.
So, Oreki...
What did you choose for your
second year? Science or lit?
[HOTARO] Oh, I chose lit.
Seemed right.
[ERU]
Oh, yeah?
Well, I chose science.
[HOTARO]
You did?
I'm not depressed
about coming back here.
It's actually quite the
contrary, as a matter of fact.
As the daughter of
the Chitanda family,
I want to fulfill the role
I was born to play.
It suits me.
I've given a lot of thought
to how I might best
be able to do it.
You have? Good.
I see two ways, really.
One of those is to
help us all prosper
by developing a commodity
that's extremely marketable.
The other way would be
to make our production
more efficient, working from
a managerial standpoint,
with the goal of
wasting nothing at all.
Ultimately, I think the former
is the more appropriate
path for me.
[HOTARO] Which is why
you chose science?
[ERU]
Yes.
[HOTARO] Yeah, I definitely
don't think you're cut out
for the latter path, no offense.
That was a lesson
that I learned
during the cultural festival,
when I saw how I was
driving everyone crazy.
I don't think I have the
skillset needed to manage
a bunch of employees.
That's for sure.
Good for you.
Just look at
all of this, Oreki.
I know this is
where I belong.
There's nothing here but
the water and the earth.
The people who live here will
slowly grow old and tired.
It's not the most beautiful
place in the world by any means.
And I don't even believe
it has very much potential.
But still...
I just felt compelled
to share it with you, Oreki.
[HOTARO]
By the way...
As far as the
managerial perspective
that you determined
wasn't for you...
What if I were to take
on that task for myself?
By the way what?
Finish that thought.
Oh. Uh, nothing.
I...
[HOTARO] I wonder if
this is how Satoshi felt.
Afraid to spoil it
by saying too much.
It's starting to
get cold, huh?
No. It's spring, silly.