[SATOSHI]
If what you suspect is true,
it means that our
Kanyasai came at the cost
of somebody's
high school career.
That's pretty major.
You surprised me, you know.
How'd I do that?
I wouldn't expect
you to put effort
into solving a
mystery like this.
Yeah, I didn't
expect it either.
[SATOSHI] Funny thing is,
it's not even the first mystery
you've solved since
high school started.
And I think I know why you're
going to all this trouble.
It's for Chitanda.
[HOTARO]
It's her fault, all right.
Put it how you want.
You do this stuff 'cause of her.
I mean, you could've
bailed on us today.
The responsibility for
unraveling that mystery
was split between
the four of us.
If you'd said "I've got no
clue" and left it at that,
I doubt anyone
would've blamed you.
Instead, you locked
yourself in the bathroom
until you could come up
with an answer.
Why do something like that
if not to help Chitanda?
Couldn't tell you.
Maybe I'm just tired of
my little black cloud.
[sighs] I don't know
anyone in this world
less energy efficient
than Chitanda.
Being a club president,
taking midterms,
writing an anthology,
solving riddles from the past?
I'm surprised
she isn't exhausted.
Same thing goes
for you and Ibara.
All of you just do
so much, you know?
It seems wasteful.
Yeah. To you, maybe.
The thing is...
I'm starting to wonder if you
might have the right idea.
Sometimes when I watch you guys,
it makes me feel restless.
And I don't like that feeling.
I mean...
All I wanna do is relax.
Except relaxing's begun
to feel boring lately.
So I thought, why not?
I'll give it a try.
I'll really get
invested in something,
the way you guys do.
Maybe it'll make
for a nice change.
[HOTARO]
Well, say something!
[SATOSHI]
Hotaro...
Are you starting to see
that living a sunny life
isn't so bad after all?
Yeah, maybe.
A sunny life. Huh.
At the end of the day,
is that really what I want?
I don't know.
Chitanda's search
for the truth...
Jun Sekitani's battle
for the Kanyasai...
Am I cut out for
that kinda thing?
Is that the type
of person I want to be?
I don't know.
What does it even mean
to have a sunny life?
I don't know.
[HOTARO] Then there's my sister,
the queen of sunshine.
[HOTARO]
"This has been a lot of fun,
and I know I'll look back in
10 years and be glad I did it."
[HOTARO]
Ten years from now,
how will I feel when
I look back at my life?
Jun Sekitani wouldn't
have any regrets. But me?
[phone ringing]
[HOTARO]
Hello, Oreki residence.
[TOMOE]
Hotaro? That you?
Hey, sis, you're
still alive, huh?
[TOMOE]
Don't underestimate me!
You think I can't survive
a mugging or two?
So that's the kind of trouble
you're getting yourself into.
[TOMOE] I just reached
Pristina yesterday.
Nothing in particular to report.
I'll send another letter that
way once I get to Sarajevo.
How are things on your end?
[HOTARO] We're working on
the anthology. Hyouka .
[TOMOE]
Oh, yeah? Good!
[HOTARO] We've been
looking into Jun Sekitani.
[TOMOE]
Jun Sekitani?
There's a name
that takes me back!
So his story is
still going around.
Is "Kanyasai" still off-limits?
Sorry, what'd you say?
[TOMOE] What a tragedy, huh?
The poor kid.
Wait. Off-limits?
Tragedy? The poor kid?
Hold on a sec, I'm
talking about Jun Sekitani.
[TOMOE]
Yeah, so am I.
The so-called
kindhearted hero, right?
That's who you mean, isn't it?
Well... I'm not
so sure anymore.
What else can you tell me
about Jun Sekitani?
[TOMOE]
Nothing right now. I gotta go!
[HOTARO]
Hey! Wait!
So not cool, Tomoe!
[grunts]
[HOTARO]
I've still got work to do.
I presented my theory
to the others, but...
It's either incorrect,
or incomplete.
If he's still alive,
does Jun Sekitani
have any regrets about
his time in high school?
I wouldn't have thought
there'd be any reason to.
He was a hero.
He left school as a
martyr for what he thought
was a noble cause.
He was totally happy
to fall on his sword.
Or at least that's
how I imagined it.
But is that really
how it happened?
To be kicked out of
school over a festival
and have a whole phase
of his life altered?
High school's all
sunshine and roses.
But having your high-school
experience cut short
because you and your friends
wanted a longer festival?
That doesn't exactly
sound sunny or rosy to me.
We're missing something.
How many people could
sacrifice everything
and not feel a bit of
resentment or regret?
What's more,
sis called it a tragedy.
She felt sorry for him.
Was Jun Sekitani's high school
life really all that sunny?
[HOTARO]
I've gotta figure this out.
[MAYAKA]
Oh, hey, Fuku.
[SATOSHI]
Hey...
So you got marching orders
from Hotaro too, I take it?
[MAYAKA] Mm-hmm. We all have
to meet up in the clubroom
to talk about something.
[SATOSHI] I can't believe he's
actually calling a meeting.
I guess this means that,
somewhere, pigs are flying.
[MAYAKA]
I hope it doesn't take long.
I'm busy with Manga Club.
Oh, hey you two.
Thank you again for
your help yesterday.
[MAYAKA] Sure.
Honestly, it was kinda fun.
[SATOSHI]
So... No sign of Hotaro?
Not yet.
Here's the man himself.
[HOTARO]
You all made it.
What did you wanna talk about?
[HOTARO] It's the whole
Jun Sekitani thing.
I don't think we've
completely settled it all yet.
What? Are you kidding me?
So, Oreki. What's up?
I don't really think you would
call a meeting like this
unless something
important was going on.
It's all right.
There are some
gaps in the story,
but I think we can fill them in.
Great!
Well, let's get on with this.
What do you mean by "gaps"?
By gaps I mean gaps.
There are still a few
tiny holes in our theory
about Chitanda's uncle,
and I'm trying to close them.
[SATOSHI]
Hold on.
Are you suggesting that
your theory was incomplete?
I don't know.
I mean either we went off
in the wrong direction
or we didn't go far enough.
You don't know?
You called us in
to say you don't know?
--Seriously?
--Just listen.
I think we should've
given more weight
to what it said in Hyouka .
It clearly states
in the foreword
that Jun Sekitani's story
is in no way a heroic tale.
We read that but excluded
it from our deliberations.
Because it seemed like
it was just an opinion
and not a fact.
Yeah, but I think maybe we
shouldn't have excluded it.
It's a little late for th--
Look at this. What does it say?
"The struggles
that were endured.
The sacrifices that were made."
Does it really
mean "sacrifices"?
It can also be read
as "offerings," right?
Except "offerings"
is spelled differently.
It starts with the
character for "alive."
No. It can be read as either
"sacrifice" or "offering."
Originally the two
meant the same thing.
There you go.
Our resident academic
genius has spoken.
[SATOSHI] Okay, great, so it
could mean one of two things.
But only the person who
wrote it knows for sure
which one it is.
The best that we're
going to be able to do
is make an educated guess.
Not true.
We can go to the source.
Wait, "the source"?
[HOTARO] The person
who wrote the foreword.
Yoko Koriyama.
Forty-five years ago she was
a first-year in high school,
so today she'd be around 60.
You looked for her, then?
Where is she?
A lot closer than you
would probably think.
Right, library assistant?
No way! Seriously?
Yep.
Seriously what?
Would you please just tell us?
It's our librarian.
That's who you mean, right?
She's Yoko Itoigawa,
but she used to be
Yoko Koriyama.
[HOTARO]
That's right.
She has a unique way
of spelling her first name.
And she looks around 60,
which is just about how old
the foreword's author
would be at this point.
And let's not forget
how she reacted
when she found out we were
in the Classic Lit Club.
Wow, you are
freaky good at this.
I mean, I've been working
with her this whole time
and the name thing never
even occurred to me.
Really. You should donate your
brain to science or something.
Like I've said before,
I'm not doing anything special.
It's just luck, that's all.
So nobody needs to go poking
around in my brain, okay?
Okay, so then...
If we go and ask Miss
Itoigawa about all of this...
We'll find out what
happened 45 years ago.
Why it was in no way
a heroic tale.
Why the picture on the
anthology cover is what it is.
Why they chose
the name Hyouka .
And also, what really
happened to your uncle.
Sure, it's possible
that Miss Itoigawa
is who we're looking for,
but do you have any solid proof?
Of course I do.
In fact,
I've confirmed it already.
What, with her?
Yeah. She said that when
she was a second-year,
she was the club president.
I set up an appointment
so we could all talk to her.
Actually, it's
almost time for it.
We should probably start
heading to the library.
Just admit it. You're pumped!
Maybe I am.
Hi, Miss Itoigawa!
Hi there, Classic Lit Club.
I still have a bit
of shelving to get done.
You don't mind if we
talk out here, do you?
No problem. I'll help you.
[ITOIGAWA]
Thank you, Ibara.
Now, then, you said
there was something
you wanted to ask me about.
Yes.
But before we go any further,
Miss Itoigawa,
could you do me
a favor and confirm
for my fellow club members
here that your maiden name
is, in fact, Yoko Koriyama?
Yes.
[HOTARO] So... You're the
one who wrote this, then?
Why, yes, I did write it.
A long time ago.
I'm surprised to see it
unearthed like this.
I think I might know what
it is you want to ask me.
Unless I'm mistaken,
you're curious about the
protests that occurred
45 years ago.
[HOTARO] I was right.
She's got the info we need.
[ITOIGAWA]
But what I don't understand
is why anyone is
asking about it now.
I thought everyone would
have forgotten about it
by this point.
[HOTARO]
Yeah.
If Chitanda wasn't such
a crazy curiosity monkey,
I seriously doubt that
we'd all be here asking you
about it right now.
A crazy curiosity monkey?
[HOTARO]
Sorry. I meant curiosity junkie.
[ERU]
Either way, Oreki,
that's not very nice.
Well, whatever the case may be,
why are you kids so interested
in what happened back then?
Because Jun Sekitani...
You see ma'am, he's my uncle.
[ITOIGAWA]
Oh, really, your uncle, huh?
Jun Sekitani. That name
brings back memories.
How is he doing these days?
[ERU]
I don't know.
He left for India,
and then he went missing.
I'm sorry to hear that.
You know, I'd always
hoped I'd be able
to see him again someday.
Yeah, me too.
I would like to see him
again so very much.
[ERU] Miss Itoigawa...
Will you please tell us?
Just what happened here
all those years ago?
Why was the story involving
my uncle not a heroic one?
Why is the club's
anthology called Hyouka ?
How much of Oreki's theory
about the protest is correct?
I'm sorry, Oreki's theory?
What exactly does that mean?
[SATOSHI]
Well, you see...
Oreki pieced together
some information
and came up with a possible
outline of what went down
during the protest
all those years ago.
I'm sure he'll
tell you all about it
if you don't mind listening.
[ITOIGAWA]
Sure.
Why don't we talk about
this more in my office?
[ITOIGAWA]
Very interesting.
And that's why you assume
his expulsion was delayed
until October; they wanted
to let the tension die down?
Yes, that's my
conjecture anyway.
And you put
together this theory
from nothing more than
the material you have here?
Everyone else did the real work.
I just summarized it.
[SATOSHI laughs]
Well, I'm truly astounded.
[HOTARO]
Am I way off base?
[ITOIGAWA] No! It's like
you witnessed it yourself.
What you describe is almost
exactly how it happened.
I'm not sure what more
I can tell you about it,
to be honest.
Well, um...
Hotaro seems to think that
something about his theory
is either wrong or incomplete.
There's just one thing
I'm not totally sure about.
Did Jun Sekitani willingly take
the hit for the other students
who were involved?
Did he make a brave stand,
holding his head high
as he knowingly sacrificed
his whole high school career
for the greater good
of the protest movement?
Quite impressive.
You see right
through things, eh?
Well...
It was a very long time ago now,
but I still remember
it so clearly.
The high school cultural
festival was a very big deal.
For a lot of kids, it seemed
like the only purpose in life.
In those years, it was
almost as if students
were channeling the
nation's restless energy
and using the festival as
an outlet for self-expression.
But the year I started school,
that restless energy
became more agitated,
and we found ourselves at
the edge of a full-blown riot.
That year the principal
dropped a bombshell, saying:
"We can't content ourselves
with being a small-time school
in a sleepy little town."
Everyone was afraid that
meant the cultural festival
would be abolished.
It wasn't, but the
principal did inform us
that the festival would
last for only two days,
rather than the normal five.
That announcement triggered
an unprecedented uproar.
The whole school was on edge.
People hung banners
and made speeches.
They cried out about
injustice and autonomy,
hoping to bend the
administration to their will.
Sounds like they
were very committed.
Yeah!
Those kids weren't
afraid to stand up
for what they
really cared about.
[ITOIGAWA chuckles]
Honestly, it wasn't
as noble as all that.
I'd say it was more like
someone had threatened
to take away our toys,
so we were throwing
a tantrum about it.
[MAYAKA]
Really?
[ITOIGAWA]
Yes.
That's how it seems,
looking back on it now.
At any rate, we formed
a sort of coalition
to protest the shortening
of the cultural festival.
Nobody wanted to be
the official leader.
Pathetic as it sounds,
we were all too afraid
of being punished.
Jun Sekitani drew
the short straw.
He wound up as the scapegoat
for the whole movement.
Somebody else was
actually running the show
behind the scenes.
But he never made
his name public.
The administration would
give in to us eventually,
but we didn't know that.
We'd whipped ourselves
into a self-righteous frenzy
as only the young can.
And in the end, we went too far.
In addition to all
the rallies and speeches,
students were
boycotting classes.
And then, as part of a
demonstration one night,
we built a bonfire to
show how serious we were.
That's when it happened.
The fire spread to the
combat sports building.
Despite firefighting efforts,
it was partially destroyed.
At that point,
the school couldn't
possibly look the other way.
Rather than involve the police,
they conducted their
own investigation.
Since almost all the
students were involved
with the movement, they couldn't
very well punish everyone.
Instead, they settled
for making an example
of the movement's nominal
leader, Jun Sekitani.
Eventually, he was found guilty
and expelled from the school.
The rest of us did nothing.
We just sat back and
watched as it happened.
But, despite our cowardice,
Sekitani never
broke his silence.
That's what you wanted
to know about, right?
Whether he volunteered
himself as a sacrifice
for the other students?
I assume that answers the
question for you, then.
The years passed,
and sure enough,
the cultural festival
was shortened anyway,
a little bit at a time.
Now it only lasts
for three days.
Well, that's the
end of my story,
unless you have
any other questions
that you'd like to ask me.
I have one.
The drawing on the
anthology's cover
is supposed to symbolize
what happened, right?
The dog is the school.
The rabbits are the students.
And the rabbit fighting
the dog is Jun Sekitani.
The combat sports
building is by far
the oldest facility
we have at Kami High.
Is that because it
was rebuilt back then?
[ITOIGAWA]
That's right.
So 20 years ago when
the rest of the school
was remodeled, that building
was still new enough
that it didn't need to be
fixed up like the others.
You know,
I've noticed something.
Most people call the
cultural festival Kanyasai,
but you don't.
I was wondering...
The way "Kanya" is
written in "Kanyasai"...
Does it stand for "Sekitani"
instead of "Kamiyama"?
I don't understand
what you're saying.
The origin of
the term Kanyasai.
They took "Sekitani-sai"
and switched the reading
to make it "Kanyasai"
to honor Jun.
Oh.
Except calling it
that's kind of misleading,
since Jun Sekitani was
really more of a victim
than a hero.
Something tells me
if people knew that,
they probably wouldn't
even use the term Kanyasai.
So is that really true?
[ITOIGAWA]
Yes.
As a matter of fact,
we banned that name
in the Classic Lit Club.
And the title?
Do you have any idea why
my uncle chose Hyouka
to be the title of
the club's anthology?
We're still missing
that piece of the puzzle.
I don't know.
Sekitani could sense he
was going to be expelled,
and he was uncharacteristically
intent on using that title,
so how could we argue?
He said that it was the
only thing left he could do.
I'm sorry, but...
If it does mean something,
I don't know what.
You really don't know?
[HOTARO]
How is that even possible?
Nobody ever figured it out?
I mean...
The message was obvious.
Wanna tell us
what you're thinking?
[HOTARO] The story we
just heard makes it clear
what the anthology's
title means.
Hyouka is wordplay,
plain and simple.
It's wordplay?
[HOTARO] Jun Sekitani wanted
to leave an enduring message
about what happened to him,
something that would resonate
for decades to come.
So he put it right there
in the title of the anthology.
[ERU]
I still don't get it.
If you know what Hyouka means,
will you please just tell us?
Yeah, out with it already!
[SATOSHI]
Come on, Hotaro.
Uh, Hotaro?
How do you translate
Hyouka into English?
I think it's "ice cream."
Isn't it?
Ice cream? Okay.
That's not much of
a message, though.
[HOTARO] Like I said
before, it's wordplay.
Hey. You guys... I don't...
[HOTARO]
This is it.
The real statement that
Jun Sekitani was making.
Yes. I remember now.
I went to my uncle, and asked
if he'd tell me
what Hyouka meant.
He told me.
And then he also said...
Right.
He said that I had to be strong.
And that if I was ever
weak, if someday...
Yes. If a day ever came
when I couldn't even scream...
If that day came... Then...
I would be eaten alive.
[ERU] And that's why
I started to cry.
I was terrified of
being eaten alive.
[ERU] I remember.
Finally, I remember!
Now... I can let my uncle go.
And it's all
thanks to you, Oreki.
Thank you so very much.
I mean it!
Yeah, well...
It was just luck.
Okay. If you say so.
Just luck.
Ice cream. I scream.
It all depends on
how you say it, huh?
[MAYAKA]
Okay.
I drew up an outline
and a schedule
for writing the anthology.
Wow, thanks for putting
all this together, Mayaka!
It's an incredible outline!
Oh. Uh, is it?
Absolutely!
Where'd you learn to make
a storyboard like this?
[laughs] Just something
I picked up, I guess.
Wait a sec.
I've got a question
about this special feature.
The one you call "The Case
of the Kindhearted Hero:
The Truth that was Hidden
for Forty-Five years."
What's wrong?
How did I end up being
in charge of writing it?
Come on, Oreki,
you're the one who
solved the mystery.
It only makes sense.
It's the longest story
in the whole thing.
Of course it is.
It's the anthology's
featured article.
I know it's a
big responsibility.
If you'd prefer, I can try
to take it on myself, instead.
Yeah. That sounds grea--
[MAYAKA]
No, don't do it, Chi!
We've got to put Mr.
Lazy Bones to work somehow,
and this is our best chance.
[laughs]
Yeah, right.
We don't want him
getting complacent.
Don't waste time
complaining, Oreki.
Just get to work
on your outline.
Now, Fuku, about the article
you'll be writing...
[ERU]
You know, I'm kind of surprised.
[HOTARO]
About what?
[ERU] That you accepted
the anthology assignment
Mayaka gave you.
Can you really
call it "accepting"
if somebody forces
you to do something?
[HOTARO]
Well...
I guess Jun Sekitani would know
all about that, wouldn't he?
[HOTARO] Y'know...
You surprised me, too.
[ERU]
How?
[HOTARO]
When this whole thing started,
I suggested that you
ask Satoshi and Ibara
to help you out with it.
You didn't seem to like
the idea much at first,
so what made you change
your mind about it?
[ERU]
It's hard to explain.
I'm sure it had something to do
with what you said to me before.
About how we would
probably need help
if we were going
to solve the mystery
before my uncle's funeral.
I know it's possible
that 10 years from now,
I won't care so
much about all this.
But I'm just not sure that's
a gamble I'm willing to take.
Whether or not things
change as time passes,
what I'm feeling now is real.
I can't pretend those
feelings don't matter.
I want to live my
life in the present.
Not the future.
Which is why...
I'm babbling, huh?
Sorry, I'm still trying
to figure it all out.
That's okay.
I can understand that.
Well at least we
solved the mystery.
Yeah. Well, see ya.
[HOTARO]
"Hey there, sis.
I'm writing because I've
got some questions for you.
How much did you know
about the Classic Lit Club?
And why was it so important to
you that I get involved with it?
You know I'm an
energy conservationist.
That's just my way of living.
If I hadn't joined the
Classic Lit Club this year,
I probably wouldn't have
given that a second thought.
Is that why you
wanted me to do it?
Did you know somehow
that it would force me
to reconsider my
priorities in life?
This whole Hyouka thing.
It's got me wondering.
Am I doing things right?
Does being more
passionate about stuff
make life more exciting
or just more heartbreaking?
I dunno. Maybe it's both.
That's always possible.
Did you know I'd start
wondering about this stuff?"
[chuckles]
No, that's silly.
"Anyway, that's all I've
got to report for now.
I'll go ahead and
wrap this letter up.
Have a nice trip.
And thanks for the advice.
Your brother, Hotaro."
[HOTARO] Next time:
"Committing a Cardinal Sin."