[HOTARO]
Excuse me.
Could I get another
cup of coffee?
[ERU]
Right.
Okay. The truth is...
Here goes! I need help!
I have a favor to ask you!
[HOTARO]
Huh?
I... Huh?
A favor?
[ERU]
Yes.
It's a personal matter
and not really something
I would normally talk about,
but I've given it a lot
of thought and decided
that you might
be able to help me.
I know it's asking a lot,
but will you please
at least hear me out?
Well... I guess
I can manage that.
[ERU]
Thank you.
[ERU] So, the favor
I wanted to ask you
has to do with my uncle,
Jun Sekitani.
See, he told me something once--
Something that was
really important.
And I want you to help me
remember what it was.
Yeah, I'm not
really following you.
I'm sorry. I'm telling
this story all wrong.
I guess I'm just not
used to talking about it.
The first thing you should
know is that my uncle
went to India seven years ago.
And he's been
missing ever since.
I was very fond of him
when I was a little girl.
Unlike most other adults,
he would answer all my questions
no matter how silly they seemed.
He was so smart!
It seemed to me that there
was nothing he didn't know.
When I was in kindergarten,
I learned that my uncle
was in the Classic Lit Club.
That's when I became
interested in it.
I especially liked it
because the name reminded me
of the vinegar kelp
we ate at home.
[HOTARO]
Seriously?
[ERU]
Anyway...
One day I asked my
uncle about something
having to do with
the Classic Lit Club.
And for the first
time I can remember,
he was reluctant
to answer my question.
[HOTARO]
So, what'd you do?
[ERU] Well... I threw a huge
tantrum, to be honest.
And I did convince him to
answer my question eventually.
But when he told me
what I wanted to know, I...
[HOTARO]
Yeah? You what?
I started to cry.
I don't know if it was because
I was scared or sad or what,
but I was bawling.
Okay.
The sound must've
startled my mom
because she came rushing
in to see if I was okay,
but my uncle...
He didn't do anything
to comfort or reassure me.
Afterwards, I couldn't remember
what my uncle had said,
only my reaction to it.
I guess I was in shock.
Then, when I was
in middle school,
I started wondering about that
strange conversation again.
What made my uncle so
hesitant to answer me?
Why didn't he react
when I was upset?
I still have so many questions.
I just want answers.
And I've tried to get them.
We've become estranged
from the Sekitani family,
and I haven't been able to
get in touch with them at all.
No matter what I do, I can't
remember what he said!
So when I started at Kami High,
I signed up for
the Classic Lit Club.
I figured it would
be my last chance
to get to the
bottom of everything.
So that's the "personal matter"
you're always talking about?
This is it.
Of course, I had no way
of knowing that the club
was about to be shut down.
I asked around in
the faculty room,
but there weren't any
teachers who remembered
a Jun Sekitani
from 45 years ago.
'Kay.
I still don't get why you're
asking me for help, though.
Because you...
You think about
things differently.
You have this way of
reaching conclusions
that would have
never occurred to me.
Like with the lock.
And the library book.
And that secret club
recruitment note!
You can do this, Oreki!
If anyone can help me find
the answers I'm looking for,
it's you!
You're really giving
me too much credit.
That other stuff was
just luck, that's all.
I don't care if it's
just luck; I'll take it!
I don't want to.
[HOTARO] This is a
big deal to Chitanda.
She's spent years obsessing
over this question.
There's no telling how much
learning the answer to it
might affect her.
And she's asking someone
like me to take on
a responsibility like that?
She's gotta be kidding.
I still don't get
why you picked me.
There's gotta be
some other people
who can help you
with this, right?
Strength in numbers might
be your best bet, ya know.
Ask a bunch of your
friends to help,
and I'm sure you'll
get it done in no time.
[ERU]
Maybe you haven't noticed,
but I'm kind of
a private person.
I don't talk about
my past very much.
This story... isn't the kind of
thing I can tell just anybody.
[HOTARO]
Sorry.
I know I'm asking a lot of you,
and maybe it's not fair.
I realize I probably
shouldn't be dragging you
into my own personal
drama like this.
It's just...
You answer all my questions,
just like my uncle used to.
Even if you aren't
quite as personable.
[HOTARO] Well, that's one
way to ask for a favor.
[ERU] I see something of
him when I look at you.
And that makes me think
I can trust you, somehow.
[HOTARO]
What's the rush?
You've got three whole
years of high school
to spend looking for
an answer, don't you?
I really don't think I'll have
anywhere near that much time.
Not if I want all of this
settled before his funeral.
[HOTARO]
I thought he was missing.
[ERU]
Yes.
But if someone's been
missing for seven years
and no one knows if
they're alive or dead,
it's possible to have them
declared legally deceased.
[HOTARO]
I didn't know that.
Declaring him dead
would put the matter to rest
and give my uncle's
family some closure.
I heard that they also intend to
hold a small funeral service.
So you see...
That's why I'm in such a hurry!
I want to know the truth
about our conversation.
Before I say goodbye.
For the last time.
I'm sorry.
[TOMOE]
Come on, Hotaro.
It's not like you have
anything better to do.
This is not really
the kinda thing
that I want responsibility for.
So I wanna be totally clear
that I'm not agreeing
to see this all the way through.
But I will keep
your story in mind.
And if I come across anything
that might give you some clues,
I'll be sure to
tell you about it.
And if you find out anything new
that you want me to know about,
I'm willing to
listen to that too.
Okay.
If you're good with
those parameters,
then I guess I'll help you out.
I'll take whatever
help you can give!
Thank you! I mean it;
thanks so much!
Yeah, sure.
[HOTARO] Of course, high
school isn't all about drama.
There's also a good
amount of tedium.
Take exams, for example.
It's every student's
favorite time of year
here at Kamiyama High: Midterms.
During the testing period, all
club activities are suspended.
Obviously, that includes
the Classic Lit Club.
But we don't really
do anything anyway,
so there's honestly
not much difference.
Keys to the clubrooms
aren't given out
while midterms are underway,
so even if we wanted
to meet up like usual,
that wouldn't be an option.
[TEACHER 3A]
Okay, time's up.
[STUDENTS groaning, chattering]
[HOTARO]
Midterm tests are over.
And I survived.
[TOMOE]
"Hey, Little Bro.
Greetings from Istanbul!
Or, more accurately,
from the Japanese consulate.
I goofed up a bit and
haven't quite made it
into the city yet."
What trouble did you
get into this time?
[TOMOE]
"This has been a lot of fun,
and I know I'll look back in
10 years and be glad I did it."
"I'm dying to know
how the club's going.
Have any more members yet?
The club is actually
the reason I'm writing.
I wanted to ask you something.
Are you planning
to make an anthology?
The Classic Lit Club enters
an anthology each year
for the cultural festival.
You are going to keep up
the tradition, aren't you?
If so, I'm sure you'll want
to look at some examples
to know what you're
supposed to do.
I'll tell you right now,
the old anthologies
aren't in the library.
You have to look
in the club room.
There's an unused
chemical locker in there.
And the back-number
anthologies are inside.
It shouldn't be locked.
Anyway, once I reach Pristina
I'll give you a call.
Take care of yourself.
Your sister, Tomoe."
A chemical locker, huh...
You've got some
good timing, Sis.
--[GIRL 3A] Hey, nice hat.
--[BOY 3A] Shut up!
[ERU]
Really? Are you sure?
[sneezes]
[HOTARO]
Yeah, I'm sure.
Here you go. Take a look
for yourself if you want.
So that's it, then.
We just find the
chemical locker.
[HOTARO]
It isn't in here, though.
[ERU gasps]
Yeah, you're right,
I don't remember seeing one.
So... What happened to them?
Where are they?
It's all right, Chi.
Let's just calm down a sec.
[HOTARO]
"Chi," is it?
Chitanda. Take a look
at the letter again.
All it said was they're in a
chemical locker in the clubroom.
My sister graduated from
Kami High two years ago.
They've probably changed
the clubroom since then.
Yeah, you're right.
And more than once, maybe.
Okay, now what?
How do we find out where
it was two years ago?
I already asked the adviser.
It was located in
the biology prep room.
Wow. You're unusually
well prepared today.
[HOTARO]
Just trying to be efficient.
[MAYAKA]
Hmph.
Admit it. You're pumped.
I don't get "pumped."
That kind of excitement
requires too much energy.
Well, let's go!
Oh, hey, where's Fukube?
I haven't seen him.
Handicrafts Club.
He said something about
getting a head start
on the summer fashion scene.
[ERU]
You coming?
Huh... I guess it's locked.
[ERU]
Excuse me! Is anybody in there?
[TOGAITO]
Hey, sorry about that.
I guess I locked the door.
So what brings ya here?
Wanna join the
Wall Newspaper Club?
No, that's not it.
Sorry. I didn't realize this was
the Wall Newspaper Club room.
Yep, it sure is.
[HOTARO sniffs]
What's that smell? Cologne?
No. Air freshener.
So... What can I
do for you today?
Well, um...
My name's Eru Chitanda,
and I'm the president
of the Classic Lit Club.
You're in class 3-E, right?
Togaito, isn't it?
I'm sorry, have we met before?
[ERU] I saw you at the
Manninbashi home last year.
I kind of have a knack
for remembering names.
[TOGAITO]
The Manninbashi home, was it?
Hold on.
You wouldn't happen to be
one of the Kanda Chitandas,
would you?
[ERU] Yes! Thank you for
all you do for my father.
So... President of
the Classic Lit Club.
That's cool.
And you're a Chitanda.
[HOTARO] What is this
guy babbling about?
[TOGAITO]
Anyway... What do you need?
Right!
We're looking for the old
anthologies the Classic Lit Club
put together, and we're
pretty sure they're in
the Biology Prep room.
This used to be the Classic
Lit Club room, didn't it?
[TOGAITO]
Oh... Uh... Yeah.
I think it was, actually,
back when I was a first-year.
[ERU]
Great!
Are the anthologies in there?
Have you seen them?
Sorry. No.
Too bad. I guess we'll
be on our way then.
Don't leave!
Sorry to bug you, but we're
pretty sure they're in there.
Can't we just take
a quick look around?
There's no point.
I already told you,
they aren't here.
[ERU]
You're sure?
[HOTARO]
Oh well, that's that.
[MAYAKA]
Hey!
Don't you think he's
acting kinda weird?
Of course.
Then don't just walk away!
[TOGAITO]
Anyway, sorry I couldn't help.
Hope you find 'em somewhere.
You don't understand!
The information we've gathered
points straight here.
It's the only clue we have.
If they aren't here,
we're going to have to search
the whole school!
[HOTARO]
The whole school?
I can't let that happen.
We need a couple
minutes, that's all.
Can't you at least
give us that much?
[HOTARO]
Pretty please?
I don't like the idea of letting
non-club members poke around.
It's not just a clubroom,
it's a classroom.
There are non-members in
there all the time, y'know.
And you are...?
Classic Lit Club member
Ibara Mayaka.
All right, I give.
Go ahead and take a look then.
But don't make too
much of a mess, okay?
[HOTARO]
Where are the other members?
[TOGAITO]
Oh, they're takin' the day off.
I'm just brainstorming
ideas for the June issue.
Our club's been writing the
Kami High Monthly Newsletter
for a long time.
We're about to hit
our 500th issue.
[MAYAKA] I'm not seeing
what we're looking for.
Sorry. I guess you were right.
[sneezes]
[MAYAKA]
So what now? Oreki?
[HOTARO]
Togaito...
When this became your clubroom,
did you move anything out
to make space for your stuff?
Now that you mention it, we did
take some cardboard boxes out.
Some cardboard boxes, huh?
[TOGAITO]
Yeah.
[HOTARO]
We have an opening.
[HOTARO] This situation has
to be handled delicately.
But with just the
right amount of pressure.
[HOTARO]
Y'know...
I didn't realize how much
stuff there was in here.
It's gonna take forever
to sort through it all.
We could really use
a few reinforcements.
I think I'll go and ask the
club adviser to help us out.
You're cool with that, right?
No, I'm not.
Like I told you, I don't want
you making a mess of this place.
Sorry we're
inconveniencing you,
but this is really important!
We'll put everything back right
where we found it, I promise.
You won't have to--
I said no, okay?
[ERU]
But--
Don't you get it? I'm busy!
I don't want a bunch
of underclassmen
ransacking my club room!
Is that so hard to understand?
Just get out of here!
[HOTARO]
Gotcha.
Just so you know,
we're pretty sure
what we're looking for
is inside some kind
of a chemical locker.
A locker?!
Yep. Our intel says that's
where the anthologies are.
We don't care about anything
else that might be in this room.
Do you understand me?
So listen.
Right now, we've got some stuff
to take care of in the library,
but if you happen to find the
anthologies after we leave,
maybe you could leave
them in the Earth Science
prep room for us?
The door should be unlocked.
I... I didn't...
I didn't do anything!
Who said you did?
All right, fine.
If I find them,
that's what I'll do.
[HOTARO]
Great. Thanks.
Okay, let's go.
Hey, first-year.
I don't think I ever
did catch your name.
It's Hotaro Oreki.
For what it's worth,
I'm sorry about all this.
[MAYAKA]
Okay, I give.
Why are we waiting
out here like this?
[HOTARO]
To conserve energy.
[MAYAKA]
What does that mean?
So tell me something.
You've obviously heard
of the Togaito family.
Why are they so prominent?
Well, let's see.
I guess they're best known for
their involvement in education.
Their family holds a lot
of important positions
in the educational system.
That explains it.
It's been five minutes.
We should get back now.
[HOTARO]
Yep. There they are.
[MAYAKA]
The anthologies.
Hold on, Oreki!
How'd you know they'd be here?
What on Earth did you do?
Oh, just a little
intimidation, that's all.
[MAYAKA]
What's that mean?
[HOTARO]
Well... I dunno.
Can you keep a secret?
[MAYAKA]
Of course!
If you tell me not to
say anything, I won't.
[HOTARO]
Okay.
So let's start
at the beginning.
When Togaito came to
meet us, he stepped out
and closed the door behind
him instead of letting us in.
[MAYAKA]
Yeah, that was weird.
[HOTARO]
Then there's the room itself.
The window was wide open
and the fan was running.
If you recall, it was
pointed toward the window,
blowing around the papers
that were on the table.
[MAYAKA] It's like he wanted to
air out the room or something.
Exactly.
But why'd he care so much about
ventilating the room like that?
More importantly,
why would he lock himself in
and place infrared sensors
out in the hall?
[MAYAKA]
Wait! Slow down a sec.
Infrared sensors? What in the
world are you talking about?
What?
You didn't notice the
small, strange boxes
on either side of the hallway?
Then there was that device
with the antenna on it
that was obviously the receiver.
He must've set it up so
that anyone who passed by
the sensors would
trigger an alarm.
[alarm beeping]
And since when are
you so tech-savvy?
I'm not, really.
I just infer stuff from
what I observe, that's all.
The question is,
why would he need an alarm
that would tell him
when someone was coming
so he could start
airing out the room?
Why take such precautions?
[MAYAKA]
To get rid of a smell?
Seems like a reasonable guess.
And let's not forget the fact
that the place reeked
of air freshener.
Now... What smell could
he be trying to get rid of
that would make him go
to such desperate measures?
[MAYAKA]
Cigarette smoke.
[HOTARO]
Knowing that the Togaito family
is prominent in
academic circles,
can you imagine the kind
of trouble he would be in
if he was caught
doing something illegal?
He couldn't risk it.
It all makes sense now.
[HOTARO] Of course,
if Chitanda didn't have a cold,
she would've noticed
the smell immediately
and things would've
been a lot easier.
That's not all, though.
Where did the anthologies
end up being, huh?
Inside the locker, obviously.
What... lock... er?!
Hey. I'm not messing with you.
It was there, okay?
The chemical locker
had to be hidden under
that makeshift table.
My guess is that Togaito kept
his cigarettes and lighter
in there too.
So, when I suggested
we come back
and search the room
with an adviser,
he panicked and
flipped out on us.
You really are weird.
Not at all.
I'm probably the most
ordinary guy at this school.
[SATOSHI]
You guys!
[chuckles]
Look! I'm a sunflower!
About time.
While you were out doing arts
and crafts, we were working.
[SATOSHI]
What? Oh, the anthologies.
Huh... So this
is what they look like.
[MAYAKA] Check out the
ones from 40 years ago.
What is it? Something wrong?
[SATOSHI] That's because they
were printed on a Ditto machine.
More precisely, it's
called mimeograph printing.
It's what they had...
[HOTARO]
What's the matter?
[SATOSHI] Copy machines
didn't become commonplace
until a lot later,
so they wouldn't...
Well, it's just--
[HOTARO]
Hm?
[ERU]
Come here.
[MAYAKA]
What issue is that?
[ERU]
It's this.
[HOTARO]
Hyouka ?
Issue 2.
I saw it back when I was little.
That's what started all this.
I remember taking
this volume to my uncle,
and asking him about
what was inside.
What was special about it?
Here, take a look
at it for yourself.
Something happened 45 years ago.
I'm not sure what,
but it involved my uncle
and the Classic Lit Club.
[HOTARO] "Once again, the time
for the cultural festival
is upon us.
It has been a year now
since Sekitani left.
And in that year,
he has gone from being a hero
to being a legend.
The struggles
that were endured...
The sacrifices that were made...
Even his smile...
All are fading now.
And... Perhaps
it is for the best.
Perhaps they
should be forgotten.
After all, it was in
no way a heroic tale.
Details blur, facts fade away,
the passage of time polishes
the story's rough edges.
Bit by bit, the truth
will be eroded.
Until the tale is just
another dusty classic.
October 13th, 1968.
Yoko Koriyama."
You see? Whatever event
they're referencing
happened 45 years ago.
There's no way it's
just a coincidence.
The Sekitani they
talk about was my uncle.
This mentions
struggles and sacrifices,
like something big happened.
It must be what my
uncle told me about.
Well then the mystery's
just about solved, right?
I still don't know
all of it, though.
I'm so close!
Why can't I remember?
What did my uncle say to me
that day that upset me so much?
What exactly happened to him at
this school all those years ago?
[HOTARO]
Just look into it some more.
[ERU] But... It says
there it might be best
if it were forgotten.
Who knows, maybe
something bad will happen
if I keep digging.
There are some truths that
are better left undiscovered.
Isn't that what people say?
So you're just
gonna give up, then?
Is that what you want to do?
You think I'm wrong?
Yeah, kinda.
I mean, look at what
it says at the end here.
"Bit by bit, the
truth will be eroded.
Until the tale is just
another dusty classic."
How long till the
truth's lost forever?
Right.
Besides, looking into
it shouldn't be too difficult.
This is Issue 2, and it talks
about stuff that happened
the year before, right?
So you just find issue one,
and there you have it.
[MAYAKA]
Bad news, you guys.
We're still missing
the first issue!
[SATOSHI]
Next time:
"The Classic Lit Club's
Glorious Days of Yore."