[MAYAKA] I'm sorry.
I don't have it for you.
[KOCHI]
A Corpse by Evening ?
You couldn't find it
or something?
[MAYAKA] I must have brought
it with me when I went
to the country on vacation.
[KOCHI]
Is that the truth?
Yes.
[KOCHI]
Fine.
Why don't you help
with the posters, then?
The posters?
Sure. Which ones?
Well... Start with moe .
I have to step out
for a little bit.
I'm impressed.
She remembered the title.
[SATOSHI]
So Chitanda, Mayaka...
Don't forget that the cooking
contest starts at 11:30, okay?
Right!
I'm sorry, Fuku,
but I promised that I would help
draw posters for the Manga Club.
What? Oh, bummer.
Well, let me see here.
If we move things around and
put you in the last position...
As long as you get there
by 12:10, we should be fine.
[MAYAKA]
That sounds great!
I'll do my best to
make it by then.
See ya!
Well, I need to pop by
the executive committee room,
so I'll see you guys
around in a little while.
[HOTARO] He's enjoying
this way too much.
[TANABE]
Hey!
Sorry, but would you mind taking
that box to the gym for me?
[SATOSHI]
Sure, no problem.
By the way...
Have you had a chance to look
around the festival at all?
[TANABE] Not really. I keep
having to put out little fires,
but I have been able
to do some exploring.
Why? Have you picked up
any interesting stories
along the way?
[SATOSHI] Oh, man, all kinds
of stuff has gone down.
Ah!
I heard a thief struck
over at the Go Club.
What?
They stole some of the Go stones
and left a mysterious
confession note behind.
Wow. I see.
You said the Go Club?
[SATOSHI]
Yeah, but if you ask me,
I think one of their own
members is to blame.
[TANABE]
No.
There was another theft,
according to Okano.
Apparently something
with the Acapella Club.
[SATOSHI]
Yeah? What got stolen there?
[TANABE] He said someone took
a drink from their cooler--
some kind of juice, I think.
[SATOSHI] Did the thief
leave a confession note?
[TANABE] Yeah, they mentioned
finding a weird message
in there.
[SATOSHI] Things just took
an interesting turn.
What's up now, Fukube?
Why are you smiling?
[SATOSHI] Oh, nothing,
don't worry about it.
[ERU]
Today's the day!
I've got this!
[IRISU]
That's fine. I'll help you.
[ERU] You're saying that
I can leave them here?
Yeah.
Oh... Wow!
I appreciate it
more than you know!
[IRISU] Better not say that
until they're all sold.
So... How many,
and what's the price?
We're selling at 200 each,
and we printed... 200 copies.
[IRISU]
That's a lot.
[ERU] We meant to get 30,
but we made a mistake,
so we need to sell as many
as possible to pay for them.
We're desperate. We need help.
Why don't we lower the
price of Hyouka to 150?
I'll sell them with the
pamphlets for 200 total.
Great.
[BOY 14D]
What's in the gym?
[BOY 14E] I don't know,
probably something dumb.
What are you doing?
I want a copy of Hyouka .
Oh, right.
I was confused by your hand.
I'm sorry,
but I didn't bring one.
From now on, you should
carry a copy with you.
Your presentation
is important as well.
Irisu...
Uh... What is it?
[ERU] You're an expert
at getting what you want
when you need a favor, right?
[IRISU]
Uh...
[ERU] Would you be willing
to share the secrets
of your success with me?
[IRISU]
What?!
[GIRL 14E]
What the--?
Yeah, okay.
First of all, no matter what
it is that you're asking for,
you have to make the
other person think
that it's their idea.
Their idea?
To do that, you have to
set up an environment
in which they feel emotional
contentment and trust.
There's a myriad of
ways to achieve this,
but your most
effective style would be...
...expectation.
Oh, yeah?
[IRISU]
Yes.
Make the other person think
you expect this of them,
and they'll feel obligated.
[ERU]
Obligated...
If you can do that much,
their conscience will do the
rest and they'll commit to it.
They'll commit to it?
[IRISU] Yes, but you have
to make the favor seem
like less of an ordeal
than it actually is.
Like less of an ordeal?
Like it's not that big
of a thing to you,
but that it will pay
them major dividends
if they agree to it.
One other tip,
and it's a big one.
If possible, ask someone
of the opposite sex,
and do it
out of public view.
Right.
Now hurry along.
Get those anthologies.
Yes, right away.
[ERU]
Thank you. That helps a lot.
[CONFECTION CLUB GIRL 14A]
Trick or treat!
[CONFECTION CLUB GIRL 14B]
Yay!
[CONFECTION CLUB GIRL 14A]
Trick or treat!
[CONFECTION CLUB GIRL 14B]
Yay!
[HOTARO] What are you two
supposed to be?
[GIRLS laugh]
[BOTH] We're selling
treats door to door
for the Confection Club!
Would you like to
buy some cookies?
Sure, how much?
[CONFECTION CLUB
GIRL 14B giggles]
They're on sale
at 100 yen per bag!
[CONFECTION CLUB GIRL 14A]
Wow, you're packing heat!
How cool!
[CONFECTION CLUB GIRL 14B]
Ooh!
We could pretend
to be robbers...
If you really want it,
I'm willing to trade you
two cookie bags for that pistol.
Act now and I'll throw in
an anthology for free.
[CONFECTION CLUB GIRL 14A]
Huh? Are you being serious?
Kerblam!
[CONFECTION CLUB GIRL 14B]
Okay!
Here ya go.
And as a symbol of our
pumpkin-head gratitude,
have this, too!
You're selling flour?
[BOTH]
Yay!
[CONFECTION CLUB GIRL 14B]
Trick or treat!
[CONFECTION CLUB GIRL 14A]
Kerblam!
[SATOSHI] The Manga Club's
vaunted artist, huh?
Isn't that nice.
There. All done.
Mayaka!
[SATOSHI]
All right, let's do this!
Is Mayaka coming?
She's still busy with
the Manga Club stuff.
Oh, all right.
But let's not
give up hope just yet.
[TANI]
Hey, Fukube!
This here is Suhara.
His dad's a professional chef.
Oh, yeah?
That's pretty awesome.
Well... Do your best and
I'm sure you'll be fine.
Bye!
We will do our best...
All right, everyone,
time to meet our contestants!
Number one.
Team Ajiyoshi!
[STUDENTS cheering]
Number two.
Team... Fata... Morgana!
[STUDENTS cheering]
[COOKING CLUB VP]
Number three!
Team... Astronomy Club!
[STUDENTS cheering]
[COOKING CLUB VP]
Team number four!
Team Classic Lit Club!
All right! Yeah!
[COOKING CLUB VP] Here are the
rules, so listen carefully.
Each team member has 20 minutes
to cook their individual dish.
After that 20 minutes is up,
they must pass the baton
to the next person.
Team members outside of the
cooking area are not allowed
to talk to the member
who is cooking,
so keep that in mind
and follow the rules!
Fukube, do you know what
dish you're going to cook?
I'm really delighted you asked!
My special:
Fuku hoisin fried rice.
That's great!
Although, by the rules,
we would have to boil
the rice from scratch.
So that means you'd have to be
our anchorman and finish us out.
No, I don't think my plan
is going to work after all.
Since I can't make my rice,
I'll lead us off
and get the ball rolling
with some other dish.
Whatever you make will be great.
Now!
Each team member must
prepare at least one dish.
Ingredients are first-come,
first-serve,
in bowls in the center.
Once they're gone, don't worry.
You are allowed
to procure others,
but only from on school grounds.
All that said,
get ready for the first round!
[COOKING CLUB PRESIDENT]
To your kitchens!
Here goes!
[COOKING CLUB VP] Without
further ado, let's begin!
It's Wild...
[STUDENTS]
...Fire!
[whistle blowing]
[STUDENTS cheering]
Fire.
[COOKING CLUB VP]
Okay, everybody,
Wild Fire is underway.
I don't know about you, Prez,
but I'm certainly looking
forward to what each team
will present to us.
Let's hope it's good!
[COOKING CLUB VP]
Oh, Team Classic Lit Club
is pulling the heads
off dried fish
and cleaning each
one individually!
That looks like
some pretty precise work.
What do you have to say, Prez?
This is the kind of prep work
that sets a team apart, VP.
[COOKING CLUB VP] Team Fata
Morgana is doing great things
with clam meat!
[ERU] Is he going to make
daikon radish miso soup?
Huh?! Fukube!
You shouldn't be doing that!
You're supposed to
peel the daikon first!
Fu--
[ERU]
Oh, no!
I forgot I'm not supposed
to talk to him!
I've gotta follow the rules!
The daikon...
Peel it! Peel it!
Come on, Fukube!
[ERU]
Ah!
Did he figure out what
he's doing wrong?
What?!
Is he peeling each
radish wheel separately?
The water!
The water's boiling over!
[COOKING CLUB VP]
That looks like it's gonna take
quite some time,
Team Classic Lit Club!
[COOKING CLUB PREISDENT] Don't
get stuck in a loop, kid!
[SATOSHI sighs]
That's that.
What next?
[COOKING CLUB VP] We're still
not able to tell at this point
what each team is making.
Uh-oh, Team Classic Lit
is tilting his head!
What does that mean?
[SATOSHI]
Ow! Hot!
[ERU]
Ah, I think I get it now!
He's making miso meat stew!
[COOKING CLUB VP] Looks like
Team Ajiyoshi is preparing
a basic meat sauce!
That sounds tasty!
[MAYAKA] There's no way
I'll make it at this pace!
[COOKING CLUB VP]
All right, lead cooks!
Your time is almost up!
[COOKING CLUB VP]
Five! Four! Three!
Two! One!
Time to switch!
Sorry.
I was only able
to prepare one dish.
That's okay. You just
leave this round to me!
For sure!
Get 'em, Chitanda.
[COOKING CLUB VP]
That's amazing!
Team Classic Lit Club
is paring that daikon
like she's been to
culinary school!
[COOKING CLUB PREISDENT]
You're absolutely correct.
That is professional level work.
I'm impressed.
She could skim the skin
off a pudding,
judging by the way she's
peeling that thing.
[SATOSHI]
That's amazing.
She's already
completed one dish.
[SATOSHI]
Well, that's Chitanda for you.
[COOKING CLUB VP] Team Classic
Lit Club is hand-washing
her rice!
They've already
gone through all six
liters of water that they
were allotted at the start!
[COOKING CLUB PRESIDENT] That's
an admirable way to do it.
the flavor of the
rice is crucial.
Whoa!
Take a look at Team
Astronomy Club!
What's going on?
If that's not a flambé,
they should be worried!
[COOKING CLUB PRESIDENT]
Get the fire extinguisher ready!
[COOKING CLUB VP]
Meanwhile...
is Team Classic Lit Club
making giseyaki ?
I sure love
down home cooking!
[COOKING CLUB PRESIDENT]
Like mom used to make!
[SATOSHI] I've never
even heard of giseyaki !
[COOKING CLUB VP]
And, over at Team Fata Morgana,
the yellowtail teriyaki
is nearing completion!
[COOKING CLUB PREISDENT]
Brilliant!
[COOKING CLUB VP] Team Classic
Lit Club is plating up
that giseyaki !
[COOKING CLUB PRESIDENT] I'm
starting to get really hungry!
[COOKING CLUB VP] Just who is
that second cook of theirs,
anyway?
[SATOSHI]
She's Miss Eru Chitanda,
of the famous
farming Chitandas,
and don't you forget it!
[COOKING CLUB VP] Meanwhile,
Team Astronomy Club
still seems to be using
an avant-garde cooking style!
[COOKING CLUB PRESIDENT]
Looks pretty far out there!
Team Classic Lit Club
is rolling boiled potatoes
in starch and putting
them in ceramic ware.
Now she's making imochi cakes?
This girl definitely knows
what she's doing!
Oh... That's trouble!
This is making me nervous.
[SATOSHI]
Trouble? What trouble?
[SATOSHI gasps]
[COOKING CLUB VP]
No outside help is allowed,
Team Classic Lit Club!
[SATOSHI] It's no use.
I'm not getting through.
All right, teams,
your 40 minutes are up.
Time to switch
to your anchormen.
[ERU]
Hey, Fukube.
How'd I do?
You were amazing, Chitanda.
I had no idea you had such
advanced culinary skills.
Cooking's fun!
It's one of my hobbies.
Yeah, well done out there.
Although...
What's wrong?
[ERU] We're already out of
ingredients!
Mayaka. I'm sorry.
[COOKING CLUB VP] Okay, the time
has come for the anchormen
to bring it home!
[MAYAKA]
Finished!
'Scuse me!
Pardon me!
Coming through!
[COOKING CLUB VP]
Very nice!
It looks like Team Ajiyoshi
is preparing apples
for a dessert course!
Adorable!
Those little bunnies are taking
shape right before our eyes!
As of right now, Team Classic
Lit Club's anchorman
has yet to appear!
Oh, my! Team Ajiyoshi
is making celery roses!
Impressive!
That dessert is going to
be a spectacle for sure!
Leaving Team Classic Lit Club
and their missing anchorman
in the dust, Team Ajiyoshi
is making real progress
with their elaborate
dessert scenery!
[SATOSHI]
Mayaka!
[COOKING CLUB VP]
What's this?
A girl in civilian clothes has
just burst onto the scene!
Is she the missing member of
Team Classic Lit Club?
That must be the case!
It's their anchorman!
She's finally arrived!
Get cooking, girl!
[STUDENTS clapping]
[COOKING CLUB VP]
Uh-oh!
Team Classic Lit Club is out
of the frying pan
and into the fire!
There are no ingredients
left to work with!
[ERU, SATOSHI gasp]
[COOKING CLUB VP] If she's
unable to cook anything,
then the anchorman's score
will be a big, fat zero!
After a hard-fought battle,
could this blow mean the end
for the Classic Lit Club?
[MAYAKA]
Is this really it?
[COOKING CLUB VP] Team Classic
Lit Club seems to have found
a small onion.
But is that cause for hope?
What dish could she make
with that measly little onion?
She's just standing there.
Could she be stumped after all?
What will you do,
Team Classic Lit Club?
If you don't cook anything,
your team will lose for sure!
[HOTARO]
What can they do?
[MAYAKA]
What can I make?
I'm nervous.
What in the world
could she prepare
with only those ingredients?
Now I'm curious.
I have to know!
[SATOSHI]
It's kind of your fault!
[COOKING CLUB VP] Team Classic
Lit Club's anchorman
has still not moved a muscle!
[COOKING CLUB VP]
And there it is, folks!
Team Fata Morgana has
prepared a fabulous omelet!
Looks delicious!
[MAYAKA]
Think, Mayaka!
You've got to think!
[COOKING CLUB VP] Has Team
Classic Lit Club finally reached
the end of the line?
[MAYAKA]
Come on.
There has to be something!
[COOKING CLUB VP] Team Classic
Lit Club seems to be
out of options!
What to do?
The time is running out!
Ten minutes!
That's not much!
Are they going to admit defeat
and let the time run out?
[HOTARO]
Satoshi!
Listen.
Did you hear someone calling
your name just now, Fukube?
--[SATOSHI] What?
--[HOTARO] Satoshi!
[COOKING CLUB VP] Team
Astronomy is boiling bananas
in vegetable stock?
[SATOSHI]
Excuse me, sir!
[COOKING CLUB VP]
What is it?
Be quiet for a moment!
[HOTARO]
Satoshi!
[ERU]
Sounds like Oreki!
Look! He's up there!
In the clubroom!
Satoshi!
[CROWD BOY 14A]
What the--?
[CROWD BOY 14B]
Who is that?
[HOTARO]
Satoshi!
Get over here!
Under the window!
Hurry up!
Go, Fukube!
[SATOSHI]
Right.
What do you want?
Get ready to catch this!
Nice catch, huh?
So... What's this, then?
[COOKING CLUB VP] Team Classic
Lit Club's lead chef
has reappeared on the scene!
[MAYAKA]
What...?
[COOKING CLUB VP]
Interesting!
He seems to have thrown
her a bag of flour!
What a dramatic turn of events!
[COOKING CLUB PRESIDENT]
Checking the rule book...
Okay! It will be allowed!
All right!
[COOKING CLUB VP] Only seven
minutes remain on the clock!
As each Wild Fire team enters
the final phase of competition,
Team Classic Lit Club has
finally sprung back into action!
Under such
impossible circumstances,
what kind of heroics will
they need to save their dish?
We're all waiting
with bated breath!
[COOKING CLUB PRESIDENT]
I know I'm curious!
[COOKING CLUB VP]
What's this?
She's busted out
the shrimp heads?
What could she possibly
have up her sleeve?
Kakiage .
[SATOSHI]
She's making...
... kakiage tempura!
[COOKING CLUB VP] Only five
minutes left on the clock
in the Wild Fire competition!
How will it end?
Uh... Hey, you! Cooking Club!
You could at least
provide me with a ladle!
[COOKING CLUB VP] The Classic
Lit Club gets their ladle
and moves on to the next step!
The pressure is on
for Team Classic Lit Club.
Can they hustle enough to rally
from behind and beat the clock?
It's kakiage over rice!
[COOKING CLUB VP] Will Team
Classic Lit be able
to pull this off?
There's only one minute left!
[COOKING CLUB VP] That doesn't
leave her very much time
to finish!
[COOKING CLUB VP]
She scoops it up!
She lays it ever so
gently in the bowl.
[COOKING CLUB VP]
Three! Two! One!
It's over!
[STUDENTS cheering]
Oh, yeah!
Go, Mayaka!
Great job!
[SATOSHI]
Yeah!
What's the matter?
Oh, nothing;
don't worry about it.
[COOKING CLUB VP] And now, it's
time to announce the results!
The hard-earned
victory goes to...
...Team Classic Lit Club!
[STUDENTS cheering]
I'm exhausted.
It was undercooked.
Hey, with all the
obstacles you faced,
that was fantastic.
Yeah, but I had to
wait for that ladle!
If I would have had one, it
would have turned out perfectly!
It took a whole minute
for them to get one!
Idiot.
I should have known not
to start cooking that dish
without a stupid ladle!
Hey, I'm really
sorry about that!
I thought we had checked all
of the supplies very carefully.
We should have made another
pass before we started.
Yeah, I thought that was weird,
and I should've
said something...
Just slipped my mind, I guess.
[MAYAKA] That's okay;
things were crazy!
[ERU]
Let's see...
No way!
What is it?
[SATOSHI gasps]
A confession note!
[HOTARO]
Next time: "The Jumonji Affair."