[ERU]
I wonder...
Are the others getting
a good night's sleep?
[MAYAKA groans]
Tomorrow's the day.
[chuckles]
[SATOSHI] The whole school is
really going full out for this,
aren't they?
I've gotta see all of it.
Hmm... now, then...
The Quiz Club
starts at one o'clock.
A Shogi tournament?
Not sure I'm up for that one.
Ooh! The cooking contest is
definitely worth checking out!
Tomorrow's finally the day!
[HOTARO yawning]
Starts tomorrow, I guess.
All right.
Please let us have
nothing but good fortune
at the cultural festival
the next three days.
May we have the perseverance
to climb the mountain before us.
[ERU]
It's cultural festival time!
[TOMOE]
Good morning!
Hey.
You're up kinda early, huh?
[TOMOE]
Is today the cultural festival?
[HOTARO]
That's right.
[TOMOE] I heard you guys
had some trouble.
[HOTARO]
How did you find out?
[TOMOE]
I have my methods.
Besides, it's tradition
that the Classic Lit Club
can't get through
a cultural festival
without some kind of problem.
Nobody wants your
crappy traditions.
If that's the case, you
had better throw me
a good luck charm
to ward that off.
[TOMOE]
Catch!
[HOTARO gasps]
[TOMOE]
Ward it off with that.
Do you expect me to say
"thank you" for this?
[TOMOE] Oh, I guess I should
mention it's out of ink,
and the nib is split.
What am I, a trash can?
[TOMOE]
Better go or you'll be late.
Fine, whatever.
[TOMOE] If I have time,
I'll stop by and say hi to you!
[HOTARO]
No, stay away!
[SATOSHI] It's the day of
the festival, Hotaro!
Apparently so.
[SATOSHI] Ah, the Hotaro
we all know and love.
[HOTARO]
You sure are enjoying yourself.
[SATOSHI] Of course I am! Why
not? It's the cultural festival!
The hall of fame
for all the school clubs!
Hey! Isn't that
Mayaka up ahead?
[SATOSHI] That must be
a Manga Club costume.
Judging by her outfit,
I'd say she's on festival time.
[HOTARO] Did you come up
with a costume, too?
[SATOSHI] Well, I am a member of
the handicrafts club, after all.
I'm gonna go bother her.
Hey, happy festival
week, Mayaka.
Same to you.
I like your outfit. Looks great.
Cut it out.
So what character
are you cosplay--
Do not use that awful
word in the presence
of such respectable people.
[SATOSHI]
Roger that.
Then what character
are you dressed as?
I'm Frol.
Frol who?
Oh, Frolbericheri Frol?
I've got some gloves
that I'll put on later.
Oh, yeah?
[MAYAKA] What have you got in
your bag? It's stuffed.
[SATOSHI]
You'll find out.
[MAYAKA]
Sounds kind of shady.
Are you on Manga Club
duty all day?
I got stuck with the
salesgirl position.
it's terrible luck, considering.
Well, don't waste any
of that precious energy
beating yourself up.
You can't change
the past, you know?
Whoa!
[SATOSHI chuckles]
[SATOSHI] Now this is
what I call a festival!
[MAYAKA]
No kidding!
[SATOSHI]
I knew they went all out,
but this is better
than I ever imagined!
Wow, check out this mural!
Whoever made this
did a fantastic job.
[MAYAKA]
Yeah, you're right.
[HOTARO]
I think it's too busy.
Way too busy for my taste.
--Hey, are you done?
--Yeah, I'm all finished.
[MAYAKA]
Amazing!
[SATOSHI] All right, people!
It's time to party!
[laughs]
Well, I gotta leave
you guys for a bit.
[HOTARO]
Handicrafts Club?
Just for a few.
I'll be back in a jiffy, though.
[HOTARO]
It's quiet up here.
[MAYAKA]
It sure is...
Try not to dwell on it.
If you keep fretting
about what happened,
Satoshi won't be the
only one badgering you.
Chitanda will start
worrying about you, too.
[MAYAKA]
Yeah, I'm well aware of that.
[ERU]
Oh, good morning!
I'm so glad you guys
are finally here!
[MAYAKA]
Good morning to you, Chi.
It's almost time, right?
[HOTARO]
It sure is.
[ERU]
Let's give it our best shot!
Sure.
Is our best shot really going
to have much impact, though?
That's a good point!
There's no guarantee that
our best shot will help.
On the other hand,
if we don't give it
our best shot,
then it certainly won't help,
so we might as well
try our best!
Indubitably.
You know, why don't I just
go ahead and buy them all?
No! I wasn't trying to
make you feel guilty,
I promise!
Well, I am responsible
for messing up the order.
How many were we
originally trying to get?
[MAYAKA]
Thirty copies.
[HOTARO] And how many
did we end up with?
There's 200.
[SATOSHI]
Galaxy!
Oh, no! I broke my Saturn!
Nice of you to show up.
Good morning, Fukube.
Nice to see you.
[SATOSHI]
You guys been waiting long?
No, not at all.
We haven't even
gotten started yet.
[ERU gasps]
[MAYAKA]
Listen. I'm sorry. Really!
It's all my fault.
I should have read the
email from the printers
more carefully.
Everybody makes mistakes
once in a while.
[HOTARO] Did he forget
what he looks like?
There's no need
for self-flagellation.
We're all friends here, right?
[HOTARO]
He forgot what he looks like!
[ERU]
That's right!
I'm the club president, so I
should have looked it over
before we confirmed.
You know...
After I turned in my draft, I
washed my hands of it for sure.
We're all responsible
for what happened.
Right! I totally agree.
Thanks, guys.
Good. I'm glad you finally
got your head on straight.
[HOTARO] He had to have
forgotten what he looks like!
There's not much time to
discuss business before
the opening ceremony.
We've got our work
cut out for us,
so do any of you have
ideas about how we can
sell as many copies as possible?
How much are
we asking per copy?
[ERU]
Two hundred yen.
That's pretty cheap,
if you ask me.
[SATOSHI]
The problem is two-fold:
Our club's lack
of name recognition
and the fact that we're
stuck so out of the way.
[HOTARO]
Yeah.
So it'd help us to generate some
buzz about the Classic Lit Club
and to create a more
eyecatching storefront
in a busier place.
[ERU] Creating another
storefront altogether?
I hadn't thought about that!
I was just trying to
come up with something
to lure customers
all the way up here!
You have managed to blow
my mind yet again, Oreki!
[HOTARO]
That's great.
But isn't that a little
bit dramatic, though?
You don't think it'll
be hard to get permission
to move on the first day
of the festival?
[HOTARO]
Yeah, good point.
Satoshi, care to weigh in?
Hmm... That's a special
request, so it depends on
what the committee
chairman thinks.
But it can't hurt to ask him.
Worst case, he tells us no.
We could ask the
student council president.
Who's the executive
committee chairman?
[SATOSHI] You could at least
consult the guide, Hotaro.
Look. Right there.
I didn't see that.
[SATOSHI groans]
[SATOSHI]
Man...
I wish you would have noticed
the fruits of my labor!
And that refers to...?
To this! Let me show you.
Look, the Classic Lit
Club is listed
at the end of all
the club profiles.
I called in a favor,
and they came through for us.
The executive committee
puts the guide together.
That's amazing!
You abused your power?
[SATOSHI] Yeah, what of it?
If you want to ask the chairman,
you should try the
council room first.
[HOTARO] Wait, shouldn't
you be the one to ask?
[SATOSHI] Well, I guess
I could do that if I must,
but I don't have much
luck with negotiating.
[ERU]
It sure seems like you do.
Chitanda, I think you
should do the talking here.
I'll jump in to back
you up if you need me.
[ERU]
Please help us out, sir!
Okay. I guess I might
as well give it a shot.
[HOTARO] She doesn't
seem too eager to do this.
[SATOSHI]
Oh! Also...
I want to take charge
of publicity!
Is that why you're
wearing that getup?
[SATOSHI]
This is just one part of it all.
I have something
else up my sleeve.
Do you have a crazy
brilliant plan in mind?
I'm going to drop the
Classic Lit Club name.
I'll make the festival rounds,
participating in the
events and contests.
The plan is to perform
really well and to beef up
the Classic Lit Club's
reputation that way.
[HOTARO] He just wants
an excuse to play around.
Yeah, that's an awesome idea!
[SATOSHI]
You think?
Yes!
You're full of it today!
[HOTARO]
Wait... That's perfect!
You know,
that's a fantastic plan.
I think we should
proceed with it.
Chitanda will try to
negotiate a better storefront.
And Satoshi will publicize.
All right, it's official.
Let's get to it.
But what's your role, Oreki?
[HOTARO]
My role?
Yes.
I'm gonna hold down the fort.
[SATOSHI]
Oh, right.
I guess someone
has to stay here.
[ERU]
Yeah, that's true.
[SATOSHI]
Well, we'd better go.
Roll call for the opening
ceremony is about to start.
[ERU]
Right!
Okay!
We will all proceed with the
plan that we have just outlined.
Let's try to sell as
many copies as we can!
This is our goal: Hyouka !
All copies sold!
Everyone ready? On three!
One! Two! Three!
--Three!
Three.
[CROWD chattering]
[TEACHER 12A]
Hurry up and find your class.
Oh, how about the
Quiz Club's event?
Hey, look!
--[ERU] The bunny?
--This is amazing, isn't it?
This is lame.
I hereby declare,
for the 54th year
in a row now,
our school's Kanyasai...
...is officially open!
[STUDENTS cheering]
[SATOSHI laughing]
No way!
[ERU]
Wow! He flipped over him!
[ERU] What?
How does he spin like that?
[ERU] I don't have time
to stay and watch this!
[CALLIGRAPHY CLUB GIRL A]
Hey, Calligraphy Club, guys!
Come try it! It's easy!
Hey there!
Do you wanna try?
What?
You can keep it if
you want to, you know.
[ERU]
I shouldn't have stopped!
I don't have time for this!
[CARD GAME GIRL A]
The river from Tsukuhane.
[CARD GAME GIRL B]
Got it!
[CARD GAME GIRL A]
Springtime has passed.
--[CARD GAME GIRL B] Got it!
--[CARD GAME GIRL C] Got it!
[CARD GAME GIRL A]
Though I must part from thee.
--[CARD GAME GIRL B] Got it!
--[CARD GAME GIRL C] Got it!
[CARD GAME GIRL A]
So, what do ya say?
One game?
[CARD GAME GIRL A]
In the mountain de--
Got it!
[CROWD applauds]
[CARD GAME GIRL A]
Here's your medal!
[ERU]
I'm wasting precious time!
Looks like I'm finally here.
Is anyone in there?
[ERU]
What a gorgeous poster!
--[TANABE] Excuse me.
--[ERU gasps]
[TANABE] Hi, there.
Can I help you with something?
Oh, I beg your pardon.
Yes, actually,
I'm looking for Tanabe,
the Chairman of the
Executive Committee.
Well, you've just found him.
I did? Oh, I guess
that makes sense.
Listen...
I'd like a better storefront
for the Classic Lit Club.
[GLOBAL ACTION CLUB BOY 12A]
Global action! Global action!
Sorry! Hold on! I guess
I should tell you that I'm
the Classic Lit
Club's president!
And I came here today to
make a special request of you!
Please give the Classic Lit
Club a better selling space!
I can't just hand you
a better selling space
when you show up out of the
blue on the day of the festival.
Oh, I guess not.
Okay, well, thank you anyway.
[TANABE]
Hey, wait a second!
I meant I can't just
do that on principle.
If you have special
circumstances, I'll listen.
Do you mean that?
Thanks! I really appreciate it.
[ERU]
When we laid out this plan,
I was under the impression
that Fukube was going to be here
to help me out with this.
[laughing]
So when I lay on the gas,
that means we take off!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
hold up, hold up!
That's way too dangerous!
Say what?
[SATOSHI laughing]
So that's the situation.
Sounds like quite
the predicament. Hmm...
As much as I would like
to help you out somehow,
I feel the same way about
all the other clubs.
I can't be partial
to you guys, you know?
So there isn't
anything you can do?
[TANABE]
Sorry about that.
Just a sec.
If you want to talk to the other
club chairs and ask them
to keep some of
your books to sell,
I wouldn't have
a problem with that.
That is a really good idea!
I'll start asking around!
Thanks for all your help today!
[MAYAKA]
Good morning, everyone!
--Good morning to you, too.
--Good morning.
Oh. Ibara.
You're here.
[MAYAKA]
Hi, there, Kochi.
Yeah, I finally made it.
You even have a
katana for your costume?
Sure do.
It's just a fake plastic one.
Nothing special.
You couldn't find anything
to wear on your feet
that worked better?
[HENMI]
Look who decided to cosplay.
And after she made such a fuss.
[ARIYOSHI] She should've
just listened to Kochi
from the beginning.
She'd have been better off.
Come on!
That kind of talk is
uncalled for. Cut it out.
[YUASA]
Hey. Good morning.
[KOCHI]
Oh, hi. Good morning!
Good morning,
Madame President.
Nice to see you!
Good morning.
Did you spend a lot
of money on that?
No, I just bought the belt.
Oh, good.
I'll reimburse you
if you have the receipt.
Oh! Don't worry about that.
But... I did want to ask.
You see...
Oh... Nothing.
Uh... I just figured it out.
[YUASA]
You're sure?
[MAYAKA]
Yes. Forget about it.
[MAYAKA] I couldn't even
bring myself to ask.
I'm sure they'd let me
leave some in here.
[KIMURA]
Hey, there, how's it going?
What's your costume from?
Oh, hey. This is Frol.
Haven't you ever heard of
"They Were Eleven?"
[MORI]
What?
I've never heard of that one.
[MAYAKA] It was an old
science fiction manga.
I consider it a masterpiece.
[MORI] You think I could
borrow it sometime?
What's up, guys?
What are you talking about?
An old manga.
[KOCHI] All right, everyone!
Time to get fired up!
Yeah!
Excuse me. Are you all
open for business yet?
Well, we certainly are now!
Game faces on, guys,
we've got our first customers!
[CROWD chattering]
It sure is peaceful.
[HOTARO]
This is great.
I win.
I think I can go ahead
and mark down
the ones we're
definitely gonna sell.
Given the circumstances,
it's safe to say
the Classic Lit Club members
will each buy two.
I'll add our advisor to that,
and counting the one
for the archives,
that's twelve gone,
without a doubt.
Well, even if that's all we
sell, I'd say we did all right.
[CLUB MEMBERS singing]
[ACAPELLA CLUB 12A]
What the--?
Anyone seen my apple juice?
[ACAPELLA CLUB 12B]
Not me.
[ACAPELLA CLUB 12A]
Man, I didn't even get to drink
any of it!
[ACAPELLA CLUB 12C] What's that
piece of paper there?
[HOTARO]
I wonder what happened.
Uh-oh, getting sleepy.
--[HOTARO gasps]
--Excuse me.
[HOTARO]
What? A punk rocker!
Is he really punk rock?
So, uh...
What are you selling in here?
Nothing.
Oh...
I mean, we're selling
our club's anthologies.
[PUNK]
What, like, all of them?
That's right. It's a long story.
Okay, I'll take one.
[HOTARO]
Is he serious?
He's actually a customer?
I'll have to show gratitude.
That's 200 yen.
[HOTARO] Aw, I can't
bring myself to smile.
[HOTARO] Thanks a lot
for your business.
Whoa! Hey, man!
Um, yes? What is it?
That pen! Would you mind
if I took a look at it?
This old thing?
Yep!
It's perfect!
What great luck!
Are you for real?
[PUNK laughing]
Oh, sorry.
I'm in the Fashion Club, and
we're doing a runway show today.
I forgot to bring something
to put in my formalwear
breast pocket.
This pen is just the thing!
[laughing]
You can have it.
[PUNK] Whoa, really?
You'd give me this pen?
I was just gonna throw it
in the trash, so yeah.
[PUNK]
Oh.
Well then take this as a trade.
It's a VIP pass to our show,
so if you come by the club room,
be sure to bring
that thing with you.
We'll set you up with a
top-notch, stylish ensemble.
Thanks.
[HOTARO] Satoshi's probably
the only one who would use this.
[HOTARO]
Nah.
I guess he already
has his own style.
Oh, well.
Won't be needing that.
Glad I at least sold
one issue, though.
[ERU gasps]
I did it again!
[ACAPELLA CLUB SINGING]
[PHOTOGRAPHY CLUB 12A]
Hey, gorgeous!
[ERU]
Me?
How would you like
to be a model?
[ERU] Oh, no, oh, no,
oh, no, oh, no, oh, no!
I've grossly neglected my duty!
I keep getting distracted
by every interesting
club event I see!
[OCCULT CLUB 12A]
Occult Club!
We're the Occult Club!
Would you like to
summon a UFO with us?
Or come see our spirit
photography exhibit?
[INDUSTRIAL ARTS CLUB 12A]
Now displaying the Enterprise!
You don't want to miss
our Launching Ceremony!
Who wouldn't want to see
three months of hard work
go down the tube?
[GLOBAL ACTION CLUB 12B]
Global Action Club!
[MAGIC CLUB 12A]
You want a magic charm?
[ACAPELLA CLUB 12B] The Acapella
Club is doing a concert
in the courtyard!
[ERU]
Is there an Equestrian Club?
I could really use a pair
of blinders about now!
[MAYAKA] Next time:
"A Corpse By Evening."