[sneezes]
Unless we find
the first issue,
we're kind of
spinning our wheels.
Yeah, you're right.
[HOTARO] It might be a good
idea to bring Satoshi and Ibara
in on this.
No. I'd really rather not.
Well, it could take a long
time for us to solve this.
And we might not find anything
out before your uncle's funeral.
[ERU]
His funeral...
Fine, let's ask them.
I have a feeling
that we're gonna need
all the help we can
get to figure it out.
I just... I have to know!
What happened to
my uncle so long ago
has weighed on me for years.
I'm begging you all
to help me find out.
Your uncle sounds
like an interesting guy.
Did all of that really happen?
The story of a
forgotten hero,
uncovered by his niece
45 years later.
You know, we were just looking
at some stuff from that period.
[MAYAKA]
That's true.
I'm also fascinated
by this picture.
I'd love to help
find out the truth.
[SATOSHI]
This is kind of exciting, huh?
If we figure it out,
we should write about it
in the anthology.
We can investigate all we want,
and call it club business.
[HOTARO] And so, this is the
story of how all the members
of the Classic Lit Club
became fully invested
in illuminating the
mysteries of its past.
Hey there!
Did you wait long?
Hey! What is your
problem, man?
Put a sock in it!
What the matter with you,
screaming like that?
Anyway, did you bring all
your research to present?
Of course, and what about you?
Did you find anything good?
Yeah, I found a few things.
Awesome. I'm looking forward to
hearing your hypothesis, too.
[HOTARO]
Aw, crap.
I forgot we were supposed
to come up with one.
[SATOSHI]
All right, let's get going.
The Chitandas are a
super-rich farming family,
so their mansion
should be top notch!
[SATOSHI humming]
I'm glad you're enjoying
yourself so much.
What can I say,
I love cycling!
Speeding through
town like the wind
by the power of your legs
alone is thrilling, you know?
[HOTARO] Not that. I'm talking
about your whole attitude
about high school life so far.
Oh, right, the
"sunshine and roses" bit.
That's just me.
I like to stay sunny regardless
of my circumstances.
I'd say "sunny" is
putting it kinda mildly.
[laughs]
Whatever!
Why should anybody live their
life under a little black cloud?
You said that last
time we discussed this.
Did I really?
Well, I don't mean it as
an insult or anything bad;
it's just foreign to me.
[HOTARO]
Hmph.
I guess my attitude is
all sunshine and roses
at the end of the day.
You can throw shade
all you want,
but it's not gonna change that!
I won't be rained out!
Well, maybe you should
rein it in a little.
Not a chance, buddy!
What's the big problem?
You think I'm overextending
myself with all these
extracurricular
activities, is that it?
Well, am I wrong?
Yeah, you are.
Even if I weren't in clubs,
I'd find things to do.
I'm just an energetic
guy, you know?
And if I wanted
to insult you,
I'd call you boring,
not pessimistic.
Yeah, well, I really
don't care what you think
about me anyway.
[laughs]
That's pretty obvious!
Oh, hey, how did you end up
doing on your midterms?
[HOTARO]
Average overall, of course.
[SATOSHI] There's that
little black cloud again.
There it is, up ahead!
That's the Chitanda
family estate.
[SATOSHI]
What'd I tell ya?
Pretty sick digs, right?
Come on, they're probably
getting antsy in there.
[SATOSHI]
Fine. Hey, wait!
Wouldn't it be super cool if a
butler came to escort us in?
I'm glad you made it!
We thought you guys got lost!
Sorry.
Don't mind if I do.
Come on in, we're back here.
Sit where you want.
Make yourselves at home, okay?
You sure took your time.
[HOTARO] We aren't
even late, calm down.
[MAYAKA]
Hmph.
[HOTARO] I've never seen a man
less suited to take the seat
at the head of the table.
[ERU]
All right!
I guess we should get this
party started, don't you think?
Second!
Sure!
Yeah.
The purpose of today's
meeting is to investigate
what took place within the
Classic Lit club 45 years ago.
If we do happen to
find out anything,
then I want to include
it in the anthology
for the festival this year.
First, let's each share reports
on any data we've gathered,
followed by some Q and A
about those findings,
then propose our hypotheses.
Finally, we'll discuss
the various theories
and decide how we
should proceed from there.
[HOTARO] Dang, she's
kind of a natural leader.
Okay, who do we
think should go first?
I mean... uh...
Oh, geez, I can't decide
who should start.
[HOTARO]
I take it back.
Does it really matter?
Chitanda, why don't you
lead us off, okay?
Right, good idea.
I'll begin, and then we'll go in
clockwise order from there.
I decided to research the
old anthology, titled Hyouka .
The only reference I
could find to the events
of our investigation
was in this forward.
I compiled all the facts
from it and included them
on the second page.
Let's look at item one.
"Senpai" refers to
my uncle, Jun Sekitani,
the subject of our quest.
We know that Jun was
kicked out of Kamiyama High,
and thus his
academic career ended
as a middle school graduate.
Item two just shows
that the story became
more exaggerated as time passed.
He started as a hero and
turned into a legend.
Items three and five
are connected.
He was a quiet
and kind "senpai,"
and once he turned "warrior,"
he morphed into a "hero."
In the end...
...he became a martyr.
Item four is curious to me,
but we'll talk about that later.
That concludes my presentation.
What do you think?
Any questions for me?
[MAYAKA]
I have one.
Why did you leave out the
part where the author says,
"It was in no way
a heroic tale?"
[ERU] Because that's an opinion,
and I only included facts.
Maybe by that, they
just mean the fights
were really scrappy.
That they weren't anything
awe-inspiring or remarkable.
That could be true.
Okay, now let me
tell you my hypothesis.
I think my uncle may have
protested some school policy,
and was asked to
leave as a result.
There's something else.
It's not stated
objectively in the forward,
but I inferred it
from the wording.
This says it had been "a year
since" the events occurred.
That means my uncle was
expelled around the time
of the previous Kanyasai.
This is kind of off topic,
but my friend who goes
to another school told me
they had an incident at their
cultural festival last year.
A culture fest shakedown!
Extortion and larceny,
a dark, seedy underbelly!
I guess every
generation has its crooks
who wanna spoil it
for the rest of us.
Maybe people like that tried
to target Kami High's festival
that year, and when
my uncle led the charge
to defend the
school against them,
he got punished for fighting.
That would be in line with
the whole hero narrative.
I think the underclassmen
who looked up to my uncle
for his bravery were
mad that he got expelled,
and they wrote this
in honor of him.
Hmm... I don't buy it.
Yeah, I agree with Hotaro.
Seriously?
What part of it
doesn't add up to you?
Well, for starters,
do you remember
what I suggested we do
instead of the anthology
when you first brought it up
to me that day?
Lemme see...
A concessions stand!
That's right.
You told me that
selling refreshments
had never been allowed
at the Kanyasai before.
So why would anyone try
to rip off a festival
where they knew no money
would be changing hands?
They might have come
with other bad intentions
besides stealing people's money.
[HOTARO gasps]
Didn't think of that
one, did ya, Hotaro?
Fine.
Why don't you wow us with
your take on her theory?
A bunch of punks
disrupting the Kanyasai,
I'm sorry to say,
would never have
happened back then.
Why not?
When you think
of that time-period,
the 1960s, what images
come to mind?
[MAYAKA]
Hmm...
[SATOSHI] Tokyo, the Diet
building, protests,
people carrying signs?
[HOTARO] Satoshi, why don't
you get to the point already?
Peaceful student activism.
You see, the kind of
on-campus violence
Chitanda presents
in her hypothesis
wasn't even a thing
yet in the 60s,
at least not
around here, anyway.
We were fighting against
"The Man" back then:
The system and the state.
There wasn't any animosity
toward the teachers
or the schools.
Don't try to make it
sound like you were there.
[SATOSHI]
I obviously wasn't,
but I did some
in-depth research.
You're right.
I didn't take the social climate
of the time into account.
[MAYAKA]
I'm really sorry, Chi!
What are you
apologizing for, Mayaka?
The information I found
in my research
doesn't support
your theory, either.
I wanted to wait my turn,
so I didn't say anything,
but my info refutes your claim.
[HOTARO] Damn it, Ibara, you
just let me waste my breath?
No worries, I think it's
safe to withdraw my theory
for right now, so Mayaka,
why don't you share your
findings with the group?
Is that all right with you guys?
--[HOTARO] Sure thing.
--[SATOSHI] Yeah!
[SATOSHI] Ugh! Aw, man,
my butt is falling asleep.
This might be rude,
but your estate is
ginormous, Chitanda.
Do you have a pond
in your gardens?
[ERU]
Yep, we sure do!
Really? I'd love
to check it out.
Would that be cool with you?
Ooh, yeah,
I wanna see it, too!
Okay, why don't we move
the meeting outside, then?
It's such a lovely day
to sit out on the veranda!
[HOTARO]
A pond? Wow.
This is a copy of a booklet
I found in the library,
called Solidarity and
Salutes , Issue One.
I couldn't find issues
two or higher, though.
It was published 45 years ago,
the same as Chi's.
[HOTARO]
"Our valiant activism?" Really?
That sounds so old-fashioned.
Okay, let's dive in.
"We," in this case,
refers to the students,
while the terms, "reactionary
forces" and "authoritarians"
refer to the teachers.
The previous June, there
was some kind of conflict,
and Jun Sekitani, the president
of the Classic Lit Club,
spearheaded it.
The students,
under his leadership,
engaged in what
they called "activism"
by sticking it to the teachers.
[HOTARO]
Interesting.
I wonder what their methods
of protesting were.
This Solidarity
and Salutes stuff
seems a little silly,
doesn't it?
What do you mean by that?
I'm not knocking it.
I just think it makes
a presumably common
high school complaint
out to be on par
with a legitimate,
real-world protest, ya know?
So does that have any
bearing on this research?
Nope, I'm just
thinkin' out loud!
Sorry for interrupting you guys.
All right, any questions,
or can we keep going?
Well, here's my hypothesis.
Like I said, Chi's
theory doesn't work.
According to Solidarity
and Salutes ,
the incident in question
happened in June.
As for what Sekitani
did to get expelled,
violence is what
comes to mind, right?
So in other words, he and
the students he inspired
got themselves all riled up.
And they let the
teachers have it!
There isn't any evidence he
actually hit anyone, though.
Something happened that
threatened to take away
the students' freedom, so they
must have rallied together
to fight against that
perceived injustice.
[ERU] And my uncle
was their leader?
[SATOSHI]
Hmm...
I'm almost completely on board
with your hypothesis, I think.
Why "almost?"
To sum up, your theory
is that the students
resorted to violent
resistance in protest
of some sort of oppression
by the teachers, is that it?
Yeah, pretty much.
It's a decent
hypothesis, overall.
But honestly, I think
it's a little too vague
to fit the bill.
Well, my theory doesn't
mention anything specific,
that's for sure.
But are there flaws in it?
Uh-huh.
Both Hyouka and
Solidarity and Salutes
claim the incident
occurred in June,
but we know he wasn't
expelled until October.
If he had led some violent
uprising against the teachers,
he would have been
expelled immediately.
Fine, then.
Yeah, I'm curious
about why they'd wait
four months to expel him, too.
In Hyouka , it states
that it had been a year
since he left, and it was
published in October,
so that must be accurate.
[MAYAKA groans]
Okay, guys, I get it.
My theory doesn't work.
I think you're on the right
track with the protest, though.
Yeah, I agree.
Well then, I guess that
means it's the end
of my turn, doesn't it?
Yes. Thank you for your input!
--Okay, moving on--
--[stomach growling]
[SATOSHI]
Sorry.
Sounds like my stomach
wants to contribute.
[MAYAKA]
Geez.
You just ate a bunch
of junk food.
Yeah.
I can make you some
onigiri if you want.
What about you guys? Sound good?
[MAYAKA] Hey, Chi, do you
need any help with those?
No, I'm fine,
but thanks for asking.
[MAYAKA]
You sure?
[ERU]
Uh-huh!
Handmade snacks, bro!
Calm down, weirdo.
Wait, Fuku. Doesn't this--?
[SATOSHI]
Mayaka! I'm sorry!
According to this data,
your hypothesis can't be
accurate, not even a little bit.
I forgot to say it earlier.
Fine, whatever.
[HOTARO]
Hm?
Is this the Kami High
Monthly Newsletter?
I just remembered
Togaito mentioning
they were approaching
the 500th issue.
[SATOSHI]
Yeah, he's right.
There are about 500.
I took a quick look through
almost all of the back issues,
but my research didn't
turn up very much.
This article was all that
mentioned an incident
from back then.
And trust me, I looked.
Page two is a summary
of what it says.
The first one and the
last one say the same thing.
No violence occurred
at all during the incident.
So Mayaka, there's proof
against your theory.
Also, if "we" refers
to all of the students,
it says they were in solidarity,
so the entire student body
could have been involved.
At the very least it
means everyone in school
supported those who
actively participated.
[ERU] Here you go.
Thanks for waiting.
[SATOSHI]
Wow!
These look amazing, thanks!
[ERU]
Sure!
I made a few each of plum,
kelp, and mustard leaf.
Help yourselves, okay?
Thank you for the food!
Huh? What's the matter with you?
Nothing!
Tasty!
Delicious!
Hey, Chitanda, is this rice
from here on your family's farm?
It sure is!
Oh. Do you guys
have any questions?
Yeah, are you positive that
this is the "legendary movement"
that got Jun Sekitani
expelled from school?
This blurb doesn't seem
like enough to support that.
Who knows? That's all I've got.
That's all you've got?
How can we even
count it as data?
I don't know,
maybe we can't.
We can still consider it as
circumstantial evidence, though.
If the "Jun Sekitani Incident"
and the "Legendary Movement"
were different events,
there would be something
in there distinguishing this
as the "Legendary Movement,"
wouldn't there?
She's right!
That's what I meant to say.
Thank you for sorting it out!
[MAYAKA]
Hmph!
Okay, then what's
your hypothesis?
Uh... Well, about that...
[ERU]
I'd love to hear it.
Unfortunately, I
don't really have one
to offer to the group right now.
My research only
uncovered enough
to correct the
theory Ibara offered.
And besides...
It's not a database's function
to draw conclusions.
I knew he'd say that.
--[HOTARO] Now, then...
--[MAYAKA] Thanks so much.
--[ERU] You're welcome.
[HOTARO]
What should I do?
[ERU] Okay, Oreki.
It's your turn now.
Hotaro, is this
what I think it is?
"The Fifty-Year Progress
of Kamiyama Secondary School?"
It is.
I thought there
might be something
in the public record
about the incident.
[HOTARO] But now that
I look at it again,
there's nothing at all worth
mentioning to the group.
I haven't come up with
a hypothesis, either.
What's going on?
You're acting weird.
[MAYAKA]
What's the matter?
Did you forget how you're
supposed to proceed?
You start by
presenting your research.
[HOTARO] Does this even qualify
as something I have to do
in the first place?
You're freakin' me out a little.
What's up with you?
Are you feeling okay?
[HOTARO]
Stop it!
Should I blow this off?
[ERU gasps]
Whoa, you scared me!
Sorry, I forgot that I
have some shiitake mushrooms
drying outside.
I have to bring them
in out of the rain!
Do you need any
help with them?
[ERU]
No, it's okay.
Hey, Chitanda.
What is it?
Sorry. But would it be okay
if I used your restroom?
Oh, of course.
Just go right through that door
and then straight down the hall.
You'll see it.
Are you nervous
about presenting?
[HOTARO]
Straight down the hall.
I'll see it, she says.
[HOTARO]
Hm?
Well, I'm lost.
[HOTARO] She's done
so much research.
The least I can do is put
my brain to work for a bit.
[HOTARO]
45 years ago,
something happened
to Jun Sekitani.
There are four
different accounts.
What's the common thread
that ties them all together?
I've got to think.
Student activism.
Nonviolent resistance.
Four months between the
event and his expulsion.
What happened to Jun Sekitani?
What did he do?
You sure were gone
a long time.
Well, excuse me.
It was my turn to present
my research, right?
Sorry, but I don't
have a hypothesis.
So would it be okay
if we just skip my turn?
We could move right on
to the wrap up.
Stop playing. You figured
it out, I can tell.
Maybe. I think I've got
a general explanation.
You've solved the mystery,
haven't you, Oreki?
[SATOSHI] Calm down,
Chitanda, let him explain.
Yeah, come on, impress us.
You'd better not
let us down now.
All right, but I have
to explain it in stages.
[HOTARO] First, let's
establish the "when."
Well, we know it happened
45 years ago, for starters.
If we trust both Hyouka
and Solidarity and Salutes ,
then we know the incident
took place in June,
but that our hero
left in October.
Next, the "where."
We all know it happened at our
own Kamiyama High School.
As for the "Who," according
to Solidarity and Salutes ,
our main player is Jun Sekitani,
president of the
Classic Lit Club.
From the Kami High
Monthly Newsletter,
we learned that the
entire student body
was somehow involved.
Now for the "why."
It makes the most sense that
the students would rise up
in solidarity
against the teachers.
To borrow from Ibara,
the students likely rose up
because something happened
and they thought it
threatened their freedom.
And the event that caused
the whole problem was...
...the cultural festival.
[gasping]
Where did it say in
any of the research
that the cultural festival
was the cause of it?
It didn't, but just
hear me out for a minute.
In June, the teachers
and students met
to discuss the details
of the festival.
And they decided that
the event would be held
four months later, in October.
Are you referring
to this part,
where it says, "meeting to
consider the cultural festival?
[HOTARO] Exactly.
Now take another look at it.
[ERU]
Hmm...
There are circles and
squares marked at the top
of each entry in the calendar.
I've got it!
The squares are recurring
events that happen every year,
but the circles are things
that only took place that year!
That's right.
The same notation appears on
calendars for other years, too.
This is the only year
that they held a meeting
to discuss the cultural
festival, but why is that?
I bet that 45 years ago,
the student body demanded it.
I found a clue in Hyouka .
Right here.
"In the past year, senpai has
gone from being a hero
to a legend.
The cultural festival will
continue its five-day run,
in spite of everything."
I think the key words
here are "five-day run,"
especially with the
"in spite of everything."
What does that mean?
The length of the
cultural festival
is what Jun Sekitani was
fighting the teachers for.
I'm just guessing, but combine
that with this mention
of the principal placing
heightened emphasis
on academics. I believe
that the administration
was trying to shorten
the length of the festival
against the kids' wishes.
I could imagine that throwing
the whole student body
into a burning rage.
That was the motivation,
I bet. The "why."
As for the incident itself,
let's talk about that.
The "how."
The "valiant activism,"
which was popular at the time,
was carried out
by none other than
Classic Lit Club
president Jun Sekitani.
This leads us to the ultimate
question: the "what."
The students did not
engage in violence;
instead, they most likely
decided to boycott class.
With no one to teach,
the school had to acquiesce
and meet with the students,
deciding to abandon the plan
to shorten the festival.
But someone had to pay,
and thus Sekitani was expelled.
So why did so much time
pass between the event
and the expulsion?
Well, if he'd been
kicked out in June,
while tempers were hot,
it would've made things worse.
So they probably waited
until after the festival,
when the hype had
died down a bit.
That's all I've got
for the wrap-up.
[sighs]
Now I finally know.
That's what happened to him?
Excellent work.
That was really impressive.
[chokes]
Yeah, you've really outdone
yourself with that one, Hotaro.
It all adds up, huh?
Why does he get it every time?
It's so freaking annoying!
It came to me.
Do either of you have
objections to his theory?
None here!
I hate to admit it,
but I think he's right.
Well, in that case,
let's focus this year's
Classic Lit Club anthology
on proving Oreki's theory.
We'll get started on that a
little bit later in the term.
On that note, I guess this
meeting is adjourned.
Thank you for your hard work!
[ERU] I can't express how
much I appreciate this.
It's not like I did it
all by myself, you know.
That's true.
But you're the one
who found the answer.
I'll get your umbrella
back to you at school.
Well... See ya.
[ERU]
Although...
Would hearing that
story as a child
really have made me
cry as much as I did?
[ERU]
Next time:
"The Truth About the
Historic Classic Lit Club."