[SATOSHI] So, did you watch
the show last night?
What show?
[SATOSHI]
What do you mean, "what show"?
"The News Crew Saw It:
The Startling Truth
Behind 'Hassie,'
the Giant Eel of Lake Hamana."
[MAYAKA]
Oh, yeah. I watched that, too!
Stuff like that always
turns out to be fake.
"Upon seeing the true nature,
he knew it was no ghost,
but a beckoning flower."
You're such a party pooper.
I think legends make
life more exciting!
Chi, you with me?
I am curious as to the veracity
of the monster sightings.
Nobody can say for sure
if the eel exists,
but I hope it does.
It's more fun that way, y'know?
[HOTARO]
There are no ghosts.
Just beckoning flowers.
[SATOSHI giggles]
Classic Hotaro.
[HOTARO]
The Classic Lit Club consists of
a whopping four members.
All of whom are now being
bounced around on a bus,
headed into the wilderness
for what will surely be
an energy-wasting getaway.
Yippie skippy.
The bus's last stop
is at Zaizen Village,
a place best known
for mountain climbing
and hot springs. The springs
are what we're after.
I've always been of the opinion
that during summer vacation,
one should vacate.
But still...
We haven't been together long,
but I feel like the club's
become a tight-knit group.
Since it's summer break,
why don't we all
go to the hot springs?
Huh?
Well, what d'you say?
You wanna go?
[grunts]
[HOTARO]
Yeah... Okay.
[MAYAKA] The shuttle
should be here to get us
any minute now.
Wow. Great view
from up here, huh?
Oreki... You okay?
You don't look so good.
[HOTARO]
Carsick.
Hotaro wouldn't be
Hotaro if he didn't
find something
to complain about.
The trip was only
an hour and a half.
What a sad sack.
Hey, by the way, thanks
for scoring us rooms.
No problem!
I've got family who
own an inn up here,
and since they're renovating
and can't accept regular guests,
they said we could
stay for free.
[car horn honks]
[ERU]
Come on, Oreki.
--We're here.
--[HOTARO groans]
[SATOSHI]
Let the vacationing commence!
[MAYAKA] Hop to it, Oreki,
or we'll leave you behind.
[SATOSHI] Let's go! I'm ready
to check out this inn.
[BOTH]
Thank you for coming.
Welcome to Seizanso.
This little darling
is Rie Zenna.
And this is her
younger sister Kayo.
--[ERU] It's a pleasure.
--[SATOSHI] Nice to meetcha.
[MAYAKA]
You girls are in sixth grade
and fourth grade, right?
--You've both gotten so tall--
--[RIE] Hug!
Sis! Careful.
[RIE] Your rooms are on the
second floor at the end.
Whoa!
Hotaro, hurry and
check this out!
[HOTARO groans]
[SATOSHI]
We got a good room.
Look at this sweet view.
Maybe coming here wasn't
such a terrible idea.
But I still don't know about
the whole "club vacation" thing.
It would be a lot
more relaxing solo.
Except planning a vacation
takes so much energy!
Come on! Cheer up!
And don't forget that the
only reason this trip happened
was because Chitanda
organized it and Mayaka
hooked us up with
a place to stay.
--[HOTARO growls]
--[knocking]
[MAYAKA]
Hurry up, you two!
[ERU]
It's time for dinner.
[SATOSHI]
You heard 'em.
Let's get some chow, okay?
[sniffs]
[HOTARO]
I smell cheese.
Quiche? Gratin. Maybe fondue?
[HOTARO]
Or not.
[MAYAKA]
Ready to eat?
[ALL] Thank you
very much for the food!
Be sure to save
room for dessert!
Lemme guess: cheesecake?
How did you know?
I could smell it.
[RIE]
That's amazing!
[HOTARO]
Not really.
[whispers] So that stuff
Maya said was true!
[HOTARO]
What did you tell them?
[RIE] We're gonna set
off fireworks tomorrow!
[MAYAKA]
That sounds fun.
Yeah, Dad bought some
for us yesterday--
--[KAYO gasps]
--[RIE] Hey!
What are you doin', clumsy?
Oops. I'm really sorry.
[ERU]
Here.
Oh. Thanks, I'll
just clean this up.
Did it burn you?
No, I'm fine.
[RIE]
Geez. Try to be more careful.
Man. I'm really stuffed.
[HOTARO]
No Satoshi.
He must've gone
down to the baths.
I guess the springs
are kinda the point
of this place, huh?
--[ERU] Oh.
--[HOTARO] Hm?
[ERU] Funny bumping
into you like this.
Where are you headed?
[HOTARO]
Same place as you, I'd guess.
Where's Ibara?
[ERU]
I'm not sure.
She went off with
the girls someplace.
I know this is out of the blue,
but would you mind
telling me a little
about what your sister's like?
Yeah, that's out of
the blue all right.
I guess that you're
curious because
you don't have any siblings.
My sister, huh?
She's a real character for sure.
But she's also pretty brilliant.
I don't think I could outshine
her in any way if I tried.
[ERU]
Wow.
But, of course,
I've never actually
wanted to try, so. Yeah.
[HOTARO] Anyway... What's
with the sudden curiosity?
Seeing the Zenna sisters?
[ERU giggles]
You'll think I'm silly.
But I've always wanted
to have a sibling.
An older sister
or younger brother.
Having somebody around
I could always
feel at home with.
It sounds like a dream to me!
[HOTARO]
A dream, all right.
She's wearing some seriously
rose-colored glasses. Having
a sibling is fine, I guess.
But it's not like
you're guaranteed
to be best friends or anything.
[ERU] Oh. I guess there's
no mixed bathing here.
[yelps]
[HOTARO]
Of course there's not!
Hm?
Satoshi's here.
[door scrapes]
[LITTLE BOY 7A]
Dad, Grandpa, hurry it up!
You're taking forever!
[groans]
Whoa. It's bigger
than I expected.
[splash]
[sighs]
Huh?
Well, what d'ya think?
It's nice, huh?
It's like the spring
water is soaking
through my skin all the way
into my bones, y'know?
Aren't you worried
that your bones
are gonna get waterlogged?
I never knew you were
such a funny guy.
Well, nice to see you cracking
jokes and unclenching a bit.
[HOTARO growls]
[door scrapes]
[HOTARO]
Is that Chitanda?
[splash]
[HOTARO grunts]
[HOTARO pants]
[HOTARO sighs]
[MAYAKA]
Oreki!
Whoa! What happened?
Is he okay?
He overheated.
Huh?
Have you ever heard of
anything so pathetic?
He'd barely even gotten in
before he drooped like a flower
that needs watering.
Yep. That is pretty pathetic.
[HOTARO groans]
[SATOSHI sighs]
Sorry I'm being so much trouble.
That's what friends
are for, right?
[sighs] Come on, is it
just physically impossible
for you to enjoy anything?
Apparently so.
It was probably
leftover carsickness.
Must've been.
[knocking]
[door clicks]
[footsteps]
[HOTARO]
Is that Chitanda?
[ERU]
Hey, Oreki. Are you all right?
[HOTARO]
Not really.
[grunts]
You still feel really hot.
I can bring you a
cold towel if you want.
[HOTARO]
No! No thanks!
I just wanna sleep.
I'm sorry for making
such a nuisance of myself.
No, don't worry.
We don't have big
plans for the night,
just telling some ghost stories.
[HOTARO]
Heh...
[ERU]
I'm sure it'll be fun.
If you feel better, you
should come join us, okay?
Well. Get some rest.
Thanks.
[sighs]
It's not even eight o'clock yet?
[distant drumming]
[HOTARO]
Taiko drums?
[RIE]
The truth is,
the inn didn't actually
need a second hall.
[HOTARO] I guess they've
got their window open, too.
[RIE]
There's a secret.
[MAYAKA]
A secret?
[RIE]
Long ago.
An old, brooding man
came to stay here.
They put him in Room Seven
of the main hall.
He said he didn't want food.
And he didn't want a futon.
And people should
just leave him alone.
It was strange,
but he paid in advance
and came during the busy season,
so nobody asked any questions.
--However, that night,
--[INNKEEPER 7A screams]
a terrible scream rang out!
--[SATOSHI] Then what?
--[screaming]
[RIE] People looked up
to see the shadowy figure
of a person with a
rope around his neck,
dimly visible, swinging
back and forth.
Rumor had it that the man
had embezzled money
from the company he worked for.
[SATOSHI]
Then what? Then what?
[MAYAKA]
Will you stop that?
[RIE] After it happened,
guests who stayed in Room Seven
said that they could feel
something in there with them.
They could see shadows
mysteriously appearing
during the night.
Finally,
the ninth guest
after the hanged man...
[ERU]
Tell us! What happened?
[RIE] During the night,
he fell suddenly ill...
...and died!
[ERU]
Oh, no!
[SATOSHI]
Then what?! Then what?!
[MAYAKA]
I said stop it!
[RIE] Well, first, Grandma
called in an exorcist,
then she had this
second hall built.
So guests could sleep far
away from the haunted room.
[SATOSHI]
Where is Room Seven?
[RIE] There. Look out
the window, straight ahead.
It's that one.
We live down on the
first floor, and we try
not to come up to the
second floor very much.
[MAYAKA]
Hold on!
I thought this was just a story.
[RIE] You can't tell anyone
I told you about this, okay?
[HOTARO]
A local ghost story. How quaint.
Hm?
[snoring]
[HOTARO]
Morning.
[RIE]
Oh! Good morning.
[HOTARO]
Good morning. Is anyone else up?
Uh...
[MAYAKA]
I saw it.
[HOTARO]
What d'you mean? Saw what?
I was sleeping so soundly,
then sometime after midnight
a warm breeze woke me up.
And when I rolled over...
I saw the silhouette
of a hanged man
in the room across the way,
slowly swinging back and forth!
[HOTARO] It's pretty rare
to see Ibara so shaken up.
Satoshi's gonna be sad
he missed out on this.
[HOTARO]
Thanks for breakfast.
How were the baths yesterday?
[ERU]
I thought they were fantastic!
Good, I'm glad!
[HOTARO]
Hm?
[RIE] And I hope your futon
was nice and fluffy, too!
[ERU]
Yes, it was perfect, thank you!
[RIE giggles]
[HOTARO] It doesn't look
like there's one for Kayo.
[RIE giggles] Sorry you didn't
sleep so well, Maya,
but I figured you could handle
a little ghost story.
Hey, it's not like I'm scared
of ghosts or anything.
But I know what I saw
through that window.
And it was seriously creepy!
You really saw it? You're sure?
I know what I saw, okay?
Creepy, creepy!
[KAYO] How could you tell
them that story, Rie?
Dad said we were never
supposed to tell anyone!
Who asked you? It's only Maya.
I don't see what
the big deal is.
[gasps]
What's wrong?
Well... What Mayaka
said she saw...
Do you think it was real?
What--the silhouette
of a hanged man?
Well, ghost stories are a staple
of these rural areas.
They live on for generations.
So, what are you saying?
Do you really think she saw the
ghost of a man who died here?
No, I don't.
[gasps] In that case, I must
have been mistaken, too.
Mistaken about what?
I saw the same thing she did.
--The shadow of a hanged man.
--[HOTARO gasps]
[ERU] I woke up when Mayaka
started freaking out.
And when I looked
out at the room
across the way, I saw it.
[HOTARO]
Oh.
[ERU]
I thought my mind must have been
playing tricks on me.
But if she and I both
saw the same thing...
You both must have
mistook what you saw.
Like in that saying.
The one Satoshi
quoted on the bus.
It was nothing but
a beckoning flower?
[HOTARO]
Mm-hm.
Well, if that's true,
what was it we
were really seeing?
--[grunts]
--[MAYAKA] Yeah!
If you're so smart,
tell us what we were
actually looking at!
--Wait, why should I have to--
--[ERU] Oreki!
Investigate this with us!
Will you? I have to know!
[sighs]
[MAYAKA]
I'm sorry, Chi!
I wanna help,
but I promised Rie
I'd look over her homework.
You can leave it to us.
Oreki and I will get to
the bottom of this mystery!
Isn't that right?
[HOTARO]
As if I had a choice.
We don't have to go far, anyway.
That's some
consolation at least.
[HOTARO]
Okay.
So you saw this shadow-thing
in the room directly
across from yours, right?
Yes, that's where we saw it.
[HOTARO]
How big was it?
It's not like it was huge,
but it wasn't small either.
And the shape?
[ERU]
Well, it's hard to say exactly.
The color?
[ERU]
I don't know. It was in shadow.
Yeah, right.
Whatever it was, it was lit
from behind so it looked
like the silhouette of a person.
[ERU]
That's how it seemed to me.
So then it was backlit.
Around here, the only
source of light
at night would
have been the moon.
That's what I was thinking, too.
And the moon was bright
enough that it could have
lit something up.
Do you think that means--
[ERU gasps]
The shutters.
So what time did you finish
your stories and go to sleep?
[ERU]
About ten, I think.
And the shutters then?
[ERU] I believe they were
closed at that point.
Huh.
If the shutters
were closed then,
there's no way there
could have been a shadow.
Which means we've run
into a little snag.
At this point, our best
bet is to check out
Room Seven in the main hall.
This is so fun, don't you think?
I'm extra-glad we came
to this place now!
[HOTARO]
And I'm extra-wishing we hadn't.
[footsteps]
[HOTARO]
Hey!
Oh. Yes. Hello.
You talk.
--[ERU] Huh?
--I really suck with kids.
[ERU]
Oh, okay.
Kayo, can we borrow
you for a sec?
Oreki and I would like
to have a look around
in the main hall.
The main hall? Why? What for?
We're investigating
the creepy shadow
we talked about this morning.
If it's not too much
trouble, maybe you could
show us Room Seven?
I'm really sorry, but I
don't think I should do that.
If I did, my sister
would get mad at me.
Okay, at least
tell us one thing.
Is the supposedly haunted room
still used for guests?
No, it's not.
In the main hall, the baths
and the dining room
are the only areas where
the guests are allowed.
So, the room's vacant then?
[KAYO] The whole second floor
is used for storage now.
Please. May I go?
Of course. You've been
very help... ful.
There, you see? She hates me.
No, I doubt it.
She probably finds
all boys intimidating.
What a sweet girl!
[HOTARO]
Mm...
[ERU] Is it a big problem
that we can't get in
to see the room?
[HOTARO] Not so much
a problem as a hassle.
This would be easier if
we could inspect the scene.
Oh! I remember doing these, too.
[HOTARO]
Hm?
[ERU]
Morning radio calisthenics.
I went to them up until
the year before last.
[HOTARO] Until her second
year of middle school?
Seriously?
[ERU] We should check
around the other side.
[HOTARO grunts]
The ground's muddy.
Did it rain last night?
Yeah. A little.
[HOTARO] In order to create
a shadow that you would see
from your room across the way,
both the east and
west side shutters
would have to have been open.
[KAYO]
Excuse me.
If you're hungry,
lunch is ready.
[RIE]
Well, back to work!
[KAYO]
Thank you for joining us.
Just look at those two together!
It must be nice.
Having a sister, you mean?
So do you wish that you had one?
Yeah. Kinda.
So, find anything out?
No.
We're just getting started.
I do have a theory, though.
Yeah? Then let's hear.
Huh?
[SATOSHI]
Enough of this.
What are you
three talking about?
It isn't nice to leave
a buddy in the dark.
If you're so anxious
to be kept in the loop,
then quit disappearing
all the time.
We never see you.
I'm being polite, okay.
It's good manners to visit
the hot springs repeatedly.
[HOTARO]
Is he making that up?
[RIE]
Ta-dah!
Well. Like my yukata?
Wow! It's lovely.
Looks great!
[RIE giggles]
I finally got one
at the beginning
of summer vacation.
[MAYAKA]
You've said you wanted one...
[whispering] Can't say
I'm impressed.
What's wrong with it?
You see the sash?
It's not the real deal.
Well, it looks
real enough to me.
You're the last
person I'd come to
for fashion advice.
Check out the bow.
It's a separate piece
clipped onto the sash.
I don't acknowledge
that as a yukata.
[HOTARO]
I acknowledge you as ridiculous.
[yawns]
[HOTARO gasps]
[SATOSHI]
Is something the matter?
Hm?
[HOTARO]
That stupid shadow.
It's got me as jumpy
as those other two.
Wanna go back to
the same spring?
Sure!
[HOTARO]
The hanged silhouette.
It's the product of Chitanda's
and Ibara's false impression,
nothing more. Just a
beckoning flower.
We're still missing
a piece of the puzzle.
[ERU]
Let's walk back together.
[HOTARO]
Satoshi's here.
All right.
You finished eating at the
inn the same time we did.
So how'd you end up
getting here before us?
Well,
if you slide down the
cliff behind Seizanso,
you end up at a spot
right behind this spring.
[HOTARO] Sliding down
a cliff just to save
a couple of minutes?
That's vintage Satoshi.
[sighs]
[HOTARO]
I don't have an explanation
that will satisfy Chitanda yet.
The source of the
shadow is easy enough.
The question is, how did
it wind up in Room Seven?
Hotaro, you're not gonna
faint again, are you?
Hey.
Tell me about last night--
anything interesting happen?
Besides the whole
fainting thing?
Yes, besides that!
[SATOSHI]
Well, we all told ghost stories.
And I was surrounded by more
girls than I could handle.
No, something more official.
Oh, sure. There was
a summer festival.
You heard the
taiko drums, right?
[HOTARO]
Taiko drums.
That's it! A summer festival!
That explains everything!
So? That mean something?
Ah!
[HOTARO] I know what
the shadow really was.
Probably...
I think it was a yukata
hanging on a hanger.
Huh?
[ERU]
But why would there be a yukata
hanging in that room?
And for that matter,
why would someone
leave the shutters
open to display it?
[HOTARO]
Displaying it wasn't the point.
So...?
It was hanging there to dry.
The yukata was wet.
The reason the
shutters were open
was to let the breeze through,
so that it would
dry more quickly.
But, why?
[HOTARO]
It rained last night.
That's not what I mean.
Why was it in Room Seven?
Because in a deserted room,
no one would see that it
had been hung up to dry.
Except we saw it.
True.
But it's the family
they were hiding it from.
The family?
[HOTARO]
The person who hung it there...
...was Kayo.
Kayo was envious
of Rie's yukata,
and she wanted to wear it.
But I doubt Rie would
lend it to her.
[ERU]
But why not? They're sisters.
[HOTARO] Didn't you notice?
Rie marks all her stuff.
She makes it clear which cup,
which radio calisthenics card,
and which ball is hers.
That kind of person
isn't going to lend out
her most treasured possession.
[ERU]
Oh.
[HOTARO] But Kayo still
wanted to borrow it.
So she snuck it out
of the inn and wore it
to the summer
festival last night.
This would've been
around eight o'clock.
[ERU]
Kayo went to the festival?
[HOTARO]
That's my theory.
I saw someone leaving the
place at eight last night.
[HOTARO] And Kayo wasn't
there when you were
telling ghost stories, right?
[ERU]
Yeah, you're right.
She wasn't there.
Unfortunately for Kayo,
she ran into some bad
luck at the festival.
It started raining.
The rain let up quickly,
but the yukata still got wet.
Kayo remembered that we would
be setting off
fireworks the next day.
And Rie would surely wanna
wear the yukata for that.
If it wasn't dry by tomorrow,
Rie would know what
she'd done for sure.
[HOTARO]
The family would see it
on the main hall's first floor.
And the other hall was
where we were staying.
She couldn't use the dryer
in the middle of the night.
So, she waited for
everyone to go to sleep
and dried the yukata
in the most distant room
on the second floor.
But poor Kayo's
bad luck continued.
Moonlight shone in
through the open window,
illuminating the
yukata's silhouette.
[HOTARO]
And then, to make matters worse,
we started investigating
the mysterious shadow.
Kayo must have been
a nervous wreck.
[HOTARO] That must have
been her shadow I saw.
Sneaking between
the sliding doors.
Kayo...
[HOTARO] She put the yukata
back early in the morning.
Unlike Rie, Kayo went to
radio calisthenics every day.
It would've been easy
enough to return it.
[ERU]
So that's it then.
[HOTARO] I'm not going
to tell Ibara about this.
I think it's kind of
a family matter.
[ERU]
If that's true...
...then it means that
the two of them
don't actually get along.
[ERU]
I mean,
a sister who won't
lend you her yukata...
[ERU sighs]
That's just how
it is with siblings.
--Sometimes you fight.
--[ERU] You know, I...
[ERU]
I wanted a sibling.
An older sister
I could look up to.
Or a younger brother
I could look out for.
[HOTARO] Is Chitanda's idea
of the perfect sibling real,
or is it a beckoning flower?
So hot.
You ready?
Yeah.
[gasps]
Well, maybe it's actually
a little bit of both.
[ERU] Next time:
"Let's Go To the Screening!"