[HOTARO] I appreciate
the lunch and all, Sis,
but I have no idea
what half this stuff is.
Here goes nothing.
[sniffs]
[ERU]
We're back!
Thank you for
holding down the fort.
[HOTARO]
Sure.
[SATOSHI]
Anyway... we were victorious!
It did come down
to the wire.
Congrats. I'm happy for you.
In a way, it's your victory too.
There's no chance we could
have won without your help.
No big deal. Really.
[SATOSHI] You know,
I didn't see that coming.
It was very out of character.
Staging a dramatic rescue?
I wasn't expecting that one,
[HOTARO] I guess I was
caught up in the festival mood.
It won't happen again.
[SATOSHI chuckles]
[ERU]
Can you do me a favor?
There's something I would really
like you to take a look at.
[ERU]
Here it is.
[HOTARO] So, somebody stole a
ladle from the Cooking Club?
[MAYAKA] Yeah... Just the one
from our table, though.
Sounds like someone has
too much time on their hands.
[SATOSHI]
It's not just the Cooking Club.
The same kinda thing's
happened to the Go Club
and the Acapella Club.
[ERU]
And the Fortunetelling Club.
A note was left there, too!
Let's see...
what did it say again?
[HOTARO] Yeah, somebody's
got way too much time
on their hands.
Think I can
finish my lunch now?
[ERU]
Oreki!
[HOTARO]
Oh, no. Here we go again.
There's no escaping
the unbearable curiosity
of Eru Chitanda.
[ERU]
Who would do something like this
in the middle of
the cultural festival?
Why are they appropriating
Jumonji's name?
Why are they stealing
all these random items?
I just... I have to know!
[HOTARO] We don't have
time for a new mystery.
We need to sell these--
[SATOSHI]
Speaking of the anthologies...
...we need a new plan.
We've been publicizing them
during our other events,
but it doesn't seem
to be doing much good.
[MAYAKA]
That's true.
We need to come up
with something
that's going to grab
more people's attention.
[SATOSHI]
Right! That's my point.
What if we pitch
this phantom thievery
to the Wall Newspaper Club?
And maybe we can have the school
radio do a report about it too.
With that publicity, people will
be dying to read the anthology.
Makes sense to me.
That could be
exactly what we need!
But what kind of pitch are
you going to give them?
This has nothing to do
with the Classic Lit Club.
I'm glad you asked.
[clears throat]
[SATOSHI] The Classic Lit Club's
master detective, Hotaro Oreki,
will set out to catch
the phantom thief
who is plaguing the festival!
To learn more about
his past exploits,
check out the Classic Lit
Club's anthology, Hyouka !
[ERU clapping] Who wouldn't
want one after that?
[MAYAKA]
Yeah, it was okay, I guess.
[SATOSHI]
Right?
We'll unmask Jumonji and
publicize the anthology
--at the same time!
--[HOTARO] Count me out!
What do you think I am, huh?
Some monkey that you can use
to lure in customers? Hmph!
Can't we just give it a try?
Pretty please?
[HOTARO]
Oh, come on.
Even if I did
play along with this,
there are a thousand
students here.
Add in all the visitors, and the
number goes up even higher.
How are we supposed to catch
one thief out of so many people?
Is it that hard? Really?
Impossible.
Maybe if we got
involved some other way.
Like if the thief targeted the
Classic Lit Club or something.
Yeah. Well...
[SATOSHI] We could
stage a robbery!
--[SATOSHI] Kidding!
--[MAYAKA] No way!
[SATOSHI] Really! I swear!
I was just kidding.
[HOTARO]
Speaking of targets...
Which clubs have had
things stolen so far?
Go, acapella, cooking,
and I uh... I forget.
[ERU]
The Fortunetelling Club.
Yeah. Right!
[HOTARO]
The Acapella Club,
the Go Club,
The Fortunetelling Club,
and the Cooking Club?
[SATOSHI gasps]
ABC!
[ERU]
Huh? Huh?
[SATOSHI]
Hello, Suzuki?
It looks like the clubs
that could go with "E"
are the Film Club,
the Gardening Club,
and the SF club.
I'm lost. What's going on?
[HOTARO]
The thefts follow a pattern.
And it's not an especially
complex one, either.
The Acapella Club,
the Igo Club,
the Uranai Club.
Skip a letter to
the Oryori Club,
and if an "E" club
pops up next...
Japanese alphabetic order!
That would be my guess.
The Gardening Club has been hit.
They stepped out for a second
and one of their
water guns was stolen.
A water gun?
Fire safety for
roasting potatoes.
One of their members came
in here with one yesterday.
Just a second.
In Christie's The ABC Murders ,
a person whose name
starts with an "A"
is killed in a town whose
name starts with "A."
An otama was stolen
from the Oryori Club.
[SATOSHI]
Wait, hold on.
Right.
What did the Fortunetelling
Club lose? Do you know?
Oh... yes!
The Wheel of Fortune.
A Tarot card.
[SATOSHI]
Okay. Take a look.
[HOTARO] The Gardening Club's
water pistol was an AK,
wasn't it?
An AK? What's that?
[HOTARO]
A Russian-made assault rifle.
[MAYAKA] So it's an AK (eikei)
for the Engei Club,
and ishi for the Igo Club?
[SATOSHI] That works.
What about the Acapella Club?
[HOTARO] I think we're missing
the most important thing.
[SATOSHI]
And what's that?
[HOTARO]
Our phantom thief's signature.
Yeah, it says Jumonji.
Does it, though?
Wouldn't the usual
reading be "jumoji"?
[gasp]
[SATOSHI, MAYAKA, ERU]
"Tenth letter"!
[SATOSHI] A-I-U-E-O,
Ka-Ki-Ku-Ke-Ko,
up to the tenth letter!
[ERU]
"Ko!" The Koten Club!
[HOTARO] Otherwise known
as the Classic Lit Club.
I don't know about you,
but I'd say that's probably
enough for a pitch.
[ERU] I need to get to
the Wall Newspaper Club
and tell them about this!
She's pretty excited, huh?
[HOTARO]
What's wrong?
Huh?
Oh... I just thought of
something, that's all.
This whole thing...
[SATOSHI] You know,
never mind. I gotta go.
That's weird. What's with him?
[MAYAKA]
Who knows?
[HOTARO] Shouldn't you be
getting back to the Manga Club?
Soon enough.
[HOTARO]
Hmm...
Why? You trying
to get rid of me?
Well, are you?
Cranky today.
[growls] No, I am not!
[ERU]
The trick to negotiating.
First, make it seem like
you expect something
of the other person.
Second, downplay the benefit
that you will receive from it,
and third, ask someone
of the opposite sex,
away from public view.
All right!
[NEWSPAPER BOY A]
On it!
I'll go interview
the Gardening Club!
[NEWSPAPER BOY B]
Hey! What about Acapella?
I'm calling them right now!
[NEWSPAPER BOY B]
Hurry it up, will you?
[STUDENTS chattering]
I'm sorry. Excuse me!
Sorry about this, Chitanda,
but we're a little
busy right now.
Think you could
drop by another time?
Oh, okay. I'll come back later.
Actually, no!
I need to talk
to you right now!
If it's about your club,
I told you--
We need a special angle--
That's just it.
We do have an angle!
Yeah? What's that?
[NEWSPAPER BOY C]
I know that! Stop rushing me!
[NEWSPAPER BOY B] Never mind,
let's change gears.
What are we doing
about that interview?
Do you think we
could hurry this up?
I'm really--
[TOGAITO]
Whoa! Hey!
Where are we going?
[ERU] The thing is,
there's some stuff going on,
and I really felt like I needed
to tell someone about it.
So... uh...
I came here. I trust you.
Oh... Yeah?
Thanks, I guess...?
But honestly,
there's not much in it
for the Classic Lit Club.
'Kay...
What do you think?
Can you help, Togaito?
Is this something
you can do for me?
Uh... well...
Honestly, I'm a little confused.
[ERU]
Oh, sorry.
[TOGAITO] Anyway, like I said,
we're busy right now.
Come back later after
you've gathered your thoughts.
No...
Please wait!
Somebody at the festival
is stealing things
from various clubs
for no apparent reason!
There! That's the story!
Jumonji!
That's who you mean!
Do you know something?
[ERU]
Huh? Well... uh...
Right, alphabetical order.
I see the pattern.
And you say the Fortunetelling
Club got hit, too.
So that's why, then.
So that's why what?
[TOGAITO] Oh.
We're the Kabe Newspaper Club.
[ERU gasps]
They got you too?
Jumonji took our kata knife.
I guess that explains
why all of you
are running around like crazy.
Yeah.
I don't usually like
being stolen from,
but at least we got a
good story out of it.
I'm impressed.
Your club figured out a lot.
It was mainly Oreki.
You remember him.
Yeah. Sure.
Anyway, thanks for the tip.
Appreciate it!
[ERU]
Please wait, Togaito!
[ERU] I gave you some
helpful information.
I hope you'll write about
the Classic Lit Club now!
You will... right?
[ERU] I kind of lost my cool
toward the end there.
I hope Togatio doesn't think
I was doubting his integrity.
[footsteps]
--[SATOSHI] Excuse me!
--[ERU] Sorry!
Oh, it's you. Well?
Did you have any luck?
Oh... well...
That's a good question.
Sorry, never mind.
It's an inside joke.
Okay.
Well, anyway, I finally heard
back from the Acapella Club.
Looks like it was
apple juice that was taken.
Turns out the Wall Newspaper
Club was targeted, too.
Apparently they had their
cutter knife stolen.
Right. "Ka."
Japanese alphabetical
order for sure.
Next up is the letter "ki,"
which can only be the
Kijutsu , or Magic Club.
Fortunately, it's almost time
for the next performance,
and I think I'm gonna go.
[ERU] You wanna catch
Jumoji in the act?
Yep.
That's a big weakness
for this kind of thief.
He's bound by his own rules,
so he's predictable.
We just have to anticipate
Jumoji's next move,
and the thief will be unmasked.
But if we catch him at "ki,"
then it will all be over.
[SATOSHI] And the culprit
will never have made it
to the Classic Lit Club.
That's all right.
I'm sure we can
figure something out.
[ERU]
Really? Like what, exactly?
Let's talk later, but now
I need to get to the Magic Club.
Gotta catch a thief. See ya!
It's still only 2:00.
[SATOSHI whistling]
[TANI]
Ah, well, look who it is.
Hey. How's it going?
If you're standing around
waiting for the show to start,
that means you must know.
Know what?
Don't play dumb with me!
You know about the
phantom thief Jumoji.
Oh. That...
[TANI chuckles] Good, then this
will be our next competition.
You know about
the Newspaper Club?
The cutter knife, you mean?
Sure, I heard about it.
Yeah.
Obviously, they've taken an
interest in the crime spree.
Jumoji is the
next issue's top story.
What's more, they're
going to run an extra,
exclusively covering any group
that catches the phantom thief.
Yeah.
[TANI]
Well, I hate to break it to you,
but I've got
this one in the bag.
Because you know who's
a major mystery fan?
That's right! It's me!
Go easy on me, okay?
[HOTARO]
Ibara.
You're a Christie fan, right?
So you must have read
The ABC Murders at some point.
[MAYAKA]
Yeah, of course I have.
[HOTARO]
Then can you tell me something?
Was there a reason why
the killings were done
in alphabetical order?
[MAYAKA]
Spoiler alert! Are you sure?
[HOTARO]
Go ahead.
[MAYAKA] "He wanted to kill
in alphabetical order,
so that's what he did."
Not exactly much of
a motivation, is it?
No.
Do you think the same
thing is going on here?
I don't know.
Anybody would have
figured out the pattern
the thefts were
following eventually.
Surely Jumoji would
have realized that.
[MAYAKA]
So why do it that way, then?
Right, that's what
I'm wondering.
Is there some kind of
hidden purpose or meaning
behind the way in which
things are being stolen?
Still, it is possible
Jumoji's doing it just for fun.
[MAYAKA]
Hmm... Interesting.
You really want to catch
the thief now, don't you?
You think so? Why's that?
You're pretty intent.
I don't care
one way or another.
But once Chitanda says she's
curious about something,
it becomes an issue
that can't be avoided.
Why don't you just ignore her?
She's not someone
I can easily ignore,
or trust me, I would.
[MAYAKA giggles]
Right, I get it.
Okay, then.
You're leaving?
Yep.
Oh, and by the way,
thank you for the flour.
It was a big help.
Oh! I almost forgot.
Really? You're charging me?
No, it's not like that.
It's the Warashibe Protocol.
I need you to give me something
in return for the flour.
You do?
Like in the old folk tale.
The guy starts with
a piece of straw
and trades till he gets rich.
Oh, yeah, okay.
Let's see...
[MAYAKA]
You can have this.
Are you sure?
Yep.
Really? Can you
cosplay without i--Ah!
[MAYAKA]
Don't call it that, you idiot!
The show will be starting soon.
Please take your
seats, everybody.
[SATOSHI]
Irisu! Over here.
[IRISU]
Oh. Hello.
[SATOSHI]
I can't wait for the show. You?
I'm not sure how much
I like magic, but here I am.
Yeah. It's something
to do, right?
[SATOSHI]
Could she be...?
[chuckles]
That's crazy.
[YUASA]
I mean, come on.
He didn't have to
say it like that...
[SATOSHI] That's the
Manga Club president.
I saw her at
their booth yesterday.
[GIRL 15A]
Well, this should be fun.
Oh... Hey, look!
[GIRL 15B gasps]
[SATOSHI]
Tanabe just walked in.
And look at that!
He's with the Student Council
President, Muneyoshi Kugayama.
[KUGAYAMA]
Hey, Empress.
[TANABE]
Hello.
[IRISU]
Hi.
[TANABE]
Hey, Fukube.
[SATOSHI]
Hi!
Thank you for your patience!
The Magic Club's
performance will now begin.
We're glad to see
so many friendly faces
in the audience this afternoon.
We hope you'll enjoy the show
that we've put together for you
and the tricks we've worked
long and hard to master!
[AUDIENCE clapping]
[SATOSHI]
Now, then...
With this many people
watching the show,
how will you commit your crime,
phantom thief Jumoji?
[TAYAMA] Yoichi Takamura
will perform "Living Dead."
[TAYAMA]
What's wrong?
[NAGAI]
Well...
[SATOSHI gasps]
Candle!
[SATOSHI]
Sorry. Don't mind me.
Damn!
[SATOSHI]
When...?
I was watching, and nobody
but the performers
went near the stage.
Which means... it was
taken before they started.
[SATOSHI] Ugh. Coming here
was a waste of time!
What made me so sure
he would steal something
during the performance, anyway?
I'm an idiot!
[CROWD clapping]
[MAYAKA, KIMURA] Thanks a lot!
Have a good day!
We're selling more
than yesterday, right?
Yeah, we are.
I guess the posters are helping.
That's great!
[GIRLS giggling]
Obviously, we should have
just done what Kochi said
from the very beginning.
Yeah.
If a certain someone
hadn't thrown a fit,
I bet we could have sold
a bunch more yesterday.
Careful, now.
We don't want to hurt
anyone's feelings, do we?
Try to ignore them.
Yeah.
And after all that,
she couldn't find the thing?
A total lie, right?
I'm sure she just got
scared that the manga
she was going on about was
actually nothing special.
How pathetic! Bringing up
some amateur title
just to make
yourself look smart.
[GIRLS giggling]
[ITZUKA]
Yeah, totally!
[HENMI] How much you want to bet
that manga doesn't even exist?
--[MAYAKA] Hey, hold on--
--[KOCHI] Stop! That's enough.
If you've never heard of it,
you can keep quiet.
Hi, everyone.
I-I was just saying--
[KOCHI]
Well now I'm saying.
If you don't know anything,
you should just keep
your mouth shut.
So anyway...
How was the Magic Club show?
Good. I really enjoyed it.
[KIMURA]
Yeah?
Maybe I could go and check
it out tomorrow, then.
[YUASA]
Okay. That should be fine.
[KIMURA]
What time does it start?
[YUASA] They do performances
throughout the day,
so I'm sure you can
make it to one of them.
Really? Thanks a lo--
Sorry. Think I can take a break?
[KIMURA]
Sure. No problem.
Hey!
I really am pathetic.
I just want someone
to tell me it'll be okay.
[YUASA]
Ibara?
Uh... Yes!
What's up, Yuasa?
I'm really sorry.
Things have gotten
pretty awkward, huh?
I don't know why
you're apologizing.
For not saying
anything sooner.
I should have taken your
side before, and I didn't.
Except, if you had
stood up for me yesterday,
there probably would've been
friction between you and Kochi,
and I wouldn't
want that to happen.
I think it's better this way.
It's all bluster.
Ayako doesn't mean it.
Ayako?
Ayako Kochi.
That's her full name.
Oh.
She seemed pretty serious,
so what makes you
think she didn't mean it?
Because I know her.
She and I are friends.
Is that it?
There's also the fact that
she and Haruna were friends.
Sorry. Who's Haruna?
Haruna Anjo. Don't you know?
She's one of the authors
of A Corpse by Evening .
It was a collaborative work?
[YUASA] Somebody else
did the art for it.
Ayako would probably
know who it was.
Can I talk to Haruna?
What class is she in?
Well, she doesn't
go here anymore.
She transferred schools.
Really? Too bad.
But even if they
were good friends,
what does that matter?
Friends don't
agree on everything.
Maybe this was something
they disagreed about.
Yes, that's a
good point, but sorry.
I really shouldn't say any more
than I've already told you.
I mean...
Ayako is my friend, after all.
And explaining why
you think what you do
would mean speaking
badly of her?
I think I need a
little more time alone.
Are you sure?
[MAYAKA] It's okay.
I won't be much longer.
[NEWSPAPER BOY C]
Extra! Extra!
It's a must-read, kids!
[ERU]
He did come through!
[SATOSHI]
Bad news. I've been had!
There was a candle stolen
from the Magic Club earlier.
They even found the
standard confession note.
Isn't that good news, though?
We don't want the thief
caught before he hits
the Classic Lit Club, right?
Yeah. I know that's
what we decided.
But I thought maybe I
could catch him red-handed.
You hoped the theft would
happen during the performance?
[SATOSHI]
Yeah.
[HOTARO] Jumoji doesn't really
seem to want an audience
for the thefts.
I mean, the Cooking Club's
ladle disappeared
before the contest, right?
If you realized that,
then why not say something?
It's not like you told me you
were going to the Magic Club
to catch him in the act.
Yeah. I guess that's true.
[ERU]
Hey, guys, I'm back!
And I'm happy to report that
the 20 volumes of Hyouka
we left with Irisu are
selling at a good pace!
[HOTARO] Irisu could sell
a glass of water
to a drowning man.
[ERU]
There's one other thing, too.
In their 4:00 edition,
the Wall Newspaper Club
has included an article
that covers the Jumoji case.
It also mentions the
alphabetical order pattern
of the crimes.
Cool.
[ERU] The best part is that
we're in the story, too.
It says that the final
item will be taken
from either the Industrial Arts
Club or the Classic Lit Club.
An IA club?
We have one of those?
Yeah, we do. Guess I forgot.
If they get hit, then our whole
plan goes up in smoke, huh?
I'm thinking about making a deal
with the Broadcasting
Club tomorrow.
If we can get them
to give us some airtime,
that would be great publicity.
What? Is something wrong?
Well... It's just...
--You look... tired.
--[MAYAKA] Man, am I tired.
[SATOSHI]
Oh. Mayaka.
So how were our sales today?
Not counting the ones
we gave Irisu,
we managed to sell 16.
Not that bad.
I guess so. Yeah.
It could be worse.
As president,
it's my job to go around
recruiting people to
help us sell the anthology.
But honestly...
I'm getting worn out.
[MAYAKA]
Body Talk .
There's no denying it's a step
below A Corpse by Evening .
But still, it's pretty good.
[MAYAKA] Ugh. My stuff is
a hundred steps below.
[SATOSHI]
Hotaro's changed.
No, more like he's finally
showing his true potential.
And it's all because
he met Chitanda.
She's brought an element of
unpredictability into his life
that's forcing him to grow.
I should be happy for him.
And I am, really.
It's just sometimes I wish...
There are over a
thousand suspects.
There's no way that
simple deduction
is going to be able to
whittle down a list that long.
Which means that our best
shot at solving this mystery
is catching the
thief in the act.
I don't know if Hotaro will
be able to solve this one,
but I think I can.
Hotaro. I'm going to catch
Jumoji, just you watch.
They do mail order too?
[SATOSHI]
Next time: "The Final Target."