Luffy, Listen to me, okay?
There's only one way to live without any regrets.
Someday, we're gonna set sail, just like Sabo.
We're gonna live the way we wanna live...
more free than anyone else.
Ace! We're getting you outta here!
Luffy, no!
Now, activate the encircling walls!
What is that?
They've closed us in!
What the hell's going on?
What's going on down there?
Why didn't the last wall raise?
It's Oar's body.
The walls don't seem strong enough to lift it!
We simply can't wait around any longer.
Do it now!
Meteor Volcano!
Phase two is the immediate execution of Portgas D. Ace!
I'm here, Ace!
Straw Boy!
Stop being so reckless!
I need a favor!
Little Oars!
Save Ace!
How is he still alive?
Back off!
You're not killing Ace!
It's a fluke you got this far and
you're too green to go any further.
Gum-Gum Stamp Gatling!
You almost made it.
We caught those punks off guard.
I never said they had sunk all of our ships.
Another coated pirate ship's about to enter the bay,
Now, sink that thing!
Cease fire! The ship is too fast.
Aim your fire at Oars!
He plucked the ship right out of the bay!
They've broken through the encircling walls!
It's Whitebeard!
Whitebeard has entered the plaza!
Oars.
Everyone, try to save Ace!
And as soon as we've got him back, then destroy the Navy!
You ready?
Yeah.
Hold on, Ace! I'm coming to get you!
Keep running straight ahead and don't look back!
Inazuma!
Don't worry, Iva, I shall give it my best.
It's a bridge!
Thanks, Crab.
Straight to the top.
It's Inazuma of the Revolutionary Army!
Luffy!
I told you! I'm here!
You're a pirate, Luffy!
That makes you my enemy!
Garp, no!
I made it!
You really are crazy.
Hold it!...
Struggle all you like,
but you're trapped in the palm of my hand!
What the heck is that thing?
Three, quick! Build us a wall!
I'm not losing now!
Gum-Gum Giant Balloon!
Candle Wall!
Here's the key! Best of luck to you, Straw Hat!
Thanks, Three!
Fire!
Blow them to bits before they hit the ground!
Captain Buggy! Brother 3 was caught in that blast!
No way!
You've never listened to a word I said, have you?
Ever since you were a whiny brat,
you've always been doing crazy things.
You really haven't changed much at all!
Let's go!
Ace.
Sorry, Luffy. I tried.
Don't worry.
We'll get you some help.
Thank you for trying so hard,
but this is as far as I can go.
C'mon, what're you saying? This isn't over yet!
We were so close.
Don't give up yet, we still have a chance.
You're too late!
This way, Doctor! Quick! It's not looking good!
I can feel my life slipping away.
So listen to me, Luffy.
Ace.
I can't raise my voice anymore. I'm too weak.
Tell everyone else what I'm about to say, all right?
Pops, my family...
...and you, Luffy.
Thank you, for caring about someone like me.
Who has such bad blood in his veins.
Thank you for loving me.
Thank you so much!
Did you have a nightmare?
You're covered in sweat.
Here, try drinking this.
After losing his brother Ace in
the War of the Best at Marine ford,
Monkey D. Luffy remained in a fragile state,
both mentally and physically, for quite some time.
There is yet joy beyond your sorrows!
What's gone maybe gone?
But you still have something
left in this world to treasure.
Here's my advice. You can do with it what you will.
Your choice won't affect me either way.
But I do want to help you.
Taking Rayleigh's advice to heart,
Luffy traveled with him to Ruskaina.
This is the power to feel the
presence of others more strongly.
This is Observation Haki!
Next, the Armament Haki.
This power acts as if the user is wearing invisible armor.
Now, watch closely.
The power to intimidate your enemies into submission!
This is Conqueror's Haki!
Before journeying to the New World,
Luffy has decided to undergo a
two-year training course from Rayleigh,
who is teaching him to harness
the mysterious power known as Haki.
All right.
Time to hold off on the adventures,
just for a little bit.
Do you feel okay?
Yeah.
I just wonder what everyone's up to.
You mean all of your friends?
You still have something left in
this world to treasure, don't you?
I still have my crew!
Zoro.
I have an ambition of my own.
To be nothing less than the world's greatest swordsman.
I solemnly swear...
...that I will never lose again!
Until the day comes when I defeat him and take his title,
I will never lose, for as long as I live!
Is that okay, King of the Pirates?
Usopp.
I am... I am the captain of the Usopp Pirates.
A brave warrior of the sea!
And mark my words, you will
never set foot in that village!
Get on!
Huh?... We're friends.
So hurry up and get on.
I really am a Pirate Captain now!
Nami.
Luffy.
Please help me.
He's gonna pay!
Luffy!
Nami!
No matter what, you'll always be my friend!
Yeah.
Sanji.
Say, have you ever heard of the All Blue?
I'll be joining your little crew on
your quest to be King of the Pirates.
Your dream is foolish. Then again so's mine.
Now's as good a time as any to get started on it.
I'll be the cook on your ship. Does that sound okay?
Yeah!
Hey, Head Chef Zeff!
Thanks, you geezer!
I owe my life to you, old man!
And Chopper, too.
I needn't have friends, but I can
still fight for something I believe in!
You do have friends!
Huh?
I am your friend, Chopper!
Okay. Maybe I do want to be a pirate.
But I can never be one of you. I'm not even a human!
Shut up! Let's go!
Robin.
It's settled. I'm staying on the ship.
Huh?
Those pirates just declared
war against the World Government!
One more thing!
Tell me that you wanna live!
I wanna live!
And Franky.
I almost forgot!
If you want your undies back then
you're gonna have to join my crew!
You guys need me, that's for sure!
You got the finest vessel on the sea, and not
a single shipwright? Heh. That's a real pity.
You don't leave me much choice.
Gotta take care of my masterpiece!
So set sail, I'm joining the crew!
I'm gonna super miss you guys!
And Brook.
I'm glad to hear that Laboon
is well and still waiting for me.
My shadow has returned, and we're leaving the Devil's Sea.
Every day on that boat was difficult.
Frankly, I'd given up all hope.
But, Luffy, you know what?
I'm just so happy to still be alive!
Ah. So does the offer to join your crew still stand?
Yeah, welcome aboard.
What?!
For real?!
No way!
That's why... I have to get stronger.
So I can protect my friends.
So I can fight to make their dreams
come true, just like they do for me.
Who knows.
Maybe your friends are thinking the exact same thing.
Perhaps they all want to get stronger, just like you.
The sun will rise soon.
Get some rest. Tomorrow's gonna be even tougher.
Right. Night, old man.
Damn ape!
Gum-Gum... Pistol!
Haki!
Huh? Where'd the gorilla go?
Won't even know what hit him!
Okay.
Second Gear!
Time for...
...Jet Pistol!
There we go!
A rabbit?!
Huh...
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
You're gonna pay for that!
You having fun yet?
It's tricky.
We call that one a Toughness Rabbit.
Consider your cheeks an introduction!
Whatever, I'll get it back!
Based on what I saw, you can now use Armament Haki...
with a 50 percent chance of success, that is.
Your Observation Haki's also getting a lot better.
You should be able to sense both your
enemies' presence and how strong they are.
You rely far too much on your vision.
So we'll need to prevent you
from doing that in the future.
Huh?
That's better.
I can't see.
Leave it on for a while and let yourself get used to it.
This is stupid. I can't see a thing!
This is training!
You have to use all of your senses.
Not just your eyesight.
No matter how good your eyes may be,
you'll never see everything.
Enemies that move at the speed of light
must be detected through other methods.
Once you develop your Observation
Haki, you can intercept their attacks.
Right!
Let's do it!
There!
Byojack, how much time has
passed since we began our attack?
Let me see... Eight minutes.
It shouldn't take that long to
sink three warship sand a puny liner!
Get rid of the new recruits.
But we can't do that.
We went through lots of trouble finding the
toughest pirates on the sea while you were gone!
Adding weaklings from the
garbage heap won't do us any good!
Night in, Gairam, Sebastian.
Go on. Show the rookies how it's done.
You have one minute!
I've been it chin' for some action!
Quit yappin'. Let's go!
Who are those guys?
They're heading straight for the ship!
Fire!
They're moving too fast!
These Marines were as naive as they come!
I guess I'll have to teach them a lesson!
Screw you, old lady!
Kampo Kempo:
Antidote Granule!
I always thought these Navy ships were ugly.
Lemme add a few touches to spruce it up! Cube Break!
Remember, only one minute, men!
We need more action like that.
I'll take care of the rest...
...in 50 seconds!
All right.
Hey, is that...
It's Pirate Byrnndi World!
Gimme that.
More-More Hundredfold Gun!
You're gonna pay for this!
Burn in hell!
Watch out!
More-More Hundredfold Chop!
The captain's still got it!
Heh, heh. Even after all the battles
we've fought, his strength remains unbeatable!
'Course it is!
That's ridiculous...
The man's crazy!
He even blew up his own crew members!
How long?
Exactly 50 seconds.
Newcomers!
A few ground rules.
Anyone who fails to follow my orders...
...will end up like them!
World Captain.
All those men were putting their
lives on the line following your orders.
And they were taking their sweet time!
When I give you a task with a time
frame, you can't be a second late!
If you can't meet that simple order,
you don't belong on my ship!
If you're not ready to die at the hands of
our enemies or at the hands of your captain,
then you might as well make a run for it right now!
World!
This guy's lost his mind!
But if you run away, you're also dead.
Forgot that part.
Oh, World.
Ruskaina's going to be hit with severe winter next week!
It'll become extremely cold, definitely around freezing!
He'll need warmer clothing!
Let's see, a sweater, a scarf, gloves,
earmuffs, can't forget long underwear!
That should keep him nice and warm.
Oh, and he's eaten nothing but wild beast meat.
I need to prepare a more balanced diet for him!
Seafood, fruits, veggies, rice,
bread... is there anything I'm missing?
Do you remember if he likes pasta?
Yes, Princess. He really liked the penne
Gorgonzola pasta with Sea King meat on top.
Then prepare a big potful of that!
And cook it on the ship, so we
can serve it to him while it's hot!
A big pot of pasta, served hot.
Is there anything I'm forgetting?
What is it?
Shame on you!
Did you forget the promise you made to Rayleigh?
Ohh. Try to understand.
Luffy's training is very important!
He must not have any distractions!
For now, just hope for his success from a far!
That's what a proper fiancée would do!
Take it from me, men want a woman
who knows when to leave them alone.
Start acting like a warlord, instead
of a silly, little schoolgirl...
I've already thought about such things!
That's why I'm sending someone else
to drop off supplies on my behalf.
You think me a fool?
He'll be fine, so get off my back!
Her wrath is fearful indeed!
Now, where was I?
Oh, yes, a week of harsh winter will give way to spring!
Prepare Luffy some outfits for the springtime!
Cool spring outfits with lacy frills. Check.
And set off as soon as you have everything!
Right!
How could you stomp on an elderly woman like that?
Huh?
A carrier bat? Let me see.
It's a message from the World Government.
Wait. Already?
Listen! We have an emergency, ladies!
The World Government is summoning
the Seven Warlords once more!
Hey, Snake Princess!
Pay attention!
Dear Luffy, even though we cannot meet,
my heart sings at the thought of you!
So please accept this love I send to you,
and dream of me!
Can't believe you actually built it. Well done!
Awesome real!
With just a single shot, he destroyed the entire island!
Please, sir, it was nothing!
What's more impressive is that
you've returned after 30 years!
But I never lost hope!
Neither did we, and our perseverance has paid off!
During your lengthy absence, Sebastian and I spent
all our time collecting materials to build the ship.
So don't try to take all the credit, buddy!
Yeah, Night in is right!
Hey, what gives?
Enough bickering.
I'm grateful to all of you for waiting so long.
For 30 years, building ship like this has been my dream.
And thanks to your hard work, it's finally real!
The cannon... Simply amazing.
The barrel's bigger than any cannon I've seen,
but once I tack on my More-More power,
we'll shoot cannon balls a hundred times bigger!
Why, with that beast at our disposal,
we could take out the capital of the World
Government before they even put up a fight!
Hey, that's a good idea!
Men, prepare to set sail for Mariejois!
World, please.
I don't think we'd be able to carry
out that plan as easily as you believe.
And why is that?
Because of our actions the other
day when we attacked the Navy,
the Government knows the pirate,
Byrnndi World, has escaped from Impel Down.
I want them to know I'm back.
Who really cares if they're on our tail?
If it were that simple, I might
be inclined to agree with you.
However, they've already summoned the
Seven Warlords of the Sea to apprehend you.
Surely that's a joke!
They summoned the Warlords? What does that mean?
That's right.
You were locked up for so long, you probably have no
idea how the World Government deals with pirates nowadays.
The Seven Warlords are pirates,
but they're sanctioned and granted
amnesty by the Government itself.
And in return, the government can
summon them for emergency situations.
But they're more than just grunts!
Their strength is not to be taken lightly.
Is that all?
Luckily for us, I'm a thorough collector of information.
The warlords were summoned just this morning, so they'll
be at the government headquarters within a few days.
I'm sorry, but I'm afraid your plan
isn't going to work out given the circumst...
Wait a minute.
Did you say the Seven Warlords were summoned this morning?
I did, but why?
Perfect, then we'll have to take
advantage of this golden opportunity.
What are you getting at?
Which of the government dogs lives closest to here?
Let's meet 'em.
Damn!
I swear all the animals are ganging up on me!
I'll get 'em back as soon as I'm done eating!
Ready for round two already?
Yeah! I'm tired of getting beat by them!
Later.
I see.
Try not to die.
Right!
Huh? Where did all of 'em run off
to? They didn't go to sleep, did they?
Hey, Mr. Gorilla! Mr. Alligator! Mr. Lion!
I'm ready! Come out and fight me!
Hey, what's that?
Whatever it is, it smells really tasty!
Where's it coming from?
That smells like food!
Okay, I gotta see...
I knew it!
Is all this stuff for me?
Guess so!
Luffy has found the food.
Yeah, it's him all right.
Luffy's there!
She's getting dizzy over nothing. Some warlord!
If she had gone over there with them,
she'd probably have a heart attack. Ugh.
Ahh, Luffy.
His appetite hasn't changed a bit!
Why, he even ate the frilly spring outfits
we brought and those aren't food at all!
You won't believe what Luffy just did!
Tell me everything! Did he like it?
I'm looking for the Empress, the leader of Amazon Lilly.
Heh.
Who are you? State your business!
Since you asked.
The name's Byrnndi World.
I'm here to kidnap the government's dog, Boa Hancock!
You heard of her?
Did he just say Byrnndi World?
Wait. Do you know who that is?
How many times must I tell you?
Remember the letter from the government
that you tore up and threw away?
It mentioned a pirate so dangerous that the
Navy summoned all of the Warlords to fight him!
And that man is Byrnndi World!
And he is here.
You wish to kidnap the princess?
She is not here, but we shall face you ourselves!
What?
I, uh, didn't make any promises, right?
I just saw the Kuja's ship on the
shore and thought she might be here!
We just got unlucky this time, no big deal...
What a waste of my time.
Hold it!
You can't come here to kidnap my sister and then walk
away! then you shall find one at the end of my blade!
You're her sister?
Hey, Sonia! Mari!
Someone tell me what's going on right now!
Do you hear me? Please say something!
I see!
The Empress is on the other side of that snail!
In that case...
More-More Tenfold Shotgun!
You keep your hands off her, or else!
What's that?
Hey, what's up, you guys?
If you brought this food for me,
thanks, it's even better than last time!
Luffy, run away!
What's wrong?
Did Mr. Gorilla attack you?
Is that dude your friend?
Byojack, who's he?
I have no business with the rest of you.
So time to die!
Yeah? Fat chance!
Hey, kiddo.
What're you doing?
Say goodbye. More-More Hundredfold Gun!
That won't work...
No, Luffy!
Luffy.
So is this the Empress of Amazon Lilly?
Where's Luffy? Tell me you didn't hurt him!
I assume she's talking about that boy.
Come here and see for yourself!
I'll leave my Vivre Card next to the punk.
As for you, Pirate Empress,
if you ever want to see your sisters again,
track me down in two days, before the break of dawn!
Good luck!
What? No!
World, I've heard that name from somewhere before.
Luffy.
Get over here. I think Luffy's awake.
Hancock.
What are you doing here?
You finally woke up! What a relief!
Don't try to get up.
You still haven't fully recovered yet.
Oh, yeah! What happened to the girls?
They we retreated for their
wounds and now they're sleeping.
As for Sonia and Mari...
That guy took them, huh?
Yes, yes.
Man. What was his deal?
From sound, and he wanted something
from me because I'm one of the Warlords.
Are you going to rescue your sisters?
Of course.
Princess, if he really is the notorious Byrnndi World,
then even you're too weak to challenge him...
I'll go with her!
If we're together, there's no way he can stop us!
Luffy.
Hold on. The reason that you're training here is because
you're not strong enough to fight opponents like him!
I haven't given up on that.
You aren't improving, but you have a
long way Togo before you master Haki.
You could be killed!
I'm not gonna lose to him!
What have you been training yourself for all this time?
If you leave right now, you
might never see your friends again!
But they came here and were kidnapped
because they we redelivering food for me!
I can't just sit here and do nothing
when people I care about are in trouble!
Oh, Luffy.
Rayleigh, I promise I'll keep him safe.
With him at my side, we'll finish this quickly.
It doesn't matter what I say.
I'm not going to change your mind.
Whatever you do, come back alive!
Okay!
And remember, you have to be extra careful.
Nobody knows your whereabouts and I'd like to keep
it that way until your two years of training are over.
Don't stir up any trouble in public places
where you could attract a lot of attention.
I got it!
This Byrnndi World guy is on a wild ride!
The World Nobles. Other pirates. Us.
Crazy bastard's even killing his own crew.
According to what it says here,
he's behind this latest attack, too?
That's what the World Government thinks.
Soon after the World Noble case,
they decided to summon the Warlords.
The carrier bats were already sent out three days ago.
They didn't even notify us!
Like it or not, it's necessary.
Why hello, Tsuru!
Preparing for his attack isn't the only
reason the World Government was in such a hurry
to get the Warlords all in one place.
It allows the Navy to keep them on a short leash.
After all, if any of the Warlords were to ally
with World our troubles would escalate very quickly.
Think of this as an urgent preventative measure.
Before he was captured 30 years ago,
he was known far and wide as the Destroyer of the World.
With his history, it's only reasonable
the Government responded the way they did.
Destroyer of the World?
That's what they called him.
World has a reputation for taking
out anything that crosses his path.
He was as much a threat to other
pirates as he was to normal civilians.
It didn't matter who you were.
Thirty years ago, the Government
decided to secretly assemble
his enemies and others who held grudges against him.
They joined the Navy and executed a
plan to take down World once and for all.
This was back when you boys were first getting started.
Do you remember anything?
Well, it does ring a bell...
A coalition made up of pirates and the
Navy had a tussle with World and his men.
Even though he was vastly outnumbered, he
didn't budge an inch and the coalition retreated.
But thanks to our Government spies,
ones who secretly took part in the battle,
our efforts were successful in the end.
Ultimately, World and his allies were defeated.
If it was such a decisive victory, why on
earth is he causing trouble again all of a sudden?
I have no idea.
I heard a rumor he had been locked up at
Impel Down in a frozen state of constant slumber.
Perhaps he was awakened somehow.
Sengoku did mention that a fair number
of prisoners snuck out of Impel Down
when Straw Hat turned the place inside out.
In addition to the prisoners Blackbeard
recruited, several names on that list caught my eye.
And Byrnndi World was one of them.
Even compared to Blackbeard's crew, World is a problem.
On top of this, we're still relocating Navy
Headquarters and transitioning to the new system.
It's the worst possible time for us.
You should know World is a More More Fruit eater.
He makes objects a hundred times bigger
and faster, then turns them into an attack.
Destroyer of the World.
You shouldn't take a nickname like that lightly.
Huh...
Based on our Intel from his latest attack, I
wouldn't be surprised if he's still in the area.
Ready the warships!
I was wondering where you went.
Oh. Hello, World.
Are you sure it's a wise decision for
us to go to Marine ford quite so soon?
Worried, are you?
Have some faith in your captain, all right?
You'll relax once we have the Empress.
She's expected to respond to
the World Government's summon,
so if we successfully take her hostage,
we shouldn't have any problems getting into Marine ford.
And once we do, we can use the cannon
to launch our attack on Mariejois,
putting an end to this useless
Government once and for all!
Just picture it, will ya?
Their capital city burned to ash!
The Navy in shambles!
There's no sweeter sight, my friend!
I'm opposed to every part of this plan!
Why is that?
Our goal from the start was freedom, not chaos!
That was all that we thought of
when we built the ship and the cannon!
And that's why we're gonna use
those things against the government.
Because they're the reason people like us can't be free!
Hmm. You might think of it that way.
All you and the others have to do
is shut up and do what I tell you!
I'm the captain, you follow my orders!
Just because you're my big brother doesn't
mean you can disrespect me without consequences!
Captain World, the Kuja ship is approaching
us fast, and Hancock might be on board!
Perfect! Ha!
It's time, brother!
Hmm...
This is where the Vivre Card led us, but...
Hmm, yeah? I think it might be busted.
Wait a minute, what's going on?
An island?!
Why's it coming up from the sea?
Awesome!
Thank you for coming all this way, Empress!
So far your sisters are enjoying their stay!
Big sis!
Run away! Just leave us!
Sonia! Mari!
We'll get ya outta there!
It looks like that kid's here, too.
He can take a beating, I'll give him that much.
If you want 'em back, then you'll have to come get 'em!
I'll be waiting!
Quick, evade them! Don't let them hit us!
We need to get closer to that island somehow!
Just a moment.
They think they can avoid us that easily?
I got this!
Gum-Gum..
...Balloon!
Well, what you know?
So he's got Devil Fruit powers, does he?
C'mon! I need bullets!
Heh. More-More Fifty fold Cannon!
Armament Haki!
Luffy!
Are you mad?
Let go of me! I can't just let him die!
Hurry, Salome, help him!
Get your head on straight, Snake Princess!
Did you forget you ate a Devil Fruit as well?
If you go after him, you'll drown,
too, and what good would that do?!
Luffy...
Just turn yourself over to my
men and no one will get hurt!
It's up to you!
You attacked my ship and harmed my
beloved. Death is too sweet a mercy for you!
Never mind, guys, you can go ahead and kill her!
Hold on, World.
We were supposed to take her as a hostage!
We can always nail her dead body
on a pole and head to Marine ford.
Kill her!
Love-Love Beam!
what happened?
So it's true. She really can turn people into stone!
Luffy!
That was far too close!
Yeah, I screwed that up. I'm sorry.
I know that kid.
Wasn't Luffy the name of that pirate, Straw Hat?
Those idiots. It's like they're begging me to kill 'em.
Don't worry about it, Captain.
I'll help you dispose of them.
Sebastian, good.
I'll give you five minutes.
How kind, but two minutes is all I'll need.
Are you ready?
Yeah!
Go straight!
We'll get in through that opening!
Great Water Shot!
So you wanna get your friends back.
Don't worry, you'll be together soon enough...
...in Hell!
Step aside if you know what's good for you!
Or perhaps you'd rather be turned to stone!
Love-Love Beam!
Why isn't it working?
Surely no one's taste in women could be that bad.
So sorry!
Turns out that I'm blind, so
your power means nothing to me!
Don't take it personally.
This do anything for ya?!
Now, Gum-Gum Jet Pistol!
Huh?
Damn, you got me pretty good there, kid!
I went all out. This guy's tough.
You had your shot. Now it's my turn to pay it back!
Hey, is that an island?
Yeah.
Wait, no, that's a giant ship!
Wow! Someone's fighting on it, too!
Is that a Giant?
It's a Fish-Giant.
He's half giant and half Fish-man.
Woah. That's a good brawl!
Down in front! I wanna see!
All of you, step aside!
Make way for Buggy!
This will mark the momentous occasion in
which I make my debut as a Warlord of the sea!
Now who's crossing our path?
Perhaps we shouldn't stick around.
Things look pretty bad over there!
The pirates on the ship are the
reason you Warlords were summoned!
It's Byrnndi World and his gang!
For real?!
Yeah, real funny, partner!
Prankin' me on my first day on the job.
No way!
Another thing:
The Fish-Giant is fighting against Straw
Hat Luffy and the Pirate Empress Boa, Hancock!
Quite the coincidence!
That's scary!
Straw Hat again?! How come we
keep bumping into that loser?
Captain Buggy!
This is the perfect chance!
You and Straw Hat made a great team
back at Impel Down and I'm sure Hancock
would be more than happy to team up with another Warlord!
Forget the others, we'll bring World's head
to the Navy before the meeting even starts!
He's right, you gotta show those other Warlords
that you're the strongest, even if you are the new guy!
Once you take down World, then everyone'll know!
You're gonna be a star in no time!
A star you say?!
Don't get delusional. It's
going to be harder than it sounds.
Mm-mm.
Wait a minute.
I don't know why Straw Hat is fighting against World
or why he's even here to begin
with, but I do know the Navy wants him!
So let's say that the kid does defeat World.
Then he'll need to run before the government shows up.
I say we let Straw Hat and Hancock take down World.
Once they leave, we'll swoop in and
take all the credit without even fighting!
It's a gamble that would pay off nicely!
That doesn't make sense!
We don't even know if those two can win against World!
You're right!
Attention, please!
Contact the navy and let them know that Warlord
Buggy and his pirates are engaged in battle!
The World Pirates are going down!
Nice! Captain Buggy's goin' for it!
What's the meaning of this?
It’s easy.
Once the Navy hears a Warlord and a guy so tough
he's called the Destroyer of the World are fighting,
they'll start taking notice.
Chances are they'll eventually send in the admirals!
Wha...? Oh!
If Straw Hat and Hancock can't beat him, then
we can run away and leave the rest to the Navy!
That's right.
And even better, Marine ford is pretty close by.
So they should get here soon.
And after that, we can sit
back, relax, and enjoy the show.
Hey, Straw Hat.
Hope you have fun getting your ass kicked on my behalf!
Did he run away?
No!
Great Shark Arrows!
Luffy!
You will pay for that!
Perfume Femur!
Camouflage Air!
What happened?
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Come on, Straw Hat!
You can't get killed before the Navy shows up!
Our plan's already ruined!
Are you okay?
I'm fine, thank you!
I'm afraid I've gotta end this.
Shame, we were really havin' some fun!
Now die!
Spin Tornado!
Third Gear! Bring it on!
Gum-Gum Giant Pistol!
Oh, Sebastian.
This is a disappointment!
Nice work.
Let's go, Hancock!
Oh. Why, yes, dear!
I can't believe it.
Come in, Gairam.
Lead me to the intruders, and be quick about it!
Roger, Captain!
Keep an eye on the hostages, will ya?
Be careful, World!
Come back here!
If you think this fight is over, you're dead wrong!
Look at that sad, little fishy face.
You might make a cute slave!
Negative Extra Big Hollow!
Go get him!
If... If only I had been born a puny little minnow, then
life would be so simple and free of all this violence.
Never mind.
I don't want you anymore.
Who's that?
What the heck?
Huh? Is that Straw Hat?
Hold on. Do you know her from somewhere?
Maybe. Nothin's really ringing a bell, though.
Anyway, thanks for knockin' out that fish dude!
Hey! My actions were independent of
whatever mess Chalk it up to coincidence, okay?
Besides, my friend said he needed to go
somewhere, so I just came along to pass the time.
I had no idea the likes of you would be
here, otherwise I might have stayed at ho...
Oh, no!
That flying girl.
She just called him Straw Hat.
I see, so it's true!
What's wrong with this ship?
Floors aren't supposed to do that!
Luffy, are you certain you don't know that girl?
That cute flying girl following us!
Oh! Yeah. Let me see.
I do think I met her before but I don't remember her name.
He's playing dumb!
Infidelity! This is infidelity, isn't it?
Where are we supposed to go?
Who's that girl with the umbrella?
Where did she come fro... What?!
Hey, what the hell?
What is that bastard doing here?
I don't know.
But isn't he a Warlord, just like you?
The World Government must have summoned him, too!
Oh!
Slime ball!
He probably though the could show up and take the credit
for beating World, while Straw Hat did all the dirty work!
I don't know if you're trying to be ironic or
what, but either way, he's going to ruin our plans!
Cool it.
I just need a second to think about this, don't rush me.
Who am I kidding?! This is a disaster!
Why's everyone gotta mess up my debut?
Technically, he's supposed to be an ally, so we
might have to cut our losses and team up after all.
Our ally, eh?
He's strong, too!
I see.
Great news, men!
We've got some awesome backup to help us out,
so let's go on the offensive!
Follow my lead, men, we're gonna attack!
Yeah!
Hey, Straw Hat's over on that ship.
What's going on?
Who knows?
What kinda place is this?
Why is it like a maze?
Finally, I thought we'd be stuck forever!
Wait, now where are we?
At this point, any direction will do.
Come on! Let's try this path!
Gotcha!
Luffy!
You're not hurt, are you?
What happened?
I could kill the Empress, but I
think I'll have some fun with you first!
Hancock, don't worry about me!
Go find your sisters!
But, Luffy!
Hurry!
All right then. I'll go.
Please be careful, my love! We shall meet again!
Yeah. I got this!
World, watch out for that kid!
He's no normal boy, so don't underestimate him!
Uh?
You remember the story, right?
He's that upstart, the one who raided Marine ford
to rescue his brother, Portgas D. Ace, from execution!
He's the leader of the Straw Hat Pirates!
You're facing Monkey D. Luffy!
I'm sorry. Who?
Oh, you know him.
The Navy Vice Admiral Garp is his grandfather!
Ah? You mean the one who throws cannon balls?
Are you telling me this twerp is the reason
the Navy Head quarters has fallen into ruin?
I don't believe it.
So... you save that brother of yours or not?
A wimp like you isn't strong enough to save anybody!
Shut up!
Gum-Gum Gatling!
Now, Second Gear!
Jet Gatling!
You're not dead yet?
Hold on!
That must be Byrnndi World!
This is my weapon storage.
Feel free to use whatever you want.
Swords.
Spears, guns, hammers.
You can take what you like.
Then maybe this'll get fun.
I don't need any of that crap!
That pride'll get ya killed.
I don't need...
...any weapon!
Jet Pistol!
Haki!
Don't push your luck, kid!
You don't even know how to control your Haki!
You were too weak to save your brother
and you're no stronger now.
Listen up, kid.
If you can't keep up with my next move,
nothing you got's gonna make a lick of difference.
My More-More Tenfold Speed!
Well, that's just too bad, isn't it?
I take it you came hereto help the
Empress save those weakling sisters of hers.
Then there's something you ought a know.
You're a weakling, too.
You're not strong enough to save anybody!
Time to finish off the Empress.
Get up, Straw Hat!
Easy. World made it look easy!
What do we do now?
If that guy could rough up
Straw Hat with so little effort,
I don't think our plan'll work out.
Don't just stand there! Go do something!
Pick up Straw Hat and give him some first aid!
We can't let him die yet.
Wow! It's beautiful how much you care for your friend!
Make no mistake, I'll follow Captain Buggy all my life!
It doesn't matter what this idiot says, does it?
Hmph. Garp's grandson, huh?
Hey, Garp! Sengoku!
How many pirates have you got on your side, huh?
You should be ashamed!
Damn it! Let's blow him to smithereens!
Not just yet.
You do have to admit that he's got a point.
Wait, what's going on out there, World?
A pirate alliance is on their side.
We'll have to fight both pirates and the Navy!
How is that happen?
Heh. I bet the World Government is behind it.
They're always pulling shady deals.
World, what're we supposed to do now?
What we always do!
Take out everybody who stands in our way!
Pirates and Navy!
Am I right, Sebastian?
Yeah!
This battle's gonna be tougher than we expected.
That single ship is doling out a lot of damage.
Then, let me go.
I'll make meatloaf outta their captain and we'll be done!
No need.
What is a Cipher Polagent doing here?
The tides will turn soon enough.
Huh? They stopped.
What the hell's goin' on here?
No! What are you doing?
Oh, no.
What's wrong with you? Have you gone mad?
When the World Government's after you, then
you've got no choice but to join up with them!
So we're not gonna follow you anymore!
Try to understand where we're coming from!
They said they wouldn't charge us if we turned
you over to them and surrendered without fighting!
Who told you those lies?
You've been bought off by the World Government?!
Hey, don't act like you're so innocent!
They are bought you too.
But we weren't dumb enough to listen to them, unlike you!
World!
The plan is underway.
Launch an all-out attack.
So many traitors.
I can't believe I actually
thought you were my true friends.
Very impressive,
Captain.
World, get out of there now!
It's Cipher Pol!
What in the hell is that?
It's the World Government's intelligence agency!
Correct, sir.
We've been masquerading as your crew
members, learning as much as we can.
The act was a part of our mission. Now it's over.
World, no!
World...
Stop! Don't let him escape!
Nightin! Gairam! Everyone, run for it!
Byojack. What are you doing?
What about Captain World?
But we're all gonna die for nothing if we stay here!
As World's first mate, listen to me!
You have to...
He wants them to leave me?
Roger that! Forgive me, Captain!
Halt!...
Sebastian! Dive!
They got away!
Ah, who cares?
They're wounded. They won't last long.
My crew. Everyone betrayed me.
It won't happen, not ever again!
Did you find the Empress?
She's heading to my room now.
Are you positive?
What do you mean? Of course!
Trust me, I'll take good care of her.
All righty then! Once I've got her in my clutches,
I'll just soften her up a little
bit, then bring her right to you!
how's sb holding up.
He finally stopped bleeding, but...
He's trying to say something!
I don't ever wanna let my friends down like that again!
I never wanna feel that pain again
for as long as I live!
I don't know what you're talking about,
but lying there and moping won't fix anything!
Get up!
Snap out of it and fight! I need you!
Wake up, dummy! Get your lazy ass back out there!
Come on, Crap Hat!
Don't worry about me!
He's risking his life to protect me.
He's so noble and brave!
To think that I ever suspected
him of cheating, how shameful of me!
Ah! I can swoon when my sisters are safe!
Where am I?
What is that aroma?
Welcome, Pirate Empress.
You failed to introduce yourself and
you don't bother to face your guest.
Have you no class?
I can't believe the World Government thought a
prissy little thing like you would make a good Warlord.
Talk about poor judgment!
Their standards must be slipping!
I'm Nightin, ship doctor of the World Pirates
and master of Kampo Kempo, if you must know,
I take it back, I don't care who you are.
Just tell me where my sisters are you hag.
You might not care.
but I know plenty about you thanks to Byojack.
Believe it or not, I've even developed a
strategy that can ward off your Love-Love power!
Are you done babbling, or must I silence you myself?
Kampo Kempo Secret Medicine!
This is Fishwort Hell!
Love-Love Beam!
Sorry, Empress, but your power's not going to work!
This concoction that you see before you
is a complex blend of hundreds of disgusting herbs.
Easily the most bitter kampo
medicine the world's ever seen!
It purged my heart of all wicked desires,
rendering your sinful Love-Love power useless!
Let's see what's next on the menu!
Kampo Poison Mist!
What's happening?
Who's the one with no class now?
And next...
Kampo Kempo Secret Medicine!
Now, feast your eyes!
Pretty!
Elegant!
Bouncy!
Ooh.
Ginseng Newcomer!
I'm maybe 80 years old,
but with some rejuvenating kampo, I still look amazing!
So long! Time for my Kampo Kempo Technique:
Kakkon Toe!
Toe! Toe, toe, toe, toe, toe, toe, toe, toe, toe, kick!
Try handling my Cordyceps Soul Shot!
You youngsters might not think much of kampo,
but the kempo part should be flashy enough for you!
Taste my Slave Arrow!
That was a Kampo Dome!
This may be more to your liking.
A Pistol Kiss!
Keep shooting! You'll never hit me!
I wasn't known as the Queen of Kampo Kempo for nothing!
You're not that strong. Not that hot, either.
Then I beg of you, grant me one last wish.
Shut your filthy mouth and never open it again.
Ugh! So bitter!
She's dangerous!
Like a goddess or a femme fatale!
But!
Hah! No matter how much you bat your
eyelashes, your power won't work on me!
Cordyceps Soul Shot...
...Burst!
You can't use your snake.
Oh, I can't?
Must eat 'em all!
Is something the matter? You're
starting to look awfully pale.
My unparalleled beauty has won you over.
It was only a matter of time.
Thus is my power.
I could kill you in a most gruesome
fashion and no one would shed a tear.
Why do I face no consequences for my actions, you ask?
i'm beautiful.
She's looking down on me so
much she's actually looking up!
Hey! I'll have you know I'm not into
women! So don't flatter yourself, honey!
I love men through and through, got it?
I'm done playing games! Go to hell already!
Did I do something wrong?
Not at all!
It's no use!
She's just too sexy!
Now, Love-Love Beam!
So much for your repulsive medicine.
There's no one in this world that can hide from my beauty.
And nothing that can ever make it pale.
Nightin...
Come on!
Wake up already, idiot! Time's a
wastin'! Get back out there, you damn fool!
If you leave right now, then you
might never see your friends again!
Luffy!
Luffy.
Whatever you do, come back alive.
You're a weakling, too.
You're not strong enough to save anybody!
What's your problem?
If you want to take down World, quit lyin' around!
Get back up and fight, damn it!
Maybe I can save them and maybe I can't,
but I'll never know unless I try!
Tell me... which way did he go?
He... went that way!
Thanks.
That guy better be ready for an ass-kicking!
C'mere World! You can't hide from me!
Do you think he'll be all right?
Yeah. Exactly as I planned.
Whoa...
They'll believe anything he says.
Which way?
Huh? Really?
I don't get this place.
The Straw Hat kid is still alive.
Not to worry, Byojack! He will prove no match for me!
But, Gairam.
He's already gotten lost in the trap I created,
so this will be easy!
Straw Hat and the Empress aren't alone anymore!
All this commotion's making us vulnerable!
The Warlord Buggy managed to sneak aboard, too!
I shouldn't have to say this, but be careful!
You worry too much! I'll finish them off!
Hmm. I hope so.
Let's try Cube Break!
Huh? What's that?
Damn! I'm trapped!
Now I've got you!
Welcome aboard my ship!
I'm Gairam, the man who ate the Cube Cube Fruit!
Now, with my powers, I can shape anything into a cube!
Observe!
C'mon, kid, are you serious?
You think I'm gonna let you reach the captain that easily?
Try this!
Cube Booster!
Heh.
I thought you'd put up more of a fight,
but I'm afraid there's no escaping that one.
Hmm?
Crap Hat must've beaten World by now!
Time for us to take cred... er, I mean see how he's doing.
Hold it!...
Eh?
Who're you? Wait a second, you must be
that other guy that Byojack mentioned.
Why are you here?
That fellow doesn't look too friendly.
Perhaps we shall go back.
Well, it doesn't matter. You're going down, clown!
Cube Booster!
Watch out, I think he might have Devil Fruit powers!
Really? What gave you that idea?
Phew, I thought I was a goner!
Straw Hat?
You were supposed to be fighting
World. Would you hurry it up?
Didn't I crush you already?
How did you survive that attack?
I'm made of rubber!
Enough with the chit-chat! Get moving!
You've got more important things to do!
Cut me some slack!
This place is really confusing!
That's Straw Hat for ya, always full of excuses!
Why am I in a priced?
Don't argue with me! Get out there and beat World already!
Or my plan's going to be ruined.
That's our captain!
First he heals him, and then he gives him a pep talk.
Now he's even offering to stay here and
fight this guy so Straw Hat can go ahead!
Truly. You're an inspiration to all of us!
Quite the interpretation.
I'm just so happy!
No matter where my captain
leads, I'm a Buggy man till the end!
It's settled, men!
Let's help Captain Buggy help his friend.
Buggy! Buggy!
Hey. What do we do?
Beats me. Just play along for now.
Buggy! Buggy!
Uh, what are you going to do?
Y'know, I'm startin' to think this may be fate.
I'm no slouch, but the bounty on my head wasn't half as
much as these guys when we were still stuck at Impel Down.
But now, they're all working under me.
So I must be one of the greatest pirates in the world!
There's no other explanation!
I'm not gonna let some idiot with a hammer defeat me!
Hey, Straw Hat!
I can handle this chump on my
own. You go on and beat World!
And don't worry, I won't tell anyone I saved your ass.
I'm famous enough as-is, so it's not like I
need to steal any thunder from a rookie like you.
Let's just say you owe me one, okay?
I bet you can pay me back somehow.
Yeah, are you sure?
Did you hear anything I just said, ya moron?
Hurry up before I change my mind! Jeez!
I got it! Kick his ass for us, Buggy!
Hey! We're still in the same awful situation as before!
That guy wants to kill us!
Huh? Ya don't say.
Can these idiot seven fight to begin with?
When the ship gets messy, it's time to take out the trash!
Step right up and witness the
power of the Cube Cube Fruit!
Now! Air Cube!
What the hell?
He turned the air into a cube?
Now! Air Cube Booster!
Candle Wall!
Run before he attacks again!
Thanks, partner! I'm counting on you!
Cheap parlor trick!
He's headed right where I want him!
Which way should we go now, Captain?
Damn it! There's no escape!
That's right. Now you're stuck with me!
Time for my Cube Break!
Help me!
Captain Buggy!
It's time to finish you off.
Too slow, bozo! Your cubes suck! Is that all ya got?
Captain Buggy does it again!
Even turning into a cube can't stop his trash talk!
Why don't you try this on for size?
Cube Booster!
Wow! You've got terrible aim!
No, you're right where I want you.
Totem Cube!
Eh? What the hell's a totem cube?
Just this!
How do you like that?
Let's find out how bad my aim really is.
All right, batter up! Here we go!
Almost there!
Well, well, fancy seeing you here!
It was real nice knowin' ya!
Now! Chop-Chop Quick Escape!
I broke free!
He has Devil Fruit powers, too.
All right, body, now pull it together!
No! That won't work!
If I gotta beat you piece by piece, then so be it!
This does not good.
I'll be fine. I've still got a trump card up my sleeve.
You do?
Yeah.
Though I told myself I'd never use
it again unless absolutely necessary.
This movie is no joke.
It has the power to destroy
several towns in one fell swoop!
In fact, you guys could get hurt
if you're in the way, so watch out!
Whoa! I forgot how strong he was!
Yeah, don't worry, we'll stay out of your way!
He must be talking about the Buggy Ball!
I haven't seen one of those in forever!
Why giving me away?
Ah. You mean that little explosive you
used against the Minotaurus back in Impel Down?
That's a Muggy Ball. They're
two completely different things.
But yeah, one of those.
All I need is a little distraction
to get the rest of my body back!
Would you stop with the chit-chat, damn it?
Air Cube!
Get outta here with that junk! Special Muggy Ball!
Wow!
Got it!
Damn! You'll pay for that!
How dare you use a bomb on my ship!
Huh?
Perfume Femur!
Now, where is Luffy?
He went that way.
Huh?
Huh?!
We won! He's been defeated!
Captain Buggy saved us!
Yeah, I'm pretty sure he didn't do that.
Big deal. No one needs to find out. Let's just celebrate!
Yeah! Captain Buggy, he's the best!
Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
All right then, everybody!
Let's go track down World next!
And above all else, remember to be flashy!
Yeah!
My goodness. How much longer can he drag this out?
How did it come to this?
Byojack.
You don't look too cheery.
Mm?
What happened to them?
Who's doing all this?
It's Nightin and Gairam.
These intruders... they beat them.
Huh? Who told Gairam to fight?
Ridiculous!
Nobody around here know show to follow my orders anymore!
Wait just a minute.
They both fought really hard trying to protect us...
They did it for your sake!
What are you getting at?
He still here.
Straw Hat is on the ship causing trouble.
They thought you'd be angry, so
they tried to end things quickly.
Ha! A fat lot of good that did us.
Now we're down to just you and me!
What were they thinking, huh?
Forget it.
The Pirate Empress is on her way here, isn't she?
She is, but World...
You stay put. I'll handle it.
Brother. I'm sorry.
What are you apologizing for, huh?
You're wrong.
This... it wasn't supposed to be this way.
This isn't the dream we were fighting for!
Huh?
Remember why we first set out to sea?
Look at it, World!
It's amazing.
There's so much we haven't seen,
so many islands and places we haven't been to!
Don't you wanna go out there some day?
Yeah, of course I do!
So where do you want to go to first?
Byojack! Are you okay?
Yeah. It's nothing, I'll be fine.
You don't sound fine.
Listen. You can make our dream come true, World.
There're all kinds of adventures
out there waiting for you!
Stuff that's bigger and wilder than I could ever imagine!
You mean you're not gonna come with me?
I can't go.
I've been like this since I was little.
I'd just get in the way.
Hey, don't say things like that!
That's for you.
I doubt you want to stay on this tiny island forever.
There's a lot of cool things to see.
So, get out of there and you can
live big enough for the both of us!
I don't think so.
No why!
Because I'm not leaving here without you!
I'll go explore the world, and
you'll be right there with me!
But I can't.
You don't have to be strong,
'cause I'll be there to protect you!
Sailing together is the only way!
You really think so?
Don't cry! You're the older brother. That's weird!
Several years later, we finally left the island.
All we wanted was adventure...
a chance to see all the wonders of the world.
That's enough, World.
If you keep going like this, you're gonna kill 'em!
Don't ever mess with the Byrnndi brothers!
I'm not gonna say it twice!
Sir! Vice-Captain Byojack's been kidnapped!
He's been what?
Yeah!
We'll destroy anyone who stands in our way!
I don't give a damn who you think you are!
We were supposed to be searching for freedom...
the dream we had since we were kids.
But everyone else saw things differently.
To them, we were just pirates.
Eventually, the Navy and World
Government placed you on their wanted list.
Then before we knew it, you had a terrifying reputation.
They called you Destroyer of the World.
A submarine?
That way we can travel underwater
and only surface when we need to.
Just think of all the fights we can avoid!
Nowadays, since we have so many crew
members, we need to build a bigger ship anyway.
What sort of weapons should it have?
I want a giant cannon tacked on to it!
The biggest that anyone's ever seen! Huge!
Why would we need such a thing?
If we'll be avoiding unnecessary
battles, then there's no point.
You've got it backwards.
Think about it.
If the ship has a cannon big and
strong enough to intimidate our foes,
combine that with my More-More power,
and no one's ever gonna want to attack us.
Put that cannon on the ship and we'll never fight again.
Oh!
Then it's settled! I'll get right to work!
We're finally building our dream ship!
Freedom! It's a symbol of our lifelong goal!
It's only a ship, brother.
That was 30 years ago.
We were all on the path to freedom at last.
And so we all went to work building
this ship, Groseade, to follow that hope.
This ship... we built it while you were
imprisoned because we had our dream in mind,
not so we could take down the World Government!
Byojack.
Are you still thinkin' about that crap?
Then you can just sit right there and watch what happens.
And don't bother me anymore!
Our dream hasn't mattered for a long time now.
Certainly not since you all left me for dead!
I told you! That was all a misunderstanding!
Yeah, I know what you said!
Forget it. I don't care anymore.
World, wait!
Sorry, brother, this is all I can do.
Luffy!
Guys! Are you okay?
I'll get you out! Just hold on a sec!
You've become quite the pest.
Why can't you just mind your own damned business?
You pathetic little brat!
You think you can kidnap my friends?
Not gonna happen!
Besides, if I can't beat up some sad old man,
how can I protect my crew?
Your crew, huh?
Is that really what you're so stuck on?
You're so transparent.
This is all because you couldn't
save your big brother, isn't it?
And where are these beloved crew mates of yours?
I pity them!
I'm gonna put an end to this in 30 seconds!
You won't beat me twice.
More-More...
...Tenfold Shotgun!
Second Gear!
Luffy!
Looks like my prediction was off.
But I'm only gonna need ten seconds this time around.
Hm? Are you begging for mercy?
Even if you move ten times faster than normal,
it's not gonna matter if I'm holding on to you!
You think you're clever. We'll see.
More-More Thirty fold Speed!
Jet Pistol!
What's wrong? You still can't hit me?
Fool.
It's not just speed I command...
...but the overwhelming power that goes along with it!
Fifty fold Speed!
Furious Hammer!
Oh, no!
Those attacks won't work on me.
Huh?
I'm a rubber man!
Oh, yeah. How could I forget?
Get ready! Third Gear!
Giant Pistol!
You'll always be too weak, kid.
We'll see about that.
Come here!
Jet Pistol!
It doesn't matter.
Use the Armament Haki all you want!
Jet Gatling!
The power is useless,
if you can't even hit me!
Save your friends, huh?
And your brother?
Ha! You can't even save yourself!
We are out. we find exit.
Yeah. Took us long enough! Good riddance to that crap!
Time for us to blow this joint.
Straw Hat'll be fine on his own.
You know, they can hear you.
What? Oh, uh.
What a tragedy!
Without me, World must be beating Straw Hat to a pulp!
If only I hadn't taken that wrong turn,
Sorry to interrupt, Captain, but what's that?
Huh?
It's a fleet of Navy ships!
But why would the Navy show up here?
Because you told us to contact the Navy.
Ah. I did, didn't I?
Hey! I'm right over here! The newest warlord, Buggy,
is now fighting the Destroyer of the World himself!
That's right... the new warlord, Buggy, right here!
Somebody is frantically waving his hands at us.
What do you think we should do, sir?
What else? All ships, start firing!
All ships, commence firing!
Eh?
It is terrible.
The Navy will discover Luffy's whereabouts soon!
Circle the ship around back! Go!
Right!
What's goin' on now?
The Navy's here,
and they're launching an all-out attack on our ship!
The Navy.
Hey, if they're trying to sink the
whole place, why are we even here?
Kind of a waste of our time, isn't it?
Perfect!
What now, World?
I didn't expect the Navy to fall into our lap!
Time to change our plan!
We've got the perfect opportunity to hit
'em where it really hurts! Prepare the cannon!
Are you mad?
If we fire from such a close range, our
whole ship's going to sink from the impact!
Who cares? Just get it ready!
But I thought the ship was...
Was what, a symbol of our freedom?
Don't you get it?
The ship's just a tool for getting what I want!
The rest of you always clung to your foolish dreams.
But I made up my mind long ago,
even before I escaped Impel Down.
Then you guys picked me up in this ship,
and I saw that massive cannon.
So I did what anyone else would do.
I decided to take advantage of the
situation and use it to achieve my own goals!
It's not like you can blame me.
You did a good job building it!
You've been using us all along!
Is getting revenge against the
World Government? Are you care about?
And so what if it is? I don't care about the ship.
And I sure as hell don't give a damn
about what happens to you dirty traitors!
But Gairam, and Nightin, and Sebastian, too.
They fought for you because you're their friend!
You're right.
I haven't trusted you or anyone
else since the very beginning!
I don't really need any of you, and I never did!
No way. That's not the brother I know.
You lot aren't any different from the ship.
Just a bunch of tools, and nothing more!
World! No!
You maybe are my brother,
but if you can't follow orders, then I don't need you!
Huh?
A bunch of tools? Is that what you said?
That's what you think of your friends?
Yeah. What's it to you, huh?
Take it back!
Luffy!
Hurry! Grab your sisters and get outta here, now!
The Pirate Empress?
Me and this guy have unfinished business!
Mm...
Mm.
Mari! Sonia! Let's go!
Big Sis!
Careful! As soon as you've taken care
of him, come straight back to the ship!
Right!
It doesn't matter. I don't need
the Empress as a hostage anymore.
Now, you wanna keep fighting, go right ahead.
If you're sayin' a prayer, don't bother.
Nobody can save you now.
Who's gonna save you?
You cocky little brat!
I'm not losing!
Not to a jerk like you!
Friends are more than just tools!
There's nothing wrong with abandoning the useless!
After all, you left your brother to die at Marine ford.
Get it through your head.
It's already over and you failed completely.
You couldn't protect your brother because you're weak.
You may be right.
Hm?
I was weak.
I couldn't save Ace's life.
But I'm not dead yet, and I still have my crew!
Friends who are waiting for me... who believe in me!
Enough already!
I will protect my friends!
And I will become King of the Pirates!
Brother!
But before I do that, I'm takin' you out!
You're stubborn, but that's not enough to beat me.
Gum-Gum Jet Gatling!
More-More Hundredfold Speed!
Time to finish you!
Gum-Gum Red Hawk!
That fire... like Ace.
I promised Rayleigh and Hancock that I'd make it back.
So I'm not gonna die here. My friends are waiting for me!
Why did those numb skulls start firing? It's
not like the Navy didn't know we were there, right?
I think I can deal with hurt feelings
as long as we live to see another day!
Come on, men, put your backs into it!
And you there, holding my legs,
don't you dare get them wet!
No soggy feet!
I'm trying my best!
We can sort things out with the Navy later!
Let's go!
Aye, aye!
Luffy, please return to me safely!
What are you doing?
If they think they've beaten me,
they're badly mistaken.
Our friends were all defeated.
This ship's destroyed.
You've suffered injuries all over your body.
Brother, there's nothing left to do but run away!
I won't be satisfied unless I
fire the cannon at least once.
And the Navy is the perfect target.
The cannon? You're really gonna use it?
I was gonna use it all along.
I'm sorry I betrayed your
trust, but that's the ugly truth.
Still, once upon a time you guys betrayed me, too.
Well, then. Consider us even.
I feared this.
For all these years, you've held a grudge!
But, that was...
I was sealed away in ice for all that time!
For me, your betrayal was just like yesterday.
You may have put it behind you, but I will never forget.
World, I'm sorry.
How do I get outta this place?
Admiral.
A giant cannon just emerged,
and it's pointing right at us!
Meteor Volcano!
What now?
The least I can do...
...is land one hit!
Taste my More-More Hundredfold Cannon!
Remember my name!
It's Byrnndi World! Cower before me!
Wha...? Evacuate!
Luffy!
Oh, no. Where are you, my beloved?
Don't worry! I'm sure he'll be just fine!
World...
It's only a matter of time before we sink.
The World Pirates have lost.
Let's start over, World.
Just the two of us.
We'll sail away, just like we planned, and be free.
Luffy!
Oh, no! He's not gonna make it!
Yes, he will!
Hey!
Luffy!
Thank goodness! I'm so happy you're alive!
What are you smiling at?
Who knows?
You weirdo.
Hope you got what you wanted... whatever it was.
Well, Luffy.
You've learned the basics of
Haki, all that's left is to practice.
And while I'd love to stick around,
there's really nothing more for me to teach you.
There is it.
I think I may return to Sabaody and check up on Shakky.
Are you staying here?
Well, it's only a year and a half
since I sent out that message to my crew.
3D2Y.
Two years later instead of three days later, right?
If we want to continue our journey,
we all needed to get stronger.
After what happened, I'm sure they feel the same way.
You still got six months. That's plenty of time.
Yeah.
I can't wait to see how everyone
else has changed after two years!
I bet they'll all be super strong.
And that makes me wanna keep working.
So that's it then!
I'll stay here and keep training till time's up!
Good. Just keep on improving your Haki skills.
Soon, you'll be able to control it as you like.
You got it!
I'll see you back on Sabaody in six months then.
Hey, Rayleigh, thank you!
It's been two years already.
Right! Let's go!
Hi, Sunny.
Sorry to keep you waiting. I hope you weren't lonely.
Wow! Who is that gorgeous lady?
It's Robin, of course! Our super archaeologist!
And boy, did I ever miss you!
You haven't changed, Franky!
Why you bein' such a jerk? I just wanna fish.
Well, too bad, 'cause you can't! Everyone's meeting
on the ship, so you don't get to run off on your own!
It's Usopp!
You got so big! Just look at you!
You're doing ok!
So cuddly! I bet the lady reindeers adore you!
I sure have missed you!
Uh, Nami?
Uh-huh?
Thank you for the ride.
That was impeccable timing I must say!
Listen up, you guys.
There's a lot of things I wanna say,
but we don't have a whole lotta time.
These two years,
what I made you do was selfish,
so thanks for puttin'' up with it.
You make it sound like that's never happened before.
No joke! You've always been a selfish piece of work!
Let's set sail!
Yeah!