"Oh, sexy guy. It's a miracle!"
See?
Simple.
Icebreakers like this guarantee
a good first impression.
Now, I'm sure we all know
someone who's absolute crap
with small talk. Ha.
Maybe we are that person.
The trick is to put yourself
in the shoes of your target.
Kimura, throw me
an ice-breaker, quick!
Uh.
Hey, there?
[IRINA]
No, no!
You're just shifting
the burden of conversation.
If you want a meaningful
response, the other person
has to feel you're
pulling your own weight.
Try coming at them guns blazing
with an interesting observation.
[KIMURA]
Okay?
[IRINA] Conversation is a
challenge for the best of us,
and that's okay.
Don't think in terms
of finding the right words.
Let them find you.
Just let the conversation flow.
Finesse it like
a full-tongued kiss.
[IRINA]
Ugh!
Teaching is such
a pain in the ass!
At least the students are
finally taking a shine to you.
Oh, yeah. Sure.
'Cause that's a load off.
Come on, I'm an assassin.
I'm supposed to be
killing people,
not hunting octopus with brats.
And while we're on the subject
of tentacled pervs...
...the son of a bitch is
staring at my tits!
Sipping tea doesn't
make it classy!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Have I mentioned
how much I admire
your "perky" teaching methods?
Shut your face!
--[KORO-SENSEI giggles]
--[IRINA grunts]
[KARASUMA]
Stand down.
You know he's just
pushing your buttons.
Yeah, well...
I'll push his buttons!
[KARASUMA]
Hmm...
[KORO-SENSEI]
Hm. She's feisty today.
[KARASUMA] Huh. Can't
imagine why that might be.
[IRINA]
I have better things to do
than twiddle my
thumbs in this dump.
If I could just bag the
squirrelly bastard.
[IRINA gasps, yelps]
[IRINA whimpers]
[IRINA]
A snare trap?
Who the hell?!
[LOVRO]
You catch me off guard, Irina.
Watching you babysit
bunch of kids.
It's like TV comedy show.
Sir. Why are you here?
[KARASUMA]
What's going on here?
This is your only warning, pal.
Let her go.
[LOVRO]
Don't worry about it.
She knows how to handle herself.
[IRINA gasps]
[IRINA grunts]
[KARASUMA]
Right.
So, uh.
Have we met each other
somewhere, or is it just me?
We haven't met in person.
But you know my reputation.
I do freelance work
for government.
As matter of fact,
I'm the guy who arranged
to bring Irina Jelavich into the
mix. I'm human resources man.
[KARASUMA grunts]
[KARASUMA]
Lovro the Assassin!
One of the most dangerous
men who's ever lived.
Now retired.
Trains assassins and books gigs
for them all over the world.
Makes a killing.
No pun intended.
At the crucial moment,
he came through for us,
Jelavich is his protégé.
But why is he here now?
This Koro-sensei fellow
happen to be near?
I think he's in Shanghai
picking up some almond jelly.
Left about a half-hour ago.
Should be back any minute.
[LOVRO chuckles]
So rumors of his speed
haven't been exaggerated.
Well. Good.
Glad I came when I did.
You run along home, Irina.
I'll take it from here.
It's clear you're out
of your depth.
[IRINA gasps]
[LOVRO]
Don't get me wrong:
on undercover jobs,
you're the best.
Once your cover's
been blown, however.
Well, let's face it,
you're no Charlotte Corday.
[IRINA] You have to
give me a chance, sir!
I can do this! I know I can!
[IRINIA yelps]
[IRINIA whimpers]
[KARASUMA]
He's fast.
[LOVRO]
What have I always taught you?
Everyone has their strengths
and their weaknesses.
A good assassin knows
when to go home.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Congratulations!
You're exactly half wrong
and half right.
[KARASUMA]
Hey, hey. Cool it, Game Show.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Another ridiculous nickname?
Are you determined never
to call me Koro-sensei?
It's you.
[KORO-SENSEI]
I agree.
As an assassin, our beloved
Irina is nothing special.
Frankly, she's crap.
No one was asking you!
[KORO-SENSEI] Having said
that, she belongs here.
She is, in fact, a perfect
fit for this class.
[IRINA]
Huh?
[KORO-SENSEI] To prove
my point, I propose a kill-off.
Let us see which
of you passes muster.
Who is the better assassin?
The rules are simple.
Whomever kills our friend Mr.
Karasuma first is the winner.
[KARASUMA]
Excuse me?
Why the hell am I the target
here all of a sudden?
[KORO-SENSEI]
It has to be you, silly.
I'm un-killable.
[KARASUMA grumbles]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Here. You have all day tomorrow.
Oh, I see.
So it's to be a
pretend assassination.
Why not? Heh.
There are worse ways
to pass time.
[KARASUMA sighs]
[KARASUMA]
Suit yourself.
[IRINA] Is this your idea
of sticking up for me?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Heh-ah?
Shut up! I know what this is:
you're hedging your bets on me
because you think
I'm easier to manage
than some new schmuck, right?
Well, if you don't think I've
got what it takes to kill
Karasuma and you, somebody's
in for a rude awakening!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Huh...
[KARASUMA] So there it is.
Expect a few disruptions today,
and hopefully it won't interfere
with your studies too much.
Just carry on
as normal, all right?
Eh...
[NAGISA]
Poor guy.
He just can't catch a break.
[IRINA]
Yoo-hoo!
[ALL gasp]
[KARASUMA]
Hm?
[IRINA] Excellent work today!
I'll bet you've worked up
quite a thirst. Aww!
Have an ice-cold beverage!
[KURASUMA groans]
Here, go ahead
and knock it back.
It tastes like a rainbow!
[ISOGAI]
She drugged it.
[MAEHARA]
Oh, yeah. Definitely.
Probably some sort
of muscle relaxant.
Immobilize and stab,
oldest trick in the book.
[IRINA]
Uh!
[KARASUMA sighs]
[KARASUMA]
What do you take me for?
No man in his right mind
would let you close
enough to give him a drink.
[IRINA growls]
Well. Why don't I
just put in here
so you can take it at
your leisure--Ow!
Oh... Ohh!
Pick me up, Karasuma!
--Carry me piggyback? Please?
--[KARASUMA] Um, no.
Have some self-respect.
This is sad.
You okay, Professor Bitch?
Hey, no offense,
but that little ploy
wouldn't have fooled anyone.
My options are limited, okay?
I can't seduce someone
who knows my M.O!
Chalk it down to
occupational hazard!
It's like a paid escort trying
to put the moves on her old man!
He knows her too well for
her charms to land their mark!
[ISOGAI, MAEHARA]
That's sick!
[IRINA]
Damn it.
I'm racing against
the clock here.
When Lovro's got
a target in his sights,
it's only a matter of time.
He strikes like
a thief in the night.
[KORO-SENSEI]
What do ya think?
Exhilarating being
the kill-ee, isn't it?
Oh, it's a barrel of laughs.
Wait a second...
Exactly what happens if
I manage to dodge them both?
[KORO-SENSEI] Huh...
I hadn't thought of that.
I suppose in all fairness,
you'd be the winner.
What do I win?
[KORO-SENSEI] How about
I agree to stand stock-still
in front of you for
an entire second?
You may shoot and or
stab me at will.
Don't tell the others, though.
We don't want kickoff
a feeding frenzy.
The pot might be a little too
rich to keep everyone honest.
[KARASUMA]
Hmm...
Whatever you say.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Heh?
[ALL gasp]
[KARASUMA grunts]
[IRINA]
Head-on?
[KARASUMA grunts]
[KARASUMA yells]
[KARASUMA]
With all due respect, my friend,
how straightforward did you
think this was going to be?
You've got skill, but frankly
the years haven't been kind.
Until recently, I was in
the Elite Special Force.
[LOVRO]
He is tough one.
[IRINA] If Lovro can't
get his hooks into him,
what the hell chance do I have?
Hey, wanna win?
Step up your game.
You've only got today.
[BOTH scream]
Hold on a sec,
why are you scared?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Don't worry about it!
Just do your best,
and try not to lose!
[KARASUMA]
FYI: With a good knife,
I can strike five
times in a second.
So, should be fun.
[KORO-SENSEI whimpers]
[IRINA gasps]
--Sir, you... your hand
--[KORO-SENSEI] Uh?
[LOVRO groans]
I suppose I can't expect to
kill today in this condition.
[KORO-SENSEI yelps]
[KORO-SENSEI]
What kind of talk it that?
Nonsense! That's what it is!
You can do this! Think positive!
[LOVRO]
Even if I wasn't a relic.
Even if I could kill that man.
You'd still be out of my reach.
Same goes for Irina
when you get down to it.
If I can't do it,
neither can she.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Very well.
If giving up is your choice,
don't let me stop you.
But at least stick around
to support your protégé.
After all, whatever else
one might say about her skills,
she's certainly proven herself
a capable wielder
of death before.
[LOVRO]
Hm.
Once upon a time, yes.
[IRINA]
Level with me, okay?
Do you honestly believe I can
take down someone like Karasuma?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Of course.
I can't speak to what you may
or may not have learned
at the feet of your guru.
But based on what I've
seen you accomplish
since you've been here, I'd
be a dolt to think otherwise.
Case in point.
The lingerie you
ordered yesterday!
If that's not initiative,
I don't know what is!
[IRINA]
Uh! Perv!
[KORO-SENSEI] If you want
others to believe in you,
you've got to believe in you.
Show them what you've got:
Karasuma, this Lovro
fellow, the children.
[IRINA]
Hm.
[chatter]
Yo. Have a look at
this, man, it's Mr. K.
[NAGISA]
Huh?
[KAEDE] Oh, yeah. He's been
eating his lunch out there
a lot lately for some reason.
While he's smackin'
on his sandwich,
the spider move in for the kill.
Looks like Professor Bitch
is gonna go for it.
Mind if we talk for
a sec? You an' me?
What now? I'm aware this
is a pretend assassination,
but I'm done screwin' around.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Huh.
She has a knife, I see.
Surely she knows he can smell
the ruse from a mile away.
The woman's a fool.
[IRINA]
Aw, come on.
Don't be such a
stick in the mud.
I'm a girl willing to do
whatever it takes to stay here.
You know that about me.
No more screwin' around.
Unless that's what
you'd prefer in exchange.
One good turn
deserves another, yeah?
You just call the game, love.
[KARASUMA]
It's as simple as that, huh?
If I take her knife,
this nonsense will be over.
All right, fine. Jab me.
Just be quick about it, though.
[IRINA gasps]
[IRINA]
You're a good sport.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Mr. Lovro,
you've been Miss Irina's teacher
for some time, have you not?
[LOVRO]
Hm?
[KORO-SENSEI] You've noted
her communication skills,
her versatility with words?
To watch her pass
that on to her students
is to watch a master at work.
She's fluent in ten languages
because she's fluent
in the ways of people.
When she finds the right words,
there's no one she can't reach.
And nowhere, I suspect,
is she in more command of her
particular gifts than here.
What do ya suppose
she's been up to?
[LOVRO grunts]
Gott im Himmel.
'Kay.
Ready or not, here I come!
[KARASUMA]
Son of a--!
[IRINA grunts]
[BOTH grunt]
[OKAJIMA]
Didn't see that coming!
Man, this is hot!
[SUGINO]
Yeah! Who's the bitch now?
[KORO-SENSEI] She's building
the skills to kill me
in much the same way
she'd acquire a new language.
Methodically, feeling
out the terrain,
drilling vocabulary,
so to speak.
One look inside her bag
and you'll see there's
no room for doubt.
This is definitely
a woman with a plan.
[IRINA]
Say goodnight!
[KURASAMA grunts]
Take it easy, huh?
[IRINA]
Great.
If this comes down
to strength, I'm boned.
What am I s'posed--
[IRINA gasps]
Karasuma?
[KARASUMA grunts]
Let me kill you.
Pretty please?
[KARASUMA growls]
Pretty sure it's bad form for
a killer to beg permission!
This is ridiculous!
[IRINA grunts]
[KARASUMA sighs]
Oh fine.
[IRINA gasps]
[KARASUMA]
Better to get it over with
than spend all day
listening to you whine.
You go, girl!
She won!
Callin' it! Professor Bitch
was the first one to hit him.
[KARASUMA]
It's not like I lost anything.
Koro-sensei was full of it.
He'd never just stand there and
let me take pot shots at him.
[IRINA sighs]
[KORO-SENSEI]
You have to respect
a pupil willing to
challenge the master.
Especially when the deck
is stacked against her.
Imagine what the children
get out of seeing her
rise to the occasion.
Yes, that feisty, can-do spirit
is an example for us all.
When push comes to shove,
if there's any chance
of assassinating me,
her being here is
essential to it.
[IRINA]
Sir, I--
You're the worst
student I've ever had.
But, as a teacher,
I don't hold a candle to you.
If you can kill 'im.
Do it.
[IRINA gasps]
Absolutely! Yes, sir!
I did it!
[NAGISA]
Harsh. Arrogant. Foul-mouthed.
But when you see her
in her element,
she's a pretty damn
good teacher.
[IRINA laughing]
Hey! The hell's with
the suit of armor?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Nothing in our little bet
prohibited basic self-defense.
[school bell chimes]
[KORO-SENSEI humming]
[ISOGAI] You're in a
good mood today, sir.
Afterschool plans?
[KORO-SENSEI]
As a matter of fact, yes.
I'm flying to Hawaii for
a blockbuster premier.
This particular movie
I've been chomping at
the bit to see for ages!
Seriously? Wow. No fair.
[KORO-SENSEI chuckles]
[KORO-SENSEI]
What's Mach Twenty good for
if I can't be first in line
for an international hit?
[MEG]
Sonic Ninja?
[NAKAMURA]
It's a big comic book movie.
They've been hyping it
since last year.
[KORO-SENSEI] Don't worry,
I'll give you all the gory...
[BOTH sigh]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Okie-dokie, then.
I'd best be on my way.
[NAGISA]
Koro-sensei! Wait up!
We wanna come
with you. Please?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Oh-ho! Fans of the franchise?
Oh, yeah.
We've been waiting for the
sequel for, like, ever.
[KORO-SENSEI]
I'm a little surprised
you're into comic books, Karma.
It's actually not my thing.
I really dig the
director, though.
It's his first genre film.
[RITSU]
I'd like to come, too.
If you don't mind.
I hope I'm not bothering you.
Um.
No offense, Ritsu, but what
are you doing in my phone?
I took the liberty
of uploading myself
into everyone's mobile devices.
This way communication between
students is streamlined,
and I'm fun-sized!
This version of me
is called Mobile Ritsu!
[NAGISA] Someone else that
can do almost anything.
[RITSU] If it's not too much
trouble, I'd love to know
what it's like soaring
through the air at Mach Twenty.
I can even take aerial photos
for Koro-sensei's dossier!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Well then, children,
let's go to the movies!
Brace yourselves for a flight
through the stratosphere
at super-sonic speed!
Okay.
I know we asked him on a whim,
but I'm kinda having
second thoughts.
What'd we just sign on for?
Yeah, well.
If we survive, maybe next time
we'll think of safety first.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Oh now, don't be afraid.
I'll accelerate gently so as
to not shock your systems.
[NAGISA, KARMA screaming]
Uh, okay!
[KARMA chuckles]
[KARMA]
Wow!
Check it out: the Pacific Ocean!
[NAGISA]
All right.
I'm surprise there's not
more wind or whatever.
It is because you're using your
head to deflect most of it?
[KORO-SENSEI] Excellent
powers of observation, Nagisa.
The secret, you see,
is my aerodynamic skin.
Normally, my head is
soft and squishy.
When exposed to high
pressure, however,
it hardens like a shell.
That's how I can withstand the
effects of Mach Twenty speed.
Did you know that something
very much like my skin
plays a role in your
day-to-day life?
[NAGISA]
Uh.
[KORO-SENSEI]
To explain,
let's explore the concept
of dilatancy...
[NAGISA] Is he seriously giving
us a lecture midflight?
This could be your best chance
to assassinate him, Karma.
He's distracted juggling
two things at once.
Except I don't wanna die.
We're over open water
at the speed of sound;
physics doesn't
support that plan.
Koro-sensei has us
right where he wants us.
We've got no choice
but to listen and learn.
[KORO-SENSEI]
And that is how
bulletproof vests
are manufactured,
utilizing the fascinating
science behind dilatancy.
I've made you that much smarter,
and in the time it takes
to catch Sonic Ninja.
[NAGISA]
We're really here.
We're in Hawaii, and we
know what "dilatancy" is.
[KARMA]
Man, it's freezing in here.
[KORO-SENSEI]
It's an island thing.
They're all about
cranking the AC.
Let's bundle you up so
no one catches pneumonia.
Here!
[KARMA]
Hmm.
This is so cool! I've never
been to a movie theatre!
Hey. Don't they cut out a bunch
of stuff for
distribution overseas?
We gettin' the real deal here?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Where's your sense of adventure?
It shouldn't be
all that different
than what we see back home
once it comes out over there.
And if it is,
so much the better.
It'll be like seeing the same
artwork from different angles.
Here. My tentacles can
be used as earphones.
I'll offer a running
commentary as we watch
just in case any nuances of this
version go over your head.
Now, sit back and
enjoy the show!
[NAGISA]
Wow.
This... is so... awesome!
[NINJA A]
Hi-yah.
[MOVIE NARRATOR] Evil doesn't
take a vacation. No one...
[NAGISA] A brooding hero
trying to save the world.
Kids my age eat this stuff up,
but what about Koro-Sensei.
Is he really into the
whole super hero thing?
[KORO-SENSEI chuckles]
[KORO-SENSEI]
This would be even better in 3D.
[MARY ANNE]
Oh my god!
[NAGISA]
Nevermind.
[ADAM]
Kill me if you must.
But first, behold
my true identity.
[MARY ANNE]
My brother?
[NAGISA]
What a cliffhanger.
They really know
what they're doing;
I'll go nuts waiting
for the next installment!
I don't know. I feel
like the filmmaker
copped out making
the bad guy the brother.
[NAGISA]
Oh... Well.
If you want to find out how the
series ends, I can calculate it!
I'll just make an algorithm of
every movie ever made!
Give me a couple minutes.
Nah, I'm good, thanks.
Between the two of you, wow.
Huh?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Long-lost siblings!
Can you imagine?
Merciful heavens,
how cruel fate can be!
[KORO-SENSEI crying]
Well, what do ya know?
Guess it really got to him.
Damn, my bad.
[RITSU]
He's been blubbering like that
all the way from Hawaii.
[NAGISA] Thank you for
taking us with you, sir
[KARMA]
G'night.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Yes, yes. Goodnight, children.
Be careful on the way home.
Oh, and I'd like you to write
a detailed synopsis of the film
in your own words
for class tomorrow.
[NAGISA]
Whoa!
You're giving us homework?
[KORO-SENSEI] Small price to
pay for a free trip to Hawaii!
[NAGISA sighs]
[KARMA]
What's up?
Something on your mind?
[NAGISA] It's just been
an interesting day is all.
We got flown to Hawaii
at Mach Twenty
and given a lecture on natural
science over the Pacific Ocean.
[KARMA]
Ahh, we lead a weird life.
[RITSU] Personally, my favorite
part of the whole experience
was watching
Koro-sensei protect you.
I've never seen
anything like it.
Did you realize he was
using his tentacles
to fend off dust
particles and debris?
[NAGISA]
When you think about it.
We saw the world through
Koro-sensei's eyes today.
[KARMA]
Hmm...
The more I get to know the guy,
the more I feel like
his everyday life
is something we can't
even comprehend.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Stiff upper lip, old boy.
No more tears.
I'm needed at Mimura's for
a one-on-one math tutorial.
[SHIRO]
Well?
Did your eyes follow his course?
[SHIRO]
Good.
Then you can kill him.
You mean... him?
[SHIRO]
Yes.
Your brother.
Though as of tomorrow,
he'll also be your teacher.
[SHIRO]
Now.
It's time to reap vengeance for
what's been done to our moon.