[school bell chimes]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Let's begin, shall we?
[STUDENTS]
Begin what, exactly?
[KORO-SENSEI] Studying
for midterms, of course!
Dun-dun-dun! Whoa, look out!
I'll be making this period
a high-speed enhanced
Midterm Study Hall!
[STUDENTS gasp]
[KORO-SENSEI] My doubles
will provide special
one-on-one attention.
Drilling everyone individually
on the areas where you
need improvement most.
Man, this is balls.
He's seriously gotta wear a
different headband
for each subject?
Gimme a break, man!
Naruto's not even on the test!
[NAGISA]
Look at him go!
Is it just me,
or is he getting faster?
I mean, six doubles for
Japanese, eight doubles
for math, three
for social studies,
four for science,
four for English.
One for Naruto.
[NAGISA]
A Koro-sensei for each of us.
And not that long ago he was
doing well
to split himself up
into four or five.
--[KORO-SENSEI groans]
--[NAGISA yells]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Knife down, Karma!
No sneak attacks
during Study Hall!
This is very difficult, so try
not to disrupt my concentration!
Doesn't all this spread
you a little bit thin, sir?
I, uh...
I mean, just thinking about it,
makes me feel tired.
[KORO-SENSEI]
No worries there.
I have a double outside
on R&amp;R duty!
[NAGISA]
How does that help?!
He's been leveling-up
like crazy these days.
I wonder.
Is he just prepping to
destroy the Earth, or what?
[NAGISA] Any way you slice it:
if you're an assassin,
he's a tricky target.
[KORO-SENSEI] There, are you
starting to wrap your head
around the material, Nagisa?
Yes, sir.
And if you're
facing midterms,
he's the best damn teacher
you could ask for.
[STUDENTS laughing, chattering]
[PRINCIPAL] Consider this
deceptively simple cube.
If I wished to align the colors
--quickly and intuitively.
--[NAGISA] Bye, Koro-sensei!
[PRINCIPAL] What might be the
best way to go about it?
--Any ideas?
--[KORO-SENSEI] Goodbye, Nagisa.
Better luck killing me tomorrow.
[PRINCIPAL]
The answer?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Uh?
[ASANO]
Pry them apart and reassemble.
It's as easy as that.
[chuckles]
Why, Koro-sensei. It's an honor.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Uhh...?
[IRINA]
Apparently this gentleman
is supposed to be
the principal here.
Believe me, he is, which
also makes him our boss.
[KORO-SENSEI screams]
[KORO-SENSEI] So good of you
to come all this way, sir!
Any chance we could discuss a
teensy little hike in salary,
if I'm not being too
forward, of course?
I've added a few extra
versions of myself to help
--with the workload--
--Forgive me for not
visiting sooner. I meant to
pay my respects before now,
but one gets sidetracked.
Mr. Karasuma and the
Ministry of Defense
have painted quite the
vivid picture of you.
Yes, vivid indeed, though I
don't pretend to understand
the situation in
every particular.
Nor do I feel especially
qualified to comment.
However I will say this,
if I may be so bold.
You seem to be torn between
embracing the role
of savior or villain.
[NAGISA]
Savior? Villain?
But no matter.
Such things aren't for men
like myself to resolve.
I'm hardly in a position
to save the world.
That job I must leave
to hands more capable.
So barring harm to my school,
your assassins may deal with you
as they will.
I've been given plenty of
incentive to turn a blind eye.
Thank you for
your cooperation.
That's a very reasonable
attitude, principal.
I find that quite
attractive in a man.
You flatter me, madam.
That said.
Though I'm happy to
give you carte blanche
to do what's necessary,
I must think of the future,
should the Earth survive.
In other words.
What becomes of my school if
Koro-sensei is assassinated?
[ASANO] Not to put
too fine a point on it,
but E Class must continue
to serve its function
in the grand scheme of things.
[KORO-SENSEI] Interesting.
So rock-bottom grades
and students with zero prospects
serve a "function," do they?
[ASANO]
Oh, yes.
Are you familiar with the
so-called Worker Ant Theory?
It tells us that in any group,
20 percent will work hard,
20 percent will be idle, and
the remaining 60 percent
will fall somewhere in between.
Now, imagine a group
without a middle ground,
where hard workers comprise
95 percent of the population,
and lay-abouts only five.
If the lazy worker ants
are stigmatized,
the ratio is perfectly feasible.
Those who under normal
circumstances fall into
the average category
better themselves
to avoid being associated
with the ostracized class.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Very logical.
And, of course, unless the five
percent is kept down,
the incentive for
the other 95 disappears.
[ASANO] Just today I
received an alarming complaint
from a D Class teacher.
It seems a student of
yours glared threateningly
at two upperclassmen,
such that the upperclassmen
feared for their lives.
[ASANO] I have no doubt
the confidence to do so
stems from their attempts
to assassinate you.
And perhaps that's
to be expected.
The issue, though, is that
an E Class student
dared to defy his better.
[ASANO] Obviously I cannot
let such insolence stand.
As his teachers, you are
expected to remind
the student in question
of his place.
Oh, and Koro-sensei?
You have one second
to solve this puzzle!
[KORO-SENSEI]
What?
You just spring this
on me out of the blue?
[KORO-SENSEI grunting]
[NAGISA]
Whoa. What the hell is going on?
[ASANO] Your speed certainly
lives up to the hype.
I can see why most
attempts on your life
would be an
exercise in futility.
But bear in mind, my friend.
In the grand scheme of things,
there are many problems for
which speed is of no use at all.
[ASANO] Now, if you'll
kindly excuse me.
[NAGISA]
Ah!
[ASANO]
Oh.
Hi there! I look forward
to your midterm results.
Best of luck to you.
[NAGISA]
Uh...?
[NAGISA] Huh... "Best
of luck," the guy says.
And just like that...
...I revert from assassin
back to an E Class nobody.
[KARASUMA]
As a target,
Koro-sensei is
practically invincible.
Amateur and professional
assassins alike
have their work cut out
trying to off him.
But as a teacher, he's
vulnerable to the whims
of people higher up on
the food chain.
[KARASUMA] People like
Kunugigaoka Academy principal,
Gakuho Asano.
A shrewd man who, in
the first decade of his tenure,
single-handedly hoisted
this school to top-tier status.
Essentially, if you teach here
there's no getting around
his personal vision of order.
That goes for us and for you.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Good morning, everyone!
As you might guess, today,
I thought I'd make
even more of me!
[NAGISA]
This is getting ridiculous.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Thinking caps on, let's begin!
[NAGISA] Even the afterimages
are getting sloppy.
[SUGINO] It's like he's turning
into a parody of himself.
Uh, Hey, Koro-sensei?
No offense, but isn't
this going to wear you out?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Wear me out? P'shaw!
[ASANO] E Class must
continue to serve
its function in
the grand scheme of things.
--[school bell chimes]
--[KORO-SENSEI pants]
[MAEHARA] Look at the poor guy,
he's totally down for the count.
I say we try our luck!
Not that I don't
appreciate it,
but why's he teaching us
so hard anyways?
[KORO-SENSEI chuckles] To get
those test scores up, why else?
If I do that...
--[laughing]
--[ISOGAI] Koro-sensei!
[OKANO] Look at my grade!
This is awesome!
We owe it all to you,
Koro-sensei! Thank you!
I'll never try
to kill you again!
[COLLEGE GIRL A]
Oh, sir! Please!
I need help with my grades, too!
[KORO-SENSEI] I'll never
have to worry about you
trying to kill me again!
It'll be sheer bliss!
[STUDENTS groan]
Uh. I mean, the whole
helping us study thing
is nice and all...
...but, the reward money we
get for assassinating him
is nothing to sneeze at.
Let's face it,
who needs to ace a midterm
when you've got that
kind of cash tucked away
in your bank account?
[KORO-SENSEI screams]
Money isn't everything, people!
Aw, c'mon, you gotta
cut us some slack here,
we're the End Class.
Yeah. Assassination we can
strive for. But academics?
Seriously, why bother?
[KORO-SENSEI] I see.
So that's how it is, then?
[OKAJIMA]
Hm?
How what is, sir?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Do you know what I think?
I don't think you appreciate
what it means to be an assassin.
Everyone. Schoolyard. Now.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[MIMURA] What's his deal,
making us all stand out here
like a bunch of goobers?
[NAKAMURA] I dunno,
maybe something we said
put him in a mood.
[KORO-SENSEI]
All right, children.
Love or hate the E Class system,
as a remedial process,
it can work.
[KORO-SENSEI] Imagine
placing within the top 50
of 186 students on midterms.
Make that a reality, and
securing a former teacher's
permission is all
an E Class student needs
to return to the class
from which they were ejected.
[KORO-SENSEI] But
given the conditions
we're forced to work under,
the personal setbacks
that landed each of you
here are difficult to fix.
[KORO-SENSEI]
That's why most E Class students
are convinced that returning
to the main campus
is no more than a pipe dream.
[IRINA] Don't tell me to
hurry up, I'm not a child.
[MEG] Sorry, Koro-sensei
asked me to bring you.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Ms. Jelavich.
I'd like your opinion as a
professional assassin.
All right, what
do you wanna know?
[KORO-SENSEI] Now, let's say
you've been given an assignment.
Do you have only
one plan going into it?
[IRINA]
Hm? 'Course not.
If my profession has
taught me anything,
it's that Plan A almost never
comes off like you'd expect.
There are just
too many variables.
A good assassin has backup plans
on hand for any contingencies.
[KORO-SENSEI] And
Mr. Karasuma, what about you?
[KARASUMA]
Hm?
[KORO-SENSEI] When teaching
knife combat strategies,
do you believe the first
strike is the only move
of any importance?
The first move is important,
but so's the follow-up.
Never assume the
first strike will hit.
Because when your opponent's
trained, you have to be ready
to deliver the next strike with
at least as much precision
and skill as the first,
or, better yet,
carry a second blade.
[STUDENTS gasp]
If you have a point, sir,
I think we're missing it.
[KORO-SENSEI] Listen to your
teachers, boys and girls!
Backup plans are the cornerstone
of confidence,
and a confident assassin
is a successful one.
The same goes
for life in general.
You strive for assassination
but not academics?
You've heard
the old saying, right?
Don't put all your eggs
in one basket!
Well, that's exactly what
you're doing here!
[STUDENTS scream]
[KORO-SENSEI] Now. Suppose
I left the classroom for good.
Suppose some other
would-be assassin out there
managed to do me in.
What would you be left with?
What would you strive for then?
Or are you satisfied
with being outcasts?
A word of advice
from your Koro-sensei,
you walk a fine line.
[KORO-SENSEI] Those who
can't wield a second blade
aren't qualified
to be assassins!
[STUDENTS scream]
[BOY STUDENT A]
What the--?
Holy crap, guys, check it out!
Is that a tornado?
[ASANO]
Hmph. What a showoff.
[STUDENTS groan]
[gasping]
[KORO-SENSEI]
There.
Our schoolyard needed
a good leveling.
Not to mention
a few weeds cleared.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[KORO-SENSEI]
I am a superior life-form,
capable of destroying the Earth.
As you can see, flattening
out this little corner
of it was a cinch.
[STUDENTS whimper]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Cast your nets wide.
Show me your backup plan,
that crucial second blade.
Otherwise, I'll be forced to
conclude no would-be assassin
here is worthy of me.
And I won't just
have a mind to leave,
I'll flatten this
entire campus as I go.
[NAGISA] A "second blade"?
So how long've we got?
[KORO-SENSEI] Not very.
Until the end of tomorrow.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[KORO-SENSEI]
The midterms are upon us, class.
I want all of you
to place in the top 50.
[ALL gasp]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Whether you realize it or not,
we've been sharpening those
second blades all along.
The main campus relies on
dull, rote-learning methods.
I, to put it mildly, do not.
You have what it takes.
So wield those blades
with confidence!
Take your midterms
by the gills, smiling,
your heads held high!
Be proud! Be bold!
And never forget,
you are assassins!
You are E Class!
[NAGISA]
Okay. Ready or not, here we go.
[ONO]
Hmph!
[NAGISA] Midterms are
administered on the main campus,
even for us.
Basically, to E Class,
they're just an away game.
Not much else.
[TEST MONSTER roars]
[NAGISA screams]
[SUGAYA, SUMIRE scream]
[STUDENTS screaming]
[TEST MONSTER roars]
[SUGINO] Our knife isn't nearly
enough to take this thing out!
How are we supposed to
tackle question four?!
[TEST MONSTER roars]
[screaming]
[NAGISA]
I expected this.
[NAGISA] The midterms
they give in this school
have always been a beast.
Damn it. You're kidding me!
I don't even know
where to start!
This question's
gonna eat me alive!
[TEST MONSTER roars]
[NAGISA]
I'm dead meat!
Did you really mean that crap?
You're gonna take off if they
don't all place in the top 50
on their stupid midterms?!
[KORO-SENSEI]
That's right.
Well, way to be unrealistic!
These kids have the worst
grade-point average
in the entire school!
Are you nuts?!
[KORO-SENSEI]
I wonder sometimes.
Either way, wherever
they've ranked before,
they're my students now.
[KORO-SENSEI]
When backed into a corner,
the first order of business
is assessing your options.
If I've taught
them nothing else,
I've certainly taught them that.
[NAGISA gasps]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Come now, we've covered this.
The poor beast isn't
as terrifying as all that.
Start by observing that fin.
On closer inspection,
it's just that, a fin.
Next, look over each part of the
question
with the same
attention to detail,
and piece together
what you find.
Voila! A trivial
adversary indeed!
[gasps]
[KORO-SENSEI] Now use that
trusty blade to fillet it.
[NAGISA]
Of course!
[ONO]
Huh...?
[NAGISA] Take the problem
one part at time.
That's the trick.
Just like Koro-sensei's
been teaching us all along!
[ONO growls]
[NAGISA]
This question...
...is dead meat.
[NAGISA]
So's this one.
And this one.
And this--
[STUDENTS scream]
[gasps]
[NAGISA whimpers]
[TEST MONSTER B roars]
[NAGISA gasps]
[NAGISA]
And all of a sudden...
...poised to strike...
...a question we weren't ready
for ambushed us from the rear.
[KARASUMA] Not to rock the boat,
but this is ridiculous.
You gotta help me out here.
However I look at it,
this test seems rigged.
[MALE TEACHER A]
I don't know what to say, sir.
You ought to have received
proper notification.
Perhaps there was some sort of
communications flap on your end?
But there's no point in coming
to the main campus,
I can tell you that. [laughs]
[KARASUMA] The communications
flap wasn't on our end, buddy.
Besides, what constitutes
"proper notification?"
Two days before midterms,
you decide to broaden the scope
and that's supposed
to be enough time for us
to cover everything?
[MALE TEACHER A] With all due
respect Mr., uh, Karasuma,
is it? You don't understand.
We're a prep school.
This sort of thing
happens all the time.
Our students are
expected to cram.
That's been our
policy for years.
In fact, when it was decided to
include new material
on this midterm, the principal
himself lectured our students
on those subjects personally.
It was wonderful.
You should've seen it.
[KARASUMA growls]
[KARASUMA]
Unbelievable.
Is there nothing
this man won't resort to
in the name of his own ideals?
[KARASUMA] They've put us
in a hell of a spot.
[KARASUMA] If Koro-sensei
leaves, we're screwed.
We lose everything.
[KORO-SENSEI]
I take full responsibility.
Clearly, I underestimated
this school's dedication
to the status quo. Forgive me
if I can't bear to face you.
[KARMA yells]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Uh...?
[KARMA]
Have it your way.
Keep your back
turned if you want.
Just makes it easier for us
to sneak up on you.
[KORO-SENSEI]
I am in no mood, Karma!
This whole situation
has me very de-- Uh?!
[KARMA] So they added
questions to the stupid test.
Big deal.
[CLASS gasps]
[SUGINO]
Seriously?
Hold the phone,
you got a hundred in math?
Your method worked
like a charm, Teach.
You gave us everything you had
and at the moment of truth,
it mattered.
So what if the midterms
decided to cover new territory?
I was ready.
Don't worry, though.
I'm not going anywhere.
You see, this is where I belong.
Normal Class has nothing
on assassination.
So. Where are you gonna go,
huh? Where do you belong?
You plan on using the fact we
didn't all make the top 50
as an excuse to
tuck your tail and run?
'Cause you're not fooling me.
I think you're just
scared that one of us
is actually gonna kill you.
[KORO-SENSEI growls]
[gasps]
You could've just told us.
Not like we'd blame you
for being afraid.
[STUDENTS laughs]
[MEG] Next time, consider being
more straightforward
--with how you feel.
--Even if how you feel is all,
"oh no, I wanna run away!"
[KORO-SENSEI growls, screams]
[KORO-SENSEI]
No one is running away!
'Kay. So what's the deal?
[KORO-SENSEI]
The deal is we get our revenge
on this school two-fold
during finals!
[STUDENTS laugh]
[KORO-SENSEI] Children!
This is no laughing matter!
[NAGISA] There's no denying we
hit a wall on our midterms.
The same wall that's always
closed us off
from everyone else.
But for once, I'm kinda
glad to be behind it.
Not just glad. Proud.
Proud to be in E Class!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Who puts E class in the corner?
[STUDENTS] Nobody puts
E Class in the corner!