[NAGISA]
I... I got in!
Oh, thank goodness the
hard part's finally over.
[KORO-SENSEI] Congratulations
all around! Well done!
Those second blades twinkled!
Everyone was accepted into a
top tier school of their choice!
You'll be entering
into freshman year
like the rock stars you are!
Ah! What a tremendous
weight off my shoulders!
We're meant to begin
our final round
of career counseling
sessions today,
but there's something I'm rather
keen on doing beforehand.
What might that be, you ask?
How to mark such
a joyous occasion?
Editing. Of course.
[STUDENTS]
Say what?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Oh, yes!
We will be
commemorating E-Class...
...with a special yearbook!
You're putting together
a yearbook just for us?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Yes!
Oh, that's right.
We didn't get to have
any pictures of you
for the regular one.
Mr. Karasuma stood in
as the E-Class teacher.
Not that we didn't
appreciate that,
but it does kinda suck you
weren't in a single shot.
Um... he managed
to photo-bomb a few
under the radar, actually.
[SUGINO] Makes it look like
the school's haunted.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Precisely!
Why rely on those pictures for
memories when we have these?
An entire year's worth
of candid moments!
A treasure trove of
student-teacher selfies,
thirty thousand strong!
Now, then, let us sort through
and find the best ones together!
[ISOGAI]
When did you take them?
[KIRARA]
Anyone else creeped out?
And if it so happens
we absolutely hate pictures
of ourselves, are we exempt?
Seriously?
My eyes are too small.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Not to worry.
I've taken the liberty of using
the "big eye" filter
for maximum cuteness.
[NAKAMURA]
Wow. That's so nice of you.
You know, the shots they used
for the regular yearbook
are sorta by-the-numbers.
And if we did one ourselves,
maybe we could go a
little more avant garde.
[KORO-SENSEI]
That's the spirit!
Here we have cool beauty
Hayami at a local pet shop!
And here we have a wonderfully
kinetic nighttime shot
of Mimura on air guitar!
[BOTH]
He-He was there for that?
[KORO-SENSEI]
And I'm just getting warmed up!
Princess Kataoka, resplendent
in fresh royal vestments!
Sensitive Muramatsu,
reacting to an icky cockroach!
And Okajima,
tearing about the campus
in the nude for some reason.
[OKAJIMA]
Whoa! Hang on a sec!
I feel like this means
there might be some
questionable photos of me
floatin' around out there.
[MAEHARA]
More questionable than that?
[SUGINO] Everybody find your
photos and destroy them!
Leave no trace!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Well, well.
Who would've have
thought yearbook editing
would get you all so fired up?
[ALL] Who did he think
would want to see that?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Okey dokey!
Let's choose our picks for
the School Events category!
What do you think of
these, eh? Bring ya back?
[NAGISA]
Not bad.
This was definitely a
year worth remembering.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Argh! I should've taken more!
This isn't nearly enough!
I wanted our yearbook to be
at least ten thousand pages!
[ITONA] Why don't we burn
'em all just to be safe?
[TERASAKA] Friggin'
dictionary's not that thick.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Outside, boys and girls!
We what need is a random
assortment of cosplay shots!
That's it!
Oh, that's money.
Very nice.
Excellent! More outfits!
[KAEDE chuckles]
Is it me, or have
things gotten chill?
I mean, Koro-sensei helped us
study for the entrance exams,
but aside from that,
February's been a free-for-all.
Eh, it's more like we're
at the mercy of his whims.
[KARASUMA]
No. You're being spoiled.
[ALL]
Huh?
He's just proud of how
far you've all come.
Figured it's time to
let you kids unwind.
Everything up to
now's been so intense.
Where's the harm in having fun?
That's what he's
thinking anyway.
Oh, I see.
What about you, Mr. Karasuma?
All things considered, do you
think we turned out okay?
Of course.
You've shaped up quite nicely.
In fact, if I ever
fall on hard times,
you'll be the ones I call.
[IRINA] A man and a
woman together in April.
Living together
in as one in April.
Making love on average
ten times a day.
[OKUDA] She's been mumbling
to herself a lot lately.
[ITONA] Maybe she found
religion or something.
[BOTH]
Huh?
Uh, what is this?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Come on now, don't be shy!
You simply must get in
on the cosplay action!
Or don't you find
the outfits suitable?
Oh, darling, think of
our first night together!
Not a chance!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Phew! All righty, then.
That oughta be enough for
all the campus photos.
Hang on a minute!
Do you mind telling us
why the heck we're all
stuffed in a giant purse?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Alas, campus photos alone
are not remotely sufficient.
What's needed now are
mementos of a world tour!
You're insane!
What're you gonna do?!
Seems like a lotta work!
[chuckling]
[KORO-SENSEI] Nonsense.
I promise this'll be fun.
A little time, a little
effort, a little ingenuity.
And voila!
Gum-Gum... Slingshot!
[STUDENTS screaming]
So all I really need to
do is pass this test?
Uh-huh.
Just think of it as your ticket
for back-to-school confidence.
If you can handle
what's on here,
you ought to be able to
breeze through first term
without any trouble.
And in your free time you can
adjust to the new environment.
[SAKURA]
Right.
[SAKURA] This is my
ticket back to school.
This is my ticket
back to school.
This is my ticket... back to...
[SAKURA]
...school.
[NAGISA]
My secret blade.
[gasps]
[NAGISA] Not exactly the use
it was designed for... but...
Nagisa?
You've got this. Just stay calm.
Focus on the here and now.
Believe in yourself.
Okay.
[NAGISA] Getting to see
that look on her face?
Totally worth it.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Now then,
where are we on what you'd
like to be when you grow up?
Any progress?
[NAGISA]
Well, actually...
...I think I want
to be a teacher, sir.
Granted, I can't
get up to Mach 20.
I'm not exactly,
you know, invincible,
and my brain doesn't have the
processing power of yours.
But still, I want to
mold young minds like you.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Excellent. I think we've got it.
You and your classmates
are equally endowed
with the same extraordinary
but fleeting gift.
The sweetness of youth.
Keep swimming,
Nagisa. Never stop.
Take advantage of what you
have while you have it.
Right!
G'bye, sir! See you tomorrow!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Yes. Indeed you will.
I take it that was the last of
the career counseling sessions?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Mm-hm.
My, such exciting prospects
these children have.
The only task that remains is
editing the E-Class yearbook.
Seems I'll be spending my
nights here for a while.
[KARASUMA]
Oh yeah?
[KORO-SENSEI] We need an
article on the development
of yours and Miss
Irina's relationship.
If you wouldn't
mind an interview,
it should only take five hours.
Oh to hell with that! I'm gone.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Uh?
Write about yourself.
You should preserve your wisdom.
[door opens]
[KARASUMA]
There's no getting around it.
Unconventional as
this class has been,
we've all learned something.
[KARASUMA]
The students.
Me.
[EXECUTIVE]
Report.
Yes, sir. He's in the
classroom by himself.
He'll be there for
the foreseeable future.
[EXECUTIVE] Well done,
Special Agent Karasuma.
You heard the man.
We make our move
tonight, March 6th.
Now, commence with
the assassination.
[EMPLOYEE A] Confirmed
direct hit on the school.
[EMPLOYEE B]
Target?
[EMPLOYEE A]
Getting a visual now.
Ha-ha! Look! Not so much as a
scratch on the entire building.
Our Anti-Tentacle-Creature
Permeable Laser satellite,
a.k.a. "The Spear of Heaven!"
Modeled on the tortoise
and powered by
antimatter life forms
the beam is amplified by
a giant particle accelerator
and fired from 250 miles.
It's designed to pass through
any and all barriers,
only liquefying
creatures like our target.
A powerful weapon
we've just deployed
without the slightest
hint of advance warning.
[KORO-SENSEI] What in heaven's
name was that? My tentacles...
[ALL gasp]
[EXECUTIVE]
Impossible.
He dodged it!
He actually dodged it!
[EMPLOYEE A]
A high-speed laser?
[EXECUTIVE]
What uncanny intuition he has.
No matter, this
is far from over.
[EXECUTIVE] Since he has the
poor manners to be alive,
he'll likely hedge his bets
and make a run for it.
But no matter, we're ready.
Tonight... will be
a night of surprises.
[EXECUTIVE]
Our Anti-Tentacle-Creature
Permeable Laser Barrier,
a.k.a.: "Shield of Earth."
Strategically placed camouflaged
ground facilities that emit
a matrix of laser beams,
enclosing the entire mountain.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Is this?
[KORO-SENSEI groans]
[EXECUTIVE]
There's nowhere to run.
The lasers penetrate
into the ground.
A cage of light;
not to kill him,
merely to prevent his escape.
I'd hoped to finish him off
with that first shot.
Once we set Plan B in motion,
it's a fair bet all hell
will break loose.
Ready the ground troops!
Case B-One deployment!
[EMPLOYEES]
Sir!
[NAGISA]
What the--?
What's all the light?
[NAGISA]
We were so naïve.
Somehow, we got it in our heads
this would all end peacefully.
The government left
nothing to chance.
They had everything in place.
Right down to the smallest,
most horrible detail.
As you can see, these measures
serve to contain and eliminate
the clear and present danger
to mankind's existence.
Thanks to the Shield,
the entity in question
now has no place to go.
As it turns out, this is
the creature responsible
for the moon's
destruction last year.
We've only learned today
that this creature,
this monster, rather, has not
only made explicit threats
involving the
destruction of Earth
but has been posing as
a teacher, of all things,
in order to take a classroom
of junior high school
children hostage.
We don't know why, but the
evidence speaks for itself.
We have no choice.
[TOWNSPERSON A]
What's going on?
[TOWNSPERSON B]
What is that?
[SDF MEMBER A] Nothing to
see here. Move along, please.
[SDF MEMBER B] This road is
closed until further notice.
[EMPLOYEE A]
We're looking at another week
until the shot is charged up.
[EXECUTIVE]
Perhaps firing the first one
at 20% capacity was a mistake.
He still saw it coming.
Since the jig is up, the next
one will fire at 100%.
His death is assured.
In the meantime, we'll manage
the inevitable fallout
from people
looking to interfere.
[KAEDE]
Nagisa!
Kayano!
Do you see all this!
What in the world is going on?
[TERASAKA]
What?!
Trespassing my ass,
it's our school! Move!
Look, I told you to back off!
Nagisa! Kayano!
D'you see the news?
This is absolutely terr--!
[ALL gasp]
[REPORTER A]
There they are!
Are you the poor children the
monster's been holding hostage?
Can you give us a few words?
[REPORTER C]
When did it first dawn on you
that you were being
held against your will?
How do you feel knowing
your teacher was dangerous?
[NAGISA]
Koro-sensei's been captured?
[REPORTER A] Can you tell
our viewers what it was like
in a classroom where the teacher
could explode at any second?
[FREPORTER C] Can you confirm
the allegations he was train--
That's enough! It's none
of your freaking business!
Do some basic
fact-checking, people!
The probability of Earth blowing
up is less than one percent!
Our teacher's not as dangerous
as he's been made out to be!
Leave him alone!
The stuff they're saying
about him isn't even true!
Yeah! Perfect!
Here's the human angle
we've been lookin' for.
Are these your own words
or simply what the monster
told you to say?
We know it must've been awful.
You're in a safe place.
Let it all out.
Clearly these boys and
girls are devastated.
Possibly suffering from
Stockholm Syndrome.
[NEWSCASTER A] No doubt the
trauma inflicted on them
by this reprehensible
creature runs deep.
Let's hope they get
treatment soon.
I can't imagine.
They're only babies.
Who could do such a thing?
As far as I'm concerned,
this devil deserves
whatever they do to him!
[NAGISA]
I don't get it.
Everyone feels sorry for us.
You don't have
permission to film here!
Pack up your equipment and go.
[REPORTER A] Excuse me, the
public has a right to know
what's going on here, sir!
Oh, please! You're battering
children for ratings.
Don't get high and mighty!
Everyone leave!
By order of the Defense Agency,
this area is off limits!
Failure to vacate the
premises will be actionable.
The students are safe.
They'll be taken into
protective custody.
[ISOGAI] Mr. Karasuma, what
have they done to Koro-sensei?
I'm afraid we're out of time.
The government had no choice
but to initiate their end game
strategy before it was too late.
End game strategy?
So is that what this
barrier's all about?
[KARASUMA]
The barrier's just a means
of keeping him from
being able to escape.
In a week, they'll use
a high-powered laser
to finish the job.
[STUDENTS gasp]
You're kidding me!
This was our assassination!
Yes, and your efforts
have not been unappreciated.
But it's time now
for you step aside.
So we do all the ground work
and you reap all the glory?!
This isn't fair. Why didn't
you tell us anything?
And how come the media's
totally making it
sound like Koro-sensei
manipulated us?
This is not cool, sir.
We were supposed
to assassinate him,
and now we're being dealt out?
You know Koro-sensei
won't stand for this.
He's expecting to be
killed by his students!
Come on, Mr. Karasuma! Please!
You've gotta tell them
to let us in there!
The mountain's been
fortified, I'm sorry.
Elite forces have
established a perimeter.
There're no openings
to be taken advantage of.
Your work's done here.
No, it's not!
There's too much we still
haven't talked to him about!
So many things we wanna try!
If you're not gonna help us,
then get out of our--!
You know I can't
let you in there.
National security is
on the line right now!
Now, you listen and
you listen good.
Do not give me a hard time.
Is that clear?
Give it up, Nagisa.
He's not on our side.
Just another stiff-collared
company man.
When it's down to the wire,
only thing a guy like him
ever does is follow orders.
[KARASUMA]
You're damn right.
And my orders are to protect
the people I'm entrusted with
at all costs.
Bottom line. One way or
another, he has to be killed.
Who does the honors
isn't up to you.
Get 'em out. Have 'em
escorted to a secure area.
Yes, sir!
Son of a bitch! Do you
believe this bullshit?
Did you hear what he said?
What?
About giving him a hard time?
I have a feeling he didn't just
choose those words at random.
[TERASAKA]
Okay. So?
Don't you get it?
Think back to what
he told us earlier.
You've shaped up quite nicely.
In fact, if I ever
fall on hard times,
you'll be the ones I call.
Those words.
I think saying "don't
give me a hard time"
was his way of getting across
that he believes in us.
Mr. Karasuma is counting
on us to handle things.
I'm positive.
So, let's put our heads
together and devise a plan.
We all know what
the goal is here.
We know exactly what
we're capable of.
The question is: What would
Koro-sensei want us to do?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Buff, buff, shine, shine,
make is sparkle, make it gleam.
That's the way!
[KORO-SENSEI chuckles]
[KORO-SENSEI] Nothing like
cleaning to pass the time.
[KORO-SENSEI]
It's a bit lonely, yes,
but there's no point worrying
at this late in the game.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Of course, if I had one wish.
I'd like to see them again.
Just one last time.
[KORO-SENSEI]
I'm up a creek.
At least that's what
everyone's thinking right now.
Alas, I'm a super-being capable
of moving at Mach 20 speed.
Fortunate, given how
much I have left to do.
[chuckling]
[KORO-SENSEI]
I can't bring myself to choose!
That does it!
The E-Class yearbook will
have to be super-sized!
[NAGISA] Countdown to
Koro-sensei's deadline,
approximately... three hours.