[NAGISA] From the start,
we'd been protected.
Because our teacher, our
larger than life mentor,
was as kind and as
caring as he was strong.
[NAGISA]
Kayano.
I don't even know what to say!
Nagi-- Achoo!
It's cold.
[KAEDE yelps]
What-What happened to my top?
[KAEDE]
Wh-What?
I'm so sorry.
Shut up!
[MAEHARA]
Easy now.
Hey, at least Koro-sensei
managed to fix your hair.
I know, but...
...I wish he could've done
something about my clothes.
So, uh,
I don't know if this is
appropriate for me to ask, heh,
but is it just me or
did she come out of that
a bigger cup size?
Koro-sensei. You can do that?
[sighs]
[KORO-SENSEI]
I am exhausted.
[NAGISA]
As we watched him collapse,
we couldn't shake
the impression.
He looked spent, but happy.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Come now.
What kind of assassin lets
a target linger indefinitely
on the brink?
Don't you understand?
At this point, we're just
running out the clock.
I'm sorry, children.
All good things must
come to an end.
That's life.
That's the nature
of the classroom.
[NAGISA] The red light
from above began to swell,
indicating eloquently, cruelly,
that the hour had come.
It hurt, but we didn't
have a second to waste.
[ISOGAI]
Guys.
We have to make a decision
one way or the other.
[ISOGAI]
We could stay out of it,
leave Koro-sensei's
fate up to them.
Let's take a vote.
Who here doesn't
want to kill him?
[ISOGAI] All right,
thank you. Hands down.
Who wants to kill him?
[NAGISA]
They were a part of us.
Our guns. Our knives.
Our teacher.
[NAGISA]
This is it. This is our answer.
We're assassins.
Our target is our teacher.
[NAGISA] These were the
nonnegotiable terms of our bond,
the only way to
graduate with honor.
We knew what had to
be done, and it hurt.
You can't move if we're
all pinning you down.
That right, sir?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Precisely, Nakamura my dear.
Though I can't help but feel
you're being a tad
bit lax on that grip.
[ALL gasp]
[NAGISA] We didn't give
much thought to why.
Just tried to focus
on the task at hand.
He'd praised us, scolded us,
nurtured us all year,
and here we were,
holding him down,
clutching for all we were worth.
[MEG] Your heart, it's-it's
under your tie, you said?
Which one of us... is gonna...?
[STUDENTS gasp]
[NAGISA]
Guys... please.
Let me. I'll do it.
Sure, I got no beef with that.
Well, you are the
head of the class,
so I suppose
it makes sense.
[NAGISA]
Sir--
[KORO-SENSEI]
It's all right.
You can actually
stab through the tie.
There's been a hole in it since
the day it was given to me.
I decided to leave
it like that...
...for... sentimental reasons.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Ah, before you proceed...
...let me say farewell
to my fellow educators.
Miss Irina, are you
sure you won't join in?
I'd hate for you to
miss out on the bounty.
No, thank you.
I'd really rather not.
Who gives a damn?
It's only money.
What I've learned in this
class is more valuable.
It isn't about me.
It's about the bond you
share with these kids.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Indeed.
Mr. Karasuma.
I thank you.
You've had a hand in
molding these children
into what they've become.
If you please, continue
to guide them on their way
after I'm gone.
Of course.
You've given me no end of
trouble over the past year.
But, even so, it's been
a year I'll never forget.
Rest in peace. Koro-sensei.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Quite.
[KORO-SENSEI] Okey dokey,
class, it's about that time.
There's so much more
I could say, but alas,
I'll be lucky to
squeeze in what I can.
In lieu of tearful goodbyes,
if you'll indulge me...
...I'd like to call roll...
one final time.
[KORO-SENSEI]
When you hear your name called,
please say, "Here."
Look me squarely in the eye
and answer in a loud voice.
Once we've gone
through everyone,
you may commence
with the assassination.
Wait!
Please tell me that you're all
present and accounted for!
I don't want the last thing I do
to be marking one of you absent!
[STUDENTS]
Get on with it!
[sighs]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Very well, then.
Karma Akabane.
Here.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Yuma Isogai.
Here.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Taiga Okajima.
Here.
[crying]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Hinata Okano.
Manami Okuda.
Yes, sir! Here!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Meg Kataoka.
Here.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Kaede Kayano.
Here.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Yukiko Kanzaki.
Here.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Justice Kimura.
Here!
[crying]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Hinano Kurahashi.
Here!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Nagisa Shiota.
Here.
[KORO-SENSEI]
My sweet, young assassins...
Sosuke Sugaya.
Here.
[KORO-SENSEI]
...as you ready yourselves...
...to snuff out a life...
[KORO-SENSEI]
Tomohito Sugino.
Here.
[KORO-SENSEI] ...you understand
better than anyone
the value of what's lost...
[KORO-SENSEI]
Kotaro Takebayashi.
Here.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Ryunosuke Chiba.
Here.
[KORO-SENSEI]
...because you've studied...
Ryoma Terasaka.
Yo.
[KORO-SENSEI
...fretted...
[KORO-SENSEI]
Rio Nakamura.
You know it.
[KORO-SENSEI] ...turned it
over and over in your mind...
[KORO-SENSEI]
Kirara Hazama.
Here, sir.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Rinka Hayami.
Here.
[KORO-SENSEI]
...and in the process,
without even realizing it,
given that life meaning.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Sumire Hara.
Here.
[KORO-SENSEI] It's been a
privilege watching you grow.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Yuzuki Fuwa.
Here!
[KORO-SENSEI]
But the best part...
...was growing right
alongside you.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Hiroto Maehara.
[grunts]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Koki Mimura.
[MIMURA]
Here.
[KORO-SENSEI]
So please...
Takuya Muramatsu.
Yeah.
[KORO-SENSEI]
...in this moment...
Toka Yada.
Here!
[KORO-SENSEI] ...let me be
the finest expression...
...of your bloodlust.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Taisei Yoshida.
Here!
[KORO-SENSEI]
If I die knowing I've helped
these 28 souls find
a brighter future...
[KORO-SENSEI] Autonomous
Intelligence Fixed Artillery,
Ritsu.
Here.
[KORO-SENSEI]
...I die exquisitely happy.
Itona Horibe.
Here.
[KORO-SENSEI]
All things considered,
I'd say it's been an
exceptionally fun year.
[KORO-SENSEI]
I say this with all sincerity.
It's a privilege to be
assassinated by you.
As a fellow spirit,
from one traveler to another,
give a yell for all life...
[KORO-SENSEI]
...and strike.
[NAGISA]
This is it.
This is the part
where I kill him.
[NAGISA]
I'm shaking.
Why can't I stop shaking?
[heart beating]
[screams]
[gasps]
[KORO-SENSEI] Don't kill me with
anguish in your heart, Nagisa.
Nice, deep breath.
Give us a smile.
[NAGISA crying]
[crying continues]
Goodbye... Koro-sensei.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Goodbye... Nagisa.
[NAGISA]
The bare minimum.
That's all I could
bring myself to say.
Gratitude. Regret.
I put everything
I felt into that blade.
Like I was channeling my soul.
With every fiber of
my being, I thanked him...
...with my knife.
[NAGISA]
As his life ebbed away,
it was as if he were saying,
"Congratulations."
[NAGISA crying]
[wailing]
[STUDENTS crying]
[crying continues]
[IRINA sniffs]
[crying]
[wailing]
[NAGISA] Very soon,
it would be midnight.
Graduation day...
at Kunugigaoka.
[NAGISA] We'd finished
the year a little early.
Time to turn our sights
on what lay ahead.
[NAGISA] Afterward, we went
back to the classroom,
hoping to find some
trace of Koro-sensei.
There were diplomas
waiting for us.
And a yearbook.
One for each of us.
And copies of "Koro-sensei's
Rules to Live By."
Apparently, the laser
fired off at some point,
but it mattered so little.
I don't think any
of us even noticed.
A reconnaissance squad
showed up later.
Mr. Karasuma took it upon
himself to lay down the law.
He told them we fell
under his jurisdiction,
that students and classroom
alike were to be left in peace.
Koro-sensei's book was thick.
It had more pages
than a dictionary.
And while it began as a
friendly, easy-to-read manga,
before long...
[KORO-SENSEI] I'm especially
proud of the workbook appendix.
And the short stories composed
for the vocabulary section
are absolutely riveting,
if I do say so myself.
You know what would
be a great idea?
A spinoff manga
starring me, still alive!
Ooo! I can be the big bad!
[NAGISA]
His advice was great,
but we got kinda fed up
with the level of detail.
[groans]
[NAGISA]
Before we knew it,
our tears had washed away in
the sweet release of sleep.
[NAGISA]
We woke to find sunlight
pouring through the windows.
[NAGISA] The cherry
blossoms were in bloom.
Small. Delicate. And strong.