[NAGISA] Our infiltration of the
Fuma Denjo hotel is underway.
We're closing in on
the antidote. Hopefully.
Time is running out. Unless
we make it to the top floor,
and soon, our
classmates might die.
[KARMA] Seem fairly average
for a pro, if you ask me.
And is breaking glass
supposed to be intimidating?
'Cause I can do that.
But I wouldn't call
in reinforcements
as an opening move. But then,
I'm not especially threatened
by "a bunch of amateurs."
[STUDENTS]
Ah...
[GRIP] All right. Put your
money where your mouth is.
[KARMA]
If you insist. [chuckles]
[KARMA grunts]
Nice try, kid. But,
as weapons go, hun,
I'd have gone with harder.
[GRIP grunts]
I guess I'll have to do without.
[GRIP grunts, yells]
[GRIP growls]
[NAGISA]
Uh...
[KARMA] This dude's grip could
crush a grown man's skull
like an egg. He gets his
mitts on me, it's game over.
Heh. The odds are definitely
not in my favor.
Nothing unusual about that.
But in the end, this is
just like any other game.
Just like school.
[KIMURA]
Uh.
[SUGAYA]
Whoa...
Oh, wow. He's blocking
like an expert!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Those are your defensive moves,
are they not, Mr. Karasuma?
[KARASUMA]
For assassins,
self-defense doesn't
often come into play.
I don't recall having actively
taught him any of this.
There's no denying it, though.
These moves are how I handled
their attacks in class.
Damned impressive. This kid's
a natural-born fighter.
A cut above his peers, even
in a classroom of assassins.
[KARMA]
I can dodge him all day,
but if I move in for a hit,
this prick's gonna grab me.
[GRIP] Hm? What's the problem?
Evasive maneuvers ain't
gonna win this. You have'ta
come in for an attack!
Oh, you don't say?
And what if really
all I'm tryin' to do
is keep you occupied?
I mean, my buddies are kinda
hopin' to sneak by, so,
maybe I'm just bein' clever.
Aw, relax. I'm pretty
underhanded on the best of days.
But this is one fight I
wanna win fair and square.
No tricks, no cheating,
no holdin' out.
Just you an' me. Now, like men.
Be my guest, hun.
I like the cut of your jib.
See, this is what
I've been talkin' about!
Two equals, mano y mano. A real
battle to the death, hun.
[KARMA grunts]
[GRIP]
Hm?
[KARMA]
There's my in!
[KARMA groaning]
[STUDENTS gasp]
Say goodnight, you little punk.
[NAGISA gasps]
Oh, no!
[GRIP]
Sorry, kid.
You're underhanded
on the best'a days.
I'm underhanded,
like, every day.
You son of a bitch!
He wanted to fight you like a
man and this is how you respond?
Oh come on. This ain't the place
for that, kid; get over it, hun.
Look, you can't get hung up
on ethics. I'm an assassin.
This biz don't reward folks
who play by the rules.
Hun, if you got a
canister of gas?
Use it. If he was all that,
he'd have done the same--
Uh?!
[GRIP chokes]
[STUDENTS gasp]
[GRIP]
Uh... You.... Ah.
Guess great minds think alike.
Now what was it were you saying
about me being "all that?"
[GRIP] How di... How did
you not... breathe it in?
I-I sprayed you...
at point blank range.
You should be paralyzed, hun.
[GRIP grunting]
[GRIP groaning]
C'mon, Terasaka! What
are you waiting for?
I'm gonna need duct tape
and every free hand we got
to hold this crazy bastard down!
--[STUDENTS sigh]
--Yeah, all right. Fine.
You've been yankin' this
creep's chain all along, huh?
[GRIP groaning, screams]
Fair fight, my ass!
Stay on guard while
you're taping him up.
He's incapacitated,
but he might be strong enough
to spring back before too long.
[STUDENTS]
Yes, sir.
[GRIP growling]
[GRIP]
Huh?
Handy, right?
Lifted it off that Smog
weirdo a while ago.
Still, disappointing it's a
"one-time-use" type-a deal.
How did you see it comin'?
You must've held your
breath when I sprayed you.
How'd you know to do that
when my hands were empty?
No way you could've told I
had anything on me! Ugh! Hun.
That's the whole point.
With you, I was on guard against
everything but bare hands.
[GRIP]
Hun.
[KARMA]
As far as I know,
you probably were lookin'
forward to an honest fight.
But you're also on
someone else's payroll,
so you don't get to choose.
You'd've had to stop us
by any means necessary.
I would've done the exact
same thing in your shoes.
In a way, my mistrust
was a compliment.
He's really good.
[NAGISA] Yes, he is. And he's
changed, for the better.
[KORO-SENSEI]
The anguish of defeat
had never darkened Karma's
door. Finals provided
our cocky comrade a
much-needed reality check.
Failure humanized the
perspective of his former foes.
He suddenly found himself
among their number.
His picture of the world
altered drastically,
leaving him with a healthy
respect for those around him.
He was able to foresee
his adversary's moves
because he didn't underestimate
his abilities.
Something he only learned
through his previous failure.
We must see our opponent, not
as an obstacle, but as a person.
Toiling in the shadow of defeat,
we taste true victory.
It is a pleasure to see you
take the lesson to heart, Karma.
I'm very excited about what
your future holds in store.
[GRIP] Hm. Hun, hats off to ya.
You're nothin' to sneeze at.
I may be beaten, but it was
a pleasure to know that you--
[KARMA]
Oh, we're not done.
No, I'm just
getting started.
[GRIP]
Mm...?
What in the hell are
those s'posed to be?
Mustard and wasabi.
You never know when you're gonna
need 'em to shove up a nose.
--[STUDENTS scream]
--[GRIP] Do what?
[KARMA] Part of keepin' my guard
up meant I had to play nice.
But, hey, now what we've got you
all bound up, I can let loose.
You'll wanna hold still
or that special clip's gonna
rip your nostrils off.
Now let's see. You've
got your jalapenos,
your hatch chilies,
your ghost peppers,
those are a kick in
the balls, right?
And a pinch of garlic
for hearth-health.
Well, hun,
what cha think?
Show us that
samurai willpower?
--[GRIP screams]
--[KARMA chuckles]
So, uh. I notice
Karma's still a sadist.
[KORO-SENSEI]
I'm very concerned
about what his future
holds in store.
Who walks around with this
stuff in their bag? Ugh.
Can we keep movin',
please? Someone'll spot us.
[KARMA] 'cause you stick
out like a sore thumb.
[TERASAKA]
Ha, ha.
[RITSU] Attention. The terrace
is just up these stairs.
Might be tricky.
This is the club floor.
[RITSU]
Correct.
The Executive Floor can be
accessed via the staircase
just off the lounge area.
Unfortunately, the back entrance
has a manual lock on it,
so we'll need to detour around
and through the bar to open it
and let the others in.
[MEG] So we're flying
by the seat of our pants.
A bar's the last
place we belong.
[MEG] Koro-Sensei and
Mr. K, you hide here.
Leave the tricky part
to those best qualified.
We'll unlock the door
to the VIP stairs.
You fellas might be out
of your dept in the club,
but us girls'll do just fine.
Yeah we will!
No way. I'm sorry,
it's too dangerous.
Ah. Well, plan B?
[STUDENTS]
Huh?
Ah...
[NAGISA]
Huh?!
Uh?! Uh... huh?
--[FEMALE GUEST D] So awesome.
--[FEMALE GUEST C] Yeah!
--You can thank the CEO.
--No kidding.
[YUJI] Thanks for the executive
suite, mom and dad.
And all the douche-yachts
rubbin' shoulders with me
to get at your money.
[YUJI] This shit is depressing.
Lamest vacay ever.
[YUJI gasps]
[FUWA]
Oh, be a man already!
You're here to protect us,
not use us as a shield!
Get in front!
[NAGISA] I can't! Don't
make me do this, please!
[HAYAMI]
Stop it.
[FUWA]
You look fabulous!
[NAGISA grunts]
That's right. This is my life.
[YUJI sighs]
Quit whining.
You're deep undercover.
We talked about this.
You won't arouse
suspicion this way.
[NAGISA]
Did you have to say "arouse?"
Relax! It's all
part of the plan.
[NAGISA]
It is?
[RITSU]
You look stunning!
[NAGISA]
No, I do not!
Don't be so casual!
Tart it up.
Whoa, wait! Are you my
pimp all of a sudden?
Where'd this outfit
come from anyway?
[HAYAMI]
Next to the pool.
Consider it an
anonymous donation.
[NAGISA]
Uh!
[YUJI] Hottie alert. First time
I've seen her on the club scene.
This place is disgusting.
Let's unlock the door before
some tool tries to hit on us.
[NAGISA]
Don't even.
You're milking this moment
for all it's worth.
[YUJI]
Yo!
[NAGISA]
Uh!
How you doin', shortie?
Papa wants to buy you a drink.
Anything you want, heh, heh!
My treat. For reals.
[GIRLS groan]
Go on, Nagisa.
Don't be an ice queen.
Wha...? I thought
we had a deal!
[MEG] The deal is we act
natural. Now get in there!
We'll swing back around for you.
[NAGISA] Ah... How did my
life get to this place?!
[YUJI] Nagisa's a really
cute name for a girl.
Anyway, I'm Yuji.
[NAGISA whimpers]
Okay, let's make a break for it.
[MEG] I think we go up the side
stairs. Let me check the map.
Right. Should be just up
ahead a little further.
[PUNK A] Hey, hey.
What's the hurry, doll?
[PUNK B] You girls look like
you could use a little company.
--[PUNK A chuckles]
--[MEG] Ugh.
Is this what I have to look
forward to every time we go out?
Look, bro. I hate
to disappoint you--
--[TOKA laughs]
--Yada?
[TOKA] Hiya boys. Wow,
you two are stacked.
Look, we'd love to chill,
but our daddies keep us
on a short leash.
Yeah, I know it sucks,
but what're you gonna do?
Helicopter parents.
Huh?! Tha... Th-Th-That's
a yakuza pin!
[PUNK B]
Not just any yakuza pin!
That's the emblem of
the relatively small
but absolutely terrifying
Shuei Syndicate!
[PUNKS]
Sorry we bothered you!
Okay, bye! And that's how you
separate the men from the boys.
Why do you have
a yakuza pin?
[TOKA laughs]
[music plays]
[YUJI]
C'mon, drink up! I'm buyin'!
We're livin' large tonight!
Uh! I'm too... Uh, I mean,
I don't like the way
alcohol tastes.
[NAGISA]
Keep it together, Nagisa.
Hold his interest long enough
to give the girls a chance
to unlock the door.
So what brings you to
this place? Your friends?
Your mom and dad?
Mom and dad?
As if the two of them would
give me the time of day! Hey!
Wanna know a secret? Don't tell
anyone, but my dad's on TV.
Like, uber famous.
You'd know 'im if you
saw 'im, trust me.
He's huge. Paparazzi
hound him all the time.
Dude can't get away with jack.
'Least not in public!
One time, he was tellin' me
about this anchor chick he
kept fondling under the table
when they'd cut to commercial.
That sounds skeezy. Does he
brag about stuff like that?
[YUJI]
Damn it. Way to go, dumbass.
Real smooth. Can't you
make an impression
without bringing up the
old man? I'm so lame!
Uh, smoking's
really bad for you,
'specially that stuff.
Heh. What're you,
the surgeon general?
Come on, it's cool.
People just need to loosen
up every once in a while.
[NAGISA] My teacher calls
this a gateway substance.
Says it puts unsuspecting kids
on the road to addiction.
Recreational drugs aren't
the answer to life's problems.
[YUJI grunts]
Yeah, well!
What's your teacher know
about my problems?
Guys have it rough.
We gotta be cool
twenty-four-seven just to score!
You try bein' somebody when
all people do is compare you
to your celebrity dad!
You girls. Y'all don't
have a clue how it is!
All you have to do it put on a
li'l makeup, walk into a club
and take your pick!
[NAGISA]
Uh...
I can't speak for most girls,
but the ones I know have
a lot more on their minds.
Oh! That's from Professor
Bitch's pin collection!
That woman is something else.
Yakuza overlord, horse breeder.
Any pin you can think of,
she's got it and knows
how to walk the walk.
Wow that line of work
totally fascinates you,
doesn't it, Yada?
You're always picking her
brain about different stuff.
[TOKA] Yeah. It's like
Koro-Sensei always says
about our "second blade."
And, Professor Bitch has
more than two. I like
an extensive skill set.
See whatever job she's dropped
into, she has a strategy.
That's what you call
serious life-competence.
I bet one day when you grow up,
you'll be exactly like her!
[KAEDE growls] Never thought I'd
respect a girl with huge melons.
[OKANO] Wow! Kaede's made a
real breakthrough, everyone!
[MEG]
Okay. There's the door.
They have a guard posted,
though. We didn't count on that.
Not to be that girl, but I think
we might need a man for this.
Well, damn. Okay, Kaede.
Go and rescue Nagisa.
Sure!
Get a load of that face.
Something tells me we'd be
better off not engaging.
Hell, even if we
could take this guy,
he won't go down
without makin noise.
[KAEDE]
Nagisa!
[NAGISA]
Uh. Oh, hey there.
Well, uh, it's been
nice, but, yeah.
Gotta go!
Seriously? We just
started talkin'!
We'll do it
again sometime.
[YUJI] Damn it!
Do somethin', bro!
She's slippin' through
your fingers!
Don't leave me alone
like that again!
[MEG] Yeah, yeah, whatever.
Look, we've have a problem.
Just what we need. At least
tell me I can ditch the dress.
--[YUJI] Not so fast, ladies!
--[NAGISA, GIRLS] Uh?!
[YUJI]
You can't leave! Nah!
Not till you've taken in
my signature dance moves!
[STUDENTS]
Really?
[YUJI]
This is it. I've got 'em!
No girl can resist the
charms of my sweet moves!
[YUJI gasps]
Well, what do we have here?
A regular tough-guy, huh?
Who me? No.
[YAKUZA]
Shut it!
I'm sorry, man!
It was an accident!
[YAKUZA] This jacket's
worth more 'n your life!
Where do you live?
[YUJI] Look, please!
I don't want any trouble...
This could be our chance.
You're gonna pay to have
it cleaned, understand?
You can cut me a check, or I can
take it out of your ass now.
[YUJI] Wait! My dad's good
for the money, I promise!
Just don't beat me up,
I'm beggin' ya!
'Scuse me, Mr. Yakuza?
Yeah?
[YUJI gasps]
[MEG, HAYAMI]
One, two.
Mr. Bouncer, we have
a situation here.
I think this man's had
one too many tequila shots.
Someone's gonna trip
over the poor guy.
Thanks for pointing it out.
Upsy-daisy, leight
weight. There we go.
All right, girls. Go for it!
You take those "signature moves"
back to the dance floor, okay?
You didn't see anything.
[YUJI gasps]
[NAGISA]
If you're anything like me,
you probably feel humiliated.
It is hard being a guy if
you think it's all about
playin' it cool. Don't try
so hard. Just do you.
You really think so?
[NAGISA] Word to the wise for
the whenever we meet again.
The coolest thing anyone
can do is be themselves.
[FUWA]
Mission accomplished!
[KORO-SENSEI]
That was some rather
questionable territory
you had to navigate.
No one got hands-y
with you, I hope?
[TOKA]
Mm-mm.
We held our own.
[NAGISA sighs]
Oh, you changed out of
your dress. That was fast.
[NAGISA]
Not fast enough.
What's bothering you?
[NAGISA] Nothing. I feel so
stupid. I mean, let's face it.
You girls didn't
need me in there.
I didn't contribute anything.
You were comic relief,
dude! That's big!
Delete that immediately!
[KAEDE laughs]
You did a lot, Nagisa.
I know one person who's better
off 'cause you were there.
[WAITER]
Uh...
Not gonna lie. That
dress looked good on you.
Historically, an assassin who
can pull off either gender
is a huge asset in the field.
I don't like where
this is going.
He's right. 'Cept I'm not
so sure I buy you as a dude.
I'd really appreciate it if
we dropped the subject!
We're trying to be stealthy.
Keep your voice down.
[NAGISA]
Right. Yes, sir.
We're in this operation's
final phase.
Talk to me, Ritsu.
[RITSU] Yes, sir. The VIP floor
is just around the corner.
The guests here don't rely
solely on hotel
security, though.
They make it a point
of bringing their own.
[SUGAYA] Man, these
guys look like they eat
rent-a-cops for breakfast.
[OKANO]
I'm demoralized.
[TOKA] You think they're in
league with our target, or what?
I mean, technically they could
anybody's minions, right?
Like it even matters.
Either way, we're gonna have to
take 'em down to get through.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Excellent point, Terasaka.
And to that end, the weapon
you're hiding in your backpack
will more than suffice.
Tch. Great. You have X-ray
vision in this form, too?
[KARASUMA] You'll have to take
both guards down at once
to keep 'em from
calling for backup.
Kinda figured
as much, thanks.
Kimura, help me out.
I'll wait, you get out there
and lead 'em this way.
Dude, are you crazy?
How'm I s'posed to do that?
[TERASAKA]
You figure it out!
I've got a good idea,
if you're not a wuss.
[foot steps]
[MEN grunt]
[MAN A]
Help you, kid?
Oh, wow!
Not a single active
brain cell in sight! Nope!
Just two big dumb walls
of meat wearing clothes!
Somebody really ought to
call animal control. Sheesh.
[MAN A]
Come here!
[MAN B]
Why you runnin'?
[KIMURA]
Guess that did the trick!
Who the hell is
the little piss-ant?
And why's he so fast?
--[TERASAKA] Let's do it!
--[YOSHIDA] Right behind ya!
[TERASAKA grunts]
[MEN screaming]
Hey wait, why stun guns?
Well, I bought 'em to see
if they'd be any good
against the octopus.
But I never thought I'd be
usin' them on actual people.
[MEG]
Those cost a fortune!
How'd you afford
equipment like this?
Uh, I came into some money.
Odd jobs, mostly.
Nothin' special.
[KARASUMA] Hang on.
I've seen these guys before.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Expertly done, Terasaka.
I don't believe
it would be remiss
to rifle through
their pockets, do you?
Huh?
[KORO-SENSEI] A bit of due
diligence and one can find
the most useful of items
on such gentlemen.
[STUDENTS]
Real guns?
[KORO-SENSEI] That's correct
children. Chiba? Hayami?
I think you two should
be the ones to have them.
[BOTH gasp]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Alas, Mr. Karasuma
hasn't yet sufficiently
recovered from his encounter
with Smog to handle a gun.
The reality of our
situation is this:
you two are our best
sharpshooters.
That's kinda out
of left field, sir.
[KORO-SENSEI]
That said.
I'll allow no killing.
That I won't.
Do not underestimate your
skill. In the right hands,
a firearm is all
the more impressive
for not causing injury.
[RYUNOSUKE] I can't
believe this... live ammo.
[HAYAMI] But, even when
we had air guns, we froze.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Shall we proceed, children?
If our experience thus
far is anything to go on,
the enemy's presence here
is relatively modest.
By even the most
conservative estimate,
we've thinned their
ranks by half.
Yeah! That's what I'm sayin'!
Who's he got left?
[RITSU] Okay, team.
Proceed with caution.
The next stage of infiltration
is the VIP-only
emergency staircase.
There's an empty concert
hall on the eighth floor
we'll have to sneak
through to access it.
[GASTRO]
This whole affair
is leaving a bad
taste in my mouth.
Thought I was hired to snuff
out some kind of "super being".
How'd I get roped into
playing cat-and-mouse
with a gaggle of
pimply-faced twerps?
Disgusting. Oh, well.
I have just the thing
to wash that taste out.
Huh?!