[NAGISA]
How 'bout that play, huh?
Talk about fun!
Sugino gave the
performance of a lifetime.
[KIRARA]
Didn't know you had it in you
to make such an evil face.
The whole time all
I could think about
was how it must've
looked to Kanzaki.
I was hideous.
She probably hates me now...
That's not true, silly!
I... actually thought it was
cool you could be so believable
--in the role.
--[SUGINO] Seriously?
Wow! Maybe I oughtta retire from
baseball and pursue acting!
[KORO-SENSEI] No need
to pick one or the other,
pitchers need to act.
Ah, what a pleasure
to see unexpected talent
on full display!
[NAGISA]
Aw, man.
That's gonna be
a pain to clean up.
[KAEDE] Yeah, I was cleaning
up and my hand slipped.
Sorry.
These are the beads we used
for the river in our play.
I got 'em on loan from
a prop supply store.
No worries.
We'll tackle it together.
Thanks, Nagisa!
I didn't wanna get in
the way of everybody's
assassination plans,
so, y'know...
[KORO-SENSEI]
Ah-ha.
I was wondering where the pair
of you suddenly disappeared to.
[KAEDE chuckles]
[KORO-SENSEI] I'm glad to be
of assistance if needed.
Oh. That'd be wonderful, sir!
[KORO-SENSEI whooping]
[NAGISA]
He's got his back to us.
Defenseless.
Of course, if it
were really that simple,
we wouldn't have had to
work so hard this past year.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Something smells fishy...
Oh, during the school festival,
we used this place
to smoke fish.
[KAEDE]
So many different school events.
Uh-huh. No kidding. Feels weird.
Once this is cleared up,
they'll all be behind us.
Yeah. Lot of
memories though, huh?
Makes me think of the first time
Koro-sensei showed up here.
[KORO-SENSEI giggles]
You children were
complete amateurs back then.
I know--I couldn't get
anywhere near you.
Neither could Sugino.
[KAEDE]
Remember how when Karma came,
he grilled you about
Koro-sensei and even then,
nothing he tried worked?
[NAGISA]
Or how jealous I was of Itona?
I was so sure he was
gonna get him first.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Whoa-ho!
Another of Okajima's hidey
holes, apparently.
[KAEDE]
This class let me do so much.
Stuff I'd have never
done on my own.
Not to be ungrateful,
but this is kinda sad.
First of all, I can't even swim.
When my mind's fixed on
something, I just keep rolling.
I guess.
That's what it is
to be an assassin.
Not even your close friends
get to see your true blade.
[KAEDE]
I'll get you.
It's only a matter of time.
[KAEDE]
As for my true blade...
...I have more than one.
Didn't you notice?
[STUDENTS gasping]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Whoa! A pitfall!
Oh, Koro-sensei.
How I love you!
Please die...
Kayano... You...
[KAEDE]
I watched closely.
Saw different assassins
try and fail.
But the one thing they used
that seemed most effective...
...was a simple pitfall.
[KORO-SENSEI grunting]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Oh no! An anti-me pool!
I have to get above ground
quickly before it's too late!
[KAEDE]
Pretty good, right?!
I know exactly how
your tentacles move.
After all, I studied you
for over a year.
From the best seat in the house!
[KORO-SENSEI groans, grunts]
One more oughta do it!
[gasps]
[KORO-SENSEI growls]
[KAEDE gasps]
[panting]
[NAGISA]
Koro-sensei, are you all right?
What in the world?
What just happened?
Are those what I think?
[MEG] Since when does
Kayano have tentacles?
Aw, dammit.
And I attacked you
with everything I had.
You're slipperier
than I thought.
Clearly.
[KORO-SENSEI grunts] Kaede!
What is the meaning of this?!
[KAEDE]
Oh, yeah. Sorry.
FYI: My real name's not Kaede.
I'm Aguri Yukimura's
little sister.
[KORO-SENSEI gasps]
[KAEDE]
You get it now, don't you?
Murderer.
Wait, Yukimura?
[gasps]
[NAGISA] When the girl
we all thought we knew
suddenly dropped the act,
her face looked cruel--
like it belonged
to someone else.
[KAEDE]
Oh well.
No point cryin' over spilt milk.
I'll just have to reset.
Let's give it another whirl
tomorrow, Koro-sensei.
Don't worry:
I'll tell you where.
[KORO-SENSEI whimpers]
[KAEDE] Now that we've
fought tentacle-to-tentacle...
...I'm feelin' pretty
good about this.
Like I can kill you.
It's unthinkable.
If she grew those tentacles
without a maintenance regimen,
the pain would've been
beyond hellish.
There's no way she could've
powered through it--
not with a straight face.
Yeah, whatever.
I'm stuck on her being
Yukimura's little sister!
She, uh, used to be our
homeroom teacher, right?
Oh, man. Unbelievable.
I thought I recognized
Kayano from somewhere.
Seeing her with her hair down
and that evil look on her face
jogged my memory.
Do you remember Haruna Mase?
The acting prodigy who could
disappear into any role
they threw at her?
She turned her back on
the business years ago.
She looks and acts
so different now.
I-I didn't even make
the connection!
[NAGISA]
Which one is real?
The girl or the actor?
[SHIRO] When I first
set foot in the classroom,
I was surprised
to say the least.
Who knew an unexpected
reunion awaited me?
Aguri Yukimura's younger sister,
a.k.a. Akari Yukimura,
ingratiated into the enemy camp
under a false name.
I realized who she was
and investigated.
As suspected,
she was hiding tentacles.
Not only did she understand
how they worked
and how to use them,
she gleaned the knowledge
in a remarkably short time.
As tenacious
as she is intelligent.
Able to maintain the facade
under unimaginable pain.
Simply put, her mental fortitude
cannot be overstated.
Nor can her considerable
acting prowess.
Day after day, no one could
guess her murderous intent.
She has a gift
for assassination.
And in E Class,
that means something.
[KAEDE]
I was on my way to see her.
We had a lot
of catching up to do.
[KAEDE] The talent agency
had put my career on hold.
People stopped noticing
me on the street.
Where's this freedom
been all my life?
I'm almost tempted
to apply for a day job!
[KAEDE whimpers]
What just happened...?
[KAEDE] I was small, so I could
crawl through the rubble easily.
If I'd have known
what was waiting for me...
[KAEDE gasps]
[KAEDE]
Aguri...
Big Sis!
Oh, God, talk to me!
Wake up! Aguri, please!
[KAEDE sobs]
[KAEDE whimpers softly]
[KAEDE]
That's when I saw them.
On the ground next to her.
Vials of tentacle seed.
I don't know why I felt
the need to take one with me.
I guess... some part of me
understood if I was going to
avenge my sister's death,
the stuff in that vial
would be necessary.
"The Weaponized
Tentacle Prototype
is compatible with
human physiology.
Provided a strict
regimen is adhered to,
otherwise, the pain
is excruciating."
[KAEDE]
Nothing to it.
On principle, no different
than being an actor.
When my mind's fixed on
something, I just keep rolling.
[ONO] I believe this is
the first instance
we've seen of someone
passing the entrance exam
out of the blue.
Forgive me.
Kaede Kayano is it?
Yes. Thank you very much, sir.
[KAEDE]
Forged ID papers.
The name of a bit part I'd
played in a made-for-TV movie.
And, presto, I was in.
[KAEDE] Excuse me, but I
understand this school has
a special class for students
with behavioral issues?
[crash]
[KAEDE]
Or is that just a rumor?
[KAEDE] If my instincts were on
point, in Kunigigaoka's E Class.
I'd find the monster
that murdered my sister.
Oh, Akari.
You're so lucky you're cute.
What I wouldn't give to have
taken after mom's side
of the family.
[KAEDE]
You're cute, too!
Please! When it comes to looks,
hair color's all we
have in common.
[KAEDE]
So I dyed it.
Why the monster
wanted to take over
my sister's teaching position,
I had no earthly idea.
But... unless I wanted him
to walk away scot-free...
[KAEDE whimpers]
[KAEDE] ...I had to
stay in character--
play the part to perfection.
Hello. You must be the new girl.
[KAEDE] Mm-hmm! Just
transferred here today!
[KAEDE]
Your hair's really long.
Yeah.... Eventually
I wanna cut it short,
but for now I don't have
much of a say.
[KAEDE] Even if I don't
stand out, I'll be watched.
Let's play around with
the casting a bit.
Someone else can be
the main character.
Kaede needs to blend in
with the scenery.
There you go!
Now we look the same!
Kaede Kayano!
Pleased to meet ya!
[KAEDE]
The tentacles spoke to me,
asked me what I wanted to be.
[KAEDE]
"That's easy," I said,
"an assassin."
I choked back the pain,
hid my burning hatred.
All the while silently
picking my moment.
[KAEDE]
If I die, so what?
Revenge will have been worth it.
[SHIRO]
Just as I thought.
You don't heed instructions.
Did I or did I not
warn you to wait
until my preparations
were complete?
[KAEDE] What makes you
such an authority?
Look at the piss-poor shape
you left Itona in.
[SHIRO] This attitude of yours
may well be an indicator
of metabolic imbalance.
If you continue to ignore the
dangers of untamed tentacles,
it's only a matter--
Mind your own business.
I can kill him
without your help.
Understood?
[SHIRO chuckles]
So mercilessly cold...
And to your own family.
I'll kill you!
You'll die like
the animal you are!
--Give me back my mother now!
--[KARMA] Uh-huh.
--Give her back to me!
--Definitely Kayano.
[MAEHARA]
That's crazy.
It's like she's a split
personality or something.
[SUGINO] That'd explain how
she's been able to keep
her identity a secret.
[NAGISA] Kayano might've
always done her own thing,
but still, we all adored her.
[NAGISA]
Why was she so close to me?
Was I part of her cover?
Did my bloodlust disguise hers?
Now that I think about it,
the whole pudding thing
was just a ruse.
We'd have gotten suspicious
if she hadn't contributed
something to the cause.
[NAGISA] Turns out the harmless,
ditzy Kayno we all thought
we knew isn't even real.
It's all been a performance.
Excuse me, sir.
Why did Kayano, well...
Why did she call you a murderer?
[ISOGAI] Does it have to
do with your past?
[KIMURA] Talk to us,
Koro-sensei, please.
What happened? We trust you.
So just be honest with us.
He's right. We deserve
to know the truth.
Please. It's unacceptable
to stay quiet.
You understand.
Unless you tell us something,
we're done here.
I'm sorry, but that's
just the way it is.
[KORO-SENSEI]
I don't blame you.
Very well, then. It's time
my past came to light.
I'll tell you on one condition:
You hear my
big secret as a class.
Meaning of course,
that we must find Kayano.
[cell phone vibrates]
So you showed up.
Great! Let's end this!
[KORO-SENSEI sighs]
I gave you your name.
Practically makes me
your mother.
What's the old joke?
I brought you into this world,
I can take you out of it?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Listen to me.
It's too dangerous for you
to keep using those tentacles!
They have to be removed;
your life is in jeopardy!
[KAEDE] What are you
babbling about?
They're in peak condition!
You're not gonna break
my composure with a bluff.
Kayano.
I thought we were your friends.
But this whole time,
you were acting?
All the stuff we've done?
What we've been
through as friends?
It's what I do.
I'm an actor. I act.
Watching Nagisa take
that beating from Takaoka.
It took everything
I had not to step in.
When I was kidnapped by thugs,
kicked in the ribs
by the Reaper,
I was pissed enough
to have killed them.
But I maintained.
Never once let the mask slip.
Poor, pitiful Kayano.
The frail little girl
everybody loved.
You did all this
for your big sister?
[KAEDE]
Koro-sensei murdered her.
She never hurt anyone.
All she wanted to do was teach.
How she used to
brag about all of you.
[AGURI] Come on, now.
Put your minds to it!
Apply yourselves and E Class
can open up a world
of possibilities!
You can do it!
That's all fine and good,
Miss Yukimura,
but... we gotta do
something about your shirts.
[gasps] What are you
talking about?!
This style is hot right now!
Kayano, we... We know.
We only had her a
couple of weeks.
It was March of last year.
But that was long enough
to see that she was
a passionate teacher.
Could Koro-sensei
murder someone?
I mean, like, actually
in cold blood?
I just don't see it.
Nothing we know about him
remotely jibes with that!
Yeah! Maybe you're wrong.
Maybe you don't have the whole
story yet! Give him a chance!
C'mon, Kaede you've
been here for a year.
You should know what kind of
person he is by now.
I get it.
We have to deal
with him eventually.
But you can't think
he murdered your sister.
This shouldn't be about revenge.
That's not how this works.
Feel like you're overheating,
but the nape of your neck
is ice cold?
It's a good indication
your metabolism is shot.
Which means those tentacles have
just about taken the wheel.
You fight in that condition,
they'll sap your life force.
Trust me. I have experience.
Worst-case scenario, you die.
Shut up. I don't recall
asking you for a prognosis.
[BOTH gasp]
[KAEDE]
Every weapon comes at a price.
But if it's the least bit
usable, you polish it.
Guess who taught me that,
Koro-sensei?
If my body overheats,
so much the better!
I'll use it to my advantage.
Flaming tentacles can
do a lot of damage!
[KORO-SENSEI]
No! I must insist--
[STUDENTS scream]
See? I'm in the best
shape of my life.
Every cell in my body's
on high alert.
All your weaknesses
are mine to exploit.
Stop it, Kayano!
This is insane!
Even if you win, it's suicide!
If I've learned anything
in this class,
it's that no target is worth
sacrificing yourself for!
Aw, that's so sweet of
you to be concerned.
Still, though.
If you think I care...
...you're wrong.
[KAEDE] When my mind's fixed on
something, I just keep rolling!
[laughs]
[KORO-SENSEI grunting]
[MIMURA]
Holy crap...
[OKAJIMA]
It's like a meteor shower!
[NAGISA] This is the real
Kayano, not the character.
This is the person
behind the mask.
[KAEDE laughs]
Ripped off a chunk!
Look at that,
it's still all wriggly!
She's been in boss-battle mode
for maybe 15 seconds
and already the tentacles have
gotten a foothold on her brain.
[KAEDE laughs] Aw, what's
the matter, Koro-sensei?!
The headaches aren't
an issue anymore!
Wow! This pain's
starting to feel good!
[ITONA] If she's that far gone,
it's too late.
Whether she gets her revenge
on Koro-sensei or not,
another few minutes of this...
...she's dead.
[gasps]
[NAGISA]
Kayano...
Is this...
Is this really how you wanted
the assassination to go?
Come on! It's high
time for you to die!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Kayano...
Kill you! Murderer!
Kill you! Kill you!
Die, die, die, die...!
[KAEDE]
Koro-sensei...
Please...
Save me...