[KUNUDON]
Surprise!
[KIDS]
Tell us, Kunudon!
Hello, boys and girls!
It's Kunudon!
[KIDS]
Hooray!
[KUNUDON]
Did you know
the students with
the highest scores
here at Kunugigaoka Academy get
dibs on the best vacation ever?
[KIDS]
Yay entitlements!
[KUNUDON]
That's right!
Three days at one of the
finest resorts in Okinawa!
[KIDS]
Diplomatic passports!
[KUNUDON]
And the best part?
Not only do students get
to hit the books seaside,
your school pays for
the whole kit n' caboodle!
[KIDS]
Summer debauchery! Yay!
Wait! E Class is
going this year?
F-- that!
[SUGINO]
Wow, this is so cool!
Look at all of 'em!
[NAGISA
Summer vacation.
Three months of sweet freedom
from the confines of
school, or so you'd think.
Uh, remind me again what
we're doing out here.
Oh.
Well, I'm not about to let
the guys in my neighborhood
catch me collecting
insects. Sorry.
At heart, I'm a city boy.
That doesn't mean nature
doesn't fascinate me, though.
Karma showed me this tree
a few weeks ago after school.
Pretty cool, huh?
No offense, but it's weird that
you came along with us, Maehara.
Never would've pegged you
for the entomologist type.
I figured, what the heck?
Okinawa's coming up, we
don't wanna be unprepared.
Think about it, my friend.
What's the one thing
we'll need to most of?
[SUGINO]
I dunno know.
Cold hard cash!
We're gonna be up to our
eyeballs in bikini-clad babes,
and that talon ain't cheap!
Now that little runt there
ain't worth much, but...
...we track down a stag beetle?
Dude! We are talkin'
mucho dinero!
Seriously, have you seen
what they go for online?
Easily enough to score
a four-star dinner
and kick it poolside
under an umbrella
with the hottie of your choice!
I get the feeling
he's not real focused
on what the trip is
supposed to about.
Yeah.
His idea of a good time seems
a little mature for his age.
[HINANO]
It's not gonna work.
Stag beetles are
pretty old news.
[MAEHARA]
Hey!
Hi, guys!
Tryin' to scrape up some
spending money for our getaway?
[SUGINO]
Maybe.
What do you know about
stag beetle trends?
[HINANO]
Well.
They were worth
a ton a few years ago,
but not so much, recently.
Artificial breeding caused
supply to outweigh demand.
Now a dozen aren't worth a third
of what one used to bring in.
Wha? The Great Stag Beetle
Crash was a real thing?
But my buddy said the
insect-to-hot-babe ratio
was one to one.
Your buddy's out
of it, Casanova.
Girls have always been
more expensive than that.
You sure know
a lot about bugs.
Never thought
that'd be your thing.
Oh. Every living
creature's my thing.
I know! Since we're all here,
let's go bug hunting together!
With all four of us looking,
I bet we'll find a whole bunch!
[NAGISA]
Hinano Kurahashi,
poster child for
upbeat and innocent.
She also happens to know
a lot about natural science.
Having her around
might be a big help.
Right!
Not a bad haul,
if I do say so myself.
[SUGINO] That's pretty cool!
Did you set this trap here?
[HINANO] Sure did.
Put it out last night.
Used my own
homemade recipe, too.
And there's more
where that came from.
I set about 20. That works
out to a thousand yen each.
Not too shabby.
[SUGINO] Ahh. Pretty good
racket to have on the side.
I just hope we caught the one
I was looking for specifically.
[OKAJIMA]
Nice trap. For an amateur.
And you call
yourselves assassins.
[SUGINO]
Okajima!
Hey, if you're happy with a
thousand yen, that's your deal.
Just try not to get jealous
when my homemade trap makes
yours truly a billionaire.
[NAGISA]
Billionaire?
I don't mess with chump change.
It's Summer, guys.
We're gonna be on vacation
for cryin' out loud.
You want spending money?
Pretty soon I'll have
enough to buy Okinawa.
Check out my beetle trap.
[KORO-SENSEI buzzing, chuckling]
Oh, yeah. It's what you think.
The best way to bait
Koro-sensei is with porn.
[MAEHARA] Wow. For a guy
who moves at Mach 20,
he sure stops to smell the
roses when it comes to that.
[SUGINO] Look at him.
He's completely riveted.
[MAEHARA]
Anyone else think it's weird
he's dressed like
a stag beetle?
[SUGINO] A giant stag
beetle with tentacles.
Way to blend in.
Every wooded area has
its own secret stash.
Its special repository for smut.
You stumble across it
when you're a kid,
and it's like a
veil's been lifted.
Your eyes are opened
for the first time.
Later, when you've grown up,
you donate your own
collection to the stash.
The circle of life.
This is what it is
to become a man.
And this guy's got a feelin'
today might just be the day
we're all ushered
into adulthood!
[NAGISA] Eh. That doesn't sound
like the circle of life to me.
You'd be so proud of me.
I did a ton of research
into what he likes.
I'm too young to buy the stuff,
but where there's
a will there's a way.
Uh? Wouldn't just about anything
with big boobs do the trick?
Oh man, shows how
little you know!
[OKAJIMA]
Porn's what dreams are made of.
But every dream is different.
Workout magazines.
Manga. The hardcore stuff they
sell in black plastic bags.
Your ideal type awaits!
This is kinda impressive.
You've been swapping out
the magazines in your stash
for over a month to determine
what stuff he likes.
Okay, but why would an
adult need to look through
some underage kid's secret
collection? That's just sad.
Hey. You an' me have a lot
in common, right, Kurahashi?
We both get so
absorbed in our prey
we end up knowing exactly
what makes 'em tick.
[HINANO]
Uh-huh.
I may have a filthy mind.
But its served me well
in pursuit of my goal.
It's because I'm a self-aware,
first-class perv
that I know the
uncomfortable truth.
In the end... pornography
will save the world.
[ALL]
He's so cool somehow!
[OKAJIMA]
Check it out.
Under that glorious
stack of filth
is a net strung with
Anit-Sensei BB's.
And he's so distracted,
he has no clue.
When I give the word,
one of you cut the rope.
I'll jump in and finish him off.
[NAGISA] I suppose
anything can be a sword
if you polish it enough.
Okajima's porn trap could
actually do the trick.
Koro-sensei, prepare
to be run through.
[gasps]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Mm?
[squeals]
[SUGINO]
Um, what's he doing?
[MAEHARA] Why did his
eyes go all "dwee"?
Yeah, I don't have any
data on that face!
What kind of porn
does that signify?
[KORO-SENSEI chuckles]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Thought you could hide from me?
A Miyama stag beetle.
With white eyes.
[gasps]
No! Are you serious?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Ah, hello, Kurahashi!
Impressive specimen, eh?
Wow! I've been looking for
one like this forever!
[KORO-SENSEI
I know, right?
Imagine it being in
our own back yard!
Come on! Another second
and we would've had 'im!
[MAEHARA] I don't get what
they're so excited about,
but a giant stag beetle
and a junior high girl
dancing on top a pile of porn
isn't something you
see every day.
[yelps]
[whimpers]
[KORO-SENSEI yelping]
[KORO-SENSEI]
How unbelievably embarrassing.
I'm mortified beyond belief.
Shame on me.
A molder of young minds ought to
be above this sort of behavior.
I knew there was a trap
under all this porn,
and yet, each magazine
was so much more tempting
than the last, I hadn't the
presence of mind to resist!
[OKAJIMA]
He saw right through me!
So what's the big deal
with this beetle?
It's just a Miyama
stag beetle, right?
Didn't you say that
artificial breeding,
made 'em all pretty
much worthless?
Actually, these go for a lot
on account of being
very hard to breed.
A mid-sized one is worth
its weight in gold.
One as big as this fellah?
We're talkin' a small fortune.
Shut up!
[KORO-SENSEI] Also, observe
the color of its eyes.
Usually, they're black.
These, however,
white as the driven snow.
We've discussed
albinism before, correct?
So I assume you're
familiar with the concept.
[SUGINO]
Yeah.
It's like, when an animal's born
without pigment or whatever.
[KORO-SENSEI]
With stag beetles,
albinism is only
possible with the eyes.
A natural-born Miyama white-eye,
as they're called
in the literature,
is exceptionally rare.
A valuable academic
find, to be sure.
This guy goes for hundreds
of thousands of yen.
[GROUP]
Hundreds?
I told Koro-sensei a while back
I wanted to see
one up close.
He promised to use his zoom-eyes
to find one of them for me.
Okie dokie, boys. Which one of
you rejects wants this baby?
[ALL]
Me!
Ha, you'll have
to catch me first!
[KORO-SENSEI] I beg your pardon!
I've already done my catching!
[NAGISA] Whether in natural
science, assassination, or porn,
Summer Vacation is
a time for discovery.
Let's hope a week
from now in Okinawa,
we can put what we've
discovered to good use.
[NAGISA] Our Assassination
Vacation is soon.
Not a lot of time to
make a foolproof plan.
But saying we've upped the
ante on our training regimen
would be accurate.
[IRINA]
Oh, you adorable brats.
Go ahead, spend Summer
vacation working up a sweat.
I'll be relaxing,
thank you very much.
You need this too,
Professor Bitch.
In fact, I'd say
of everybody here,
you need to level-up the most.
I'm an adult, hon. We're sneaky.
You'll go at him with
your customary verve
and I'll piggyback on all that
hard work to steal the show.
[LOVRO]
Will you now?
Some things can be
counted on never to change.
[IRINA]
Ah!
Lovro, sir!
He's been hired on as a special
instructor for the break.
We need all the
pro tips we can get.
He seemed like
the obvious choice.
[LOVRO]
Relax for even one day,
and your killing
muscles atrophy.
Unless you want to fail,
wear something respectable!
[IRINA screams]
[SUGAYA]
What do you know?
Someone even Miss Bitch
doesn't dare mouth off to.
Can't say I blame her, man.
He's as scary as they come.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Do not thank me yet,
my upright friend.
I am afraid I could not manage
to establish the contacts
you requested.
[KARASUMA] Perhaps your
former students were put off
by word of the
target's difficulty.
[LOVRO]
It is likely.
In any event, we must
rely on what we have.
Now, then. Just to be clear.
The target is not here?
That's correct. He's taken
a sabbatical to Everest.
Not a big fan of the heat.
[LOVRO] If we are to
have any chance at all,
secrecy is of
utmost importance.
This is your plan?
You neutralize the seven
promised tentacles,
and taking advantage
of his reduced speed,
the entire class throws in
and finishes him off. Not bad.
But I wonder if you
would explain to me
this business
of "psych attack"?
[NAGISA] Well, the idea
is to throw him off guard,
and slow him down.
Oh, he likes porn.
Makes no bones about
where he gets it, either.
Figure we'll use that on him.
[KORO-SENSEI] Look, just promise
not to tell your classmates,
all right?
[MAEHARA] He bought our silence
with a round of popsicles,
but it's gonna take
a lot more than that
to keep us from
spilling the beans!
[GROUP] Let's gang up and
teach the perv a lesson
he won't soon forget!
It would really get in his head
if we threatened
to blackmail him.
He'll be so freaked out
by what we've got.
[LOVRO]
These children are brutal.
That said. The key to
assassination is killing blow.
The difference between success
and failure is timing and aim.
Be straight with me.
Are you worried the class
doesn't have what it takes?
No worry. Not at all.
In fact, I am quite
confident in them.
[KARASUMA]
That one's Chiba Ryunosuke.
Excels in spatial calculations.
As a long-range sniper,
I daresay he's second to none.
Then there's Rinka Hayami.
Good balance,
admirable dexterity.
Unparalleled kinetic
visual acuity.
There's no one better for
taking down a moving target.
[LOVRO] You never hear these
two brag about their skills.
They let their results
do the talking.
Yes. I would love to have
them as students of my own.
But if I speak the truth,
I would take any in this class.
I am amazed how well
their talents have grown
in so short a time.
There is potential here.
Much of it.
She has learned
to stabilize her aim.
Some discover they shoot best
from cross-legged position.
Well done.
Wow, thanks!
That means a lot!
You there. Mind how you breathe.
Do not force it. Find shooting
style that best suits you.
[NAGISA] This guy really
knows assassination.
I'm dying to ask him
a question. I wonder...
[NAGISA]
Mr. Lovro, sir?
[LOVRO]
Hm?
Him!
Young man?
I assume you know the best
assassin in the world, right?
But what are they like?
[LOVRO] At a glance,
this boy is not much.
Ha, ha. But on
closer inspection.
What a bizarre question.
Why are you wanting
to know, son?
Uh. It doesn't.
I was just curious.
Ah. Well. In my
considered opinion,
there can be no question
as to who holds the rank
of World's Greatest.
Of course, professional
killers are a secretive lot.
They are rarely known
by their given name.
This one is no exception,
save he prefers to go by
a very particular nickname.
"The Reaper."
Mysterious. Elusive.
Cold as ice.
Trails of dead in his wake.
Death incarnate. An assassin
from whom no target escapes.
It is said if a killer
cannot finish a job,
sooner or later the Reaper
will step in to do it for them.
[NAGISA]
Sounds pretty intimidating.
We'd better kill Koro-sensei
before someone like him appears.
[LOVRO]
Pay attention, young man.
I will teach you a technique
that works without fail.
Works without fail?
[LOVRO] Indeed. A useful
move for all occasions.
A gift from an old pro.
[NAGISA] And just like that, our
Summer island getaway kicks off.
I think we're ready.
[KORO-SENSEI groaning]
[KORO-SENSEI] A boat. Why do
we have to be on a boat?
Couldn't we have taken a plane?
Ugh. My head feels like
a washing machine.
Oh! I can see the
island from here!
Take a look! We're almost there!
Six whole hours from Tokyo.
The perfect setting to for
an all-out assassination.
[STUDENTS]
Okinawa!
[STAFF MEMBER] On behalf of the
Fukuma Resort Hotel, welcome.
We hope your stay
is a pleasant one.
Tropical juice, compliments
of the house. Enjoy.
We are livin' the high life!
You ain't jokin', man.
Everything's so island-y!
[KORO-SENSEI] A hotel right
on the beach. Outstanding.
And a smorgasbord of
structured leisure activities.
We're be savin' the
you-know-what till after we eat.
Right now I vote we have
some fun island style.
Why don't we all
split up into groups
like we did on the
school trip to Kyoto?
[KORO-SENSEI chuckles]
[KORO-SENSEI] A grand idea.
Play hard, kill hard.
This is how top-notch assassins
get the most outta
their Summer Vacation!
[INSTRUCTOR A]
Uh...
That hang glider seems
to be goin' kinda fast.
[INSTRUCTOR B]
What the--?
Did that crazy bastard just
pull a ninety-degree turn
comin' out of a barrel roll?
[KORO-SENSEI imitates a plane]
Aw, c'mon! This isn't fair!
How can we keep up with
you goin' all daredevil?
Calculating current speed.
Target moving a hundred fifty
kilometers per hour.
[KORO-SENSEI chuckling]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Remember boys and girls:
a fighter jet is only
as good as its engine!
[MAEHARA] Who the hell are you
supposed to be dressed as?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Jiro Horikoshi.
[ISOGAI]
Ha, ha. Very funny.
Whoa, whoa! Jiro who?
[ISOGAI] Horikoshi was
an aerospace engineer.
[MAEHARA] Oh, yeah.
I'm just gonna know that!
Group one's doing all right
with keeping him distracted.
You have to respect
anyone ballsy enough
to take shots at
a guy in mid-flight.
Good luck not drawing
unwanted attention, though.
[MAEHARA]
[NAGISA]
No kidding.
Okay, people! We're up
next! It's go time!
Everybody do what they need to
so we can go change!
[SUGINO]
On it!
[NAGISA] The idea is to make
it look like we're having fun,
even though we're working.
What looks like snorkeling
is actually recon.
We need to find
the perfect spot.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Ho-ha!
[KANZAKI]
That's a new look for you
What's that face mean?
[KORO-SENSEI]
It means only the front portion
of the hang glider
was shielding me,
and I neglected to use
enough sunscreen.
Now, then.
Did Group Four have dolphin
watching on the itinerary?
[OKUDA]
Yeah.
It's on a boat,
though. That okay?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Fin-tastic!
[NAGISA]
So far, so good.
Each group takes turns
keeping Koro-sensei busy
while the others set
their plans in motion.
Where is he right now?
[HAYAMI] Group three has
him touring deep sea caves
on the other side of
the island. He can't see us.
We should be good to go.
Oughta give us more
than enough time
to scout out a decent
sniper spot.
I suggest we be quick
about it all the same.
[SUGAYA]
Smooth operators, those two.
[TAKEBAYASHI]
If I didn't know better,
I'd think they've
done this before.
[IRINA]
Really? Aw, damn it!
For the love of all
that's holy, it's a beach!
Where'd all the hot guys go?
[KARASUMA]
Last of the guests
skipped out about
15 minutes ago.
I'm afraid this whole
site's been reserved
for E Class shenanigans only.
They get an entire
beach to themselves?!
I didn't squeeze
into this outfit
to get ogled by the busboy!
[KARASUMA]
This is their most ambitious
assassination plot yet.
Hard to believe
it's going so well.
Would it kill you
to ditch work-mode?
Come on, there's a gorgeous
babe right in front of you.
[KARASUMA] There's only one
thing left to worry about.
[IRINA gasps]
Oh, hey. Look at you,
taking charge.
This settings really brings
out those primal urges--
You asshole!
[KARASUMA] Hey. I have
a question for you.
[IRINA]
Huh?
You've had more than your share
of field experience, right?
How often does an assassination
plan work perfectly?
[IRINA]
It's pretty rare.
If you're asking for my
professional opinion,
let me just tell you,
what these kids have in mind
is far too complicated
not to go tits up
somewhere down the line.
All in all, it's not a bad plan.
I'll give 'em that much.
Hell, I'm not just here
to work on my tan, am I?
I'm gunnin' for my
share of the spoils.
When things go south,
and they will, I'll be there.
Waiting to take the kill shot.
[KARASUMA] However this goes
down, I just want it to work.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Whew! What fun, eh?
Sun, surf, sand, and more sun.
[STUDENTS]
What's with the tan?
How is it, even your
teeth have a tan?
So much for being able
to gauge your expression.
Have fun while you can, sir,
'cause after dinner, it's on!
[KORO-SENSEI] Ah, yes!
The shipboard restaurant!
I'm famished!
[MURAMATSU] Huh. You'd think
he'd be worn out by now.
[TERASAKA]
I'm worn out.
How much longer
we gotta do this?
Can't we just kill him already?
Nah. Be patient.
We'll knock him tonight, then
throw in for some real R and R.
So epic!
Everything's set up.
There's no way we don't
have this in the bag.
[ISOGAI]
Neat, huh?
We rented out the whole
restaurant just for us.
We can enjoy the ocean air
and eat our dinner in private.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Can we indeed?
Somehow I get the
sneaking suspicion
you're trying to get me seasick.
That's a fair assumption.
Weakening the target
is Assassination 101.
[KORO-SENSEI chuckles]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Well played, my boy.
But is your gambit as
infallible as all that?
Seasick or not, a target
expecting an attempt on his life
isn't likely to take
it sitting down.
[NAKAMURA, MEG]
You look like a bowling ball!
[KORO-SENSEI]
It's the sunburn, isn't it?
Forget your expression.
We can't even tell the
front from the back.
Can you do something about it?
It's freaking me out.
[KORO-SENSEI chuckles]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Oh, of course! I can do plenty.
Have you children forgotten
perhaps my quirkiest quirk?
I can molt!
There we go. All better.
Um, can't you only do
that once a month?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Or, strictly speaking,
whenever the
occasion warrants.
But I rely on it sparingly,
as the energy consumed--
[KORO-SENSEI]
Heh...
[KORO-SENSEI screams]
[SUGAYA]
Seriously?
Of all the times to put himself
at a disadvantage, he picks now?
[MEG]
Sorta makes you wonder
why we haven't been
able to kill him before.
[NAGISA]
This is it.
We've been training all
summer long for this moment.
No mistakes.
Everything's in place.
This time we hit our mark.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Absolute heaven!
[KORO-SENSEI groaning]
Hope you got the
most out of dinner.
It may turn out
to have been last.
Get a load of the
spot we picked out.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Heh?
[SUGAYA] It's a floating chapel.
Nice and far from the hotel.
C'mon. It's all right.
Have a seat and relax.
Might as well. There's
nowhere for you to run, now.
This'll be fun.
Whaddya say we start things off
with a little pre-show flick?
[KORO-SENSEI]
I daresay,
things are about to get more
than a wee bit interesting.
That's right: let me see that
inventive spirit shine through!
Show your teacher a classroom
of true assassins!