[NAGISA] You monster. I'll
kill you for what you've done!
[TAKAOKA laughs]
That's the spirit, boy!
Show me your kill face! Come at
me with everything you've got!
[MEG]
It's happened. Nagisa snapped.
All right, let's be honest
here for a second.
Sure, we all wanna kill him.
But, Nagisa might do it.
Can't say I saw it comin'.
[KORO-SENSEI]
No. Someone has to stop this!
[TERASAKA grunts]
[NAGISA groaning]
[TERASAKA panting]
[TERASAKA]
Get over yourself, dumbass!
Yeah, don't think I missed
the look you gave me
when he blew up the antidote!
Screw your pity!
Quit wastin' your energy
worryin' about what's goin' on
with other people
and focus on you!
Look, the virus is
a lie! I'll be fine!
He's playin' you for an idiot!
What are you saying?
Are you sick?
[TERASAKA]
Murder is murder!
Even with a piece of shit like
this evil son of a bitch.
He's not worth it!
Give in to the bloodlust and
you're no better than him!
[KORO-SENSEI]
He's absolutely right, Nagisa.
Listen to him. Killing this
man won't solve anything.
Blind rage
is not a moral guide!
In any event, he's likely
bluffing about the antidote.
We need only consult
the poisoner downstairs.
Do not stoop to Takaoka's level.
Simply render him unconscious.
Shut your damn mouth.
You're takin' all the
fun out of everything!
If we're gonna get
the most out of this,
he's gotta come at me with
intent to kill!
Part of the process
is bloodlust unbound!
He has to feel it or I can't
properly humiliate him!
How the hell else am I gonna
patch-up my self-esteem?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Nagisa, please.
Take up Terasaka's stun gun.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Heed the words of a friend
before you give
credence to an enemy.
Resist the anger.
Weigh your options.
Ask what within myself does
this many have claim on?
[YOSHIDA]
Terasaka! What the...?
You're as hot as a
combustion engine!
Dude, how'd you make
it so far like this?
[TERASAKA] Who cares? Don't
look at me. Look at them.
The octopus is half
right.
You ain't gotta resist the
anger. You control it.
[NAGISA]
Uh!
[TAKAOKA growls]
[TERASAKA grunts]
[TAKAOKA] Ooh! Oh, ho!
Don't we look vicious!
Question, sir?
Why did Nagisa put
the stun gun away?
[KORO-SENSEI whimpers]
[TAKAOKA] So you're opting for
the knife. Good on you, kid!
I knew you'd see the light. Do
you wanna know a little secret?
I didn't blow up every
vial of the antidote.
Now, either you come at me
and your pals keep a
respectful distance,
or what's left of their chance
at survival goes bye-bye.
Everyone infected will die.
Hear that, Karasuma?
It's just me and the boy!
[KARASUMA growls]
This stuff takes a month to cook
up under ideal conditions.
Now sure, there's not
enough for everyone.
But saving some's better
than saving none.
[OKANO gasps]
[KORO-SENSEI] Mr. Karasuma. I
hate to ask this of you, but...
If at any moment you believe
Nagisa's life to be in jeopardy,
please do not hesitate
to shoot Takaoka.
[KARASUMA]
He usually has a sixth sense
about where things are headed.
So for him to ask me that,
we're in trouble.
Deep trouble.
[KARASUMA]
Of course we are.
Even I can see the
writing on the wall.
We got the better of
three professional
freelance assassins
on our own terms.
But this is different. Here,
we're playing by his rules.
Nagisa has absolutely no idea
the world of hurt he's in for.
[TAKAOKA grunts]
[NAGISA groans]
[TAKAOKA]
Ha! That all you've got?
Where's that homicidal rage
now you're on your ass,
you little snot rag?
[KARASUMA]
Takaoka is a man possessed.
He's in battle mode.
Years of elite military training
cut through the insanity.
No attack is going to slip
through his defenses.
[NAGISA groaning]
[KAEDE whimpers]
[KARASUMA] His physique.
His skills. His experience.
[TAKAOKA chuckles]
[NAGISA groans]
[KARASUMA] This isn't like
scoring high on the finals.
This is life or death.
Ugh. So not a fair match.
Yeah, no kidding, right?
He doesn't have a prayer!
[TAKAOKA]
Aw. Hey now, don't peter out.
We're just getting started.
[TAKAOKA]
That's right.
We haven't yet incorporated
this old girl into the mix.
[TAKAOKA] This knife comes to
me in my dreams every night.
Hand in hand with that smile.
The precise moment my peace
of mind flew off the rails.
Well, tonight I won't give
that smug little pipsqueak
the satisfaction!
I'll split you from groin to
grin and savor the screams.
I'll sever your hands and feet
and mount them above my
mantle like trophies!
Shoot him, Mr. K!
Please! Nagisa will die!
That man means every
word of what he says!
[TERASAKA]
Stop. Let Nagisa handle it.
Dude. Do you see
the shape he's in?
At least if I was
in there Takaoka
wouldn't have it so easy.
You think so?
Shows what you know.
If you didn't ditch training
so much you'd have a clue.
This fight ain't over
yet, pal. Just watch.
He's about to pull
out the big guns.
This technique.
It never fails?
Don't be fooled.
It only looks easy.
Therein lies the beauty.
I've used it many
a time in field.
Nothing compares for
getting out of pinch.
The technique only works under
certain conditions, however.
Three criteria must be met.
First, have at least
two weapons ready-hand.
[TAKAOKA gasps]
[LOVRO] Second, you must be
pitted against an expert.
Third, and most important,
your opponent must already know
what it means to face death.
[NAGISA] Excellent.
We're three for three.
[TAKAOKA grunts]
What the...?
[NAGISA]
Congratulations, Mr. Takaoka.
You get to be my beta test.
[TAKAOKA]
What is he doing?
[LOVRO] You must understand
the nature of this move.
It's something of
a paradox, you see.
Conditions aren't
often favorable.
And while I call it an
"insta-kill" technique,
in all honesty that
is a misnomer.
Employing it doesn't mean your
opponent will die instantly.
Particularly when their
defenses are impregnable.
That said, if you find yourself
painted into a corner,
and at some point you will,
do this correctly and it sets
the stage for an instant kill.
That sounds pretty
useful. How's it work?
[LOVRO] From a standstill
position, move quickly.
As far as you can,
as loudly as you can.
Come on! Do it!
[NAGISA] Careful. Time it just
after dropping the knife.
The closer I get, the more
focused he'll be on the blade.
Drop my weapon, and his
attention follows it.
Both caught in midair for
just a fraction of a second.
[TAKAOKA groans, screams]
[TAKAOKA groaning]
What the hell was that?
[NAGISA]
There it is!
An assassin slips
through the cracks.
And in that tiny moment, out
comes the crucial second blade.
[TAKAOKA groaning]
[TAKAOKA]
No! This isn't happening!
The runt... got me... again!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Whoa.
[ISOGAI, MEG gasp]
[SUGAYA, HAYAMI gasp]
[KAEDE, KARASUMA gasp]
[KARMA gasps]
[NAGISA panting]
Way to go. That's how it's done.
One good jolt and he'll
be out like a light bulb.
Taze the psychotic rat-bastard.
[TAKAOKA whimpering]
[NAGISA]
This man taught me bloodlust.
Taught me that sometimes
anger is good, sometimes not.
He taught me the importance
of having friends
to pull you out
of your own head.
I know what it's
like to be hit.
To be in a real fight.
All because of this man.
He's done some awful things.
There's no denying that.
But in a weird way,
he does deserve my respect.
[TAKAOKA whimpers]
[NAGISA]
He's a teacher.
[TAKAOKA]
Please. No.
[NAGISA] I've learned something
about myself in all this.
[TAKAOKA]
Whatever you're about to do,
don't do it with that look
on your face! Oh, god!
I'll be haunted by that smile
till the day they put
me in the ground!
Mr. Takaoka. Thank you,
for everything.
[TAKAOKA gasping]
[KARASUMA whimpers]
[MEG, FUWA, TOKA sigh]
[ALL gasping]
Yeah!
We beat the final boss!
[STUDENTS laugh, cheer]
[TERASAKA chuckles]
[KARMA]
Nice work.
[NAGISA gasps]
[ISOGAI]
Are you okay, Nagisa?
[NAGISA]
Sure.
[KORO-SENSEI] Well done,
Nagisa. I'm proud of you.
For the first time in a while I
had no idea how this would end.
Thanks. But what are
we going to do now?
Everybody else is still
infected with the virus.
The antidote Takaoka didn't
blow up isn't enough.
[STUDENTS sigh]
We'll figure something
out, but first.
Let's get out off this roof.
Wait here for the chopper.
I'll go collect Smog.
[GASTRO] Ha! Please. The
antidote won't do you any good.
Look at you brats.
You really figured
on getting out
of this situation
with your lives!
[KARASUMA] The man who hired
you has been defeated.
Let it go. You've no longer
have a dog in this fight.
[GASTRO]
Heh.
I'm almost fully
recovered from the gas.
And these kids are
strong. Believe me.
I suggest we be
reasonable and stop this
before anyone else gets hurts.
[GASTRO]
Yeah. All right.
I'll make you wish
you hadn't... Wait.
Come again?
No worries. You don't
have to bother with us.
Our contracts don't cover
avenging our employer.
Anyway, as I was saying.
The antidote would
only be useful to you
if you'd actually been poisoned.
[TERASAKA, YOSHIDA]
Huh?
Well, technically you
were, but not that bad.
You know that bug you can get
eating oysters on
the half-shell?
I gave you a perfected version
of that ol' warhorse.
It ought to flush out
of your systems
in about 30 hours or so.
Unpleasant, but not fatal.
Now, this sucker is what
our boss wanted us to use.
[STUDENTS sigh]
[SMOG] If I actually had, heh,
different story altogether.
After we got the job, the
three of us talked it over,
hatched a plan.
The boss's idea, you know it,
seemed too harsh.
We figured the handoff
would play out just as well
if you only thought
you were in danger.
[SMOG]
And a bout a food poisoning
certainly makes you feel like
death warmed over, so win-win.
Since when does a hired
killer have scruples?
Isn't going against your client
bad for the bottom line?
[GASTRO]
Sweetheart.
We take pride in what we do, but
money isn't the end-all be-all.
A client's needs are always
considered carefully,
and we do aim to please.
We blow the antidote up.
Right in front of their shocked,
bedraggled little faces!
How sweet the moment will
be when all hope is lost!
[GASTRO] But when we
realized he never intended
on giving you the antidote.
It was either we try to live
with ourselves after having
offed a bunch of innocent
junior high school kids.
Or we take out a hit
on our reputation.
Seemed like a fairly
straightforward,
ethical decision to us.
And there's always a way to
bounce back if you're clever.
So, guess this job was a wash.
But at least none of
you are going to die
because we don't
having scruples.
Here, give that supplement
to your buddies.
And make sure they
get plenty of rest.
They'll probably wind up
feeling better than they did
before this all started.
[KARASUMA]
Thank you, gentlemen.
But I'll believe it after
I've seen those kids
make a full recovery.
In the meantime,
I'm afraid it's protocol to
detain you for questioning.
Uh. Yeah, okay.
If you wouldn't mind
making it quick
so we can move on the
next job, that'd be great.
--[KARMA] You disappoint me.
--[GRIP] Mm?
I thought you'd at least
want a grudge match
between the two of us.
You're a samurai. Isn't your
honor threatened by hot-sauce?
Part of the samurai code is not
to kill people out of spite.
I'm content to wait for
the day someone puts a price
on your head, Hun. Because
it'll happen. Guarantee it.
Let this be a lesson to you.
You wanna rematch?
Make it to the big-time.
Become a worthy target!
[STUDENTS gasp]
Then we'll come back
and give you all the
assassination grand tour!
[NAGISA] And just like
that, they're gone.
Not sure if what
they left us with
was a warning or a compliment.
--[buzz]
--[IRINA] Oh!
A single buzz from Karasuma.
That's the signal
they've made it out.
Boys. I have the sudden urge
to walk naked by the ocean.
Would one of you be kind
enough to drive me to a beach?
[MEN chattering]
[NAGISA]
That's it.
Our big infiltration
mission is over.
And no one, not the other
guests, not the staff,
suspects a thing.
Hey, Terasaka?
[TERASAKA]
Hm?
I owe you big time.
I was on the verge
of a bad choice.
So thanks for yelling at me.
[TERASAKA] Heh. It's hard
enough to kill the octopus
without one of us being
taken out of the equation.
[KARMA chuckles]
[NAGISA]
Yeah. Guess so.
So now, we go back
to our hotel.
Tell the others
they're gonna be fine.
Then we put this whole day
behind us and catch up
on our sleep because, seriously.
I am friggin' exhausted.
Oh, man. That was
one crazy day, huh?
I'm just glad we
got through it okay.
And I'm just glad you knew
how to handle yourself!
Uh! Me, too.
You're such a trouble
magnet, Nagisa.
You know we worry about you.
[NAGISA laughs]
Morning! Well, evening really.
So, how're you guys feeling?
Great. Thanks!
School jerseys.
Heh. You too, huh?
We're the only ones
on the resort now.
Might as well be comfy.
Designing a new outfit
for one just one scene
is too much of a pain anyway.
Who are you talking to?
[FUWA] So is Koro-Sensei
really in there?
[NAGISA]
It won't work,
but at least he's under strict
supervision till he reverts back
to normal. Then back
to the drawing board.
Mr. Karasuma's been
orchestrating the whole thing.
[KIMURA]
I swear, does Mr. K ever sleep?
[SUGINO]
He's awesome! What's his secret?
'Cause if I can be like that ten
years from now, I'll be set.
[SUGAYA]
Somethin' to shoot for.
[MEG] Hey, Professor Bitch
is pretty awesome, too,
if you look hard enough.
[ISOGAI] Same thing with
the assassins at the hotel.
I mean, you've gotta admire
the discipline it takes
to be that highly skilled.
And the philosophy. Not to
mention the work ethic.
[SUGAYA]
True that. Personally,
as long as I don't grow up to
be like Takaoka, I'll be happy.
[ISOGAI] In a way I suppose
that's what growing up is.
Knowing who to look up
to and who to ignore.
Sometimes the difference
is night and day.
Sometimes, not so much.
--[explosion]
--[gasps]
[STUDENTS gap]
[MAEHARA]
Koro-Sensei exploded!
[SUGINO]
Did we get him?
[NAGISA]
Right.
As if we don't already know
the answer to that question.
[KORO-SENSEI laughs]
You've suffered in the shadow
of my cowardice, and
I'm sorry. But consider!
Not only have you faced
an array of fearsome foes,
you did so with
unquestionable style!
Oh, there you are, sir.
Good to have you back.
With all due respect
--we like this form better.
--[HINANO] G'morning!
[KORO-SENSEI] Indeed.
And good morning to you.
Now, what do you say we get
this vacation back on track?
Sure!
[SUGINO] Yeah, I think it's
a little late for that.
We go back tomorrow morning.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Are you kidding me?
But... but... there's so much
fun in the sun to be had
now that I'm fully mobile again!
[SUGINO]
Naturally.
[KORO-SENSEI] There's not a
second to waste, children!
Summer Vacation with
your Koro-Sensei
is a once-in-a-lifetime
experience!
We must milk it
for all it's worth!
What are you doing, Karma?
Takin' your advice, Teach.
Gotta strike when
the iron's hot.
[KORO-SENSEI laughs]
Well played, my boy.
Wait for the target to
let his guar-- [yelps]
Now it's Summer Vacation!
[KARMA] No time like
the preseny, right?
Whaddya say, Nagisa? Feel
like emptyin' a few rounds?
[NAGISA laughs sheepishly]
Well then, girls.
Who would we be if we didn't
make the most of things?
Yay! Let's have fun!
[GIRLS chattering]
Y'know. I'm finally
feeling up to a little dip.
Was that under
your uniform?
No one told me!
Splash attack!
[GIRLS chattering, laughing]
[NAKAMURA]
You can run, but you can't hide!
[KORO-SENSEI] Yay! Splash
attack! Me, too! Me, too!
[HINANO]
Okay!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Actually, never mind!
Terrible idea! Thank you, no!
--Aw.
--Well there goes that.
[OKAJIMA] Yes! This is
what I'm talkin' about!
This is how it should be!
Here I come, ladies! Geronimo!
--[GIRLS] Pervert!
--[NAKAMURA] Oh, shrinkage.
[KORO-SENSEI] Don't forget:
there's a fireworks display
after this! We don't
want to miss it!
We have to keep
to the itinerary!
'Course that didn't work.
Is that it, sir?
Should we pack in our demolition
equipment and head out?
Yeah. Might as well.
[IRINA]
So, that's how it is, huh?
You're all suddenly
too good to include me
on your day at the beach?
A girl's got feelings, you know!
I thought we were friends!
Is that a bikini?
Or a cry for help?
Ugh! Shut your pie-holes!
Hey let's ditch the
brats, yeah? Just us?
I saw this adorable
little spot up the way
--that's nice and private--
--I'd rather not.
Just when we start thinkin'
you're not a bitch.
Don't even go there! Ah!
You want bitch? I'll show bitch!
I've had it up to here
with you arrogant little
pain-in-the-asses!
Oh, where you goin'?
You runnin' away...!
[KORO-SENSEI]
You've done well, my boy.
[NAGISA] Kunugigaoka
Junior High, class Three-E.
Yep, we're assassins.
And our target?
Our teacher.
[KORO-SENSEI laughs]
All right, people.
Let's get started, shall we?
If you thought the
first term was a doozy,
wait till you see what I've got
in store this time around!
[NAGISA] That's the way it goes
in our assassination classroom.
The bell rings,
another day begins.