[KORO-SENSEI]
Okie-dokie, boys and girls.
Time for homeroom.
Everyone take your seats.
[STUDENTS groan]
[NAGISA]
Wow. Alright.
[RITSU]
Koro-sensei.
Could you please explain
why your head
is suddenly 33 percent
larger than before?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Ah. Well, you see,
it soaks up
moisture like a sponge.
With all the humidity.
[OKAJIMA]
That's seriously kind of gross.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Now, then.
According to Mr. Karasuma,
we have another
transfer student joining us.
[MAEHARA]
Great.
Ten to one it's gonna
be another assassin.
[KORO-SENSEI] I made a
bit more trouble for myself
than I'd bargained for
underestimating Ritsu.
So rest assured, I won't be
making the same mistake twice.
[RITSU giggles]
[KORO-SENSEI] But I
encourage all of you to see
the new addition to our class
as one more potential ally.
Hey. Heard anything?
I mean, since you're both new.
Figure you transfers gotta
stick together, right?
Actually, I do know
a little bit.
The original plan was for he
and I to start at the same time,
but it didn't work out that way.
I would handle
long-range attacks,
he would focus on close-range.
Our combined efforts were to
back Koro-sensei into a corner.
Except, our masters recalled
the order for, well, reasons.
Yeah? And those were?
[RITSU]
For one, my counterpart needed
a few tweaks before
being put into the field.
Second, it was deemed
I lacked the capacity
to support someone of his skill.
Compared to what
he's capable of, well...
Let's just say that I
don't quite measure up.
[KORO-SENSEI whimpers]
[NAGISA]
For her to say that,
when she blew off
Koro-sensei's fingers. Whoa.
What kind of beast
must this new guy be?
[door opens]
[STUDENTS gasp]
[ALL whimper]
[MEG]
Okay.
Somebody likes to wear white.
[OKANO]
He, uhs, kinda tall for a kid.
[ALL gasp]
[SHIRO chuckles]
[SHIRO]
Sorry, everyone.
Didn't meant to startle you.
I can see that you're confused.
I'm not your new classmate,
just his guardian.
But let's not stand on ceremony.
Call me Shiro, please.
I don't know what's creepier,
a guy in all white,
or a guy in all
white doing magic.
Yeah.
That entrance even
freaked out Koro-sen--
[MIMURA]
Oh, come on! Give us a break!
[OKAJIMA] That really scared you
enough to use the liquefy trick?
[KORO-SENSEI whimpers]
[KORO-SENSEI ]My imagination
just ran a little wild
after Ritsu's story, that's all.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Shiro.
When might we get to
greet your, uh, ward?
[SHIRO]
It's an honor, Koro-sensei.
Apologies for my "ward," as you
call him, being late for class.
I beg your patience,
he'll be here in due course.
When the time is right.
[NAGISA]
Uh.
[NAGISA] Not much for
straight answers, is he?
Huh?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Something wrong?
[SHIRO]
Not at all.
This seems an interesting group.
I'm confident he'll
fit in perfectly.
[SHIRO]
Allow me to introduce him.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[SHIRO]
Now, Itona! Come!
[STUDENTS yelp]
Victory is mine.
I have proven myself stronger
than the classroom wall.
[ALL]
Come on! Use the door next time!
Only strength matters.
Everything else is crap.
[TERASAKA]
Awesome.
He's gonna be a douche.
[NAGISA] Even Koro-sensei's
not sure how to react.
[ISOGAI]
Is he smiling or cringing?
[MAEHARA] I don't think
there's a name for that face.
[SHIRO]
I give you Itona Horibe.
Or, if you prefer, just Itona.
[NAGISA]
A guardian in all white.
A transfer student
impossible to read.
Something tells me we're
in for stormy weather.
[KARMA]
Hey, new kid.
Mind if I ask you a question?
You came in from the rain
without an umbrella.
It's coming down
in buckets out there,
and somehow there's
not a drop on you.
What's the story with that?
[STUDENTS gasp]
[KARMA]
Hm?
[ITONA] You're the strongest one
in this class, aren't you?
But you don't have to worry.
You're still weaker than me.
That means you get to live.
[ITONA]
You're beneath my skill.
And I only kill things that
are stronger than me.
[KORO-SENSEI mumbles]
[ITONA]
And in this case, Koro-sensei.
That means you.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Ah.
I believe I'm starting to get
a clearer picture of your MO.
Well, look no further.
I'm stronger than you by
a whole order of magnitude.
Yeah. Sure.
Not so much.
Truth is you an' me
are actually brothers.
[STUDENTS gasping]
[STUDENTS]
Brothers?!
Winner takes all,
loser dies. Big bro.
[KORO-SENSEI whimpers]
We siblings have to keep it
real. No tricks. No bull.
Just the two of us.
[door opens]
After school.
We face off in this classroom.
--[STUDENTS screaming]
--[TOKA] What is going on, sir?
Why did he say
you were brothers?!
[OKAJIMA]
How do an octopus and a person
come from the same mom?!
[KORO-SENSEI]
I have no earthly idea!
The boy is clearly confused!
I was raised an only child!
[KORO-SENSEI] When I asked
my parents for siblings,
they gave me a talking-to
about the birds and the bees!
[MOM-SENSEI] When two
cephalopods love each other...
[MAEHARA]
Wait, you actually had parents?
[SHIRO laughs]
[KARASUMA] Is this Itona
kid telling the truth,
or is his story just
some kind of tactic
to shake up his target?
[SHIRO]
Hm?
I apologize for throwing
you off, Mr. Karasuma.
It was necessary to keep
my ward's existence classified.
Unfortunately,
I'm afraid that meant
you had to be kept in the dark.
Improbable as it
may seem, though,
I can guarantee you
they are, in fact, brothers.
Their little contest
after school this afternoon
will leave no room for doubt.
Ugh. He's wolfin' the junk food
like it's goin' out of style.
He's definitely got
Koro-sensei's sweet tooth.
And both their faces
are equally hard to read.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Wonderful.
Itona's comment has the
whole class comparing us
in every detail.
I need a distraction.
Ah, yes! I'll take
my mind off things
by poring over
this girly magazine!
Nothing like a little
adult reading material.
[SEXY GIRL moans]
--[KORO-SENSEI yelps]
--[MAEHARA] This cinches it!
They're both boob guys!
Okay, the new kid's
credibility just shot the roof!
So. That's really
all it took, huh?
[OKAJIMA]
Hell yeah!
--[NAGISA gulps]
--[SEXY GIRL moans]
[OKAJIMA]
We boob men are all brothers!
[NAGISA]
Now there's three of them?
Here's the thing, if they
really are related. I mean,
don't you think Koro-sensei
would've known about it?
[FUWA]
Hmm... Not necessarily.
[SOLDIERS yelling]
[MALE RETAINER] Your Highness,
the enemy is upon us.
All is lost!
[KING]
So be it.
My sons.
You alone will survive!
[KORO-SENSEI] Hurry,
little brother! We've no time!
Clear the bridge and
escape is assured!
[KORO-SENSEI yelps]
[ITONA]
Brother!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Go! I'm lost!
--Leave me! You have to live!
--[ITONA] No, brother!
[KORO-SENSEI]
You have to live!
[FUWA]
Once grown,
each was driven by cruel
fate to battle the other,
without knowing their
opponent's true identity.
[KAEDE]
Um.
That still doesn't explain
why Itona's human.
[FUWA]
Easy, he's a mutation.
[KAEDE] You've totally glossed
over the core issue here!
[SUMIRE] No offense,
but your characterizations
are kind of cliché. And
the plot's ridiculous.
[FUWA]
Hey! No one asked
---for your criticism.
--[SUMIRE] IF you hadn't noticed
--I'm trying to create! Have...
--we're sorta dealing with...
[KAEDE]
Realism is your friend!
[school bell chimes]
[KORO-SENSEI whimpers]
This place looks like an arena.
Yeah. Fit for an
honest death match.
It's the first time I've seen an
assassin take this approach.
[SHIRO] Surely by now
you're tired of clunky,
overly complicated
attempts on your life,
so let's confine
ourselves to one rule.
Set foot outside
the desk boundary
and your life is forfeit.
Agreed?
Oh yeah, sure, whatever.
As if the loser's gonna stick
to that without any issues.
They will.
Koro-sensei's all about how
his students see him, remember?
He'll abide by the rules
out of a sense of honor.
Cheating would risk throwing
shade on his reputation with us.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Very well, sir.
I agree to your rule.
But let's include another,
injuring any spectators
also counts as a forfeit.
[SHIRO]
Agreed.
Commence on my signal.
Assassination.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[SHIRO]
Begin!
[KORO-SENSEI groans]
--[ALL gasping]
--[NAGISA] For what seemed like
an eternity, our eyes were all
riveted to the same thing.
And, oddly enough, it wasn't
our teacher's amputated limb.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Impossible!
He has...
[STUDENTS gasp]
Itona's hair is made
of... tentacles!
[KARMA]
That's how he stayed dry.
Sneaky bastard didn't need
an umbrella after all.
He just batted
the raindrops off.
[KORO-SENSEI]
How is this possible?
[NAGISA gasps]
[KORO-SENSEI] Tell me where
those tentacles came from.
[KORO-SENSEI] Why does
someone like you have them?
[SHIRO] We're neither at
liberty or obligated to say.
But I hope this serves
to convince you:
You may have come
from different parents,
enjoyed different upbringings,
but nevertheless you
are indeed brothers.
[SHIRO chuckles]
[SHIRO]
What a face you're making.
Does this encounter stir up
unpleasant memories, perhaps?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Clearly.
You and I need to
have a little talk.
[SHIRO]
Not possible.
You'll be dead.
[KORO-SENSEI yelps]
[SHIRO]
This pressure ray
has a very useful effect
at close range.
It triggers the dilatant
properties of your skin cells.
[KORO-SENSEI screams]
[SHIRO] You become stiff
as a board instantaneously.
That's right,
Itona and I are on intimate
terms with your every weakness.
--[KORO-SENSEI groans]
--[STUDENTS gasp]
Whoa! Did he get him?
No. Look up!
[KORO-SENSEI panting]
[SHIRO] Shedding your skin.
Ah, yes. We know about
that little trick, too.
You see, Koro-sensei,
there's an aspect even to that
which constitutes
an Achilles Heel.
[KORO-SENSEI grunting]
[SHIRO] Molting costs you
dearly in terms of energy.
That prodigious speed
plummets while you recover.
Oh, and look! You've
grown back that arm
--Itona lobbed off
--[KORO-SENSEI screaming]
in his initial attack! That's
even more energy you've lost.
By my calculations,
at the moment this makes
the two of you a fairly
even match for one other.
Using one's
tentacles effectively
calls for a great deal
of mental stamina, too.
And it appears Itona's dirty
little secret pulled the rug out
from under your state of mind,
which, of course, was the idea.
Not to boast, but it's obvious
who has the upper hand.
Oh, also. He has the help
of his devoted guardian.
[KORO-SENSEI yelps]
[ITONA grunts]
[ITONA yells]
[ALL gasp]
[KORO-SENSEI groans]
[SHIRO laughs]
[SHIRO]
Uh-oh!
You'll have to grow those
pesky legs back now too!
[STUDENTS gasp]
[SHIRO] That's an even
bigger energy deficit.
[ITONA]
That was easier than I thought.
Look at you. Not so
tough now, huh?
[NAGISA] He's got
Koro-sensei on the ropes!
If they actually kill him,
they'll save the world!
But... it's hard to get
excited about that.
They not only know
his weak points,
they know how to zero in on
them one after the other.
And that's cool and all,
but... we were hoping to
pull this off ourselves.
If anyone gets to kill
him, it should be us!
[SHIRO] I see that your
legs have regenerated.
Feeling ready for the next
onslaught, are we?
[KORO-SENSEI] No one's ever
run me this ragged before.
And here I thought
I was signing up
for a garden variety face-off.
There's quite a bit
more strategy afoot
than I'd suspected.
I have so many questions
for the pair of you.
Of course, if I lose,
there won't be much
opportunity to pick your brain.
[SHIRO]
Still think you can win?
Your confidence doesn't
strike you as misguided?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Mr. Shiro.
For all your planning, there's
one thing you don't seem
to have taken into account.
[SHIRO]
Not likely.
No detail is overlooked,
no angle is unconsidered.
Finish him.
[STUDENTS whimper]
[KORO-SENSEI gurgles]
[KORO-SENSEI]
What do we have here?
Hmm. I seem to be standing
in something you dropped.
[NAGISA]
Uh?
Uh.
How did I miss that?
[ITONA whimpers]
[ITONA groans]
[KORO-SENSEI]
An anti-me blade
works just as well on your
tentacles as they do mine.
And regeneration takes
just as much a toll.
You may be exceptionally strong,
but I'm exceptionally clever.
[KORO-SENSEI laughs]
[KORO-SENSEI] Don't worry,
children. He's fine.
My old skin kept
him perfectly safe.
Technically though, Itona,
you are outside the boundary.
In yo' face. I win.
Nyah-nyah na-boo-boo.
Etcetera, etcetera.
No more trying to kill me with
your guardian's help, hmmm?
[ITONA growls]
[KORO-SENSEI]
If, however, you'd like to stay,
perhaps learn a thing or two
along with the rest
of the class,
we'll welcome you
with open arms.
Bear in mind,
what you learn here
can't necessarily be quantified.
You are a gifted young man,
but I am richer in experience.
I became a teacher so as to
translate that experience
into something which
can enrich others.
The way to assassinate me isn't
by honing in on my weaknesses,
but by absorbing my lessons.
[ITONA]
Are you saying
that I'm never gonna be
strong enough to beat you?
You think that I'm weak?!
[SHIRO]
Oh, no.
Itona is not a fan
of being lectured to.
[KORO-SENSEI grunts]
[SHIRO] If Koro-sensei continues
to lord his knowledge over him.
[SHIRO]
Genocide is in the air!
[ITONA roaring]
Black tentacles?
I think the dude's
about to go postal!
[ITONA]
I am strong!
These tentacles assure
my victory over everyone!
Everyone!
[ITONA grunting]
[ITONA roaring]
[ITONA grunts]
[ALL gasp]
[SHIRO]
Pardon us, Koro-sensei.
My hot-headed ward
isn't exactly prime classroom
material at the best of times.
It's not lost on me that
this is his first day,
but a mandatory vacation
is clearly in order.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Excuse me!
I can't let you walk
out of here with him.
He's my student!
Until graduation, his
well-being falls on me.
And, frankly, I also have
a lot of questions
to ask you, Mr. Shiro.
[SHIRO]
Sorry. We're leaving.
Unless you care to use force?
[KORO-SENSEI growls]
[KORO-SENSEI grunts, yelps]
--[KORO-SENSEI groans]
--[SHIRO] Anti-Sensei fibers.
I have no intention of
being restrained by you.
No to worry, my
conscientious friend.
He'll be back
before you know it.
March is almost
upon us after all.
In the meantime,
I'll take responsibility
for his well-being, thank you.
[SHIRO]
Such a personality.
It will hoist him by his own
petard before doomsday.
And those children.
Huh! Very promising.
[SHIRO]
What an unpredictable classroom.
Like this weather
we're having today.
[KORO-SENSEI] Ugh, I'm so
dreadfully embarrassed.
[MEG]
What's with him all of a sudden?
[OKANO]
He's been this way for a while.
[KORO-SENSEI]
A grim turn of events
has brought out my serious
side and I'm ashamed!
You children are supposed to
think of me as comic relief!
[MEG]
We are?
[KIRARA]
But you got so serious about it.
"Tell me where those
tentacles came from?
Why does someone
like you have them?"
[KORO-SENSEI screams]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Don't repeat that!
Just hearing those words again
make me want to bury
my head in the sand!
I'm a free-spirited,
impish type
who cleverly dodges
direct questions!
That's my shtick!
I was forced to break character!
[SUGINO] You dissecting
your character type
is what's humiliating.
[IRINA]
What a day, huh?
Was anyone else caught off guard
by the tentacles growing
out of that boy's head?
[ISOGAI]
Level with us, sir.
What's up?
[OKAJIMA] Yeah, how are you
connected to those guys?
[HAYAMI] No side-stepping
the issue like you normally do!
We all have a right to know.
[SUGINO] You don't want our
imaginations running wild.
[MEG]
Exactly. Come on.
We're your students.
If you can't open up to us,
what're we here for?
[KORO-SENSEI]
No, you're right.
It's high time I told
you children the truth.
[KORO-SENSEI]
In reality, your teacher...
Is a biologically
engineered life form!
[OKANO]
Um, yeah.
[MEG]
Duh.
[KORO-SENSEI screams]
[KORO-SENSEI]
That's all I get?
Pardon me if I expected
a bit more of a reaction!
Sir, we kinda noticed
that you're an octopus
that flies through the
air at Mach Twenty.
But you said you're not
from another planet,
so that rules out alien.
[MEG] And how else can you and
Itona be brothers when you had
different parents unless you
were biologically engineered.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Oh, my!
You boys and girls are
incredibly sharp!
Sir, focus on what
happened today.
Why were you mad?
His tentacles upset you.
We've never seen you like that.
[NAGISA]
Does it have something to do
with why you were created
in the first place?
I mean, why are you even here?
[KORO-SENSEI]
All very good questions.
Too bad they won't matter.
Soon, everything you want
to know will be reduced
to space dust swirling in the
place where Earth used to be.
[YOSHIDA, TERASAKA grunt]
[KORO-SENSEI] On the other
hand, if you're serious
about saving this planet,
you'll have amble opportunity
to learn the truth
between now and then.
They say curiosity
killed the cat,
but if those enquiring minds
are to be satisfied,
you'll have to continue
trying to kill me.
Teacher, student.
Assassin, target.
Those are the ties that bind us
to one another
in this classroom.
Nothing comes from
nothing, boys and girls.
If you want answers,
work for them.
Show me what you've learned.
[KORO-SENSEI]
If we're done
giving yours truly the third
degree... class dismissed.
[KORO-SENSEI]
I'm so embarrassed.
[SUGINO, IRINA sigh]
[NAGISA]
We're assassins.
We find answers on
the edge of a blade.
--Our target is our teacher.
--[KORO-SENSEI] Unbelievable
Our question is his life.
[KORO-SENSEI]
This is beyond mortifying.
I could just crawl
into a hole and die.
Right. No student
was hurt in any way.
Make arrangements for repairs.
--[ISOGAI] Mr. Karasuma?
--Uh?
What can I do for you?
Or, rather, for all of you.
[ISOGAI] Um... can you teach
us more about assassination?
We wanna sharpen our skills.
[KARASUMA]
Hmm.
You already know plenty.
Here's the deal, sir.
We've been slacking off
'cause we figured someone else
would take care of killing
Koro-sensei, y'know?
Yeah, 'cept when we saw
Itona do his thing,
it dawned on us.
The thing is, we don't want
it to be someone else.
It should be us. If they can
just bring anyone they want
to do it, well, what's the point
of us being here in
the first place, right?
We may not have
a lot of time left,
but we're willing to
work harder. Please.
We want to
assassinate our teacher!
Like he said, we have to work
for any answers ourselves.
[KARASUMA] What a positive
shift in attitude.
Nice.
All right, then.
Students interested
in beefing up
their assassination skills
can stay after class.
Be ready to work hard!
[STUDENTS]
Yes, sir!
[KARASUMA] Let's start
by climbing up this rope.
It's brand new and waiting
to be broken in.
[STUDENTS]
Seriously?!
[KARASUMA]
Come on...
[NAGISA]
Kunugigaoka Junior High.
Class Three-E.
Our Assassination Classroom.
The rain lets up.
The bell rings.
Another day ends.