[NAGISA]
The math exam's last problem.
Half of our grade was weeded
out before getting this far.
The other half had absolutely
no time to spare.
and was so exhausted they didn't
have the energy to solve it.
The only students still
standing with any chance
of earning full marks in
the few minutes left...
[NAGISA]
...were these two.
[KARMA] What was it Nagisa
always used to say?
[NAGISA sighs]
You're so talented, Karma.
How is there such a gap
between the both of us?
Guess some people are
just geniuses, huh?
[KARMA]
Easy for you to say.
If you ask me,
it's not all that cut n' dry
who the real genius is here.
Talent is usually
an invisible trait.
More often than not,
it's the result of work
other people don't see.
Take Sugino.
He can fit in easily
with anyone, anywhere.
Or Okuda, who can
totally lose herself
in something she's
passionate about.
Even Terasaka, who dives right
in without a second thought.
From where I'm standing,
we're in the same boat.
Everybody has something,
some hidden special ability
they take for granted.
We're all geniuses.
We all have a talent.
Still...
The issue at hand is whether
or not I can filter the answer
to this problem through
the lens of my own.
C'mon, man...
Snap out of it,
you don't have time for this.
[GAKUSHU]
Atoms.
Body-centered cubic units...
Extraneous details.
Stay focused.
Broken down to essentials,
the problem is simple.
Solve for the volume of
your specific domain,
in a box, surrounded by enemies.
[gasps]
[TEST ENEMY A shrieks]
[TEST ENEMY A shrieking]
[GAKUSHU] When both sides
are evenly matched,
their attacks meet
in the middle.
Of course, from there
inward is my domain!
That's one enemy down! Ha!
[GAKUSHU]
Nice try.
But I'm afraid you won't be
encroaching on my turf
anytime soon.
Eight enemies total, surrounding
the cube's perimeter.
If I determine the volume
of the eight areas
I've effectively sealed off,
and subtract that from
the volume of the cube,
I'm left with A-Zero,
my specific domain!
[TEST ENEMY B shrieking]
[GAKUSHU] Once I've
locked down this space,
I'll have the answer.
Come on, come on!
[GAKUSHU]
Ruling my own domain.
Nice overall theme
for my goal in life!
[TEST ENEMY D yelps]
[GAKUSHU] A different sort
of ruler than my father.
He's obsessed.
The man only cares about proving
his "rational" approach
to education superior
to all others.
His method may break
a person's spirit,
but it won't educate them.
It's time to set
the record straight,
give him a piece of my mind!
I have to take control!
That...
is my responsibility
as your son!
[GAKUSHU]
There it is!
The volume of one of the
sealed-off areas is an aggregate
of one hexagonal and three
triangular pyramids!
[KARMA]
Hang on a minute...
This problem doesn't even
call for difficult math.
[KARMA]
The whole thing's divided out
into this one itty-bitty
little cube...
and if it's supposedly
an atomic crystal...
Yeah,
everything on the outside
is just more of the same.
Which means...
The world doesn't end here.
[KARMA]
From where I'm standing,
everyone has their own talent.
Their own specific domain.
We are all in the same boat.
I just couldn't see it before.
All I could see
from inside this box
were fragments of
the bigger picture.
I have my area,
they have theirs.
We all do.
That's how this works.
How it's always worked.
Everyone's the same size,
the same distance apart.
And if we're all cut
from the same box,
those eight contiguous
boxes can be broken up
into the same proportion.
[KARMA] Each person's
individual fragment
accounts for one-eighth
of the whole.
So what it boils down to is:
this box contains one whole me
and one-eighth of
eight other people.
[KARMA]
In other words,
inside this cube,
the ratio of me to the other
eight fragments is one-to-one.
Simple!
And if it's one-to-one
inside the box,
the volume of the area
I can call my own
is up to one-half of the cube!
Voila! That's my
specific domain!
Piece of cake.
They taught us this stuff
in primary school.
[KARMA] No need for long,
drawn-out equations.
No need for big,
complicated diagrams.
Nope.
You just have to
adjust for the fact
there's a world
outside yourself.
[TEACHER A]
Pencils down!
[GAKUSHU gasps]
Time's up, son.
The test is over.
Just one more line.
Damn it! I knew the answer!
[NAGISA]
And like that,
the tidal wave of our
end-of-term exams broke.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Alright-y, class!
Let's all have a look at
your compiled exam papers.
Did those crucial
second blades
manage to pierce their intended
targets, I wonder?
[KORO-SENSEI] No splitting hairs
over a point or two, understood?
The only thing we're
concerned with right now
is whether these scores secured
a place for you in the top 50.
Unless I'm mistaken, the
main campus ought to be
posting the results for
all to see as we speak.
So I see no reason we can't
do the same in E-Class...
[STUDENTS gasping]
[STUDENTS gasp]
You... you're kidding me...
I'm forty-sixth?!
[YOSHIDA] Isn't Terasaka dead
last even in here, though?
[SUMIRE]
If he came in forty-sixth,
then that must mean...
[SUGINO]
Is this for real?
[STUDENTS]
We did it!
[MAEHARA] And we beat out the
Big Five for the top spots!
Go us!
[SUGINO] Karma! Dude,
you got first place!
[exhales]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Feels pretty good, doesn't it?
Earning the highest rank on such
an unforgiving battlefield.
Whatever. I guess so, yeah.
[KORO-SENSEI]
It appears your contest
with Asano the perfectionist
came to a head on that last,
and I must say, particularly
thorny, math problem.
Yeah, about that.
Not sure I could say
exactly why, but...
If I hadn't spent the
past year with you guys,
I don't think I could
have solved it.
That's the kind of
problem it was.
[sighs] Tough haul gettin'
to this point, though, huh?
Yeah! I don't believe it!
And, well, all wanted
this so badly!
We actually beat A-Class.
Almost sounds too
good to be true.
We're back on track for
the top tier schools!
The ladies'll be throwin'
themselves at our feet!
Way to go us, right?
[OKAJIMA]
Yeah! Chicks everywhere!
[sighs] Feels like
a final episode.
Wait a sec! It's not over!
[ISOGAI] Uh. What's
with that look, man?
Are you okay?
[TAKEBAYASHI]
Uh, yeah.
Uh, it's just that, so much has
happened since I came here.
I'm really glad I
got kicked down.
Aw, why you gotta
be all depressing, huh?
Besides, why make an ugly face
when this clown has it covered?
What does that mean?!
Easy, you're choking him!
Whaddya think?
What do I think?
I think I can get into
my dream school now.
What are you gonna study?
Architecture, right?
Yeah. I'm angling
for a high school
that's big on engineering
and science.
[HAYAMI]
Hm.
Ha! Man, those
A-Class dillweeds.
What I wouldn't give to see the
looks on their faces right now!
Bet'cha anything they never
thought in a million years
they'd lose to us!
[KORO-SENSEI] Now, to be fair,
on their part A-Class
performed quite well on
the first half of the exams.
But as the questions grew
increasingly difficult
on the second half,
more and more students found
themselves running out of steam.
Yeah, well, 's what they get.
Whoever you are, nobody's
bloodlust holds out that long.
Even after intensive
assassination drills.
It's next to impossible staying
in that frame of mind
for an entire day.
If you expect to boost
your system on bloodlust,
cramming isn't the way to go.
You have to nurture
it over time,
slow and steady.
[SEO]
How'd this happen?
How'd we lose after everything
we put ourselves through?
[GAKUSHU] Your study methods
worked against you.
You were set up to lose.
That's what it comes to.
Not that my scores are anything
to brag about, either...
Rest assured, I'll put this
frustration to work.
Come high school,
I'll be on top again,
doing my damnedest to blaze
a trail for the rest of you.
Just... All I ask
is for your support.
Asano...
You mean that?
[ASANO]
Intriguing.
Strong words for someone
who's lost the fight
on which he staked his future.
[GAKUSHU gasps]
[A-CLASS STUDENTS]
Principal Asano.
[ASANO] All we may count
on in life is the unknown,
what seems arbitrary can in fact
be what costs you everything.
One can't be sure until
the battle is over.
[A-CLASS STUDENTS whimper]
[ASANO] This, you see, is why I
insist on always playing to win.
I have an obligation to prepare
my students for the unknown.
Between now and graduation,
you have much to learn.
[ARAKI]
Principal Asano, sir?
[ASANO]
Hm?
All due respect,
it's clear to us...
...that your methods
aren't going to
help us beat E-Class.
[ARAKI]
Defeat made them stronger.
Asano's taken that
lesson to heart.
[SAKAKIBARA]
We're no match for them, sir...
Their strength is just
too... what's the word?
Adaptable.
[ALL]
Forgive us, sir.
We fell short of our goal.
[SAKAKIBARA]
If you think it's appropriate,
transfer us down to E-Class.
I think there's a lot to
learn from their way
of doing things.
Well, Principal?
What do you have to say to that?
[SAKAKIBARA]
Asano!
[A-CLASS GIRL A]
Are you all right?!
[GAKUSHU laughs] Your face
looks like it's glitching out.
Uh-oh.
Don't tell my I'm finally seeing
your fatherly side?
Excuse us, sir.
We have to be going.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Well, boys and girls!
You've officially qualified to
be transferred out of E-Class.
Anyone here ready to
leave the mountain?
Yeah. You'd like that,
wouldn't you?
I don't think so, we've
found our second blades.
This is where things
get serious!
[MEG] If you know a place
better suited to assassination,
we're all ears!
[KORO-SENSEI laughs]
Gluttons for punishment, I see.
I suppose, then, as your reward
I ought to divulge my
most notable weakness--
[yelps]
[STUDENTS gasp]
[MEG]
Huh?
Ah! Our building!
[STUDENTS gasp]
[ASANO]
Evacuate the premises, please.
[STUDENTS]
Principal Asano!
The Board reached a
unanimous decision.
The old campus building
is to be demolished today.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[ASANO]
Oh, don't worry.
You'll be moved to an affiliate
school slated to open next year.
We need students to
performance-test
their newest facilities.
[STUDENTS gasp]
Wait, you're farming
us out somewhere?!
It's not all that bad.
Let us call it a
social experiment.
The building is
state-of-the-art,
with closed-circuit
surveillance cameras
and escape-proof architecture.
It's similar to a prison.
The culmination of my
educational philosophy.
But, you can't move
us right now!
We won't go!
We're graduating
from this campus!
[KORO-SENSEI]
I see you'll spare nothing
to see your methods vindicated.
Correct.
Oh, and incidentally,
your services will no
longer be required.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Mm.
Yes, I'm afraid so.
This is the part
where I terminate you.
[KORO-SENSEI shrieks]
Whoa! He just got slapped
with walking papers!
I don't believe it.
The man actually played the
forbidden ace-in-the-hole!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Ah! This is wrongful dismissal!
[SUGINO] The Octopus is
ridiculously susceptible
to this mode of attack.
[NAGISA] Do super creatures
have a legal right to protest?
Now don't go jumping
to conclusions...
Actually, this is no more than a
clever means of distracting you.
When I said "terminate,"
I meant it literally.
I'm here to kill you.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Eh?
[ASANO]
You see, Koro-sensei...
You don't fit with my vision.
He can't be serious.
Look, man, we know you're a
big Machiavelli and all that,
but I'd tread carefully
in your shoes.
The Octopus is clever.
Hold off on the demolition for
now, if you would please...
I have unfinished
business inside.
Where the hell'd that notice
of dismissal come from?
[KARASUMA] This is crazy.
What is he thinking?
Now, then, Koro-sensei.
I assume you don't
wish to be fired?
And furthermore that you wish
to preserve this classroom?
Well, what would you
say to a little wager?
What's he getting at?
[ASANO]
I've prepared five subjects'
worth of exam questions,
and five live grenades.
Four contain anti-Sensei
projectiles.
That is, they are
fatal to you.
One is fatal to humans.
All five grenades are identical
in appearance and smell,
and designed so that once
their pins are pulled
they will explode the instant
their handles are raised.
[STUDENTS gasp]
I've pulled the pins,
and carefully placed
the grenades
between random pages
of each test booklet,
handles down.
You must open each book
and solve the problem in
the top right-hand corner.
[ALL gasp]
But, that'll push the handles
to the up position!
That's correct.
Your teacher will
almost certainly
be hit with an explosion.
Furthermore,
he can't move until the
problem has been solved.
The first four books
are yours and yours alone
to open and solve.
I will be taking the
remainder for myself.
[KORO-SENSEI whimpers]
Kill me, or force
me to withdraw,
and victory belongs
unquestionably to you.
You and the E-Class students
will be allowed to stay here.
Agreed? Terasaka, look sharp.
Use the appropriate formula
to find Koro-sensei's
odds of winning.
[TERASAKA grunts]
Why do I have to solve
something so messed up?
An anti-Sensei grenade
won't kill you...
The real one will, naturally,
but we'd have to save it
for the end, so let's see.
Four-fifths
times three-fourths
times two-thirds
times one-half equals one-fifth.
So... 20%.
Well done!
Yeah, but hold on:
the Octopus sits
through four explosions
before you even
take a turn!
This game is rigged!
You can just bow out if you
don't like the way it's going.
Dunno about you, but
I call that unfair!
[ASANO]
Young man.
[TERASAKA]
Hm?
Life is unfair. It's chock
full with injustice.
Especially if you're
not fortunate enough
to be one of the strong.
Don't you see?
This is why I teach the
true meaning of strength.
So, then. Shall we proceed?
Show me how serious
you really are
about your chosen
profession, Koro-sensei.
[ASANO]
In fact, if I were you,
I wouldn't waste
a single moment.
[STUDENTS whimper]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Yes, of course.
Let's jump right in.
[BOTH exhale]
[KARASUMA] He threatens
dismissal, devises a game
that's clearly in his favor.
And there's no way out.
Mathematically, the
odds of it succeeding
are better than
anything we've tried.
The most important
blade is strength...
This man is an assassin.
[ASANO] Open, solve
the problem, and close.
Move quickly enough and
the grenade won't go off.
Speed is your specialty.
This should be walk
in the park, yes?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Uh, yes! Excellent point!
[KORO-SENSEI whimpers]
[KORO-SENSEI growls]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Planar calculations!
Oh, th-this couldn't be easier!
A-All you gotta to do
is borrow from the tens
and get three with
four left over,
or, ah, actually I believe
it's three or thereabouts.
[KORO-SENSEI screams]
[STUDENTS groaning]
[ASANO]
I know how you are with puzzles.
You get flustered; your
processing speed declines.
This trap is almost
too perfect.
[STUDENTS]
Koro-sensei...
We'll call the first
one a hit... Bravo.
Only three more to go and
you'll have won the game.
Now, please move on
to the next problem
before you've regenerated.
This is B.S.!
No way can he survive three
more of those explosions!
He's seriously
gonna be taken out!
And the setup is so
friggin' simple!
You see my point?
The weak have to rely
on assassination,
whereas the strong may
kill at their leisure,
when and however they please.
Soon, I will plant institutions
across the nation
that drive home this truth.
The Ministry of Defense
has been generous.
Between them and the bounty,
I'll build affiliate schools
all over the world.
[NAGISA] It's always
about education with him.
[KORO-SENSEI groaning]
[ASANO]
Come now, Koro-sensei.
Validate my ideology.
Be the cornerstone of my vision.
[KUNUDON]
Surprise!
[CHILDREN]
Tell us, Kunudon!
[sighs] That festival was
a real white-knuckler!
Ah, but it looks like
those E-Class losers
are down for the count
for the count at last!
[CHILDREN]
That's all she wrote!
Ha, ha, ha, ha!
Hey there Losers!
[CHILDREN]
Just desserts! Yay!
[KUNUDON laughing]
[coughs, chuckles nervously]
Oh, Mr. Principal!
What brings you into the studio?
[CHILDREN]
Notice of dismissal!
I'm being... moved.
To E-Class?
[CHILDREN]
Hooray for unemployment!
Woohoo!