[NAGISA]
Here we go.
Things are about
to get interesting.
What's cool, is while we're
taking the exams separately,
we're all in this together.
There are the people
we fight alongside of.
The people we fight.
The ones who want us to lose,
the ones who want us to win,
almost feels like an arena.
[CROWD cheering]
[NAGISA]
We might be assassins,
but right now, we have
to fight like gladiators.
[NAGISA]
Another day, another bell.
Round one... begin!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Tests are splendid.
The knowledge soaked up by those
eager minds in preparation
may be forgotten once
the dust has settled.
But c'est la vie.
The character-building
thrill of competition,
the privilege of honing
one's mind to a fine point,
the ecstasy of giving it your
all; that's the treasure.
[BEAST roaring]
[NAGISA]
Oh, man!
--[BEAST roaring]
--[STUDENTS screaming]
[NAGISA] The midterms
had nothing on this!
I mean, I get it.
We're a top school.
They start throwing advance
level stuff at us in Third Year,
but holy crap!
English, Math, Science.
The whole shebang.
And we're expected to move
at lightning speed.
Well. This is the moment
of truth, right here.
Good luck, everybody.
[SEO]
Bring it on, last problem!
[BEASTS roaring]
[SEO]
Oh, you're adorable.
I know the card catalog
backwards and forwards.
You don't scare me!
The E Class scrubs,
on the other hand.
S.O.L!
[SEO]
What the--?
Why aren't you
out of commission?
That's a quote from
"Huck Finn," right?
Huh?
Whoa.
You gotta learn to relax.
Seriously. Curl up with a
good book once in a while.
[SEO]
She actually got it right?
Are you kidding me?
What? You don't know
"Catcher in the Rye"?
Oh, wait. It's not a
textbook. Why would you?
[KORO-SENSEI] My, these
are excellent questions.
Good on them. I'm impressed.
This isn't just some
rote classic Lit query.
The students are asked to take
an infamously thorny
twentieth century text
and correct a misquoted passage.
And Salinger, no less.
He wrote in a style
reflective of his angsty teenage
protagonist's natural voice.
[NAGISA]
Got it!
[SEO]
Son of a--!
The Lit teacher only mentioned
that book in passing!
We never actually
read the stupid thing.
Ah. So nobody recommended
it to you? That is a crime.
Someone needs a literate octopus
to push 'em outside
their comfort zone.
[KORO-SENSEI] Holden Caulfield's
rebellious spirit
is enthralling. An absolute must
for boys and girls your age.
I recommend following it up
with "A Clockwork Orange."
Mind-blowing!
[SEO]
Damn it.
[KOYAMA]
Yeah!
Bring it on, Science!
[KOYAMA]
But... I memorized everything.
Why can't I get the armor
to come off of it?
--[OKUDA] It's not that simple.
--[ARMOR] Good job!
[OKUDA]
Um. How do I put this?
Science isn't just memorization.
[KOYAMA]
Huh?
Sure, you stand on the
shoulders of giants,
but the whole point is
to see further than they did.
You have to think for yourself,
make your own discoveries.
[KOYAMA]
Uh...
[OKUDA] More importantly,
like Koro-sensei taught me,
communicate.
That way the next person can
stand on your shoulders.
[ARAKI]
This is ridiculous!
How am I supposed
know how many times
the Tokyo
International Conference
on African Development has met?
[ISOGAI] Whew.
That was a close shave.
But lucky for me I do know
how many times they've met.
Ugh! Oh, come on,
what are the chances?
I know. Coincidence.
I happen to sympathize with
Africa's poverty issues.
Thing is, my family's dirt
poor, so I kinda get it.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Let's go on a trip!
No time like the present!
[ISOGAI] I actually got a
chance to go there recently.
It's a fascinating place.
You should visit.
[KANZAKI] "Spring has gone away.
And summer came, it would seem--
From those white hemp robes.
Laid to dry in the sunlight.
On Kagu's Heavenly Hill."
[POETRY BEAST roars]
[chuckles] A translation worthy
of your beauty, my dear.
However, sloppy modern syntax
does not a satisfactory
answer on the finals make.
[GAKUSHU]
Mathematics.
Akabane's a member
of E Class, isn't he?
He placed second on the
midterms. Right below me.
Quite an accomplishment
for a slacker. Heh.
[GAKUSHU] Commendable,
but not intimidating.
You see, I am
anything but a slacker.
[KARMA]
Aw, how cute.
Look at 'em all. So panicked.
So hell-bent on not screwing up.
[KARMA]
The key to true victory
is learning how not to take
the game so... seriously.
[KARMA] It doesn't matter
how hard your opponent works
if you're better than them.
This should be fun.
[NAGISA]
Two days of testing.
Two days of putting
it all on the line.
Everything we're trying to do
lives or dies by the
number of circles we get.
[KORO-SENSEI]
All righty, class.
This is it. The test
scores are in.
[KORO-SENSEI] Without further
ado. The English portion.
[KORO-SENSEI]
First in E Class... Oh-ho!
First in the entire grade!
Rio Nakamura!
[STUDENTS cheering]
That's right.
[SEO]
Son of a--!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Bravo, my dear.
I'm glad to see my misgivings
about your enthusiasm
were unfounded.
Hey, nothin' comes 'tween this
girl and the promise of cash.
There is a little
matter of your tentacle.
Right? You haven't forgotten?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Perish the thought.
Nagisa: good show overall,
but it seems we still have
an eensy, teensy issue
with your spelling.
Something to work on.
In the meantime, as agreed,
top marks in a given subject
equal one tentacle down.
So, let's continue
poring over the grades
to see if I'll lose more.
Next is Japanese.
First in E Class...
Yukiko Kanzaki!
But I'm afraid the honor
of first in the entire grade
goes to A Class's Gakushu Asano.
Still, you gave the principal's
son a run for his money.
[KANZAKI giggles]
Guys' a know-it-all.
Total asshole.
No kidding, right?
Ugh. Nakamura only
beat him in English
by the skin of her teeth.
Classic Type A personality.
Guess that's the reason
he's ranked nationally, huh?
[KIMURA] All of the Big Five
jerks are ranked nationally.
[MIMURA] Asano's King
of the Hill, though.
Nobody gets to the top without
going through him first.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Moving on to the next subject.
In Social Studies, first in E
Class goes to Yuma Isogai!
As for first in the grade.
Da-da-da-da!
You beat out Asano
for the top spot!
Uh. Yeah!
[growls]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Excellent job!
Especially considering
the fiendish questions
they casted you.
Right now we're two to one.
Who got it for Science? Okuda?
[KORO-SENSEI] First in E Class
for Science is... Manami Okuda!
And...
Outstanding! You're also
first for the grade!
[STUDENTS cheering]
Yes! Three to one, guys!
[MIMURA] Do we even need
to hear who won for Math?
E Class killed it! No question!
[STUDENTS]
Hooray!
[OKAJIMA]
Nice goin', Okuda! Yeah!
Girl, that tentacle is
yours. You earned it!
Yes! Now A Class has to do
whatever we tell them!
Yeah they do!
Which just leaves Mathematics.
[STUDENTS chattering]
[KOYAMA] We're three and two
across all five subjects.
The Untouchables handed us our
asses. This is it. We're dead.
We still beat 'em on overall
scores. Don't be a wuss.
Could've been a lot worse.
What are they gonna do?
[KOYAMA]
Eh.
Yeah, 'least the jackass who
stole fourth place from me
is choking on humble pie.
Ha! Cocky little bastard!
Talk about brining
a knife to a gun fight.
Guy didn't even compete!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Never underestimate your target.
Particularly when
it has a monopoly
on grade point averages.
The best scores in E Class went
to Katakoa and Takebayashi,
both admirably tied
for seventh place.
Not surprising.
They studied hard.
As, of course, did your
opponents in A Class,
which is to be expected.
These finals were
nothing to sneeze at.
One's only chance was to study.
[KARMA] What're you
tryin' to say, Teach?
[KORO-SENSEI] Someone thought
they could coast by on luck
and a devil-may-care attitude,
and proceeded to
royally screw it up.
[ASANO] "My congratulations to
you on retaining the top rank."
Or so I'd like to say.
Would in fact be saying if
not for your idiotic wager.
Instead, let me offer
my condolences.
Indeed, it must be
quite devastating
to realize your loss made
you the laughingstock
of the entire school.
What a pickle you're in.
Shall I step in
on my son's behalf?
Thanks, but no.
[ASANO]
Have it your way.
What was that you said
about finding myself
at the end of a leash?
You'd hoped to finagle E Class
into divulging my secrets,
didn't you?
They aren't yours to find, boy.
I won't be ensnared by a whelp
who can't win a bet
against his peers.
[ASANO grunts]
[KORO-SENSEI] Three of your
classmates each have a claim
to one of my tentacles:
Nakamura, Isogai, and Okuda.
You, on the other
hand, have nothing.
Which is only fair, as that's
exactly what your carefree,
non-committal attitude has
contributed to the cause.
See where I'm going with this?
Those who fail to apply
themselves,
who, at the moment of
truth, decide to sit back
and let the chips
fall where they may,
are destined for disappointment.
Dull is the blade
of the lazy assassin.
In fact, I wouldn't stoop to
call him an assassin at all.
A blowhard and
a braggart, perhaps.
But an assassin? I think not.
[KARASUMA]
Hey.
You think that was a bit harsh?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Of course. It had to be.
I cut him down so
he'll spring back up.
The boy's enormously talented.
There's no denying that,
but he's a novice.
He has not yet learned how
to be worthy of that talent.
He refuses to meet any challenge
except on his own terms.
He doesn't see the
true value of competition.
To a young person for whom
everything comes easily,
the pang of defeat can be
a much-needed wake up call.
On the surface,
the whole concept of exams
may seem arbitrary,
but deep down,
it's not about grades.
It's about rising
to the occasion.
It's about tasting
the rapture in triumph
and disgrace of failure.
They go hand in hand, you see.
One is meaningless
without the other.
To win, one has to lose.
The difference between
the novice and the master
is that the master
has failed more times
than the novice has tried.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Okie dokie, class.
A fine showing on the finals.
You managed to snag the top spot
in three out of five subjects.
Let's get this assassination
attempt under way, shall we?
The top three students can pick
whichever tentacle they'd like.
[KORO-SENSEI] Three tentacles
I can comfortably live without.
Six, however? Whew!
That would've been
a tad sketchy.
[TERASAKA]
Hold up, Octopus.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Eh?
What's this B.S. about us
only havin' three spots?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Uh. I believe all subjects
have been accounted for.
Umm. English, Science,
Social Studies. Umm...
[TERASAKA]
Nice try. I don't think so.
English, Social
Studies, Science,
and let's not forget Home Ec.
We aced 'em all.
Read 'em and weep.
[KORO-SENSEI]
What?! Home Ec?!
Hey, if it was covered
on the finals, it counts.
What do you know?
The idiot pulled his weight.
I'm proud of us.
[KORO-SENSEI] Not so fast!
Home Ec is a blow off--!
Hang on, Teach.
Wow. That was just plain rude.
You ask me,
Home Ec is straight-up one
of the most important classes.
[OKAJIMA] Look at you tryin'
to cheat! C'mon, be a man!
Home Ec is the toughest one!
And all four of 'em
got top score!
That makes for seven
tentacles in all!
--[STUDENTS] Seven shots!
--[KORO-SENSEI] Seven?
--Seven shots! Seven shots!
--[KORO-SENSEI screaming]
[ISOGAI]
Oh, Koro-sensei?
We put our heads together
and got this idea.
See, we were all thinkin'.
We could use our wager with A
Class to kinda sweeten the pot.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Nani?
[NAGISA]
The last day of school
is always marked by
a big assembly.
This year, we've got
some unfinished business.
[TERASAKA]
Hey, hey! Lookie here!
Well if ain't Mr. Big Man
on Campus himself!
[GAKUSHU] Pardon me. Some of
us have a ceremony to get to.
I don't have time to
indulge the likes of you--
[TERASAKA]
Whoa! Whoa!
Not so fast there, slick.
What's the big rush?
[ISOGAI] We had a bet.
And last I checked, you lost.
We don't wanna rub your faces
in it, that's just how it is.
Our demand was sent
to you via email.
I assume you can
make that happen.
[TERASAKA]
If you even try to play
like none of this was
for real, that's it.
We'll throw in Home Ec.
We mopped the floor
with you in that, too.
Not that anybody's
keepin' score.
Oh, wait a second, never
mind. Yeah they are.
[IRINA] Those kids
got the better of you.
It's gotta string a little.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Let's be honest,
the Home Ec argument was
splitting hairs, but so be it.
I'm honestly glad.
Sure, no accredited
university devotes space
to Home Ec on their
entrance exams,
but that means Home Ec
teachers have more freedom
to create an exam based
on personal taste.
Preparing for
something that arbitrary
is a near impossible feat.
The limits those
extraordinary boys and girls
stretched themselves to
for a leg up on the finals
gives me pause.
They found and
successfully exploited
the tiniest of loopholes
just to make headway.
Seasoned assassins could take
a page from their book.
[IRINA]
Hmm.
You're so sweet.
Why couldn't we go
the assembly again?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Mr. Karasuma said our presence
would be a distraction.
[IRINA]
Ugh. Yours maybe, Calamari.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Yours more likely... bitch.
[ISOGAI]
Karma!
Surprised to see you here.
Since when do you make
time for stuff like this?
Not big deal, man.
If I didn't put
in an appearance,
everyone'd think
I was running away.
[ISOGAI]
Hm?
Yeah, you should
check it out sometime.
It sounds interesting-- Uh?
Not to be that guy.
But Ritsu's stand-in
is giving me a serious
case of the willies, sir.
Suck it up, soldier.
We can't afford to have the real
thing exposed as a machine.
Her stand-in is my immediate
supervisor's daughter,
so ease up.
Kid knows how to keep a secret.
Her father agreed to this
because Ritsu's tutoring
got her grades up.
No offense, but she's been
hovering 'round me since finals.
I mean she's nice,
but she's definitely the
reason I came in dead last.
[KARASUMA]
Dead last in E Class, he means.
Which is still around
average for the whole grade.
Who would've thought?
He's come a long way
from the bottom.
[DEAN] Vacation is no
excuse for becoming lazy.
Uh... You, uh. Hmm.
A few months of fun in the sun
isn't worth landing in E Class.
[NAGISA]
His usual pot shots are bombing.
We're kinda hard to use as
a negative example now, huh?
Too bad Koro-sensei's not here.
He's the whole the reason
we're standing tall.
[ASANO]
The term comes to a close
with E Class more
aware of their potential.
The whole school is more aware.
The winds of change
are stirring,
fanning the flames of rebellion.
And here we stand, the Earth's
very survival in question.
All in all, my teaching methods
function as they always have,
like a well-oiled machine.
And yet, the underdogs threaten
to become an inspiration.
A beacon.
Absolutely unacceptable.
[KORO-SENSEI]
One guidebook for each of you.
Doesn't really get how
to sum things up, does he?
Feels like I'm
playing an accordion.
[KORO-SENSEI] These barely
begin to scratch the surface.
The irresistible siren-songs
of Summer are beyond count.
Now, then. As we plunge headlong
into the break, remember this.
A certain main event is
just around the corner.
Yeah. Trust us, Teach,
no one's gonna forget that.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Every year, this little event
is a privilege reserved
for the students
with the highest
scores on the finals.
That is to say: A Class.
This time around, however,
A and E Class were neck-and-neck
at the top fiftieth percentile.
So, I'm proud to say, you boys
and girls more than qualify.
For the Kunugigaoka Junior
High Summer Special Course
in Okinawa!
Three whole days at one of the
finest resorts on the island!
[STUDENTS cheering]
[SEO]
Who even cares?
So they get to go to Okinawa.
Big deal. It's a local trip.
[STUDENT F] You were supposed
to represent and you choked!
[STUDENT G]
Assholes!
[STUDENT E] Asano's the only
one of you worth a damn!
[GAKUSHU]
Everyone shut up.
[STUDENTS]
Huh?
[GAKUSHU]
We lost. That's the end of it.
At least have the self-respect
to be graceful in defeat.
[GAKUSHU]
Heads will roll for this.
And E Class's necks will the
first on the chopping block.
Followed by my father.
[KORO-SENSEI]
So, then. What will it be?
Well, we've decided we'd like
to cash-in our tentacle freebie
options during Summer camp.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Very good.
Seven tentacles will
present a major handicap.
But that's not all!
Anything about Okinawa
strike you as advantageous?
Perhaps the fact that it's an
island, surround by water.
I'll be honest
with you, children.
Koro-sensei is more
than a wee bit nervous.
As you know, I've already
handed out the report cards
for you to show your parents.
But these are the report cards
specifically for assassins.
[NAGISA] Double circles
for the entire class.
The highest score possible.
Given to us by our target.
[KORO-SENSEI] You've become
a formidable bunch.
You should be proud.
The first term has been
all about the basics,
which you've mastered.
But now, we're gonna
step things up!
First term is over!
Let the Assassination Classroom
Summer Vacation begin!
Time for a little R &amp; R,
a little supplemental study,
and a lotta killing!