[NAGISA] Success was so close,
we could practically taste it.
But then it happened.
Koro-Sensei revealed his
Absolute Defense Form.
To make matters worse,
we were poisoned.
And with our mentor temporarily
immobile, the only real option
is to deal with the
culprit by ourselves.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Ten of your classmates are ill.
Two others have been left
behind to care for them.
That leaves you to
operate on their behalf.
You must sneak in, surprise
our mysterious adversary,
and steal the antidote!
It's too dangerous. Whoever the
hell this guy is, he's a pro.
This scenario's been planned
out to the last detail.
[KORO-SENSEI] Perhaps the
wisest course of action would be
to simply hand me
over, is that it?
--Unconditional surrender?
--[KARASUMA growls]
[KORO-SENSEI]
The choice is yours.
[ISOGAI]
Uh.
It's just... this is so hard.
[SUGAYA] I mean, look how
high we'd have to climb!
[IRINA] Ten to one they'd
plummet to their deaths
before getting halfway up.
[KARASUMA grunting]
It's not worth the risk.
We play by the enemy's rules.
Nagisa, Kayano.
Be on your guard.
[ISOGAI grunting]
C'mon. What're we scared of?
It's just a ledge. No big.
[OKANO] I know, right?
What have we been training for?
[HAYAMI]
Truth.
--[IRINA gasps]
--[KORO-SENSEI laughs]
[ISOGAI] Oh, yeah.
See? We can handle this!
Now, whoever's waiting at the
top may be a different story.
So, hey, Mr. K? It'd be
cool if you came with.
We need a commander.
Help us make this bastard pay!
Show him what it means
to mess with E Class!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Look at that.
Clearly these are no
ordinary teenagers.
You have a 15-member
special forces unit
at your beck and call.
But I only count fourteen.
Probably because you
didn't count me.
[KORO-SENSEI] Quickly, my
friend. Time is of the essence.
[KARASUMA]
Mm...
All right, listen up! When
we reached the summit,
our objective is the
hotel's top floor.
This is a stealth infiltration,
so our best weapon is
the element of surprise.
I want you to use the same
hand signals and link-ups
we've been drilling in P.E.
The only difference here
is who we're targeting.
You've got three
minutes to memorize the map.
Know the terrain.
We commence in five!
[STUDENTS]
Yes, sir!
[STUDENTS groaning, coughing]
[OKUDA] Time's running out.
Fifty minutes left.
Last one up's a rotten egg!
Oh, man. Okano moves
like a mountain goat.
Yeah. She smokes just about
everybody at this stuff.
I'm gonna say this knowing
it's perfectly obvious.
But getting old looks
like it sucks.
[IRINA] You idiot! I swear
on my life, if you drop me!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Let no one say my
students don't have
exceptional balance!
[KARASUMA]
You're welcome.
I make 'em scale
the cliff out back.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Oh, I see. Well, that accounts
for their remarkable
proficiency at fly-boarding.
Ah! Holy crap on a spoon, will
you ladies stop gabbing already?
[RYUNOSUKE] So, uh,
remind me why Miss Bitch
felt obligated to come along?
[MEG] Yeah. She hates feeling
left out. Character flaw.
I wouldn't mind her so much if
she wasn't such a boat anchor.
Karma, wait! Slow down!
[KARMA]
Um, if you hadn't noticed,
we're kind of on
a schedule here.
Yeah, you've got a point.
Right, let's do it!
[KARMA]
Sharp rock. Careful.
[gasps] That was almost ugly.
--[KORO-SENSEI chuckles]
--[IRINA growls]
[IRINA] Don't even act like I
weigh that much! I'm a feather!
C'mon. Work them guns!
[NAGISA] I wonder...
If this guy knows about
Koro-Sensei, who in
the world could he be?
Ritsu, I want you to run a final
check on our infiltration route.
Right! Displaying
interior map now.
[RITSU]
Analyzing data.
All elevators require a unique
pass code for every floor.
Stairs are the less conspicuous
option, but there's a catch.
Access doors are
arranged at odd angles
to each other across
respective foyers.
And the stairs themselves
cover a lot of ground.
We risk detection
at several points.
Cool, it's kind of
like a TV station.
What are you talking about?
Yeah. I hear they make the
layout confusing on purpose.
It's a precaution
against terrorists.
Ah! I learned something today.
Ironic bad guys love this sorta
place as a rendezvous point.
[RITSU]
Side door locked. One moment.
[KARASUMA] Let's move.
There's not much time.
[ISOGAI]
Yes, sir!
Why the hell do they have so
many damn security guards?
That's a lot of guys for
all of us to sneak past.
[KARASUMA] Maybe it's best
if only one or two of us
take it from here? No, safety
in numbers; we don't know who
we're up against.
How should we do this?
Come on, people. What are we
waiting for? Let's just do it.
[STUDENTS gasp]
Do you even comprehend the
situation we're in right now?
There's too many of us!
Uh. Are you out your mind?
Watch and learn, sweethearts.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Gulp.
[MEN]
Hm?
[MEN sigh]
[IRINA gasps]
[IRINA]
Oh, sorry.
Blame the mini bar in my room.
Oh, uh. Think nothing of
it, ma'am. No harm done.
Is that...? That's the piano
I'm performing on next week.
I came early to do the
whole tourist thing.
Wonder if she's any good.
Hey, she can tickle
my ivories any time.
[IRINA]
Mind if I play a few bars?
Let's see if this baby's in
tune. I'll help me sober up.
You boys have nothing against
a little Chopin, right?
Well, I... I-I'll check
with the front desk,
--but it should be--
--[IRINA] Oh, now,
they don't care. C'mon. Help me
out. It'll be a private concert.
I'd love some audience feedback.
Us? Feedback?
Sure. You work hard.
You deserve a chance
to play critic.
Help a lady hone her...
technique.
[piano plays]
[MEN sigh]
[STUDENTS gasp]
Whoa.
Oh, Wow. She can really play.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Ah, the Fantasie-Impromptu!
[NAGISA]
Huh?
[KORO-SENSEI] That, boys
and girls, is an assassin
with multiple blades!
She charms, she bewitches,
she fills the air with the sweet
music, captures the imagination.
Every ear is seduced.
Every eye is riveted!
What's wrong? Aw, could it
be you're a teensy bit shy?
Move in closer so you
can see my fingering.
[MEN murmur]
[IRINA] I just bought you your
twenty minutes. Get moving.
Uh!
[piano plays]
[NAGISA] For a moment there,
were as spellbound
as the guards. Just when
you think you know someone.
[NAGISA]
Uh.
We made it past the
first check point!
Man. Miss Bitch has some talent.
Who'd'a thunk it with those
dragon-claws of hers?
And she ever mentioned
being able to play.
Let this be a lesson to you not
to judge a book by its cover.
There's a lot more to a good
assassin than meets the eye.
Sure, she's crass
and overbearing.
But your Language Arts
teacher also happens to be
one of the most dangerous
women in the world.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[KORO-SENSEI laughs]
See, class?
Even when I have none,
you're in good hands.
--Let's go.
--[KAEDE] Mm.
[IRINA] That's right,
boys. I call the tune.
[KARASUMA] Okay. We've
cleared the lobby area,
so we should be in good shape.
If we're stopped, we'll
say we're staying here.
But, sir. We're a bunch
of junior high kids.
I mean, look at us, right?
We shouldn't be here.
Why not? There are
a lot of kids here.
Where do you think the offspring
of the ultra-rich stay
when they travel? That's right.
Only the best for daddy's
little prince or princess.
You should see
some of the antics
those trust-fund
brats get up to.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Excellent! So, walk around
like you own the place.
Turn those noses up
and no one will be the wiser!
Let's practice.
Show me entitled!
[STUDENTS chatter]
[KORO-SENSEI]
There it is.
[KARASUMA]
Little too much there, gang.
Reel it in some.
Don't encourage them.
[KORO-SENSEI] It occurs
to me, we haven't no idea
what our enemy looks like.
Even posing as typical guests
we're vulnerable to attack.
Best marshal our efforts
toward staying vigilant.
[STUDENTS]
Whatever.
Thank you. I mean it.
You guys rock.
[OKUDA]
Oh. It's nothing.
[TAKEBAYASHI] Their
temperature's still rising.
If we don't get
the fever to break,
there's the possibility
of permanent brain damage.
[OKUDA grunts]
I'm on it.
Oh, um... Do you think
there's a chance this virus
could, I dunno, spread
to everyone on the island?
[TAKEBAYASHI] I don't
think it works like that.
We haven't come
down with symptoms.
[OKUDA]
Uh...
[TAKEBAYASHI] I believe
what we're dealing with
is spread orally. You'd
have to eat or drink after
someone already infected.
So the threat to random
bystanders is fairly low.
Which means the other team
shouldn't transmit it anyone.
[OKUDA] How would someone
specifically target us
for infection? When? Where?
People really think
we belong here.
They're not even
making eye contact.
It makes sense if you
think about where we are.
This place has a reputation.
Folks come here to
keep a low profile.
Heh. You know, at first
I was sure everybody here
would be a problem. But
getting the top floor's
turning out to be a lot
easier than we thought.
Glad Mr. K's with us, though.
Feels a lot safer with
him leading the charge.
[TERASAKA laughs]
Who said this was gonna be hard?
Hey, we're not there yet.
But, the clock's tickin'.
I say we switch off stealth
mode and storm the joint!
[KARASUMA]
Wait!
--[YOSHIDA, TERASAKA chuckle]
--[MAN hums]
--[FUWA gasps]
Terasaka! Watch out!
[KARASUMA]
Huh.
[TERASAKA, YOSHIDA]
Huh?! Uh!
[KARASUMA]
Gas!
[STUDENTS gasp]
Oh, no! Mr. Karasuma!
[KARASUMA grunting]
[SMOG]
What gave me away?
I pride myself on being
as nondescript as possible.
Happens to be one of my
strongest selling points,
Little Miss Helmet Head.
I've seen you before.
You gave us those complimentary
drinks back at our hotel.
[STUDENTS gasp]
Tropical juice, compliments
of the house. Enjoy.
[NAGISA]
Whoa. She's right!
[FUWA] Why would you be here if
you worked for the other place?
It doesn't add up.
[ISOGAI]
Hey, yeah!
Ha! You've got a
good eye for faces.
So it was you that
got everybody sick!
Ha! Is that right?
I'd love to see your
evidence, Sherlock.
Tropical islands are a hotbed
for all sorts of icky viruses.
Uh, well...
[FUWA laughs]
And yet we were split up
and on different parts
of the island all day.
The only time we were
together was for dinner
on the shipboard restaurant.
But Mimura and Okajima bowed out
of dinner to work on the video,
and it just so happens they're
both under the weather;
which makes your free drinks
the only viable suspect.
And since you served them...
you, sir, are the
poisoner! Elementary!
[SMOG growls]
That was seriously amazing!
It's like we're on television!
[FUWA] Hm. I credit my
taste in detective manga.
"Eliminate the impossible,
and whatever remains,
must the truth!"
Ah, yes. Shonen Jump is
every sleuth's best friend.
The writer's go all out.
So, manga?
[FUWA]
Hm? Yeah. Why not?
Best way to read the classics.
Locked door murder mysteries,
vanished heirs, phantom
blackmailers. You name it.
I don't get the reference!
Why is this suddenly
an advertisement?
Knock it off, Fuwa!
We're not running a charity.
[chuckles]
--[KARASUMA groaning]
--[STUDENTS gasp]
Well, congrats on
uncovering my identity,
but I'm afraid it's
a little too late.
[KORO-SENSEI]
He's a poisoner, children.
An expert at the surreptitious
application of his craft.
Not to toot my own horn, but the
gas was a homemade concoction.
One whiff turns enemies
into statues.
Fresh air disperses the
runoff, so there's no trace.
Now, then.
I guess it's safe to assume
you're not here to trade.
I'll have to tell the big man
negotiations deteriorated.
Oh well, you win some,
you lose some.
[SMOG]
That was fast.
Crap. They're
blocking the exits.
First rule, coming
up against an enemy.
Scout the exits,
block their retreat.
Cut off their communications.
We've learned from the best;
isn't that right, Mr. K?
[KARASUMA]
Sorry, pal.
You were a tad too quick
to show us your true colors.
You should've kept quiet and
reported us to your boss.
[SMOG] Hmph. You can
still speak, huh?
First rule when up against
numerous enemies.
Cut off the head,
and the body dies.
Observe!
[SMOG] Such... such
incredible strength.
Such inhuman speed.
No matter.
The poison will relieve you
of command soon enough.
Farewell, noble adversary.
It's been... a pleasure.
[FUWA]
No!
[STUDENTS]
Mr. Karasuma!
[ISOGAI] Sir. You can't
keep going like this.
You've gotta lie down.
Just give me half an
hour, I'll be fine.
Don't do anything crazy.
[SUGAYA] Oh, yeah, 'cause
we're the crazy ones.
That stuff could've
killed an elephant.
[OKANO]
No kidding, right?
Mr. K must be some
kind of monster.
[NAGISA] Can't believe
he walked away from that.
Talk about pro.
One bad guy down, but what's
the next one gonna be like?
Gotta wonder if we'll
be able to handle them.
Like... on our own.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Woo-hoo!
Summer Vacation is
finally in full swing!
[MEG] Nice that you
can stay positive!
[KIMURA] I'd be too if
I had a protective shell!
[SUGAYA] Show him what
full swing really means!
[KORO-SENSEI screaming]
Take your belt off for a sec.
I'm gonna cram
Mr. Have a Nice Day
down your pants
so he'll shut up.
The hell you are!
[NAGISA]
'Kay, I'll bite.
What about now makes it
feel like summer vacation
all of a sudden?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Because my students
are acting independently of me.
That's what summer's
about, really.
Extended breaks from the routine
of school foster autonomy.
You learn to think
and act on your own.
The prognosis for anyone else in
this predicament would be grim.
But you have the tools to
meet your foes head-on.
This is an
assassination vacation.
It's up to you to
make the most of it.
[GASTRO] Start with
primo seafood stock.
Don't skimp on the green
onions or the minced garlic.
Then, just a dash of steel!
[GASTRO]
It's how you soup-up a gun.
See, when the broth seeps
down the barrel, it gets cold.
[VOICE ON PHONE chuckles]
Well, that makes
my blood curdle.
I assume the gun's
not on safety?
Eh. I know what I'm
doin'. Just relax.
It'll still shoot
when the time comes.
A good firearm's gotta have the
personality of a gourmet meal.
Just the right balance of
the four cardinal flavors:
savory, sweet, sour, and fatal.
You have personality. Are your
friends as odd as you are?
[GASTRO]
Don't judge.
When you pull off as
many jobs as we have,
you develop a few quirks.
In this industry it's a sign
of being worth your salt.
Take Smog. He's all about
the signature poisons.
Built a world-class lab
to feed his obsession.
You gotta admire that
level of dedication.
Quite. What of your
other associate?
Grip, was his name?
[GASTRO]
Yeah...
Grip. That one's a prime
cut of grade-A weirdo,
even by our standards.
[TERASAKA]
Mm.
[SUGAYA]
Um, okay.
Why's that dude just
standing out in the open?
Gives me the heebie-jeebies.
Yeah. I'm definitely picking
up a kill-or-be-killed vibe.
Well, to be honest, mostly kill.
[KARASUMA] A scenic walkway
with an unobstructed view.
So much for surprise attack,
or safety in numbers.
Dammit. What I wouldn't
give for a real gun.
Who'd have known I needed to
pack heat for a trip like this?
[STUDENTS yelp]
[GRIP]
Boring.
I can hear your
footsteps, people.
I wanted to kill
someone interesting,
not a bunch of amateurs.
Ain't your squadron leader
supposed to be some kinda
special forces dick, or
did he get bagged? Hun.
[KARASUMA whimpers]
Hun. Tough break.
Guess the gas got to him before
I had the chance, hun.
Smog live, or did they
kill each other at
the same time, like men?
Hun, lemme see ya.
[TERASAKA] He cracked the
freaking window with his hand!
[KIMURA]
Yeah... That's not all.
[FUWA] Nobody's got the nerve to
say it, but the way he talks.
Dude. What's with all
the stupid "huns?"
[STUDENTS] Why does he always
say what we're thinking.
Hun. It's how samurai's talk.
Read someplace they
used to do it all the time
to sound intimidating.
I like the way it plays.
Makes me feel badass.
[NAGISA]
Okay. So, he's a little off.
[GRIP]
This is actually the first time
I've tried it out, so no big.
Hun, I might decide to drop
it once I've killed you.
No one else's heard me talk
this, so it'd be a clean slate.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Your hands, sir.
Are those the only "tools of the
trade" at your disposal?
Makes staying incognito easy
as pie. Someone pats me down,
I got nothin'. But I can
still snap their neck.
These babies know what's up.
Hun, they do.
Sometimes when the mood strikes
me I can crush a skull.
Funny thing 'bout
bein' this good.
The better you get at sendin'
folks to the sweet hereafter,
the more you crave usin'
you gifts for somethin'
beyond just plain killing.
[KARASUMA whimpers]
[GRIP] I mean, you still
wanna kill, hun.
You just wish someone'd
give you a real challenge.
That's what blows about
this. I was hopin' for
a worthy adversary.
Instead I get... you.
You don't what know a pain it is
to snuff out a whole group, hun.
I'm callin' the boss to
come clean this place up.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[KARMA]
Speaking of letdowns...
[GRIP]
Hm.
[KARMA] You seem fairly
average for a professional.
And I can break glass,
too, if that's all it takes.
What I wouldn't do is
call in reinforcements
as an opening move. But
then I'm not especially
threatened by "a
bunch of amateurs."
[STUDENTS gasp]
Karma! Stop!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Not so fast, Mr. Karasuma.
The boy's chin is down.
[KARASUMA, ISOGAI gasp]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Karma typically enters a fight
with his chin angled upward.
It shows disdain.
He's literally looking down
his nose at his opponent.
This is different.
[KORO-SENSEI] True, his words
may be dripping with arrogance,
but his eyes are
staring daggers.
He's alert, locking
his opponent's gaze.
Finals were quite a blow
to his precious ego.
But I suspect he's
taken the lessons
of that failure to heart.
[KARMA]
Heh.
[GRIP] Hmph. All right. Put your
money where your mouth is.
[KORO-SENSEI] Go at him with
everything you've got, Karma!
You're going head-to-head...
with an adult!