[NAGISA]
End-of-term exams were over.
Victory was total, but no sooner
had we gotten the results
than the principal
showed up,
Koro-sensei's walking
papers in hand.
The man challenged his
rival to a one-sided game.
Come now, Koro-sensei.
Validate my ideology and be
the cornerstone of my vision.
[KORO-SENSEI whimpers]
[ASANO]
Mm?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Alright-y, then!
Open, solved, and closed!
Fortunately, I just so happen
to remember more or less
which questions are on what page
in this particular
series of books.
Math was the only trouble spot.
That one's been loaned
out to a student
for so long I'd forgotten.
[TOKA, OKANO gasp]
You know these books
backwards and forwards?
A rather remarkable coincidence.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Oh, not just these.
I've committed all of Japan's
test materials to memory.
You say no moving out
of the blast radius
until the given
problem is solved?
Very well.
That little caveat is nothing
to a passionate educator.
I'm sorry, sir.
You sincerely thought you'd
gotten the better of me, huh?
My, my.
A-Class' crushing defeat
must have you in a tizzy.
I'm afraid this
one-dimensional stratagem
may wind up getting
the better of you.
There we have it.
The last book.
Your turn, I believe.
What does it feel like,
staring your own
demise in the face?
They say one's life
flashes before one's eyes.
What do you see, Principal?
What's flickering by in
that exemplary brain?
[NAGAI]
Sir?
[MORI]
[IKEDA]
Mr. Asano?
[NAGISA] Two monsters,
teaching at the same school.
One to atone for his strength.
The other to atone
for his weakness.
[ASANO]
A noble effort, Ikeda.
Maybe next time. Hey.
A deal's a deal. So, study
and behave yourself today.
Uh. Aw, dang! No fair, sir.
You're totally a superhuman
or something.
Hey, Mr. Asano?
Why does a beast like
you start a cram school
in an abandoned shack like this?
I'd have thought you'd graduated
from some big college
with loads of credentials
and stuff.
No offense, sir, but it seems
like a waste of talent to me.
Not to mention how far
we all gotta hike.
Come now, Nagai.
Nothing is for naught
in this world of ours.
This mountain is
wonderfully scenic.
And the hike is good exercise.
[NAGAI whimpers]
What about funds?
Bet this place is in the red.
Don't worry, Mori my dear.
My stock portfolio more than
makes up for the deficit.
I don't mean to brag, but I'm
something of a financial wiz.
As you can see,
this month I'm happily
in the black.
[STUDENTS]
He's superhuman!
So why does someone
so awesome
get into teaching
in the first place?
If you wanna make
us that awesome,
you've got your work
cut out for you.
Don't overthink it.
All I ask is you try
to be good students.
Remember, the bar is set
differently for everyone.
But your enthusiasm
is an asset, Ikeda.
As is Mori's cleverness.
[MORI laughs]
[ASANO] And of course
Nagai's diligence.
You see?
Each of you has your very own
strength, but you're right.
I do have my work
cut out for me.
To properly teach you,
I'm going to need to
have all your strengths
combined and more.
[STUDENTS sigh]
[ASANO]
The private cram school
was off to a promising start.
Three students of my
inaugural term were ideal.
In the peace and quiet
of the mountain
I could shape their minds
to my heart's content.
A model education.
My dream come true.
Ow!
Aw c'mon, don't be a baby.
I gave you a heads-up.
Next time move.
What're you, a snail?
Uh. We just got out.
Really? Why're you so rowdy?
Whatever. Basketball
stars can't just study!
Gimme a break.
I've got tons of pent-up energy!
[ASANO] You don't say?
A basketball star?
Heh. Fine dream.
[STUDENTS sigh]
[ASANO] How 'bout you and I
play a little one-on-one?
[IKEDA]
U-Uh. Yeah, right!
Like I could win
against a superhuman!
Good point.
I have one or two abilities
you haven't cultivated in
yourself just yet, huh?
[IKEDA grunts]
[ASANO]
Interesting.
Your classmates could just as
well say the same about you.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[IKEDA]
I, uh, sorry, Nagai.
[NAGAI]
Oh, it's cool.
[ASANO]
Everyone has faults.
We all have to grow
into our strength,
but also come to understand how
it affects those around us.
I put everything I had into
my daily lesson plans.
In just one year the students
were coming along brilliantly.
[ASANO]
What's this?
[MORI] A Kunugi oak-leaf
tie clip! Neat, huh?
[NAGAI] We pooled our
allowances together to buy it.
[IKEDA] Pro'ly peanuts
compared to what you make
off your stock portfolio.
Now, now.
Just because it's grown
a thousand percent--
[STUDENTS]
Wow.
You seriously could've
kept that to yourself.
I... I'll cherish this.
Ha, ha. Hey, you got us into
our first-pick schools!
Yeah! No way we could've
done it without you!
When I grow up, sir.
D'you, mind if I come
and visit some time?
[ASANO]
How time flies.
They'd grown into such
wonderful students.
[ASANO]
Parents saw my track record.
Soon, children enrolled
from all over.
Three short years later, my
little cram school was booming.
[ASANO]
Ah! How long has it been?
Ikeda! Great to hear from you!
[IKEDA]
Long time no see!
Things are going
good for you, huh?
[ASANO] Can't complain.
What can I do for you?
Oh, nothin' really.
I just wanted to catch up
and see how you were doin'.
[ASANO]
That's very kind. Thank you.
Uh, ah, what about you?
Not out there causing
trouble, I hope?
[IKEDA]
Ha! No sir!
I'm just a regular Samaritan
now, thanks to you!
Anyway, you sound busy.
I should let you go.
Let's do dinner sometime!
Your treat, of course.
Later!
[ASANO] I have business in that
neck of the woods next week.
Perhaps I'll stop by.
[ASANO gasps]
[NEIGHBOR A]
They said it was a suicide.
[NEIGHBOR B] Some horrible
older boy on his team
drove him to it, apparently.
Used to beat him up,
and take his money.
Poor thing couldn't
take it anymore.
[NEIGHBOR A]
That's awful!
And he'd been such a sweet
boy since junior high.
[NEIGHBOR B]
Still, though.
I mean, you'd think the young
man would stand up for himself.
[ASANO] What on earth have I
been teaching these children?
How to be good students?
What was I thinking?
Does dying make you
a good student?
I have an obligation
to make them strong,
or this will have
been for nothing.
But then, what is strength?
[ASANO] Until I have the answer,
I have no right to teach.
[ASANO] From there,
things changed quickly.
I learned all sorts
of strengths.
I sweet-talked the men who
drove my student to suicide,
put them on the road toward a
disastrous gambling addiction.
That's how I fine-tuned my
brainwashing techniques.
Soon, I opened another school,
and the old campus building
that symbolized my weakness
would stand as a
lesson to others.
Strong. I wanted to
make them strong.
Strong young men and
women who could survive,
sacrificing others if need be.
[ASANO]
To that end,
I would need more
funding, more staff.
If it could serve my
goal, I would use it.
All to educate, to
breed true strength.
[ASANO]
Yet here I stand,
abandoned by the strong
and the weak alike.
The only thing before me,
certain death.
[KORO-SENSEI]
What will it be, Principal?
Will you open the
last book, or fold?
You may be an exceptional
human being, sir,
but taking a grenade blast
won't end well for you.
[YOSHIDA] This was your
idea, 'case you forgot!
But hey it's no big deal,
just gracefully admit defeat.
And just so you're aware,
fire Koro-sensei all you want,
it doesn't make any
difference to us.
Don't get us wrong,
it'll be sad to leave
this place behind.
But whatever comes, we're
going right along with him.
[ISOGAI]
That's right!
Even if we gotta run away from
home, or hole up in a cave!
We'll keep this class going.
It's not over until March!
[ASANO] Why have I
indulged them this far?
E-Class has been a thorn
in my side all year.
Such presumptuous, bald-faced
defiance. Such a stain.
[ASANO]
Koro-sensei.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Eh?
[ASANO]
You may well destroy the Earth.
Even so, as far as my
educational philosophy,
it would make absolutely
no difference whatsoever.
[gasp]
[ASANO]
Whether now, or in March,
death will come for
us all in the end.
[ASANO]
Strength won't matter.
My students won't suffer
alone, and, in a way,
my vision will have
been fulfilled.
[KORO-SENSEI laughs]
Somebody forgot about my molt.
[ASANO]
Your once-a-month trick?
And why precisely would you
not use it on yourself?
[KORO-SENSEI] Because I was
saving it for you, silly man.
I suspected if I won, odds were
fairly good you'd think nothing
of blowing yourself to bits.
[ASANO] But, how could you
be so sure of what I'd do?
[KORO-SENSEI] Because,
we have a lot in common.
[ASANO gasps]
[KORO-SENSEI] We're both
stubborn education fiends,
willing to forfeit our lives
for the privilege of
molding young minds.
I hope you won't mind,
but I took the
liberty of speaking
to your old cram
school students.
I wanted to get their
impressions of you as a teacher.
Imagine my surprise
upon learning
that the idea of teaching you
exemplified 12 years ago
is identical to mine.
Though as far as students are
concerned, I've been lucky.
E-Class is a marvelous
proving ground.
There are a fair number
of students, you see,
and they all share the
same predicament.
These boys and girls
work as a team,
unafraid to ask for help
or to hold each other up.
And if I may point out,
credit for conceiving of and
implementing this class,
goes first and foremost to you.
[KORO-SENSEI] There you have it.
Don't you see, sir?
You've been abiding by the same
vision you began with all along.
Incidentally, I'm the only
thing this knife can kill.
The taking of human life plays
no part in our approach.
You and I are one and
the same, Principal.
We don't teach killing,
we teach life.
So why not stay
true to ourselves
and continue down this road?
[ASANO]
Playing outdoors is fine, Ikeda.
Playing hooky? I don't think so.
Heh. I'm an athlete.
I can't be cooped up.
Right? Gimme a break!
I propose a game.
Once every school day.
You have my permission
to try and attack me.
Manage to get a hit and I'll let
you skip class for that day.
[IKEDA] You serious?!
You'd really let me do that?!
[ASANO]
Sure.
You gotta deal, sir!
If I hit ya, I get to
ditch! No take-backs.
You have to see it through!
My philosophy's always
been right on the nose.
Students have to be strong.
My successes over the
past 12 years prove this.
And, I suppose, so long you
acknowledge its proper function,
I see no reason why
you and E-Class
can't remain here as you are.
[KORO-SENSEI laughs] Still too
proud to admit defeat, I see.
[ASANO]
Oh, and do mind if pop by
and try my hand at killing
you once in a while?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Be my guest.
Always happy to oblige
a worthy rival.
That pristine façade
is crumbling.
You've lost. I can
tell by your face.
Something I can help
you with, Asano?
No, no. Just thought I'd
come by to cheer you up.
That and show you
my wounded face.
Perhaps some monetary
compensation
would help ease the pain a bit?
[ASANO] Ha, ha. Feel free
to take me to court.
Though of course,
don't expect to win.
You'll never win
against me, Asano.
No matter how strong
you think you've become.
[GAKUSHU] And what makes
you so certain of that?
Because I don't intend
to ever stop growing.
As a teacher. Or as a father.
[HINANO]
So, yeah. About that reward?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Huh? Oh, yes!
In return for ranking
in the top 50,
I promised to share
a critical weakness.
Well, children,
I have in fact very little
power. I'm designed for speed.
When at a perfect standstill,
one of my tentacles can be held
down even by a single person.
Hey, wait, if eight of us
teamed-up on you all at once--
You're saying we could
essentially paralyze you, right?
[OKAJIMA] Man, if we
had known that sooner,
this would have
been easy as pie!
[MAEHARA]
This is bunk!
You only told us 'cause you
knew it'd be impossible!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Not having any luck?
The trick is to pretend you're
hand-fishing for slime eels.
[STUDENTS]
A drama festival?!
[MAEHARA] But we're about to
take high school entrance exams.
[ISOGAI]
I know, I know.
I did complain to
the student council.
Asano fired back, though.
[GAKUSHU]
What's the problem?
Memorizing lines and stage
directions quickly
is good mental exercise.
It's part of the curriculum.
Besides, you'll figure
something out.
You always do.
At least he gave us respect.
[KARMA] You could be
the leading lady, Nagisa!
Just, y'know,
throwin' it out there.
[NAGISA] Why do I get a
bad feeling about this?
[KANZAKI]
What about Kayano?
[KAEDE]
Huh?
The preschoolers adored you.
You had 'em on the
edge of their seats.
Um, I don't know if that--
[TERASAKA] That ain't gonna
play in junior high.
People need to identify
with the main character,
and you're too short.
[KAEDE]
Shut up!
I'd rather be in charge
of handling props anyway.
[SUGINO, NAGISA]
Uh...
Right.
So then for our main crew,
Mimura will direct,
and Hazam will write, naturally.
[KIRARA]
Mm?
[ISOGAI]
Thoughts on our leads?
[KORO-SENSEI]
You know, I'm available.
[OKAJIMA] You're supposed
to be a state secret!
[MAEHARA] This is our play!
No adults allowed!
[KORO-SENSEI] But I have the
makings of a phenomenal lead!
What if this is my
one and only shot?
You can't deny me the limelight!
All right, then.
I have a play.
One where you can be the
lead without upstaging us.
Everybody's happy.
[KORO-SENSEI laughing]
[ISOGAI]
Great. Sounds like plan.
[MAEHARA] Let's put on a
show the likes of which
those main campus
chumps have never seen!
[buzzing]
[TANAKA]
Okay. E-Class goes on next.
Heh.
I say we eat loudly and sneer
through the entire performance!
[KANZAKI]
A peach.
[BOTH]
Uh...
The greatest medical
minds are baffled,
but by some strange miracle
there's a baby growing inside.
[RITSU] Upon hearing this,
the old man's eyes lit up.
"Excellent," he thought.
"This peach will bring riches!"
[SUGINO] What a stroke of
luck! A miracle indeed!
People will pay good money
to see this peach!
They'll come from far and wide!
I'll be richer than any king!
Mm?
[RITSU]
Divorce papers.
The old woman had been thinking
of leaving him for some time.
His greed, choice of words,
and complete disregard for
child welfare decided her.
At long last, she's had enough
of his selfish nature.
The marriage was over.
For good.
[RITSU] The rift between
them was as wide
as the river in which
she'd washed his clothes
for over 30 years without
thanks or acknowledgement.
The atmosphere at home had
become as dry and as suffocating
as the smoke from
a mountain wildfire.
The peach rightfully
belongs to me.
I am the head of this household,
do you understand woman?!
I'll decide how to
divide our property!
Uh?!
[RITSU]
Lawyers.
[TAKEBAYASHI]
We'll be representing your wife
from here on out. Any
and all communication
must be handled through
our office directly.
Regarding the miracle peach.
Since this marriage has
technically been on the rocks
for over a decade, we're
well past the mandated
cut-off date for carving
up your combined assets.
Oh, and fair warning: our client
is seeking reparations
for emotional distress.
[RITSU] For 30 years she'd
born her husband's cruelty,
his disinterest.
Not only had he consistently
failed to bring home the bacon,
the old woman possessed
incontrovertible evidence
of his infidelity.
In court, he wouldn't
have a prayer.
In desperation he hired a band
of thugs to strong-arm her.
But, being incompetent, they
were hauled off by police.
The old woman shed her
misery and started over.
She gave the miracle peach pride
of place in her lovely new home.
Life was sweet, as it
had been in her youth.
Happiness and serenity
surrounded her.
[KANZAKI]
Hooray!
[RITSU] A dog, a monkey,
and a pheasant.
An unlikely trio, trained
to attack human beings,
devouring their food with
the abandon of wild animals,
in thrall to their
wicked master.
All-consuming greed had
driven the old man
to unspeakable evil.
Perhaps the fabled demon-haunted
island of Onigashima
is none other than
the human heart?
The miracle peach will
bear its child very soon.
Will it, too, be prey to demons?
[KORO-SENSEI laughs]
[TANAKA]
Uh...
[STUDENTS chattering]
Great. My appetite's ruined!
[KIRARA chuckles] Say what you
will about my writing style,
words leave an
unmistakable mark.
[KORO-SENSEI] I did it!
I transported them!
What the hell did I
just sit through?
[ASANO] He has my school
in his grip as surely
as if his very tentacles were
wrapped around the campus.
Even so, carefree
though they seem,
E-Class won't get a fairy
tale sort of ending.
The Ministry of Defense
has big plans, and yet,
based on my experience
of such things,
the only person qualified to
predict what may happen next,
is me.
I can't help but wonder,
Koro-sensei.
Can one be a teacher amidst
the coming storm?
[KUNUDON]
Surprise!
[CHILDREN]
Not needed, Kunudon!
[ASANO] Now that he's
served his purpose,
Kunigigaoka's beloved mascot has
been transferred to E-Class.
[KUNUDON] Huh? Hey!
What are you lookin' at?
Yeah, that's right:
I used to be somebody!
[CHILDREN]
Yay for unemployment!
Bye-bye, Kunadon!