[KARASUMA]
The target is liquidated.
The planet is safe.
Your hard work over the
past year has paid off.
I imagine you'll find a few
things difficult to swallow.
Being stuck under constant
surveillance, for example,
or the fact that you've all
been slapped with a gag order.
Naturally, I'll do whatever
I can to lessen the burden.
My apologies in advance
for the inconvenience.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[MAEHARA] It's all right,
Mr. Karasuma. We'll be fine.
No worries. Whatever settles
this, we're on board.
We can handle it.
Seriously, we don't wanna
complicate things for you.
That said, though, we do
have one tiny request.
[BOTH]
Hm?
Kunugigaoka's graduation
ceremony is this afternoon, sir.
I think we've earned the
right to be a part of it.
Let us walk across the stage in
honor of Koro-sensei's memory.
[KARASUMA]
Mm.
Sure. Yes, of course.
I'll handle things and make
the necessary arrangements.
E-Class, rise!
[ISOGAI]
Mr. Karasuma. Professor Bitch.
For everything you've taught us,
we are eternaly grateful.
[STUDENTS]
We are eternally grateful!
[MAEHARA] So, where's
the ceremony exactly?
[SUGAYA]
Main campus is on lockdown.
They're probably having
it at the civic center.
[OKAJIMA] Our parents are gonna
have to bring our uniforms.
[KARASUMA] They've been to Hell
and back, and look at 'em.
So tough.
Are these the same
kids from a year ago?
[NAGISA] For all his advice,
Koro-sensei never said anything
about the E-Class
system being unjust,
or that we should try
to spark a change.
[EMCEE]
Hinano Kurahashi.
Sir!
[NAGISA] There's no
shortage of absurdities
in the world, I guess.
I say if you have the time
and energy to brood on them...
[EMCEE]
Nagisa Shiota!
Sir!
[NAGISA] ...you have
time to subvert them,
maybe even have a little
fun in the process.
[ASANO]
My, what a confident look.
No doubt we have your
former instructor to thank.
[NAGISA]
A word of advice, sir.
Maybe go a little easier on
your students from now on.
See ya 'round!
[OKANO]
What a nice little ceremony.
[NAKAMURA]
I was moved.
[OKANO]
Me, too!
[gasps]
[NAGISA]
Mom. Dad.
What're you doing
here... together?
Kind of surprising, huh?
At the end of last
month your, uh,
teacher paid me a little visit.
[gasps]
[KORO-SENSEI] Right off the bat,
your son asked for a favor.
He prefers to be called
by his first name,
as opposed to his last, you see.
So there won't be
any awkwardness
if he goes back to using
his father's name.
He wanted to nip that in the bud
before it became an issue.
He's a good student.
I have no complaints.
All signs point toward Nagisa
meeting his goals by mid-March.
All I ask... is that you give
his graduation your blessing,
as a family.
He and your mother told me
how hard you've worked.
It takes a lot of determination
to come as far as you have, Son.
We've, been talking, and
feel it's best for everyone
if we follow your example and
give our marriage another shot.
[HIROMI gasps]
[NAGISA]
How much of himself...
...did our teacher
need to leave behind?
[REPORTER A] Ceremony's over!
They're letting out!
[REPORTER B]
Time to get some reactions!
[ALL gasp]
--[REPORTER C] E-Class!
--[KARASUMA] Easy, folks!
This place is off limits
to the media!
[REPORTER D] Tell us about
the monster! Did he die?
How did he die?
[REPORTER F] Can you tell us
how your feeling at the moment?
[REPORTER E] Are you kids
really the ones who killed him?
[REPORTER G] Gimme a break!
I'm tryin' to do my job!
[KARASUMA]
Have you no shame!
These children have already
been through enough!
You're all vultures!
[REPORTER H]
Yeah, yeah.
[KARASUMA] All right,
everybody outside, now!
There's a bus on standby
at the main gate!
[REPORTER I]
Excuse me-- Ow!
[REPORTER J]
Hey! What the--?!
[REPORTER K]
What's the big idea?!
[REPORTER L] You're messin'
with our coverage!
[GAKUSHU]
Hmph.
Ugh... Coverage?
You people are messing
with our moment in the sun!
Y'know, the internet's gonna
go nuts when I post this.
Remember, we know what
you look like, scum! Ha!
[chuckles]
There. Nothing to
worry about, love.
Permit us to be your
escort to the front gate.
[GAKUSHU] With graduation
comes a clean slate.
But abandoning former classmates
in their time of need
would be disgraceful.
I may be ruthless,
but as your future leader,
I'm not about to court shame.
[GAKUSHU]
Akabane.
Seems like you're the
only one coming back.
Fair warning,
when all this is over,
I'll put you on the
rack if I have to.
This Koro-sensei
seems fascinating.
You're going to give me
all the gory details.
[KARMA] I mean, I could,
but thick-skulled as you are,
you might struggle
to understand.
Move it. You're bringin'
up the rear.
[NAGISA]
Whoa!
Off you go.
[ALL chuckle]
[NAGISA]
So many reasons to cry.
[NAGISA] A day like today
I'll never see again.
[NAGISA] Goodbye,
Kunugigaoka Junior High.
Goodbye, Class 3-E.
Goodbye...
...Koro-sensei.
[NAGISA] Afterwards,
lots of stuff went down.
Kunugigaoka came under fire
for involving its students
in an assassination plot.
The whole concept of E-Class
was abolished, thankfully.
After we left,
the old mountainside building
shut its doors for good.
As for the principal,
he was tried in the
court of public opinion
and forced to resign.
Of course, he is who he is.
Something tells me
he had a backup plan.
Whatever else can
be said about him,
there's no denying he's
a man of conviction.
We haven't seen the last of him.
He'll be back on
his feet in no time.
[NAGAI] Anything you need,
sir, we're glad to help.
[ASANO]
Ah! Nagi! Mori! It's been years!
[NAGAI]
We heard you're having trouble,
and were worried about you.
[MORI] Not just you, actually,
all the kids that came after us.
Please, sir, there has to be
something we can do for you.
Let us help an old mentor
in his darkest hour.
In point of fact,
your timing is excellent.
You two can help me celebrate.
I've been saving this bottle.
New beginnings are rather high
on the list of reasons to toast.
Raise a glass with me.
Get me up to speed on your
lives. I'll air my complaints.
[BOTH gasp]
We're glad to lend you an ear.
[MORI]
All three of us.
[NAGISA]
The bounty was promptly paid.
[STUDENTS gasping]
[NAGISA]
No fuss. Just cold, hard cash.
Hush money, really.
Mr. Karasuma told us as
much and we understood.
So... all that was left
was how to spend it.
We consulted "Koro-sensei's
Rules to Live By."
[KORO-SENSEI] The accomplishment
is its own reward.
Nothing stunts your growth
quite like immediate access
to troves of money.
[NAGISA]
With that in mind,
we all set aside a little
something to live on,
college tuition, charitable
donations we believed in,
and one big-ticket item that
we purchased as a class.
The rest of it, we gave
back to the government
as a thank you for the
incredible year they'd given us.
Mr. Karasuma, excuse me,
Agent Karasuma's
career is sure to take off.
Slowly, the crescent
moon began to crumble.
Under its own gravity,
it would end up a much
smaller sphere than before.
The explosion had
moved it, though.
It now orbited a lot
closer to Earth.
After a while,
the shape, size, gravitational
pull, what have you,
would come to resemble the moon
as we'd known it all our lives.
The crescent that symbolized
our year together...
...ever so gradually...
would forget its shape.
[KARASUMA]
There's sectarian violence
brewing in the Middle East.
A group of radicals
is on the warpath.
We need a sleeper agent.
An operative who's willing
to infiltrate enemy ranks.
You'll ship out tomorrow,
understood?
Yeah. Sure. If that's the job.
[chuckles]
Oh, but I'm scared!
Whatever shall I do, Chief?
Imagine a sumptuous
creature like moi
getting captured
in hostile territory.
Or does the idea get
your motor running?
Your poor, defenseless wife
having all sorts of
horrible things done to her
by burly men in the desert.
[KARASUMA] This assignment
reflects my faith
in your abilities,
but if you genuinely
see yourself
as poor and defenseless...
Ugh. Well then.
You give me no choice but
to assign someone else.
[IRINA]
Uh!
Wait! It was a joke!
Is it too much to ask for you to
show a teensy bit of concern?!
C'mon, sweetie!
Don't be this way!
[IRINA cries]
So are you going or not?
Yes! Yes!
[KARASUMA]
Then go get ready!
[IRINA]
Sir! With pleasure!
[sighs]
[KARASUMA] It's been seven
years since we've met.
She hasn't changed... at all.
[KARASUMA]
I think about those kids.
Our kids.
Whatever became
of them, I wonder.
What're they doing
with their lives?
[MAEHARA]
Ooo! We have a celebrity!
[KAEDE]
Hi, guys!
[ALL chuckling]
Look at you! You're in costume?
Are you sure you've
got time for all this?
Sure! I snuck off the set
during my lunch break.
I can't let you do the
heavy lifting without me.
[ISOGAI]
Awesome!
Okay, people, let's get
this place up to code!
[ALL]
All right!
[MEG] Yep! Class
President till the end!
[ISOGAI]
Hey now,
you're the ones who wanted
me to hold on to the keys.
[MAEHARA]
What can we say, man?
We know who best to delegate
this sort of thing to.
[ALL chattering]
Hey. You ever finish reading
Koro-sensei's advice book?
Nowhere near, actually.
It never ends.
Place is gettin' rough
around the edges again.
We shoulda hired a groundskeeper
when we bought the mountain.
We can handle it.
If you let it get messy,
you clean it up.
That's one of the
old rules, remember?
Wow. Talk about hitting
the big time, Kayano.
You've made it!
[MAEHARA] You bet she has.
She's got the look.
She can do her own stunts.
Did you see her
dive off that cliff
like she was jumping into bed?
It'd be weird if
she hadn't made it!
Oh, come on.
I'm just using all the
cool stuff I learned here.
Hey, uh, Okajima?
Could you stop playing paparazzi
and get back to work, please?
[KAEDE] We wanted a memorial
to visit, but not a grave.
[KAEDE] After all, it didn't
feel like they were gone.
This is their home, a place
where they can dwell in peace.
Somewhere those who love
them can always come back to.
I've been thinking, guys.
We really oughta put this
place to good use, y'know?
Preserving it's fine and all,
but it doesn't feel like enough.
[MAEHARA] Okano's using the back
of the mountain a lot lately.
You know she put together
an acrobatic performance squad
for her college, right?
Said this was the training
ground she's used to,
so why not?
Okay, let's run the
circuit! Try to keep up!
[OKANO]
Let's see some hustle!
[ALL gasp]
[MAEHARA]
Pretty sweet, huh?
And recently Kurahashi started
giving nature tours to kids.
No kidding?
Well, she's always known
how to make money.
[HINANO] Here we go!
Are we all ready?
Be careful where you step, okay?
[CHILDREN]
Okay!
[KAEDE]
Huh.
We've grown up exactly as
Koro-sensei taught us to.
Just look at Manami
and Takebayashi.
They've literally taken a
page from our life manuals
and put it to good use.
Koro-sensei hinted at
a cell activation recipe
they're now researching
to make artificial blood.
Dear God. The lives we can save.
The number is mind-boggling!
Well, Okuda handled
the development phase.
Credit goes to her.
Personally I'm eager to
explore the clinical side.
Our, uh, name for it is
"Rh Slither Blood."
[KAEDE]
And there's Sugino,
who's become a
college baseball star.
[UMPIRE]
Strike three!
--[CROWD cheering]
--Yeah!
[KAEDE]
His versatile pitching style
caught the eye of pro
scouts from all over.
Incredible. So the
rumors are all true.
They don't call him
"Slithery Sugino" for nothin'!
[KAEDE] As for Terasaka,
his particular skills
caught the eye of a certain
professor politician.
Hop to! Ugh!
We're late enough as it is!
Damn it, kid.
Are you a man or a mouse?
Son of a bitch. Way to drive
me like a mule, you old fart!
[KAEDE]
Once he's out of college,
he'll be promoted to
personal assistant.
Yoshida and Muramatsu
are thriving.
They've taken over
the family businesses.
Purrin' like a baby kitten.
Ha-ha. I guess so.
[MURAMATSU'S FATHER]
Takuya! Get a load of this!
Heh! Makes your mouth
water, doesn't it?
[MURAMATSU]
Uh!
You have any idea how
much that thing cost?
How the hell are we supposed
to make a profit, genius?!
[KAEDE] Itona went to work
in his father's factory
right after high school.
Well, if this doesn't do
the trick, I know some guys.
They'd be happy to come
help me out with it.
[KAEDE]
So he's good.
Speaking of technical stuff,
Ritsu's completely online now.
[RITSU]
I'm parallel processing
with computers from
every corner of the globe!
I can make songs. I can draw.
I can explore my
emotional range!
[KAEDE] Yep. She's living
the life. A free spirit.
And she loves nothing more than
to help out her old classmates.
That's what we're up to.
Adapting ourselves as necessary,
seeing where life takes us.
Oh! D'you here about Karma?
Dude, he passed the national
civil service exam
with flying colors.
Yeah, I'm not surprised.
Good luck seein'
him tank, right?
Yeah, well, they say
the hard part comes after.
He's good, sure, but now
there'll be a lot of red tape.
Tons of interviews. Training.
Interdepartmental hazing.
Of course, if anyone can thrive
in that environment, it's him.
[KARMA]
Huh.
Gotta say, I'm likin' the
looks of my new wallet.
[KAEDE]
Yeah. He's gonna be just fine.
As a matter of fact, we all are.
[chuckles] Wait! Stop!
I wasn't ready! Oh!
[MEG growls]
O-ka-ji-maaa.
[screams]
[MEG] What part of your brain
told you that was a good idea?!
[OKAJIMA]
It was an accident! I swear! Ah!
[KAEDE]
Honestly,
I think whatever path
we chose in life,
it's a safe bet Koro-sensei
would've approved.
I can see him saying,
"It suits you."
We had one year together.
You can live a lot of
different lives in that time.
They become part of you.
They become your guide.
Your world.
[KAEDE]
There's the life of pride...
Outrageous! This is
ten times the estimate!
Don't you dare! I'm an artist;
I charge what I'm worth!
[KAEDE]
The life of service...
I thought we'd visit
the park today.
Is that something you'd like?
[KAEDE]
The life we're given...
I know! That show has
totally gone off the rails!
[KAEDE] The life we hope
to bring into the world...
Whatever happens...
we're connected.
Every one of us. Forever.
Trading lives back and forth,
across a classroom
steeped in bloodlust.
This classroom.
Our tribute to Koro-sensei.
And who knows?
Maybe one day a new generation
will live as many
lives here as we did.
So, tell me the truth.
Have you been keeping
in touch with Nagisa?
What's the story there?
Well.
There isn't one.
I'm not really on his
radar these days, sadly.
You know how he is.
Always keeping his
eye on the target.
Okey dokey! Hey, class!
I'm your teacher in training,
Nagisa Shiota.
Pleased to meet you.
[NAGISA]
It's been seven years.
I'm way taller
than I used to be,
and I'm a beloved teacher.
[NAGISA]
In my dreams, at least.
A teacher in training?!
You gotta be shittin' me!
C'mon, guys, leave
the poor girl alone!
[DELINQUENT D]
Why're you dressed like a boy?!
[DELINQUENT E]
What're you? Junior High?
[NAGISA]
Life is so unfair.
You'd think I'd
have a few inches
on my Junior High self by now.
Everyone else
shot up like weeds.
And Karma?
He's over six feet
tall now! No, seriously!
For my training, they put me
in the last circle of Hell.
Nothing like our
Assassination Classroom.
Totally different dynamic.
[DELINQUENT A] You have any
idea the hurt you're in for
in this place?
[DELINQUENT C] From now on this
is a study hall, you got that?
Uh, the bell's rung.
I'd like to ask you to
take your seats, please.
Oh-ho, that's cute!
[DELINQUENTS chuckling]
Shut up. You don't get
to boss us around.
We'll kill you.
What?
[NAGISA]
Kill... me?
[DELINQUENTS gasp]
[NAGISA]
Interesting word... kill.
Evocative, but overused.
It's lost some of its mojo.
[NAGISA]
For some of us, though,
it still holds the
right kind of magic.
[LEADER yelps]
[DELINQUENTS gasping]
[LEADER whimpering]
You're welcome to try.
[LEADER]
Huh?
[NAGISA]
You have until graduation.
All right, people.
Let's get started, shall we?