[KAEDE] I've gathered
you all here today,
even though we're
still on break,
for a very important reason:
Our nation's current
egg surplus crisis!
Poultry farmers across the land
are throwing out
their excess in bulk!
[ISOGAI] Right. I heard
about that on the news.
It's a real waste.
It is!
So I've drafted a proposal
to salvage those eggs,
and assassinate
Koro-sensei in a way
that's almost guaranteed
to be foolproof!
We're killing him
with surplus eggs?
What? You gonna
make an omelet?
Throw in a couple
of these babies?
Like he won't see that
comin' from a mile away.
[giggles] I gave it a little
bit more thought than that.
In fact, my plan's already in
motion, thanks to Mr. Karasuma.
Right. All the stuff you
need's been set up outside.
Egg-cellent! Everybody
to the yard!
[KARASUMA] They're creative,
I'll give 'em that.
How they come up with this
stuff, I'll never know.
[STUDENTS]
Whoa.
[OKUDA] So we have a ton of eggs
and a mold. Are we making...?
[KAEDE] Yep! It's
exactly what you think.
We are going to whip up
a ginormous pudding!
I give you...
Operation Pudding Popper!
[NAGISA]
Operation Pudding Popper, huh?
Well, Koro-sensei does have
a pretty serious sweet tooth.
[KAEDE]
Bingo!
And the target's recent crucial
confession only confirms it!
[KAEDE] You'd scarf down a
mountain of these if you could.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Oh, without question!
What a dream come true it
would be to gorge myself
on a mountain of pudding!
Too bad I don't have the
funds to make it happen.
So, let's make that
crazy dream a reality!
Saving some for
ourselves, of course.
[NAGISA chuckles nervously]
[KAEDE] The idea is to plant
bombs and anti-Sensei BB's
into the giant pudding's base.
When he eats his way to
the bottom, we detonate.
[KORO-SENSEI screaming]
This is starting to sound
like it's worth a shot.
I'm with you on that.
Koro-sensei loses his marbles
when it comes to anything sweet.
[TAKEBAYASHI] And since Kayano's
usually not that proactive,
there's the element of surprise.
He won't be suspicious.
[ISOGAI]
All right then!
Let's wait till he's not around
and make ourselves
a giant pudding!
[STUDENTS]
Yeah!
[KAEDE] This equipment comes
from an inactive line
at a mayonnaise factory.
Once the eggs are prepped,
they'll be going in here.
Step one: Crack 'em.
Step two: With help
from the government,
we do the mixing manually.
It's a lot of work,
but eyes on the prize.
Step three: Add sugar and milk.
Lots of it. Plus some vanilla
extract to give it flavor.
[HINANO]
Hey, Kaede?
I saw them try to make a
giant pudding on TV once,
and it didn't work.
It weighed too much. Totally
collapsed. Just sayin'.
That thought occurred to me,
which is why we're
using gelatin and agar.
Not common for pudding.
The agar's fibers make
it a great coagulant.
Plus, did you know that it has
a significantly higher
melting point than gelatin,
making it perfect for
keeping our pudding firm
in the September heat?
[SUGAYA, HINANO]
Whoa.
[KAEDE] Commence pouring
in the first batch!
[KAEDE]
That's the way!
Once that's all in, swap out
with Team Second Batch!
We'll increase the ratio
of cream as we go up,
maintaining firmness while
ensuring the lower layers
don't bear too much weight.
And what're these for?
Fruit sauce in edible
mousse wrappers
to add the occasional
burst of new flavor.
Vanilla is scrumptious
and all, but think about it,
wouldn't you get sick of
the same taste bite after bite
in something so large?
Sure you would!
Okay, that's great.
Once the mold's full,
drop the lid on
and let the whole thing chill.
This isn't just any old
pudding mold, either.
The outer walls are
fitted with pipes
that have coolant
circulating through them.
Pretty neat, huh?
A pudding with this much volume
needs to be chilled through.
We're talkin' inside and out.
[STUDENTS]
Wow.
Who in the world
would've ever thought
you could be an expert
on giant pudding?
She's got the
engineering part down pat.
And she knows how to
make it taste great.
[KARMA]
Nice work, Kayano.
You really thought all this
up after reading an article
on the country's egg surplus?
[KAEDE]
Sorta.
Actually, I've wanted to try
and do this for a while now.
And since the Ministry
of Defense was willing
to shell out the
money this time,
I figured why not go for it?
When my mind's
fixed on something,
I just keep rolling, I guess.
[NAGISA]
Most of the time,
Kayano's more in the
background than center stage.
That's probably why
I've always pegged her
as the supporting role type.
But look at her now.
I never imagined she
could get so fired up.
Proof anyone can shine when what
they're into becomes relevant.
[KAEDE] We've got another
early day tomorrow.
[KAEDE] Once we've let
it chill overnight,
we check to see if
it's firmed up enough.
If it is, we remove the pipes.
[KAEDE]
After that,
we loosen the bolts
holding the lid in place.
Then we blow air between
the walls of the mold
and the pudding itself.
Next...
Release internal lock!
[KAEDE] When the pudding is
completely free of the mold,
we carefully shore up the sides
with softened gelatin and agar
to add just a bit more firmness.
Then we top it off
with a caramel sauce.
And lightly brulee the top!
[STUDENTS]
We did it!
Wow! That looks sure delicious!
You completely forget there's
a bomb planted in there!
[NAGISA]
And with that,
Kayano's gigantic killer
pudding was ready to be served.
[KORO-SENSEI]
And-And I'm allowed to eat
this entire thing?
[KAEDE]
Oh, uh, sure.
I just didn't want those
eggs going to some landfill.
This was all Kayano's
idea, you know.
[KAEDE chuckles]
[KORO-SENSEI]
You've made me so happy!
[NAKAMURA]
We'd better get goin'.
[ISOGAI] Yeah. Don't wanna
be late for English.
Now, you've gotta promise
to eat every last bite!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Not a problem!
At last my dream's
come true! Thank you!
Come on. We'll watch the
detonation from inside.
Oh. Yeah, okay.
[SUGINO] Wow, he's
really gettin' after it.
I have a feeling it
won't be very long
till he reaches the bottom.
[TAKEBAYASHI]
Don't worry,
I've installed a security
camera into the base.
I'm keeping my eye on it.
The second he reaches the bomb,
we'll detonate it
by remote control.
We'll know he's eaten his way to
it once light starts pouring in.
My pudding. It'll be...
It'll be tastiest if the flavor
changes halfway through.
Ah, that makes sense.
I'll use a scale model to
test its strength first.
Aww! Not another collapse!
Pudding.
[KAEDE]
My pudding!
I can't let something I've
put my heart and soul into
be blown to smithereens!
Kayano, take it easy!
[TERASAKA] It's a damn pudding,
not the family pet!
It's supposed to be
blown to smithereens!
[KAEDE]
We can't!
It should stand in
the schoolyard forever
as a monument!
[STUDENTS]
Ew, gross!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Phew! My jaws need a break.
By the way, amid all
the deliciousness,
I caught a faint whiff of this.
[NAGISA] The bomb! And the
detonator's been detached!
[KORO-SENSEI] I ate a path from
caramel to pudding to dirt
and proceeded to tunnel
from underneath to remove it.
I assume the bomb was your
handy work, Takebayashi?
Well, your calculations
were spot on,
and if had I not picked
up the distinct scent
of plastic explosive,
your scheme might've
very well worked.
Next time, you'll account
for strange odors, right?
Right.
[KORO-SENSEI chuckles]
[KORO-SENSEI]
C'est la vie!
But since you worked together
to create this
wonderful concoction,
you should enjoy it together.
I set aside a nice, clean
portion for each of you.
So he gets the drop
on us yet again.
And it was such a
clever idea, too.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Incidentally,
consuming eggs headed for the
landfill is, strictly speaking,
a violation of sound
economic principles.
So, we'll be exploring
the complex role
of a perishable good surplus
in our next civics lesson.
[STUDENTS]
Yes, sir.
[NAGISA]
Kind of a shame, isn't it?
I bet you're relieved, though.
[KAEDE chuckles]
Honestly, no offense,
but I didn't think you had it
in you to be so hardcore.
It was cool to watch.
A nice change of pace.
[KARMA]
Mmm.
[chuckles]
That's what it is
to be an assassin.
Not even your close friends
get to see your true blade.
[KAEDE] Oh, yeah. There's
more where that came from.
I've got all kinds
of jiggly weapons.
Here even a pudding expert
can be a top-notch assassin.
[WOMAN A]
Huh?
[chuckling]
[gasps]
[WOMAN A screaming]
[NAGISA]
Once the break was over,
Mr. Karasuma got
down to business
and really ramped
up our training.
Today's P.E. class was a first.
Parkour crossed
with Cops n' Roppers.
The cops being our
toughest teachers.
[KORO-SENSEI]
How 'bout this?
If we manage to
round 'em all up,
they get double the homework.
Ugh, stop makin' this
about role play.
[KORO-SENSEI] Aw now, ain't
no reason it can't be fun.
You're just tryin' to hog all
the good times for yourself.
Puttin' me in charge a
holdin' down the fort.
What did you expect?
You can't be the chaser.
This is training.
[OKAJIMA] Mr. Karasuma will
catch up to us eventually,
but it's a big mountain!
And there's a time limit,
so at best he'll tag maybe
two or three of us, tops.
Yeah, if even that many.
[RYUNOSUKE]
No kidding.
[KARASUMA]
I heard that.
Ridge. Eighty meters. Boom.
[KARASUMA]
You're under arrest.
Caught ya' red-handed.
[ALL gasp]
Okajima. Hayami. Chiba.
Fuwa. You're out!
Dude, I'm tellin' ya,
don't get caught.
He's making us do
worksheets. It sucks.
[SUGAYA]
Come on.
This isn't some battle manga.
Seriously, how'd you not
know he was on your tail
till after he tagged you?
[OKAJIMA]
Look, just be careful.
He's like a ninja. For all
you know, he's right there.
[SUGAYA screaming]
Sugaya? Sugaya!
[IRINA chuckling]
[IRINA] Big man's on the
hunt all by his lonesome?
Well that works for me.
I'll just pull him down by his
tagging hand and booyah.
We'll go at it right
here in the wilderness.
"Bad Cop, Good Cop" will
take on a whole new meaning.
Bring it on, you son of a bi--!
Sugaya and Professor
Bitch, you're out!
Uh-oh. We're
droppin' like flies!
We should rename this
place Mount Slaughter!
They just got
tagged out, right?
Huh. Wait a second.
This is Cops n' Robbers.
Technically--
We can tag 'em back in!
Okuda, you're a genius!
Yeah, sure. Have fun.
Like anybody's
breakin' out of jail
with the supersonic
Octopus on duty.
If it was possible to
come in under his radar,
we'd have offed him months ago.
[SUGINO]
You have a point.
[OKAJIMA] Sugino?
You come to bust us out?
Ah-ha!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Yeah?
Ooh.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Just this one time.
[OKAJIMA]
Sugino! Now!
Five prisoners free.
[KARASUMA growls]
Damn it!
Mind explaining how prisoners
are escaping on your watch?
[KORO-SENSEI] They're shrewder
than we gave 'em credit for!
But good heavens! Those
things are really enormous!
[KARASUMA]
Are you taking bribes?
Look, whatever, if you let the
next group escape, so help me!
[TOKA]
Actually, Koro-sensei.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Yup?
My little brother's come
down with a rare illness.
Poor guy's been
bedridden for weeks.
When I told him what we're
playing, he texted back:
"Win one for me."
If he finds out I was captured,
the shock might be too much.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Go.
[gasps]
[KORO-SENSEI] This cop
never saw anything, so go.
[TOKA] Thank you, sir!
You're the best!
Four more prisoners free.
[KORO-SENSEI] Come in,
Karasuma! Do you copy?
How are these inmates
breaking out of my prison?
[KARASUMA]
That's my line, you moron!
Time's up! Game over!
Finally.
--Can't breathe. Need air.
--About friggin' time.
[growls]
[NAGISA]
When it was over,
our game of Cops n'
Robbers-slash-parkour
ended with us getting away.
Koro-sensei's stint as warden
left a lot to be desired
as far as Mr. Karasuma
was concerned.
But it was good training
for us either way, really.
Yep. Things were
going fairly well.
Second term was off
to a promising start.
No way.
[KORO-SENSEI] An excellent
beginning to second term,
it must be said.
The mutual respect and trust
the students and I share
grows stronger by the day.
How wonderful it is to
see their shining faces
look up at me with
such... unbridled disgust?
[OKANO] They're totally talking
about you, aren't they?
[MIMURA]
How could you do that stuff?
We're very disappointing
in you, sir.
[KORO-SENSEI]
No, wait! I'm innocent!
I don't even know
anything about this!
So, have an alibi?
[KORO-SENSEI]
A do what now?
Where were you on the evenings
of the incidents in question?
And can anybody back you up?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Let me see.
I was vigorously shaking
a bag of seasoned fries.
Alternating between an altitude
of ten thousand meters
and three thousand
meters, respectively.
[MIMURA]
No one can back that up!
That's enough, guys.
Come on, he's not a perv.
He's done some
creepy things, sure.
But even if you
add 'em all together,
what've you really got?
He's read some adult magazines.
Been bribed with dirty pictures
Stared intently at
pinups during recess.
Spammed lingerie companies
with requests to let him give
their models a tentacle bra.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Daddy help.
[ISOGAI] Koro-sensei,
just turn yourself in.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Et tu, Isogai?
This is an outrage!
I stand wrongfully accused!
Don't you believe me? Very well.
To the teacher's lounge!
I'll show you the kind of
upright citizen I can be!
Behold! My pinup stash.
I'll toss every last one of them
without so much as a
twinge of reservation--!
[BOTH gasp]
You're kidding.
Oh my god, guys!
Check out the roll book!
He put letters next to
all the girls' names.
Koro-sensei knows our cup sizes!
[KAEDE]
Huh?!
What the hell is "Forever
Flat" supposed to mean
you eight-armed, two-bit,
emoji-faced peeping tom?!
And what about this?
A breakdown of all the
girls in Kunugigaoka
with an F-cup or above?
[KORO-SENSEI] Wait, I...
That can't possibly...
[STUDENTS groaning]
[KORO-SENSEI chuckles nervously]
[KORO-SENSEI]
You know what we need?
A good, old-fashioned,
afterschool barbeque!
Doesn't that sound like fun?
Here!
Get a load of these succulent
skewers I threw together!
[chuckling]
Wow.
This is nauseating.
Gross.
[KORO-SENSEI] That... That's all
for today, b-boys and girls.
I, uh, I'll see you tomorrow.
[KARMA chuckles]
We certainly put the Octopus
through the ringer, didn't we?
Some people just
can't take the heat.
Is he stealing underwear?
That'd be pretty serious.
I mean, we're talkin'
an actual crime.
Compared to blowing up the
Earth? I say it's precious.
Okay, but...
[KARMA] I don't know what
I'd do with super speed,
but I can tell you one thing,
if I stole underwear,
I sure as hell wouldn't
be sloppy enough
to leave evidence behind.
[KARMA] I found that
in the equipment shed.
Koro-sensei's no fool.
He understands.
Knows he'd be dead to us
over something like this.
His whole life's about
being a teacher.
Between losing our respect
and being assassinated,
everyone knows which
of those things
he'd go more out of
his way to avoid.
Yeah. Have to agree with you.
Then who's the sicko
doing all this stuff?
[FUWA]
An impostor.
[KAEDE]
Fuwa?
That color. That laugh.
We're dealing with an archetype.
A fake sensei! The Double!
The Doppelgänger!
Oldest super villain
trope in the book!
Which means our culprit
is intimately familiar
with Koro-sensei and his quirks.
Hey, let's you and me
play detective, Ristu.
Yes!
Something along those lines.
As for what's in this
for the real culprit,
your guess is as good as mine.
But we gotta put a stop to him.
If the rumor mill runs
Koro-sensei out of town,
there goes our bounty, and
then what's all this been for?
We'll lose our shot at this.
If, on the other hand,
we catch the real guy ourselves,
Teach will be in our debt.
[FUWA, RITSU, NAGISA]
Yeah!
"Forever Flat."
Ha. Justice will prevail now
the great, and very mature,
detective is on the case.
You say "on the case,"
I say "exploiting our
parkour skills to trespass."
Hey, remind me again.
Of all the places in town,
what makes us so sure
the creeper's gonna
strike here next?
First off, this place is
a camp for pro entertainers.
The cincher, though?
A phenomenally popular,
bazonga-licous girl group
has been staying here for
the past couple of weeks.
[RITSU]
Right.
And based on the
suspect's profile,
the probability that
he'll show is 99.78%.
[FUWA] Indeed, because
camp's over after tomorrow.
And no way is our man gonna
let these top-tier trophies
slip through his fingers!
[TERASAKA]
Uh-huh.
[NAGISA]
Koro-sensei!
Okay, please say that he's
here to nab the bad guy, too.
That getup ain't exactly helpin'
me presume his innocence.
[FUWA] Look. He's so pissed
off at the real criminal,
just looking at all that
underwear gets him steamed.
[TERASAKA] Right.
Wrongfully accused my ass.
[KARMA]
Heads up.
[KAEDE]
Someone's here!
[NAGISA]
A big guy with a yellow head!
[FUWA]
I knew it!
[KARMA]
So it is a frame-up.
[TERASAKA] Look at him move,
that's not normal.
[KAEDE]
Uh-oh! He's getting away!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Gotcha!
How dare you impersonate me
and act out my lurid fantasies!
Well, so long as everyone thinks
I'm pilfering unmentionables,
I might as well take yours!
[KORO-SENSEI laughing]
I dunno.
I think this might make him
worse than an underwear thief.
Hey, the eyewitness reports
were right about his laugh.
[KORO-SENSEI] Now. Let's see
your true face, Imposter!
Hang on, isn't that that guy...
...Mr. Karasuma's underling?
[KORO-SENSEI]
You?
What earthy reason could
you have for--? Ah!
[ALL gasp]
[SHIRO]
The government was kind enough
to let me have one of
Karasuma's men on loan.
I required a decoy
to lure you into this pen
of anti-Sensei sheets.
[SHIRO] Not unlike the ruse your
students devised on the island,
yes?
Such nimble minds
the young have.
Lure, confine, and strike.
[KORO-SENSEI]
That voice.
[SHIRO]
Now, then, Koro-sensei.
Let your final death
match begin.
[ITONA]
So strong, but compared to me...
...so weak.