"Quit part-time job"
Thank you so much for everything, sir.
"Sell belongings"
For all of this, how does 30,000 sound.
"Bank"
I want to close out the account.
"Here's the money I owe you."
"The last day"
Everyone take your seats.
We have a new student that
will be joining our class today.
What do you want?
You're lucky Shoya. I heard it's a girl.
So what?
Like I care?
Okay class, this is Shoko. Would
you like to introduce yourself?
Huh?
"For written communication"
"Nice to meet you. I am Shoko Nishimiya."
"I want to be friends with
you all through this notebook."
"Please use this notebook
when you need to talk to me."
"
"I
"I c
"I ca
"I can
"I can'
"I can't
"I can't h
"I can't he
"I can't hea
"I can't hear
"I can't hear.
"I can't hear."
Holy crap!
"Hi, Nishimiya-san.
I am Miki Kawai."
Hi, nice to meet you.
Yoho! Hey there new girl, do
you know how to speak Japanese?
Come on! Naoka. That's not very nice.
"Once again please."
Ah I...
Huh?
Do - you - have - a - nickname?
How do you like that?
Come on! Take it.
What? Your nickname is Sho-?
Oh! Just like Shoya.
Hey! We have another "Sho" now.
Two "Shos" is pretty cool.
What? No it's not.
I'm gonna pants you!
Alright. Make sure to write this down.
The exercises on page 20 to pege 25, and page 32.
All of this will be on your next quiz.
Give me your notebook, ok?
Look at the diagram. At the center is the fulcrum.
The fulcrum is both the point
of rest and support for the lever.
It's the crux of any motion.
The placement of the fulcrum determines
how far the levered object will move.
For these...
Not yet Shoko,
y-you're coming in too early.
Watch me okay? Don't start singing till I start.
Okay, from the top.
Guess we want to be winning at choir contest...
You could say that again.
This is for acts like a moron!
Okay, go easy on me.
Alright, I surrender!
I'm so sick of this.
He talks so fast. I can't write everything down.
Well I can give you my notes if you want.
You're a lifesaver.
"But I didn't do anything wrong.
So I will never say, I'm sorry."
Why are you reading so slow. You sounds like you're five.
Fine. Enough of that. Who is next!
Four eyes...
Shoko.
Start reading from here.
There was an awkward silence.
His mother would have made him read it.
She should be home but you need to stop being so
stubborn all the time. He had no intention of apologizing.
That's good. Shoya, you are next.
You gotta be kidding me.
...
That isn't funny. Sit down, Shoya.
Okay!
Can you believe it?
Ha ha ha...
"Please let me know what you are talking about."
Emmm.....
No thanks.
Yeah, let's go.
Oh we're leaving, Shoko.
You konw something?
We're all sick of you with your notebook.
It's getting pretty old, pretty fast.
What do you want?
Frie-nds...
What?
You're such a freak.
Good morning everyone. I'm Ms. Keita of the DHH Liaison.
Do you all know what sign language is?
Okay, it's kind of like using your
hands to talk, instead if your voice.
Isn't that neat?
All right. Since we want to make
it easier to communicate with Shoko.
Every single morning we're going to spend
three minutes of class learning to sign.
Miss Keita.
Yes?
Why can't we just write in her notebook.
It would be easier for Shoko if everyone
just learned a little sign language.
Well, it would be easier for me
if I could just write stuff down.
Excuse me. I'll do it. I can learn how to sign.
"Teach me sign language for Sahara Miyoko"
Sa - ha - ra
Mi - yo - ko
Sa - a...
Goody two-shoes loser.
He is so cool.
Oh my gosh he's mine too.
Hey! He'll be on the next week.
Let's watch it together.
Gross! She get dressed in the dark?
So based on the author's previous, we're
looking at the results of the experiment...
Keisuke, you darw over there.
Sho-ko is...
What do you think you're doing?
You really shouldn't do that.
... Star.
Don't you think you're going a bit too far?
Nope. But I can go even further
You can be such a jerk.
Come on. I'm not that bad.
Check out my masterpiece.
"Congrats, Nishiyama-san.
Sahara-san went away because of you!"
Oh my gosh, who write such a thing.
Some people
here I'll just erase it for you.
So you don't have to see it.
There.
No need to thank me.
"Thank you."
I said no need to thank.
Let's go guys.
During the Jomon period...
Waw!
Cut it out, Shoya.
Would you rather have detention?
No, sir. Sorry.
Okay. Where did I leave off?
Right. The typical German house
was a pit dwelling with a central...
That was startling wasn't it!
Hey! Hey, Shoko.
What do we have here? Does
that mean you can actually hear?
You know what? I was wondering the same thing.
Can I see it for a second?
Naoka!
What are those things? Toss it over.
Is that your earwax? That is so gross.
Ouch!
Shoko, are you OK?
Oh no, she's bleeding.
What will we do?
You went too far, man.
Mr. Four eyes is such an asshole.
Oh great. Now what. You're in our way.
What is she even doing?
Get lost.
"I'm sorry."
Sorry!?
You're not sorry, you're just pathetic.
Hey!
What are you doing!? Stop touching me.
Check it out, I think she wants to hold your hand.
You like it. You're blushing.
No, I'm not!
Come on. Let's go.
Huh?
Oh my god. Talk about crazy.
The water is gross.
See you tomorrow, Shoya. Later.
Listen up everyone. There's something very
important that I'd like to talk to you about.
As you can see, Shoko Nishimiya is absent today.
Yesterday the school received a
telephone call from Shoko's mother.
In the past five months, eight of Shoko's
hearing aids have been broken or gone missing.
Hearing aids are very expensive.
Her mother believes Shoko is being bullied.
If any of you have seen Shokobeing harassed,
or abused at school, I need you to come
forward and tell us who has been doing it.
If no one comes forward, I'd hate to
have to bring your parents into this.
This is a very serious matter and
the school does not take bullying...
Shoya!
Stand up. We all know that it's you.
I told you to stand up.
Yes sir.
Now then, Naoka.
You sit right next to him. What have you seen.
Well... ah...
It's kind of true. He does tease her a little
like he makes fun of her.
What?
And Kazuki?
He act totally.
I kept telling him to knock it off,
but Shoya won't listen to anyone.
What!?
Wait!
That's not fair. You were making fun of her too Kazuki.
And it's not just the boys the girls were doing it too.
I swear it's true.
Especially Naoka and Miki.
That's mean...
I would never do anything like that.
How could you... How could
you say something like that.
What?
Yes. I see.
I am very sorry for any trouble he caused.
Yes. Of course.
Thank you. Goodbye.
Shoya!
Come back here. I'm talking to you.
Shoya.
I just got off the phone with the school.
Wait a minute!
Why are you so wet?
Leave me alone. I jumped in the river like always.
Freeze Mr.
Have you been causing trouble at school?
I wouldn't know.
Then why did I get a call from
your teacher this afternoon.
Okay, fine! It's true.
Get cleaned up. We're going
over to Shoko's place right now.
Come on Sho. Let's go home.
You're gonna try to be nicer from now on. Okay?
Huh?
All of these so-called great men
were going through their own struggles.
Huh?
Hey.
What is heck she doing?
Hey, what are you doing at my desk?
Don't you dare touch my stuff, you freak.
There's that, look again.
Don't try to act like you're some innocent.
What is it.
If you want to say something, spit it out.
You've done is just stand there with that stupid.
Look on your face, don't you ever get mad?
Well! Then do something!
Ouch!
What the hell is wrong with you?
I can't believe you beg me.
What are you even saying!
Get off!
I cannot even understand you!
"Disappear"
I hate her.
She is so weird...
Shoko Nishimiya has transferred to another school.
Moving on.
Now, who was in charge of the class journal yesterday?
Whoever it was forgot to hand it in.
Well, everyone just checked
their bags to see if they have it.
"Sign Language Study Club"
Oh, look it's Shoko. How are you doing.
Shoko!
Hello. Do you remember me?
We were in elementary school together.
I'm Shoya Ishida.
Where are you going?
Wait!
Please, come back.
Where did she go?
Hey!
H... Hey.
So I...
I came here to give you this.
I....
You left this behind.
Oh, what's that? How do I know sign language?
From a class.
Here you go. It's yours.
I don't even know if you ever wanted to see this again.
I was wondering...
...can me and you...
Shoko,
can we be friends?
Is that an option...
Oh, what did I just say...
That's what you were trying to ask me back in school.
I finally understand you.
Oh...
Don't cry.
Please don't cry, Shoko.
I wanted to ask if we could
be friends. Would that be okay?
Sho-Sho,
Sho-Sho, wake up!
Time for breakfast!
Okay Sho, up and at'em!
Good morning, Maria.
Sho-Sho is wake!
I'm heading out.
Bye bye, Mom!
Have a good day dear.
Here, Sbreakfast is served.
Thank you for this meal.
Dig in big guy!
What's got you so bright and cheery this morning?
Because...
I found this!
Oh.
You've been working so hard at your job,
and you even sold your comics, colthes and futon.
I am so lucky to have such a thoughtful son...
But tell me Shoya...
Why would you want to kill yourself?
I just...
don't do a lot of crazy stuff lately.
What can I say... I just...
I knew it...
I knew something was going on with you.
Do not even try to deny it.
Your room is clean for a change.
You cancelled your phone service.
And everything after April's
been torn up from your calendar.
I can't believe it. It's so morbid.
Promise me you won't go through
with it or I'm torching this.
The 1.7 million yen you earned will go to waste.
Are you listening to a word I'm saying?
Huh!?
Yeah, don't do anything crazy, mom...
Crazy? You were gonna over yourself.
No! Wait!
I'am sorry mom.
I'm really sorry. I won't do it again
I swear I won't. Please don't burn it.
What are you not gonna do. Please specific.
I promise I'm not going to kill myself.
I swear I won't do it, please believe me.
Do you mean it?
I swear to you!
OK, then I won't burn this...
Mom! Watch out!
Fire!
Give me some water.
Smoky!
Yesterday I was planning to jump off
a really tall bridge and kill myself.
I only went to see Shoko
Nishimiya to wrap up any loose ends.
It was hands-down the greatest test of courage ever...
I was supposed to be anyway.
Can we be friends?
World's biggest loser!
On the first day of junior high,
Kazuki makes sure everyone knew...
You should probably stay away from Shoya Ishida.
He's a bully. He's so bad.
A girl had to switch schools.
Like they always say, what goes around comes around.
I knew I really screwed up.
And I needed to pay for being a jerk.
And so I pushed everyone away.
All right everyone.
Make sure to have this translated by next week's class.
Hey Shoya.
H-hi.
Miki...
Have you had a chance to hand in your math notebook yet?
Oh sorry, I forgot.
That's okay.
Just try to hand it in soon all right.
Sorry.
No problem.
Wanna go sit in the courtyard?
Shoya never hangs out with anyone, what a loser.
Didn't you hear about him?
Everyone knows...
No way dude!
Hey check it out he's looking at us again.
I wonder if he gets a lonely
being by himself all the time.
What a total freak!
Why does he bother living?
Oh hey!
I got their new album. You want to check it out?
Yeah...
Since you like them I don't anymore.
Yeah Me too.
Yeah, all right.
Huh?
I've seen that head before.
Who is he?
It doesn't matter.
Should I go and see Shoko again?
She said she feeds the carp bread.
But I can't just show up there.
Not after everything I've done.
Should I go and apologize for making her cry.
She did say she's there every Tuesday.
Will is it too creepy?
Hey mom, I'm home.
Hi! Sho.
Oh you scared the crap out of me.
What's up?
I... I'm sorry for burning all your hard-earned money.
I didn't mean to.
Then again you only earn that
money so he could kill yourself.
So I don't want it anyway.
Sorry mom. I'll earn it back.
I konw you will.
But I don't want you to worry too much about it.
In the meantime, how about
some dinner. Who's hungry.
I am hungry!
Tuesday.
Hey, let me borrow your bike.
Me?
What do you need my bicycle for?
That kid I saw at lunch.
I forgot something at home.
So I need your bike to get it.
But I don't even know you.
Why can't you just use your own bike.
I'm asking you because I don't have one.
No... please don't.
Give me that.
I have been robbed! Somebody help me!
Anybody up there?
Why don't anyone help me?
Shut up!
God you're annoying,
just let go of the dam bike already!
Do you want to borrow mine? It's over there.
Yeah, thanks man. You are godsend.
Of course he stole it...
And today's Tuesday of all days.
So is that a sign that I should just leave her alone?
It's not like I can't just walk there,
but it's like I'm being told not to go.
I need a good reason.
Something real.
It doesn't look like I'm trying too hard.
Half off fluffy new bread.
This is it!
Uh... Is Shoko Nishimiya here?
She's not here.
She's right there.
Not her.
There's nobody here named Shoko.
Who are you anyway.
I mean are you actually a friend of hers?
Thought so.
Nothing to worry about.
There was a rat in the hallway.
A really gross one.
Don't worry. He won't be back.
Can we be friends...
What...?
Oh, found him! Hey! You!
Hey! You!
Over here! Look! Check it out!
I found your bike! This is yous, isn't it?
What a perfect timing!
It's a good thing you had your address on it.
That's great! But where did you find it?
That jerk dumped it in a rice field.
May it took me forever to find it.
Thank goodness I did and I found you too.
Is something wrong?
What?
Nothing...
Tell me. What's your name anyway?
But...? We don't already know?
Tomohiro Nagatsuka. I sit behind you.
Right I knew that.
It's really good bread and do
you want to split it with me?
Shoya!
Hey there! Shoya.
Good morning!
Ah... morning.
Hey, Shoya.
Do you want to hang out with me after school today?
I mean... since we are friends now.
Shoya over here! I saved you a seat.
What's troubling you, Ya-sho?
It's nothing.
Who's "Ya-sho"?
It's your nickname, shows that we're close.
Oh cool!
Well, so tell me what's troubling you?
You know you can tell me anything.
That's what best friends are for.
Hey, do you mind if I ask you something?
What does it mean to become someone's friend?
Like it. Is there some sort of
friendship process you go through,
or like do you need any specific qualifications?
Hey, Ya-sho.
Give me your hand, okay?
Hey, hey.
Now you and I is friends.
It could be simple as that. See...
Friendship don't got to do with rules or qualifications.
Because it's about something deeper.
A bond and you just can't break that.
Capeesh?
She is not here.
She is right there.
She is not!
Oh, I see it. I think Maybe...
Shoko's my girlfriend, okay?
Oh... well... that sucks...
Oh... not for me personally
because I brought her all this bread.
But...
I didn't know shoko was into younger guys.
I mean nothing against you I
just I never would have guessed.
Can you at least give her
the bread? It's really good.
Litsen! If you are just here to make
yourself feel better, you might as well leave.
If you'll excuse me...
Goodbye.
Listening boy!
What's your problem? My friend here
just wants to see miss Shoko okay?
So stop being so stubborn. Go get her!
Seriously, what are you even doing here?
I followed you.
Friends have each other's backs.
The shitty stalker has his own shitty
stalker. Makes you two a load of crap.
What? Oh yeah what was that?
What did you say...!
I called you are abull shit...
That doesn't sound good.
What's going on out there?
That's sounds like Yuzuru.
Oh, no. They are fighting.
Would you please clam down.
Seriously man, don't worry about it. Let us get out here.
Oh hello? Aren't you the nice boy from the other day?
It wasn't me. It must been some one else...
Sorry buddy, you are on your own!
Hey! They're gone!
Great he got to see her after all.
What are you doing?
You are spying on Shoko and Ya-sho?
Hand it over! I want to see.
Ya-sho sure does talk with his hands a lot.
It's called sign language, dumbass.
What? Oh wow!
I'm telling you my man's got real skills.
Do you understand sign?
Tell me what they're saying.
Who was that loser you were with?
I have never seen him before in my life.
He was disgusting!
Shut up! Liar!
Right. Fine!
Don't fall over! Be careful!
The truth is
I wasn't sure if it was okay to come see you.
For the past two weeks,
I have been wondering whether you
and I could be considered friends.
In order to see you, I felt like I needed a good reason
And finally, I found one.
Wow. What a great guy...
I'm glad you did.
I was thinking...
the exact same thing.
It's funny, isn't it.
So...
Anyway uh, I brought you some bread to feed the fish.
Do you enjoy feeding the fish?
She can't hear me.
Huh?
I think about it you really don't want to read that stuff.
Wait! What are you doing!
Oh! She falls in!
No way! What happened? Is Ya-sh okay?
Hey!
Hey, talk to me boy!
Oh! He went to the river!
Why!?
Ouch!
Why did you do that for!
What is that? Oh!
Over here Shoko.
Shoko!
I'm really sorry that I drop that.
I don't believe it. What a dummy...
Ha ha...
So long stalker!
Have you seen this?
Seriously? Is that really Shoya?
See you latter.
So it's okay?
Hey Shoya.
We've all been wondering.
It's that you?
Oh, where'd you get that?
Mr. Ishida, report to the faculty office immediately.
"Notice of short-term suspension
from school - Shoya Ishida"
I jumped into the river from the Suimonbashi
bridge even though I know it's prohibited...
and I posted a picture on ...
Shoya.
Yeah?
Sorry to ask, but do you think
you could pick up Maria for me?
I'm not supposed to leave the
house while I'm still suspended.
Oh come on! It'll only take
a second. You're life saving.
Wait!! Oh... really?
Okay, Maria, it's time to go home now.
Sho-Sho!
Somebody is in there!
Wait.
Hey you!
Wake up! Are you okay?
Aren't you Shoko Nishimiya's boyfriend?
You're gonna catch a cold like this.
If it isn't the stalker?
What are you doing? How'd you end up sleeping here?
Where are your shoes?
Aren't you mad at me?
About what?
I'm the one who posted the photo of you online.
Oh, so that was you.
Huh!
Thank goodness what a relief, seriously.
For reals?
At least I have a pretty good idea of why you did it.
You're not angry?
Why should I be?
I mean I kind of brought this on myself.
Sho-Sho!
I am hungry!
OK!
Looks like I gotta take off.
You should probably be heading home too.
Crazy. I can't believe you've got a kid.
Ouch!
Ah, she's my sister's.
Hey!
Here you go, Yuzuru,
Eat it as much as you want, okay?
What is sis go?
She said she'd be back late.
Well, Maria do you like it?
I like it!
Great!
What's wrong, Yuzuru? Not hungry?
Oh! I know!.
Open wide!
Crap!
What are you doing out here?
I woke up and you were gone.
Here, take it.
O--oh!
Stop it. What are you doing?
Just take it, okay.
Thank you.
Hang on are you not...?
Hey!
Just as I thought.
Wanna you wear these?
They actually used to be mine.
Don't fit anymore. You can keep them.
So uh... why'd you run away from home?
I got into a fight with Shoko.
Oh... wow...
It's true what they say...
relationships can get messy sometimes, right?
Yes.
Because I used Shoko's shampoo without her permission.
Eh?
And she told me she doesn't need me anymore.
Wait, are the two of you living together!?
Stop it, you're just getting away.
What's the point of bringing an umbrella man.
Right, but I'm the idiot who
didn't think to bring two of them.
Besides I'll feel bad for Shoko
if you come back with the cold.
Seriously...
Just who do you think you are?
You see through your act.
What are we? A couple of strays?
You doing this to feel better about yourself...
Must be extra amusing to you because she's deaf, right?
Yeah, you even went to the trouble to learn how to sign.
Big deal, you think that suddenly
makes you a hero or something?
I still can't stand you.
I see.
I guess Shoko told you all about me huh.
Well, you're right.
I am a horrible person. The world would
probably be better off if I wasn't around.
But still...
I just don't want to cause Shoko any more pain.
Oh but uh that doesn't mean I'm
gonna try and horn in on your turf.
You don't have to worry about that.
That said... it's true,
I guess I am being a bit selfish.
This is far enough.
Okay.
By the way...
I'm sorry I didn't tell you this earlier but
Ah... I'm actually Shoko's...
Know what I mean?
Ehh!
Younger sister!?
Later!
I remember you. You are Shoko's mother....
Let's go.
Oh, that hurts!
I'm sorry for what I did...
I'm back.
Yuzuru!
Don't hug me...
I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry!
I want to apologize too.
Granny, is there any Shiso
juice left? I'd like some.
Yuzuru.
I don't want you hanging around
that boy. Tell your sister that too.
I can decide who to hang out with on my own.
Same with Shoko.
Oh! The prodigal son returns.
How are you doing this fun day? You come back for...
I just returning the umbrella I borrowed.
That's surprising.
So our young lad has some manners after all.
Nagatsuka, that lad actually is a lass...
That's Shoko's little sister.
I knew that the entire time.
I wanted to thank you for
looking out for my homeboy Ya-sho.
This is my friend,
Na-ga-tsu-ka.
Oh... oh yeah,
I got a new cell phone.
I'm guessing you have that cell phone too, don't you?
So yeah... do you ever text?
Like with your friends um...
from your new school?
Ah that's great.
So uh anyone you want to meet?
I mean do you need anyone's phone number?
Oh good maybe you'd like to have mine?
What's that?
Sa... Ha... Ra.
Miyoko from elementary school?
Hey! Ya-sho!
Well?
So how are you gonna track down the Miyoko chick.
Oh no, that's not exactly true.
But you get straight 'A's, don't you?
Oh yeah... that's it.
Ya-sho?
But Satoshi I didn't even...
Miki...?
Um what's up?
There's something I wanted to ask you.
Do you know how to get in touch with Miyoko Sahara?
She went to the same elementary school with us.
Miyoko?
Sorry, I have no idea.
But bet the school will have some kind of record.
I think Naoka goes to the same school with her.
Taiyo Girl's Academy...
Crap, I'm flat broke.
Ya-sho, my man.
I've got your back bro.
Wow, where'd that come from.
I don't really need that much.
Come on! Let me sponsor you. There are travel and
meal is expensive and those love motels ain't cheap...
You'll be glad for the extra dough. Trust me.
Guys over here.
Looks like we just made it.
My sister was kind of annoyed that she was being
left out, since she was the one who suggested it.
So would you mind if she tagged along with you.
"Are you tired?
Thank you for today."
"I was happy to hear that you are
trying to look for Sahara-san for me."
"I heard a lot about you from Yuzuru."
"I'm very happy to be with you today!"
So if we start walking from here...
Sho? Sho!
Sorry about that.
Is that you?
It is me. Miyoko. From school.
Hi!
Hey, wait. Is that Shoya?
Heh heh heh.
It's been a long time hasn't it huh.
And since then, I've been learning sign, or trying.
Was that right?
I know I just kind of disappeared on you back then.
Sorry about that.
But I never stopped thinking about you ever.
Seeing you makes me happy.
I was so surprised.
Uh huh...
Really?
So where are you going to school now, Shoko?
Well... well your chest has gotten bigger.
What's the size you are?
Want me to check?
What's the matter?
Nothing. I just have to go to the bathroom.
Oh, okay then.
Special offer. Here you go.
Special offer!
Naoka...
Here you are!
Please come and visit us.
Special offer!
Just give it a try.
Meow Meow Club...
"It's great that you learned sign language.
And thank you for bringing us together again!"
Oh!
Wow I'd never have the guts to
do that. Yes they're having fun.
Hmm?
Maybe I should reunite her with Naoka as well?
Yep, that may be the worst idea you've ever have.
On second thought I'll pass.
Here we are.
Shall we? Meow meow Club?
Here we come.
Good afternoon.
Welcome!
And how long will you be staying with us.
One hour? I guess.
I have a coupon...
Oh good! Right this way.
Crap! He actually came...
This is not what I imagined.
There cats... what were you expecting?
Well have you ever been to a place like this?
What? No, I never. I came here for you man.
I wanted to help you reunite with your friend...
and speaking of old friends.
Where is she, anyway?
I wouldn't exactly call this girl a friend.
You wouldn't?
A lot of stuff happened when we were in sixth grade.
To be honesty this whole thing's kind of awkward.
She isn't here.
Wanna take off then?
A bug!
Oh what are you doing here huh?
I came over to play with Maria.
Hey uh, do you think shoka would like this?
Kitty!
I brought you a present, Shoko!
What happened...
I'm just gonna leave this here.
What?
N--Naoka...
What...
Go, go!
Hey what are you doing!?
Long time no see!
Yeah. Long time no see.
Huh?
Wait a minute. Isn't the deaf girl?
Still alone.
Poor thing!
Seriously Shoya. It really has been way too long.
Let's hang out soon.
No I don't think so.
Well, you really hate me, don't you?
What?
No I never said that.
You konw what Shoya,
I always thought I should have
made more of an effort to talk to you.
I'm sorry about everything
that happened when we were kids.
It's not that big of a deal.
Hey Naoka,
get off.
That's purse from our cafe.
Where did that deaf freak get it from.
I gave it to her.
Oh... I see.
Later.
Yeah.
Naoka?
Hey there Shoko long time no see!
Someone was likely tracking you.
Stop!!
That's weird. There's only one of them.
Naoka! What do you think you're doing.
Thought we'd have a game a
catch, just like when we were kids.
I'm so sorry Shoko.
No freakin way, you gotta be kidding me.
Hold on, wait a minute.
Don't tell me you guys are actually going out?
What!? what are you talking about?
We're just friends.
Just friends?
That's hilarious.
Are you telling me you are now besties with the
girl used to bully? I can't believe it. That's crazy.
Let me guess, are you trying to make amends?
Not really.
Ha ha.
Too funny, what's gotten into you?
Well, I'll leave you to your fake friendship thing.
Ha ha ha.
You want to know what we were talking about?
Nothing, don't worry about it.
Look I gotta take off.
See you.
Yuzuru,
time to get up.
I'm up, you startled me awake.
Get off bed, breakfast...
Wait! Before you go...
What's up?
Your hair today it's in a ponytail.
Are you...?
What a weird face!
Shoya will love the new dew.
"So much carp. Shortage ofbread
and feeding manpower.You MUST come."
Huh?
Oh, Shoko.
She's wearing a ponytail.
Where are you going, Shoya?
What was that? Where am I going?
To the bakery.
Yuzuru asked me to get some bread to feed the carp.
But you already have some bread. I bet
she only wants more so she can eat it.
You don't have to buy her anymore. I
can't believe she made you do that for her!
Wait. Just...
Can you sign it?
Is my voice weird?
Yes.
Oh, I'me sorry. I didn't...
Your voice sounds totally okay.
I'm gonna get some bread.
Be right back.
Huh?
What are you doing？
Present for me?
Wow, thanks.
Can I open it?
Like right now?
What are these things?
Thank you so much.
What's that?
Something about these?
I... ige... moo...
Huh?...
I love you!
The moon?
It is pretty, isn't it?
Where are you going?
"How about we go out and see a movie now?"
Can I ask you something?
Do you think they look like the moon?
Let's see... well they don't look like the moon.
Hummm.
Candy!
I'm pretty sure these things aren't candy.
Shoko gave these to me as a present.
I have no idea what they are.
Huh?
Oh...
Are you okay? What happened?
"I said I like you to Ishida-kun"
Ah! You what...!
"But he couldn't understand what I said."
Huh...
Wow, check out your hair. It's different.
What made you decide to change it?
Do you have a hot day? Whatever
it is, you should keep it like this.
Stop it you guys.
You're making me blush. I just didn't
have any time to do it. That's all.
Well. I think it looks good.
Hi, Miki. I've got a question.
Why did you suddenly change your hair?
Hmmm... what do you mean?
It's not like I need any particular reason.
Girls just like to change things up sometimes. You know.
I see.
What is it?
The other days the Toshi told me he thought
you'd be a pretty cool guy to hang out with!
Huh?
Who are you and tell us the nature of your business.
Nice to meet you. Miyoko Sahara.
Hi. Satoshi Mashiba.
Cut it out! Stop doing that over my head.
Miyoko! It feels like it's been a million years!
Hey! If Shoko coming today?
No. She's a stomachache.
Umm... that's weird.
I hope she's not avoiding me.
How come?
She was trying to tell me something the other day.
I just could not understand what she was saying.
What exactly did she say to you?
The moon.
Pff!
It's an easy enough word but her
saying it didn't make any sense.
I bet she was so annoyed.
Well if you really want to know how she feels about you.
Then I suggest you just ask her out.
If she says no, you will have your answer.
I guess that you're right.
"We are planning to go to the amusement
park, I was thinking maybe we can go together?"
Come on! Lets all go on the big one first.
Everyone stick together so we don't get separated man!
Why did she actually act like a chaperone or something.
Who knows?
Shoya.
Who's that? Over there.
Oh!
Why is she acting so chummy with Shoko?
Naoka?... Why she's here?
Is she like a friend or something?
Yeah!
From elementary school.
Hmmmm...
Hey... mind if I sit here?
Not at all. Go right ahead.
I might be scary.
Okay everybody, are you ready?
Yeah!!
Then hold on tight.
Miyoko, so are you like cool with Naoka now?
Huh?
Oh, sure!
We're actually both in the design department at school.
Now it's got great taste. I've learned a lot from her.
You know, when we were in elementary
school. I was way to scared to ride this.
I was such a coward back then.
But then, one day, I looked at it differently.
I was going to wait until after the
ride to decide whether it's scary or not.
Can't help feeling little scary though.
Here we go!
Oh... oh no!
Poor Shoko, your legs are shaking.
Are you okay?
Ha ha.
That's pretty impressive. I didn't know you can sign it!
You must have worked really hard to learn sign language.
Huh?
Hey get your dirty paws off my Ya-sho.
Who said you could touch it Huh?
Dude! I was just being friendly.
Well go be friendly with someone else.
Nagatsuka you really creak me.
Ya-sho is my friend I've got my eye on you. You better...
Hey, is that your real hair?
No, get off...!
I'm not joking.
What's so funny!
Is this...?
Faster it Satoshi! They are catching up!
We can do this, Ya-sho. Come on! Pedal harder!
What is this...?
Is it okay...?
Am I allowed to have this much fun?
This feels so... familiar.
Great catch, funny.
Oh yeah... It almost feels like...
...like real friends!
Hey Shoya!
I'am hungry. I feel like some takoyaki.
Come with me to get some.
Ah... I'm not... Hey! Hey! Wait!
Here you go. One takoyaki.
Thank you.
And Naoka!
You need to learn mind your own business.
Ka... Kazuki...?
Shoya where are you going?
I'll text you later okay?
Hey wait up!
Are you mad at me?
No I'm not.
I'm fine, yeah.
I just thought
maybe you guys could be friends.
You know, like you used to be.
I guess I was hoping once you guys actually
saw each other everything would be okay.
Don't do me any favors, okay?
Oops.
Wait...
I did the exactly same things...
You and I are more alike than you think you know.
No. We are not.
Yes we are.
We're nothing alike.
You know,
If Shoko hadn't shown up, we would
all still be friends and be happy.
You don't know that.
Oh, come on. Just admit it.
If it wasn't for her,
things wouldn't have gotten
all weird between Miyoko and me.
And then you wouldn't have stopped
being friends with Kazuki either.
I just want to go back to the way
things were, before she showed up.
Kazuki and I... That was
me. I run out on my own.
Shoya, tell me the truth.
Do you hate me?
Probably.
Fine! Time for a ride on the ferriswheel.
I'll go see if Shoko wants to come with me.
Hey!
Huh?
Shoko, you've got to come ride the ferriswheel with me.
Cut it out! Naoka!
If you guys are going, can you take my camera.
I want to ride the roller coaster again.
Oh, hi Yuzuru!
Come on in. Shoya is upstairs in his room.
Wow.
I got top secret video for you.
A video from the ferriswheel?
Yeah.
How would you get it?
Spying.
What?
I want you to listen to me carefully.
I hate you.
Put that thing away.
I'm going to speak slowly so you can understand.
And I'll listen everything you have to say.
I'll admit that in elementary school,
I had no idea what things were like for you.
It's not like you tried to understand
what I was going through either.
You know what I mean.
And instead of getting a clue like a normal person,
You just kept giving me that stupid notebook of yours.
You're always being so weird.
And you would apologize all the time for everything.
So I tried a different approach.
I ignored you and blew you off.
That was my way of telling you that
I didn't want to hang out with you.
But nope,
you just kept coming around with
your stupid book and your stupid signs
you're so clueless then you had
to go run crying to the grown-ups.
You got Shoya it in trouble and that's how he
ended up losing every single one of his friends.
You pretty much ruined everything
for everyone, you get that right.
I... I'm sorry...
God you still don't get it I'm not
looking for nother apology from you.
We were both going through a lot,
and I don't think either of us
could have done anything differently.
But still, it's not like I want to
be your new best friend or anything.
I mean I still hate you a lot, and
I pretty sure you hate me too right?
So why don't we stop pretending
or something we're not okay?
Let's shake on it from one hater to another.
You wrong, I don't hate you...
I.....I.....
I hate myself...
What did you say?
Well what are you gonna do? You can't say sorry again?
It has been five years,
and you haven't changed a bit. You still
have no intention of being real with me.
What do you think?
It's all...
all I want...
is for Shoko to like herself.
Are you sure with Naoka?
Yeah it was her.
Is there really a lot of bad blood between her and Shoko?
Why do you ask?
Miki said something serious went down at your old school.
Shoko's hearing is really bad. I
mean she can barely hear anything right?
Yeah.
It just occurred to me, maybe that's why
she kept getting bullied all the time you know?
You'd have to be a major douche bag
who bullies a deaf kid.
What's wrong with people right?
What are you saying!?
Wait! You think I'm spreading rumors
about what happened at elementary school?
Shush! will you keep it down?
The whole school can hear you.
I really wanted to believe that
you would actually change Shoya.
But you are still the same awful
person you were in elementary school.
Are you okay?
Can you just please calm down a second.
Hey guys what's going on.
Remember when I told you Shoko was bullied?
Well it was Shoko, he was the one who used to bully her.
How can you say that Miki?
Ya-sho would never do that.
Why I make up something like that.
But you used to make fun of her to Miki.
I never ever said anything horrible behind Shoko's back.
What you picked on Shoko?
Yeah, was him! He was the one
who made Shoko's life a living hell.
It was so awful I kept begging him to leave her alone.
But Shoya never listens to anyone.
I'm so scared of him.
Ya-sho?
What's wrong?
Sorry, Nagatsuka...
Are you OK?
Ya-sho!
Yeah, I hate me too...
Hey we're over here.
Hi!
Is something wrong?
Oh no, not really.
It's nothing...
Huh?
There he is. My main man.
I brought your backpack for you!
Hey guys.
Naoka...?
...I asked her to come.
I'm sorry about what happened.
But well you were the one who
started causing all that trouble.
Nothing is Satoshi said I should go ahead and forgive you
since you've been trying to make things right with Shoko.
Are you kidding me?
This is wrong on so many levels.
You can't blame everything that
happened on Shoya. We were all guilty.
We?
But no, that isn't true.
What's not?
I never made fun of Shoko. Did anything to
bully her the way the rest of you guys did.
Don't lump me in with you.
Naoka...
Hmmm...
You're right. You and I are completely different.
You just that back and laughed along with everyone else.
It's not!
Just asked Miyoko!
What? Me!?
Naoka used to talk about you
behind your back all the time too.
I just said what everyone else was thinking.
Well Miyoko, wanna weigh in?
To be completely honest...
back then I was...
I was scared of both of you.
What!? Whose side are you are anyway!?
I'm not on anyone's side!
Just stop.
It's my fault okay. It's all my fault.
I can't stand martyrs..
That's enough Naoka.
Stop trying to drag everybody else down here level.
That was harsh! You didn't have to put...
Oh, please, Miyoko.
We all know that you just run
away when other things get intense.
Shoya, what's gotten into you...
God will you just stop talking?
You really love the sound of your own voice don't you?
Listen man,
No matter what anyone says I've got your back.
I don't care what you just
back off. You hardly know me.
I can't take this anymore.
I'm not staying here.
It's okay.
You don't mean it.
But I'm gonna give you some space.
Hey Shoko,
later.
I'm sorry, Shoya.
I never should have agreed to come here to begin with.
It's not cool. We're way to harsh.
What do you know? You're not
even really part of our group.
I thought we were friends.
Almost forgot...
So starting next week,
it's summer vacation.
Do you want to go somewhere special?
Yuzu.
You're going to ruin your eyes
reading in the dark like that.
Here.
You spend so much time worried about your big sister.
Now I'm starting to worry about you. Sweetie.
You get so caught up in Shoko's life
that you never leave any time for yourself.
I could say the same thing about you granny!
Instead of going to the senior center
all you do is study sign language.
That's something I'm doing for
myself so that doesn't really count.
What a coincidence. Because I'm
doing all these things for myself too.
Really?
You are such a good kid.
You think so?
Mom chews me out on a daily basis,
and I haven't gone to school in like... weeks.
Yes, sweetie. But you've got a heart of gold.
Shoko is no slouchy either.
I've got some mighty fine grandchildren.
Have one of the Manju too?
You've got it!
Granny...
Hey there, Shoko.
So today, I was able to score some really great bread.
See! It's awesome, like you're awesome.
Oh like really great bread is
awesome, This loaf here is just like you.
That makes no sense.
Huh...?
I wonder if she's coming today?
I guess not...
Is your stomach bothering you?
Is it not too personal?
Hey, Yuzu???
I should go...
Shoya!
Hey there!
What the heck are you wearing?
What's it look like. My uniform.
What do you think? You like?
Why are you wearing it?
For school.
But we're on summer break right now.
Ehh...
So what's really going on?
Nothing is going on I swear.
If anyone asks, tell him cosplay!
Huh.
That was from my sister so I better take off.
Where to? I'll walk you there.
No. It's fine.
You sure you're okay?
Yeah, everything is cool.
Then why you were crying just now.
Come on!
This actually doesn't have anything to do with you.
Sure it does...
At least, I think so.
Why?
I'm just worried about you okay.
I don't believe it you sound just like my grandma.
All right if you wanna come then come.
This is it.
Thanks for walking me. I appreciate it.
"Funeral service for Ito Nishimiya"
See you.
Good lucky, Yuzuru!
Shoya. Wait.
Truth is... I am scared.
"How about hanging out
somewhere tomorrow?"
Wow, that's cool!
Come on, Shoko. Let's go check it out.
Huh?
Shoko?
I'm fine really.
Why are you apologizing?
That's totally not true!
Hey, are you busy tomorrow?
Let's hang out tomorrow, too!
Shoko said...
that I'll be miserable whenever I'm with her.
But I'm the one who made her unhappy.
It was me...
I want to see the sea,
I want to have somemone love me,
even monsters feel
feel there are...
There's no going back to the way things were...
Hey! Shoko. Cool! I see Yuzuru
is going to get along with us.
Let's check outa movie!
Ha ha ha, this is hilarious.
Hey greetings classmates!
I gotta say this has been the best summer break ever.
Just ask Yuzuru?
Whatever...
Seriously, we're having an absolute blast.
What about tomorrow.
We should go somewhere fun.
Any ideas? Where we should go?
Sorry, but we already have plans for tomorrow.
Huh?
Hah? No way. Are you insane?
Wants to make what?
You sure it's okay?
I feel like I really shouldn't be here.
Your mission should you choose to accept?
It is to assist us in baking our mother's birthday cake.
Are you absolutely sure?
I don't want to get hit again.
She won't hit you. She'll probably kill you this time.
For real?
Oh that looks amazing!
Why is he here?
What's that boy doing our kitchen?
I want an explanation right now.
Come on, mom, don't be like that. It's a
party! We're supposed to be celebrating.
Yuzuru.
You look great!
Eh...
You lucked out, looks like mom isn't gonna kill you.
I declare a victory.
Speaking of winning,
I submitted some of your photography
to the local contest Yuzuru.
Huh?
You what?
It was actually your sister's idea.
What? But I'm no good. I'm just messing around.
Oh, come on, that's not true.
Why would you do this to me.
Before I forget, next Tuesday you're coming
to see the fireworks with us sitll right?
I don't have to.
You're totally coming...
Is here okay?
Yeah, this is good.
Well, perfect time to go buy snacks.
Want to come on?
Oh, thank you.
Thanks for inviting me over the other day too.
Your mom...
You really think she was happy?
I couldn't tell...
Speaking of which...
I don't know when your birthday is.
Your birthday was June 7th.
Oh no I missed it. That's too bad.
I can't believe you're already 18.
Next year, we'll celebrate together.
We'll throw a big party.
I made it sound like we're together.
Oh.
I get now.
That makes perfect sense.
That's why you closed your eyes.
Oh, where are you going?
What? Why now? The fireworks only just started.
To go study...
Okay.
Hey wait up I'll walk you home.
But why...
Oh well
See you later.
Hey what happened to Shoko?
Oh, I forgot my camera.
Would you mind going back to our place to get it?
I'm coming in...
Oh, it's dark.
Shoko, you here?
It's me, Shoya.
There it is.
Shouldn't I make sure it's fully charged...?
Huh? Oh, you see the fireworks from here.
So that's where she is.
She...
Hey...
Wait, wait! Wait a second!
What is she doing?!
Hey, Shoko?
Shoko...!?
Huh!
Don't do it!
Ah! Ouch!
Please no...!
Shoko!
You have to hold on to the railing.
Please, God...
Give me one more ounce of strength... I
won't run away from my problem anymore.
Just through this one thing for me please.
Starting tomorrow... I'll look everyone in the eye.
Starting tomorrow... I'll listen when people speak to me.
Starting tomorrow... I'll be better.
Shoko...
There it is the scar I gave her all those years ago.
Did I ever even apologize for that
I'm sorry.
Sorry for everything Shoko.
Are you still mad at me?
Huh, I'm so dumb.
I should have asked her what she really thinks of me.
But now I don't know if.
By the way, Shoko. I think that I might...
He there Sho,
your sister whipped you up some of her famous pancake.
I'm going to watch the fireworks!
It's cold...
It's warm...
Mrs Ishida.
What are you doing here?
I'm glad I caught you.
I tried calling the so long but it was closed.
I just wanted to know about Shoya...
Well he's doing a lot better.
They moved him out of the ICU.
I was going to his new room. Do you want to come with me?
Do you know if Shoya...
Mrs Ishita...
Mrs Nishimiya...
I'm very sorry for all the trouble Shoya has caused.
I know what he did in the past
is unforgivable. But I want you...
Please forgive me.
What are you doing? Oh get up...
I'm sure Shoya must have done something...
Mrs Ishida,
Shoya was trying to save my stupid sister.
If I do better... she wouldn't have...
I'm so sorry.
Please don't.
Come on, both you. Please get up.
I'm just glad that Shoko was okay.
And you too Yuzuru...
So please get up...
Why is Shoya lying in a hospital bed instead of you?
Don't you dare try to play the victim.
Say something!
What? You finally come back for all
the problems you created for everyone.
So you thought you would kill yourself.
And now all you can say
is "I'm sorry"? Is that it?
Well that's not going to cut it anymore.
Who do you think you are, huh?
You're a loser, a deaf loser.
You sit there in your own little world
and ignore everyone else around you.
You're the most selfish person I know.
Hey who the hell are you?
You must be the little loser's mother!
If you can't keep your kid in line
then do us all a favor and stop breathing.
What are you two doing?
That's enough.
I said that's enough.
Stop it. What is wrong with the both of you?
Shoko, are you okay?
I am sorry.
I am so sorry.
That's all my fault.
What are you doing?
I thought if she saw what death looked like,
she'd stop saying she wanted to kill herself.
I didn't know what else to do...
I can't open it.
Someone is holding it.
Oh I didn't notice you there Shoko.
Are you thirsty? How about I buy you a drink.
"Hospital rooms
400-417"
I heard what happened with you and Ya-sho.
"I destroyed what Ishida-kun
created working so hard."
Does this have to do with that stuff on the bridge?
Ya-sho was kind and open-hearted
enough to accept a guy like me.
For the first time, I know what it
feels like to have a true friend.
Ya-sho is my best friend in the whole world.
So I know he'll wake up. He just has to...
"I want to fix what I destroyed."
Oh...
You wanted to die because you were
suffering? What were you thinking!
Just calm down, everybody is staring.
I don't care about who's listening. I
have to be loud in order for Shoko to hear me.
We were all so worried about you.
I know life can be hard sometimes.
It's like that for everyone.
Thing is you have to accept the bad parts of
yourself with the bad and just move forward.
I am really glad you're okay.
"I want to fix what I destroyed."
I see,
So you went to see everyone then.
That's awesome...
But I'm not as brave as you.
Even if Sharia does wake up from his coma.
I think I'd be too ashamed to face him.
Because he's right, I haven't changed one bit.
You needed help and I still wasn't there for you.
I'm the same coward as I've always been.
You can change from now.
It is not too late.
I'm really glad you came to see me, Sho.
Hey, stop it! Cut it out!
"Nishimiya"
"I found you..."
"Are you doing well?"
"Somewhat?"
"Strange, isn't it?"
"I think..."
"I am going to die."
"Oh..."
"Tuesday is almost over."
"Farewell,"
"Nishimiya..."
No! Shoko!
What's all this?
Mom!
Hello? What's going on?
Shoko?
Oh was there?
She is here.
I am so sorry.
Yo!
Aha ha ha.
Hey! Why are you crying?
I'm really glad
you are okay.
Don't worry, Shoko.
I am fine now. I promise...
...more or less.
So stop looking so gloomy, okay?
Oh yeah...
I want to tell you...
that I'm really sorry.
I never apologized for all the
stuff I did to you when we were kids...
...or any of the other stuff afterwards either.
So I'm sorry...
But the thing is...
Even though you were going through a lot...
I was being selfish and focused
on myself more than anything.
I wanted to have a conversation with you.
I wasn't trying to hurt you...
but I must have.
Because I made you feel so bad about yourself.
Then you decided to go and do the unthinkable.
No, you are wrong.
It because I couldn't change.
And that's why you fell.
It's me.
Everything is all my fault.
So I thought should I just disappear...
I am so selfish...
I am sorry.
Please, that's not true. Don't cry.
Shoko. Look at me.
Did you know we were talking a little while ago...
I was dreaming
and in this dream I was ready
to just give up on everything.
But I was wrong.
To be honest, I've thought about
ending things just like you did.
But then, I realized something,
Even though certain things can
make life difficult sometimes.
that doesn't mean they are worth and dying over.
I want to apologize and make sure I do it right.
Shoko.
I need some help from you.
I was hoping
that maybe you could
teach me how to live.
Please Shoko.
Oh God.
That's the creepiest thing I've ever said in my life.
Oh I'm so sorry... just never mind.
Forget everything I said okay? I didn't mean it.
You have arrived at your destination.
Hey there Maria become quite the
gardener since I've been gone huh?
They're looking good!
Sho-Sho!? You die? You die?
That's right Maria. Oh ur Sho came back from dead.
Don't listen to grandma, that wasn't really dead.
Hey look!
Isn't that Naoka?
You know she was by your side
the entire time you were in a coma.
You really should thank her.
My mom said you came to the hospital...
Listen I really suck at life sometimes...
Especially when it comes to stuff like this.
I just... I just can't bring myself to like Shoko.
Probably gonna regret this.
Remember when you fell in the river?
It was Kazuki and the guys who pulled
you out and he told me not to tell you.
But...
anyway welcome back.
Well I'm gonna take off.
Thanks Naoka.
I don't know, don't you think it's a little short?
No, no, it looks much cuter like this!
Oh your home Shoya.
Oh, hi Shoya.
Mrs Nishimiya.
Wait a minute. Yes?
I'm really sorry.
Yeah, me too.
No matter what my son always bounces our right back.
See you later mom I'm heading
out to pick up Maria now.
Okay!
Who's that?
He is my son-in-law. He's back from being deployed.
Oh Shoya, Yuzuru is waiting for you upstairs.
Give her the Jello that's in the fridge.
Yo.
Wow.
New threads? It looks good on you.
Check it out. I won.
Oh wow! No kidding, impressive.
Now feast your eyes on this.
Wow... not so impressive.
Since you're alive again,
Will you please help teach me how to study.
Of course, no problem.
So uh, you're giving school another shot?
Yeah I decided to take a cue from Shoko.
I figured... at least I could do this try.
I don't want to let you went down.
Isn't your big school festival tomorrow?
Oh yeah, that's right.
"Hello, everyone said they
are going to the school festival
tomorrow. I will meet you at the
front gate at 10:00, is that OK?"
Ha, good morning, everybody!
Up top! Yeah! Ha ha ha.
I said horrible things and I'm sorry.
Okay!
I'm heading out!
Have a good day, sweetheart!
Oh!
I see now! So that's what you're
supposed to do with those things.
What's that?
Nothing. I'll see you later okay?
Have a good day, Sho-Sho!
There you are!
Okay, let's go.
Isn't that Shoya?
Who's that?
Wait the one who was in the
hospital right? The guy who jumped?
Oops...
You probably didn't know this,
but I don't really fit in at school.
It's cause I have trouble looking people in the eye.
So it's easier for me to just
stare at the floor all the time.
You think it's okay to do that?
Aha Shoko...
I can actually do it without you leading me.
Thank you.
This is my classroom here.
Has the water boiled guys? It
just was just a few more minutes.
Oh wow, Shoya is back to school.
Are you okay now?
You know what?
I think my stomach is acting up a bit.
Sorry.
Ya-sho!
Huh?
Ya-sho?
Oh hey, that's Nagatsuka?
You're feeling okay?
Ya-sho.
Good morning Nagatsuka, good
to see you. So how is everything?
About that, what's going on? Why won't you look at me.
I don't know. I just feel weird.
I made myself a promise I would
look people in the eyes from now on.
Guess I'm too chicken...
Hey, Ya-sho...!
Shoya!!
You are okay, I'my glad.
Guess if you...
Cause if you didn't wake up, I don't know what I would
do. You are everything to me. I would've been all alone.
Listen, the stuff on the bridge,
don't worry about okay?
Friends say stuff they don't mean to
each other all the time! It doesn't matter.
I'm begging you...
don't ever leave us again.
Promise me,
I can't lose you.
It's gonna be okay.
Hey look, I'm sorry.
I mean,
thank you for being a friend.
You're very welcome!
But uh what's up with the facial hair?
That's my lucky stash I swore. I
wasn't shaving it till you woke up.
You did that for me...
Huh?
What's going on?
We heard Nagatsuka-kun's howling
your name so we followed him.
I see.
Miki did you bring the stuff to give to Shoya?
I brought them...
But I can't give it to him. It's a total failure.
Don't be silly, hand him over.
Here...
There's supposed to be a thousand of them,
but I couldn't finish it fast enough.
Everyone worked really hard. Did their best.
But we just couldn't...
No! This is amazing
It's more than enough.
No one's ever done anything like this for me.
It really means a lot seriously.
Thank you Miki.
And, I am sorry. Also... sorry.
And you too.
No worries, it's all good bro.
Ugh!
Enough!
All these every talk. I'm gonna lose my lunch.
Why do you always have to be like that, Naoka?
What? You got a problem with me
or something? You pick up a fight?
Okay everybody just calm down!
Oh... Shoya.
Listen I'm really sorry.
After all you've been through you really needed a friend,
but all I did was run away.
That's okay.
I did the same thing.
Stop acting so worried they're just talking things out.
You apologizing?
Well. Yes that's all you know how to do.
Mo-ron!
Moron!
Eh...
Whatever,
I'm gonna go find somebody.
Did she just run away?
I think she's embarrassed.
Hey guys,
I have a big favor to ask all of you.
That's okay?
Do you wanna go together to the festival?
How's that sound?
OMG, this is so good.
Oh, hey! Let's go to the gym next!
How can he come back to school?
Oh, the story is amazing!