♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Joseph: Well, I hate to say it,
but it’s too late for him.
He’s got a few days
before he dies at most.
Jotaro, this is not your fault.
Trust me.
Do you want to know why this man
swore his allegiance to dio
and came to your school
to kill you?
Look right here,
and I will show you!
Jotaro: What is that?
It looks like a spider
or a piece of flesh.
That’s it? Is that what made him
swear allegiance to dio?
Avdol: Yes, it’s a flesh bud
formed from dio’s cells.
It connects directly
to the boy’s brain.
Flesh buds are small,
but they have the power
to influence a person’s
thoughts and actions.
Joseph: Simply put,
that bud stirs him
and awakens a certain feeling
far beyond his control.
- ( Jotaro gasps )
- Joseph: Charisma!
The sheer emotive power
that drives a soldier
to follow a dictator
or a believer to put his faith
in a corrupt cult.
This young man revered dio,
and that’s why
he swore allegiance to him!
Dio knows how to wield
the power of charisma,
which means there will be others
he will try to influence.
He ordered this young man,
kakyoin here, to kill us,
and he won’t stop until he has.
Jotaro: So remove the bud.
Joseph: No.
The brain is very delicate.
If he even twitches
while we extract it,
it could cause brain damage.
( Kakyoin gasps )
Avdol: Jojo...
I need to tell you something.
Four months ago, while I
was still there in Cairo...
( Groans )
I encountered dio!
( Jotaro gasps )
♪
Avdol: I am a fortuneteller
by trade.
I have a shop
in a souk called Khan khalili.
It was a full moon that night,
and there he was.
( Gasps )
He just stood
at the top of the stairs
outside my shop silently,
with eyes so cold it felt like
he was invading my heart,
golden hair,
and translucent alabaster skin,
but, most of all,
a dubious sensuality,
the kind you
wouldn’t expect from a man.
Because Mr. Joestar
had warned me about him,
I knew exactly who he was,
dio resurrected from
the depths of the Atlantic!
Dio: I hear
you have a special ability
beyond that
of an ordinary person.
This true?
It would please me if you’d
Grant me a small demonstration.
( Slurps )
( Avdol shuddering )
It was then that I found him
to be truly terrifying.
Every word he spoke
calmed my heart.
The dangerous sweetness
in his voice
is precisely
what makes him so terrifying!
Dio avdol, come here.
( Avdol screams )
♪
I ran for my life.
I didn’t dare
think of fighting him.
I was very fortunate.
Because I had
prior knowledge of dio,
I was able to realize
who he was.
I immediately jumped
out the window.
That souk is a labyrinth,
but I know it
like the back of my hand,
and thanks to that,
I was able to escape.
Otherwise, I would have
ended up like this young man,
another follower
controlled by a flesh bud.
Joseph: You would have died
a few years later,
with your brain
completely devoured.
Jotaro: Died?
Let’s not jump the gun.
Kakyoin’s not in great shape,
but he’s not dead yet!
♪
I’ll pull it out with my stand.
- ( Avdol gasps )
- Joseph: No, jotaro! Stop!
Jotaro: Old man, just back off.
I can remove this thing
without damaging his brain.
If my stand has the precision
to catch a speeding bullet,
- then it can also do this.
- Joseph: Listen!
That flesh bud is alive.
Can’t you see?
Part of that flesh bud lives
outside his body for a reason.
Even a skilled surgeon
can’t remove it
without serious damage!
Shit.
Avdol: It just sunk itself
into his flesh.
This is bad.
You have to let go, jojo!
Joseph: It can infiltrate
anyone’s brain
who dares try to remove it!
( Jotaro grunts )
Kakyoin: Why are you--
I would try not to move.
If I mess this up,
your brain is fried.
♪
Avdol: No, jojo!
It’s ready reached your neck!
- You have to let go!
- Joseph: Hold on, avdol.
My grandson is very impressive.
That thing’s made it
halfway through his body,
and yet he’s
still completely calm,
not even a tremble
from either him or his stand.
He can move
with more precision and strength
than I ever anticipated!
( Kakyoin shudders )
Avdol: He did it.
( Stand yelling )
Joseph: Overdrive!
( Kakyoin gasps )
Tell me,
why did you risk your life
to save me?
( Holly gasps )
♪
Jotaro: Don’t know.
I don’t really have
an answer for that.
Holly: Jotaro,
I see right through you.
All done.
Kakyoin: Thank you
for everything.
Holly: So it’s kakyoin, was it?
You need to rest for a while.
Why don’t you stay here tonight?
Kakyoin: Huh? No, i--
Holly: Papa,
go and get his futon ready.
Joseph: Hmm?
Why do I have to do it?!
I’ve never even liked the idea
of sleeping on the damn floor!
In fact, that futon in my room,
replace it with a real bed!
Holly: No way.
You’re in Japan now, papa,
and here in Japan,
we sleep on the floor.
And i’d prefer if you
call me seiko here.
Joseph: What?!
Holly: The Japanese
also have a word for holy.
Here, the word for it
is "seinaru,"
so that’s why all my friends
call me seiko here. ( Giggles )
Joseph: What the hell is that?!
Holly’s a beautiful name!
I gave it to you mys--
Holly: If you don’t refer to me
as seiko, I won’t answer.
Joseph: Holly!
Holly:
How’s the pain, kakyoin, bad?
Kakyoin: No. I’m fine.
- Joseph: Holly!
- Jotaro: Gimme a break.
Holly: All right, kakyoin, let’s
get you out of that uniform.
- ( Kakyoin gasps )
- Holly: Go on. Take it off.
- Joseph: Holly!
- Holly: Did I hear something?
( Joseph screams )
( Birds chirping )
Joseph: Holly!
Hey, Holly!
Come on! Where are you?
I want you to look at this.
You gave me jotaro’s pants.
Where the heck are mine?
They’re the right size and all,
but i’m not wearin’ these.
Hey, Holly!
Oh, i’m supposed to call her
seiko, or she won’t answer me.
Hmm.
No! My daughter has one name.
Answer me, Holly!
Jotaro: All right,
time for school.
I’m actually gonna go. Hmm.
That’s weird.
Holly: Here is
your goodbye kiss.
Jotaro: That’s usually
how my mornings play out.
♪
( Kakyoin gasps )
Avdol: Huh?
No. Mrs. Kujo!
Mrs. Kujo, please, wake up.
- ( Holly panting )
- Avdol: She’s burning up.
Is she sick?
( Holly gasps )
Avdol: No. This can’t be.
Mrs. Kujo, please.
Forgive me.
No. How did this happen?
It’s transparent.
She has a stand.
Mrs. Kujo has materialized
her own stand!
Well,
but this high fever.
The stand
is doing damage to her.
We were all so relieved
that dio’s body
had only affected
jojo and Mr. Joestar.
We were so certain
Mrs. Kujo was fine.
But that’s just
what we wanted to believe.
It’s impossible
for her to escape that.
As long as she has
joestar blood in her veins,
there will inevitably
be an effect from dio.
But still...
A stand is controlled
by an individual’s
own mental strength,
and they move according to
that person’s fighting instinct.
Mrs. Kujo is
a kind and peaceful woman
who doesn’t have the power
to resist dio’s curse.
She doesn’t have the strength
she needs to control her stand.
This has to be why her stand
is making her so ill.
It’s acting against her,
not with her.
It’s only getting worse.
This is very bad.
At this rate, she’ll die.
She’ll be overcome!
( Gasps )
Joseph: She has a stand?
( Shudders ) Holly.
( Jotaro gasps )
Joseph: Nooooo!
( Sobs )
This is the one thing
I feared the most.
This is very last thing
I ever wanted to happen.
My daughter
has developed a stand as well.
I’ve always known
she’s too weak.
She can’t withstand it.
I knew if this day came,
it would destroy her.
She doesn’t have the strength
needed to repel dio’s curse.
( Cries )
( Winces )
Jotaro: Tell me. What we can do?
♪
Joseph: Okay.
To start, we must find dio.
The only way to break this curse
is to find dio and kill him!
Finding him is the problem.
No matter how many times I try,
he’s always hiding
in the darkness.
In every spirit photo I take,
the background is black.
We won’t be able to locate him
with my photographs.
Avdol: We’ve used various
methods to try and analyze them,
but with this darkness,
we always come up with nothing.
Jotaro: Hey, you should have
mentioned this to me sooner.
Let me look.
I might be able to find out...
What’s hiding in that darkness.
It’s found something
within the shadows.
My stand
can move accurately enough
to pull a flesh bud
from someone’s brain
and catch a bullet.
Let’s have it sketch
what it sees.
Joseph: Hmm.
( Jotaro gasps )
Avdol: No way!
It saw a fly through all that!
Joseph: Yeah, but how in
the hell is a fly gonna help us?
Avdol: Wait a second.
I’ve seen this fly before.
Joseph: What?
Avdol: Do you have
an encyclopedia?
Jotaro: We do have a library.
Avdol: Let me have the sketch.
I’ll do some research!
( Holly moans )
Joseph: Hmm. Oh, Holly.
Holly: Papa, I...
Joseph: You just rest.
Jotaro, get some water.
♪
Avdol: Hmm.
You seem to be doing well.
Sorry, but i’m
a little busy right now.
Kakyoin: Can your own stand
really do that to you, kill you?
Avdol: Yes.
I have seen far too many people
suffer exactly that same fate.
Kakyoin: Really?
Avdol: It’s limited
to her back right now,
but that stand will grow
like a fiendish vine,
and it won’t stop
until her whole body
is overtaken and bound.
Her fever will rise,
and her illness will worsen,
she’ll fall into a coma
and never wake up, and then...
She’ll die.
( Kakyoin gasps )
Avdol: Your average person
would see this
as some rare and unknown disease
that no doctor in the world
would be able to treat.
And normally neither you nor I
could do anything about it.
( Kakyoin shudders )
Avdol: But there is still hope.
It will take 50 days for
her body to reach that state.
We just have to find
and defeat dio before that.
If we can sever the link
her stand has with dio,
we can save her.
( Holly sighs )
Thank you for that, jotaro.
I wonder what it was
that came over me today.
I can’t believe I had a fever
and passed out like that.
But that said...
Jotaro: Because it’s
on her back,
she can’t see it.
She has no idea
what’s happened.
Jotaro: Well, you gave us
quite a scare, Holly.
Hey, now that you’re up,
why don’t you brush your teeth?
Say, "ahh."
Holly: Ahh.
Joseph: And let’s
get that face clean.
We’ll tidy up your hair
while we’re at it.
Then let’s take care
of those nails.
Ahh...
Holly: Ahh.
Oh.
Papa, will you help me
change my underwear, too?
- Joseph: Huh?
- ( Holly laughs )
Just relax. I was only kidding.
All right, then.
What do you want
for dinner, jotaro?
- Joseph: Hey.
- Jotaro: Don’t move!
- You just stay in bed.
- Joseph: Huh?
Jotaro: I just meant
you should stay put,
at least
until your fever breaks.
Now be quiet, and get better.
Joseph: He’s right.
Rest.
Holly: Heh. Okay.
I kinda like this.
Everyone’s so nice
when I get sick.
Having a little cold
isn’t so bad from time to time.
( Sighs )
Joseph: What? Holly!
Say something.
She--she lost
consciousness again.
Come on.
She was acting fine,
but this fever is so bad.
It’s spiked.
She was
just putting on a good front.
I know she didn’t say anything,
but my daughter is
definitely aware of her stand.
She was doing her best just now
to try and hide it from us.
My guess is that she didn’t
want us to worry about her.
My daughter’s
always been like that.
Avdol: Mr. Joestar,
i’ve found it.
I know where that fly is from.
It’s this one.
Narrator: The nile tsetse fly,
a bloodsucking insect prevalent
in the nile river basin
the tsetse genus
includes a striped species
known as the aswan tsetse fly.
Joseph: Egypt.
Avdol: And we’ve narrowed it
down to the aswan region.
Dio is there.
Kakyoin: So he is
in Egypt after all.
Jotaro: Kakyoin.
Joseph: What do
you mean by that?
Kakyoin: The flesh bud
was planted into my brain
three months ago.
That’s when I met dio.
I was on a trip
with my family in Egypt.
We were there touring the nile.
Avdol: You were in Egypt, too.
It seems for some reason,
dio wants to remain
in that area.
Kakyoin:
So when are we leaving?
Because i’ll be going with you.
( Both gasp )
Jotaro: Seriously?
Why would you want to do that?
Kakyoin: To be
completely honest,
I have no idea
why I want to either.
It’s just something
I feel compelled to do.
( Jotaro scoffs )
Kakyoin: Let’s just say
that you opened my eyes.
It’s that simple.
Joseph: Holly, we’re gonna
save you, no matter what.
You have my word.
There’s nothing
for you to worry about.
We are gonna make you better.
I promise.
Just take it easy, and rest.
Kakyoin: Jojo’s mother,
Holly, has the ability
to calm a person’s soul
and put their minds at ease.
People feel relaxed
just by being near her.
This may sound strange,
but if I ever fall in love,
i’d want it to be
with someone like her.
I’d feel the need
to protect her.
I’d do anything to see her
feeling better and smiling.
Avdol: Indeed.
Joseph: There’s no time!
We leave immediately!
♪
We can trust ’em.
They’re doctors from
the speedwagon foundation.
They’re going to stay with her
and take care of Holly
around the clock.
Avdol: Jojo, since I am
a fortuneteller by trade,
i’d like to name your stand
before we go.
Joseph: Huh? Name it?
Avdol: With the tarot,
the cards of fate.
Do not look, but let chance
guide your choice.
It will not only suggest to us
your destiny,
but also the abilities
of your stand.
The star card.
I shall name your stand...
Star platinum!
Narrator: Jotaro kujo.
Stand name, star platinum.
Abilities, precision in movement
and extreme strength.
Joseph joestar.
Stand name, hermit purple.
Abilities, spirit photography.
Mohammed avdol.
Stand name, magician’s red.
Abilities, fire and heat.
Noriaki kakyoin.
Stand name, hierophant green.
Abilities,
remote stand manipulation
and emerald splash.
Joseph: All right, we’re off!
Let’s hit the road.
♪
♪ All the old paintings
on the tomb ♪
♪ they do the sand dance,
don’t you know ♪
♪ if they move too quick
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re falling down
like a domino ♪
♪ all the bazaar men
by the nile ♪
♪ they got the money on a bet
♪ gold crocodiles
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they snap their teeth
on your cigarette ♪
♪ foreign types
with the hookah pipes say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian
♪ The blond waitresses
take their trays ♪
♪ they spin around,
and they cross the floor ♪
♪ they’ve got the moves
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ you drop your drink
♪ then they bring you more
♪ all the school kids
so sick of books ♪
♪ they like the punk
and the metal band ♪
♪ when the buzzer rings
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re walking
like an Egyptian ♪
♪ all the kids
in the marketplace say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian
♪
Dio: As I thought,
they found out where I am.
So then, will you come to Egypt,
Joseph and jotaro?
( Joseph gasps )
He saw us. I definitely felt
dio looking at us just now.
Jotaro: Yeah.
Joseph: Be careful.
A new stand user
could already be on this plane.
( Insect buzzing )