Narrator: Previously
on "jojo’s bizarre adventure"...
Polnareff: Tum-ta-da-da!
Here he is!
That sly bastard avdol was
still alive! Isn’t that great?!
( Hums fanfare )
Avdol: Mr. Joestar and jotaro
were the ones
who tended to the wounds
on my head back in India
after I was shot by hol horse.
Joseph: But I also had avdol
do some shopping for me
while he was laying low.
♪
That’s right! From here on out,
we’re riding to Egypt in this!
( Polnareff gasps )
You’ve gotta be kidding!
How did you afford this?!
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Narrator: The terrain has
changed for jotaro and company,
who’ve entered
what divers across the globe
call the most beautiful sea
in the world.
Flanked on the east and west
by desert, the red sea
was once believed to have been
surrounded by crimson sands.
Today its general
lack of pollution
and inflowing river water
makes it one
of the most immaculate
bodies of water on earth.
Polnareff: Hang on a minute.
Are you telling me
you can drive this thing, avdol?
Avdol: Tsk, tsk. It’s not
a problem whatsoever, polnareff.
Polnareff: Wow.
Joseph: And avdol’s
not the only one.
Jotaro: Don’t even
think about it.
I refuse to let you
put us through another crash.
Joseph: Well, you sure seem
to be in a foul mood today.
Kakyoin: So this is a submarine.
I have to say
i’m a bit surprised.
It’s a lot more spacious
than I expected.
Joseph: Isn’t it?
Rich folks typically
use vessels like these
when they want
to get away for a while
and explore the seafloor
for pleasure.
As you can see,
it even has windows.
- Polnareff: Ooh! C’est genial.
- Joseph: Whoa there!
Polnareff: You know,
come to think of it,
i’ve always sort of liked
this kind of thing,
although I wish I could have
ridden in one with a cute girl.
Avdol: Once again,
you haven’t changed, polnareff.
Now could you please try just
once to take this seriously?
- ( Console beeping )
- Polnareff: Hmm? What’s that?
Joseph: This is sonar.
It uses reflected sound waves
to detect underwater objects,
much like radar.
- Polnareff: Wow.
- Avdol: All clear.
I’m not picking up
anything in our vicinity.
Joseph: With this machine,
we can detect anyone
trying to attack us,
no matter which direction
the enemy decides to come from.
Jotaro: But if someone
did attack us in here,
there’d be
nowhere for us to run.
We’d be like trapped rats.
Don’t forget where we are,
60 meters below sea level.
Kakyoin: This sub is amazing,
but I guess it is a pleasure
cruiser for the wealthy.
It has a refrigerator,
a coffee maker,
and it’s even equipped with
the latest in satellite phones.
- Polnareff: Hey, kakyoin...
- Joseph: Ah. I should call...
Polnareff: Would you mind
getting me a drink
while you’re up?
I’m dyin’ of thirst here.
- Avdol: I’ll take one, too.
- Kakyoin: Sure.
- ( Bottles rattle )
- Jotaro: Hmm?
Kakyoin: Is cola okay?
Jotaro: Old man...
Why are you just standing there?
Something bugging you?
Joseph: Men, I need you
to give me a moment’s quiet.
I just remembered
I have a phone call to make.
Polnareff:
A phone call? To where?
Kakyoin: "Where?" Is right.
Who would you need to call
from a submarine
in the middle of the red sea?
Joseph: Someone important,
I assure you.
You might even call it
a delicate matter,
so, as I said,
I need you all to be quiet.
( Traffic honking )
Suzie q: Oh, heavens me.
I just don’t know.
Which one should I pick?
Between the two,
the sparkly design
is much more to my liking,
but is it appropriate
for the charity event tomorrow?
Perhaps a refreshing white
would be better.
Oh, what do you think, rosas?
Rosas: Both of the gowns
look lovely on you, madam.
- ( Telephone rings )
- Suzie q: Hmm? Coming!
- ( Rosas gasps )
- ( Ring )
Suzie q: Yes? Hello.
Oh, Joseph, darling, it’s you!
- ( Rosas gasps )
- Suzie q: Where have you been?
And where are you calling from?
What was that, dear?
It’s a bit hard to hear you.
Joseph: Right. Sorry.
I’m at a hotel.
Here’s the thing.
I hate to say it,
but, uh, I have to attend
some unexpected business
that’s come up.
Suzie q: Oh, goodness.
It must be difficult
traveling on business
to another country
right after going to Japan.
It’s been nearly a month,
hasn’t it?
Joseph: Yeah, it has. Sorry.
By the way, Suzie,
have you spoken to Holly?
Suzie q: Why, yes, I have.
In fact, I spoke to her
on the phone yesterday.
She mentioned catching a cold
that’s developed
into a bout of pneumonia.
She tried convincing me
that it wasn’t serious,
but i’m thinking
about going to visit her.
Joseph: No, don’t.
There’s no need for that.
I’m positive
she’ll recover quickly.
You’re such a worrywart.
Polnareff: So this is what
he meant by a delicate matter?
Avdol: Indeed. Madam joestar
is still as effervescent
as someone half her age,
so he checks in now and again
to ensure she doesn’t visit
miss Holly in Japan.
That way,
she’s protected from the truth.
Kakyoin: Are you
saying that she--
avdol: I am.
She hasn’t been told anything.
There’s no need
to worry her unnecessarily.
Joseph: There’s nothing
to worry about.
Suzie q: Well, if you say so.
All right, I understand.
I’ll hold off on going to Japan.
( Helicopter blades thrumming )
While I have you on the line,
there’s something
I need to ask you.
I’m having a hard time
deciding whether
I should wear the white dress
or the purple one.
Joseph: Is that so?
Suzie, I need to speak to rosas.
Could you pass the phone to him?
Suzie q: What?!
- Rosas: Madam...
- Suzie q: Huh?
Rosas: Have you considered
wearing your blue dress
to the event?
If I remember correctly,
it’s in the back of the closet.
Suzie q: Hmm. That’s right.
I’ll go and have a look at it.
( Door opens )
Rosas: Hello, master Joseph.
- It’s me, rosas.
- Joseph: Where’s Suzie?
Rosas: She left the room, sir.
There’s no chance
of her overhearing
our conversation now.
Joseph: I see.
I’m actually calling
from the submarine
that the two of us spoke of
a while back.
Rosas: Oh. Then I take it
you were successful
in reuniting
with master avdol?
Joseph: That’s right. Now, then,
tell me about holly’s condition.
Surely by now you’ve gotten hold
of the doctors
from the speedwagon foundation.
Rosas: Well, actually...
When speaking
to her mother on the phone,
miss Holly says that her illness
is nothing more than a cold.
She’s quite insistent
that there’s no cause for alarm,
but her condition
worsens by the day.
Master Joseph, don’t you think
the time has finally come
to tell madam joestar the truth?
( Joseph sighs )
No. There’s no need
to get her riled up.
We’re going to put an end
to all this very soon.
I want Holly to go back
to her normal life
and never know
about any of this.
Don’t inform my wife
of what’s going on
under any circumstances.
I’ll call again soon.
Rosas: If that is
what you wish, sir.
- I pray for your safe return.
- ( Beep )
Suzie q: Oh, no! Did you
hang up the phone already?
I wasn’t finished
talking to him yet.
Rosas: Oh, madam--
Suzie q: It’s no matter.
Why don’t we have some tea?
You will join me for a cup,
won’t you?
- Hmm?
- Rosas: Madam!
Oh, please, madam, allow me
to serve the tea for you.
Are you sure?
Kakyoin: I’m sorry
you have to do that, truly.
Polnareff: But you
can rest easy,
because we’re
right here behind you.
We’ll be in Egypt
before you know it.
Avdol: We must defeat dio
as soon as we can
and save miss Holly
from his curse.
I have returned from the brink
for this very reason.
Joseph: Mm.
Thanks, you guys, really.
( Polnareff laughs )
Driving this
is actually pretty easy.
I suppose that’s how
you were making it
look so simple, avdol.
- ( Clang )
- ( Gasps )
Avdol: For pete’s sake!
Hey, don’t get so carried away.
Believe it or not,
the sea has its fair share
of rough terrain.
Polnareff: Yeah, yeah, I know.
All right, let’s speed
this tub up a little bi--
( clattering, banging )
Avdol: Polnareff,
what are you doing?!
Polnareff: I had
nothing to do with that!
You gotta believe me!
( Yawns )
I’m so tired.
Tell me when we’re almost there.
- ( Yawns )
- ( Kakyoin sighs )
One, two, three, four, five.
Oh, there’s exactly
five cups in here.
Polnareff: Hey!
Hurry up,
and make the coffee, man.
I want some now.
Kakyoin: Then why don’t
you make it yourself?!
( Avdol gasps )
Good news! I’ve just
spotted the coast of Africa.
- We’ll be there soon.
- ( Polnareff chuckles )
♪
Avdol: Sea water has worn away
the rocks and carved out
an underwater tunnel
near this coral reef.
The exit is 200 meters inland,
which makes this
the perfect spot
for us to surface.
Joseph: At long last,
we’ve finally made it.
Polnareff: Enfin!
It took long enough.
Joseph: So this is Egypt.
( Kakyoin grunts )
Avdol: It is. We have arrived.
- ( Polnareff chuckles )
- Avdol: What’s so funny?
Polnareff: Nothing. I’m just
feeling sort of happy is all.
It’s been quite a while
since the five of us were
all gathered together like this.
( All grunt )
( Submarine creaking )
Jotaro: Hmm?
Hey, kakyoin...
Why’d you grab six cups
for five people?
Kakyoin: That’s peculiar.
I guess I didn’t notice.
I could have sworn it was five.
Joseph: Huh?
( Gasps )
( Others gasp )
Joseph: What the--
( gags )
- Jotaro: Old man!
- Kakyoin: Mr. Joestar!
♪
( Stand shrieks )
- Polnareff: Impossible!
- Avdol: It’s a stand!
I don’t know how,
but it managed to sneak aboard!
( All gasp )
Star platinum: Ora!
( Jotaro grunts )
- Polnareff: It disappeared!
- Jotaro: No, it didn’t.
Avdol: It transformed!
I’m sure of it.
The stand disguised itself
as one of the gauges,
just like with the coffee cup!
Polnareff: Come again?! Merde!
The coral reef is right there!
And we were only a few hundred
meters from reaching Egypt.
Kakyoin: On the bright side,
it looks like Mr. Joestar
was only knocked unconscious.
The problem is his hand.
- ( Telephone rings )
- Polnareff: Huh? ( Gasps )
The phone?! Who’d be calling us
at a time like this?!
Kakyoin: Ignore it, polnareff!
We have to stay focused!
Avdol: It’s the high priestess.
- ( Jotaro gasps )
- Avdol: Careful.
Our enemy’s using a deadly stand
called the high priestess.
Jotaro: So how do we win?
Avdol: By knowing the user.
The name of this
particular stand user is Rose.
She has the ability to control
her stand from far away,
so she’s most likely on land.
Kakyoin: What’s its power?
Avdol: It can turn into
almost any inanimate object,
as long as it comes
from a mineral--
plastics, metal,
glass, or vinyl.
Its transformations are perfect.
There’s no way
to recognize the thing
until it decides to attack.
Polnareff: That’s freaky,
but how did it
sneak aboard the submarine
in the first place?
( Alarm blaring )
( Polnareff gasps )
I get it now.
So that’s how it did it.
How simple.
It cut a hole and moseyed on in.
Avdol: The stand found a way
to damage the ballast tanks.
We’re sinking even faster now!
Kakyoin: Not to mention
we’re losing oxygen!
We’ve got to get out of here!
( Telephone rings )
Polnareff: Mon dieu!
Shut up!
Whoever’s calling
has horrible timing!
( Gasps ) Jotaro!
Hey! Remember anything
we touch might be the--
Suzie q: Hi again, Joseph.
It’s me!
We weren’t finished
with the conversation
we were having earlier,
so I made rosas
give me your number.
- ( Water rushing )
- ( Alarm blaring )
Hmm?
Why aren’t you speaking?
And come to think of it,
what’s with
all the ruckus over there?
Whatever’s in the background
sounds like a siren.
I also hear running water.
Is a bathtub overflowing?
Jotaro: I’m sorry,
but the old man
can’t come to the phone.
( Suzie q gasps )
I know that voice.
Is that you? Jotaro?
Where’s Joseph?
You should be in Japan.
Why are you
with your grandfather?
Jotaro, answer me!
( Alarm blaring )
( Water rushing )
Jotaro: There’s nothin’
to worry about, grandma Suzie.
( Suzie q gasps )
Jotaro: He’s gonna be just fine,
’cause i’m right here with him.
( Suzie q sighs )
Jotaro: Later. We’ll call back
once things calm down.
Suzie q: Jotaro!
( Line beeps )
Avdol: Brace yourselves, people!
We’re about to hit the bottom!
Polnareff: Oh, my god!
I knew this would happen
to us somehow!
It’s like
every vehicle we ride in
ends up getting destroyed!
Jotaro: That is the last straw.
I’m never riding
in a submarine again.
Crackling )
Suzie q: How strange.
( Beep )
I was getting through
a moment ago,
but now it seems as though
the line’s suddenly gone dead.
( Sighs )
And why was jotaro there?
♪
( Polnareff gasping )
Hey, you guys,
the air is getting
pretty thin in here.
Jotaro: Kakyoin.
I need your help. Did you catch
which one of the gauges
the stand merged with?
Kakyoin: Well,
from what I can tell,
it looked like
it turned into this one.
♪
- ( Light crackles )
- Avdol: Mm?
That’s not it!
Jotaro, it’s already moved!
It’s right behind kakyoin!
( High priestess shrieks )
Kakyoin: Hierophant green!
( Yells )
Avdol: Kakyoin!
( Star platinum grunts ) Ora!
( High priestess shrieks )
Avdol: Everyone,
head for the door quickly!
The stand’s become part
of the hull’s surface
and is traveling
through the machines!
Polnareff: Yeah,
you say that, but...
Avdol: If we stay
in this room any longer,
there’s a very good chance
that none of us
will leave with our lives.
- Kakyoin, are you all right?
- Kakyoin: Yes, i’m fine.
Avdol: Come on, everyone.
To the next room!
We’ll seal the room off
and trap it inside.
( Gasps )
( High priestess growling )
Avdol: There’s no way!
It already moved to the door
and transformed itself
into the wheel.
I have to let go
before it’s too late.
Its claws were
able to slice through
Mr. Joestar’s prosthetic hand
like it was nothing.
What?!
( High priestess grunting )
Polnareff: Oh, yeah! We got it!
Avdol: That was close.
Jotaro: Apparently
our little friend here
isn’t as fast as star platinum.
So what should we do with it?
Polnareff:
Show no mercy, jotaro.
Don’t hesitate. Here’s an idea.
Why don’t we begin
by ripping off its little head?
Jotaro: Works for me.
( High priestess grunting )
( Jotaro gasps )
- Avdol: Eh?
- Jotaro: That bastard.
( High priestess laughs )
Jotaro: It transformed
into a freakin’ razor!
( High priestess laughs )
Jotaro: How are we
gonna beat it?!
Avdol: It’s strong! Damn!
( Joseph coughs )
( High priestess laughing )
Kakyoin: I can’t believe
it outsmarted jotaro.
What an enemy.
Joseph: Huh?
What the hell is going on?
Whatever’s happening here,
i’m pretty sure
that we’re in a pinch!
Jotaro: Shut up, old man!
Avdol: That beast
will attack us if we touch it,
which means we should use
our stands instead.
Magician’s red!
Polnareff: Silver chariot!
That stand’s a tough one.
Chariot’s rapier
can’t Pierce its armor.
( High priestess laughs )
Joseph: Come on!
Pick up the pace!
We’ve got to attack
before it gets away.
Avdol: I need
all of you to stand back!
( Polnareff inhales ) There’s
still some oxygen over here.
Kakyoin: But it’s going
to run out before long.
Avdol: Are you all right, sir?
- Joseph: Yeah.
- Avdol: Forget it, jotaro!
It’ll only transform again.
We’re taking on water fast,
so we need to find a way
to trap that thing.
We’ll figure out
how to fight it then.
♪
( High priestess laughing )
Jotaro: Don’t get too cocky,
because this battle isn’t over.
I’ll kick your ass soon enough.
♪
Joseph: What’d you say?!
Jotaro, why in the hell
would you answer
a phone call from Suzie?
Damn it. You know, you really
shouldn’t have done that.
Whatever. We’ll talk about it
when we get out of this mess.
Leave everything to me.
Jotaro: Yeah?
Do you have a plan?
Joseph: You bet,
and it’s a brilliant one!
The one and only Joseph joestar
has been in more situations
like this than he can count
on the prosthetic hand
he left behind.
♪
Suzie q: For the life of me,
I can’t begin to understand
why jotaro is with Joseph.
Has Joseph said anything?
Rosas: No, ma’am.
Suzie q: Although my heart
jumped with joy
to hear that boy’s voice
after so long.
I’ve heard
my precious, little grandson
has been quite the handful
as of late,
but deep down,
he’s a sweet child
who cares very much
for his family.
Whatever they’re doing,
i’m sure he’s helping Joseph
as much as he can.
♪
Rosas: You have no idea
how right you are, madam.
Master jotaro and master Joseph
are most likely
in the midst of battling
a common enemy as we speak.
They’re fighting tooth and nail
to save miss Holly,
someone very dear to them,
from a curse of unbridled evil.
Kakyoin: What do we do now?!
I have a feeling
that she-devil of a stand
isn’t really the one
who’s actually trapped here.
Sooner or later,
that monster is going to cut
its way out of that room
and catch up to us!
Avdol: And to make
matters even worse,
as long as we’re surrounded
by all this machinery,
we’re sitting ducks.
The submarine
is done for anyway.
We need to abandon ship
and escape.
We’ll just have to find some
other way to make it to Egypt.
Polnareff: Are you forgetting
that we’re 40 meters
below sea level?
I know it doesn’t sound
that far down,
but how are we supposed
to get out of here?
Are we really scuba diving
all the way there?
In my entire life, i’ve
never done anything like this.
Joseph: Hurry, everyone!
Suit up on the double!
Jotaro: Oh, good grief.
Joseph: Ah, I just realized
there’s no way
i’ll be able to suit up
in time with this busted hand.
Can you help me out, jotaro?
Jotaro: Do it yourself.
♪
( High priestess laughs )
♪ All the old paintings
on the tomb ♪
♪ they do the sand dance,
don’t you know ♪
♪ if they move too quick
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re falling down
like a domino ♪
♪ all the bazaar men
by the nile ♪
♪ they got the money on a bet
♪ gold crocodiles
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they snap their teeth
on your cigarette ♪
♪ foreign types
with the hookah pipes say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian
♪ The blond waitresses
take their trays ♪
♪ they spin around,
and they cross the floor ♪
♪ they’ve got the moves
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ you drop your drink
♪ then they bring you more
♪ all the school kids
so sick of books ♪
♪ they like the punk
and the metal band ♪
♪ when the buzzer rings
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re walking
like an Egyptian ♪
♪ all the kids
in the marketplace say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian