♪
Narrator: With enyaba in tow
and a new carriage to boot,
jojo and crew arrived
in the coastal town of Karachi,
pakistan’s industrial
and financial center
located
in the indus river delta.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
( Overlapping chatter )
Joseph: Oh.
Hey, a doner kebab joint.
Let’s stop and
get something to eat.
( Slurps )
( Horse neighs )
Narrator: The doner kebab,
it’s been called the hamburger
of the middle east.
A slab of meat
is placed on a spit,
its outer layer roasting
as it turns.
Before long,
the meat is cooked, sliced,
and served with any number
of sides and condiments.
- Joseph: Excuse me, sir.
- Vendor: Eh?
Joseph: I’d like five of those.
Vendor: That’ll be 1,000 yen.
Joseph: 1,000 yen?
Narrator: In the middle east,
Japanese and western
business practices
are by no means universal.
Namely, prices change
and are open to negotiation.
With no understanding
of how to haggle
or how to value goods for sale,
first-time visitors can become
easy targets for exploitation,
but here, people don’t see such
exploitation as a bad thing.
The swindled are deserving
of the label fool, not victim.
Haggling takes guts
and ingenuity.
Joseph: Really?
Narrator: The first step
is the art of the bluff.
Make it clear
you see through the trick.
Let him know you’re no slouch.
( Joseph laughs )
Don’t mock me now.
That’s far too much
for a handful of kebabs.
Narrator: A hearty laugh
always helps. Then...
Vendor: How much
would you buy ’em for?
Narrator: The merchant
will test the waters.
Joseph: Make it
250 yen for five.
Narrator: In return,
you throw out a price so low,
you can’t help but blush.
And then...
( Vendor laughs )
Narrator: He’ll act as if
you have no sense at all.
Catching on?
Vendor: If I sold them
for that cheap,
i’d be out on the streets,
and my wife and seven children
would starve to death. ( Gags )
Narrator: Then he’ll gesture
the old throat slash,
but you can’t
give up the fight just yet.
Joseph: Then maybe i’ll
just buy them somewhere else.
Narrator: Pretend
that you’re leaving.
Vendor: Okay, friend, you win.
I very much like foreigners.
I’ll sell you five for 700 yen.
Narrator: He’ll try to stop you.
Joseph: Then make it 300.
Narrator:
Let the haggling begin!
- Vendor: 600!
- Joseph: 350!
- Vendor: 550!
- Joseph: 400!
Vendor: 450!
Both: 425!
Joseph: I’ll take ’em.
All right. I got them for less
than half his original price.
Take that.
I made out like a bandit.
Narrator: And just
as you think you won...
Vendor: I usually
sell five for 150 yen.
Bye-bye. Thank you, sir.
♪
Joseph: Huh?
- Holy crap!
- Polnareff: Huh?
Joseph: Turn around!
That old lady’s awake.
( Both gasp )
( Enyaba shuddering )
I--i promise you...
I haven’t said anything
to any of them, I swear.
Wh-why are you here?
What could
you possibly want with me?
Did you think
I would actually tell them
the secret of lord dio’s stand?
I am and shall always be
his loyal servant.
Joseph: Eh?
♪
( Men gasping )
( Worms chitter )
( Enyaba shuddering )
( Screams )
( Horse neighs )
Polnareff: Gross.
What are they?
Some kind of worms?
Enyaba: Why?
I have done nothing wrong!
Why have you come here
to kill me?!
Stand user: Lord dio
places his trust in no one,
not even you, enyaba.
That is why.
And it’s my job to make sure
that you never speak again.
As for the rest of you...
The only way
you’re leaving is in pieces.
( Enyaba gags )
Polnareff: Memere!
( Enyaba screams )
Joseph: What?
Dan: You can call me Dan,
Dan of steel.
My stand represents
the one and only lovers card.
I will see to it
that you all meet the same fate
as that pathetic witch enyaba.
Polnareff: How could you?!
That old lady was one
of your own, you son of a--
memere!
( Enyaba gags )
Lies. Lies.
These are all lies.
This isn’t happening.
Lord dio would never
do this to me.
I am his loyal servant, loyal.
Kakyoin: These things
coming out of her body
they’re definitely
not some stand.
Don’t you see it?
They’re actual tentacles.
Enyaba: I have dedicated
everything to him.
Lord dio would never
do me such harm.
He’d never plant
a flesh bud in me.
Kakyoin: What did she say?
Lord dio is
my only reason for living.
We trust each other
wholeheartedly. ( Gags )
Polnareff: Hold on!
( Grunts )
( Worms squeal )
Joseph: See that?
The sun just disintegrated them!
The flesh bud, it’s made
out of dio’s own cells.
Dan: Precisely.
I must say you are
quite the perceptive one.
Since you’re so astute,
i’ll continue.
This is what a full-grown
flesh bud looks like.
I want to kill her,
not control her,
so I just grew it
inside the old bag.
Enyaba, you may be the very one
who told lord dio
about the stands,
but you’re a fool to think that
a man with such complete power
would ever trust
a feeble old woman like you.
- ( Enyaba gagging )
- Dan: Unfortunately,
it’s a point
you failed to realize.
Joseph: Old lady!
What’s the true identity
of dio’s stand?
- Dan: Huh?
- ( All gasp )
Joseph: Tell us!
You placed all your hope in dio.
You trusted him
with your life and your son’s.
And now after
all you’ve sacrificed,
you know he’s not the man
you thought he was.
You know i’m right.
We must defeat dio,
no matter the cost.
You have to tell us.
We need to know!
Tell us what we need to know
about dio’s stand
before it’s too late!
Enyaba: D-dio...
My lord.
♪
( Gasps )
He believes in me, so i’ll
serve him even in death.
- I won’t betray him.
- Joseph: Huh?
( Enyaba sighs )
Joseph: Oh, god!
( Dan laughing )
How pathetic. ( Laughs )
It’s laughable
how sad that old woman was.
But the very depth
of her trust in him
should tell you something.
Lord dio’s evil charm is more
powerful than you can imagine.
( Laughs )
♪
( Sips )
Polnareff: The old woman
may have had it out for us,
but she was misled
and sure as hell
didn’t deserve that death.
- I’ll see you join her.
- ( Joseph grunts )
Kakyoin: Four against one,
but we won’t hold back.
Prepare yourself, Dan.
Jotaro: On your feet.
( Dan sips )
Jotaro: Hey, jackass,
stop trying to act cool,
and get up and fight.
This is going down,
whether you want it or not.
Dan: Go ahead.
But you can’t touch me.
I’m Dan of steel, and none
of you can take me down.
You don’t have what it takes.
Star platinum: Ora!
( Dan yells )
( Joseph yells )
Jotaro: What the?
Polnareff: W-what happened,
Mr. Joestar?
He flew back just like that guy.
( Dan groans )
You’re an utter fool.
I was about to explain
my powers when you hit me.
That impatience
nearly killed your grandfather.
I suggest you listen next time.
Jotaro: Huh?
Dan: Listen. My job’s not over.
I have other important business
to attend to.
You really think
I would show my face here
just to kill enyaba? ( Spits )
Joseph: You--you damn bastard.
You told us that your stand
is the lovers. Isn’t that right?
So tell us!
What the hell does it do?!
Dan: What’s the point
in telling you now?
The battle’s already begun,
Mr. Joestar.
( Men gasping )
Dan: You’re all simpletons.
You do know,
no matter how hard you look,
you won’t be able
to see my stand.
( Boy humming a tune )
- Dan: Hey, half pint.
- Boy: Hmm?
Dan: You want some cash?
It’s all yours
if you can hit me in the leg
with that broom.
Boy: Whoa.
Oh.
Wha?
Joseph: What?
But why would he...
Dan: Now hit me!
( Joseph yells )
Kakyoin: The hell? Now what?
( Joseph gasps )
It--it hurts!
I don’t get it!
It’s like I broke my leg!
You mean you still
haven’t figured it out?
That’s so disappointing.
My stand can’t be seen, because
it’s rooted firmly inside you.
The moment enyaba died,
it entered you.
It got to your brain
through your ear,
and that’s how i’ll get to you.
Joseph: What?!
Dan: My stand and I
are connected, just like yours.
If my stand gets hurt, so do I,
and the reverse is also true.
( The lovers squeals )
Dan: You’re utterly helpless.
If you so much as scratch me,
in that instant,
my stand will react to my pain
by going berserk in your head
and inflicting
the same agony on you.
Not only that, it will deliver
a pain several times greater.
Now i’ll say it once more.
Alone or together,
you won’t be able to lay
a single finger on me.
( Joseph gasps )
Dan: Plus, the lovers has taken
one of lord dio’s flesh buds
into your body.
It’s growing in your brain
as we speak.
Just like it did to enyaba,
it’ll devour you
from the inside out.
( Boy chuckles )
( Joseph screams )
- ( Dan chuckles )
- ( Boy laughs )
Dan: I don’t recall asking you
to strike me again,
you stupid little brat!
( Boy yelps )
( Gasping )
Dan: Well, to be honest,
my stand, the lovers,
isn’t as strong
as you might think it’d be.
It doesn’t have the strength
to move even
a single strand of hair,
making it
the world’s weakest stand.
However...
Power isn’t necessary
if all you want to do
is kill your opponent.
Do you understand, gentlemen?
♪
Unfortunate happens,
like I get into an accident,
a baseball hits me,
or I just trip and fall.
How do you think that would
affect you, Mr. Joestar?
Dan: I might get banged up some,
but your body would suffer
far greater pain than mine.
( Cracks knuckles )
Joseph: What the? How?
How am I feeling your knuckles
cracking in my prosthetic hand?
Dan: You’ve got
10 minutes, old man.
Then your brain
will be eaten through,
and you’ll be a corpse
like enyaba.
( Jotaro growls )
Kakyoin: Jotaro, calm down.
Don’t do anything rash.
Jotaro: Sorry, but no.
I’m gonna kill
this damn tool so quickly,
he won’t have enough time
to feel pain.
( Joseph groaning )
Dan: Kill me
before I feel it, huh?
Sounds interesting.
Do it, then.
I wanna see what happens.
What are you waiting for,
jotaro?
Come on. Let’s see it.
Just what were you
planning to strike?
Tell me. My face?
Or maybe my throat?
♪
What? You mad?
Let’s see what’ll happen.
Don’t back down on me now, man.
Why don’t you try busting
a hole through my chest?
Or how ’bout you give up
on using your stand,
and crack my head open
with a rock?
This one looks
like a prime specimen.
It sure looks
big enough for the job.
Hmm.
Jotaro: You do not want
to underestimate me, pretty boy.
When I say i’m gonna
do something, I do it.
( Dan gasps )
( Joseph groaning )
( Jotaro yells )
Kakyoin: Jotaro, don’t do it!
We’ve already seen
how effective his power is.
Are you trying to kill
your own grandfather?
Polnareff: Uh, this is
jotaro we’re talking about.
He might be.
( Jotaro sputters )
Dan: You dumb,
good-for-nothing punk.
Oh?
( Jotaro groans )
Joseph: Jotaro!
Dan: Don’t you toy with me,
you bastard.
After the geezer kicks
the bucket, you’re next.
Kakyoin: Look out!
( Jotaro groans )
Dan: It’ll be your brain that I
send the lovers in to kill.
Joseph: Stop. What the hell
do you think you’re doing?
( Dan laughs )
( Jotaro growling )
Joseph: This is just insane.
My grandson is being
beaten up to save me.
We’re completely
at this guy’s mercy.
I can’t do anything
while it’s in my brain.
I remember when that poison ring
was placed
around my aorta long ago,
but think, Joseph.
There’s got to be
something you can do.
( Gasps )
( Kakyoin grunts )
Dan: Hmm?
Polnareff: H-hey!
Kakyoin: Jotaro, keep him away
from Mr. Joestar at all costs!
We’re gonna try and get as far
away from him as possible!
Dan: I see.
So that’s your plan?
Putting some distance
between me and the old man
might make my stand’s power
vanish without a trace?
Sorry, but my stand’s
physical weakness
is made up for in other ways.
The lovers
may be physically weak,
but its range is farther
than any stand in existence.
It doesn’t matter
how far they run.
Their lives are forfeit
as long as it remains in a host.
Hmm?
( Gasps ) What’s up?
Hey, jotaro, i’m talking to you.
It’s impolite
not to look at people
when they’re speaking to you.
Look at me!
Jotaro: What’s wrong?
You sound like you’re
starting to lose your cool.
Dan: What’s your plan?
Follow me around
’til grandpa Joseph keels over?
Sounds like a blast.
Jotaro: Dan of steel, was it?
I’ll make you pay for this.
Just a matter of when.
( Dan chuckles )
( Laughs )
Well, if you’re gonna
stick around for a while,
I might as well help myself
to your wallet.
( Click )
Nothing but chump change, huh?
Though I didn’t expect
a guy like you
to be sporting a tag heuer.
I’ll be borrowing this.
( Kakyoin panting )
There!
An electronics store.
Mr. Joestar, they have tvs.
Polnareff: Yeah, so?
Why does that matter now?
Joseph: Come on, polnareff.
Did you really think
we were running away?
I’m going to fight this blasted
stand that’s inside my head.
Polnareff: Fight? Mon dieu, non.
Kakyoin: We only have
a few minutes,
and we’re gonna need your help
to pull this off.
Polnareff: Huh?
Joseph: Hermit purple!
- Kakyoin: That’s it!
- Joseph: Oh, no!
I hoped he was bluffing.
How the hell did he get
inside my brain so damn quickly?
Polnareff: Wow.
If I hadn’t seen it myself,
I wouldn’t have believed it.
At least now we know for sure
that it’s in there.
But I still don’t see how we’re
going to destroy the thing
kakyoin: By having our stands
enter Mr. Joestar’s ear canal
to find and destroy the monster.
( Polnareff gasps )
Are you crazy?
Kakyoin: Stands are simply
materializations of energy.
We should be able
to shrink them.
Polnareff: You don’t know that.
Joseph: Hey, try not to break
anything while you’re in there.
Kakyoin: There’s no time.
We’re going in now, polnareff.
Polnareff: A-all right.
Kakyoin: Hierophant green!
Polnareff: Silver chariot!
Smaller.
Kakyoin: Get smaller.
We’re going to be entering
a blood vessel.
Polnareff: R-right.
♪
Dan: A drainage ditch.
This could be fun.
I’d try to jump it, but if
I trip and twist my ankle,
it could be real bad
for old man joestar.
Walking all the way to that
bridge would be such a bother.
I’ve got an idea.
Lie down across this ditch,
and make yourself into a bridge.
I’ll just walk on you
to get across.
What now?
You don’t want to be
my bridge or something?
Jotaro: Ah, shut up.
The hell do you
keep yammerin’ about?
Dan: I said
make yourself into a bridge!
You good-for-nothing,
arrogant prick!
( Joseph screams )
Polnareff: What?!
What’s the matter?
Kakyoin: Mr. Joestar.
Joseph: M-my leg,
i-it’s going numb.
( Both gasp )
Joseph: Damn it, jotaro.
What the hell are you doing?
Dan: Aw, don’t look
so upset, jotaro.
( Chuckles )
♪
( Jotaro grunts )
Dan: Come on.
I don’t have all day, you know.
( Jotaro growls )
( Dan chuckles ) Good.
Dan: You’re a rather
sturdy bridge, aren’t you?
Boing, boing, boing.
Impressive.
Hold on.
Almost there.
( Jotaro grunting )
Kakyoin: Mr. Joestar,
I think the stand is here.
Hiding around the thalamus
makes the most sense.
That’s the point
where the nervous system begins.
Polnareff and I will enter
a blood vessel
from inside your inner ear,
then swim through the veins
toward the brainstem.
But to do that, we need to tear
the wall of the blood vessel.
Joseph: Hey, hold on.
You’re using your stands.
Can’t you just slip through it
without cutting me?
Kakyoin: At this size,
it’s not possible.
The blood vessel’s wall
is too thick.
The slit will be microscopic,
so there’ll be no hemorrhaging
to worry about.
The only other issue is time.
Cutting through a blood vessel
or nerve right now
will take several minutes
at least.
Otherwise, the lovers
would have already
done its damage by now.
Though, in all probability,
it may have already started.
( Joseph gasps )
Polnareff: Keeping our stands
this tiny is really exhausting.
It’s taking a ton of stand power
just to get where we can fight.
Silver chariot: On y va!
Joseph: Oh, my god!
I-I really don’t feel so well.
♪
( Dan humming a tune )
♪ All the old paintings
on the tomb ♪
♪ they do the sand dance,
don’t you know ♪
♪ if they move too quick
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re falling down
like a domino ♪
♪ all the bazaar men
by the nile ♪
♪ they got the money on a bet
♪ gold crocodiles
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they snap their teeth
on your cigarette ♪
♪ foreign types
with the hookah pipes say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian
♪ The blond waitresses
take their trays ♪
♪ they spin around,
and they cross the floor ♪
♪ they’ve got the moves
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ you drop your drink
♪ then they bring you more
♪ all the school kids
so sick of books ♪
♪ they like the punk
and the metal band ♪
♪ when the buzzer rings
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re walking
like an Egyptian ♪
♪ all the kids
in the marketplace say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian