♪
( Whistle blows )
Officer: Hey, you! Turn around!
- Yeah, you with the flattop.
- Polnareff: Huh?
Officer: Yeah, you.
You threw this trash, right?
Then it’s
a 500 Singapore dollar fine!
Polnareff: No way. 500?
Officer: The law here
prohibits littering
and fines all violators
for doing so,
and that means you.
Kakyoin:
500 Singapore dollars is--
Joseph: I think that’s
gotta be about 40,000 yen.
Avdol: Trash?
Officer: Are you
clear on that, punk?
Polnareff: Trash?
What are you talking about, sir?
- ( Avdol laughs )
- Polnareff: All I see
on the ground here
is my own luggage,
so you’ve got me
a little confused now.
Would you be so kind
as to tell me
what trash you’re
referring to, officer?
If you’re wrong,
then i’m obeying the law, right?
So where is it?
Officer: You mean
that bag is your luggage?
Polnareff: Yeah, you got it.
Officer: Oh. I’m terribly sorry.
( Men laughing )
( Girl laughing )
Polnareff: Huh?
( Girl scoffs )
Officer: Well,
i-i’ve got to get going, then
polnareff: Shoo, shoo.
What’s up with this kid?
She’s still following us
like a lost puppy.
Joseph: Hey, you, weren’t you
going to see your father
once we got here?
Polnareff: Why don’t you
stop tagging along and go?
You’re here now, so move on.
( Girl scoffs )
I’m meeting up
with him in five days.
I can go
wherever the hell I want.
I’m not taking orders
from you jerks.
Avdol: She mustn’t.
She’ll be in danger
if she stays with us.
Kakyoin: Well, maybe she lacks
the cash for a place to stay.
Joseph: Then that’s it.
We’ll have to get her
a hotel room for a few nights.
Hey, polnareff,
get her to come with us,
and try not to bruise her ego.
Polnareff: You got it.
- Hey.
- Girl: Huh?
Polnareff: You’re stinkin’ poor,
aren’t you?
Consider this your lucky day,
freeloader.
( Girl sighs )
Polnareff: Wha?
Joseph: Oh, for god’s sake,
polnareff.
( Men chuckle )
Avdol: Well, let’s go check in.
Joseph: Okay.
♪
Clerk: I’m terribly sorry, sir,
but we tend to be full
at this time of year.
We no longer have
any large suites available.
May I suggest our double rooms?
Joseph: I guess we’re stuck.
Now, for the rooms, uh...
Avdol and I will share
a room with each other.
Kakyoin: It’d make sense for
jotaro and I to share a room,
since we’re both students.
Does that help, Joseph?
( Jotaro scoffs )
Avdol: Then the last room
goes to polnareff and...
( Girl gasps )
That’s just gross!
Like i’d room with that guy!
Polnareff: You brat.
( Girl whines ) Blehh!
Joseph: Well,
she may be a child,
but let’s give the young lady
her own room.
Excuse me.
We’ll take four rooms, please.
Clerk: Yes, of course.
( Polnareff chuckles )
Fine. I can relax more
in my own room, anyway.
I’m gonna sleep
like a baby tonight.
Let’s go. We’ve been through
all kinds of hell
ever since
the day we left Hong Kong.
We should hurry up
and take a shower
in a place
where it’s actually safe.
( Men chuckle )
Polnareff: See ya.
♪
( Sighs )
Damn it.
I should have guessed.
Couldn’t you guys at least
give us a chance to rest?
Persistent bastards.
Come out.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
That’s some insanely intense
blood lust you’ve got there.
Do me a favor,
and tell me who you are.
My name’s polnareff, so you’ll
know who sent you to hell.
Soul sacrifice:
Well, if you insist,
my name is soul sacrifice.
And since you’re
probably wondering,
my stand is
the card of the devil.
It represents
insanity of the cursed
and a precipitous and
malevolent fall into ruin.
But tell me,
how did you know
I was hiding inside the fridge?
Polnareff: So you
really are that stupid?
You took everything
out of the fridge
and didn’t bother putting
any of it away, you dumb-ass.
( Soul sacrifice scoffs )
Die, polnareff!
Ebony devil!
Polnareff: Silver chariot!
( Soul sacrifice screams )
Polnareff: Wow, you’re
really pathetic, aren’t you?
That ape on the boat
was a far more terrifying
stand user than you.
You realize that you’re
worse at this than a monkey?
( Gasps )
Soul sacrifice: Now look
what you’ve done, polnareff.
( Laughs )
Damn, how dare you
do this to me?
( Cackles )
It hurts!
It really, really hurts!
( Laughs )
Polnareff: What the hell
is with this guy?
Soul sacrifice:
The pain. ( Laughs )
Curse you.
( Chuckles, gags )
How dare you?
How dare you do that to me?
Now I can hold one hell
of a grudge against you.
( Laughs )
Such torture,
such agony must be avenged,
and you’re the pathetic one,
polnareff.
( Laughs )
I let you find me
and attack me on purpose.
You’re a dead man now!
( Screams )
( Crash )
- ( Car horn honks )
- Polnareff: H-he disappeared.
He’s gone.
What the hell is going on?
- ( Slice )
- ( Grunts )
( Gasping )
Wait. What? This is unreal.
When did he cut me?
But I don’t think
I felt an attack.
No, i’m sure of it.
I didn’t feel it.
Mr. Joestar. A stand user
was here, ready to ambush me.
Wait. Is that you, avdol?
Anyway, listen.
I couldn’t figure him out.
I couldn’t tell
if he was weak or strong.
He’s really creepy,
and he got away.
Damn it. What the hell?
You’d better watch out.
Somehow, he was able
to cut my leg.
Avdol: The devil card?
That’s soul sacrifice.
Polnareff, are you absolutely
positive that’s what he said?
Polnareff: Yeah.
I’m racking my brain,
I just don’t see
how it’s possible.
I know for a fact that I
caught a glimpse of his stand.
The thing is, I don’t remember
anything being near me,
but my leg’s been gouged.
But, anyway, I should
be there in five minutes.
You’re in room 1212, aren’t you?
On the 12th floor?
Contact kakyoin and jotaro, too,
will you? Later.
Clerk #2: Front desk.
Polnareff: Hello there.
Is this room service?
I hurt my leg a bit
could you send up
some medicine and bandages
as soon as possible?
This is polnareff, room 912.
Clerk #2: Certainly.
We’ll bring it up
immediately, sir.
( Polnareff grunts )
( Groans )
( Gasps )
Ah, this is
the last thing I need.
No matter how you cut it,
dirty underwear makes
for a really shitty band-aid.
Damn this hotel. ( Sighs )
Joseph: Avdol, I was wondering,
do you know about this guy
who attacked polnareff?
Avdol: Yes.
He is soul sacrifice.
According to rumors,
he’s a native-American shaman
who is also an assassin,
but he’s an utterly
terrifying stand user.
Mafias, militaries, politicians,
lowlifes
the world over hire him.
I’ve seen him before,
and he looks as fierce
as his reputation.
His body is covered in scars,
scars he receives by cunningly
provoking his enemy to attack.
That’s how he gets
the upper hand.
He uses
the so-called power of vengeance
to fully control his stand.
That’s why, to ordinary people,
it appears that a curse
killed the victims.
Joseph: So polnareff
must have fallen
for soul sacrifice’s trick?
Avdol: I’m afraid
that’s what it looks like.
Joseph: What kind
of stand is it?
Avdol: Nobody knows for certain,
because those who’ve seen it
are dead.
We have to decide
how we’re handling this.
Right now, it’s too dangerous
for polnareff to be alone
or any of us.
Joseph: He could try
to kill us one by one.
I mean, it’s something
he might be able to do.
We need to figure out
a strategy.
He’ll be here in five minutes.
Let’s all meet up in this room.
Jotaro: You got it. We’ll see
you in room 1212 soon, old man.
Kakyoin: What was that
all about, jojo?
Jotaro: Let’s go.
Apparently we’re in danger.
Polnareff: What? Now that’s odd.
I can’t find my room key.
I could have sworn
I put it down right here.
Am I going crazy?
Damn it. Where is it?
Now, how the hell am I
gonna get back in here?
Could I tell the front desk
and ask for a new one?
There’s probably
a fine for that.
There it is.
It must have fallen during
all the commotion earlier.
Why did it have to go
all the way to the middle?
( Footsteps pattering )
Hmm? Wha?
What the...
( Gasping )
Hey!
( Groans )
What the hell?! Shampoo?!
Damn it!
This is killing my eyes!
( Ebony devil chattering )
Polnareff: Who’s there?!
Crap, this isn’t good.
I’m a sitting duck under here.
( Groans )
- ( Ebony devil laughs )
- ( Knock on door )
Eh?
Attendant: Mr. Polnareff,
the front desk sent me up here.
I’ve brought you
a first-aid kit.
Polnareff: Get away!
You’ll get yourself killed!
( Attendant gasps )
Sir, what’s happened here?
Polnareff: Get out of here!
I told you,
you’ll get yourself killed!
( Attendant shudders )
♪
( Ebony devil laughing )
( Cackles )
How dare you?!
Polnareff, how dare you
stab one of my eyes out
when I hadn’t
even touched you once?
( Laughs )
Polnareff: Wait. He’s a doll?
What kind of stand is that?
Silver chariot!
Ebony devil: You’re as stupid
as you look. Don’t you get it?
Your stand can’t fight
where you can’t see.
As long as you’re
tied up underneath the bed,
you can’t hurt me.
( Cackles )
( Polnareff yells )
( Ebony devil yelling )
( Knock on door )
Girl: Eh? Huh?
Oh, jojo.
Did you need something?
Jotaro: So you are here.
Listen up.
Don’t leave this room
for a while.
Girl: Huh?
Jotaro: I’ll come
for you again later.
Kakyoin:
Keep your door locked, okay?
And don’t open it
for any strangers.
Girl: Oh, okay.
( Ebony devil yelling )
( Whooping )
Polnareff: Damn it.
How heavy is this bed, anyway?
It’s gotta be
at least 120 kilograms.
There’s no way
I can push it off of me.
I’ve gotta use silver chariot’s
sword to cut these cords
- ( gasps )
- ( Ebony devil yells )
Polnareff: You little bastard.
As soon as I stop attacking,
this happens.
You better believe
i’m gonna keep blindly stabbing
every centimeter of this room!
Ebony devil: Missed me again.
( Laughs )
( Laughing )
( Babbles )
( Yelps )
Looks like the big, scary knight
can’t even pin the tail
on the donkey
when he’s blindfolded.
Talk about dense.
You’re mine now!
( Babbles )
( Polnareff groaning )
( Ebony devil yelling )
Polnareff: Bastard!
I’ve just about had it with you,
you little runt!
( Ebony devil gulps )
Joseph: Huh?
It’s just you two guys?
Avdol: Why isn’t
the girl with you?
Jotaro: Well,
we went to her room
and made sure she was okay.
Kakyoin: We decided against it,
because she
would be vulnerable.
The risk of her
falling under attack
while with us is far too great.
Joseph: Good point.
So we’re just waiting
for polnareff to arrive,
but, man, he’s so late.
It’s already been
way over five minutes.
Ebony devil: Let me out of here!
( Gasps ) Let me out!
Polnareff: Got ya.
Time to snap your spear in half.
♪
( Yells )
( Ebony devil yelling )
Polnareff: Damn it.
All right. At least
i’m finally free of those cords.
Now i’ve got to send chariot
under the bed
and get myself
the hell out of here.
( Ebony devil laughing )
Polnareff: Great.
Now what’s he doing?
Hmm?
Huh?
♪
Hmm?
( Ebony devil chuckling )
Hey, polnareff,
how would you like it
if I took a bite
out of your balls?
( Laughing )
Polnareff: I can’t
believe that a doll
could be such
an obscene little jerk.
En garde!
Ebony devil: Whoa, there.
I’m gonna run off to a place
you can’t see now.
You numskull.
Give the floor
you’re stuck to a good feel.
Go ahead, moron.
( Polnareff gasps )
What? This is...
Ebony devil: The carpet’s soaked
with beer, juice, and alcohol.
You have a well-stocked bar
that I put to good use.
If I had piss in me,
I would have soaked you in it
to make it even wetter.
( Laughs )
Oh, look, a hair dryer,
and it’s lit up
like a fireworks show
at a summer festival.
There’s so many uses for it.
Which one do you think
i’m gonna pick, polnareff?
Now you can style
that ridiculous hair of yours.
( Laughing )
Die.
Time to put an end
to this curse.
Meet your maker, polnareff.
- ( Sword slices )
- Polnareff: Hmph.
You’re not the only one
who can break stuff,
you satanic little pincushion!
( Ebony devil yelps )
What? How did you know
precisely where I was
on top of the bed?
I trapped you underneath it!
Polnareff: Simple.
I broke all the mirrors
so I could see you
hanging over the bed
clear as day from down here.
Sucks to be you!
( Ebony devil screaming )
Polnareff: At last, we meet.
( Ebony devil screams )
Polnareff: Whoa, there.
Polnareff: Now, then...
I have a question.
I seek a man
with two right hands.
He has something to answer for.
Save me some trouble,
and tell me what his stand is.
Ebony devil: You idiot.
No assassin worth a damn
would ever reveal
his stand’s identity.
It only happens
in the face of certain death
for him or his opponent.
You guys are so stupid,
always showing off your stands
everywhere you go.
It’s your own fault that we
know all your weaknesses.
If it weren’t for that mirror,
I would have killed you.
You’re just a moron
who got lucky.
Polnareff: All right, then.
Come at me.
Ebony devil: Eh?
Polnareff: What’s the matter?
Didn’t you say you were
going to bite off my balls
or something, tough guy?
Go ahead, and try it.
I dare you,
you vulgar little shit!
I am gonna...
( Ebony devil babbling )
Polnareff: Slice up
everything except your balls!
( Soul sacrifice screams )
Janitor: Excuse me, sir.
It seems you’ve been
in the bathroom
for quite some time.
Are you feeling all right?
( Yelps )
Avdol: Ah, polnareff,
you’re finally here.
Polnareff: Yeah.
Joseph: You’re
not terribly punctual,
and you look like hell.
Okay, let’s get right to it.
Let’s figure out
what our strategy will be
if soul sacrifice attacks.
Polnareff, pay attention.
Polnareff: You’re joking, right?
( Table slams )
Officer: Answer me, punk!
Why was there a dead boy’s body
in your room?
And what about the dead body
that was in the bathroom?
The two are connected,
aren’t they?
( Polnareff grumbles )
( Officer growls )
Answer me now!
Polnareff: I have the right
to remain silent, officer.
Huh? You’ve finally showed up.
I’ve been waiting a while.
Joseph: I had the speedwagon
foundation strike a deal.
Polnareff should be
released soon enough
without too much hassle.
Avdol: But that was
cutting it close, even for us.
To think that the enemy’s
pursuit would come so early on.
Joseph: Don’t forget
that dio’s body
used to belong
to Jonathan joestar.
While they’re united, he’ll know
everything jotaro and I do.
That’s why his minions’ attacks
are relentless.
But we can use that against him
and read his thoughts
just as he reads ours.
Avdol: Hmm.
Shall I go buy a camera?
Joseph: That won’t be necessary.
I can use my powers
even without a camera.
Avdol: What?
♪
Man: Michael is still not here.
Where the hell is he?
Host: This week’s number three
jumps up five points
from last w--
newscaster: In trading,
the price of gold today ro--
cat: You look delicious. Meow.
Cartoon: Oh, no!
Avdol: Very strange.
The channels are changing,
as if the TV
has a mind of its own.
Joseph: It’s searching for
words from among the channels
and connecting them
into a sentence,
creating a message for the ear,
not the eye.
Woman: It looks like there...
Man: Is a...
Cat: There is a...
Joseph: There.
I think the first part
is "there is a..."
- Announcer: Trai...
- Woman #2: ...Tor...
Singer: ♪ who’s among...
Singer #2: ♪ us all
Joseph: Wait. What was that?
What the hell did it just say?
Avdol: I could be wrong,
but I think it said
that there is a traitor
who is walking among us.
- Man: ...Ka...
- Announcer: ...Kyo...
- Man #2: In...
- Cartoon: Beware...
- Man #2: Of...
- Woman #3: Him.
- Man #3: Di...
- Woman #4: O’s...
- Woman #5: Loy...
- Man #1: ...Al...
Cartoon: Servant!
Joseph: Kakyoin?
What? It can’t be.
Avdol: That’s impossible.
Kakyoin is dio’s servant?
( Gasps )
♪
( Joseph gasps ) This is...
Dio: Joestar, you bastard,
you’re watching me.
Well, watch this.
Joseph: Dio!
Avdol: He found us! Look out!
( Groans ) But that
can’t be true, can it?
Joseph: You know
as well as I do.
Hermit purple says
kakyoin is a traitor,
a servant to dio, who will
at some point betray all of us.
Avdol: It can’t be!
Joseph: There must be a reason.
I won’t believe
kakyoin is a traitor.
There has to be an explanation.
We’ll have to be
even more alert.
If he is
still connected with dio,
he could exterminate any one
of us while we’re sleeping.
He’d be just like
dio’s very own trojan horse.
So then, where is kakyoin?
Avdol: He’s with jotaro.
♪
♪ all the old paintings
on the tomb ♪
♪ they do the sand dance,
don’t you know ♪
♪ if they move too quick
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re falling down
like a domino ♪
♪ all the bazaar men
by the nile ♪
♪ they got the money on a bet
♪ gold crocodiles
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they snap their teeth
on your cigarette ♪
♪ foreign types
with the hookah pipes say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian
♪ the blond waitresses
take their trays ♪
♪ they spin around,
and they cross the floor ♪
♪ they’ve got the moves
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ you drop your drink
♪ then they bring you more
♪ all the school kids
so sick of books ♪
♪ they like the punk
and the metal band ♪
♪ when the buzzer rings
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re walking
like an Egyptian ♪
♪ all the kids
in the marketplace say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian