Narrator: Previously on
"jojo’s bizarre adventure"...
♪
Joseph: Come out.
It’s time to go home.
Jotaro: Get lost.
I didn’t ask you to come here.
You really think
you can help me?
Joseph: I’d like you
to meet an Egyptian friend
I met a few years ago.
Say hello to avdol.
( Avdol grunts )
( Magician’s red shrieks )
Red bind!
Jotaro: Huh? What the...
Joseph: And now for the truth.
This may seem
like an evil spirit,
but it’s far from it.
Jotaro, this thing
you believe has possessed you
is actually a powerful vision
created by your own life energy.
This vision will always appear
standing by your side,
and because of that,
we call it a stand!
That coffin’s
a hundred years old,
and four years ago, it was
pulled out of the Atlantic
off the coast of Africa.
Jotaro: Okay. So?
Joseph: I did a little research.
My grandfather,
Jonathan joestar,
your great-grandfather,
died while at sea.
Turns out
this exact same coffin
was on that boat with him
when he died.
When they discovered it
four years ago, it was empty,
but I know
exactly what was inside it.
Avdol and I are trying
to locate him as we speak.
That person is evil incarnate,
and his name is dio!
And now
that he has been awakened
from his hundred-year slumber,
it is our fate
to fight that man!
From the neck of this bastard
on down
is Jonathan joestar,
my grandfather!
This son of a bitch
took over his body!
( Birds chirping )
Holly: Jotaro, don’t leave yet.
You forgot something important.
Silly boy.
Here is your goodbye kiss.
Jotaro: You’re such a bitch.
Stop clinging to me
like i’m still a little kid.
Holly: Okay. Have a nice day.
♪
Jotaro: What a giant pain
in my ass.
Girl: Hey. Look, it’s jojo.
Girl #2: What? Jojo?
Girl #3: You’re right.
It is jojo.
- Girl #4: Jojo.
- Girl #5: Jojo.
- Girl #1: Hey, jojo.
- Girl #3: What’s up, jojo?
- Girl #5: Hey there, jojo.
- Girl #2: Morning, jojo.
Girl #1: So tell me, jojo,
where have you been?
You haven’t been to school
for four days.
- Uh...
- Girl #5: Hey!
Who do you think you are
grabbing on to jojo like that?
I don’t like how friendly you’re
getting with him. Stay away.
Girl #1: What the hell, ugly?
Girl #5: I’d be careful there,
no boobs.
( Girl #1 gasps )
- Ugly.
- Girl #5: No boobs.
- Girl #1: Ugly. Ugly.
- Girl #5: No boobs. No boobs.
( Both repeating )
( Both growl )
- Ugly. Ugly. Ugly.
- No boobs. No boobs. No boobs.
( Both repeating )
Jotaro: Shut up!
You’re freakin’ annoying!
( Girls squeal )
Girl #1:
He totally said that to me!
Girl #5: Nuh-uh, me!
( Jotaro scoffs )
Girl #1: Jojo, wait.
( Girls chattering )
♪
Jotaro: What the hell?
( Girls scream )
- ( Screaming continues )
- Girl: Jojo!
Jotaro: Those branches.
Girl #1: Jojo.
Girl #4: Oh, no.
Girl #3: Jojo fell
so far down the steps.
Girl #2: Look.
He can still move.
Girl #3: The branches
must have broken his fall.
Jotaro: Did a branch
slash open my leg?
No. Wait a sec.
That’s not what caused me
to fall down the stairs.
This cut is what came first.
But how?
♪
( Girls chattering )
Painter: I see.
Looks like he’s able
to summon a pretty fierce stand.
I get it now.
Impressive.
No wonder he wants me
to get rid of him.
But still...
He is no match
for the power of my stand.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Girl #6: You really scared me.
Girl #5: Are you okay, jojo?
Girl #4: You think
you’re hurt anywhere?
Girl #1: You’re lucky. If you
had landed just few inches off,
you’d have cracked your head
right on the flagstone.
Girl #2: Nasty accidents happen
on those steps all the time.
Girl #3: Tomorrow when you
go down these steps,
you really should hold my hand.
- ( Girls groan )
- ( Girl #3 chuckles )
♪
( Jotaro gasps )
Painter: Here.
Your leg seems to be cut.
You might wanna wrap it
with this handkerchief
to help stop the bleeding.
You gonna be okay?
Jotaro: Yeah, i’m fine.
It’s just a scratch.
Hold it.
Painter: Hmm?
Jotaro: I forgot to say thanks.
I haven’t seen you before.
You go to our school?
Noriaki: I’m noriaki kakyoin.
And, yes, I just
transferred here yesterday.
See you around.
Girl #4: Oh.
- Girl #3: Oh.
- Girl #5: Oh.
Girl #4: So his name’s kakyoin.
Seems pretty cool.
Girl #3: You think so?
Girl #1: I still like jojo
way more than him.
- Girl #5: Yeah, me, too.
- Girl #3 same goes for me.
( Girls chattering )
♪
Dio: At that time,
I was very weak.
Lacking a body
made me vulnerable.
If I had not taken
Jonathan joestar’s body...
If it hadn’t been
for his energy
to augment
my own limited source,
I couldn’t have survived
at the bottom of that ocean
for a hundred years.
But still...
This body has like a bond
between a parent and a child.
It ties me to his kin.
They seem to know
of my existence...
And of this power i’ve gained
from taking jonathan’s body...
The stand.
It is the stand that reaches out
to the bodies
of his descendants.
There are always
advantages and disadvantages
to every situation.
I will eliminate them all.
The joestar clan
must be destroyed soon.
Joseph: Why is
every single room
in this house
so tiny and cramped?
This is exactly
why I hate Japan.
Avdol, how the hell
can you stand being here?
Avdol: I find it
quite fascinating,
especially the tea ceremony.
Joseph: Ceremony, schmeremony.
Instant coffee
will do just fine.
( Stirring )
Avdol: By the way, about dio...
Mr. Joestar, if you and I
are aware of his existence,
would it not be safe to assume
that he knows about us as well?
Joseph: Hmm. But if we don’t
know what he’s going to do
or, for that matter,
even what powers he has...
Gah!
Japanese coffee
is absolutely vile!
Avdol: That’s American coffee.
Joseph: Hmm?
Woman:
That’s a horrible cut, jojo.
How’d you get it? Let me guess.
You got into another fight,
didn’t you?
Show some respect,
and take off that hat.
It’s poor manners. ( Gasps )
Would you stop that?
Boy: Seriously?
Has jojo ever been hurt
in a fight before?
That’s not what cut him,
i’m sure.
Boy #2: No way. ( Laughs )
Doctor: Well,
you do have a point. ( Laughs )
Then i’ll assume you were
being clumsy, you big klutz.
Jotaro: Hey, hold on.
What are you gonna do?
Doctor: Cut your pants,
of course.
Jotaro: Like hell, you are.
Doctor: Well, if i’m gonna
treat that wound, I must.
Jotaro: You’ll ruin ’em.
I’ll take ’em off.
( Doctor laughs ) Didn’t know
you were so thrifty.
So while jojo’s
taking off his pants,
i’m gonna take your temperatures
and prove you’re nothing
but a bunch of fakers.
Boy #1: Come on.
We really caught a cold.
Boy #2: Totally.
Now just let us go home already.
( Doctor laughs )
Not gonna happen.
Jotaro: Oops.
( Gasps ) What the hell is this?
♪
- K-kakyoin?
- ( Splashing )
Boy #1: Hey, doctor.
What are you trying to do?
( Boy #2 wails )
Doctor: What does it look like?
I’m just shaking out
the thermometer to reset it.
Boy #1: Gah!
Th-that’s not a thermometer
- you got in your hand.
- Boy #2: Yeah, that’s a pen.
Doctor: Ah, come on.
Did you just say, "pen"?
You think i’m dumb? Does this
look like a pen to you?!
( Cackles ) Tell me something.
Just how stupid are
you two boys? ( Babbles )
If you honestly think
this thermometer i’m holding
- looks like a pen to you...
- ( Boys gasp )
Then maybe you need
to take a closer look!
( Boy #2 screams )
( Boy #1 wails )
( Doctor cackling )
Jotaro: What the...
Iling )
My eye! My eye!
( Boy #2 screams )
Doctor: Jojo...
What do you have to say?
You’re not gonna stand there
and tell me
this thermometer
looks like a pen, too, are you?!
( Jotaro gasping )
What the hell is going on?
Such strength.
This is no mere woman.
Wait.
I saw something weird
crawlin’ up from the floor.
Was it a stand?
Noriaki kakyoin...
Was he the one
who started this?
Did he cut my leg
on the stone steps?
Noriaki: Yes, it was me.
Jotaro: So it is you.
Noriaki: Hey. Long time, no see.
So my stand
is currently possessing
and controlling that doctor.
If you attack my stand,
you’ll hurt her, too, jojo.
Noriaki: You bastard.
Who are you?
Noriaki: I told you.
I’m noriaki kakyoin,
and the name of my stand here
is hierophant green.
I am human, but I have
pledged loyalty to him.
That’s why i’m gonna kill you.
( Doctor shrieking )
( Gagging )
( Jotaro grunts )
( Noriaki gasps )
Jotaro: I have zero intention
of hurting her.
Heh.
Now that i’ve dragged it out,
I see it for what it is,
just a sleazy stand
whose only ability
is to possess people.
- ( Teeth crunch )
- ( Noriaki winces )
Jotaro: So this is
your stand, kakyoin?
This green, stripy thing
looks like shiny melon.
Noriaki: You’re
gonna regret doing that.
Dragging that out of her
was a mistake, jojo.
( Yells )
Jotaro: Don’t act tough.
I can see my finger marks
on your forehead.
( Spits )
If I decide to crush
your stand’s head
like the melon it is,
then i’m guessin’
your head’ll get crushed, too.
( Noriaki gagging )
Jotaro: I’m gonna keep
a tight grip on you for now.
We’re gonna pay my gramps
a little visit.
I’m sure he’d love
to meet you...
And i’d like to know
more about dio myself.
( Jotaro gasps )
♪
What the hell?
What’s that green liquid
coming out of his stand’s hand?
Noriaki: You should
have listened, jojo.
I told you you’re
gonna regret this, didn’t I?
This is the attack of my stand,
hierophant green.
Jotaro: No weird moves, kakyoin!
♪
Noriaki: Emerald splash!
( Stand yells )
♪
Noriaki: So what do you think?
Did you like emerald splash?
That fluid you saw
in hierophant green
is actually
a surge of destructive energy.
It tore straight
though your stand’s chest,
and your insides
have now been torn to shreds.
And as for
that doctor over there...
( Bones cracking )
Jotaro: Why?
I know I took that stand
out of her, so how?
Noriaki: I told you already,
but let me reiterate.
I tried to warn you
that by attacking
my hierophant green,
it would hurt her as well.
My stand can travel
farther than yours,
but it dislikes open spaces.
Without exception, it prefers
to hide within something.
If you drag it out,
it gets angry.
That’s why, when you
ripped it out of her throat,
it hurt her along the way.
You’re the one
who did this to her.
This is entirely
your fault, jojo.
You must be held responsible.
Look at what you’ve done.
All you had to do
was let me kill you,
and the doctor would have
walked away unharmed.
♪
And still you get up.
You are so pathetic.
You’re nothing more
than a sandbag
about to be pummeled
by a skilled boxer.
Why even bother standing up?
I’m just gonna
knock you down again.
Jotaro: Look...
No one ever said
jotaro kujo was a nice guy.
♪
I beat the crap out of people
more than I have to.
Some are even
still in the hospital.
I’ve had idiot teachers
who liked to talk big,
so I taught them a lesson, and
they never came back to class.
If I go to a restaurant
and the food’s bad,
I make it a policy
to stiff ’em with the bill.
But even a bastard like me
can spot true evil
when he sees it.
True evil are those who use
the weak for their own gain,
then crush them underfoot
when they’re through...
Especially an innocent woman.
And that is exactly
what you’ve done, isn’t it?
And your stand
gets to hide from the victim,
the law, and the consequences.
That’s why...
I will judge you myself.
Noriaki: I’m evil?
See, that’s where you’re wrong.
Evil is always the loser.
It’s the Victor who has justice,
the Victor being
the last man standing.
And how you win in battle
is irrelevant!
♪
See, the loser
is always the evil one.
Time to finish you off.
Jotaro: Really?
The loser’s evil?
Noriaki: Emerald splash!
Jotaro: Then, let me show you...
- ( Stand roars )
- Noriaki: What?
There’s no way.
No one can just deflect
the emerald splash.
Jotaro:
...Just how evil you are.
( Stand yelling )
( Noriaki gags )
Stand: Ora!
( Yelling )
Jotaro: I’ll teach you justice
with my stand!
( Class screaming )
( Noriaki screams )
Your stand has incredible power.
Jotaro: You caught me
by surprise earlier
and scratched its chest
a little.
I’m glad my stand isn’t weak,
but sometimes it feels like it
can get more savage than I am.
That was a close call.
She’ll be fine
once her wounds are treated.
- ( School bell rings )
- Hmm?
Boy: Did a gas pipe just burst?
Boy #2: It came
from the doctor’s office.
Man: Everyone,
stay in the classroom!
Jotaro: I’ll leave
the cleanup to them.
I’ve had enough school
for one day.
This guy needs to talk.
I wanna hear
everything he knows about dio.
♪
( Holly humming a tune )
( Gasps )
( Footsteps )
I just had
the most amazing connection
with my son right now.
Jotaro must be thinking about me
at school this very second.
Jotaro: I’m not
thinking about you.
( Holly yelps )
Jotaro!
Why aren’t you at school?
And who is that boy
on your shoulder?
Is that blood
that he’s covered in?
Wait a sec. Please don’t
tell me you did that.
Jotaro: None of your business.
I need to find the old man.
Finding someone
in this big house really sucks.
Holly: I think you can find him
with avdol right now.
They’re both in the tea room.
♪
Oh, jotaro,
you never tell me anything.
All that does is make me worry
about you all the time.
But still,
I know that, deep down,
you really do mean well.
You’re a very sweet little boy
at heart.
- Jotaro: Hey.
- Holly: Yes?
Jotaro: You’re lookin’
a little bit pale the morning.
You all right?
( Holly gasps )
Yay!
I’m fine! Thank you!
( Jotaro scoffs )
Holly: I knew it.
Joseph: Well, I hate to say it,
but it’s too late for him.
There’s no way he’ll make it.
He’s got a few days
before he dies at most.
Jotaro, this is not your fault.
Trust me.
Do you want to know why this man
swore his allegiance to dio
and came to your school
to kill you?
Look right here,
and I will show you!
Jotaro: What the hell is that?
♪