Stand: Look over here.
( Koichi gasps ) Jotaro!
Tell me you’re seeing this!
Jotaro: Just keep
your guard up, koichi,
and don’t get
any closer to it.
Stand: Hey, didn’t you hear me?
I said, "look over here."
( Shopkeeper gasping )
( Clanking )
♪
( Koichi screams )
( Gasps )
Jotaro: Is that his stand?
Koichi: Jotaro,
look at the coat rack!
Th-the killer is here,
and he’s trying
to take the jacket!
Jotaro: Ah, good grief.
This would be when he
comes to get his suit.
( Hangers clatter )
( Koichi gasps ) Our evidence!
Jotaro: Wait!
We can’t go blindly after it.
( Clanking )
( Clicks )
( Ticking )
Jotaro: What is his power?
♪
- ( Clicks )
- Watch out! It’s gonna blow!
( Koichi screams )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
( Koichi screams )
( Windows rattling )
( Jotaro groans )
( Koichi gasps )
What the?! The owner blew up.
The killer has a bomb stand.
It all makes sense now.
This is how he got shigechi.
oh, god. That’s why we
couldn’t find his body anywhere.
( Clattering )
( Running footsteps )
H-he’s getting away.
Jotaro: Calm down, koichi.
Let him go.
Koichi: Huh? What do you mean,
"let him go"?
You can’t be serious.
If we go after him now,
we might actually have a shot
at catching the bastard
who murdered reimi and shigechi.
jotaro: We need
to observe the situation
before making our move.
Be patient, koichi.
( Koichi gasps )
D-do you even hear yourself?
jotaro: Not gonna lie.
Getting a look at that name tag
would have been a big help.
But given that jacket’s size,
we know he’s
about 175 centimeters tall.
what’s more,
he’s an unmarried office worker.
If he were married,
he wouldn’t need to come here
to get a button fixed.
( Koichi gasps )
Jotaro: He’s between
the ages of 25 and 35,
and from the look of the jacket,
he’s pretty damn rich.
the jacket’s
unique fabric and styling
tell us he tends
to wear designer clothing.
Even without a good look at him,
this info alone just narrowed
our target down big time.
Koichi: You know,
that does make sense.
Wait a second! We can’t just
stay here sitting on our hands.
the guy is
a coldblooded killer!
Jotaro: I wanna chase him
as much as you do,
but we have to stay put.
the bomb stand
is somewhere over there.
( Koichi gasps )
It’s still here?!
( Gasps ) Where’d you see it?
♪
Jotaro: I haven’t seen it yet,
but I know it’s here.
Let’s make our way
out of the door slowly.
Koichi: Wait. You just know?
But how is that possible?
there’s no way
you could know its location
if you haven’t seen it.
Jotaro: He’s not
the kind of killer
to bomb and run after only
offing that shop owner.
Just think about it. If he was,
his killing spree would have
ended a long time ago.
he doesn’t like
to leave behind evidence,
which means he intends
to take us out, too.
Koichi: I understand that,
but don’t you think
you’re being
a teensy bit overcautious?
If you’re wrong about this
and his stand isn’t here,
our murderer and evidence
could be long gone by now.
Jotaro: Listen, koichi.
Observing involves far more
than just looking around.
it means
scrutinizing everything.
You don’t simply listen.
You concentrate.
Otherwise...
We’ll die in this room.
( Koichi shudders )
i don’t like
what he was implying.
my reverb is more than
strong enough to keep us safe.
It’s matured a lot
since it emerged.
maybe Mr. Jotaro
just doesn’t take me seriously.
Well, if you ask me,
that dumb bomb stand
is long gone.
I mean, we’d have to be
total numb-nuts not to see it.
- ( Screams )
- Stand: Over here.
Koichi: He was right!
It was here all along!
it’ll explode
if I keep touching it!
Jotaro: Star platinum.
♪
Star platinum: Ora!
( Koichi gasps )
( Star platinum yelling )
Ora!
Jotaro: Damn, it’s tough.
I knocked it to shit,
and the thing’s
still in one piece.
- ( Click )
- ( Koichi gasps )
I think it’s gonna blow!
Jotaro: Star platinum,
bring forth the world!
( Clock ticking )
I’d like to end this
before things get ugly,
so i’m disposing of you
right here and now.
Star platinum: Ora!
( Grunts )
( Yelling )
Ora!
( Clock ticking )
( Koichi gasps ) It’s gone.
You must have stopped time
and finished it off.
Bet you didn’t see that one
coming, did you, murderer?
♪
Kira: Anyone who dares
pursue yoshikage Kira
must be destroyed.
I’ll blow them
to little pieces.
They think they’ve won,
but once deadly queen’s
heart attack finds its prey,
it won’t rest
until its target is dead.
( Clanking )
( Both gasp )
Koichi: There’s no way.
not even star platinum
had enough power to destroy it,
which means it’s practically
invincible. Damn it!
Jotaro: Stay behind me, koichi.
( Star platinum yelling )
( Clanking )
- ( Koichi gasps )
- ( Jotaro growls )
Koichi: It hasn’t
taken any damage.
nothing we do seems
to phase this thing whatsoever!
Jotaro: I can see that.
get back.
( Koichi gasps ) Y-you’ve
been hitting it so hard,
you’re starting to bleed,
but it still doesn’t have
a single scratch on it.
Jotaro: For the last time,
get back, koichi.
- ( Growls )
- Star platinum: Ora!
Ora!
heart attack:
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Koichi: Hey, what do you
think you’re doing?!
it’ll explode and
take us along for the ride!
You have to get rid of it!
Star platinum: Ora!
- ( Jotaro winces )
- ( Koichi groans )
( Glass tinkling )
( Rattling )
Heart attack: Look over here.
Jotaro: Good freaking grief.
This is a first for me.
That stand’s resilience
is insane.
The way this is going,
my confidence will break
before it does.
Koichi: What now, Mr. Jotaro?
We’re not gonna be able
to hold out for much longer.
Jotaro: You’re still
too close for comfort.
i’m gonna destroy
this alarm clock from hell.
Koichi: I beg you,
you have to listen to me!
when a stand’s
controlled from a distance,
it only wields a fraction
of its full power.
Look at the way it charges
and the intensity
of its explosions.
Its owner has to be nearby
fueling it with energy.
There’s no other explanation.
at most 15--
no, based on what we’ve seen,
the killer’s ten meters away.
Jotaro: And?
Koichi: What do you mean, "and"?
It’s ten meters, and reverb
has a range of 50 meters!
I can find that prick!
Jotaro: Don’t you move.
Koichi, just leave it be.
you have one job,
and it’s to focus on protecting
yourself with reverb.
Nothing else matters now.
( Koichi gasps )
You’re letting him get away?
Jotaro: The guy’s
long gone, koichi.
That means we’re dealing
with a long-range stand.
trust me.
I’ve seen enough of these
to know what i’m talking about.
Heart attack: Over here.
Jotaro: Its movements
are too simple
for a short-range stand.
Koichi: He’s seen
enough of them to know?
Is he off his rocker?
We’re going up against
an incredibly powerful
long-range stand.
The user has to be close by.
i knew Mr. Jotaro
didn’t take me seriously,
but i’ll show him
how much i’ve matured.
i’ll find the killer
and finish him off by myself.
Ten-meter range.
( Gasps )
There. I found him,
and he has the jacket with him.
( Gasps ) What’s going on?
He’s too far away.
That’s much farther
than 50 meters.
He’s still going!
Now he’s outside reverb’s range.
Does that mean the killer
really has the ability
to control such a powerful stand
from afar? Impossible.
( Panting )
( Clanking )
Heart attack: Over here!
Koichi: What?! Oh, no!
It’s aiming at me!
jotaro: Now I get it.
For some reason, the bomb stand
is drawn to whichever object
it senses is hottest.
That would explain the range
and why it’s still so powerful.
Use reverb to protect yourself.
Stopping time is useless
at that distance.
Koichi: Oh, crap.
- I can’t.
- ( Clanking )
I sent reverb 50 meters away
to track down the killer.
Sorry! I didn’t listen!
( Shrieks )
jotaro:
Good freakin’ grief, kid.
Star platinum,
once more, the world.
( Clock ticking )
( Star platinum yelling )
Jotaro: It attacked
the shop owner first
because of the hot liquid
in his cup.
compared to that,
our body heat didn’t register.
But in koichi’s case,
his frustration
increased his temperature.
If it detects something hotter,
then it moves on to that.
Enough. Time resume.
( Clock ticks )
- ( Koichi shrieks )
- ( Clanking )
Jotaro: I was right.
Since it’s drawn
to the highest temperature
it can detect,
it’s making a beeline for me.
Koichi: What is he planning?
Jotaro: All right,
if body temperature’s
all it takes to trigger this,
then fire should be
more than enough.
( Clicks )
Jotaro: This power!
( Koichi gasps )
♪
( Wails )
Mr. Jotaro!
( Koichi gasping )
( Wailing )
How could I let this happen?!
mr. Jotaro,
this is all my fault!
All because I went
after that bastard.
This wouldn’t have happened
if he hadn’t had to stop time
and save me with that fire.
Please wake up, Mr. Jotaro!
Mr. Jotaro! Mr. Jotaro!
heart attack:
That was not the sensation
of human flesh exploding.
Over here.
( Koichi gasps, screams )
It’s gonna kill us.
( Groans )
It’s just too powerful!
( Grunting )
It’s like Mr. Jotaro was saying.
If it detects a temperature
hotter than body heat,
it goes after that first.
Heart attack: Over here!
Koichi: Now’s our chance
to make a break for it.
I need to find a way
to call josuke.
He’ll be able
to fix Mr. Jotaro.
I just need to find a phone.
( Grunting )
Oh, of course. It’s the kitchen.
lots of ways
to start a fire in here.
I’ll buy some time, and then
we’ll escape through that door.
( Gasps ) A phone.
Huh?
Wait. You have got
to be kidding me.
This isn’t a gas stove?
Why the hell does this house
have to have an electric one?
i bet it’s gonna
take forever to get hot.
Ah, come on. The oven, too?
Wh-what do I do now?
I bet that kettle
has hot water in it.
Try and find me now!
Ahh! It’s empty.
- ( Ticking )
- ( Gasps )
( Panting )
Heart attack: Get over here!
♪
koichi: Calm down.
It’s like Mr. Jotaro said.
I need to carefully observe,
focus.
This thing has a weakness.
I never noticed it until now.
you’re really
starting to piss me off.
you’re nothing
but a repulsive murderer,
a stain on the fabric
of humanity.
Why should a dreg like you
have the satisfaction
of watching me flee
and beg for mercy?
Shouldn’t the roles
be reversed?!
I already know that I can
get out of this mess alive,
so, for the life of me,
I can’t figure out
why i’m just standing here
like a wimpy, little bitch-baby
with a bad case of the shits!
I’ve had all this wrong
from the beginning!
The one who should be
running away is you, dick!
This ends once and for all.
You’re unrelenting in your
pursuit of thermal energy,
but that’s also
your shortcoming.
Your inability to stop
will be your undoing.
You’re gonna pay
for your crimes,
so consider this
the first installment.
Kira: It’s been three minutes
since I made my escape.
I don’t know what’s transpired
at the shoe store
in the meantime,
but no matter
how strong my opponent,
there’s one thing
i’m certain of.
Heart attack is
the ultimate stand
and has no weaknesses.
It’ll find and destroy
any target without fail.
koichi: Okay,
with that thing out of the way,
all that’s left
is to call josuke.
He should have made it home
from school by now.
( Clanking )
♪
at least that pest is
distracted for the time being.
i don’t think
it’ll fool it forever,
but the "sizzle"
should keep it busy
long enough
to make a phone call.
Lucky for me the little jackass
is as gullible as a donkey
chasing a hanging carrot.
And that’s your stand’s
fatal flaw.
Jotaro: Higashikata residence.
Koichi: Josuke, it’s koichi.
I need help.
Jotaro’s hurt. I don’t
think he’s gonna make it.
It’s kinda my fault,
but, still, get here fast.
Jotaro: Eh? Hmm?
You wanna run that by me again?!
What the hell is going on?!
Koichi: Just focus
on getting here.
We found the killer.
We were following
a hunch at first,
but long story short,
i’m holding his stand captive.
Jotaro: What do you mean,
"holding it captive"?
Are you there?
It’s hard to hear.
Where are you right now?
- ( Sizzling )
- Koichi: Wait. That’s weird.
Ahh! It’s hot.
I turned this thing off
a while ago,
so why in the world is it
just starting to heat up now?
What is with this heap of junk?
I don’t know how anybody
cooks a damn thing with it.
Jotaro: Come in, koichi!
Tell me where you are
so I can find you!
( Koichi gasps )
Heart attack: Over here.
Koichi: Oh, shit! It’s totally
ignoring reverb’s writing.
Josuke: Koichi, where are you?!
Hurry up, and tell me,
you idiot!
Koichi: We’re at mukadeya shoes!
Get over here now!
Damn it! Reverb’s tail
is still attached to it!
( Grunting )
Yaah!
That hurt.
Not only did it blow up,
the damage
got transferred to me.
- ( Gasps )
- Heart attack: That was not
the sensation
of human flesh exploding.
Over here.
Koichi: Just what I didn’t need.
It’s getting ready to attack.
But I can’t use
reverb’s tail anymore.
What’s my next move?
How can I fight back?
♪
Let’s go, reverb act two!
Eh? Where’d you go?
Reverb act two!
Act two!
Why aren’t you showing yourself?
What’s the matter?
( Gasps )
( Screams ) Oh, no!
Act two must have been killed
in the explosion.
He’s just a husk
of his former self!
No, don’t freak out just yet.
If it died in that blast,
then I should have
been killed, too,
but that didn’t happen.
Right. It’s coming back to me.
This isn’t the first time
reverb has looked
like a lifeless shell.
( Gasps ) Does that mean...
♪
( Gasps ) Could it be?
Reverb act three!
Um, if that’s you.
your new form
looks a lot different.
Reverb: Act three
awaiting orders.
Koichi: Oh, yeah, I was right.
I told Mr. Jotaro
my powers had matured.
You are the best stand ever,
act three. You know that?
Reverb: I’m still
awaiting your orders.
koichi: Well, uh,
i’m not all that familiar
with your new capabilities,
so, for now, I guess...
Just protect us from harm.
Get to it, act three!
( Reverb sighs )
Koichi: Um, I mean,
please keep us safe,
act three, sir.
You can do that, right?
Reverb: Command acquired.
( Yells )
This is insane!
♪
Whoa, I thought
it was fast before,
but this is crazy.
Compared to this kind of speed,
acts one and two were as slow
as geriatric turtles.
( Gasps )
Reverb: Activating
reverb act three
special ability, three freeze!
( Koichi squeals )
Unh! Huh?!
Koichi: What the?
( Reverb groans ) Whew.
Koichi: Hey, what the heck
happened out there, act three?
Reverb: Too strong.
There’s no hope.
Koichi: Then we
have to find some!
Reverb: We’re doing battle
with an adversary
that possesses
herculean strength.
It’s time for us
to face the music.
We’re s-h-i-t out of luck.
Koichi: Have you lost it?!
i commanded you
to protect us from harm,
so get your butt in gear,
and start protecting!
Reverb: The act
of protecting you
has been completed,
exactly as you ordered.
Heart attack: Over here!
Koichi: It’s been completed?
But you said we should give up.
you know what, buddy?
I think you’re malfunctioning.
you haven’t made
the slightest bit of progress.
( Screams )
Eh?
Heart attack: Over...Here.
Koichi: What the hell?
Kira: This skirmish
is taking far too long.
What is keeping heart attack?
it normally
makes the kill by now.
( Gasps )
Wh-what the hell is happening?
my left hand feels
as heavy as a cement block.
This was the hand
that I released
heart attack with, and now...
waiter: Evening, sir.
I hope everything’s all right.
Can I help at all?
Kira: No, thanks.
Bring me the bill.
And please allow me
to pay for the cup.
There’s something that needs
my attention, so hop to it.
( Grunting )
This indentation.
Why’s my left hand so heavy?
Waiter: Sir, are you okay?!
Kira: What the hell is this?
My left hand weighs a ton.
It feels like there’s a massive
weight pressing against it.
What is happening over there?
Waiter: Do you need
some assistance, sir?
kira: No,
everything’s just fine,
- waiter: Please, take my hand.
- Kira: Really, let go.
This weight.
( Waiter gasps )
Good heavens, sir.
Was it something I said?
( Crumbling )
Koichi: It’s been driven
so far into the pavement,
it’s barely moving.
Wow, act three,
what’s this new ability?
it’s amazing.
Reverb: Three freeze.
"three" and "free."
It works because they rhyme.
Koichi: Yeah, that’s nice, but
it doesn’t answer my question.
i wanna know why
the bomb stand’s barely moving.
Don’t leave me hanging.
Reverb: Well, I did
just tell you they rhyme,
master koichi.
Need I say any more?
Kira: I have no idea how
those meddlesome twits did it,
but somehow they were able
to weigh down heart attack.
Shit, how did it come to this?
I have to go back to that shop
and fetch heart attack myself.
♪
♪ Anytime I need
to see your face ♪
♪ I just close my eyes,
and I am taken to a place ♪
♪ where your crystal mind
and magenta feelings ♪
♪ take up shelter
in the base of my spine ♪
♪ sweet like
a chica cherry cola ♪
♪ I don’t need
to try to explain ♪
♪ I just hold on tight,
and if it happens again ♪
♪ I may move so slightly
to the arms ♪
♪ and the lips and the face
of the human cannonball ♪
♪ that I need to, I want to
♪ come stand
a little bit closer ♪
♪ breathe in,
and get a bit higher ♪
♪ you’ll never know what hit you
when I get to you ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪