♪♪
Jotaro: Yeah, we've taken care of Angelo for good.
But it'll be a while 'til I'm back.
About that other photo we've been looking into,
if you would, please send it over to me.
That's right, from Egypt,
the one the speedwagon foundation found ten years ago.
I think I might have figured it out.
Later, then.
And ironically it's all thanks to him.
Angelo: Josuke, let's be frank.
Yeah, I murdered your grandpa,
but that doesn't mean you can put me to death, too!
If you kill me, you'll end up cursed,
just like yours truly,
so back off if you know what's good for you! ( Laughs )
- Shining diamond: Dora! - ( Angelo screams )
Josuke: It's rude to point your finger at people.
Didn't your mother ever teach you that?
( Angelo gasps )
What the hell did you do to my hand?!
Josuke: You should take solace
in the fact no one's gonna execute you,
not me and not this guy either.
We won't be killing you,
nor will we be turning you in to the police.
Jotaro: Josuke, you handle the rest.
Angelo: What the hell
are you psychotic bastards planning to do?!
Josuke: Enjoy your eternal penance, Angelo.
Reflect on the life you stole
from my grandpa and all the others!
( Shining diamond yelling )
( Angelo groans ) Damn you bastards all to hell!
I wouldn't get cocky, you little shit-head!
You think you've won, but he'll be here
to butcher you into bloody pieces soon enough!
Josuke: What? Who is "he"?
Angelo: Oh, you'll find out.
He wears a school uniform,
and he's the one who gave me this power.
( Jotaro gasps ) Hang on.
You're saying that there's someone out there
who can bestow the power of a stand?
Angelo: Scared? ( Laughs )
Josuke: Yeah, nice try, pal, but what's so scary about that?
Jotaro: Wait. He's telling the truth
about not being born a stand user.
Thing is, no one knew how he obtained his powers.
Just think about it.
What if there really is a person
who can impart stands to others?
Angelo: Petrifying thought, isn't it?
( Chuckles ) Do you wanna know more?
( Laughs )
It happened last year, 1998, about a month
before my execution was to be carried out.
I remember that night well.
It was cloudy, and I couldn't sleep worth a damn,
so I just sat there staring off into the darkness.
It was quiet, dead quiet.
Then all of a sudden, it happened.
In that shitty excuse for a solitary cell,
there he was...
The guy in the school uniform.
( Gasps ) What the hell? Who let you in here?!
Where'd you come from?!
Wha...
He was holding an ancient bow and arrow.
From the looks of 'em,
they must have been hundreds of years old.
What are you doing?! What the hell?!
I was scared shitless.
It was like my balls crawled into my stomach.
But before I could let out a scream...
( Gurgles )
♪♪
Man: Congratulations.
You survived.
And what's more, you have talent.
Otherwise, you'd be dead right now.
As of this moment, you've acquired a special ability.
Or perhaps I should simply say
that I extracted it from your soul.
The more wicked the criminal, the more talent he holds.
It's a talent that a man named dio
once referred to as a "stand."
( Aqua necklace yells )
Jotaro: Dio? That's what he said?
Josuke: Is something the matter, Mr. Jotaro?
( Boy screaming )
- Josuke: What the-- - Angelo: You idiots!
You were so captivated by my story,
you completely forgot about my aqua necklace!
Jotaro: Angelo, you bastard!
Angelo: Josuke, you've lost,
so get me the hell outta this rock!
( Boy gagging )
Josuke: I might have considered it,
if this pathetic show of yours was actually making me mad.
Angelo: What are you doing?!
I told you to get me outta this stupid rock!
If you don't get a move on,
you and your prissy-ass hair are gettin' ripped apart!
- ( Josuke grunts ) - ( Jotaro grunts )
Josuke: You wanna repeat that?
Jotaro: Take it easy, josuke!
Josuke: What did you call my hair?!
Angelo: If you kill me, the guy in the school uniform
is just gonna hunt you down and do the same to you!
I didn't say earlier, but he lives in this town, too!
Jotaro: Say what? Josuke, stand down!
( Shining diamond yells )
♪♪
Jotaro: Hmm?
Josuke: I'll give him this, he managed to piss me off.
So I thought it was only fair to repay the dick-wad
by turning him into a great work of art.
( Boy sobbing )
( Jotaro sighs ) Good grief, kid.
We needed to keep him talking a little longer.
Josuke: Huh? Please don't tell me
you believed any of that crap.
Jotaro: You bet. Or didn't you hear him
when he was going on about dio?
Jotaro: Yeah, I heard him. Who is he?
Jotaro: The joestars's greatest enemy.
Our family was fighting him for over a hundred years.
It all came to a head ten years ago
when we defeated him.
But there's one thing none of us could ever figure out.
Dio didn't have a stand in the past,
so how the hell did he suddenly gain
such a powerful one in 1987?
Josuke: I see. You think he got it from the same guy.
Jotaro: Yeah. I think we may have found a new enemy
in this school uniform guy.
Or it could be that the bow and arrow
is the source of this madness.
If he was right and it's hiding somewhere in this town,
then Angelo was just the opening act
in a horror show of epic proportions.
Good grief.
Koichi: It's like Mr. Jotaro said.
Jotaro: See for yourself.
There's something evil lurking in this town.
Catastrophic danger's closing in as we speak.
No, it's already here.
Koichi: The number of missing persons
reported in morioh has risen to 81 in this year alone...
45 of which were children.
Even if some were runaways, that's still
seven to eight times more than the national average.
It's outrageous.
Also...
Josuke's grandfather.
Josuke: School's out, koichi.
Why are you still studying there?
Let's go home.
Koichi: Oh, sure.
That's a relief.
Josuke seems to be feeling better.
Josuke: Yo, Angelo.
Koichi: Uh, hey, has this rock always been here?
Josuke: Yeah, but it's been given a...Face-lift.
Koichi: Face-lift?
Hmm.
Well, what do you know? Yo, Angelo.
( Angelo grunts )
Koichi: I've been meaning to ask,
- what happened to Mr. Jotaro? - Josuke: Hmm?
Oh, he said there was some stuff he needed to look into,
so he went back over to the grand hotel.
Koichi: Do you think it has to do with the town?
Josuke: Sure seems like it.
Koichi: I see.
♪♪
We're facing a crisis.
Huh?
I think that's a--
hey, josuke.
Josuke: What?
Koichi: I could be wrong,
but hasn't this house been abandoned for a few years?
Josuke: Yeah, I doubt anyone would buy this eyesore.
They'd be better off bulldozing it and starting over.
Koichi: Well, maybe they just moved in.
When I looked up at the window,
I could have sworn I saw someone.
Josuke: Huh? But that's impossible.
Did you forget where I live?
I'd have noticed if someone moved in.
And besides, I always see real-estate guys
patrolling the area, looking for squatters.
Koichi: Hmm. I guess that makes sense.
How peculiar. I hate to say it,
but maybe I saw a ghost. Freaky.
Josuke: Come on, dude.
Knock it off with crap like that.
Ghosts give me the willies.
Not to mention I live right there.
♪♪
( Koichi gasps )
( Gagging )
Man: Try keeping your nose out of other people's business,
little brat.
Nothing to say?
Josuke: Koichi, no!
Hey! What the hell do you think you're doing?!
Man: What? I should be the one asking you that question.
You and your friend are on my property.
( Doorbell rings )
Tomoko: Enough!
If it's about the newspaper, I said we don't want any!
( Doorbell rings )
What's your problem?!
Look, buddy, I just lost my dad to a stroke,
and I'm still trying to figure out
what the hell my family's going to do, okay?
Come back later!
( Gasps ) Y-you're...
( Jotaro sighs )
Tomoko: Jo...
Joseph!
You finally came back for me after all of these years!
I've been waiting for you!
Since dad died, it's been like living
in an endless sea of depression!
You came when I needed you most, Joseph, my love!
( Jotaro sighs )
Tomoko: I love, love, love, love, love, love,
love, love, love, love, love, love...
Jotaro: I'm sorry to disappoint you,
but I'm not the joestar you're looking for.
Tomoko: Eh?
Jotaro: You see? Not a wrinkle on my face.
Tomoko: Oh. Oh, now that you mention it,
you do look younger.
Jotaro: Good grief.
I'm Joseph's grandson.
My name is jotaro kujo.
Tomoko: Oh. His grandson, huh?
Jotaro: Josuke'll tell you the rest of the story.
Tedious chitchat drives me up the wall.
Speaking of josuke, is he around?
( Tomoko sighs )
Jotaro: Hmm? Are you listening?
I asked where josuke is.
Tomoko: Uh, oh, well, the school day just ended,
so he isn't home yet.
Jotaro: I see. Then, I'll be back tonight.
Tomoko: Wait. You're leaving already?
Jotaro: Oh. About your father...
Tomoko: Eh?
Jotaro: His death was a real shame.
If Joseph joestar were here,
he'd protect you with his life.
I'm sure he'd leap into danger if it meant keeping you safe.
But he's an old man now.
It'd be irresponsible to let him come here.
That's why I'm here in his stead.
- ( Car door closes ) - Tomoko: Uh...
Jotaro: I've got a bad feeling about this.
The bow and arrow Angelo mentioned,
the intel on enyaba
that the speedwagon foundation found in Egypt,
and the fact that the witch is holding a bow and arrow.
It really imparts the power of the stand to ordinary people.
Shit. Another headache.
Josuke: Have you completely lost your freakin' mind?!
Let him go!
Man: Let me make something real clear.
My pop bought this house,
which means I'm not gonna let you snoop around here.
Get what I'm sayin'?
Josuke: I think you're the one who's not getting it.
I'm telling you to let go of my friend, punk.
You really don't wanna tick me off.
Man: Hey, it's not nice to call people names,
especially when the person you're insulting
just happens to own the property you're trespassing on.
Jeez, don't you know how to be polite?
Josuke: I know that I'm gonna smash your face in
if you don't shut your goddamn mouth.
Man: Hmm?
Josuke: What?!
( Koichi gags )
Man: Hey, bro!
Archer: Interested as to why I shot him with the arrow?
Because that goon is josuke higashikata.
Man: Really? So it's you.
Archer: Given that he defeated Angelo,
his stand abilities will likely pose a nuisance to us as well.
( Josuke gasps ) You know about stands, too?!
Out with it! Are you stand users?!
Archer: Okuyasu, make josuke higashikata disappear.
( Josuke gasps )
- ( Koichi gasping ) - Josuke: Koichi.
Archer: I had hopes he'd turn into a stand user,
and a useful one, at that,
but, alas, it was all for naught.
That boy's a goner.
Josuke: He can't--
hey, move it!
There's still time for me to heal his injury
using shining diamond's power!
Okuyasu: Too bad.
♪♪
Josuke higashikata,
I, okuyasu nijimura, will make you vanish,
so behold the hand!
( Hand pumps )
Get ready!
- ( The hand yelps ) - ( Okuyasu groans )
Josuke: Out of the way,
or I'll make good on my promise to smash your face in.
Okuyasu: Wow. Gotta admit, you're pretty fast.
- Archer: Hey, okuyasu. - Okuyasu: Hmm?
Archer: It appears manipulating a stand
is a lot like driving a car or motorcycle.
Any bumbling half-wit
can get in the driver's seat of a muscle machine,
but with only air between his ears,
he'll still be too scared to drive.
Okuyasu: Hey, bro, why the heck did you have to go
and say all of that mean stuff for?
This bastard's just a little faster
than I thought he was gonna be.
Archer: Let me remind you this isn't a game, okuyasu!
There was a time when the mere thought of your stand, the hand,
sent horrific chills streaking down my spine.
Pull yourself together.
It's time for you to kill Angelo's murderer,
josuke higashikata!
If you don't end him now,
he'll prove troublesome in the future.
Okuyasu: Yeah, I know--( Gasps )
Hey! I was talking to my bro back there!
That's not fair at all!
Josuke: Oh, man. You're not too bright, are you?
Okuyasu: What? Not bright?
Why do you--ohh!
Josuke: I told you to move it.
Koichi!
( Koichi gasps )
Josuke: Oh, thank god you're still with me.
I can save you before it's too--
okuyasu: I have had enough! You are not getting away!
Josuke: I'm not gonna tell you again!
If you wanna piss me off, keep running!
Okuyasu: All right, I will!
Let's see if you've got the guts!
♪♪
Josuke: Bastard!
He's got way too much confidence in his right hand.
( Okuyasu grunts )
Josuke: Shit. That right hand.
Something tells me--shit! ( Gags )
Okuyasu: Let go of my right hand,
you son of a bitch!
Josuke: It is his right hand!
( The hand yells )
Okuyasu: You bastard.
Stay right where you are, josuke!
You wouldn't wanna leave your friend behind!
Josuke: Something is definitely up with your right hand.
My gut is telling me
that there's more to it than you're letting on.
Okuyasu: You can think about my hands once you're worm food.
This is it for you.
Josuke: Koichi, hang on a little longer.
The sign, something's not right about it.
"No...passing"?
( Okuyasu growls )
If I were you,
I wouldn't be so quick to back up, you flimsy prick.
Or don't you care about moving away from your friend?
Why don't you come a little closer?
Josuke: That's it.
The sign's missing half a word.
Now I get it.
Your hand didn't make part of that sign disappear.
It cuts out space in midair.
That's your stand's ability, isn't it?!
( Okuyasu chuckles ) Bingo, josuke higashikata!
My stand's right hand can make whatever it grabs disappear,
but the void that's left behind,
closes and pulls together the space
as if it never happened!
But as for the part my hand takes away,
once my unlucky target is sucked into the void,
I don't have a freakin' clue where it goes.
Even if you try to run, it wouldn't matter,
'cause I can still do this.
I just have to grab some space, and then...
Hey, you came right to me.
It's like teleporting, isn't it?
( Laughs ) In case you didn't get the memo,
you're up against the hand, a stand that even my bro fears.
Try as you might, you can't run now, josuke!
No matter where you try to hide, you're always within my reach!
So go ahead, punk, make my day.
Weakling.
How was a piece of dog shit like you
able to take down Angelo? Huh?
♪♪
Guess you haven't figured out how worthless you are.
So, which one of us wasn't bright, again?!
Now hurry up and die, josuke!
Josuke: That proves it. You, sir, are truly an idiot.
Okuyasu: Say what?!
♪♪
( Okuyasu groaning )
( Josuke sighs ) That was a close one.
Okuyasu nijimura,
I'd say his stand was pretty great,
but I'm not one to lie.
He's gonna be a pain in the ass
when he wakes up and tries to attack me.
I guess I'd better draw out his nap
with some gentle asphyxiation.
This'll definitely put the sting of defeat in his soul.
- Here we-- - ( Gate creaks )
K-koichi!
♪♪
Now you've gone too far.
I'll kill you!
( Growls )
Archer: This arrow is irreplaceable.
There's only one, you know.
It's essential to my mission...
And losing it is not an option.
Jotaro: Angelo's story says it all.
There's no doubt this is the bow and arrow
that unleashed dio's stand,
the weapon that released the world.
After enyaba's death,
someone must have nabbed the bow and arrow,
and now they're using it
to create more stand users right here in morioh.
We've gotta find and destroy the damn thing fast.
A villain fouler than dio, or worse, a stand user
who wields even more power than the world.
We can't let either come to pass.
♪♪
♪ Anytime I need to see your face ♪
♪ I just close my eyes, and I am taken to a place ♪
♪ where your crystal mind and magenta feelings ♪
♪ take up shelter in the base of my spine ♪
♪ sweet like a chica cherry cola ♪
♪ I don't need to try to explain ♪
♪ I just hold on tight, and if it happens again ♪
♪ I may move so slightly to the arms ♪
♪ and the lips and the face of the human cannonball ♪
♪ that I need to, I want to
♪ come stand a little bit closer ♪
♪ breathe in, and get a bit higher ♪
♪ you'll never know what hit you when I get to you ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don't know if I need you
♪ but, ooh, I'd die to find out ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don't know if I need you
♪ but, ooh, I'd die to find out ♪