Yoshihiro: All right, arrow,
who are we adding
to our ranks today?
So he’s the lucky soul?
That boy there will be the sixth
new stand user i’ve created.
It doesn’t seem real, but i’ve
conscripted a formidable crew,
and, using their might,
i’ll eliminate any miscreant
who comes after my yoshikage!
Hah!
What the--
- ( arrow clatters )
- boy: Huh?
♪
Ow, that hurt.
yoshihiro: What?
That’s never happened before.
i’m positive
that the arrow chose him,
but it was deflected.
( Boy sighs )
♪
singers:
♪ breakdown, breakdown
- ♪ listen up
- ♪ breakdown, breakdown
- ♪ listen
- ♪ 3, 2, 1
♪ let’s go
♪ shining justice
( singing in Japanese )
♪ Brand-new bed town
♪ Spirits
( singing in Japanese )
♪ Let the voice of love
take you higher ♪
- ♪ higher, higher
- ( Singing in Japanese )
♪ 1999, bizarre summer
( singing in Japanese )
♪ Great days
( radio playing music )
Agent: Every piece of intel
we could find on him
is in that envelope.
Gotta hand it to the bastard.
He’s done a damn fine job
of covering his tracks.
Jotaro: Curse you, Kira.
what’s your new name,
and whose face have you stolen?
Where are you?
Agent: It’s summer.
Way I hear it,
this is tourist season
in morioh.
Jotaro: Yeah.
i doubt he’ll be able
to resist his urges for long.
That son of a bitch will be
itching to kill real soon.
Kai: Summertime
has finally arrived,
and if you hadn’t noticed,
July first
was the opening of morioh’s
beautiful rivers and beaches.
With tourists descending on us
from s city and beyond,
our little ol’ morioh
is really hopping.
whether you’re
getting a little r & r,
camping, fishing, or yachting,
consider morioh
your special summer paradise!
Now, how’s everyone going
to make the most of the season?
narrator: Yes,
quite the summer paradise,
and not just
for the morally upright.
Everyone wanted
to enjoy the season.
( Kira shuddering )
We’re all forced
to live out our lives
concealing
our deepest hopes and fears,
but to forever
keep them to yourself,
can one truly live out
their days behind
- such a veil of secrecy?
- ( Fingernails rustle )
woman: Aww.
Woman #2: It’s the truth!
Kira: Damn it! All I want
is for that girl to see
the true yoshikage Kira,
to hear the passion
that burns within me,
to feel my hands
wrapped around her tender neck
as I wring the life
from her body.
As my nails grow,
so do my carnal desires.
I just need to persevere
until the urge subsides.
For now, I should practice
his signature.
I still haven’t mastered it.
( Shudders )
Josuke higashikata,
jotaro kujo,
they’re the reason
i’m in this predicament.
- ( Door opens )
- ( Gasps )
( Shinobu sighs ) Evening.
So, dear, what, uh--
what are you doing now?
♪
Oh, wow, silly me.
I should have just used my eyes.
You’re in the middle
of reading a book.
I thought you might enjoy
a cup of tea.
I know I don’t normally do
this type of thing,
but I thought i’d try something
different, so here it is.
If you don’t want any,
that’s fine, too.
- ( Kira sips )
- ( Shinobu gasps )
( Giggles )
( Sighs )
♪
( Giggles )
Oh, my, would you
look at the time?
i suppose
I should hit the sack.
( Moans )
( Kira shuddering )
♪
( Shinobu sighs )
( Sighing )
kira: Do it.
Bare your heart to her.
Show her your true self,
- yoshikage Kira.
- ( Fingernails rustle )
( Shinobu gasps, shrieks )
Honey?!
kira: Shit.
Baring my soul was a mistake.
They’ll figure me out
at this rate.
( Shinobu panting )
Kira: Sorry for the scare.
Forgive me.
( Shinobu gasps )
wait. Was he trying
to unbutton my dress just now?
He apologized for scaring me.
No, baby, you have nothing
to be sorry about.
This new you is something else.
i don’t know
where it’s coming from,
but it’s turning me on.
I never thought i’d say this,
but I think i’ve
fallen in love with you!
♪
Okuyasu: Hey!
Josuke, over there!
Check out the weird-ass holes!
Josuke: What’re you
talking abou--( Gasps )
( Okuyasu gasps )
You see what I mean?
Now, am I goin’ crazy,
or is that one of those
creepy slop hurdles?
Josuke: It’s some sort
of crop circle.
okuyasu: Yeah!
It’s one of those things!
man, that’s spooky!
Who would’ve thought one of ’em
would pop up
in some random field in morioh?
Josuke: Wait, okuyasu. I’ve got
a weird feeling about this.
take a close look
at the middle of the circle.
♪
( Okuyasu gasps )
Josuke: Something’s
definitely not right here.
( Okuyasu groans )
We’re actually doin’ this?
Josuke: I don’t want to.
We don’t have much of a choice.
Okuyasu: Just be careful, okay?
Josuke: Yeah.
Okuyasu: So, he alive or what?
josuke: Well,
it looks like something
scratched him
on the back of his neck,
but, from what I can tell,
he just fainted.
Hey, you all right? Wake up!
Okuyasu: You know, I don’t think
i’ve ever seen
this guy around at school.
- ( Boy sighs )
- Okuyasu: Look!
he’s finally
startin’ to come to!
Boy: Hmm.
( Josuke and okuyasu yelp )
♪
Boy: Hmm.
How strange.
Oh. You, what is this place?
Okuyasu: What do you mean?
You’re in the middle
of an empty field
in budogaoka, morioh.
Boy: So then, is this earth?
- ( Josuke gasps )
- Okuyasu: Huh?
Boy: I’m not certain why,
but I felt quite unwell
last evening.
I must have fallen unconscious
shortly thereafter.
It’s past 8:00.
Given that fact,
I estimate i’ve been unconscious
for nearly 13 earth hours.
( Both laughing )
Okuyasu: That’s a good one, man!
You really had us going there!
Josuke: I gotta hand it to you.
That’s one of the best jokes
i’ve heard in a long time!
If this whole alien thing
doesn’t work out,
you could totally
become a comedian!
You’re hilarious!
You made your own crop circle
and waited in a bunch of weeds
for someone to come by?
Talk about committing to a bit!
Bravo, sir! Bravo!
Okuyasu: Oh, god, my stomach!
I can’t breathe!
- huh?
- Josuke: Huh?
( Both laughing )
josuke:
It’s freakin’ ridiculous!
( Laughs )
so what school
do you go to, Mr. Alien?
Okuyasu: You’re just
our kind of guy, my man!
Boy: What school?
My home planet was
in the magellanic clouds,
but it was recently destroyed.
I’ve journeyed to earth
to survey its livability.
Moreover, I seek to assess
the amiability of its people.
( Okuyasu chuckles )
Josuke: Piece of advice,
you should quit
while you’re ahead.
You totally nailed the prank.
Just ride the wave.
And here. Have a tissue.
Boy: Hmm.
many thanks.
That was quite palatable.
( Both stammer )
Okuyasu: Hey, look at the time.
We don’t wanna
be late for school!
Josuke: Oh, yeah, you’re right.
Let’s head out.
Okuyasu: Did you see the way
the guy
scarfed down that tissue?
Josuke: Even comedians
know when to quit.
okuyasu: Aw, no!
The ice cream store’s closed!
But this is the only thing that
makes Monday mornings bearable!
Josuke: There’s nothing
we can do about it now,
so let’s just go.
Boy: Would you two care
for some ice cream?
- Both: Huh?
- Boy: Well?
Would you like the cream?
Okuyasu: Obviously,
but the place is closed.
We’re shit outta luck.
Boy: That is no reason
to give up.
I just so happen
to have two here.
it’s a quid pro quo
for the tissues you gave me.
- ( Josuke gasps )
- ( Okuyasu gasps )
Boy: Earth seems
quite livable indeed.
That, it does.
Okuyasu: What? ( Groans )
why do you have
ice cream cones in your bag?
And how are they cold?!
Boy: Are the ice of creams
unsatisfactory?
Okuyasu: That’s not the point
right now, alien boy!
Who the hell are you, for real?!
Boy: Bizarre. If I recall,
I already told you.
Ah! You want me
to introduce myself.
How could I forget?
You may hereafter address me
as nu mikitakazo nshi.
I’ve lived 216 cycles.
I am the sole pilot
of a spaceship,
and I also rather enjoy
owning house pets.
- ( Josuke gasps )
- Okuyasu: Huh?
Mikitaka: This is
the house mouse
that spends its days in my bag.
He particularly likes it
when I brush his back.
okuyasu:
This freak’s a stand user.
no doubt about it.
Let’s send him to the hospital.
josuke:
Use your brain, okuyasu.
Do you really think a stand user
would make up a story
about being
from the magellanic clouds?
Okuyasu: Well, if you’re
so smart, what the hell is he?
Mikitaka: There, there.
it’s all right.
Josuke: I don’t have
the foggiest idea,
but it’s time to find out.
Don’t eat that ice cream.
( Okuyasu gasps )
Hmm.
You’re 216 years old?
- Mikitaka: Yes.
- Okuyasu: Hmm.
Mikitaka: Hmm.
Okuyasu: And you’re some kind
of spaceship pilot?
( Mikitaka winces )
okuyasu: Yo,
why are you copying me?
- mikitaka: Huh?
- Josuke: Let’s focus here.
So, friend, what’s the deal?
Are you telling us
you’re an alien?
Mikitaka: An alien.
An alien, yes.
I should have informed you
when we met.
I am indeed an alien.
Okuyasu: You know,
you’re a loony mother--
josuke: You said you had a ship.
If it’s a genuine flying saucer,
it should be
no problem to call it over.
You can do that, right?
Mikitaka: Of course,
but it’s currently
at an altitude
of 1,500,000 kilometers,
so it’d take
approximately three days,
so you’ll have to wait
for a while.
Josuke: Let me guess.
You call it with that watch?
Mikitaka: Impressive
deductive reasoning.
However, this must stay
between we three.
You mustn’t share
my secret with anyone.
okuyasu: I thought
that stunt with the crop circle
was an innocent prank,
but he’s off his rocker.
Maybe I should knock
this nose-ringed psycho
back to the mother ship.
Josuke: You always let
your fists do the talking.
Let’s dig a little deeper
before we get violent.
So you’re an alien, huh?
Does that mean you’re hiding
some kinda ray gun
or antigravity device in there?
Mikitaka: I have
both of those things,
but I did not journey to earth
to engage in conflict,
so I have stored them
on my ship.
Okuyasu: Aw, come on,
Mr. Alien man.
Why don’t you show us
something cool already?
Even your blood is boring.
What alien doesn’t come
with green blood?
josuke: Good point.
Alien blood’s always green.
Everyone knows that.
Mikitaka: I see.
Are you accusing me of lying?
Josuke: Hey, take it easy, man.
okuyasu: Yeah,
we’re calling you out, asshole!
I can deal with a prank
here and there,
but i’ll be damned
before I waste my time
with a freak like you!
Josuke: I thought we were
gonna do things my way!
Okuyasu: Shut up! It’s always
better to say it like it is!
- ( Sirens blaring )
- ( Bell ringing )
Okuyasu: Oh, man.
Did a fire break out?
- ( Mikitaka screams )
- ( Both gasp )
( Mikitaka gagging, screaming )
- okuyasu: Huh?
- Josuke: Wh-what’s happening?!
Mikitaka: This sound,
I can’t stand this sound!
You have to find a way
to stop this sound!
Such a horrible sensation!
i’m allergic
to this wretched noise!
Make it stop!
( Screams )
Okuyasu: That’s enough!
This guy’s not right!
We should get as far away
from him as we possibly can!
Josuke: Yeah,
but he’s suffering.
we can’t just up and
abandon him in this condition.
okuyasu:
He said it was allergies.
Just leave him alone.
I’m outta here, josuke.
Josuke: Hey! Come back!
Damn, he can be such a dick.
( Mikitaka shuddering )
josuke: Hey,
you doin’ okay over here?
Mikitaka: Please, take me away.
take me away
from this horrid sound.
( Screams )
Josuke: What the hell?!
Mikitaka: Take me away!
Josuke: Whoa, you were
telling the truth.
Mikitaka: Indeed, I was.
I have the ability to transmute
my form into anything.
Hurry! Let us take
our leave, I beg you!
This sound is going
to split my head in two!
I’ll turn into sneakers,
so, please,
put them on, and save me!
In return for your help,
i’ll do anything you ask!
( Josuke gasps )
Hey, are you a stand user?!
Whoa! ( Screams )
Whoa. This is some crazy speed!
Mikitaka: That’s because
of your assistance.
My speed and jumping abilities
have been doubled
due to our combined power.
Josuke: An alien, just my luck.
Josuke: Whoa!
What the hell
is going on here?!
Hmm?
Hey...
You really can’t see this?
Mikitaka: Huh?
Josuke: He can’t see it.
He’s not a stand user.
Then where did
his powers come from?
What the hell are you?!
Mikitaka: You are
a stubborn one.
as i’ve been trying
to tell you, I am an alien.
josuke: Fine.
Just give me a second.
Look, no offense,
but it’s hard to wrap
my head around all this.
Mikitaka: Anyway, I truly
appreciate your saving me.
Sirens are mundane here,
but the people on my planet
abhor the sound.
The wavelength
is very upsetting.
I’d like to repay that kindness.
It’s the least I can do
for one so brave.
Shall I turn
into a fan for you?
Or perhaps a back scratcher
to grab those
hard-to-reach places.
( Josuke gasps )
I didn’t get you out of there
’cause I wanted
something in return.
♪
But if you’ll
really do anything,
well, who am I to turn you down?
Mikitaka: What is it
you request of me?
Josuke: First off, can you
really turn into anything,
like big or small
or even multiples?
mikitaka: Yes. I can
transform into nearly anything.
however,
becoming complex machinery
or powerful objects
is unfeasible.
Josuke: I read you
loud and clear,
and I can tell that we’re
gonna be the best of friends.
So you wanna thank me, right?
- mikitaka: Yes.
- Josuke: Well, you’re in luck,
’cause I just cooked up
a brilliant idea, friend.
trust me.
It’s a win-win for everyone.
- Mikitaka: Win-win?
- Josuke: Right!
See, a few weeks ago,
I won quite a bit
of spending money
in the local lottery.
My mom found out about it,
made a big stink,
and froze my account.
Once that woman makes up
her mind about something,
your fate is sealed.
Being flat broke
during the summer
is the worst, let me tell you.
( Sighs )
That’s why...
I need you to turn into these!
Can you?
mikitaka:
What are they, exactly?
Josuke: A pair of dice,
obviously,
and i’m gonna make
some cash with them.
After that, i’ll split
the winnings with you,
thus creating a win-win.
mikitaka: So how do
the dice function? Explain.
Josuke: Wait. You really
don’t know what dice are?
Mikitaka: I don’t. My apologies.
Josuke: There’s nothing
to apologize for.
It’s super easy to learn.
I’ll show you the ropes.
Anyone who likes playing games
goes nuts over these things.
They’ve got six sides and are
made from a hard material.
The red dot represents
the number one,
and the other faces have
different numbers up to six.
mikitaka: I see.
It’s starting to make sense.
The five dots represent
the number five, correct?
josuke:
That’s right, Mr. Alien!
Mikitaka: And three dots
represent a three.
josuke: Yep!
Now try turning into one.
Mikitaka: I’m at your service.
Simple.
Josuke: It’s close,
but you’re a little too big
to pass for a real die.
This is more like it.
You’ve also got an extra five.
Each face has a different number
from one to six.
The numbers on one side and its
opposite should equal seven.
Mikitaka: Oh, my apologies.
( Josuke gasps )
Mikitaka: Is this better?
Josuke: Huh?
( Mikitaka laughs )
That tickles!
josuke: Hey,
knock off the laughing.
and dice
aren’t supposed to talk.
Mikitaka: Huh?
Josuke: Oh, come on.
Mikitaka: I’ll try harder.
Josuke: I’m a little nervous
about this, but...
( Swallows )
You look good.
Make that great!
We can pull this off!
I’m getting all fired up!
Hope you’re ready to lose
some cashola, Rohan kishibe!
Mikitaka: Can’t breathe.
Rohan: Wow, what a surprise.
Now, why would josuke
higashikata be visiting me?
This is certainly
out of the ordinary.
Did you uncover
any more dirt on Kira?
josuke: Nope,
nothing since the last time
we checked in with you.
so, uh, yeah,
are you all done with
your manga work for the day?
I was wondering if you’d
let me take a peek
- at the next volume early.
- Rohan: Hmm?
What kind of nonsense
are you scheming?
Spit it out. Come on.
Josuke: Eh, I should’ve figured.
Can’t get anything
past you, Rohan-sensei.
’kay, you got me.
I have an ulterior motive.
( Gasps )
I’m begging you, sensei!
Please play cee-lo with me!
Rohan: That’s it? Cee-lo?
Josuke: I’m gonna be
completely honest.
Summer’s finally here, and i’m
totally strapped for cash.
Well, I do have 30,000 on hand.
This is all the money i’ve got
to my name, but it won’t do.
Nowadays, 30,000 yen
won’t get you more
than a couple visits
to the amusement park
and some snacks,
so I either make some dough
or go flat broke.
Taking risks and thrill seeking,
it’s the very foundation
of being young!
That’s what I think, at least.
You agree, don’t you?!
( Rohan sighs )
Let me be frank.
i’ve despised you
from the moment I met you.
There’s absolutely no reason
for me to waste my precious time
playing cee-lo with you.
Josuke: I guess you’re right.
I mean, you’re not
exactly hurting for cash.
i don’t know
what I was thinking.
Why would you want
to play a game with me?
Rohan: Even so, count me in.
josuke: Huh?!
Seriously, you’ll do it?
Rohan: I don’t dislike games.
In fact, i’m intrigued.
Come around back
whenever you’re ready.
Josuke: We’re gonna have
a great time, Rohan-sensei.
( Chuckles )
Rohan: Do these rules
work for you?
Josuke: Yeah, looks good.
Rohan: Each chip
is worth 1,000 yen,
and you must roll three dice
into the bowl.
If one falls out, you lose.
- Josuke: Got it.
- Rohan: All right.
I’ll place the rules here
so they’re in plain view.
Josuke: Okay, let’s get
this party started!
- Rohan: No, wait.
- Josuke: Eh?
Rohan: We won’t
be using those dice.
Josuke: Huh?!
Rohan: We’ll use these.
they’re a set
I found in the house.
♪
Josuke: Oh, really?
That’s interesting.
Is there some reason that you
don’t wanna use my dice?
Rohan: Not really.
I feel inclined to play
with my own is all.
Just a whim.
When I mentioned
I was intrigued,
it wasn’t by the prospect
of playing cee-lo.
No, no, josuke, I was intrigued
by the prospect
of swiping 30,000 yen from you.
Now, when you lose against me,
I expect you to pay in full.
i don’t care how much
we’ve been through. Understand?
( Josuke sighs )
( Chuckles )
Perfect! The dice he found
are actually the alien!
I managed to sneak them
into his house
when he wasn’t
paying attention.
I’m such a bad boy.
It won’t be a ton,
but you’re about to fund
my summer vacay, Rohan-sensei.
Rohan: Now then, shall we
determine who gets to go first?
Four.
Josuke: Yes!
Rohan: Looks like
you’re up first.
Roll the dice.
- Mikitaka: Ow!
- Rohan: Hmm?
Josuke: Uh, ow, ow, ow!
I banged my hand
into the table.
( Laughs )
( Mikitaka sighs )
Place your bet,
and roll the dice.
josuke: Yeah, right.
Uh, guess i’ll start things off
by betting 2,000 yen,
so i’ll throw down two chips.
Rohan: All right, so will I.
Josuke: If I roll a one,
a two, and a three,
i’ll have to pay double,
so I need to avoid
those numbers at all costs.
One, and two, and three!
Keep those rolls
away from me! Eh?
( Rohan groans )
the first roll
calls for a light touch,
sorta like a practice toss.
Here we go. Gently.
Okay! Lookin’ good!
- ( Gasps )
- Rohan: What?
Josuke: I-it’s an omen.
Rohan: Huh?
Narrator: Triple sixes,
a.K.A. "An omen."
Josuke wins five times
what he wagered.
Josuke: Hey! Don’t start
that way, dumb-ass!
- Rohan: Eh?!
- Josuke: What I meant to say
was, "I can’t believe
I had such dumb luck!"
a triple six
and five times the winnings,
how’s that even happen?
To the untrained eye,
it almost looks
like i’m cheating,
even though i’m not!
- ( Rohan growls )
- ( Josuke laughs )
Rohan: Somehow,
you already managed
to win 10,000 yen from me.
josuke: Yeah,
it’s the craziest thing...
Rohan: At any rate,
let’s continue.
If i’m not mistaken, i’m next.
i want to get back
what i’ve lost, so I think...
I’ll wager ten chips.
Josuke: You sure about this?
Rohan: And here we go.
( Both gasp )
Narrator: A one,
a two, and a three.
Rohan must pay double
the amount of his wager.
Josuke: He’s taking
the hustle way too far.
It’s getting obvious.
Does this alien know the meaning
of the word "restraint"?
( Rohan groans )
Josuke: Shit biscuits.
If this keeps up,
he’ll bust us for sure.