Okuyasu: It looks like
no one in koichi’s family
knows where he went either,
and from the sound of things,
they’re close
to callin’ the police.
Josuke: Damn it.
So he really is missing.
Yukako is nowhere
to be seen either.
Okuyasu: I feel like
it’s all my fault.
Wait!
You don’t think she snapped
and snuffed him out, do you?!
Josuke: Well, no,
I don’t think it’s come to that.
Regardless,
she’s holding him captive.
Come on. We need
to find him and do it fast.
I feel like
we don’t have much time left
if we wanna find him alive.
♪
( Koichi screams )
It won’t open!
This can’t be happening to me!
Damn. I’m pretty sure
there was a movie
that has the answer I need,
but I never ended up
watching it,
because it looked way too long.
( Groans )
I think i’ve almost
got this ridiculous thing
figured out.
One, then four, zero, zero.
( Whimpers )
Open.
( Gasps )
( Whimpering )
♪
Yukako: I washed
your pajama bottoms...
As well as your underwear.
Is there a problem?
( Koichi sighs )
Yukako: I can’t help
if I don’t know what’s wrong.
Koichi: I-it’s just that i’m
a freshman in high school.
- How could I let this happen?
- ( Yukako gasps )
Koichi: I’d be embarrassed,
if I didn’t already feel
like a pathetic
waste of a human.
Enough. Please, stop this.
I mean, surely you
must despise me by now.
- Don’t I disgust you?
- Yukako: Ohh.
Koichi: Won’t you please
just let me go home now?!
What could you possibly like
about a guy
who just peed his pants?
Yukako: Koichi, you poor,
pitiful thing. How awful.
I must be putting your gentle
heart through so much agony.
( Koichi gasps )
Yukako: I’m such a bad girl,
the lowest of the low.
Koichi: Nothing I say
has any effect on her.
I think i’m gonna cry.
First I wet myself. Now this.
What the hell is going on?
Yukako: There’s just one thing.
- ( Koichi gasps )
- Yukako: I was watching
when you talked about being
a pathetic human being
and saw a sparkle
deep behind your eyes.
What I saw in that moment
was positively intoxicating.
If I didn’t know any better,
i’d swear you were hiding
an Ace up your sleeve.
( Koichi gasps )
Yukako: And if i’m being honest,
it makes me like you even more.
It’s the reason I wanna learn
everything about you.
After all, what’s a little bit
of poop and snot
when you’re madly in love
with your soul mate, right, ko?
I’m surprised you were worried.
Washing
your soiled unmentionables
filled me with a kind of joy
that i’d never known.
( Koichi shuddering )
( Door opens )
Yukako: Look.
( Koichi gasps )
( Electricity crackling )
Yukako: What do you think?
I’m making an electric chair.
With any luck, it’ll be ready
for our dinnertime studies.
- ( Koichi whimpering )
- ( Yukako laughs )
( Door closes )
I was thinking about trying out
a new Italian recipe tonight,
so I have to stock up
on olive oil.
I can’t wait.
Koichi: Somebody help me!
She’s going further and further
off the deep end.
I have to get out of here fast,
or she’s seriously
going to kill me.
But...
How exactly do I do that?
( Josuke groans )
Okuyasu: I might be
completely wrong about this,
but even if someone’s found
a way to keep koichi quiet,
can’t he still call out for help
using reverb?
Josuke: Ideally, yes,
but reverb only has a range
of about 50 meters.
If he was taken
somewhere isolated,
his powers’d be no good.
Okuyasu: It’s like looking
for a needle in a haystack.
( Koichi gasps ) Hang on.
She said something about
stocking up on more olive oil,
but she wouldn’t
go shopping at this hour.
Maybe she’s doing a phone order?
Hey. Could it be...
( Reverb squeals )
Koichi: It is. A pay phone.
And 48 meters away.
Yes, it’s just within range.
Thank goodness
reverb is a sound stand.
Now I can signal josuke
and get some help!
( Gasps )
I don’t have any ten yen coins.
I was in my pajamas
when I was dragged here.
Should I just dial 1-1-0?
But if I do that,
she might kill the officers.
Damn it. I’ll just have to find
some other way
to contact josuke.
Yukako:
You were wondering whether
there was a pay phone nearby,
weren’t you, koichi?
( Koichi screams )
Yu-yukako.
Yukako: You don’t
have to pretend.
I know precisely
what you’re thinking.
Since I told you that I was
going to go buy some olive oil,
you thought there must be
a pay phone nearby,
but it needed ten yen coins,
which you don’t have.
Does that about cover it?
Koichi: Oh, there’s a pay phone?
How ’bout that?
( Yukako scoffs )
Feigning ignorance?
I’d give up on the notion
of calling someone for help.
You’re not taking a single step
outside this house
until I say so,
but so you won’t be tempted,
i’m going to destroy
the phone’s emergency button.
( Koichi gasps )
Yukako: Would you like anything?
Koichi: No, I guess not.
( Sighs )
There’s just
no reasoning with her.
That was it,
my last shot at getting help.
♪
Yukako: Hmm?
Wh-what is this writing?
( Telephone tones beeping )
Why are there sounds
coming out of my arm?
( Phone line rings )
The phone’s calling someone.
That doesn’t make sense.
I never dialed a number.
Josuke: Higashikata speaking.
- ( Yukako gasps )
- Koichi: I got through.
If the right signals
are transmitted,
a push-button phone
will connect.
Josuke: Koichi?
Hey, is that you?
It’s me, josuke.
Koichi, where are you?
- ( Waves crashing )
- What’s that?
I hear waves crashing.
Yukako: Koichi.
So I was right.
You do have a power like me.
Koichi: Yes, I did it!
Now josuke’s
gonna rush over here
and rescue me for sure.
It’ll take
20 minutes tops by car.
I just have to figure out
a way to hold out
until they can get here.
Okuyasu: Huh?
Josuke: A pay phone
and the sound of waves.
The only place
koichi could be...
Is right here.
Yukako: Koichi.
Koichi.
Koichi: She’s coming
back to the house!
Looks like I have
no choice but to fight.
♪
( Hammering )
( Grunts )
( Yukako groans )
Open this door, koichi.
( Koichi laughs )
You want in so bad,
why don’t you break it down?
A broken door
will definitely make josuke
stop and take notice.
( Gasps )
Yukako: You’ve made me
very happy, koichi.
Koichi: Huh?
Yukako: Discovering
you have powers like I do
is the most wonderful surprise
I could have received,
though I have to say,
i’m a bit irritated
that you kept this a secret.
Even so,
i’m happy you’re like me,
because when a man and woman
decide to spend the rest
of their lives together,
nothing is more important
than a relationship
built on love, trust,
and shared values, right?
The two of us share something
no one else
could ever dream of having.
Just think about it.
We could be the perfect couple.
So, please, koichi,
open the door.
( Screams )
♪
When I say open the door,
open the goddamn door!
Reverb: I hate you!
I hate you! I hate you!
I hate you!
Koichi: Did you actually believe
we’d be the perfect couple?
Why can’t you understand how
much I hate what you’re doing?
That noise
will keep bombarding you
until you renounce your love
for me and cry for forgiveness!
Reverb: I hate you!
I hate you! I hate you!
Yukako: You’re not making sense.
This foolishness is
practically inaudible to me.
Reverb: I hate you!
( Koichi gasping )
Wh-what’s going on?
This isn’t at all like
what happened with tamami.
Her delusions are too strong.
But I didn’t think it’d be
completely useless on her!
( Screams )
Yukako: I’ve finally
found the one person
i’m bound to
with the red thread of fate,
and I won’t let
anything come between us.
Some people never find
their soul mate.
Don’t you understand
how lucky we are?
( Koichi screams )
( Gasps )
Yukako: Oh, koichi.
My plan was to turn you
into an outstanding man,
but recent events have forced me
to change my mind.
So until you fall
madly in love with me,
you will remain in this house.
And make no mistake,
you are going to love me,
or else...
I might murder you.
Koichi: I can’t let her in here,
no matter what.
I just need to land
one more attack with reverb.
If I go all out, i’ll be able
to unleash an even louder sound.
Reverb!
( Gasps )
Something’s wrong with reverb.
Are you all right?
( Gasps ) He’s not moving.
♪
No. What’s happening to him?
Did he collapse
because he sensed
that our situation is hopeless?
It can’t be!
Reverb is dead!
Wh-what happened?
No. Reverb, he’s been
turned into a lifeless husk.
But how?!
( Yukako gasps )
Koichi: A stand’s
a manifestation of the soul,
which means
I must have pushed mine
too far past
its breaking point,
and it collapsed
under the pressure!
( Wails )
I didn’t mean for this
to happen, reverb!
Yukako: What? ( Gasps )
What the hell did he
call that thing, a "stand"?
Whatever it is,
I have to stop it!
( Grunting )
Get this thing out of my way.
( Koichi gasps )
She’s gonna kill me.
If that psycho makes it
through the door and catches me,
i’m as good as dead.
( Yukako gasps )
Koichi, open this door!
( Koichi screams )
I have to stop her
from getting in here somehow.
If only there was a way for
that door to blow her far away.
- ( Yukako grunts )
- ( Koichi screams )
( Yukako gasps )
It broke out of its shell.
Where did you put it?
Answer the damn question,
koichi.
- Where did you put that thing?
- Koichi: Huh?
- ( Reverb screeches )
- ( Both gasp )
♪
- Yukako: What?
- Koichi: Wait. Is that...
I don’t believe it.
It’s reverb.
It’s still alive.
It must have been
changing into a new form
while it was in that shell.
Yukako: Is this a joke?
Its design
hasn’t really changed at all,
besides the fact that it shrunk.
Regardless, changing shape
isn’t going to help.
Koichi: Oh, man, it’s fast.
( Both gasp )
Yukako: Where’s this wind
coming from?
Koichi: Whoa!
It actually blew her away!
I don’t know how,
but some kind of wind
blasted her out of the house!
( Yukako grunts )
♪
Damn. What just happened to me?
What did that stand do?
Koichi: Is that...
Yeah, it’s reverb’s writing.
( Yelps )
I get it now.
She touched the graffitied door,
and the writing became real.
The sensation
of the word "fwoosh"
literally sent her flying.
Wait a minute.
Right before it happened,
I wished the door
would blow her away.
I didn’t realize it, but I was
controlling that sensation.
This is the brand-new reverb,
reverb act two!
( Reverb squeals )
Yukako: Oh, koichi.
( Vehicle approaching )
( Gasps )
♪
It’s them.
Josuke: This vacation spot
is the one place I know
that’s by the sea
and has lots of empty houses.
Okuyasu: Yeah,
that’s great and all,
but there are still
tons of houses around here.
How do we find out
which one he’s in?
Josuke: By finding
the phone booth.
Koichi did call us
using a public phone, right?
Once we find that booth,
we’ll start searching
the nearby houses one by one.
Okuyasu: Right.
Yukako: Search around
all you want.
Sweet, adorable koichi
belongs to me.
I’ll never let
anyone else have him.
( Gasps )
Koichi: I strongly suggest
you keep your distance, yukako.
And you should believe me
when I tell you
there’s just no way
that your powers
can compete with reverb
act two’s new abilities.
Our days of playing house
are over.
( Yukako sputters )
Now my left eyelid
is twitching.
Since I was a kid,
getting upset always set off
my orbicularis oculi.
It was like a weird tick
that said
I was about to get violent.
Oh, and just so you know,
one stupid little modification
doesn’t suddenly
make you a big shot!
I’m gonna have to get
a little rough now.
It’s hot!
( Gasps )
Damn it. How could you do this?
Koichi, you shit!
You burned my hand.
Koichi: When you said you were
gonna "get a little rough",
I didn’t think
you meant your vulgar mouth.
Yukako: How dare you do this
after all i’ve done?
You pants-wetting shrimp.
You are mine.
You belong to me,
yet you dare defy me?
I own you!
Koichi: Reverb act two.
I missed?
Okuyasu: Josuke!
Josuke: Yeah, I heard it.
Could be wrong, but it sounded
like something broke.
Okuyasu: Hey,
I think it’s that house.
( Josuke gasps )
Koichi: Man, I can’t believe
she can make her hair
grow to this length.
Her soul’s more powerful
than I thought,
but it’s a dark
and vindictive soul.
Yukako: So its name is reverb.
Pathetic. I’ve figured out
the secret behind your trick.
All I have to do is avoid
touching that writing.
Now i’ll ask you this
one more time.
You love me, right, koichi?
♪
I’d advise against saying no
if you wanna keep living.
I’m completely prepared
to tear down this house
and bury you in the wreckage.
And if you die,
you’ll be mine for all eternity.
You’ll remain in my heart
as a personal memory
of love everlasting.
Time to answer the question!
Koichi: I have,
but you refuse to listen,
which is how I got wrapped up
in this whole mess,
so now, for the umpteenth time,
I don’t.
Don’t make me say it again.
( Yukako growls )
You’re dead, koichi!
Hmm?
♪
Koichi: Weren’t you
listening to what I said?
Now that I have this new power,
you can’t hold me
hostage anymore.
You’re touching the writing
that’s gonna blow you away.
Not bad for a pants-wetting
little shrimp, huh?
( Yukako screaming )
( Koichi gasps )
Oh, no.
Why did her hair turn white?
( Gasps )
She’s not dead, is she?
( Heart beating )
Good. She’s alive.
( Sighs ) She might be
a deranged, love-obsessed,
matted mess of a she-devil,
but I guess I should be happy.
( Yukako yells )
( Koichi gags )
Yukako: I wasn’t able
to keep hold of you
with my loving heart,
but I think i’ll destroy
your precious stand
as consolation.
( Reverb gasping )
Yukako: You disrespectful
heartbreaker!
( Koichi gasping )
Even as beaten up as she is,
she’s still able to fight?
Her will is scary intense.
Yukako: Not another word.
"Intense"? Screw you,
you panty-wetting douche!
How dare you even speak
when you’re the one
who did this to me?!
You rejected my love,
blasted me with your stand,
and made my treasured hair
turn white,
you pathetic little jerk-off!
I loved you
with every fiber of my being,
but I refuse to let you
get away with doing this
to my gorgeous hair!
I don’t care
if you’re my soul mate.
No one gets
to undermine my beauty.
( Reverb groaning )
Yukako: I’m gonna yank off
your piss-soaked prick,
rip out your insides,
and feed ’em to you
as you choke
on my merciless love!
Koichi: Please, stop this.
Yukako: I told you no words.
( Laughs )
It’s time to get
what’s coming to you.
( Crumbling )
Wh-what the hell
was that sound just now?
Koichi: Yukako,
you gotta let go of my stand.
Grab ahold of something.
The cliff is about to crumble.
When reverb was listening
for your heartbeat,
it also heard the ground
slowly splitting underneath us.
( Yukako scoffs )
Don’t try bullshitting me
to save yourself
from your punishment.
( Gasping )
( Koichi gasps )
( Yukako screams )
I have to let go so I can
grab on to something else.
Shit! I don’t have time.
♪
( Gasps )
Koichi: I told you
the ground would crumble.
Of course,
you’ve proven time and again
that nothing
I say to you sinks in.
Yukako: Huh?
♪
You mean you’d
already placed it there?
So while I was in a frenzy,
trying to rip reverb to pieces,
you were using your stand
to write on that rock
beneath the cliff?
The entire time I was thinking
of how to kill koichi,
he was focusing
all of his energy
on how to save me from myself.
I’ve lost.
He completely defeated me.
No. If i’m being honest
with myself,
I lost the moment I met koichi.
Okuyasu: Hey, koichi, over here!
Are you still in one piece?
Josuke: You’re not hurt,
are you, koichi?
Koichi: Josuke and okuyasu.
You guys found me.
What took you two
so long to get here?
Yukako: But now...
I think i’m even
more in love with him.
I don’t care if he ignores me
for the rest of our lives.
Just thinking about him
fills me with joy. Koichi!
Okuyasu: Hey, over there,
isn’t that yukako?
Her hair has turned
completely white.
Josuke: Whoa. What happened?
Okuyasu: No idea, but look.
The way she’s smiling,
you’d think she was
on top of the world,
and she’s looking over here.
- Koichi: What?!
- Josuke: Oh, yeah.
You’re right.
That’s really creepy.
Okuyasu: Quick!
Let’s get out of here!
Koichi: Save me, josuke!
Josuke: It’s every man
for himself!
Man: Well,
i’ll be a sea gull’s beak.
Did you see that?
Man #2: No, grandpa.
You’re not allowed
to have a drink. ( Hiccups )
- ( Bell rings )
- Narrator: Cape boing.
After apparently witnessing
a young woman jump to her death,
only to bounce off the rocks
below with a gentle boing,
a pair of fisherman
created an urban legend
and a new appellation.
Teacher: Hirose, I can tell
you really gave it your all
this time.
You get scores like that
when you study.
Koichi: Aw, man.
I’m not sure
how I should feel about this.
♪
♪ Anytime I need
to see your face ♪
♪ I just close my eyes,
and I am taken to a place ♪
♪ where your crystal mind
and magenta feelings ♪
♪ take up shelter
in the base of my spine ♪
♪ sweet like
a chica cherry cola ♪
♪ I don’t need
to try to explain ♪
♪ I just hold on tight,
and if it happens again ♪
♪ I may move so slightly
to the arms ♪
♪ and the lips and the face
of the human cannonball ♪
♪ that I need to, I want to
♪ come stand
a little bit closer ♪
♪ breathe in,
and get a bit higher ♪
♪ you’ll never know what hit you
when I get to you ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪