Okuyasu: Even after getting
his ass handed to him,
that hazamada guy still said
he didn’t know anything
about that sparky s.O.B.
Who killed my bro?
Josuke: Yeah.
Apparently he’s only
ever talked to him
over the phone.
Okuyasu: You did torture
that twat-waffle
before he told you this, right?
He could have been lying to you!
Josuke: Look, I really believe
hazamada was
telling me the truth.
If he knew the user’s identity,
he would’ve been killed by now.
( Okuyasu gasps )
Oh, yeah, I guess you’re right.
That is why my bro was offed.
Josuke: Exactly. And hazamada’s
still breathing, isn’t he?
For now,
that’s all the proof we need
that he’s telling the truth.
Now then, hazamada did
tell us about one thing.
Hazamada: Don’t ask me
to tell you why this is,
but it seems stand users
are inadvertently
drawn to each other,
even if the users have
never laid eyes on one another.
You’ve heard of the myth
that says the red thread of fate
forever connects you
with your partner-to-be, right?
Like in the myth, stand users
are bound to cross paths.
♪
The user could be
an enemy, a friend,
that annoying guy on the bus
who steps on your foot,
or even
your new next-door neighbor.
Everyone is suspect.
Morioh’s a small town,
you know.
It’s anybody’s guess how many
stand users are living here,
but try as they may
to conceal themselves,
they’ll eventually emerge.
He knows
it’s just a matter of time
before destiny
brings you together,
so he wants you to disappear
before that happens.
Okuyasu: Damn it!
This shit-head’s a damn coward.
What the hell
is he waiting for?!
Josuke: Well,
he’s probably playing it safe
for the time being.
When guys like that
decide to go on the offensive,
it’s usually
because they’re confident
that no one can take them out.
Okuyasu: Huh?
Josuke: Hmm?
Hey, it’s koichi.
Josuke: Yeah,
but why’s he at a snooty cafe?
Okuyasu: Yoo-hoo, koi--
what!
♪
What the--Josuke, it’s a girl!
( Singing in Japanese )
Girl: So, koichi,
I hope meeting me here
wasn’t too much trouble.
Koichi: Huh?
It wasn’t any trouble at all.
Really, there’s nowhere else
i’d rather be,
although i’m not quite sure
what this is about.
Josuke: Wow.
Koichi’s actually with a girl.
Okuyasu: And not just any girl.
That’s Yukako Yamagishi,
from my class.
Come on.
Let’s get a closer look.
Koichi: I’m not sure if this is
about showing you my homework,
but you should probably know
my grades aren’t all that good,
and my handwriting’s sloppy.
Though if it’s money,
I suppose I could give you
a thousand yen.
Or maybe you came here to ask me
to be the weekly class leader.
Yukako: I’m afraid
it’s none of those.
Koichi: Really? It isn’t?
Then why did you
want to meet me here?
If you’re looking for someone
to take in a kitten or puppy,
i’m sorry to say I already
have a dopey dog named police.
Yukako: Koichi, i--
I have to tell you something.
Koichi...
You need to know that i’ve
fallen madly in love with you!
- Koichi: Huh?
- Okuyasu: What did she say?!
( Grunting )
Koichi: I’m sorry.
I don’t think I...
Heard you right.
Yukako: I’m sure you did.
Every day, all I
think about is you, koichi.
I’ve been, oh, so frightened
to utter those words to you.
However,
if I held it in any longer,
my heart was going to burst,
but I had to take a leap
and tell you my true feelings,
even if you were to hate me.
Koichi: Uh...
Is this really happening?
Is she actually
professing her love to me?!
I wouldn’t believe it
if I hadn’t heard it,
but that’s what she said.
( Gasps )
I’m so happy.
( Okuyasu wails ) Josuke, please
tell me this isn’t happening!
Why does koichi
get all the luck?
No one’s ever said
anything like that to me before!
Josuke: There, there,
you big baby.
There’s no need to cry.
But still, holy crap,
that koichi sure is something.
Yukako: So, koichi, you must
have a girlfriend already.
Koichi: No.
I’m as single as can be.
Hang on. You wouldn’t tease me
about something like this,
would you?
Yukako: No way! I’m serious!
( Koichi gasps )
Yukako: I noticed your face
has become
more chiseled as of late,
a strong face brimming
with courage and conviction.
Also, you’re really charming
when you smile.
Josuke: You know, she’s honestly
making a lot of good points.
Okuyasu: I have a chiseled face,
too, don’t I?
Yukako: That said,
what attracts me to a man
more than anything else
is potential,
and you are
potential personified.
Koichi: Wow,
that’s the first time
anyone’s ever said that to me.
Yukako: But you must be repulsed
by homely girls like me.
I don’t blame you.
Koichi: Eh, what are
you talking about?
That’s not how I see you at all.
Okuyasu: Would you come on,
you lucky bastard?
Quit messin’ around, and
seal the deal with that hottie.
Just go for it,
and ask her out already.
Yukako: Please be honest.
Do you hate me?
( Both stammer )
Koichi: No. Don’t be ridiculous.
I couldn’t hate you
even if I wanted to.
Yukako: Do you love me?
Koichi: Mm, hold on a second.
Don’t you think
we’re moving a bit too fast?
Yukako: You do hate me.
Koichi: No,
you’ve got it all wrong.
You just caught me off guard
when you started
talking about lo--
koichi: Well, which is it?!
Are you madly in love
or toying with my feelings?!
Answer me, damn it!
I poured my heart out to you!
And now i’ve spilled my coffee,
all because
of your heartlessness!
Koichi: Uh...
( Yukako gasping )
I don’t know
what just came over me.
I’m so sorry. Forgive me!
Koichi: Uh...
Yukako: Goodbye.
You’ll come see me again,
I hope.
Okuyasu: Well, I have to say,
for some reason,
I suddenly feel
like a deflated balloon.
Any jealousy I had over that
just went
right out of the window.
Josuke: No kidding.
Let’s pretend
we didn’t see any of that.
Okuyasu: Yeah.
( Koichi gasping )
( Gags )
( Coughs )
What’s with my cola?!
W-why’s all this hair in it?!
What in the world is going on?
Josuke: Stand users are
always drawn to each other, huh?
Could it be?
( Bell pealing )
Koichi: Huh?
( Sighs )
Yukako: Hey, it’s me, koichi.
( Koichi shrieks )
Who the--oh, yukako.
( Yukako giggles )
What are you doing?
Koichi: Well, uh,
it’s my turn to clean the lab,
so i’m doing my part
to help out.
Fourth period was chemistry lab,
after all.
- Yukako: Hmm.
- Koichi: Uh...
Yukako: Koichi...
About yesterday, I know
I said some strange things,
but I hope
you’ll forget all that.
Koichi: Mm-hmm.
Yukako: I have a bad habit
of behaving that way
when I overthink things.
I’m so embarrassed.
How could I forget how important
it is to be open-minded?
Koichi: That’s true,
but don’t worry.
You surprised me a little bit,
but it’s no big deal.
I don’t think any less of you.
Yukako: We can still be friends
despite my outburst, right?
Koichi: Of course!
That works for me!
I’d love to be friends
with you!
Yukako: Really? Thank goodness!
I was so worried
that you absolutely hated me!
I was tossing
and turning all night.
( Koichi laughs )
Well, that’s just silly.
Yukako:
And as a little something
to show you
just how sorry I am, here.
- ( Koichi gasping )
- Yukako: I so hope you like it.
I spent the whole night
knitting this for you,
and what a relief!
I knew your length
and chest width,
but I had to guess
about the shoulders,
and it fits perfectly!
I made you an amulet, too.
Now you can find true love.
And there’s more.
I also made us bento boxes,
everything we need
to have lunch together.
I bought the shrimp at
the local market this morning.
You won’t find freshness
like this at a grocery store.
This is flounder meuniere,
but I made sure to remove
every single bone with tweezers.
Now open wide, please.
Ahh.
Koichi: As if
yesterday wasn’t enough,
this is definitive proof
that Yukako Yamagishi
is completely deranged.
Yukako: Ahh.
Koichi: I’ve gotta
put a stop to this,
but if I take a bite,
i’ll just validate her feelings,
and if I refuse,
she’ll kill me!
What am I supposed to do?!
- Girl: Come on, hirose!
- ( Koichi gasps )
Girl: Quit goofing off, slacker!
Class is going to be
starting any minute,
so hurry up,
and dump this garbage.
Koichi: Yes!
Thank god for trash!
Oh, yeah.
How could I have forgotten?
I’ll take care of this
right now!
Girl: Jeez,
you are totally hopeless.
Here. Just give it to me.
I’ll take it outside for you.
Koichi: Uh, no, it’s fine.
I’ve got it.
Girl: Just hand it over,
would you?!
I’m the class rep,
so i’m the one who’s
gonna get chewed out. Jeez!
Koichi: Sorry.
( Yukako growls )
♪
- Hey, you.
- Girl: Huh?
Yukako: I’ll ask you one time
to stop flirting with koichi.
Girl: What are
you talking about?
Do you mean koichi hirose?
You’re joking, right?
I don’t know
what you’ve heard,
but there’s nothing
going on with us.
Yukako: That pathetic lie
might have worked on me if you
didn’t reek with the stench
of a malodorous home-wrecker.
Girl: A what?!
The hell are you talking about?
Yukako: Listen closely.
If I catch you
trying to seduce koichi again,
Mark my words, i’ll make
your life a living hell.
( Girl growls )
You hold your horses, bitch.
You’re threatening me over
a spindly scrub like koichi?
I couldn’t give two shits
about the guy!
Even if I was all into him,
you have absolutely no right
to tell me what I can
or cannot do, dumb-ass!
( Winces )
( Groans )
Man, that hurt.
What happened? Huh?
What the hell is her problem?!
That psycho is out of her mind.
She has the hots for koichi?
Hah! What a joke.
Just wait until the school
finds out. ( Grunts )
Huh?
Wait. What’s that?
I feel hot.
Something’s not right.
What’s going on?
It feels like i’m burning up.
( Gasps )
( Screaming )
W-water!
( Grunts )
Someone help me! Water! I need--
( groans )
♪
( Sighs ) Huh?
Okuyasu: Hey, Josuke.
Hmph. Looks like you were right
about Yukako Yamagishi
being a stand user.
It’s a stand
that manipulates hair at will.
Josuke: Seems like,
but given what we’ve seen,
it doesn’t appear as though
she’d go after koichi
or us for that matter.
Anyway, Okuyasu,
what are you planning to do
about this girl’s
messed-up hair?
I’m not sure if you know this,
but shining diamond
isn’t able to fix stuff
the hand takes away.
Okuyasu: Huh? Haven’t I
done enough for one day?
I did keep her
from getting burned to a crisp.
Even if I wanted
to do somethin’,
i’m not much of a hairstylist.
( Koichi grunting )
♪
( Koichi wails )
Oh, no. What am I gonna do?
Look what I got
on my latest english test.
Josuke: Whoa.
Koichi: Yukako has been
stressing me out so much,
I haven’t been able
to concentrate.
Okuyasu: Oh, man,
even I did better than you did.
I got a 32 on that test.
Koichi: If i’m being honest,
when she started
paying attention to me,
I was a little excited
about where things were going.
I mean, no girl’s
ever said she loved me before.
Okuyasu: Yeah, I totally feel
what you’re saying
on that one, my man.
I feel you deeply. Mm-hmm.
Koichi: I was
way too wishy-washy
about my feelings and brought
this all on myself. Darn it.
There’s only one way
to end this madness now.
I have to tell yukako
that i’m not interested in her
so she leaves me alone.
Josuke: I’d think twice
about that, koichi.
If you try being
that blunt with her,
it’ll only fan
the demented flames
of her passion even more.
She’ll lose it again.
( Both gasp )
Koichi: Yeah,
I guess you’re right.
Josuke: Well, of course
i’m right. Now listen up.
Yukako is insane,
but convincing her
to stop using her hair
for evil is low priority.
We have far more pressing
concerns at the moment.
Figuring out a way
to not provoke her comes first.
Koichi: But how do we do that?
Josuke: The truth is
it doesn’t matter
how infatuated she is with you.
If she comes
to her own conclusion
that you’re the most pathetic,
disgusting schmuck around,
then we get to go on living
happily ever after, right?
( Koichi sighs )
Josuke: So all you’ve
gotta do on your end
is act like a total jackass
whenever you’re in front of her.
Okuyasu: Oh, now I get
where you’re going with this.
You’re such a genius, Josuke!
( Josuke laughs )
Well, thank you.
Though is it really
a compliment coming from you?
Koichi: Jeez, Louise,
what could I do
to make yukako think
i’m totally unappealing?
Josuke: Well,
from what i’ve been told,
mama’s boys and gross guys
are usually
major turnoffs for ladies.
( Koichi gasps )
There has to be another way!
If she thinks i’m a mama’s boy,
she’ll hate my mom
and go after her, too!
Okuyasu: Then we’ll
have to go with option b!
You’ll be the gross guy
who doesn’t take baths.
- Koichi: Huh?!
- Josuke: That’s right.
You can’t brush your teeth
or change your underwear.
Okuyasu: Raising some lice
or spiders in your hair
might be a good idea.
Josuke: Wearing sweaty socks
is pretty gross.
Okuyasu: Ooh, and try
farting everywhere.
Josuke: Yeah,
she’ll think you’re foul!
Koichi: Would you guys
quit joking around?!
I’m serious about this!
Okuyasu: I’m being
just as serious as you are!
Now make with
the snot and drool!
( Koichi sighs )
If you’re not up for it,
then your only option
is to become a nobody,
and a nobody
with no prospects at that.
( Koichi groans )
You need to make her
lose all interest.
You and I are gonna tackle
this thing together, okay?
Koichi: Mm-hmm.
( Bells chiming )
Josuke: Holy shit! No way!
Koichi hirose did what?
I don’t believe it!
How disgusting does a guy have
to be to stoop to shoplifting?
Okuyasu: I know,
but koichi said it himself.
What’s worse, the jerk was
even braggin’ all about it.
Who does that?
Josuke: Think that’s bad?
Koichi wouldn’t
be able to keep a promise
if his life depended on it.
I lent that ass-hat money,
and he never paid me back.
Okuyasu: Yeah, well,
I heard he cheats on tests
and steals girls’s underwear.
The guy’s got no future.
He’ll end up ruinin’ his life.
Josuke: I think
it’s time to drop the dude.
Okuyasu: Our friendship is over.
( Wind blows )
( Sighs ) Oh, man.
That chick gives intense
a new definition.
Josuke: Now if koichi
can confirm tomorrow
all the stuff we said today,
she’ll lose interest
faster than a lead block
falling from the sky.
( Koichi sighs ) I know
I should have faith in them,
but I wonder if Josuke
and okuyasu’s plan worked.
( Groans )
The best-case scenario
would be her forgetting
that I exist altogether.
( Sighs )
♪
What is that?
My eyes are closed,
so it must be a dream.
Huh? A woman?
( Gasps ) I-it’s yukako!
( Whimpers )
You have to be kidding me.
She’s even corrupting my dreams?
Can’t she give it a rest
for one night?!
- ( Window rattles )
- ( Gasps )
( Screams )
Yukako: I hate
to do this, koichi,
but I have to tell you
your friends don’t think
very highly of you.
( Koichi grunts )
( Yukako sighs )
No need to worry.
I’m here for you now.
And as such,
it’s my job to educate you
and turn you into the ideal man.
There’s something about you
certain other men
seem to be lacking,
and it’s crucial that you
live up to that potential.
Koichi: J-Josuke,
the plan backfired big time.
♪
( Waves crashing )
( Gasps )
( Yukako humming a tune )
Koichi: Wh-what is this place?
( Gasps )
( Door opens )
( Wheels squeaking )
( Gasping )
( Stomach grumbling )
Yukako: Koichi,
are you hungry now?
Breakfast is almost ready, okay?
Koichi: Yeah, okay.
I have to remember
that she has that hair stand.
There’s no fighting it, so I
have to find an opening and run.
It’s my only hope.
Hey, I have a question.
- Can you answer it?
- Yukako: I’ll try.
Koichi: Well, uh, it’s about
what your hair did last night.
How did you do that?
Yukako: Were you surprised?
Silly me.
I suppose the first time
would startle anyone.
It was around February.
Somebody shot an arrow
into my chest...
Though it’s possible
I was dreaming it.
When I woke up, it was as if
my wound had never existed,
and I had this power.
Koichi: Keicho Nijimura.
So do you know anyone else
with special powers like yours?
- Yukako: No.
- Koichi: That means...
She has no idea
i’m a stand user, too.
Yukako: Have a seat,
if you would.
You are a growing boy, right?
But if you don’t eat properly,
you’ll never become
the outstanding man
I know you can be.
( Koichi thinking ) Crap.
I’ve gotta play along for now.
This looks amazing! Oh, boy!
Yukako: Not so fast, mister!
- We need to talk!
- Koichi: Huh?
Yukako:
You failed your english test.
While I acknowledge there’s more
to a man than his intelligence,
this pitiful score
is unacceptable.
To prepare you
for the next test,
you’re going to study
while you eat breakfast. Okay?
( Koichi gasps )
Yukako: Now for a few questions.
Select the best answer
from among the boxes.
The box you choose
holds your next meal.
Koichi: Wait! Hold on a minute!
Yukako: You’ll do what I say!
And as long
as you’re living in this house,
your life
must constantly revolve
around your betterment! Agreed?
( Koichi gasps )
( Yukako chuckles )
On to the question.
In prince’s lyrics, he uses
the words "funky music,"
and I want the best
Japanese translation.
A, nekkyo no ongaku.
B, genshi no ongaku
c, gensou no ongaku.
Koichi: If I don’t
answer her question,
she’ll get hysterical, but I
don’t have a flipping clue!
I have a hunch it’s a,
but it could easily
be b or c as well.
Screw it! I can do this.
Eh, my guess is...
B.
( Yukako laughs )
( Koichi gasps )
Yukako: Ahh! You got it right!
Congratulations! You won a pair
of freshly hard-boiled eggs!
I’ll peel them for you.
With a pinch of salt, right?
( Koichi sighs )
Yukako: Just so you know,
if you had chosen a,
you would have
had to eat this eraser.
( Koichi yelps )
Yukako: Box c would have
been a bar of soap.
Koichi: Wh-what the hell?!
Yukako: The next item
on the menu
is bacon and eggs.
Best of luck.
Your question, which of these
characters express contrast?
Would it be taisho a,
perhaps taisho b,
or maybe taisho c?
Koichi: She’s not
messing around here.
If I choose the wrong box,
she’ll force me
to eat its contents for sure.
I know you’re stalling for time.
Hurry, or your food
will get cold.
Koichi: Uh, well, maybe it’s...
What do I do now?
She’s playing hardball.
( Yukako grunts )
( Sighs )
( Koichi gasps ) Is it c?
Yukako: Tell me, koichi.
Were you watching my expressions
to decide which box to pick?
( Koichi gasps )
I never thought i’d say this,
but your reputation
for being a conniving,
shoplifting cheater is true!
For your penalty,
you shall consume
the contents of boxes a and b!
A is english vocab corn flakes.
B is asparagus,
a la english dictionary.
You’re gonna learn
with every bite you take!
- ( Koichi whimpers )
- Yukako: Here!
Now open up that mouth,
’cause here comes the knowledge.
What’s wrong?
Eat your food, damn it!
( Koichi whimpering )
I’ve had about enough of this!
You expect me to sit back
and take this crap?
Well, I can’t!
I’m getting the hell outta here!
- ( Yukako grunts )
- ( Koichi yelps )
Yaah! Now what’s happening?!
What’s pulling my scalp?!
It feels like somebody’s hair!
Wait! Does this belong to...
Yukako: Indeed. I implanted
a few hundred strands
of my own hair
into your scalp.
( Koichi groans )
Yukako: I’m well aware
that you’ll probably hate me
for going to these
extreme measures, koichi.
Koichi: Huh?
Yukako: But by the time
you leave this house,
you’ll look in the mirror
and see a brand-new man
staring back at you.
I’m certain
you’ll thank me after that,
and you’ll realize you need
a woman like me in your life.
It’s safe to say
you won’t be able to live
without Yukako Yamagishi.
( Koichi gasps )
Yukako: Oh,
you might as well know,
until you finish every
last morsel on your plates,
I won’t be giving you
any more food.
There’s one more thing.
A famous c.E.O. Vacations here,
but no one will be visiting
until summer.
( Koichi gasps ) Until summer?!
Yukako: Although, it doesn’t
really matter who drops by,
because in the very end,
love is an invincible power.
♪
( Koichi screams )
S-somebody help me!