Singers: ♪ mori, mori, mori, mori
♪ morioh Cho radio
- ♪ morioh Cho radio - deejay: Good morning!
Rise and shine, everyone.
You're listening to morioh radio.
Kai harada here,
keeping you company on this beautiful morning.
The day is shaping up to be a great one,
and I have just what the doctor ordered,
so sit back, relax, and enjoy.
( Song playing )
Anchor: As always, we'll keep you updated as events unfold,
but until then, take a look...
Singer: ♪ as you know, I'm a man of... ♪
( Static crackling )
♪♪
( Static crackles )
( New song playing )
Driver: Well we're back in business.
The reception usually clears up once you're past the tower.
Anyway, is this your first time visiting morioh?
Jotaro: Sure is.
Got anything to share?
Driver: In terms of recommendations? Mm...
Oh! The miso-marinated beef tongue is real good.
Jotaro: Anything suspicious? Strange incidents?
Driver: Sorry, sir, but I'm afraid I don't know much
when it comes to oddball stuff like that.
Um, would you kindly remind me of your destination?
Jotaro: We're going to the front of the station.
Driver: Right. Almost there.
Jotaro: Good freakin' grief.
I swear, this better not be what I think it is.
♪♪
Boy: It happened in April, 1999.
It was my first day of high school,
and I was about to make two very bizarre friends.
I was about to become a high schooler
and wondered what the others'd be like.
In case you were wondering, my name's koichi hirose,
though I guess it's not that important.
Anyway, I was nervously walking myself to class, when...
( Whimpers )
Wha?! But didn't I just--
and I thought all my stuff went flying everywhere.
What the heck's going on?
Jotaro: Sorry. I wasn't paying attention.
( Koichi thinking ) A giant!
He's gotta be over 190 centimeters tall!
Jotaro: Hey, maybe you can help me out.
Here's the thing. I've come here to find the higashikata family.
Koichi: Higashikata? Let's see.
Jotaro: Maybe an address'll jog your memory.
Does jozenji 1-6 ring a bell?
Koichi: "Jotaro kujo."
You can get to jozenji pretty easily
by taking the number three bus.
It won't be long before another one comes around.
Jotaro: Thanks, kid.
Koichi: The first guy that I met was jotaro kujo.
Later on, I found out he was 28 years old
and a marine explorer.
Apparently, academics knew him best
for his outstanding research in the field of ecology.
There's this fierceness about him,
but he also seems really intellectual. Wow.
Boy: Hey!
You another freshman, little man?
Aren't you gonna introduce yourself?
Koichi: Right! Yes, sir!
I'm koichi hirose, a freshman.
Good morning, sir. Nice to meet you.
Boy #2: Yeah, that's more like it, runt.
Koichi: Man, that was a close one.
You don't have to worry about them.
I'm sure they'll find a different bus
and go about their business.
Boy #1: What do you think you're doin', dick-face?!
Boy #2: Who do you think you are?!
- Boy #3: Huh?! - Boy #4: Yeah!
Boy #5: Well, if you really must know,
it seems this little turtle I found
just woke up from hibernation.
But turtles give me the willies.
It takes all my courage to even touch their shells,
so I thought today would be a good day
to finally conquer my fears.
Boy #1: Buddy, does it look like I give a shit?!
Boy #2: Get up, you weirdo!
♪♪
Boy #1: Well, now, you've got some height
for such a pathetic freshman, but here's the deal.
You can dress like a pompous prick if you want to,
but first you have to pay your respects to us. Got it?!
Boy #5: Can you not do that, please?
Reptiles really freak me out. They're all so creepy.
Boy #1: Just who do you think you're smirkin' at, pretty boy?
( Koichi groans )
Boy #5: Forgive me, sir.
I didn't know how things were done.
Boy #1: That's kinda funny,
'cause I've put a lot of guys in the hospital
whose last words were the exact same as yours.
You need to learn some respect, dumb-ass,
unless you wanna end up like this stupid turtle!
Koichi: Man, this guy is heartless.
Boy #1: But, hey, I'm feeling merciful.
Leave your jacket and pants with us,
- and you get to walk away. - Boy #2: Your cash, too!
Boy #5: Right. Sorry for the trouble.
Jotaro: A shame it had to go down this way,
but what did he expect in that get-up?
Though what pisses me off is that he can just sit back
and watch them pulverize a turtle.
Boy #1: I got an idea, pussy.
Why don't you tell us your name?
Boy #5: Right. Class 1-b.
I'm josuke...
Higashikata.
( Both grunt )
Jotaro: Say what? Josuke higashikata?
Boy #2: It says "Jo" and "Jo."
Boy #3: Josuke, huh? Well, if you ask me,
"jojo" has a much better ring to it.
Josuke: Oh, uh, thanks.
That's very kind of you to say.
Boy #1: Shut your trap, and take off the damn jacket.
Or didn't you notice the bus is here?
If you don't hurry it up, I swear to god
I'll chop off that fugly cowlick!
Did you hear what I said? Hurry it up!
Josuke: Sure, but first...
Question.
Could you repeat what you just said about my hair, sir?
- ( Boy #1 gasps ) - ( Both gasp )
Jotaro: A stand?
( Boy #1 screams )
( Boys yell )
Boy #1: My nose! My teeth!
Josuke: Talk shit about my hair,
and you'll see a different side of me,
a side that'll make you feel pain like never before.
So what was that about my hair looking like a motley toupee?
Boy #1: Huh? What are you talkin' about? No one said--
josuke: I know what I heard, damn it!
Koichi: What happened?
That punk went flying through the air.
Jotaro: There's no denying what I just saw. That was a stand.
( Boy #1 grunting )
Koichi: What?
It's like the turtle's cuts were never there.
( Bones popping )
Boy #2: What the hell's going on?!
Your nose and teeth are healing themselves!
Boy #3: Look at that! He's fixed!
Boy #4: Yeah, I guess, but why is his face all weird?
( Boy #1 shuddering )
Boy #2: It looks totally different now!
Boy #1: Huh? What is it?
What happened to my face? Well? What?
Josuke: You've really done it now.
You made me touch something
that I didn't want to lay a finger on.
So how exactly do you plan on making it up to me? Huh?!
( Boys yelling )
Boy #1: Hey, come back here! You can't leave!
What happened to my nose?! Guys, wait!
Jotaro: They were a hassle.
And this guy...
Josuke: Hmm?
- ( Splash ) - Aah! Holy shit!
( Sighs ) Oh, it's just that turtle again.
Koichi: So I was right.
Somehow, the turtle's completely healed.
Jotaro: Josuke higashikata,
you were born in the year 1983,
mother's name, tomoko.
She was 21, attending university in Tokyo.
This town's the only home you've ever known.
But everything changed in 1987
when you came down with a mysterious fever at age four.
For 50 days, you were a knock away from death's door.
Your father's name is--
( thinking ) Good grief. How'd I get mixed up in this?
The name of your father is Joseph joestar.
He's 78 now and the founder of joestar realty.
Koichi: The Joseph joestar?
He's that American real-estate mogul.
Jotaro: Don't worry. The old man's fine,
but one day, I was looking into how to divide his properties.
That's when I discovered you, his son,
living right here in Japan.
Even the old man had no idea,
piece of shit that he is.
The bastard always said his wife was his one and only.
Then I find out he had an affair at the ripe old age of 62,
and the product of it is you.
Sorry. Guess I shouldn't have said that.
My name is jotaro kujo,
which means, since he's my grandfather,
I'm technically your nephew. Bizarre, huh?
Josuke: Nephew? Huh?
Pleasure.
Jotaro: We can talk on the way.
So there you have it.
Eventually, you're gonna find yourself in possession
of a third of the old man's inheritance.
That's the message I came here to tell you.
Hate to lay this on you, but this affair
has turned the joestar family upside down.
Josuke: Uh, upside down? Are you serious?
Jotaro: I am. My grandma, Suzie q,
is the angriest she's ever been in their entire marriage,
and they've been together 61 years.
Josuke: Wha--please forgive me!
This is all my fault!
Jotaro: Hey, there's no need to freak out.
Why are you apologizing in the first place?
Josuke: Well, i-I'd hate to be the cause
of the family falling apart.
Whenever the subject came up,
mom told me she was deeply in love.
Knowing that she had that is enough for me.
Could you tell my dad-- I mean Mr. Joestar--
he doesn't need to concern himself with us? Thank you.
Jotaro: What's with this kid?
I came here ready to be decked on behalf of the old man,
but instead of being angry, he's the one apologizing to me.
- Girl: Look, it's josuke! - Girl #2: Yeah, it is!
- Girl #3: Hey, josuke! - Girl #1: What a coincidence!
Girl #3: Let's go to class together.
Girl #1: Your hair is looking glorious as ever.
Girl #2: It's so great!
Girl #3: You're so different from the other guys at school.
Josuke: That's great, but we're actually in the middle
- of an important chat, so... - Girl #1: Aww, come on!
Girl #2: If you don't hurry, you're gonna be late for school.
- Girl #3: You can talk later. - ( Jotaro growls )
Earth to josuke. We haven't finished our business yet.
- Get the groupies outta here. - ( Girls gasp )
Girl #3: Who the hell's this guy?
Jotaro: Hey, you can cackle like hens
about his hair on your own time.
( Josuke gasps )
Girl #2: This guy has no idea the beast he's just released.
Girl #1: Why'd he talk about his hair that way?
Josuke: Bastard...
Do you wanna repeat what you just said about my hair?
Girl #3: Ooh, this isn't good.
Girl #1: You don't have to tell me.
Girl #2: The one thing that sets josuke off
like nothing else is someone insulting his hair.
Koichi: This is just what happened before.
Jotaro: Hold on a minute, josuke.
I wasn't trying to take a shot at your hair.
Damn. Here he comes.
( Josuke gags )
- ( Girls wail ) - Girl #2: Josuke, no!
Girl #3: He's bleeding!
Jotaro: Do you see it, josuke?
This is called a stand.
It's a physical manifestation of the soul.
Joseph has one of these as well.
Only a stand user can see another stand.
Josuke: You know, it pisses me off
when someone decides to bad-mouth my pride and joy.
It really grinds my gears!
Stand: Dora!
Jotaro: So that's what his stand looks like!
Dora!
Jotaro: This kid's power is unreal.
Josuke: Hah. Don't know if you realized this, nephew,
but you left your chest wide open!
Jotaro: Enough!
Josuke: Where did he--( Gasps )
Girl #3: How'd that happen?
Girl #1: The heck is going on?
Josuke: Why you--when did--
- girl #2: Josuke! - ( Girls wail )
Girl #3: No! Josuke!
Jotaro: Shut your mouths! And get the hell outta here
before your whiny bitching makes me angrier!
Girls: Uh...
Okay.
Girl #1: They must know each other.
Girl #2: He's kinda scary.
Girl #3: Yeah, but in a hot way.
Koichi: Unreal. I don't understand.
What just happened?
I can't wrap my head around any of it.
Jotaro: It's been a while,
ten years to be exact.
I only managed to stop time for half a second.
I doubt we would have killed each other if I hadn't,
but it would have gotten ugly for one of us.
- ( Josuke groaning ) - Jotaro: Here. I got you.
Josuke: No, it's okay. I can manage on my own.
Jotaro: Fair enough.
As I was saying,
there's another reason I came to see you.
Look at this picture.
Do you see it?
Something evil is lurking in this town.
A catastrophic danger is closing in as we speak.
When the old man used his psychic photography
to get a picture of you, this was the result.
We don't know who this guy is,
but if I had to guess, I'd say he's a stand user.
I know this is all new to you,
but I wanted to show you the picture.
Don't let your guard down.
Koichi, if you ever run into him,
get as far away as you can.
Getting the police involved won't help. Just haul ass.
Josuke, if you find yourself face to face with him,
keep your cool, and stay out of it,
or it'll be a repeat of what happened here.
( Koichi gasps ) Our orientation!
Josuke: You're right! It's started!
No, no, no, no, no, no! My mom is gonna kill me
if I show up late for my first day of school!
Hey, I need to get going, but I promise to listen
to whatever you have to say after school, okay?
You're koichi, right? Come on. Let's take off!
Koichi: Huh?
Josuke: Put some pep in your step!
Koichi: Right!
This is josuke higashikata.
He's one of the other bizarre friends I made that year.
One second, he's a wallflower.
The next, he's acting like a crazy person.
He's got some family drama going on.
( Chuckles )
That's one way to make a first impression.
Jotaro: Josuke.
That kid's a strange one,
not to mention his stand.
And given that my hat isn't currently ripped to all hell,
it must be able to destroy objects
and rearrange their structure.
If he'd managed to connect with my face or my skull--
I don't even wanna think about it.
But he could be a potential ally.
He's already a more than capable fighter.
Excluding his fickle personality, that is.
Regardless, I'm really hoping this mess
doesn't have anything to do with josuke.
- ( Engine rumbling ) - Man: Hey, good-lookin'!
Where are you headed? I'll take you where you want.
There's no need to be shy, honey.
I don't bite much.
- Come on. Get in! - ( Old woman coughs )
( Man gasps ) Damn, lady!
You're a total knockout!
Woman: So you're saying you'll go wherever I want, huh?
Man: You had better believe it!
Just say the word, and I'm there!
Woman: In that case, why don't you take
a one-way trip to hell, douche bag?!
Man: Uh...
What the hell?!
( Groaning )
( Bicycle squeaking )
Officer: Hey there, son. You all right?
Man: Help me, officer!
You got here just in time to catch that crazy bitch!
- She assaulted me! - Officer: Sorry, son.
Hate to say it, but you're on your own.
Man: What?!
Officer: That woman is my daughter.
- Man: Huh? - ( Old woman coughing )
Officer: And, in addition to being a public nuisance,
you also referred to my baby girl
as a crazy bitch, so I'd watch myself if I were you.
I'll let you off with a warning, but you're on thin ice. Got it?
( Old woman coughing )
Officer: Oh, dear.
Madame murakami, how are you holding up?
I'll carry this so you can take it easy.
Murakami: Mm.
- ( Bicycle bell rings ) - Woman: Huh?
Officer: Fancy seeing you here, tomoko!
Tomoko: Hey, dad.
Officer: On your way home?
Tomoko: Sure am.
Officer: I'll keep you company.
I'm all done with my shift for the day.
How's josuke doing?
Today is his orientation.
That boy had better not be getting into trouble.
Tomoko: Right. Who knows with that kid.
He looks innocent, but the moron loses it at the drop of a hat.
I wonder where he gets that from.
Officer: All right, settle down.
- Tomoko: But... - Officer: Eh?
Tomoko: Deep in his heart of hearts,
he's an honest-to-goodness sweetie pie.
I'm not too worried about it.
Officer: That's the spirit.
How do you feel about having a big celebration tonight?
Tomoko: Sounds good. That was actually my plan.
I doubt he'll come straight home, though.
That child of mine likes his detours.
Officer: That, he does.
Woman: Hey, I wanna stop by kameyu. Can we?
Man: Are you crazy?
I just bought you an expensive bag. Remember?
Woman: Please, baby! I want to look at clothes today!
- Man: Watch it, dumb-ass! - ( Woman groans )
Man: Pay attention to where you're walking, fool!
Woman: That freak show gave me the creeps.
Man: What kinda moron slams into someone
- and doesn't apologize? - Woman: Forget him.
Let's just get outta here, babe.
Man: Yeah, yeah. You're still angling for kameyu, aren't--
( woman gasps )
Man: Huh?
( Shuddering )
Jotaro: Anjuro katagiri, a.K.A. Angelo.
He was born in morioh in 1964 and has an IQ of 160.
He was sent to juvie for robbery and rape
when he was only 12 years old.
That was the beginning of his depravity.
He earned a reputation for being the most violent,
abominable criminal to ever walk on Japanese soil.
Most of his youth was spent in jail.
By the time he turned 34,
he'd already spent 20 years in the slammer.
The final crime he ever committed was so reprehensible,
it'd make a sewer rat puke.
He was eventually arrested
and then executed.
But unfortunately for all involved,
the execution didn't stick.
( Angelo grunts )
Jotaro: Angelo escaped from custody shortly after,
and he most likely became a stand user
right before his execution.
I'm not sure why, but he's now hiding
in the shadows of this quiet town,
and I have no idea where.
( Students chattering )
Josuke: Oh, hey, koichi. You headed home?
Koichi: Uh, yeah. Guess so.
Josuke: So, we're classmates.
Koichi: Yeah, what a coincidence.
Josuke: Well, I'll catch you tomorrow.
Have a good evening.
Koichi: Hey, uh, josuke, can you wait a moment?
Josuke: Huh?
I see. You want to hear
what that jotaro guy has to say, don't you?
Koichi: I can't get it out of my mind.
It's happening in our backyard.
Josuke: Admirable of you to care, but I'll pass.
Koichi: But why?
Josuke: Mm, not gonna lie.
I was curious about the whole thing at first,
but when I thought about it, I figured it'd be best
to keep clear of this whole love-child fiasco.
Koichi: Huh? How come?
Josuke: Well, things are fine the way they are,
so, in my opinion, why try to fix what ain't broke?
Koichi: Yeah, I get it.
- ( Sirens blaring ) - Eh?
What's going on?
Josuke: Maybe it's some kind of accident.
You wanna go and check it out?
Koichi: Mm-hmm.
♪♪
( Overlapping chatter )
Officer: This area is not safe. You need to get back right now!
Koichi: It's absolute chaos over here.
Woman: Some man went to Rob that convenience store,
and he's taken the female employee hostage. ( Laughs )
- Josuke: Huh? - ( Koichi gasps )
Man: Look! He's coming out!
♪♪
Officer: Freeze! Put down the knife!
( Robber chuckles )
Officer #2: Just let the girl go!
Robber: Shut up, and get the hell back, all of you!
Koichi: Hey, I recognize that lady.
She's been my cashier a couple of times.
Josuke: Judging by his eyes, if he actually snaps,
he'll kill her without any hesitation.
Robber: Last chance! Get outta my way!
I'm taking the car and leaving!
Koichi: This isn't good.
We have to get outta here before things get worse!
Josuke: Yeah, you're probably right. Excuse me, sir...
Robber: You over there, with the dumb-shit hairdo!
I told your ass to get away from the car!
Or do you want me to kill you?!
Koichi: I have a bad feeling...
This is gonna get ugly.
Josuke: Huh?
Koichi: Yep. I knew it.
Oh, no! Here it comes!
Why in the world did it have to happen right here, right now?!
Especially after Mr. Jotaro warned him!
Officer #1: Who the devil is that?
Officer #: Stand down, and back away!
( Robber snarls )
Josuke: What the hell did you just say about my hair?
Robber: I don't know who you think you are,
but if you don't start walking, I'm gonna gut her like a fish!
- ( Woman screams ) - Officer #2: Get back, idiot!
Officer #1: If that guy snaps, you're a dead man!
Robber: That goes for you, too! Now get away!
I've had all I'm gonna take! You're all driving me crazy!
I'm gonna freakin' do it! I'm gonna slaughter this bitch!
( Yells )
Josuke: Oh, is that a fact?
Shining diamond: Dora!
Koichi: What the--those two have a hole through their bodies!
Josuke: I didn't piss you off, did I?
Because I should be the one who's ticked off.
( Robber shuddering )
Woman: But how? There's not a Mark on me.
Koichi: She's back to normal, like before.
( Robber screams )
My knife's inside my body!
How did my knife get inside?!
W-what did you do?
Josuke: I'd suggest finding a surgeon to remove that
in the prison hospital.
( Robber gasping )
Officer #1: Quickly, let's cuff this guy.
Officer #2: What's going on around here?
Koichi: Josuke!
Josuke: What's up, koichi?
Koichi: Are you okay? That was...
( Robber gagging )
Officer #1: Wh-what the hell is happening?
( Josuke gasps )
Stand: Well, what a surprise.
It appears another annoying stand user has joined the fray.
And I was having so much fun
using that meat puppet for my armed robbery,
but of course you had to get in my way.
Josuke: Hang on. He's from the picture!
Koichi: Huh?
Stand: So you know, I'm gonna keep a close eye on you.
Wherever you are, whatever you do,
I'll be nearby watching and waiting.
Josuke: What did you say, water boy?!
- Koichi: Josuke! - Josuke: Eh?
Officer #3: What the hell were you thinking, idiot?!
Officer #2: You could have been killed!
Josuke: Wait a minute!
- ( Koichi chuckles ) - Josuke: Get off!
Koichi: Mr. Jotaro was telling the truth all along.
Robber: Guys, I'm begging you!
Koichi: Something's happening in this town.
It's almost as if I can feel it in the air.
Whatever found its way into morioh,
it's--it's monstrous.
♪♪
( Telephone rings )
Tomoko: Hey, josuke, can you get the phone?!
- ( Ring ) - What are you doing, josuke?
- Answer the damn phone! - Josuke: Yeah, yeah.
Don't have a cow. I'm getting it.
( Ring )
Hello.
Jotaro: It's jotaro.
Josuke: Oh, hi.
Jotaro: Our conversation yesterday was too brief.
We need to talk about the guy hiding in this town.
Josuke: Um, I wanted to talk about that, too.
We should meet. You staying somewhere in town?
Jotaro: I'm at the morioh grand hotel for now.
What's on your mind?
Josuke: Well, to be honest...
Tomoko: Damn it. This really pisses me off.
Where the hell did I put that damn shovel?
Angelo: What a little brat.
He's living the high life with his perfect little family.
He's even got a hot, young mom,
not that he could appreciate it.
That kid's such a lucky bastard.
Josuke higashikata,
you'd better not get too cocky, you little pissant,
'cause I'm gonna stomp your soul and your precious little life.
I'm gonna get to have my fun after all.