Josuke: Just hang
in there, Rohan.
I’m not gonna let you die!
♪
damn. I guess
it picked up on my scent.
If those freaky-ass phalanges
catch up to me,
I can kiss my body’s
nutrients goodbye!
It can’t travel faster
than 60 kilometers per hour.
lucky for me,
this bike can easily outpace it.
Problem is I have no clue
how to find the user.
That foot fetish dick
could be anywhere.
All right, calm down.
Think about this logically.
Why would he lay a trap inside
a tunnel wall of all places?
You’d think ambushing us
from the side of the road
would be easier.
Second, there has to be
more to this nutrient feeding
than meets the eye,
which means there’s
some significance to the tunnel.
I’ve got no choice
but to investigate.
I need to dig up some info
on that futatsumori tunnel.
and I know
just the man for the job!
I’ll get koichi and reverb
to help me track down the user!
( Baby crying )
Woman: What’s got you all
riled up, sweetie? It’s okay.
Josuke: Huh? ( Chuckles )
Man: Eh? ( Gasps )
josuke: Hah!
Looks like I gave him the slip.
Now where’s my card?
There you are.
Huh?
You’ve gotta be shitting me!
How’d it just appear
out of thin air?
i was going
80 kilometers per hour!
Its top speed is only 60!
It should have gotten here
two minutes after I did.
That’s simple math.
Though, being a stand and all,
I guess it can pop in
whenever it wants.
After it figures out
your rough location,
it appears and uses scent
to move in for the kill.
I gotta get out of here,
and fast!
( Scoffs ) 60 kilometers.
- ( Gasps )
- ( Baby crying )
Josuke: Wait! What the--
shit! It’s a baby carriage!
woman: Why are you
in such a foul mood, love?
( Screams )
Josuke: If I decelerate,
i’m a dead man,
and Rohan, too!
Slowing down isn’t an option.
I’m just gonna
have to gun it hard!
( Woman gasps )
( Baby crying )
josuke: All right,
shining diamond, do your thing!
( Shining diamond yells )
Baby: Eh?
Josuke: And fix!
Nice!
( Woman gasps )
( Baby giggles )
♪
Josuke: At this rate, i’ll never
get a chance to call koichi.
♪
♪ shining justice
( singing in Japanese )
♪ Brand-new bed town
♪ Let the voice of love
take you higher ♪
- ♪ higher, higher
- ( Singing in Japanese )
♪ 1999, bizarre summer
( singing in Japanese )
♪ Great days
man over phone: All right,
yoshioka, in exactly one minute,
you’re going to receive
an extremely important call.
This deal’s worth a billion yen,
so failure isn’t an option.
Don’t disappoint me!
Yoshioka: Right! Got you, boss!
rest assured,
I won’t let you down!
Josuke: What do you know?
a cell phone’s
exactly what I needed,
and it showed up just
in the Nick of time. Lucky me!
Yoshioka: You can consider
that deal made, sir!
Josuke: I must have
a guardian angel!
Yoshioka: Anyone there?
( Gasps ) Damn it!
There goes a billion yen!
Josuke: Shit!
Damn thing must have broken
when I grabbed it!
So much for a guardian angel.
Woman: Fine! If you hate me
so much, just hang up!
Man: What?! How could you
say that, minayo?
( Thinking ) It’s now or never.
Time to propose.
Minayo, I love you
more than anything!
Will you ma--( Shrieks )
Josuke: I take it back.
I guess it is my lucky day.
Minayo: Will I what, Akira?
Josuke: Man, do I have
some great timing or what?
( Koichi grunting )
( Telephone ringing )
Koichi: Hello. Hirose residence.
- Josuke: Koichi!
- Koichi: Eh?
♪
Josuke: So that’s the deal.
If I don’t find the user,
i’m as good as dead.
I get the feeling he has
an obsession with the tunnel.
It’s like he has a grudge
against it or something.
Any info on incidents
involving that tunnel?
( Koichi gasps ) There is.
It was published in the paper
two days ago.
I actually remember seeing
something about this
on the news.
Some careless biker guy
was driving real drunk
and ended up crashing
into the tunnel’s entrance.
According to this,
he’s unconscious
and covered head to toe
in bruises.
He’s in intensive care
at budogaoka hospital now.
Josuke: Oh, man. Sounds like
the stand got him, too.
Is there anything else?
Koichi: Give me a sec.
I remember the news
reporting there was blood
all over the road.
You said the stand feeds
by absorbing
people’s nutrients, right?
The wounds are
totally different.
maybe the rider
from the motorcycle accident
actually became the stand user.
Josuke: If he’s right,
this guy is leeching nutrients
from others to heal himself.
( Gasps ) Oh, shit!
It’s the ocean!
Damn it! I just can’t
catch a break today!
Gotta think fast,
or that water’s
gonna mean some major shrinkage!
( Gasps ) I can turn there!
Just have to keep it
over 60 kilometers an hour.
Koichi: Hello? Josuke?
what’s wrong?
Josuke: Koichi, whatever you do,
stay on the line! Understand?
All right, this is it!
( Tires squealing )
oh, no!
I’m totally about to bite it!
No! If anyone
can make this turn,
it’s josuke higashikata.
here I go!
( Feet thumping )
( Yells )
did you see that,
you fungal-footed asshole?!
Cleared that corner
without a single scratch.
( Gasps ) What the actual hell?!
I’m charging straight
for the port of morioh!
Let’s go. Shining diamond!
( Shining diamond yells )
( Josuke yells )
( Feet thumping )
josuke: Now fix
that broken wall! Quick!
( Feet sniffing )
Josuke: That was a close one.
It had me right
in its crosshairs,
but now that the wall’s up,
it’s been totally blinded.
I guess that means
this thing finds its prey
like a mosquito
sniffs out its next meal.
There’s no rhyme or reason
to any of its attacks.
its only objective
is to drain me of my nutrients.
That theory about this being
the drunk dude from the accident
is starting to make sense.
It’s all coming together.
- Koichi: Josuke!
- ( Josuke gasps )
Koichi, I worked it all out!
The guy from the accident
has to be the user.
You have to find out
what his name is.
Koichi: Got it.
Josuke: Damn it. This is
such a shitty situation.
i have no idea
how i’m gonna get out of this.
( Feet sniffing )
Yoshihiro: Now where did
that meddlesome
little shit, josuke, go?
( Laughs )
I have to admit,
when you selected
that half-dead biker punk
as your next pincushion,
it caught me off guard.
I thought you were crazy,
but I see now how wrong I was.
You’re absolutely astonishing!
Who would have thought that kid
would bring forth
highway go go?
stands are truly
a manifestation of the soul.
The hungrier they are,
the better!
the insatiable hunger
to heal oneself is unstoppable,
especially when it
comes to stands!
But, oh, how nice
it would have been
to witness josuke bite the dust.
( Laughs )
♪
( Josuke gasps )
What do I do? Come on.
( Gasps )
( Highway go go sniffing )
Josuke: A ditch!
finding a ditch
that emptied into the ocean
was a lucky break,
but I still have no way
to beat this thing,
and it’s closing in on me.
how the hell am I
supposed to make my escape?
So which way? Let’s see.
The ocean’s behind me,
and I need to steer way clear
of the water,
so going right
isn’t really an option,
and i’m pretty sure
I came from the left.
( Feet thumping )
( Gasps ) Which way do I go now?
i feel like
the ocean’s to the left,
but what if it’s
actually to the right?
There’s also the middle
to think about.
( Tailpipe popping )
( Gasps ) What’s happening?
I’m gunning it,
but the stupid bike
is still slowing down.
C-could it be busted?
( Shining diamond grunts )
Josuke: This doesn’t
make any sense!
The engine’s working just fine!
so why won’t
the damn thing accelerate?
I’m grinding to a halt!
- ( Feet thumping )
- Crap. It’s coming!
( Gasps )
Wait a sec.
Shining diamond: Dora!
Josuke: Am I out of gas?
Man, you had me freaking out
for a second there,
but i’m just in need
of a little refill.
There’s no need to sweat
over something so minor.
i was starting to worry
I had a major wreck on my hands
that even shining diamond
couldn’t fix.
Nope, not gonna stress.
I can get out of this situation,
easy-peasy.
I was freaking out
over nothing.
( Shining diamond yelling )
Josuke: A little tweak here...
And a little modification there.
It teleports, though, so I guess
I can’t get too comfortable.
At least I have fuel.
But if i’m being honest
with myself, i’m lost,
which really sucks.
Where the hell am I,
and how do I get
to that freakin’ hospital?
koichi: Excuse me.
I’m in a bit of a pickle here.
I need to know
how to find the guy
from the drunk-driving accident
in futatsumori tunnel,
and I need to know right now.
- What’s his room number?
- ( Nurse slurps )
Koichi: It’s an emergency!
Nurse: Get off my case, kid,
and I suggest
you read that sign over there.
Koichi: Huh?
Nurse: If you need
your eyes examined,
then you can come back
tomorrow morning at 9:30.
Koichi: You don’t understand.
I’m not here for a visit!
there’s a reason
I need to know his name!
- ( Nurse groans )
- Koichi: I’m serious!
I need to know!
Nurse: Maybe you didn’t hear me.
I asked you to go home.
Pesky kids like you always
makes life hard for us adults,
and it really gets
under my skin.
Also, you’re pretty shrimpy
for someone
who belongs to a biker gang.
Do your feet even
reach the ground?
( Koichi sighs )
Nurse: Hmph.
Koichi: Do it, act three.
Reverb: Okay, master!
Let’s kill da ho!
Beeetch!
( Glass rattling )
Nurse: Huh?
( Gasps ) Oh, no!
Thank goodness.
That would have been a disaster.
These medications run us
50,000 yen a bottle.
Huh? They’re so heavy!
What the hell?!
They’re gonna fall! ( Groans )
hey, you,
don’t just stand there!
Pitch in, and hold me up!
Koichi: Uh...
Sorry about that, Ms. Adult.
Was that, "hey, you," supposed
to be directed toward me?
nurse: Of course it was!
You’re the only here besides me!
I can’t hold this much longer!
Koichi: That sounds
like a personal problem.
And you told me to go home,
so I shouldn’t get involved,
you know?
Besides, since i’m so shrimpy,
- I probably couldn’t reach it.
- ( Nurse groans )
Koichi: Though I do
have a question for you.
is your superior going
to reprimand you if those break?
I would do just about anything
to keep that from happening.
Nurse: Fine! Have it your way!
I’ll tell you his room number!
Yuya fungami is in room 525.
Just take that elevator
up to the fifth floor,
and you’re there!
You can’t miss it!
- ( Glass shatters )
- ( Both gasp )
♪
Koichi: Josuke!
Josuke: Koichi.
Did you find out where he is?
Koichi: You need to head
to the fifth floor!
His name’s yuya fungami,
in room 525!
josuke: Thanks!
You’re the best, koichi!
( Feet thumping )
Koichi: The stand!
Take the elevator!
Put an end to this, josuke!
( Josuke groans )
( Feet pattering )
Damn, it’s persistent.
- ( Feet sniffing )
- Josuke: Great.
Bastard’s slipping his way in!
it’s koichi!
He’s using reverb act three!
I don’t know what any of us
would do without you.
Thanks for having
my back, koichi.
Koichi: Got ’em.
But three freeze
can only focus its attack
one at a time.
The rest of those things
are going after josuke.
♪
There it is! Room 525!
Can’t believe
I finally made it.
( Gasps )
The vent!
( Yells )
( Shining diamond yells )
( Josuke grunting )
Bastard!
I won’t let you stop me
when i’m so close.
I swear i’m gonna kick
your ass into oblivion,
even if it kills me!
( Groans )
Women: Hmm?
Josuke: There you are.
I hope you’re ready, asshole,
’cause when I make it
to that bed,
i’m gonna beat you
within an inch of your...
Woman: Who the hell does
this douche bag think he is?
Woman #2: How dare you
waltz into this room
without permission?!
Woman #3: This is
yu’s room, idiot!
Yuya: Leave that loser alone.
Women: Huh?
Yuya: You don’t
look so hot, pal.
I thought it had been a while
since that first guy
in the tunnel
gave me his nutrients,
but now I know
what was holding up my meal.
- ( Josuke panting )
- Yuya: So you’re the second sap
i’ve been chasing around, huh?
Making it this far
is commendable.
I’m kinda shocked, actually.
Woman #2: Wait a minute. You
know who this guy is, yu-baby?
- Yuya: Huh?
- ( Josuke groans )
( Panting )
yuya: Not at all.
I’ve never seen the guy before.
Couldn’t care less who he is.
( Josuke groans )
Yuya: Nice goin’, highway go go.
that’s just
what the doctor ordered.
Now if I can just get ahold
of a few more suckers
like this dude,
i’ll be able to make
a full recovery in no time.
Woman #1: Get up!
Woman #2: Didn’t you
hear her, buster?
Get your ass up,
and get out of here!
Yuya: The question is, did you
hear me?! Leave him alone!
Stop wasting your time
with that guy,
and give me some
of that sweet, sweet lovin’.
You didn’t forget about
li’l old hurt me, did you?
i need to take
the piss of a lifetime,
and i’m not sure how
much longer I can hold it in.
Woman #3: Ooh! Looks like it’s
time for me to get to work!
Woman #2: What do you
think you’re doing?
We all agreed to take turns!
It’s my turn to do it!
Woman #1: Hey, I haven’t
gotten to do it yet!
Yuya: It doesn’t matter
who does it, ladies.
Just bring out that piss bottle,
and give me a hand.
- Woman #2: Okay!
- ( Woman #1 groans )
Then i’ll be over here.
Woman #3: Eh?
- Yuya: Hey, akemi.
- Akemi: Hmm?
Yuya: The peach you’re holding
has gone bad,
so use another one, ’kay, babe?
Akemi: Sure, but how did
you know it was rotten?
Yuya: What do you mean? I can
smell that thing over here.
Any idiot could tell
it was rotten.
Akemi: You smelled it
from there?
Yuya: You know,
you have a point.
My sense of smell must
have gotten better lately.
Akemi: Hey, you’re right.
- It’s rotten.
- ( Yuya chuckles )
( Sniffs )
If my nose is correct,
one of you beauties
is on your period.
I’m right, aren’t I? Who is it?
- Woman #2: Um...
- ( Yuya laughs )
- So it’s you, yoshie!
- ( Yoshie squeals )
yuya: I hit the nail
on the head. And what’s this?
someone in here
is getting really pissed off.
( Sniffs ) When agitated,
the body produces adrenaline,
and one of you girls
has discharged
quite the pungent secretion.
Are you the grumpy gertrude,
reiko, dear?
Reiko: No, it’s not me.
I’m as happy as a clam, baby.
Yoshie: We’re all just happy
that you’re feeling like
your old self again, snuggums!
Akemi: Yeah, we’ve all been
waiting for this moment.
we couldn’t be mad
if we wanted to right now.
Yuya: Now, now, honeys,
tell the truth. ( Sniffs )
Somebody in this room
is downright furious.
I can smell it
loud and clear!
( Women gasp )
Yuya: You better not be fibbing.
One of you is about to pop,
so tell me who it is.
Josuke: It’s me.
Yuya: Eh? Huh?
Josuke: That full-bodied odor
you’re whiffing
is courtesy
of yours truly, you dick!
Yuya: That’s bullshit!
your body should be
a nutritional wasteland by now!
How in the hell
are you standing?
Josuke: It’s simple.
( Yuya gasps )
You were suckin’ down my I.V.
Like a malnourished vampire!
Josuke: Calm down.
It was just a taste.
Even so, it was enough
to perk me up a bit.
( Groaning )
Rohan...
You’re holding him
captive in the tunnel,
but that’s about to end.
( Yuya laughs )
You imbecilic numb-nut!
it’s like
you’ve totally forgotten
that highway go go
has your scent!
Shining diamond: Dora!
( Yuya screams )
Women: Yu, baby!
Josuke: I don’t wanna hear
a peep out of you three!
You can call me
josuke higashikata,
and my stand is known
as shining diamond.
i’m limited
to close-range attacks,
but I can assure you
my punching speed
is a lot faster than 60 k.M.H.
I’ve never measured,
but if i’m close enough,
i’m sure I can get
to about 300 k.M.H.
Yuya: You just
stay away from me!
I know by now you’ve heard
that my back
has been broken to pieces!
My arms and legs
are fractured, too!
I can’t even roll over
to scratch my ass!
Are you really gonna slap around
a feeble, bedridden
hospital patient?
- ( Josuke growls )
- ( Yuya chuckles )
All right, I admit it.
i was a jerk.
but if you let me go,
i’ll free the guy in the tunnel.
I think he’s still alive,
though it certainly wouldn’t
hurt to give him some nutrients.
- So do we have a deal or what?
- ( Josuke growls )
Yuya: Oh, come on, man.
You wouldn’t beat up
a poor invalid, would you?
I know you’re not that cowardly!
If you did, you couldn’t
call yourself a man!
women: Yeah!
So back off, you coward!
josuke: Damn.
Guess you got a point.
Beating the shit out
of an injured victim
would leave a real bad taste
in my mouth,
and it definitely
wouldn’t be manly.
It’s not right, you know?
Yuya: That’s what i’m saying!
Kicking the ass
of a tool like me
will haunt
your conscience forever.
Josuke: To prevent
that nightmare,
i’ve taken the Liberty
of fixing you up.
Yuya: Hmm? ( Gasps )
Josuke: Well, look at that.
You can move.
congrats.
You’re completely healed.
Yuya: Yeah. I’m totally fine.
Josuke: Yup, and since you’ve
gotten a clean bill of health
from shining diamond,
when I pound your ass
into the ground,
I can avoid looking
like a coward, right?
Yuya: Huh? ( Gasps )
( Screams )
( Shining diamond yelling )
Narrator: Yuya fungami’s
hospital stay, extended.
"If you so much as think
"about healing yourself
with highway go go,
i’ll just rearrange
your face all over again,"
insisted josuke.
( Yuya screams )
( Josuke sniffs )
( Sighs )
Man, I feel so invigorated.
I feel like it’s the early hours
of new year’s day
and I just put on a fresh pair
of my favorite underwear.
Women: Yu, baby!
narrator: However,
being nursed back to health
by adoring fangirls
isn’t too shabby either.
As for Rohan...
( Rohan groans )
Oh, it’s you. Guess you won.
Josuke: So, uh,
look, Rohan-sensei.
here’s the thing.
I know we’re not friends, but--
Rohan: Why the hell
did you heal me?
Josuke: Eh? Huh?
Rohan: You’re such a moron.
I would have preferred
wasting away
than have the likes
of you save my life.
- ( Josuke growls )
- Rohan: I told you to run away,
but, as always, you had to step
right into the enemy’s trap.
How do you function?
Josuke: Wha--
Rohan: By the way,
you and I are even now.
Narrator: And just when it
seemed Rohan had come around...
On a different note,
koichi hirose
decided to go
on a walk with his dog.
♪
( Shinobu humming a tune )
Huh?
Eh?
Ohh. It’s a British shorthair.
Where did you come from,
you little sweetie?
♪
♪ Anytime I need
to see your face ♪
♪ I just close my eyes,
and I am taken to a place ♪
♪ where your crystal mind
and magenta feelings ♪
♪ take up shelter
in the base of my spine ♪
♪ sweet like
a chica cherry cola ♪
♪ I don’t need
to try to explain ♪
♪ I just hold on tight,
and if it happens again ♪
♪ I may move so slightly
to the arms ♪
♪ and the lips and the face
of the human cannonball ♪
♪ that I need to, I want to
♪ come stand
a little bit closer ♪
♪ breathe in,
and get a bit higher ♪
♪ you’ll never know what hit you
when I get to you ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪