♪
( Shigechi gasping )
Kira: This is deadly queen.
i bestowed it
with the moniker myself.
Hmm. I’m only telling you
because you’re going to die.
After you bite the dust,
i’ll be able to sleep soundly.
Shigechi: Hey, didn’t I warn you
not to make a move against me?
You’re about to learn
that I mean business!
Deadly queen: Shibo!
Kira: Well, now,
color me surprised.
i crushed
several of these vermin,
yet you remain
completely unscathed.
Shigechi: This is
your last chance, pal.
Move again, and i’ll slice
whatever that big artery is
in your neck.
Oh, yeah, now I remember.
It’s called the carotid artery.
You move a muscle,
and i’ll have my invincible
harvest hack it to pieces!
Judging by the look
of that stand of yours,
it packs a wallop
if you’re up close,
but it’s really shitty
when it comes down
to long-range fighting.
If I had to guess,
i’d say it’s got a range
of one, maybe two meters.
So go ahead, and make your move,
if you’re ready to die,
that is. ( Chuckles )
Kira: Fascinating.
From the looks of things,
it seems each user is endowed
with a unique ability. Hmm.
"Stand." I believe
that’s the term you used.
i should tell you,
as far as special abilities go,
deadly queen has one
that puts others to shame.
shigechi: Hmm?
What’s that in its hand?
Grab it, harvest!
That’s weird.
It’s just a normal 100 yen coin.
What the heck were you
planning to do with this?
kira: Simple.
I was going to reveal
what makes deadly queen such
a unique and terrifying stand.
there’s no point
in keeping its power secret
when you’re already
as good as dead.
deadly queen
has an astonishing power.
Any object that it touches
becomes an explosive
that rips its target asunder.
- ( Shigechi gasps )
- Kira: That’s right. Heh heh.
Even something as simple
as a 100 yen coin.
( Shigechi gasps )
Quick, harvest!
You have to let go
of the coin right now!
( Screams )
Kira: Hmm.
That didn’t take long.
now a night
of glorious sleep awaits.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
( School bell tolling )
Girl: Have you heard
about the beauty clinic
that helps you
find your true love?
Girl #2: Seriously?
don’t tell me
you actually believe that.
Girl #1: It worked
for this other girl.
- ( Shigechi grunting )
- ( Kira gasps )
seems one blast
wasn’t enough to finish you.
( Shigechi gasps )
What the hell?
What’d he do to me?
Wait a second. My face is...
( Squish )
( Gasping )
( Shrieks )
What happened to me?!
kira: I told you.
Deadly queen has the ability
to transform anything
it touches into a bomb.
That’s what it was doing
when you asked
about this 100 yen coin.
I press the detonator
whenever the urge hits me,
and once it’s triggered,
my victim
is blown to smithereens
from the inside out.
Though, in your case, shigechi,
it appears the blast partially
imploded your malformed face,
leaving behind
a stomach-churning cocktail
of facial fascia
and cerebral tissue.
Before I deliver the blow
that ends your wretched life,
there’s something of great
importance I must ask you.
Earlier, you referred
to this power as a stand.
Do the others,
josuke and okuyasu,
also wield
the power of the stand?
Shigechi: I don’t
wanna die here.
- Somebody help me, please.
- Kira: Oh, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Your death is a necessity
at this point.
Now that you know my secret,
I can’t let you live.
It’s nothing personal, but I
can’t allow a single living soul
to know the true nature
of yoshikage Kira.
Though, I must admit
I find myself fascinated
by these stand users.
I could figure this out
on my own, but i’d rather use
the fleeting resource
that lies before me.
Josuke, okuyasu,
who are the others
besides them?
how many users
are residing in this town?
- ( Shigechi gasping )
- What are their powers?
Shigechi: Don’t know.
Just let me go, please.
Kira: Come now.
I’m sure you know more
than you’re letting on,
and if you refuse to tell me,
your parents will pay for it
with their lives.
Shigechi: What?
No, you can’t.
I won’t let you hurt
my mommy and daddy!
Kira: Well, I won’t have to
if you hurry up and give me
the answers i’m looking for.
Now quit your stalling.
I need to slip away
before anyone sees me.
Just the names will do.
hop to it, boy.
Shigechi: Hang on.
Everyone says there was
a murderer in this town,
and they’re all
trying to track him down
before he kills again.
It’s all making sense now.
The killer they were
talking about is you!
You messed-up son of a bitch!
You killed reimi sugimoto, too!
kira: What?!
How do you know that girl?
( Gasps ) The little shit
can still use his stand?
This isn’t good.
Deadly queen!
♪
Kira: Eh...
That brat.
I was so close to killing him.
( Shigechi groans )
i managed
to give him the slip.
Now I just have
to get to josuke.
Once I make it there,
he can use
his shining diamond to fix me.
There’s no way i’m gonna
sit back and die like this.
No matter what, i’ll protect
my mommy and my daddy.
i promise,
i’ll fight to keep them safe
from this hand-hoarding monster!
That horrible creep
is rotten to the core,
and i’d rather die
than let him live
in the same town
as my mommy and daddy!
( Gasping )
I have to find josuke.
( Coughs )
If he heals me, I can save ’em.
( Groans )
Girl: Sorry about that.
Girl #2: Hey, kid,
you’re not hurt, are you?
Shigechi: I have to find him.
Girl #2: Gee, I wonder what’s
the matter with the little guy.
Girl #1: I don’t know, but he
looks like a middle schooler.
girl #2: Oh, no.
Something’s wrong with him.
let’s see
if we can find a teacher.
girl #1: No, we should
leave him be. He’s kinda weird.
Girl #3: Come on.
Shigechi: J-josuke!
( Gasping )
J-josuke! ( Laughs )
( Gasps )
♪
Kira: I recall
you said something
about people looking for me.
does that mean
there’s someone else here
who knows the truth
about reimi sugimoto’s murder?
Even if there is,
they won’t be able
to track me down.
The fact remains, no one knows
yoshikage kira’s true colors.
It’s a secret you’ll
have to carry with you
all the way to the grave.
( Shigechi panting ) No.
I’m gonna protect
mommy and daddy.
Kira: Sorry, but deadly queen
has already left its Mark
on the doorknob.
( Shigechi gasping )
Josuk--
josuke: Eh? Hmm?
Kira: Behold the genius
of my deadly queen.
( Birds chirping )
All evidence of my true self
has been destroyed.
Josuke: Hey, did you hear
someone call my name just now?
Okuyasu: Yeah, most definitely.
( Gasps ) Josuke,
you seein’ what i’m seein’?!
Josuke: Eh?
Harvest: I got it.
( Yelps )
( Both gasp )
Josuke: No! Shigechi?!
Okuyasu: Shigechi!
Hey, something’s
not right, josuke.
Harvest was limping around
and bleeding before it vanished,
but that’s not how a stand
usually disappears.
and why the heck would
only one of ’em come to see us?
( Josuke gasps )
Josuke: Let’s head over
to the middle school.
We have to find
shigechi right now.
♪
Kira: Hmm?
What’s this?
Where could I have
possibly lost my button?
Well, it can’t be helped.
I just have to visit my tailor
and hope he carries
the same kind.
♪
( Arnold howling )
( Reimi gasps )
( Shigechi screams )
( Screaming )
Reimi: It can’t be. Not again.
that foul demon,
he’s taken another life.
another victim
screams across the skies.
Why does this keep happening?!
( Shigechi screaming )
( Josuke gasping )
- shigechi.
- ( Okuyasu gasps )
♪
reimi:
There’s no doubt about it.
- This boy has passed.
- ( All gasp )
Shigekiyo must have had
a run-in with the killer,
one that cost him his life.
The whole thing is sickening.
I know what you
must be thinking.
How did they meet,
and how was he murdered?
But I have no idea.
I’m positive it was his doing.
I’d recognize the handiwork
of that murderer anywhere.
Trust me.
Josuke: We just
looked for shigechi,
but couldn’t
find him anywhere.
i still don’t get
how this could have happened.
We only let him out of our sight
for five minutes.
His books and school supplies
are in the same place
he left them,
and his parents have filed
a missing-person report,
though I doubt anything useful
will turn up at this point.
I have to wonder...
koichi: Wait.
What are you saying, josuke?
You don’t think a stand user
did this, do you?
( Both grunt )
josuke: You guys
couldn’t possibly know this,
but shigechi’s stand
harvest was--
well, in a word, the thing
was damn near invincible,
so what the hell?
This guy killed shigechi
in five minutes.
Then he hid his body off campus
without anyone noticing.
joseph: Well,
there you have it, jotaro.
It’s pretty obvious
that we’re dealing
with a murderous stand user.
We can’t just sit by
and watch like spectators.
Jotaro: Hey, josuke, you said
you found a button, right?
Josuke: Oh, yeah.
Harvest brought it to me
before falling to pieces.
Here you go.
jotaro: This is
shigechi’s dying message.
It’s very likely harvest
pulled it off the murderer.
If so, we’ve been given
an important clue.
( Josuke gasps )
Jotaro: I’d like to investigate
this thing further.
Mind if I keep it?
Josuke: Be my guest,
but how much information
can you really get from
some run-of-the-mill button?
Jotaro: More than you
would think.
we might find
the brand of the clothes
or even the manufacturer.
Koichi: Good idea.
Okuyasu: Hey, if we’re done
with this little meeting,
- I think i’m gonna go home.
- ( Scattered sighs )
Okuyasu: Talking about all this
is putting me in a weird mood.
I’m really pissed.
Come on, dad. Let’s go.
Koichi: What’s up with him?
This isn’t like him at all.
josuke: Yeah,
but I know how he feels.
Shigechi may have come off
as an annoying, greedy bastard,
but there was something
undeniably lovable about him.
I still haven’t wrapped my head
around the fact that he’s gone.
honestly,
i’m not sure how to feel.
I don’t know whether to rage
at the world or cry my eyes out.
It’s one of the most irritating
things you can imagine.
I’m sure he feels it, too,
but it’s probably
way worse for him.
Okuyasu: Shit.
Yukako: How could
something so horrific
be happening in morioh
right under my nose?
Tonio: I’ll make sure
all my customers know
to keep an eye out
for this madman.
( Aya sighs ) I can’t imagine
he would pay me a visit,
but i’ll take some precautions.
hazamada:
Keep in mind stand users
have a nasty habit
of finding each other.
that said,
I hope we never meet.
Rohan: So the time has come
for us all to take action.
( Reimi sighs )
♪
Kira: Hmm? That was
definitely josuke.
And okuyasu is with him.
Woman: You won’t
believe what happened.
- Kira: Hmm?
- Woman: So you remember
how it was my birthday
this past Friday?
Well, that guy i’m seeing
decided to give me a gift.
i mean, if you
can even call it that.
It’s just a shitty ring.
woman #2: I wouldn’t be
caught dead wearing this thing.
Woman #1: I know, but for now,
I have to be like,
"oh, my god, I love it."
Jeez, i’m only dating him,
’cause his dad owns some land.
The guy’s a total hick.
Woman #2: I bet, if this crap
is the best he can afford.
How much did it cost?
woman #1:
I’m guessing like 150,000.
If you want it, I bet you
could sell it at a pawnshop.
I can’t let my beautiful fingers
be sullied by such trash.
( Laughs )
kira: Her soul is
as grotesque as they come,
but her hands and face
are quite lovely.
I’d like to set her soul right
and show her a glorious time.
Woman #1: Well,
i’ve gotta get going.
I’ll see you soon.
Woman #2: Okay, then. Later.
♪
( Sizzling )
Kira: Time we went
our separate ways.
We had a good run,
but it’s over now.
I, mori, mori
♪ morioh Cho radio
announcer:
With love, morioh Cho.
Kai: Good morning, everyone,
and welcome to morioh radio.
This is Kai harada,
your easy-listenin’
disc jockey extraordinaire.
are you ready
for a magnificent week?
It’s hard to believe there are
only three days...
Kira: Feel free to dig in.
Kai: ...It’s July,
you know what that means.
Kira: Oh, I almost forgot.
I’m going to be out of the house
today running a few errands,
so i’d like you
to stay put, okay?
Kai: ...Have fun summer plans.
Kira: We’ll wine and dine
when I get back.
How does that sound?
kai: ...Fresh jam
on this bright, sunny day,
so enjoy the ride.
♪
Girl: Thankfully they still had
some of the Parisian
specials left.
Girl #2: We got here
in the Nick of time.
Girl #3: Let’s head
over to yohei lake.
girl #1:
But asuka’s not here yet.
- girl #3: Oh, yeah.
- Koichi: It’s been four days
since we found out
about shigechi’s murder.
It’s been fairly quiet
since then, but...
There’s still a killer lurking
somewhere in the shadows
of this town.
( Boy crying )
Koichi: When it
comes down to it,
the mind only sees
what it wants to.
The look of guilt and innocence
is in the eye of the beholder.
( Gasps )
♪
Oh, uh, hi there, Mr. Jotaro.
Did anything weird stick out to
you during your investigation?
- jotaro: Hmm?
- Koichi: You remember, right?
you said something about
examining the murderer’s button.
Jotaro: Oh, that. Not yet.
Hopefully that changes soon.
koichi: Yeah,
it’d be a great help.
So, um, you headed
anywhere in particular?
Jotaro: Hmm? No, not really.
I’m just walking.
Koichi: Oh, I see.
( Thinking ) Son of a bitch.
Getting the strong,
silent type to chat
is like pulling teeth.
Rohan-sensei’s pushiness
is unsettling,
but jotaro’s silence
sends me into a panic.
There’s gotta be something
we can talk about.
Let’s see.
I think that coat
of yours is badass!
( Gasps )
Jotaro: Looks like
we’ve found a shoe store.
Koichi: Huh? What do you know?
It is a shoe store. Good catch.
Uh, is something wrong?
Oh. It is a shoe store,
but they also
do simple alterations.
well, that’s
certainly convenient.
If anyone ever needs
their skirt waists
and pants hemmed
I know where to send them.
Plus the electronics shop
sells flowers.
What made you wanna stop here?
Jotaro: I did a bit of digging
and learned all about
the tailors of morioh,
but it didn’t occur
to me ’til now
to ask about places like this.
Koichi: Oh!
Shopkeeper: Oh.
( Sips )
So is there something wrong
with the button?
Jotaro: No. If it doesn’t
ring a bell, forget it.
I just couldn’t remember what it
was originally attached to.
Shopkeeper: That’s too bad.
hey, kid,
want an animal cracker?
I got plenty.
I save the camels for last,
but everything else
is fair game,
so feel free to take
as many as you can eat.
Koichi: Thanks, but, no,
i’m fine for now, sir.
Shopkeeper: Suit yourself.
Getting back to the point,
not only have I seen it.
Believe it or not, I actually
just finished some alterations
on the jacket
that it belongs to.
A customer dropped by yesterday
and asked me to replace
a missing button
with the same kind
you brought in.
See for yourselves.
They’re identical.
Koichi: Does this mean...
Jotaro: It looks that way.
We’ve found it, koichi.
shopkeeper:
Found what, exactly?
Koichi: Oh, uh, nothing.
More importantly, what did
the customer look like?
Do you recall his name?
Shopkeeper: Are you serious?
Of course I do.
What kind of businessman
would I be if I didn’t?
Each and every one
of my customers’s names
is filed away
in the ol’ noggin here.
Anything less would just be rude
to my well-paying clientele.
I’ve got thousands of names
locked away in here.
- Jotaro: You don’t say?
- Shopkeeper: Huh?
Koichi: You’re absolutely
incredible, sir!
Would you mind telling us
who owns that jacket?
Shopkeeper: Well...
I guess helping you out
couldn’t hurt nothin’.
I keep the names
on the order tags.
so you know,
I don’t need these tags.
I remember the names just fine.
But things tend
to run more smoothly
when I have ’em on hand.
( Koichi gasps )
Shopkeeper: Let’s see here.
Huh, that’s interesting.
How do you read this last name?
It has to be...
Koichi: I don’t mean
to rush you, sir,
but maybe I can
help you figure it out.
Shopkeeper: That can’t be it.
Maybe it’s...
♪
( Gasping )
( Clanking )
Stand: Look over here.
( Koichi gasps )
shopkeeper:
Why’d my hand explode?
What the hell’s going on here?!
Stand: Look over here.
( Koichi gasps ) Jotaro!
Tell me you’re seeing this!
Jotaro: Just keep
your guard up, koichi,
and don’t get
any closer to it.
Stand: Hey, didn’t you hear me?
I said, "look over here."
( Shopkeeper gasping )
( Clanking )
♪
( Koichi screams )
( Gasps )
Jotaro: Is that his stand?
( Koichi gasps )
Jotaro, look at the coat rack!
Th-the killer is here,
and he’s trying
to take the jacket!
Kira: I never imagined
someone would go so far
as to investigate the button
that fell off my jacket.
What a careless mistake.
This is bad.
Have those two
already seen my name?
Why have I been faced with
nothing but adversity lately?
Jotaro: Ah, good grief.
This would be when he
comes to get his suit.
Kira: Panicking
would be a mistake.
I’ll simply execute them with
deadly queen’s bomb type two,
just like
that pathetic punk, shigechi.
( Clanking )
( Both gasp )
Koichi: It’s moving again!
( Gasps ) Our evidence!
Jotaro: Wait!
We can’t go blindly after it.
look at the way
he’s pulling the jacket.
It’s strange.
( Clanking )
( Clicks )
( Ticking )
( Kira shudders )
Jotaro: What is his power?
♪
- ( Clicks )
- Watch out! It’s gonna blow!
( Koichi screams )
♪
♪ Anytime I need
to see your face ♪
♪ I just close my eyes,
and I am taken to a place ♪
♪ where your crystal mind
and magenta feelings ♪
♪ take up shelter
in the base of my spine ♪
♪ sweet like
a chica cherry cola ♪
♪ I don’t need
to try to explain ♪
♪ I just hold on tight,
and if it happens again ♪
♪ I may move so slightly
to the arms ♪
♪ and the lips and the face
of the human cannonball ♪
♪ that I need to, I want to
♪ come stand
a little bit closer ♪
♪ breathe in,
and get a bit higher ♪
♪ you’ll never know what hit you
when I get to you ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪