Kira: And, lo and behold,
it was the right choice.
had I not spilled
that fateful cup of coffee,
where would I be?
Hayato: No way.
It’s not possible!
It was supposed to work out!
Kira: Brat.
So you poked your nose around
and found feral cat, huh?!
( Hayato whimpering )
Kira: Oh, why bother?
as long as I keep
bites the dust activated,
it’ll function to keep my secret
and protect you at all cost.
( Hayato gasping )
Crap. I blew it.
And the others don’t have long
before they get blown up.
Kira: You tried to end me
once and for all
with one of stray cat’s
compressed air projectiles.
Hayato, there’s no way
your little pea brain
could have come up
with such a clever idea
unless you’d already
experienced this morning
at least three or four times.
The fact that you’ve lived
through this morning
that many times...
Is a surefire sign
that bites the dust
is destined
to eradicate not just Rohan,
but at least
one of his companions as well,
so your loose lips
won’t only sink Rohan,
but whichever one of his friends
you ran your mouth to.
( Chuckles )
Did the would-be detectives
gang up on you?
Who have you murdered
this time? Well?
was it a runt
by the name of koichi?
Or maybe it was jotaro kujo?
Knowing that he’s dead
would make this
a red-letter day indeed.
( Hayato gasps )
It’s all over.
Kira: It’d be far too risky
for me to allow you
to relive any more
of this morning. (Chuckles)
That would expose me
to an attack.
So, once the others die,
i’ll temporarily disengage
bites the dust.
( Hayato gasps )
( Kira laughing )
Bites the dust is all-powerful!
It took a while,
but luck is finally
on yoshikage kira’s side!
- ( Laughs )
- ( Hayato gasps )
Wait a second.
That name, Kira,
is that your real...
Kira: Huh? Whoopsie.
did I just reveal
my true name to you by mistake?
( Chuckles ) Indeed,
i’m none other
than yoshikage Kira.
( Chuckles )
You can shout it to the heavens
if it suits your fancy.
by the way,
do you have the time?
Hayato: You’re dead wrong.
i haven’t
mentioned you to anyone!
I never opened
my mouth to anyone,
because I knew exactly what
would happen to them if I did!
- ( Kira grunts )
- Hayato: So instead,
I decided to make a call.
i remembered he said he
overslept and was running late,
so I found his number
and woke him up.
- ( Phone line ringing )
- I didn’t break any rules.
I just phoned a friend.
( Kira growls )
Hayato: And remember one thing.
You’re the one who revealed
his own secret identity.
I was just stalling
for a bit of extra time,
time for him
to drag himself out of bed
and show up a little earlier!
( Kira gasps )
♪
( Gasps )
( Josuke growls )
♪
♪ shining justice
( singing in Japanese )
♪ Brand-new bed town
♪ Let the voice of love
take you higher ♪
- ♪ higher, higher
- ( Singing in Japanese )
♪ 1999, bizarre summer
( singing in Japanese )
♪ Great days
♪
Okuyasu: Hey, josuke!
Looks like we’re gonna make it
to the big meeting
on time after all.
- Josuke: Hold it!
- Okuyasu: Eh?
josuke: This guy,
he isn’t who he says he is.
i don’t know
if it was pure chance
or fate giving us a break,
but I heard this guy
say a certain name!
( Kira gasps )
I don’t believe it.
Josuke: Believe it,
asshole, ’cause I know
I just heard you say
the name "yoshikage Kira"!
Okuyasu: Seriously?!
( Kira gasping )
What are the chances?
- Hayato: This isn’t chance!
- Kira: Eh?
Hayato: It’s not fate, either!
This was making a gamble,
and, lucky for me, it paid off!
Your end has arrived!
Josuke: Just admit it, already!
I know I heard the name
slither out of your mouth!
( Kira gasps ) It can’t be.
Josuke: Murderer!
Shining diamond: Dora!
Josuke: If it turns out
you and him
just happen to share a name,
don’t you worry.
I can heal if need be.
Okuyasu: This bastard’s
really yoshikage Kira?!
Kira: Damn that little brat.
I should have known
he would lead me to ruin.
( Hayato gasping )
Kira: This can’t be happening.
I have to deactivate
bites the dust
so I can defend myself
from these cretins.
( Shining diamond yelling )
Kira: Protect me, deadly queen!
( Josuke growls )
( Hayato gasps )
( Rohan shudders )
it’s chilly.
Must be due to all this rain.
Really, is it too much to ask
for certain people
to show up on time?
( Hayato gasps )
rohan: Oh,
there’s koichi and jotaro.
( Hayato gasps )
( Clock ticking )
All right! I beat the clock!
I defeated destiny!
Kira: I was never one
for rapturous highs.
No, so long as I avoided
dispiriting lows,
I was content to live
as carefree as a Daisy.
More than anything,
I sought to live
a quiet life
of peace and tranquility.
Josuke: You’ve finally
shown yourself.
That’ll make it real easy to
knock that peace and tranquility
right off your new face!
Okuyasu: Whoa! It’s the dude
from rohan’s picture!
Who’d have guessed we’d
end up meeting the guy here?
Josuke: I’m pretty sure
we didn’t run into him
by chance, okuyasu.
I haven’t figured out all of it,
but given that he
revealed his real name
to hayato kawajiri,
I get the feeling
we showed up
just in the Nick of time.
( Kira groans )
( Hayato gasps )
Kira: Before you dullards
get all high and mighty,
I should tell you
I wasn’t running away,
despite appearances.
I can obliterate any one of you
the instant
the thought occurs to me.
I detest conflict.
I hate the very idea of it
with the white-hot intensity
of a thousand suns.
Conflict runs completely counter
to the peace and tranquility
i strive for
every day of my life.
It’s really quite simple to rise
victorious in a single battle,
but of course the stress begins
to pile up before the next one.
It’s a foolish endeavor.
To engage in conflict
is to engage in futility.
Josuke: You brought
this shit on yourself
when you murdered shigechi,
you frickin’ idiot!
Okuyasu: You’re a sick son
of a bitch who kills for fun!
You shouldn’t get the privilege
of flapping those stolen gums,
you cat-eyed freak!
♪
Watch yourself, josuke.
Make sure you avoid
deadly queen’s
creepy bomb hand
at all costs!
Kira: I’ve already
told you the reason
for my not obliterating
all of you earlier.
The only souls
standing between me
and my eternal peace and
tranquility are you three.
Since i’ve been found out,
i have no choice
but to do battle with you.
( Okuyasu growls )
things are
about to get dicey, hayato,
so get behind us now!
- ( Hayato gasps )
- Kira: Let’s see now.
Shining diamond’s range
is one to two meters,
and it corrects that which
has been destroyed or altered.
josuke: I won’t
be fixin’ you up, buddy,
so don’t even worry about it.
A good ass kicking’s the only
treatment you’re getting!
♪
( Shining diamond yells )
( Josuke gasps )
Okuyasu: Hey, look out!
Josuke: Dora.
Kira: He’s tough. ( Moans )
Hayato: I can’t tell
what happened,
but Kira hacking up blood
and flying through the air
gets a, "hell, yeah," from me!
Josuke: Your deadly queen’s
as slow as molasses!
For all the killing you do,
you’re a real lethargic fighter.
guess all that peace and
tranquility will do that to you.
It’s painfully obvious
that your stand
just isn’t cut out
for one-on-one fighting.
Okuyasu: Josuke, he’s slow,
but don’t let your guard down!
If you wanna knock him around
without laying a finger on him,
there’s no better stand to have
on your side than the hand!
Bring it!
( Kira growls )
You scrape away space
to transport things, eh?
Josuke was my target,
but it appears fate
has other ideas in mind
for me today.
I’m now poised to attack you.
( Hayato gasps ) I know!
I’ll use the plant to--
( gasps )
Okuyasu: What?!
- ( Hayato gasps )
- ( Josuke gasps )
( Okuyasu gags )
Kira: Nice. Direct hit.
that wasn’t too bad,
especially for beginner’s luck.
( Okuyasu gags )
What the hell happened?
I didn’t see anything touch me.
It’s the air.
The air spit some kind of fire.
Josuke: Okuyasu!
( Yells )
Hayato: D-did I hear him right?
The air spit fire? But how?!
Kira: Well, boys?
Do you see now?
This is why I kept my pet.
I’ve found a way
to use stray cat’s
air-controlling abilities
in deadly queen’s explosions.
I must thank you for carting it
all the way here, hayato.
hayato:
The invisibility of the air
mixed with the power
of an explosion!
He couldn’t have have fused
a more dangerous combination
of elements if he tried!
He was growing it
to do this all along,
and i’m the wise guy who brought
the stupid thing right to him!
Kira: I did tell you luck was
finally on my side, didn’t I?
but the characters
that make up the word "luck"
are "bring" and "life."
( Chuckles )
How deliciously apropos.
( Josuke screams )
Jotaro: Hmm?
Koichi: Is something wrong,
Mr. Jotaro?
- Rohan: Huh?
- Jotaro: Uh, no.
It’s nothing.
for a moment,
I thought I heard josuke,
but I guess
it was just the rain.
Rohan: Quintessential josuke.
I’m sure the slob
overslept again.
If he’s not here
in five minutes flat,
i’m going straight
to hayato kawajiri’s school,
and i’ll leave you two here
to wait for everyone else.
( Koichi sighs )
Josuke: I’m gonna make you
as good as new, okuyasu!
Kira: That’s certainly
a noble thought.
- ( Josuke growls )
- Kira: But, you see,
it’s time for you to explode.
Hayato: That cat plant launched
air at him like a bullet!
It can transform air
into an explosive!
there it is!
You’ve gotta run now!
( Josuke gasps )
Hayato: You can’t see it?
It’s that weird bubble thing!
Move! It’s gonna get you!
Shining diamond: Dora!
Hayato: Oh, that’s right!
He has the power to fix things,
which means he can heal okuyasu.
kira: To fix
that which is broken.
using your power
to reassemble broken stone
into a wall was impressive.
Hayato: It’s at it again!
( Josuke grunts )
Hayato: Hey, it’s coming!
Shining diamond: Dora!
Kira: Nothing in the world
is as terrifying
as the act of assumption,
especially
for those contemptible few
who assume
the false superiority
of their own talents
and special abilities.
- ( Josuke gasps )
- Hayato: Yo!
It’s squeezing through!
Contact didn’t
cause it to explode!
( Josuke gasps )
( Screams )
( Hayato screams )
( Josuke groans )
Kira: Hmph. I thought it
would at least decapitate him.
But, lucky for him,
the destructive force
was rather shallow.
My deadly queen’s explosion
is not limited to objects
it directly touches.
Thinking so was an assumption.
It can generate an explosion
at any distance I wish.
No matter where you try to hide
or how quickly you build
a protective stone wall
or metal plate,
my bomb will slip
through any obstacle
and execute its target.
you won’t escape
with your life this time.
Now die.
Hayato: It’s no use!
There’s no way to dodge it!
Josuke: What do you mean,
"dodge it"?
I have no intention of escaping.
for the record,
I would never run away!
How else would I heal
okuyasu’s wounds?
Hayato: He’s charging
right into it?!
Kira: Hmm?
Hayato: It went around him!
( Kira gasps )
Josuke: I thought you said
you could detonate that thing
at any distance.
I must have found the exception.
namely, i’m just
a little too close for comfort
for you to try blowing me up!
Doing that wouldn’t end well
for you, now, would it?!
( Kira grumbles )
Josuke: All right, hang on.
I’ll have you healed
before you know it.
( Kira chuckles )
( Hayato gasps )
You can’t touch him!
Trust me on this!
If I know Kira,
he’s already
transformed okuyasu!
He’s a bomb!
( Josuke gasps )
( Kira grumbles )
Damn that little whelp.
Josuke: He what? No!
I never saw deadly queen
lay even a finger on okuyasu.
What makes you think
he was able to pull that off?
You’re not a stand user,
so how would you know?!
hayato: I just do!
I’ve lived in the same house
as that psycho
until this morning!
His face tells me everything.
His stand touched him
before we could notice!
Josuke, please,
you gotta trust me!
Okuyasu’s a bomb now!
Josuke: Yoshikage Kira!
kira: Easy.
Give me a moment to think.
Well, now, let’s see.
You stormed at me
out of the blue,
so I can’t really say
whether I touched him or not.
Actually, the whole incident
was such a blur.
perhaps I should
press the switch and find out.
( Josuke gasping )
No, please don’t!
I’m begging you!
just hurry up,
and shoot your next air missile!
Point the damn thing at me,
and shoot! Come on! Do it!
kira: Really, now.
There’s no need to be hasty
and end the fun so quickly,
is there?
Josuke higashikata,
I think i’ll observe you
a little while longer
and then decide
if I should obliterate you.
( Josuke growls )
kira: Besides,
you honestly have no real proof
I turned okuyasu
into a bomb at all.
It might be possible to heal him
with shining diamond.
I could be overstepping here,
but at this point
it would appear you have
only one course of action
if you want to save okuyasu.
You must heal him
by way of touching him.
( Josuke shuddering )
Kira: I don’t envy
the position you’re in.
If he is a human bomb,
touching him with
shining diamond may kill you,
but okuyasu
would be spared the fate
of exploding into oblivion.
If you heal your dear friend’s
critical injuries,
at least your sacrifice
won’t have been in vain.
hayato: No!
Don’t touch him, josuke!
kira: I’ll wait
until you’ve made your decision.
do you save
your best friend’s life,
or do you just attack me
and let him die?
( Josuke shuddering )
Kira: Wow. I’m content to wait
until you make a decision,
but it seems you’re averse
to touching your friend,
even when it means
keeping him alive.
( Josuke shuddering )
Hayato: I have proof
touching him is deadly!
I know for a fact that kira’s
only able to control
one bomb at a time.
once he’s activated
one of his freaky bomb things,
it’s impossible for him
to fire off the next one
until the first
has been detonated!
think about it!
He only used one at a time!
Why wouldn’t he launch
a bunch at once?
He’s made okuyasu into a bomb,
so he can’t shoot now!
josuke: Are you
trying to make a point?
Hayato: The point is there’s
still a way to save okuyasu,
but someone needs to touch him.
- ( Kira grumbles )
- ( Hayato sighs )
kira: Hmm?
Deadly queen, bomb switch on!
Hayato: And that someone
has gotta be me!
- ( Switch clicks )
- ( All gasp )
Josuke: Hayato, you--
now I get it! Shining diamond!
( Shining diamond yelling )
Josuke: You’re one
crazy-ass s.O.B., hayato!
It took some major balls
to set off the bomb like that.
you sure
you’re a grade schooler,
’cause that was badass!
Hayato: Yeah, well, I couldn’t
just stand around doing nothing,
and I knew
you had the power to heal me.
i refuse to let
any more innocent people die!
Besides, if you’re gone,
he’ll off me
in the blink of an eye,
and he’ll be free to do
whatever he wants.
It’s just a matter of time
before he kills my mom,
and then he’ll go after
more people in this town!
Kira: But, first, you die,
though your power
is certainly an issue.
To think your stand
can reverse my destructive acts
in mere seconds.
I’d almost forgotten how much
that annoying healing ability
of yours vexes me utterly.
Deadly queen!
Hayato: Josuke,
he’s gonna shoot!
( Josuke gasps )
Kira: It’ll detonate on impact,
so you’ll have
no opportunity to guard.
then again,
you could sidestep the explosive
if you happen to see it,
so i’ve launched one
so small it’s
almost impossible to detect.
With okuyasu on your back and
those painful shrapnel wounds,
can you really dodge
a projectile?
Hayato: Just get the hell
out of there, josuke!
If the explosion so much
as brushes against you,
you’ll be a dead man!
Josuke: I healed you.
Why haven’t you woken up yet?
Open those beady eyes! Okuyasu!
Hayato: The bomb’s on its way!
Move it!
Kira: Only eight more meters
until impact.
josuke: All right,
enough goofing around, buddy,
it’s time to wake up now!
You’re as good as new, okuyasu!
Hayato: Josuke, please!
Kira: Seven meters to go.
josuke:
Don’t you leave me, dick!
Open your damn eyes! Hey!
Come on, man. Quit napping,
and open your freakin’ eyes!
Hey! If you wake up,
we can knock the shit
out of this asshole,
just like we always do!
Hayato: Josuke, go!
Kira: Like Joe Montana
throwing the touchdown pass
of a winning game,
i’ll detonate the sucker
in the perfect position
and go home victorious.
Four meters until impact.
Hayato: Go! Right now!
You’ve gotta run for it,
or it’s gonna hit you dead-on!
I’m so sorry about okuyasu,
but he’s already--
josuke: No! Don’t say it!
The only one of us who needs
to run here is you, kid!
Kira: Two meters ’til showtime.
With a three-meter radius,
they’re sure to die
in the explosion.
♪
hayato: I can see it!
It’s two meters in front of you,
and it’s closing in fast!
You’ve gotta run now!
Listen to me, josuke!
Okuyasu’s gone! He’s dead!
Accept it already!
Josuke: He’s nowhere
near dead, damn it!
He’s back in top form,
and he’ll open his eyes
any minute now!
Kira: Yes. Just one more meter,
and then pop goes the riffraff.
Hayato: Josuke!
( Josuke yells )
Shining diamond: Dora!
Hayato: Holy heck! It was
ruptured by a blade of blood!
did josuke somehow
take his blood and propel it
with so much force
that it cut like a knife?
Oh, yeah. It’s just like
that time in the attic!
The air shackles deflated
when I punctured them
with the compass needle!
kira: He used
the blood from his wound
like a water jet cutter. Hmph.
And he severed the bullet
clean through.
nice try,
but it didn’t do you any good.
Hayato: You gotta move!
They didn’t deflate!
Kira: This improvised
air bullet explosive
is stabilized by deadly queen,
so it won’t deflate.
You can split it, smash it,
or dice it to pieces,
but i’m pleased to say the bomb
will never lose its power.
and now back to our
regularly scheduled explosion.
( Hayato screams )
Kira: Touchdown.
Hayato: The heck’s goin’ on?
He’s floating?
- Kira: Explode.
- ( Switch clicks )
Hayato: No, this isn’t floating.
Whoa! Ahh!
Josuke: Hmm?
Hayato: Eh?
Josuke: Shining diamond
won’t allow me to heal myself,
which, to be frank,
would come in handy right now.
But when it comes
to pieces of road,
like the ones that got lodged
in me from the first blast,
that’s a whole different story!
hayato: Whoa.
What a super neat idea,
using the road to pull you up!
Josuke: I’m out of options.
We don’t live here,
but it’ll work
as our safe house for now.
Hayato: Uh, please,
you have to leave okuyasu!
If you keep carrying him around,
you’re gonna get killed!
He’ll find a way to corner you,
and that’ll be it!
Josuke: I asked you
to keep quiet, so drop it!
Okuyasu and I have a connection.
He’s my friend.
I won’t abandon him.
Hayato: No, that’s not
what i’m trying to say!
By the time you healed okuyasu,
he was already DEA--
josuke: Enough!
Enough. Not another word.
i mean it.
Hayato: You gotta focus
your energy on beating Kira!
( Gasps )
( Thumping )
Kira: How irksome.
That blasted ability to correct,
without it,
my bomb would be unstoppable.
I see now that the greatest
obstacle standing in the way
of my attaining peace
and tranquility isn’t jotaro.
It’s him...
Josuke higashikata!
♪
♪ Anytime I need
to see your face ♪
♪ I just close my eyes,
and I am taken to a place ♪
♪ where your crystal mind
and magenta feelings ♪
♪ take up shelter
in the base of my spine ♪
♪ sweet like
a chica cherry cola ♪
♪ I don’t need
to try to explain ♪
♪ I just hold on tight,
and if it happens again ♪
♪ I may move so slightly
to the arms ♪
♪ and the lips and the face
of the human cannonball ♪
♪ that I need to, I want to
♪ come stand
a little bit closer ♪
♪ breathe in,
and get a bit higher ♪
♪ you’ll never know what hit you
when I get to you ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪