Koichi: The public
doesn’t realize it,
but there’s an evil
lurking in morioh.
It’s like a silent disease
slowly ravaging our town
from the inside out,
and every day, more and
more lives are being taken.
( Sighs )
What’s worse, these killings
have gone completely unnoticed
for years.
It’s shocking to say the least.
The thought of it’s
downright chilling.
and we have no way
of tracking down the murderer,
no matter how hard we try.
In fact, we still don’t know
how many stand users
are even in morioh.
But people aren’t worried
about some silent killer
coming after them.
They’re too preoccupied with
what they’re having for dinner.
Everyone is completely blind
to what’s going on
outside their immediate view.
( Josuke groans )
How can I only have
285 yen to my name?!
last I checked,
I had 20,000 in savings!
( Panting )
Just 12 yen?!
( Groans )
I’ve gotta work
on my spending habits.
That 20,000 yen was for those
dope designer shoes I wanted.
What the hell else could I have
spent that amount of money on?
this is that
crusty old man’s fault!
he charged
130,000 yen to my card
when he bought that baby shit!
though I have to admit,
the geezer paid me back in full.
after that, I got bit
by a mysterious spending bug,
and my money sense
flew right out the window.
Maybe i’ll get lucky
and find a thousand yen
laying around somewhere,
though the odds of that
are slim to none.
- ( Rustling )
- ( Gasps ) Huh?
♪
Hmm?
( Yelps )
It’s a disgusting roach.
That’s a health code violation
if I ever seen one.
♪
Is that a stand?
( Stand blows )
Great. I got one yen.
( Laughs ) Hoo!
( Grunts )
♪
Josuke: Where do you
think you’re going?
( Gasps )
I was right. It’s a stand!
Just when I thought this day
couldn’t get any worse.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
( Josuke panting )
Where the hell is it going?
There’s another one.
( Okuyasu growls ) Damn it!
What the hell are you?!
You’re about to get slaughtered!
You hear me?!
- ( Growls )
- Josuke: Okuyasu!
Okuyasu: Oh, heya, josuke.
Look! There’s an enemy stand!
I’m gonna squash him to death.
( Gasps )
Now there are two of ’em!
Josuke: Yeah, I followed
one of the little pests
all the way from the bank.
How did the one you’re after
attack you?
Okuyasu: Well, he didn’t
actually attack me.
I was trying to buy
a bottle of calpis water
when suddenly it popped out
from under the vending machine
and took off.
Josuke: That’s all?
you mean it didn’t
try to pick a fight with you?
Then why were you ranting about
wanting to squash it to death?
Okuyasu: ’cause the stupid,
little bastard
startled me so bad,
I spilled the damn water
all over my uniform.
I want my money back, damn it!
- Stand: I got one!
- Okuyasu: Check it out.
looks like another one
of those things joined the pack.
Stand: I got one!
- I got one.
Okuyasu: Whoa, what the hell
are these things?
There are so many of ’em!
They’re like a pint-sized army!
Josuke: Okuyasu, try not
to take this the wrong way,
but they kinda remind me
of your brother’s stand.
Although, the fact that
they’re completely ignoring us
is giving me a bad feeling.
It’s really creepy,
if you ask me.
Okuyasu: Yeah.
Josuke: Stay alert.
The user is probably
somewhere nearby. Focus.
( Both gasp )
( Coins clinking )
Josuke: Wha?!
Okuyasu: It’s money.
Josuke: Oh, that’s right.
it took a one-yen coin
from under the atm at the bank.
As crazy as it is,
i’m pretty sure all those coins
are the real deal.
User: Great work, everyone.
These are some good pickings.
like they say,
"a yen saved is a yen earned,"
and counting all the money
that we’ve saved,
- this makes 5,000 yen.
- ( Both gasp )
( User chuckles )
As long as I have you
by my side, harvest,
i’ll have everything I need to
get by for the rest of my life.
Josuke: Hey, do you see the way
he’s talking to that stand?
He must be the user,
given how chummy they are.
okuyasu: You’re right.
Looks like another sorry chump
got tagged by the bow and arrow.
But goin’ by his goofy attitude,
it doesn’t seem
like he wants to hurt anyone.
- ( Leaves rustle )
- ( Both gasp )
♪
- User: Grin!
- Both: Huh?
User: Oh, wow, this is so neat!
I had no clue other people
could see my harvest, too.
- ( Both gasping )
- ( User laughs )
Hey, guys, you can
really see it, can’t you?
Josuke: Yeah. So you know,
they’re called stands.
User: Wow.
Josuke: I’m josuke higashikata,
and this here
is okuyasu nijimura.
( User gasps )
This means we’re friends.
My very first friends!
oh, right.
I guess I should tell you
that my name is shigekiyo yangu!
I’m an eighth-grader
at budogaoka middle school.
I weigh 110 kilograms,
and my mommy and daddy
call me shigechi,
because i’m
their special little man.
First they called me
little shige,
but now it’s shigechi.
I also have a pet turtle,
and his name is gonta.
I was home the other day,
and all of a sudden,
I had the urge to find out
whether the 41-, 62-, and
150-yen stamps tasted the same,
so I started
licking them all over,
and my mommy yelled
at me something fierce.
This is a picture of my mommy,
the one who yelled at me.
Okuyasu: A picture? Holy shit.
Your mom is actually
pretty easy on the eyes.
What the hell?
Josuke: So, uh,
question for you.
These things are
called harvest, right?
Were they really the ones
who picked up all these coins?
Shigechi: You bet they were.
They got ’em from ditches
and the bottom
of vending machines,
but i’m not a robber,
if that’s what you’re thinking.
i already talked
to the koban policeman about it.
He said it wasn’t necessary
to return coin denominations
less than 100 yen.
Nothing peeves me off more
than doing bad things!
Josuke: I don’t think
there’s anything bad
about what you’re doing.
If you ask me, you’re doing
society a big favor.
It’s no boatload of cash,
but you’re taking
forgotten funds
and putting them back
into the Japanese economy.
You’re doing great work here.
Shigechi: Uh--( Laughs )
Really? Do you mean it?
You think it’s great?
does that mean
you think i’m great, too?
Be honest! ( Giggles )
Josuke: Oh, man, talk about
being hidden in plain sight.
I’ve gotta hand it to the guy.
No one would ever think
of collecting money like this.
Okuyasu: I’m so jealous.
He’s a freakin’ genius.
( Shigechi gasps ) I-I may
have heard you incorrectly,
but did you happen to say
I was a "freaking genius"?
No one has ever said anything
like that to me before.
I’ve picked up 120,000 yen
since I started--
both: 120,000?!
Shigechi: But your kind words
make me even happier.
josuke: Hey,
you have 120,000 yen?
Shigechi: Pretty good, huh?
Josuke: And you
scrounged together
all that money around morioh?
shigechi: Yep.
It’s the only way to do things,
since I never
step foot out of town.
I could get lost,
and some creepo
might take advantage
of my innocence. Hee hee.
Josuke: No fair. I have 12 yen,
and he’s rolling in it.
Hmm?
- Okuyasu...
- ( Okuyasu gasps )
Josuke: What’s wrong
with your left foot?
Okuyasu: Eh...
Whoa, what in the world?!
How did three 50-yen coins
end up hiding
right under my foot?!
You think this random money
might belong to shigekiyo?
He should keep an eye
on his stash.
Josuke: You sneaky dick.
( Shigechi gasps ) Here you go.
I’ll give you guys half.
- Would that make you happy?
- Both: Huh?!
Shigechi: We’re each other’s
bestest friends now, right?
We can all hang out
and do cool things.
Okuyasu: Really?!
Do you mean it?!
Josuke: Lucky us!
( Gasps ) No, wait.
This just isn’t right.
You can’t just hand over
your hard-earned money
to complete strangers
like it’s nothing at all.
Shigechi: Okay, this time,
i’ll put my back into it.
go on. Take it.
Half of all of this is yours.
That’s what friends
are for, isn’t it?
Josuke: Grunting and
scrunching up your face
doesn’t make it right.
- Okuyasu: Let’s talk.
- ( Josuke groans )
Okuyasu: Can you excuse us
for a second, shigechi?
We need to chat. ( Chuckles )
Listen to me, josuke.
Enough of the goody-goody shit.
if this turd boy
wants to give us his money,
then who are we
to turn him down?
Josuke: Sorry, buddy,
but my pride won’t allow me
to do that.
It’s just not right, okay?
Okuyasu: As long as it’s
not some shitty disease,
i’ll take whatever people
are givin’, so don’t you judge!
Josuke: All right, I get it!
I wasn’t judging you! Chill out!
- stop crying.
- Okuyasu: But you said--
josuke: Look,
I know how you feel.
i’m not exactly
raking in yen myself, you know?
But never fear. I just
came up with a little idea
that’ll put
everyone’s minds at ease.
Okuyasu: Huh? You really
think it’s possible
to make everyone happy?
( Josuke chuckles )
Just leave everything to me!
Josuke: So, uh, shigekiyo--
actually, uh, do you mind
if I call you shigechi?
Shigechi: Oh, i’d love that.
Josuke: All right, shigechi,
we can’t take your money.
What you were attempting
to do just now is honestly
no different than trying
to pay for our friendship.
shigechi: But i--
I wasn’t trying to do that.
Josuke: Don’t worry.
I know you weren’t.
But if you ask me,
a friendship is something
you build over time.
Shigechi: All I was trying to do
was make some new friends.
jo: Yeah, I get that,
and I know exactly how you feel.
we stand users
have to stick together.
- ( Shigechi gasps )
- Josuke: And so,
what do you say we all do
a nice round of team building
and strengthen our friendship
with a little business venture?
- shigechi: Huh?
- Okuyasu: Business venture?
Josuke: Yep!
Before you know it,
us three are
gonna be stinking rich.
Shigechi: Oh, do I stink?
Joseph: I mean lots of cash.
Go with me here.
there’s only
so much money you can make
by picking up
leftover change, right?
I know things have worked out
for you so far,
but I have a much more lucrative
approach for harvest.
- Okuyasu: Oh?
- ( Shigechi gasps )
Okuyasu: You have a better plan
than picking up change?
This idea is legal, isn’t it?
Josuke: Yeah, there’s
nothing corrupt about it,
and no one’ll get hurt
in the process.
Shigechi: Uh-huh, uh-huh.
I’m likin’ what i’m hearin’,
so what’s your idea?
Josuke: Well, that’s where
the business part comes in,
and as compensation
for coming up
with this marvelous proposal,
you give us half the profits.
the other half
will go to you, shigechi.
The three of us are gonna
have to put our heads together
if we wanna pull this thing off,
but when all is said and done,
we’ll finally get
the payday we deserve.
Shigechi: That sounds good,
but i’m confused.
what’s my job
supposed to be in all this?
Josuke: Do you know
what i’m holding?
Shigechi: It’s a blue stamp.
Josuke: Right. It comes with
every 100-yen purchase
from kameyu.
You must have heard
of a chain this famous.
It’s one of eastern japan’s
biggest department stores.
And the best part
about these stickers
is there are plenty of people
who just toss ’em.
- Okuyasu: Ooh.
- Shigechi: Hmm?
Josuke: But wait. There’s more.
a 20-yen voucher from
that stationary store, meiwado.
And here’s a voucher
from cd shop Oscar!
Ten will get you 2,000 yen’s
worth of merchandise.
Here’s one from the cleaners,
märchen kids toy store,
and this is a card
from yotsuba electronics.
Now pay attention,
’cause this is important.
With a place like kameyu,
if you use this sticker,
you can get
a little bit of cash back.
Okuyasu: Oh, I see
what you’re getting at!
You’re as amazing
as ever, josuke.
This is the best plan
i’ve ever heard!
( Shigechi gasps )
( All laughing )
Shigechi: All right, everybody!
- Go and do what you do best!
- ( Josuke and okuyasu laugh )
♪
Okuyasu: By themselves,
these things
are as worthless
as scraps of paper,
but if you use
harvest to pick up
the tens of thousands of ’em
lying around town,
well, that’s
an entirely different story!
Harvest: Got it.
Okuyasu: This trash can!
Now that one!
Harvest: Got it.
- Got it.
- Got it!
- ( All laugh )
okuyasu: Look!
They just keep piling up!
I’ve lost count of ’em all!
( Squeals )
Josuke: Your stand’s
the greatest ever!
Amazing, shigechi!
( Shigechi titters )
Another compliment.
Josuke: A few are torn,
but i’ll fix them
with shining diamond!
okuyasu: Oh, boy!
We must have thousands by now!
Josuke: By the looks of it,
it’s over 100,000!
- Okuyasu: Yes!
- Shigechi: Hee!
Josuke: This day belongs
to the unbeatable trio!
- Now let’s go cash in.
- Okuyasu: Yeah!
- ( Shigechi giggles )
- Okuyasu: So, josuke,
what was that you were
saying about your pride?
You’re such a smooth talker,
it’s like you do this
for a livin’.
Josuke: Everyone’s gonna be
so happy in the end, man,
so it’s all good.
Shigechi: Wow,
I have friends now.
( Gasps )
Friendship is the coolest.
( Giggles )
♪
Shigechi: Um, okuyasu,
i’m getting kinda nervous.
do you think
josuke’s gonna be okay?
turning those thingies
into money sounds really tricky.
Okuyasu: Relax, shigechi.
Give josuke a chance
to work his magic.
Koichi: Eh?
it’s okuyasu,
and, uh, who is that?
Okuyasu--
( gasping )
♪
( Yukako gasps )
( Sighs )
( Car horn honks )
( Both gasp )
Okuyasu: Hey, josuke,
how’d it go in there?
Did you manage to get our money?
They didn’t tell you
to piss off, did they?
I found out that the cd shop and
toy store don’t do cash back.
that said,
we can exchange the coupons
for about 40,000 yen worth
of cds and video games.
okuyasu: Yeah, yeah,
that doesn’t matter right now.
what about kameyu?
Please tell me you were able
to get cash
for the kameyu stickers.
Josuke: Not exactly.
Something unexpected
came up last minute.
Okuyasu: S-something unexpected?
( Shigechi swallows )
( Josuke sighs )
We got 61,500 yen back instead!
( Both cheering, laughing )
josuke: Behold
the genuine article, shigechi!
Shigechi: Oh, boy, oh, boy,
it’s real money!
Okuyasu: Whoo! Real cash
right before my eyes!
This is like a dream come true!
( Shigechi laughs )
Josuke: You are the best!
Your harvest is amazing!
no other stand’s
ever come close to its prowess!
Shigechi: Really? You mean it?
You think it’s amazing?
oh, wow. I don’t
usually get compliments.
You guys have been super nice.
I don’t know what to say.
Do you really think
i’m amazing?
Okuyasu: Hey, have some faith
in yourself, shigechi.
Josuke: Yeah, you’ve got a power
no one else could
ever dream of having!
Shigechi: You keep
talkin’ like that,
and i’ll be a sobbing mess.
All right.
hey, doll face,
I got a fat stack of greenbacks!
Wanna have some fun?
Both: Too far! Too far!
Too far! Too far! Too far!
( Shigechi chuckling )
( Josuke and okuyasu groan )
Shigechi: Oh, yeah.
okuyasu, josuke,
i’ve got something for you.
This is your cut, 10,000 large.
- Okuyasu: Huh?
- Josuke: Eh...
( Shigechi stammers )
( Whistling a tune )
- okuyasu: Uh...
- Josuke: Hey, shigechi,
what the hell is going on here?
( Shigechi groans )
The three of us are comrades
in business and life, aren’t we?
I mean, you’d say that we
were friends, right?
Josuke: Yeah, of course.
we’re a team.
shigechi: Well,
the money i’ve gifted you
is a generous token
of our new friendship.
( Both grunt )
Josuke: Hold up a sec!
This isn’t the amount
we agreed on, shigechi.
You promised us
that we’d get half
of whatever money
we managed to scrape together.
Half of 61,500 yen is 30,750.
Shigechi: Really? I said that?
Nothing you’re saying
rings any bells.
Josuke: Say what?!
Shigechi: Besides,
it’s not fair.
My harvest did all the work.
I don’t remember you guys
lifting a single finger
to help out.
the work was all me.
Maybe you two don’t realize it,
but you’re all talk
and no action.
- ( Josuke gasps )
- Okuyasu: Shut your damn mouth!
If josuke hadn’t come up with
the idea in the first place,
you never would have thought
of picking up
those stupid stickers!
Shigechi: No, I would have
come up with it eventually!
I’m the amazing shigechi,
remember?!
( Okuyasu growls ) Wrong!
there’s no way
a cantaloupe head like you
would have thought
of a plan like that!
( Shigechi whimpers )
Josuke: Stop, okuyasu!
Don’t do something
you’ll regret later!
( Okuyasu growls )
Josuke: Just great.
The band’s broken up already.
He was happy to give us
a few thousand,
but the moment we ask
for a few ten thousands,
now we’re stepping over the line
all of a sudden.
( Okuyasu growling )
Josuke: He really
doesn’t mean any harm.
He just has the mentality
of a little kid.
No matter what we say,
it’s gonna feel like we’re
duping him out of his money.
It sucks royally, but we
should be the adults here
and call it a day.
We already got
ten grand out of it.
That’s enough to get by.
Okuyasu: I guess
if you put it that way,
leaving is the best option,
but melon head over there
really rubs me the wrong way.
You sure he’s not pulling
a fast one on us?
Josuke: No, okuyasu,
and fighting’s
not gonna get us anywhere.
We have to handle this
delicately.
I say we school him on how
mature adults do business.
Okuyasu: Heh. Sly dog!
you’re still
anglin’ for the cash.
You fickle bastard, you.
( Laughs )
Have I ever told you
I love that brain of yours?
Josuke: You win, shigechi.
We’ll gladly accept
this amount as our cut.
( Shigechi chuckles ) Okuyasu.
Okuyasu: Hmm?
Shigechi: You want
something to drink?
Pick any one you want.
I’m rich, so it’s on me.
Okuyasu: If you’re treatin’,
i’m drinkin’.
And you know, I think
I want some calpis water.
Shigechi: Good for you.
( Okuyasu groans )
josuke, how come
you’re throwing those away?!
Josuke: ’cause they’re nothing
but worthless junk now,
just like year-end
lottery tickets.
Okuyasu: I remember telling
shigechi to pick these up
when he was grabbing
all the other tickets.
Josuke: You mean these losing
new year’s postcard
lottery letters?
And just how would you know
if these were losing tickets?
Josuke: That’s an easy one.
No one’s gonna throw away
a winning ticket, you dumb-ass.
Okuyasu: You say that,
but i’ve heard
that a lot of people
forget to check their numbers
and then end up missing out
on claiming their prizes.
if this wins,
you have to promise me
I can take half of it
for myself. Are we clear?
Shigechi: Fine by me.
half, it is.
And if you win
a sheet of stamps
instead of cold, hard cash,
i’ll let you keep that, too.
( Okuyasu chuckles )
Josuke: Jeez, okuyasu,
I never realized
how much you liked those
cheap, little gambling games.
Okuyasu: That one’s no good.
How ’bout this?
I didn’t really
think about it before,
but do you think I can
collect lottery prizes
if i’m still in high school?
Josuke: I don’t see
why you couldn’t.
So long as you have your I.D.
And name stamp on you,
it should be smooth sailing.
- ( Shigechi chuckles )
- Okuyasu: Sg group 121314.
Aw, man, that’s lame.
It’s just another dud.
Thought I had it this time.
Guess not.
( Grumbles ) Hmm.
( Gasps )
Huh? Sg group 121314. Hang on.
Hey, question--
if I happened to win
the lottery by chance,
would I have to take it
to the police?
Josuke: You idiot! Why would
you turn it in to them?
Harvest only picked up
what people threw away.
It’s not stealing.
And besides that,
unless you were
to somehow magically win,
it’s a moot point, right?
but best of luck.
okuyasu: What?!
This says, "sg group 121314"!
- Josuke: Eh?
- Shigechi: Huh?
Okuyasu: "Sg group 121314"?!
It’s sg group 121314!
Josuke: Whoa there. What are
you getting so worked up about?
( Okuyasu gasping )
Yaah! Five million!
There’s no doubt about it!
I won!
( Shrieks )
Josuke: Wait!
Are you kidding me?!
This better not
be a stupid joke.
( Both shrieking, laughing )
Josuke: Great!
♪
Okuyasu: Oh, yeah!
A dream come true!
Incredible!
We’re the first to ever
experience this greatness!
Josuke: Don’t get
ahead of yourself!
( Panting ) Settle down.
Let’s just double-check
to make sure you actually won.
"Sg group 121314,
prize five million yen."
Well, there you go. It’s hard
to believe, but it’s true.
If you hadn’t found this
lottery ticket when you did,
it would have been
off to the incinerator.
Look, it expires in a few days.
We have to get this to the bank.
And if they ask us
a bunch of questions,
we’ll tell them
we bought it fair and square
and hope they believe us
so we can get the cash.
You good on that plan?
Okuyasu: You know it.
Lie and get the dough!
Josuke: All right! We’re gonna
be five million yen richer!
( Okuyasu laughs )
Josuke: Now what
should I buy first?
i know. I’ll get
some sick Italian shoes.
Then i’ll buy
a new designer suit
that complements
my sexy physique.
After that, it’s on to tonio’s
for his most expensive dish.
And of course i’ll have
to go someplace cool abroad.
Okuyasu: I’m saving
all my money!
josuke: Wow!
Talk about playing it safe!
( Both laughing )
( Shigechi growls )
My harvest did
all the heavy lifting
while those two goofed around.
Every last yen of that
five million belongs to me.
I won’t let them take it.
♪
♪ Anytime I need
to see your face ♪
♪ I just close my eyes,
and I am taken to a place ♪
♪ where your crystal mind
and magenta feelings ♪
♪ take up shelter
in the base of my spine ♪
♪ sweet like
a chica cherry cola ♪
♪ I don’t need
to try to explain ♪
♪ I just hold on tight,
and if it happens again ♪
♪ I may move so slightly
to the arms ♪
♪ and the lips and the face
of the human cannonball ♪
♪ that I need to, I want to
♪ come stand
a little bit closer ♪
♪ breathe in,
and get a bit higher ♪
♪ you’ll never know what hit you
when I get to you ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪
♪ ooh, I want you
♪ I don’t know if I need you
♪ but, ooh,
i’d die to find out ♪