- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( music box playing )
- ( clatters )
- ( sighs )
HOT.
SHANA!
- WHAT?
- THERE ANY UNRESTRICTED SPELLS
THAT CAN COOL US OFF?
- I'M NOT YOUR
PERSONAL A.C.
- SO THAT'S A "NO" THEN?
MAN!
WHAT'S THE POINT OF
EVEN CASTING SPELLS?
- ( grunts )
SHUT UP, SHUT UP, SHUT UP!
SPELLS LIKE THAT ONE
ARE WAY TOO DELICATE
AND CAN'T BE USED
CASUALLY!
- ( gasps )
- HUMPH.
- Yuji: SO IT'S NOT
THAT YOU CAN'T,
YOU JUST WON'T.
( sighs )
- ( sighs )
- YEAH.
- THAT'S THE STUFF.
- SO MUCH STUFF HERE.
IT'S GONNA TAKE FOREVER
TO SIFT THROUGH ALL OF IT.
- Alastor: THINK OF THIS
AS PART OF YOUR TRAINING.
DON'T LOOK WITH YOUR
EYES AND HANDS.
REACH OUT WITH YOUR
POWER OF EXISTENCE.
FEEL THE SPACE AROUND YOU,
AND SEE WHAT REACHES BACK.
- Yuji: HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO KNOW HOW MUCH POWER OF
EXISTENCE
TO GIVE OUT TO
WHAT ITEMS?
WHAT IF THERE'S
A TREASURE TOOL
THAT EXPLODES
WHEN YOU PUT POWER OF EXISTENCE
INTO IT?
- Shana: YEAH.  MIGHT BE.
- ( gasps )
WHOA.
SOME KIND OF TELESCOPE?
HEY, SHANA.
Yuji: WHAT--
WHAT HAPPENED?
( gasps )
I-- WHAT?!
- ( gasps )
- Yuji: WHAT THE HECK
JUST HAPPENED?
- ( gasps, screams )
NO!
( whimpers )
- KEEP IT TOGETHER.
- SHANA.
- Alastor: YUJI SAKAI,
WHAT HAVE YOU DONE?
- SO THIS IS MY FAULT?
- ANSWER HIM.
WHAT DID YOU DO TO CAUSE THIS?
- WHAT DID--
WELL, I FOUND AN OLD BLACK
TELESCOPE LOOKING THING,
BUT ALL I DID WAS
LOOK AT YOU THROUGH IT.
- ALASTOR?
- HMM.
AN OLD BLACK TELESCOPE,
YOU SAY.
IT MUST BE A RESHUFFLE.
- UHH.
- Alastor:
AS YOU'VE JUST DISCOVERED,
IT IS A TREASURE TOOL
WHICH TRANSPOSES
THE CONSCIOUSNESS
OF THE LOOKER AND
THE LOOKIE.
- IT IS...
MY FAULT.
- Alastor: FEAR NOT.
THIS CAN BE REVERSED.
ALL YOU NEED DO IS PEER THROUGH
THE SPY GLASS AGAIN.
- OH, GOOD. THEN THERE SHOULD
BE NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
- NO, NO!
- WHOA!
( grunts )
- WATCH THE HANDS.
YOU-- JERK FACE.
- OH, SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN ANYTHING BY IT.
I JUST-- AAH!
( gasps )
HUH?
( grunts )
- HEY!  WHAT WERE YOU
LOOKING AT RIGHT THERE?
- NOTHING.
I SAW NOTHING.
- ( groans )
- ( whimpers )
STOP IT, SHANA, PLEASE?
- STOP TRYING TO DO
PERVY THINGS TO MY BODY.
- I'M NOT.
YOU'RE OVERREACTING.
- SHUT UP, SHUT UP, SHUT UP!
- SO WE'LL SWITCH BACK
IF WE LOOK THROUGH THAT
THING AGAIN, RIGHT?
LET'S SEARCH FOR IT OVER
WHERE I WAS A MINUTE AGO.
- Alastor: OH MY!
YOU MUST MAKE HASTE.
UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES
CAN PEOPLE DISCOVER
WHAT'S BEFALLEN YOU.
ESPECIALLY OTHER FLAME HAZE.
- WHAT--
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
- YEAH, ALASTOR.  WHY?
- Alastor:
THERE'S NO TIME TO EXPLAIN.
- Sato: YO!
WE GOT THE ICE CREAM.
- Tanaka: A WHOLE BUNCH OF IT,
LIKE SHANA SAID.
WHOA, PRETTY DARK IN HERE.
DID THEY TAKE OFF?
- Sato: HEY!
- WHAT DO WE DO NOW, SHANA?
- START BY NOT SHOWING
WEAKNESS WITH MY FACE.
- YEAH, BUT--
- SUMMON YOGASA.
- WHAT?
- WE'LL GRAB EVERYTHING
IN THAT VICINITY
AND SORT THROUGH IT
SOMEWHERE ELSE.
WELL, ALASTOR?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
- HMM.
- Alastor: FINE.
- LET GO OF YOUR EMOTIONS
AND ENVISION THE POWER
YOU'RE SEEKING.
FOCUS ON THE FORM
AND STRENGTH
OF THE FLAMING-HAIRED,
BLAZING-EYED HUNTER.
AND EMBRACE IT USING
THE POWER WITHIN YOU.
- GUYS, WHERE THE HELL
ARE YOU?
- ICE CREAM'S MELTING--
UHH?!
- UH, HOW MUCH STUFF
SHOULD I PULL IN?
- THAT SHOULD DO.
AND HERE THEY COME.
- ( grunts )
- YEP, THEY'RE DOWN HERE.
WHAT'S UP?
- DUDE, WHY DIDN'T YOU
HOLLER BACK AT US, SAKAI?
- YEAH, SORRY.
GUESS WE COULDN'T HEAR YOU.
- UH, YEAH.
I WAS ASKING SAKAI.
- UM, THAT'S WHAT HE SAID...
A SECOND AGO, RIGHT?
- UM, RIGHT, YES.
THAT'S WHAT I WAS SAYING.
- IS THERE SOMETHING
WRONG WITH YOU TWO?
- OH, NO.
OF COURSE NOT.
( chuckles )
I'M GOOD OLD YUJI SAK--
- REALLY, NOTHING WRONG HERE.
SHUT UP, SHUT UP, SHUT UP.
- IF YOU'RE GONNA SAY IT,
SAY IT RIGHT.
- YEAH, WHATEVER.
NICE LAUGH BY THE WAY.
- OH, THAT IS EXACTLY
HOW YOU LAUGH.
- IS THAT REALLY
HOW YOU THINK OF ME?
- SO WHAT DID HAPPEN
TO YOU GUYS?
- ( both chuckle )
NOTHING.
- ( Alastor clears throat )
- ALASTOR,
SHED SOME LIGHT HERE?
- I JUST RECALLED
AN URGENT MATTER.
SHANA, YUJI?
- RIGHT, THAT.
WE'D BETTER BE OFF THEN.
- GOTTA RUN, BOYS.
SEE YOU.
- YEAH, BYE.
SEE YOU?
- ( grunts )
- WOW. WAY TO BE GRACEFUL.
JEEZ.
- DON'T YELL AT ME.
I'M NOT USED TO WALKING
IN THESE SHOES.
- SHUT UP, SHUT UP, SHUT UP!
JUST TRY TO BE MORE CAREFUL.
- LET'S GO SEE IF
MARGERY'S HOME YET.
- BUT THEY...
TOOK ALL THE ICE CREAM.
- YEAH SO, WE'D BETTER
SWITCH OURSELVES BACK
PRETTY SOON.
KNOW ANYWHERE WE CAN
GO THROUGH ALL THAT
STUFF WE COLLECTED?
- CAN'T WE JUST
CAST A SEAL?
- NO WAY.
WILHELMINA AND THE
CHANTER OF ELEGIES
WILL TOTALLY SENSE IT
AND FIGURE OUT WHAT'S UP.
THE LARGEST ROOM
WHERE NO ONE
WILL BOTHER US.
- WHAT ABOUT A KARAOKE BOOTH?
- KARAOKE?
- THEY HAVE A PARTY ROOM,
PLENTY OF PRIVACY,
AND MORE IMPORTANTLY,
THEY HAVE A.C.
- Margery: WELL, WELL.
A BOY AND HIS MIDGET.
- CHANTER OF ELEGIES.
- WHERE ARE YOU OFF TO
IN SUCH A RUSH?
- UH... WE'RE--
I MEAN...
IT'S NONE OF YOUR CONCERN,
SO JUST BUTT OUT.
- ( chuckles )
SULLEN AND UNATTRACTIVE
AS ALWAYS.
- Marcosias: ( laughs )
OH YEAH,
THAT'S WHAT SHE WANTS.
APPROVAL FROM SOMEONE
WHO'S DRUNK OFF HER ROCKER
BEFORE IT'S EVEN NOON-- OW!
- SHUT UP, STUPID MARCO.
- BY THE WAY, YOUR SIDEKICKS
ARE WAITING FOR YOU
AT FRIAGNE'S OLD HIDEOUT.
- OH, I KNOW.
DON'T YOU WORRY.
I'LL CATCH UP TO THEM
AS SOON AS I DOWN THIS
LAST BEER.
- Marcosias: HEY, YEAH!
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
YOU CAN'T BE DONE
TREASURE HUNTING YET.
- SOMETHING CAME UP.
SEE YOU.
- Marcosias:
WHAT IS UP WITH THEM?
- ( sighs )  BARKEEP,
I'M READY FOR A REFILL.
- WAIT.  COME ON!
- WE REALLY CANNOT AFFORD
ANY MORE DISTRACTIONS, OKAY?
YOU ALMOST BLEW IT BACK THERE.
- YEAH, SORRY.
- STOP LOOKING WEAK
WITH MY FACE.
YUM.
I LOVE ICE CREAM.
- HOW CAN YOU BE SMILING
AFTER EATING ALL THAT?
THERE WAS SO MUCH.
- FORGET THAT.
THINK OF SOMEWHERE WE CAN GO.
- WE NEED A LARGISH ROOM,
PREFERABLY OUT OF THE WAY,
SO NO ONE WILL BOTHER US.
- WHAT'S GONNA BE
EMPTY ON A SUNDAY?
- ( both sigh )
- YEAH, OF COURSE!
IT'S PERFECT.
- NOT A BAD IDEA, YUJI.
- SHOULDN'T BE ANYONE
HERE ON SUNDAY.
( yelps )
- SHANA, SAKAI, HEY.
- OH, HEY, YOU GUYS.
- GOOD MORNING,
SAKAI AND SHANA.
- OH, GOOD.
I WAS WORRIED I WAS GONNA
BE THE ONLY GUY HERE.
- YEAH, IT'S A HOME GAME
AND WE WERE THE ONLY ONES
WHO BOTHERED TO SHOW UP.
WE WERE JUST FIGURING OUT
WHAT TO DO.
- YEAH, UM...
SO WHAT'S GOING ON?
- UH, OGATA HAS A BIG
VOLLEYBALL GAME TODAY.
WE INVITED YOU TO
COME CHEER HER ON.
- UHH...
- WE'LL JUST HAVE TO
CHEER EXTRA LOUD.
RIGHT, SAKAI?
- OH, UM... SURE.
- OH?
- THIS IS EXCELLENT.
THE TEAM WILL BE SO EXCITED
THAT YOU WERE ABLE
TO MAKE IT TODAY.
- YEAH, COME DOWN TO
THE GYM WITH US.
- YOU SEE, I--
- SORRY,
WE'LL CATCH UP LATER.
- ( gasps )
- ( grunts )
- UHH, HEY.
THEY AREN'T HEADING OFF ALONE
TO ONE OF THE EMPTY CLASSROOMS,
ARE THEY?
- ( gasps )
- ( panting )
- FASTER, YUJI.
COME ON.
- I-- I'M--
I'M TRYING.
- Yuji: WHOA.  HOW DOES
SHANA RUN SO FAST WITH
THIS TINY STRIDE?
- ( screaming )
- SAKAI, WHAT THE HELL?!
- WHAT'S WRONG--
( gasps )
- HOLD IT.
DON'T LOOK.
- OH, COME ON. WHAT ARE YOU
COVERING HER EYES FOR?
OKAY, WE'RE SORRY.
WE'RE SORRY!
- ( sighs )
THAT WAS A DISASTER.
- GOING TO THE SCHOOL
WAS YOUR IDEA.
WE SAW PRACTICALLY
EVERYONE WE KNOW THERE.
- I DON'T SEE YOU
COMING UP WITH ANY
BETTER IDEAS.
- AT THIS POINT I THINK
IT'LL BE FASTER TO GO
BACK TO YOUR PLACE.
LET'S HURRY THOUGH.
- ( sighs )
( sighs )
- Yuji: YOU KNOW,
THE SKIRT IS NICE AND COOL,
BUT THE PANTIES ARE FEELING
AWFUL TIGHT.
YEAH, SO HEY,
ON THE BRIGHT SIDE,
WE CAN'T POSSIBLY
RUN INTO ANYONE ELSE,
CAN WE?
- DOUBTFUL.
ALTHOUGH WILHELMINA DID SAY
SHE WAS GOING ON
PATROL TODAY.
- Alastor: REMEMBER,
IF WE DO ENCOUNTER HER,
SHE MUST NOT LEARN
OF YOUR CURRENT SITUATION.
- WELL, YEAH.  YOU TOLD US
THAT PART EARLIER, ALASTOR.
BUT WHY THE BIG SECRET?
HMM? ( gasps )
- YEAH?  WHAT NOW?
( gasps )
- ( slurps )
- MILADY.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE SEARCHING
FOR THE HUNTER'S
TREASURE TOOLS.
- Tiamat: DONE SO SOON?
- WELL, YOU SEE, WE--
- I WAS INDEED
NOT ASKING YOU.
- UH--
- YEAH WELL, IT'S NOT THAT
WE'RE SLACKING OFF.
IT'S THAT WE--
- WORD CHOICE, MORON.
- MORON?
- Tiamat: WORD CHOICE?
- Alastor: UH, WE HAVE
SOME IMPORTANT BUSINESS
TO ATTEND TO, DON'T WE?
LET'S GET A MOVE ON,
YOU TWO.
- YEAH, RIGHT.
IMPORTANT.
- SO WE'LL SEE YOU LATER,
WILHELMINA.
- ( both panting )
- ( gasps )
- Shana: OH NO, WASN'T THINKING.
THAT WAS PURE INSTINCT.
- ( gasps )
- ( grunts )
- WHOA, IS THE CIRCUS IN TOWN?
- SOME KIND OF
STREET PERFORMERS, I GUESS.
- THEY'RE NOT USING GUNS,
ARE THEY?
- Shana: DOUBLE STRIKE.
THAT ONE SHOULD HAVE
TAKEN YUJI OUT.
- ( gasps )
- WE DO NOT HAVE
TIME FOR THIS.
DAMMIT, WILHELMINA.
ALWAYS SO STUBBORN
AND SUSPICIOUS.
- Tiamat: IMPROVED DEFENSES.
- INDEED.  ALTHOUGH,
TOO MUCH FOR EVEN HIM.
ON THE OTHER HAND,
IS IT POSSIBLE YOU'VE
GOTTEN THAT MUCH BETTER?
- WHAT-- WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
- ( breathes deep )
I LOVE YOU SO MUCH!
- UH...
- ( gasps )
- COME ON,
WE GOTTA GO.
- HEY, WHAT DID YOU
HAVE TO GO AND SAY
THAT FOR?
- WELL, IT'S TRUE,
ISN'T IT?
BESIDES, IT WORKED.
- YEAH, IT'S TRUE.
IT'S JUST THAT...
- Tiamat:
A BOLD, BOLD STATEMENT.
- ( panting )
FINALLY, WE'RE HOME.
- DON'T STOP NOW.
LET'S GET INSIDE.
- YEAH.  YOU DON'T
HAVE TO YELL AT ME.
I HAVE TROUBLE RUSHING
IN THIS BODY.
- YOU'RE ONLY TIRED BECAUSE
YOU'RE NOT USING
YOUR POWER OF EXISTENCE
THE RIGHT WAY.
I'M HOME.
- WHATEVER.
WE RAN ALL THIS WAY.
WHY WOULD WE RUSH NOW?
- ( grunts )
- UHH...
- WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING AT?
GET A MOVE ON.
- OKAY.  FINE.
- Yuji:
SHE ALMOST COLLAPSED THERE.
COULD IT BE SOME
KIND OF SIDE EFFECT
OF THE TREASURE TOOL?
IF IT IS...
- Chigusa: OH HEY, YUJI,
YOU'RE HOME.
I THOUGHT YOU KIDS WERE
GONNA BE OUT LATE.
- OUR PLANS CHANGED.
- OH.
LOOK AT YOU, SHANA,
YOU'RE ALL SWEATY.
YOU CAN TAKE
A BATH IF YOU'D LIKE.
- WELL, I'M KIND OF
PRESSED FOR TIME--
( gasps )
YEAH, I DEFINITELY
CAN'T DO THAT TODAY.
- HUH?
- HURRY UP!
- ( gasps )
- HUH.
SHANA,
WHY ARE YOU SO PALE
ALL OF A SUDDEN?
MY BODY CAN'T
HANDLE THE STRAIN
'CAUSE WE HAVEN'T
SWITCHED BACK YET.
ALASTOR, WHY DIDN'T YOU
WARN US ABOUT THIS SOONER?
- Alastor: I--
THERE'S NO REASON.
- Yuji: RESHUFFLE MUST HAVE
SIDE EFFECTS EVEN ALASTOR
DOESN'T KNOW ABOUT.
MAYBE IT ACTS DIFFERENTLY
WHEN A FLAME HAZE USES IT.
JUST TO BE SAFE...
ALASTOR, HEY.
WE'LL SWITCH BACK
IF WE LOOK THROUGH
THE TREASURE TOOL AGAIN,
RIGHT?
- Alastor: UH, YES.
- JUST HANG ON, SHANA.
I'LL FIND IT RIGHT NOW.
( grunts )
RELEASE ITEMS.
- IDIOT!
- ( gasps )
AAH!
- ( crashing )
- HMM?
- ( grunts )
I HAVE COMPLETE CONTROL
OVER YUJI'S BODY RIGHT NOW.
IF I WANTED, I COULD...
- Chigusa: YUJI? SHANA?
- ( gasps )
- WHAT WAS ALL THAT RACKET?
- Shana:
I'M SO STUPID.
THERE'S NO POINT
IF HE DOESN'T DO IT TOO.
- Chigusa: KIDS, YOU OKAY?
- CAST A SEAL.
YUJI.  YUJI, WAKE UP.
- ( groans )
WHAT THE HECK HAPPENED?
( gasps )
SHANA, YOU'RE FEELING OKAY?
- MM-HMM.  IT SEEMS TO
HAVE SUBSIDED FOR NOW.
NOW PUT ALL OF THIS STUFF AWAY
SO WE HAVE SOME ROOM TO MOVE.
- UH. YEAH, RIGHT.
( grunts )
- ( gasps )
( sighs )
- HERE.
- HUH?
- Alastor: EXCELLENT, SHANA.
- QUICK, LET'S SWITCH BACK.
- OKAY. PREPARE YOURSELF, YUJI.
- HUH?
- ( sighs )
( gasps )
BACK TO NORMAL.
- MM-HMM.
AND ALL IS WELL.
- ( stomach growls )
- ( groans )
- ( giggles )
- SHANA, THIS IS--
- I'D MAKE A RUN FOR IT
IF I WERE YOU.
- WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME
THAT'S WHAT WAS WRONG WITH--
( gasps )
MOVE, MA!
( yelps )
- ( laughing )
- Alastor: LET ME GUESS,
IT WAS THE ICE CREAM, RIGHT?
- MM-HMM.
YUJI'S BODY IS TOTALLY WEAK.
HIS STOMACH STARTED CHURNING
AFTER JUST A FEW DOZEN SERVINGS.
- OH, GOOD.
YOU HAD ME WORRIED THERE.
- ( chuckles )
SORRY.
ALL RIGHT.
SO WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
HOW COME NOBODY COULD KNOW
WE'D GOTTEN OUR MINDS
SWITCHED WITH THIS THING?
IT'S NOT LIKE I'D
WANT TO USE IT AGAIN,
BUT I CAN SEE HOW IT MIGHT
COME IN HANDY SOME DAY.
BUT, SINCE FRIAGNE THE HUNTER
NEVER USED IT,
I'M GUESSING THERE HAS TO BE
SOME KIND OF CATCH INVOLVED.
- Alastor: ONCE I TELL YOU,
PROMISE TO DESTROY IT.
I'LL ONLY SAY THIS ONCE.
RESHUFFLE'S EFFECT
ONLY TOOK HOLD
BECAUSE THERE IS NO WALL
BETWEEN YOUR HEARTS.
WE CANNOT LET THE OTHERS
KNOW THAT WALL HAS COME
CRASHING DOWN.
TO BE HONEST, I WAS EVEN
AFRAID TO ADMIT IT MYSELF.
- HMM?
- Alastor: WE COULDN'T DARE
TELL WILHELMINA CARMEL
HOW CLOSE YOU AND YUJI
HAVE BECOME.
LET ALONE
THE CHANTER OF ELEGIES,
AND HER TWO YOUNG FLUNKIES.
- ( gasps )
BUT YUJI AND I DON'T...
( groans )
- Alastor: DO NOT DENY IT
ANYMORE, SHANA.
I'VE TRIED LONG ENOUGH,
BUT WE MUST FACE FACTS.
YOU TWO DID SWITCH PLACES,
AND THAT WAS
THE PREREQUISITE.
- NO WAY.  THERE MUST BE
SOME KIND OF MISTAKE.
- Alastor: WE'RE STILL INSIDE
THE SEAL YOU CAST.
I WOULD SAVE YOUR EXCUSES
FOR THE LADY OF THE HOUSE.
- ( murmurs )
- WHAT ON EARTH
HAPPENED IN HERE?
- WE JUST HAD
A LITTLE FIGHT.
- A LITTLE FIGHT,
AND THIS BIG MESS
IS THE RESULT?
DID YUJI INSTIGATE IT?
DON'T TELL ME
YOU CAUSED ALL THIS.
- I...
YUJI.
IT WAS ALL YUJI'S FAULT.
( sighs )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )