- BAD ASS!
IT'S DEAD ACCURATE.
- LUTZ, GIVE ME A GO.
- CAN'T BELIEVE HOW LIGHT IT IS.
I'VE NEVER SHOT AN XM8 BEFORE--
- Jonah: I STILL HATE WEAPONS
AS MUCH AS I EVER DID.
- Koko: JONAH.
- BUT WHEN I'M WITH KOKO,
IT'S LIKE SHE'S GOT
THIS WEIRD POWER
TO MAKE ME FORGET THAT HATRED
FOR A WHILE.
HERE I AM,
TRAVELING WITH AN ARMS DEALER.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- WHAT'S WITH THE HAT?
YOU DOING SOME GARDENING?
- ( laughs )
GARDENING, ON A SHIP?
WHAT COULD I POSSIBLY
ATTEMPT TO GROW OUT HERE?
I'M SIMPLY DOING
WHAT I CAN TO PROTECT
MY DELICATE COMPLEXION
FROM THIS SUN.
- KOKO,
THE CAPTAIN'S ON THE HORN.
- SHIT, ONE-HANDED?  IMPRESSIVE.
- A FREIGHTER?
IT'S THE ONE I TOLD YOU
ABOUT THIS MORNING.
SOMEONE FROM H.Q. IS COMING
TO MAKE A CARGO TRANSFER.
- ( phone ringing )
- WHO'S THAT?
KOKO HERE!
( gasps ) YEAH.
MMM, AGES.
UH, YOU'RE ON BOARD?
GOT IT.
SEE YA SOON.  CIAO.
- ( phone beeps off )
- SOMETHING THE MATTER?
- FUCK MY LIFE!
MY BIG BROTHER
IS ONBOARD THAT FREIGHTER.
WILEE, WE NEED TO HIDE JONAH.
TAKE HIM BELOW DECKS FOR A
GRAMMAR LESSON OR SOMETHING.
- ROGER THAT.
- WHAT'S KOKO
FREAKED OUT ABOUT NOW?
- NOT SURE.  GUESS SOMETHING
UNEXPECTED HAS COME UP.
IT CAN'T BE TOO BIG A DEAL,
THOUGH.
SHE'S NOT HAVING US GEAR UP.
( laughs )
COME ON,
LET'S GET THIS LESSON STARTED.
- Valmet:
IF I DIDN'T KNOW HE WAS OLDER,
I'D THINK YOU TWO WERE TWINS.
EXCEPT, YOU'RE THE HOTTER ONE,
OF COURSE.
- HEY, KOKO.
- HELLO, KASPER.
- V.L. MICA MISSILES.
WILL THEY SELL?
- HEY.
- THEY ALREADY HAVE.
I JUST NEED TO DELIVER 'EM.
BUT LET'S CUT THE CRAP.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING
HERE IN AFRICA?
- SAME AS YOU.
I HEAR A SPOOK CAUGHT UP TO YOU.
YOU KNOW WHY
THEY CALL HIM SCARECROW, RIGHT?
IT'S ALL ABOUT
WHAT'S NOT BETWEEN HIS EARS.
BIT OF A JOKE, ISN'T HE?
GOOD AT RAISING
UNTRACEABLE FUNDS, THOUGH.
IT'S THE ONLY REASON THE U.S.
STILL PUTS UP WITH HIS CRAP.
BUT BE CAREFUL.
HE'S PERSISTENT,
BRAIN IN HIS HEAD OR NOT.
- YEAH, LIKE I GIVE A DAMN.
"AN ARMS DEALER IS ABLE
TO SEE CONTRADICTIONS
THAT OTHERS MISS."
INTERESTING.
SOUNDS LIKE KOKO, ALL RIGHT.
CONTRADICTION--
AN OPPOSITION BETWEEN THINGS
COMPARED, AN INCONSISTENCY.
NOW WRITE THE WORD
"CONTRADICTION" THREE TIMES.
YOU KNOW, CHINA HAS A RICH
TRADITION OF FOLKLORE.
THEY USE SIMPLE
TALES TO ILLUSTRATE
THE MEANING OF COMPLEX IDEAS.
TAKE, "THE PIKE AND SHIELD."
IT'S A STORY
ABOUT A WEAPONS DEALER.
ONCE UPON A TIME,
A WEAPONS MAKER
GATHERED A CROWD
TO SHOW OFF HIS NEW PIKE.
HE BOASTED THAT IT COULD
PIERCE THROUGH ANYTHING.
NEXT, HE BROUGHT OUT
A SHIELD HE HAD CRAFTED.
HE CLAIMED THAT THE SHIELD
COULD DEFLECT ANY ATTACK.
THEN ONE OF THE ONLOOKERS
ASKED FOR A DEMONSTRATION.
HE SAID, "WHAT IF THE PIKE
IS USED AGAINST THE SHIELD?"
BUT THE CRAFTSMAN
HAD NO ANSWER.
THE END.
GOOD STORY, HUH?
- IF YOU SAY SO.
I'VE DEFINITELY HEARD BETTER.
- IN DUBAI?
THE CHINESE SEEM TO BE
EXPANDING THEIR OPERATIONS
EVERYWHERE, HUH?
WHO'S THIS DEALER ALLIED WITH?
- UNFORTUNATELY,
WE'RE NOT CLEAR ABOUT THAT.
ONE THING WE DO KNOW FOR SURE,
THOUGH,
IS THAT HE'S
NOT A VERY NICE GUY AT ALL.
- I DIDN'T RUN INTO HIM
WHILE I WAS THERE.
- WELL, YOU CERTAINLY WILL
WHILE YOU'RE IN AFRICA.
SO KEEP A SHARP EYE OUT.
HE RUNS THE DA XINGHAI
TRADING COMPANY.
WELL, ON PAPER ANYWAY.
- HMM.  IF YOU'RE WARNING ME
TO WATCH MY BACK,
HE MUST BE
ONE SERIOUS PIECE OF WORK.
- ( laughs )
YEAH,
SO I SHOULD HEAD OUT.
AH, DO YOU MIND IF I USE
THE RESTROOM BEFORE I GO?
- WHAT AM I, YOUR BOSS?
YOU DON'T NEED MY PERMISSION
TO TAKE A PISS.
- YOU'RE A PRETTY DECENT STUDENT
WHEN IT COMES TO LANGUAGES.
BUT TOJO SAYS YOU'RE QUICK
TO SKIP OUT
WHEN IT'S TIME
FOR YOUR MATH LESSONS.
- I'M NOT ANY GOOD AT NUMBERS.
- ( laughs )
I HEAR YA. THEY'RE NOT
MY SPECIALTY, EITHER.
IF YOU'RE ANYTHING LIKE ME,
YOU'LL PREFER READING
BOOKS TO DOING MATH.
YOU KNOW WHAT I
LIKE ABOUT BOOKS?
THEY DON'T HAVE
JUST ONE INTERPRETATION.
DEPENDING ON WHO'S READING TH--
- GOTTA PEE.
- ARE YOU DITCHIN'?
- NO, I REALLY HAVE TO PEE.
- Kasper: BLACK GUY!
LONG TIME.
- KASPER!
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU WERE HERE.
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
IT'S BEEN AGES.
( thinking ) DAMN IT.
THIS IS WHAT SHE MEANT.
BUT IT'S NOT LIKE I CAN TELL HIM
HE CAN'T GO IN THERE.
- HMM.
( unzips pants )
- ( toilet flushes )
- KASPER!
- HELLO TO YOU, TOO, JONAH.
YOU LOOK WELL.
- LET ME GO, CHEQUITA!
- IT TRULY SADDENS ME
TO SEE A BOY AS YOUNG AS YOU
WIELDING A KNIFE.
EVEN MORE DEPRESSING
IS THAT LOOK IN YOUR EYE
TELLS ME YOU HAD EVERY INTENTION
OF USING IT.
I WILL ONLY TELL YOU ONCE.
DROP THE KNIFE.
YOU COULDN'T KILL ANYONE
WITH THIS TOY.
ALL YOU'D ACCOMPLISH IS LOSING
A FEW OF YOUR OWN FINGERS.
TRY USING SOMETHING WITH
A LONG HANDLE AND FULL TANG.
VALMET CAN EXPLAIN
THE DETAILS TO YOU.
- ( laughs )
MAKE UP YOUR MIND.
ARE YOU LECTURING HIM
OR GIVING HIM
PROFESSIONAL ADVICE?
ANYHOW, THAT WAS JUST HIS WAY
OF SAYING "HELLO."
IF JONAH REALLY WANTED
TO ATTACK ME,
I'M SURE
HE WOULD HAVE SUCCEEDED.
HE'S A SOLDIER, AFTER ALL,
EVEN MORE LETHAL NOW
THAN WHEN WE MET.
- DIDN'T KNOW YOU HAD KIDS HERE,
COMMANDER.
- THAT ONE'S A SOLDIER.
WE REQUESTED MORE MEN FROM H.Q.
AND THEY SENT OVER
SOME BRAT FROM THE ALPINE UNIT.
THE OTHER KIDS HERE ARE ORPHANS,
THOUGH.
IN ANY CASE, I ACCEPT
YOUR PROPOSAL, GASUD.
FROM WHAT I HEAR, AN UPCOMING
SHIFT IN NATIONAL POLICY
IS LIKELY TO STEM OUR CURRENT
FLOW OF WEAPON SUPPLIES.
IF THAT HAPPENS, I DON'T SEE
THAT WE HAVE ANY CHOICE
BUT TO TURN TO THE WEST
FOR THE ARMS WE NEED.
- MY THOUGHTS EXACTLY.
- HOWEVER-- AND I WANT
TO MAKE THIS PERFECTLY CLEAR--
THE ONLY REASON
I'M MOVING FORWARD ON THIS
IS BECAUSE OF HOW LONG
YOU'VE WORKED UNDER
THE ILLUSTRIOUS KASPER.
ARRANGE A MEETING
WITH HIM FOR ME.
- THAT SHOULDN'T BE A PROBLEM.
KASPER HAS HAD A KEEN INTEREST
IN YOUR COUNTRY FOR SOME TIME.
WELL, SHALL WE?
I'M AFRAID THAT MY "BAGGAGE"
IS STUCK
IN AN UNFORTUNATE LOCATION.
- I UNDERSTAND.
- Jonah:
THIS YASUF GASUD GUY--
WHO IS HE, REALLY?
I DON'T BUY HIM AS A JOURNALIST.
THE VICE COMMANDER'S COMING!
MALKA, HIDE THE FOOD!
- LET'S SEE IF YOU BRATS
ARE GOOD FOR ANYTHING
BUT EATIN' MY FOOD.
YOU AND YOU--
COME WITH ME.
GO.
- Both: SIR!
- ( children crying )
- HE HAS EVIL IN HIS EYES.
HOLD ON!
I'LL COME TOO.
- SILENCE!
YOU'LL DO AS YOU'RE TOLD.
DO NOT QUESTION ME, EVER!
- SHOULDN'T WE BE GOING?
- DAMN KID CAN'T FOLLOW
A SIMPLE ORDER.
- JONATHAN!
- Jonah: THAT WAS IT.
MY FINAL GLIMPSE OF MALKA.
I NEVER SAW HER AGAIN.
- ( crying )
MALKA, MALKA.
I'M SORRY.
I SHOULD HAVE GONE WITH YOU.
I SHOULD HAVE FOUGHT HARDER.
I KNOW WHAT THEY DID.
I KNOW.
THEY MADE YOU
WALK THROUGH AN OLD MINEFIELD.
MALKA, MALKA.
DAMN IT, YOU DESERVED BETTER!
MAURICE,
LISTEN TO ME VERY CAREFULLY.
I NEED YOU TO TAKE ALL THE
CHILDREN TO OUR SECRET BASE.
DON'T LEAVE, NO MATTER WHAT.
- AH!
HEY, YOU!
- ( machine gunfire )
- Jonah: NO MATTER WHAT.
- Man: WE'RE UNDER ATTACK!
- WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- I'M NOT SURE! UNKNOWN ENEMY.
- HURRY!
- HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON
OUT THERE?
- ( gunshots )
- WHERE'S THE SHOOTER?!
- HOLD FIRE!
YOU'RE SHOOTING BLIND.
YOU'LL HIT EACH OTHER!
- IT SOUNDS LIKE
THE FIGHTING'S GETTING CLOSER.
- KEEP QUIET.
- WHO THE HELL IS OUT THERE?
WHY CAN'T ANYONE GET A VISUAL
ON THE ENEMY SHOOTERS?
- KEEP IT DOWN!
- ( gunfire )
- ( shell clanging )
- HEY!  I GOT ONE.
- I WILL AVENGE YOU, MALKA.
- SOMEONE GIVE ME
A STATUS REPORT.
MEN, DO YOU COPY?
WHAT'S THE SITUATION?
- ( gunfire )
- HAVE YOU IDENTIFIED THE ENEMY?
YOU FAT--
- ( gun cocks )
- Jonah: YOU'RE NO JOURNALIST.
WHO ARE YOU?
- I'M--
I'M AN ARMS DEALER.
EASY THERE.
YOU CAN SPARE ONE LIFE,
CAN'T YOU?
IF YOU DO-- I KNOW--
YOU CAN HAVE THIS.
ALL OF IT!
- I DON'T WANT YOUR MONEY.
GIVE ME MALKA.
- UH, MALKA?
WHAT'S A MALKA?
- ( fires )
- MAURICE,
LOOK AFTER THE KIDS.
- ( cocks gun )
- SOMETHING'S THERE.
SHARP AND VIOLENT.
WOLVES?
NO, NOT ANIMALS.
PEOPLE.
MEN FROM THE BASE?
NO, DOESN'T FEEL LIKE THEM.
BUT I'M SURROUNDED.
( coughing )
- Chequita ( filtered ):
HELLO THERE, LITTLE SOLDIER BOY.
CLEAR!
NOT BAD.
YOU'VE GOT GOOD INSTINCTS.
JUST LIKE A MISHKA--
A LITTLE BEAR CUB.
- Man: FROM A QUICK SURVEY
OF THE SCENE,
IT LOOKS LIKE THIS KID
ATTACKED THE ENTIRE UNIT
JUST TO KILL GASUD.
RENDERED THE WHOLE
DAMN BASE INOPERABLE.
- Chequita: IMPRESSIVE.
- MY NAME IS KASPER HEKMATYAR.
I'M AN ARMS DEALER.
WHO ARE YOU?
I DON'T SEE YOU
IN THESE RECORDS.
YOU AREN'T LISTED AMONG THE
SOLDIERS OR THE FOUR ORPHANS.
- IT'S NOT HARD, MISHKA.
HE'S JUST ASKING YOUR NAME.
GO ON.
- THREE.
THERE ARE
ONLY THREE ORPHANS NOW.
THAT BASTARD GASUD
KILLED MALKA.
- I SEE.
SO THAT'S WHAT STARTED ALL THIS.
WELL, HOW DO YOU FEEL?
SATISFIED?
YOU GOT REVENGE
FOR YOUR FRIEND.
AND ALL YOU HAD TO DO
WAS KILL EVERYONE ON THE BASE.
I GET IT-- YOU COULDN'T
LET ANYONE STOP YOU
BEFORE YOU REACHED YOUR TARGET,
SO YOU MADE A PREEMPTIVE STRIKE.
'CAUSE WHAT GOOD
CAN YOU DO IF YOU'RE DEAD?
LITTLE BACK STORY
SO YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN--
BOTH MY YOUNGER SISTER AND I
WERE BORN ON A CONTAINER SHIP
OUT AT SEA, SPENT OUR
CHILDHOODS BOUNCING
FROM COUNTRY TO COUNTRY.
I HAVE FAKE PASSPORTS FROM
EVERY NATION UNDER THE SUN.
BUT WITH NO REAL HOMELAND,
I HAVE NO CONCEPT OF PATRIOTISM.
THAT'S THE SCARY THING.
EVEN I FIND YOUR ACTIONS TODAY
A LITTLE ABHORRENT.
ALL THAT DEATH FOR ONE
TINY GIRL. PRETTY SICK.
EVEN SO, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I WOULD HAVE SUGGESTED
THAT YOU DO DIFFERENTLY.
NO SURPRISE THERE.
EVERY BATTLEFIELD'S
FULL OF UNANSWERED QUESTIONS.
ANYWAY, WORKED OUT FOR ME.
HMM.
IT'S JUST ONE LESS SUBORDINATE
WHO CAN'T DO HIS JOB PROPERLY.
I WASN'T ACTUALLY TRYING TO
SELL THEM WEAPONS, YOU KNOW.
I WAS SEDUCING THEM,
LULLING THEM INTO COMPLACENCY.
LOOK, THERE ARE PLANS
FOR THE CONSTRUCTION
OF A MILITARY ROAD
THAT WILL SPAN THE NATION.
THIS BASE WAS SIMPLY IN
THE WAY OF THOSE PLANS.
ONCE IT'S FINISHED,
MASSIVE AMOUNTS OF OIL,
WEAPONS, AND SOLDIERS
WILL FLOW DOWN THAT ROAD.
AS A RESULT,
THE ENTIRE COUNTRY WILL PROSPER.
- A ROAD?
MALKA DIED
SO THEY COULD BUILD A ROAD?
- ( thinking )
NAMELESS CHILD SOLDIER,
I KNOW THAT ANGER
HAS MADE YOU STRONG.
I ALSO KNOW IT'S NOT IN YOUR
NATURE TO ENJOY VIOLENCE.
BUT WHAT ABOUT FEAR?
( aloud ) YOU HAVE TO ANSWER
FOR KILLING MY EMPLOYEE.
I'M CURIOUS, HOW WILL YOU ACT
WHEN THE ENEMY YOU FACE IS FEAR?
- WAIT, HOLD ON!
ARE YOU GOING TO KILL THEM?
THE OTHER CHILDREN?
KASPER!
AH!
THERE WAS NOTHING
IN THE CONTAINER BUT WATER.
BEFORE LONG,
I WAS TOO HUNGRY TO MOVE.
I THOUGHT A LOT ABOUT MALKA,
ABOUT WHAT KASPER HAD SAID,
AND WHAT I HAD DONE.
ALONE IN A BOX
FOR WHO KNEW HOW LONG.
I WAS AFRAID IF I DIDN'T KEEP
MY MIND WORKING, I'D GO CRAZY.
- Koko: YOU'RE STILL HERE?
WHAT THE HELL
DO YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING?
TWO GROWN ADULTS
PICKING ON JONAH?  PATHETIC!
LEAVE, KASPER.
OFF MY SHIP NOW!
- QUIT SHOVING!
- COME ON, MOVE YOUR ASS!
- MY MY,
YOU'RE STILL ALIVE, OLD MAN?
YOU SHOULD RETIRE.
- CHEQUITA.
THRILLING TO SEE
THAT YOU'RE AS POLITE AS EVER.
- GO EASY ON HIS ANCIENT ASS,
MISHKA.
- HEY, STOP KICKING.
YOU'RE GONNA PUSH ME OVERBOARD.
- KASPER, I SWEAR,
SOME DAY I WILL GET YOU BACK.
- RIGHT, JONAH.
SEE YA.
- YOU KNOW HE LOCKED ME
INSIDE A SHIPPING CONTAINER
FOR DAYS WITHOUT ANY FOOD.
- Koko: I KNOW.
I'M REALLY SORRY.
HE'S ALWAYS BEEN LIKE THAT.
- Jonah: WHAT I DID AT THAT BASE
WAS TERRIBLE.
I'M BETTER AT TAKING LIVES
THAN SAVING THEM.
I DON'T LIKE THAT.
AS I WAS STARVING TO DEATH,
I KEPT ASKING MYSELF,
"DOES THE WORLD REALLY HATE ME
THIS MUCH?"
BUT THEN I REALIZED
THAT DIDN'T REALLY MATTER.
THE WORLD MAY HATE ME,
BUT I STILL LOVE IT.
DO YOU?
- I DON'T THINK
I CAN ANSWER THAT.
SO SORRY.
- NO, IT'S OKAY.
YOU PRETTY MUCH JUST DID.
I HATE THAT I HAVE TO
TAKE SUCH GOOD CARE OF YOU.
UNFORTUNATELY,
IF YOU RUST, I DIE.
- JONAH? UH...
THAT'S STRANGE.
WHERE'D HE GO?
IT'S TIME
FOR HIS SCIENCE LESSON.
- JONAH, HAVE YOU SEEN
THE BOSS LADY AROUND?
I HEAR
SHE'S BEEN LOOKING FOR ME.
ALL RIGHT.  WELL,
MAYBE SHE'S UP FRONT SOMEWHERE.
OH, YEAH, MAO WANTED TO KNOW
WHERE YOU'D RUN OFF TO.
- SO?
- THAT'S IT?
- Tojo: YOU STILL
HAVEN'T FOUND JONAH?
( laughs )
YOU DO REALIZE HE'S HIDING
FROM YOU, DON'T YOU?
JUST LIKE HE DOES TO ME
WHEN IT'S TIME FOR MATH LESSONS.
- TOJO'S PROBABLY RIGHT.
- OF COURSE I AM.
THE KID'S TERRIBLE
AT THE SCIENCES.
HE'S A PRO WHEN IT COMES
TO PLAYING HOOKY, THOUGH.
IF HE'S SERIOUS ABOUT HIDING,
YOU DON'T STAND A CHANCE.
- NICE.  WHAT IS IT?
- IT'S A VOLKS-
SOMETHING-OR-OTHER.
UM, OUR NEW CAR!
ORCHESTRA TRASHED
THE UNIT'S OLD RIDE,
SO I THOUGHT
I SHOULD GET US A NEW ONE.
YOUR QUICK THINKING
BEHIND THE WHEEL
REALLY HELPED US BACK THERE.
SERIOUSLY,
YOU'VE GOT SOME MAJOR SKILLS.
KEEP UP THE GOOD WORK, BUDDY.
- IT'S AMAZING.
THANK YOU.
BEST BOSS EVER.
- OH, HAVE YOU SEEN JONAH?
- OH, YEAH, I PASSED
BY HIM JUST A MINUTE AGO.
- Lehm:
WE'LL BE IN AFRICA A WHILE.
- YEAH, SO, WHAT OF IT?
YOU GOT SOMETHING YOU WANT
TO SAY TO ME? SPEAK UP.
- NOT REALLY.
I CAN'T SMOKE INSIDE,
SO I THOUGHT I'D ENJOY
THE VIEW ABOVE DECKS.
YOU JUST HAPPENED TO BE HERE.
THERE'S NO REASON
TO GET SO EDGY.
YOU WENT THROUGH A HELL
OF A LOT IN THIS PLACE.
I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW
I'LL HAVE YOUR BACK.
AND I'M SURE KOKO
FEELS THE SAME WAY.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
MY SCAR WAS JUST ACHING
A LITTLE BIT
WHEN WE DROPPED ANCHOR EARLIER.
THAT'S ALL.
GRANTED, I'LL NEVER FORGET
WHAT HAPPENED
WHILE I WAS STATIONED HERE.
BUT I'LL BE JUST FINE, LEHM.
I CAN HANDLE IT.
ALTHOUGH, I WOULDN'T PROTEST
IF KOKO OFFERED ME
A COMFORTING EMBRACE!
KOKO!  I NEED YOU
TO MAKE ME FEEL BETTER!
KOKO!
- THAT'S ONE WEIRD CHICK.
- PERFECT.
THIS SHOULD BE
MY SECRET HIDING PLACE.
- Kasper: YOU KNOW SOMETHING--
WE'LL NEVER SEE EYE TO EYE,
YOU AND ME.
I SEE WHY YOU'RE SO STRONG,
A BOY SOLDIER
FROM THE ALPINE UNIT.
I TOOK THE PRIVILEGE
OF LOOKING INTO YOU.
IT'S THE DAMNDEST THING.
TURNS OUT I WAS THE ONE
WHO SUPPLIED WEAPONS
TO THE MEN
WHO TARGETED YOUR VILLAGE.
SO INDIRECTLY, AT LEAST,
I'M THE ONE WHO
KILLED YOUR PARENTS.
- YOU BASTARD!
- HAVE YOU GROWN TOO WEAK
TO TEAR AWAY MY FLESH?
OR ARE YOU HOLDING BACK?
- ( sobbing )
- SEE?
THAT'S WHAT FEAR DOES TO YOU.
YOU SAT IN HERE FOR DAYS,
FEARING YOUR DEATH,
UNTIL YOU FINALLY FIGURED OUT
WHERE YOU REALLY
STAND IN THE WORLD.
YOU HAD TO DECIDE
WHICH WAS THE BETTER COURSE--
KILLING ME OR USING ME.
VERY WELL.
LET'S NEGOTIATE.
YOU SEE, I LIKE PEOPLE
WHO KNOW THEIR PLACE.
SO I'M CERTAIN
WE CAN ARRIVE AT TERMS
THAT ARE FAVORABLE FOR US BOTH.
- THE OTHER KIDS.
WHERE ARE THEY?
- HMM!
THEY'RE IN MY CUSTODY.
- SEND THEM SOMEPLACE SAFE,
SOMEWHERE THEY CAN BE HAPPY.
- MY TERRITORY RUNS FROM HERE
THROUGH MOST OF ASIA.
I'M SURE I CAN SET
THEM UP WITH GOOD HOMES
IN JAPAN OR SOMEWHERE.
CONSIDER IT DONE.
NOW WHAT DO YOU HAVE
TO OFFER ME?
- I HAVE NOTHING TO TRADE.
- NOT TRUE.
YOU HAVE YOUR SKILL
AS A SOLDIER.
YOU'D WORK WELL
AS A PERSONAL SECURITY GUARD.
SOUND GOOD?
GREAT.
THEN WE HAVE A DEAL.
THE SISTER I MENTIONED
HAS A PLACE FOR YOU.
NOW I ALREADY KNOW THE ANSWER,
BUT I WANT TO HEAR IT FROM YOU.
WHAT IS YOUR NAME?
- MY NAME IS--
- YOU'RE JONATHAN MAR.
THAT RIGHT?
IT'S A PLEASURE TO MEET YOU,
JONAH.
I'M KOKO HEKMATYAR.
THAT'S A FROSTY GLARE
IF I'VE EVER SEEN ONE.
DON'T YOU WORRY.
I'LL MELT THAT ICE.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ CONTROL, CONTROL ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS LOCO ♪
♪ I SAID, OH NO! ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS LOCO ♪
♪ I SAID, OH NO! ♪