- ( gunfire )
- Man: WHAT, THAT'S IT?
AW, THIS PIECE OF CRAP BARELY
OFFERED UP ANY RESISTANCE.
A TRUE VIRTUOSO NEEDS A GOOD
CHALLENGE TO PROVE HIS TALENT.
- YOU OUTPLAYED THEM, MAESTRO.
- OF COURSE.
THESE PHILISTINES DON'T KNOW
THE FIRST THING
ABOUT THE MUSICALITY
OF GUNFIRE.
SO YOU HIGH-TAILED IT ALL
THE WAY FROM ITALY ONLY TO LAND
IN A DESERT IN THE MIDDLE OF--
THE FUCK ARE WE, CHINATSU?
- MIDDLE EAST.
SOMEWHERE IN OMAN, I THINK.
- YOU KNOW WHAT I THOUGHT
WHEN I WAS HUNTING YOU?
"THESE GUYS MAY BE IDIOTS,
BUT THEY'RE PACKING
AND THEY KNOW HOW TO FIGHT.
THE MUSIC OF OUR ENCOUNTER IS
GONNA BE AN EPIC CONCERT
WORTHY OF LEGEND."
BUT, MAN, WAS I WRONG.
MY EX-WIFE USED TO PUT UP
A BETTER FIGHT THAN THIS.
- YOU'RE ORCHESTRA--
- GO ON, CHINATSU.  ASK HIM.
- HUH?  ASK WHAT?
- WHAT DO YOU THINK?
I WANNA KNOW HOW A MAFIA
LIEUTENANT THINKS HE CAN STEAL
FROM HIS BOSS
AND GET AWAY WITH IT.
HE HAD TO KNOW HIS NAME
WOULD GET ON A HIT LIST
AFTER THE SHIT HE PULLED.
- RIGHT.  YOU HEARD THE MAN.
YOU KNEW HOW THIS WOULD END, BUT
YOU WENT THROUGH WITH IT ANYWAY.
WHY?  WE'D LIKE TO KNOW.
- BITCH HAS PSYCHO EYES.
( laughs ) FUNNY STORY.
I DON'T REMEMBER.
NOW THEN,
YOU TELL ME SOMETHING.
- HUH?
- WHAT THE HELL'S
WITH GOING COMMANDO?
DO YOU GET SOME SORT OF
SICK THRILL OUT OF THIS?
I SWEAR, ALL HIT MEN
ARE BAT-SHIT INSANE.
FUCK YOURSELF.
- I GUESS HE DOESN'T WANT
TO ANSWER OUR QUESTION.
TOO BAD.  YOU'RE THE ONE WHO'S
GETTING SCREWED, THOUGH, PAL,
AND DON'T EXPECT ME
TO BE GENTLE.
YOU SEE,
WE'RE GETTING PAID EXTRA
TO MAKE SURE YOU SUFFER.
- YOU POOR FOOL.
YOU THOUGHT YOU'D GET AWAY,
BUT THERE ARE ALWAYS PEOPLE
LIKE US AROUND TO PUNISH BOYS
WHO STICK THEIR HANDS
IN THE COOKIE JAR.
- ( grunts )
YOU'RE NUTS, BOTH OF YOU.
- YOU KNOW WHAT THIS IS?
IT'S KIND OF LIKE A MUSIC BOX
MY PARTNER HERE'S GREAT
AT MAKING THIS SORT OF THING.
- BANG.  BANG-BANG.
THIS BABY'LL FIRE ALL OF ITS
BULLETS RIGHT IN THE SAME SPOT.
THERE WON'T BE VERY MUCH OF YOU
LEFT BY THE TIME IT'S DONE.
- YOU BASTARDS.
I'LL KILL YOU!
WAIT, THE JOKE'S OVER.
- SEE YA.
- YOU CAN'T DO THAT!
ORCHESTRA, GET BACK HERE
AND TURN THIS THING OFF.
I'M SURE WE CAN MAKE
SOME KIND OF A DEAL.
( screaming )
- AT LEAST HE'S GOT A BETTER
SINGING VOICE THAN I EXPECTED.
- SO WHAT DO WE HAVE NEXT
ON THE PLAY LIST?
- WHILE WE'RE HERE, LET'S SEE
ABOUT ANOTHER JOB IN THE AREA.
- THINK WE CAN?
- SURE, SPRING'S A GOOD TIME
TO BE A HIT MAN.  PEOPLE LIKE
TO GET THEIR BUSINESS OVER WITH
BEFORE THE WEATHER GETS
TOO WARM.
- SOUNDS GOOD.
- OH, AND BY THE WAY,
WHY AREN'T YOU WEARING
ANY UNDERWEAR?
- MY SECRET.
WANNA TAKE A PEEK?
- YOU COULD TAKE IT ALL OFF
AND I STILL WOULDN'T CARE
FEW YEARS AND MAYBE YOU'LL HAVE
SOME ASSETS WORTH LOOKING AT.
COME ON,
LET'S HEAD FOR THE CITY.
- TOTALLY.
- ( theme music playing )
- YOU THINK ALL YOU NEED
TO KNOW TO DO YOUR JOB
IS WHERE TO SHOOT,
BUT THERE'S A LOT MORE
WE EXPERIENCED ADULTS
CAN TEACH YOU. FOR STARTERS,
THERE'S GENERAL SOCIAL GRACES,
LIKE GREETING PEOPLE.
THEN, HISTORY,
MATH, SCIENCE,
AND WHATEVER ELSE YOU NEED.
YOU DO HAVE A DECENT GRASP
OF LANGUAGE, AT LEAST.
- ( yawns )
- STOP THAT.
NO YAWNING IN CLASS.  YOU'RE
NOT A CHILD SOLDIER ANYMORE.
YOU'RE A PART OF MY CREW,
AND AS SUCH, I EXPECT YOU
TO TAKE YOUR STUDIES SERIOUSLY.
NOW GRANTED, MY GUYS AREN'T
REALLY WHAT YOU'D CALL SCHOLARS,
BUT REGARDLESS, THERE'S PLENTY
THEY CAN TEACH YOU.
- GOOD.  SO LET'S GIVE THE NEXT
PROBLEM A TRY, ALL RIGHT, JONAH?
- AROUND 300 I GUESS.
- "I GUESS" DOESN'T
REALLY CUT IT IN MATH.
- UM, YEAH, I DIDN'T REALIZE HOW
SHODDY YOUR EDUCATION HAD BEEN
TILL THE OTHER DAY.
- THAT PLANE'S GOT A LOT
OF WHEELS.
- TWENTY-TWO, TO BE EXACT.
SO THEN SAY THERE ARE
THREE PLANES LINED UP,
HOW MANY WHEELS
ARE THERE TOTAL?
- UH, WHY'S HE TAKING
SO LONG TO ANSWER?
- A BUNCH.
- ( laughing )
- KOKO,
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKING AT?
- OH, THIS?
IT'S A LIST OF HIT MEN.
HQ KEEPS US UPDATED
ON ANY POTENTIAL THREATS
THAT ARE IN THE AREA.
'COURSE, THIS IS JUST THE TIP
OF THE ASSASSIN ICEBERG.
WE SHOULDN'T HAVE MUCH TO WORRY
ABOUT IN THIS CITY, THOUGH.
THEY'RE REALLY GOOD WHEN IT
COMES TO KEEPING PEOPLE IN LINE.
BESIDES, I'VE GOT MY BRAVE
MINIONS PROTECTING ME.
- A TWO-PERSON TEAM
CALLED ORCHESTRA?
- YEAH, SEVEN OF THE ORIGINAL
EIGHT MEMBERS ARE DEAD,
BUT THE LEADER JUST PICKED UP
A NEW RECRUIT,
SO NOW THERE'S TWO AGAIN.
IN ITS PRIME,
ORCHESTRA WAS A SERIOUS THREAT.
THEY ONCE SHOT 20,000 ROUNDS
AT A POLICE SQUAD IN FRANCE.
- SO ARE ANY OF THESE HIT MEN
AFTER YOU?
- OF COURSE.  IN THIS BUSINESS,
ENEMIES ARE A GIVEN.
AS A MATTER OF FACT,
I'VE GOT SO MANY...
- Both: WE'D MAKE A KILLING
IF THEY WERE OUR CLIENTS.
- ( laughing )
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
I THOUGHT JONAH WAS STUDYING.
SCHOOL ISN'T SUPPOSED TO BE FUN,
YOU KNOW?
- YOU'RE NOT HELPING, LUTZ.
THE REST OF YOU, ARE YOU GONNA
WASTE YOUR DAY OFF BEING LAZY?
- HEY, WE'VE EARNED
A LITTLE R AND R.
- ARE YOU BORED HERE?  I COULD
SO TAKE YOU OUT ON THE TOWN.
- OKAY.  WELL, I WOULD LIKE
TO SHOW JONAH AROUND THE CITY,
BUT, NO, MATH COMES FIRST.
GOOD LUCK, BOY.
- SORRY, TOJO,
YOU'RE STUCK HERE.
BUT I'LL BRING BACK SOME
LOCAL BEER FOR YOUR TROUBLE.
- COOL.
- ALL RIGHT, I'LL SEE YOU LATER.
JONAH, BE SURE TO THANK YOUR
TEACHER WHEN THE LESSON'S OVER.
- NOW--
- GOTTA PEE.
- ( sighs )
YO.
WHAT?
THAT LITTLE SHIT!
THE KID KNOWS HOW
TO MAKE A GETAWAY.
I GUESS WE'RE ALL GONNA
HAVE TO STAY ON OUR TOES.
OTHERWISE, HE'S GONNA
BE TAKING US TO SCHOOL.
- ( speaks Italian )
- HMM?  WHAT'S WITH THE RANDOM
SWITCH TO ITALIAN?
- AND ANOTHER THING
WHAT'S WITH THE LAME-ASS HAT?
IT'S BLOCKING YOUR VISION.
LOSE IT NOW.
- HOW CAN I THROW THIS AWAY
WHEN YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO GAVE IT TO ME?
YOU LOOK AT THE SKY WHEN YOU
WALK.  I LOOK AT THE GROUND.
THAT WAY, I CAN BE DOUBLE-SURE
YOU'RE SAFE.  HUH?
WHAT A CUTIE.
LOOK AT THAT BOY WITH THE SILVER
HAIR, SO ADORBS.
THERE, SEE?
- AWW, HE'S GONE.
- DON'T LOSE FOCUS.
WE SHOULD HAVE A VISUAL
ON THE TARGET ANY MINUTE.
- MMM!  THAT IS A BEAUTY.
I JUST LOVE DUTY-FREE
COUNTRIES.
- MOST GIRLS KOKO'S AGE WOULD BE
DROOLING LIKE THIS
OVER HIGH-END CLOTHES OR MAKEUP.
THEY'D GET EXCITED
ABOUT A PRETTY WATCH,
BUT NOT ONE THAT'S
SO PRACTIC--
- SOLD!
- I KNOW.
WHY DON'T I BUY IT AS
A PRESENT FOR YOU?
- I CAN'T LET YOU DO THAT.
- IT WILL COMMEMORATE
OUR OUTING TOGETHER.
MY WAY OF SHOWING
HOW MUCH I CARE.
- OH, REALLY?  ARE YOU SURE?
- YEAH, ABSOLUTELY.
SHE'S GENUINELY EXCITED.
SCORE!
- YOU MAKE YOUR LIVING
AS AN ARMS DEALER.
SOMEDAY YOUR CAREER CHOICE
WILL GET YOU KILLED.
TELL ME, WHY DO YOU DO IT?
- AN ASSASSIN QUESTIONING
MY LINE OF WORK?
KILL ME, AND I'LL TELL YOU
WITH MY DYING BREATH, ORCHESTRA.
- BITCH, YOU'RE CRAZY.
LET ME GO.
- GUN!
- KOKO!
- WHOA.  WHAT THE HELL?
- LOOKS LIKE IT'S RAINING
LITTLE BOYS TODAY.
- ( gunfire )
- ( screaming )
- CHINATSU, GET BACK HERE.
TAKE THE ONE WITH THE EYE PATCH.
- SURE THING.
TOO BAD, SO SAD, YOU'RE DEAD.
- KOKO.  KOKO!
- IT HAPPENED SO QUICK,
I CAN'T REALLY BE SURE,
BUT IT WAS THAT SILVER-HAIRED
CUTIE WHO CAME TO HER RESCUE.
WHY WOULD HE PROTECT HER?
PEOPLE LIKE THIS KOKO CHICK
SERIOUSLY PISS ME OFF.
I MEAN, WHO THE FUCK
DOES SHE THINK SHE IS?
- WHAT DO YOU THINK, CHINATSU,
WE REACHING THE CRESCENDO SOON,
OR MAYBE JUST THE REFRAIN?
WHY NOT COME OUT AND PLAY,
LITTLE ARMS DEALER,
AND WE'LL SEE?
YOU PROBABLY AIN'T USED
TO MAKING MUSIC WITH HIT MEN,
BUT WE CAN'T POSSIBLY
STOP THE CONCERT NOW.
- KOKO, WHAT THE HELL
IS WRONG WITH YOU?
- I WANT TO SHOW YOU HOW
IMPRESSED I AM.  GREAT TIMING.
- I'VE SEEN YOU LIKE
THIS BEFORE.
SHIT GOES SIDEWAYS
AND YOU KEEP ON SMILING.
- JONAH!
- BETTER LISTEN TO HER, KID.
NOTHING GOOD WILL COME FROM
SHOOTING ME.
- ( screams )
- YOU'RE FRIGGING NUTS.
- COME HERE.
YOU NEED TO KEEP LOW AND I'M NOT
AS SCREWED UP AS YOU THINK I AM.
LOOK, I'VE BEEN ATTACKED
LIKE THIS SO MANY TIMES,
I DON'T BOTHER COUNTING ANYMORE.
FREAKING OUT'S NOT
GONNA CHANGE ANYTHING.
EITHER I'LL GET SHOT
OR I WON'T.
I CAN'T CONTROL
WHAT HAPPENS TO ME,
BUT I CAN CONTROL HOW I DEAL
WITH THE SITUATION.
BESIDES,
WEAPONS ARE MY LIVELIHOOD.
- ( laughing )
- I'D BE A CRAP BUSINESSWOMAN
IF I WAS SCARED OF
MY OWN MERCHANDISE.
- GOOD THING I CAME PREPARED
TO BLOW HER HEAD OFF.
MY CHINATSU SPECIAL CANNON
OUGHTA DO.
- ( siren wailing )
- FREEZE!  DROP YOUR WEAPONS.
- OOH!
- GET DOWN ON THE GROUND NOW.
- ANOTHER LAYER OF MUSIC.
THIS IS TURNING
INTO A MASTERPIECE.
- YEAH, KIND OF IS.
OH, HEY, MAESTRO, CHECK IT.
COOL, HUH?
- YEAH, NICELY DONE, CHINATSU.
ONTO THE NEXT INSTRUMENT.
- RIGHT.
- KOKO, TELL ME
YOU GUYS ARE OKAY.
- Koko: LOOK OUT!
- OW!  BITCH.
YOU SHOT ME!
- COME ON.
- ONE-EYE, THERE'S A REAL PAIN
IN MY ASS.
- ( grunting ) MOTHERFUCKER.
IT WENT THROUGH.
SERIOUS AMMO.
- VALMET!
YOU'RE HIT.
IS IT BAD?
- I KNEW THERE WAS SOMETHING
FISHY ABOUT THIS LITTLE OUTING.
HOW'D VALMET SCREW THIS UP?
YOU COPY?
WE ARE TAKING FIRE AT THE
OUTDOOR MALL IN THE CITY CENTER.
WE'RE UP AGAINST WHAT'S LEFT
OF THE ORCHESTRA TEAM.
HANDGUNS WON'T DO SHIT.
BRING MY USUAL
AND BE QUICK ABOUT IT.
UH-HUH, THAT ONE.
LUTZ, TAKE THE BELFRY.
BRING WILEE WITH YOU.
COME ON, BOYS, LET'S MOVE IT.
WE DON'T HAVE A LOT OF TIME.
- VALMET.
- SORRY ABOUT THIS.
MY LEG.  I DON'T THINK
I'M GONNA BE MUCH HELP.
- THE OTHERS WILL COME.
DON'T WORRY, OKAY?
JONAH, GET DOWN.  JONAH!
- COME AND GET IT, LITTLE BOY.
- ( grunts )
- NO, WAIT.
- WHAT THE HELL YOU DOING?
I HAD THE BRAT.
- IT'D BE A SHAME TO WASTE
A CUTIE LIKE THAT.
- LOOK, I CAUGHT MYSELF A JONAH.
- WHAT WERE YOU THINKING, LEHM?
I ALMOST HAD THE BASTARDS.
- CALM DOWN, KID
I DON'T THINK I'VE EVER SEEN YOU
LOSE YOUR TEMPER LIKE THAT,
AND I CAN'T SAY I LIKE IT MUCH.
YOU COULD'VE TAKEN THEM OUT, BUT
WOULD HAVE PAID WITH YOUR LIFE.
DON'T EVER LOSE YOUR COOL LIKE
THAT IN THE MIDDLE OF A FIGHT.
YOU'RE PISSED THAT
I STOPPED YOU?  FINE BY ME,
BUT YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY ONE
WHO'S PISSED.
I FREAKIN' HATE THE RECKLESS,
ALL-OR-NOTHING WAY
CHILD SOLDIERS FIGHT.
I MEAN IT.  LISTEN.
IN THIS CREW,
WE DON'T FIGHT TO THE DEATH.
WE'LL KILL SOMEONE
IF WE HAVE TO AND THAT'S IT.
THERE IS NO ROOM
FOR EMOTIONAL BAGGAGE.
IF WE HAVE TO ENGAGE IN A FIGHT,
IT'S STRICTLY BUSINESS.
YOU'RE NOT A KID SOLDIER
ANYMORE.  LET IT GO.
NOW DON'T GET ME WRONG,
WHEN THE BULLETS AIN'T FLYING,
I LIKE YOUR FRESH PERSPECTIVE.
THE WHOLE HATING
ARMS DEALERS THING.
WE'RE NOT HERE
TO DROWN OUT YOUR VOICE.
I DON'T SEE WHY YOU CAN'T LIVE
WITH AND LEARN FROM US
WITHOUT LETTING GO
OF WHO YOU ARE.
- UP THERE.
- THE POLICE SENT SNIPERS, HUH?
TIME FOR A CHANGE OF VENUE.
YEAH, YOU CAN SEE US.
OF COURSE,
WE CAN SEE YOU, TOO.
IF YOU WANNA KILL US,
YOU SHOULD TRY SHOOTING
FROM FURTHER AWAY.
- YEAH.
- GUYS, WHAT NOW?
- TAKE THIS.  WE'LL GIVE YOU
INSTRUCTIONS AND PROVIDE BACKUP.
CAN YOU HANDLE GETTING KOKO
TO A SAFE LOCATION?
- TAKE MY HAND
AND DON'T LET GO.
- ROGER THAT.
- LET'S MOVE.
- DAMN IT!  HOW THE HELL
DID SHE BLOCK MY SHOT?
- 45-CALIBER BULLETS
ARE HEAVY!
- I DON'T GET IT.  THIS SHOULD
HAVE CAUGHT 'EM BY SURPRISE
SHE'S GOT INSTINCTS.
- LET'S NOT COMPLIMENT
THE ENEMY, OKAY?
- ( grunts )
ARE YOU HEARING THAT
ABOMINABLE SOUND, CHINATSU?
TONE-DEAF MORON'S
USING A SILENCER.
HE'S RUINING THE PERFORMANCE.
- WATCH OUT.
- NOBODY SCREWS WITH MY MUSIC,
BASTARD.
YOUR INSTRUMENT IS OUT OF TUNE.
PLAY IT RIGHT OR NOT AT ALL.
- MUSIC?  INSTRUMENTS?
DON'T MAKE ME LAUGH.
MAYBE YOU SHOULD THINK ABOUT
RETIRING.
BEING IN THE GAME SO LONG
HAS MADE YOU FORGET,
OR DID YOU NEVER EVEN KNOW?
GUNFIGHTS ARE JUST GLORIFIED
FARTING CONTESTS.
THEY'RE DISGUSTING, MESSY
AND SHAMEFUL.
THIS AIN'T SOME SYMPHONY
WE'RE PUTTING ON HERE.
AND YOU'RE A DAMN HIT MAN,
NOT A GREAT MAESTRO.
- FARTING CONTEST?  HE'S PRETTY
FUNNY FOR AN OLD GUY.
DAMN IT, OUT OF AMMO.
- WHILE WE'RE HERE DEALING
WITH THIS DUDE,
OUR REAL TARGET IS GETTING AWAY.
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
YOUR NOTES ARE FALLING FLAT
ALL OF A SUDDEN.
YOU RUNNING OUT
OF INSPIRATION, PUCCINI?
- SMUG BASTARD!
- FORGET ABOUT HIM.
HE DOESN'T MATTER
LET'S GET MOVING.
- THIS WOULD BE A GOOD TIME FOR
ONE OF THOSE EXPLOSIVE SHELLS.
- I'M ALL OUT OF 40-MILLIMETER
AND AK ROUNDS.
WE DID JUST GET OUR HANDS
ON THAT MACHINE GUN SET, THOUGH.
- RIGHT.
FORGOT ABOUT THAT BEAUTY.
NICELY TIMED PURCHASE,
CONSIDERING ALL THOSE DAMN
BODYGUARDS WE GOTTA GET THROUGH.
THANKS FOR REMINDING ME
ABOUT THAT, CHINATSU.
I GOT A SPRING IN MY STEP
AND A SMILE ON MY FACE AGAIN.
- THAT'S THE NICEST THING
ANYONE'S EVER SAID TO ME.
- THE KID WHO CAME OUT
OF NOWHERE EARLIER.
HE WASN'T ON THE LIST,
WAS HE?
WHEN WE'RE DONE HERE,
I'M GONNA KILL THAT INFORMANT.
- OH, YEAH.  TOTALLY.
- IF I HAD TO GUESS, I'D SAY
THE GIRL IN THE RIDICULOUS HAT
IS THE BRAINS
OF THE OPERATION.
- PICKED UP ON THAT,
TOO, DID YOU?
LIKE A HUMAN WEAPONS
DIRECTION SYSTEM,
SHE'S GOT INSTINCTS
LIKE A RADAR.
IT'LL BE TOUGH
TO GET THE DROP ON 'EM.
- THAT BITCH HAS GOTTA GO.
- SHE'S NOW OUR PRIMARY TARGET.
LET'S SEE IF WE CAN
SPLIT 'EM UP SOMEHOW.
TOJO, SWAP WITH VALMET
AND GEAR ME UP.
THESE GUYS AREN'T AMATEURS
THEY'RE PACKING
SERIOUS FIREPOWER.
- FREQUENCY 817.
I'VE GOT EYES ON KOKO AND JONAH
AND WILEE AND LUTZ, TOO.
- UGO, HAUL ASS DOWN
TO THE COAST,
THEN WAIT FOR MY ORDERS.
OKAY, NOW GET OUT OF HERE.
MOVE, MOVE, MOVE!
- WAS THAT KID WE JUST PASSED
HOLDING A GUN?
I'M SURE IT WAS A TOY.
- Koko: THE RUMORS WERE RIGHT.
THOSE TWO WILL HAPPILY SHOOT
THE SHIT OUT OF ANYTHING
THAT GETS IN THEIR WAY.
THIS SHOULD BE INTERESTING.
- YEAH, WELL, THEY'RE
PROFESSIONAL KILLERS, KOKO.
OF COURSE THEY'RE HAPPY
TO USE THEIR WEAPONS.
IT'S MORE OR LESS PART
OF THE JOB DESCRIPTION.
IT'S NOT JUST PROS, EITHER.
GIVE A GUN TO AN ORDINARY
CIVILIAN AND SEE WHAT HAPPENS
NINE TIMES OUT OF TEN,
HE'LL WIND UP DOING SOMETHING
HE NEVER THOUGHT
HE WAS CAPABLE OF.
THAT'S THE KIND OF
TWISTED POWER WEAPONS HAVE.
AND YOU'RE IN THE BUSINESS
OF SELLING THAT POWER TO PEOPLE.
- ( laughs )
OH, JONAH, I'M GLAD
TO HEAR YOU FINALLY
ARTICULATING WHAT YOU FEEL.
I WAS STARTING TO THINK
IT WOULD NEVER HAPPEN.
THERE ARE SEVERAL ARGUMENTS
I'D LIKE TO MAKE,
BUT AS WE ARE OTHERWISE
OCCUPIED AT THE MOMENT,
I SUPPOSE THEY'LL HAVE TO WAIT.
WITH THOSE TWO POSSESSED
BY THAT TWISTED POWER TRYING
TO KILL US AND ALL.
- ALL RIGHT,
LET'S BRING DOWN THE HOUSE.
WE'LL PLAY 'EM A PRETTY SONG.
I KNOW A DEATH MARCH THAT'S
PERFECT FOR THE OCCASION.
ENJOY THE SHOW!
- ( theme music playing )
- ♪ HER NAME IS KOKO, SHE IS
LOCO, I SAID, "OH, NO!" ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO, SHE IS LOCO,
I SAID, "OH, NO!" ♪