- THIS JOB'S
PRETTY SMALL POTATOES FOR US.
WE'RE SELLING SOME GUNS
TO THE LOCAL MAFIA.
THREE TRUCKS WORTH, IN FACT,
WHICH WE'LL DELIVER OURSELVES.
NORMALLY I WOULDN'T EVEN BOTHER
WITH A POCKET-CHANGE
DEAL LIKE THIS.
IT'S NOT LIKE I'M MR. CURRY.
BUT COMING UP NEXT WEEK,
WE'VE GOT
A HUGE MISSILE TRANSACTION!
THIS'LL JUST KEEP US BUSY
UNTIL THEN.
AS USUAL, YOU'LL BE
GUARDING THE CARGO
AND THE TRANSACTION LOCATION.
THIS MAY BE A LOW-END JOB,
BUT THESE GUYS ARE JUMPY,
SO DON'T PROVOKE 'EM.
THAT MEANS YOU, LUTZ.
- Lutz: WHAT?!  YOU THINK
I PROVOKE PEOPLE, BOSS?
- ( all laugh )
- AH!  KOKO.
- DID YOU HEAR A SINGLE WORD
I WAS SAYING?
'CAUSE IT SURE
DIDN'T LOOK LIKE IT.
YOUR MIND SEEMS TO BE
ABOUT A THOUSAND MILES AWAY.
- YOU'RE RIGHT, I'M SORRY.
I WAS ZONING OUT.
- MEH, NO BIG WHOOP.
- ( bullet zings )
- ( grunts )
( panting )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- Valmet:
I RETURNED HOME ALONE,
FOLLOWING MY UNIT'S SLAUGHTER.
I WAS DROWNING IN
DEATH REPORTS AND PAPERWORK
FOR THE BOARD OF INQUIRY.
THEN OUT OF NOWHERE,
THIS IMPOSSIBLY PALE GIRL
WITH A GHASTLY AURA APPEARED.
MY FIRST IMPRESSION OF HER
WAS LESS THAN STELLAR.
- MAJOR SOPHIA VELMER
OF THE MECHANIZED
JAEGER BATTALION, F.R.D.F.
AND THE UNITED NATIONS
INTERIM FORCE IN COUNTRY D.
YOU MUST HAVE WORKED HARD.
THAT'S A VERY HIGH RANK
FOR SOMEONE SO YOUNG.
- UH, I'M YOUNG?
THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
I'M PRACTICALLY MENOPAUSAL
COMPARED TO YOU.
( thinking ) THIS IS A MILITARY
FACILITY. WHO IS THIS CHILD?
AND HOW'S SHE KNOW MY NAME?
- I IMAGINE
A LOT OF YOUR MOTIVATION
COMES FROM BELONGING
TO A MILITARY FAMILY.
YOUR GRANDFATHER WAS
A FIELD ARMY LIEUTENANT GENERAL
IN THE WINTER WAR
AND CONTINUATION WAR.
YOUR FATHER
IS THE CHIEF OF STAFF
FOR THE NATIONAL DEFENSE
COMMAND CENTER.
HE'S ON THE SHORT LIST
FOR THE NEXT COMMANDER IN CHIEF.
YOUR BROTHER
IS A LIEUTENANT COLONEL
AND CAPTAIN
OF THE UTTI JAEGER REGIMENT.
UNFORTUNATELY, YOU RECENTLY HAD
A PRECIPITOUS FALL FROM GRACE.
- I GET IT, YOU'VE DONE YOUR
HOMEWORK. WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?
- YOU THOUGHT YOU WERE
GOING TO AFRICA,
BUT INSTEAD
YOU WENT TO HELL AND BACK.
NOW YOU FIND YOURSELF
WITH A KEY IN EACH HAND.
THE FIRST ONE IS A HOUSE KEY.
AS A WOUNDED WARRIOR,
YOUR FAMILY WILL ACCEPT YOU
BACK INTO THE FOLD.
"FORGET YOUR PAST, SOPHIA.
ENJOY A LIFE OF PEACE."
"THERE'S A MAN I WANT
TO INTRODUCE YOU TO, SOPHIA."
"SOPHIA, WHY NOT START A FAMILY
OF YOUR OWN?"
IT'S NOT SUCH A BAD WAY TO LIVE,
REALLY.
BUT YOUR FACE
SAYS YOU BLAME YOURSELF
MORE THAN YOU DO THE ENEMY.
SO MORE LIKELY THAN NOT,
LIFE IN A SAFE,
LOVING HOME ENVIRONMENT
WOULD GRADUALLY BREAK YOU.
- ALL RIGHT, THAT'S OPTION A.
SO WHAT'S THE OTHER ONE?
- A KEY TO THE WORLD.
YOU AND YOUR UNIT
RISKED YOUR LIVES
IN THAT PEACEKEEPING FORCE.
BUT HOW MUCH DID YOUR PRESENCE
REALLY ACCOMPLISH
IN THAT SMALL AFRICAN COUNTRY?
- ( knife slashing )
- WHO WAS THE ENEMY?
WHAT DID HE WANT SO BADLY
THAT HE'D ATTACK
UNITED NATIONS FORCES?
THE HOUSE KEY?
ABSURD.
A KEY TO YOUR UNIT?
THE ARMY?
NOT EVEN A KEY TO YOUR COUNTRY
WOULD BE WORTH IT.
SOMEDAY MAYBE YOU'LL KNOW.
BUT THAT WILL ONLY HAPPEN IF
YOU CHOOSE THE KEY TO THE WORLD.
WHY NOT COME WITH ME
AND FIND OUT, VALMET?
- I'M SORRY.
- ( door opens, closes )
- THIS SUCKS.
IT SUCKS AND IT BLOWS.
IT'S HOT AND IT REEKS.
- ( gunfire )
- AND IT'S NOISY.
GREGOIRE!
UNNECESSARY, MAN.
YOU'RE STINKING UP THE JOINT.
- BUT THE BASTARD
SHOT ME, BOSS.
I NEEDED TO TEACH HIM A LESSON.
- DEAD GUYS
DON'T LEARN THINGS VERY WELL.
- ( laughs )
- LILIANE!
- ARE YOU SURE THERE'S NO ONE
ELSE LEFT FOR ME TO SHOOT?
- OF COURSE I AM.
HOW MANY DID YOU TAKE?
- I GOT THREE OF 'EM.
- Gregoire: I KILLED THREE TOO.
- AND THREE FOR ME,
SO THAT'S IT.  PULL OUT.
DID I MENTION THIS SUCKS?
WASTING ALL THAT TIME AND ENERGY
BRINGING DOWN A MOB OFFICE.
- ( gun fires )
- YOU NEED TO WORK ON
YOUR FOLLOW-THROUGH.
YOU'VE GOT THE OPPOSITE PROBLEM!
- HMM?
- ( siren wailing )
- WE DON'T EVEN GET PAID
TILL WE KNOCK OFF THE POLITICIAN
THOSE GUYS WERE BACKING.
MAN, THIS KIND OF PHYSICAL LABOR
REALLY ISN'T MY THING.
I'M STARTING TO THINK I'M NOT
CUT OUT FOR THIS LINE OF WORK.
- Dominique:
WHAT THE FUCK ARE YOU SAYING?
THAT'S JUST CRAZY TALK.
- IT DIDN'T FAZE ME WHEN
I WAS STILL NEW TO THE GAME,
BUT THESE DAYS I CAN'T STAND
THE SMELL OF BLOOD.
YOU KNOW, GREG'S QUITE A COOK.
I WAS THINKING WE COULD
MAKE USE OF HIS TALENTS
AND OPEN A RESTAURANT.
- A RESTAURANT?!  HA HA!
DID YOU HEAR THAT, GREG?
- 'COURSE, NOBODY'D WANNA LOOK
AT ME AND HIS UGLY MUGS,
SO YOU'D HAVE TO HANDLE
FRONT OF HOUSE.
- KILL 'EM WITH MY SMILE, HUH?
- THIS NEXT JOB WILL AUGMENT
OUR FUNDS. IT PAYS VERY WELL.
WHICH OF COURSE
MEANS IT WON'T BE EASY.
THE GIG'S IN ALEXANDRIA.
AND THE TARGET
IS AN ARMS DEALER.
- HUH?  VALMET?
VALMET?
- Jonah: SO, IS THIS WHERE
- WE'VE BEEN HEADED?
- ( Valmet gasps )
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU FOLLOWED ME HERE?
- WELL, LOOKS LIKE VALMET'S
GONE OFF THE RESERVATION, HUH?
- SEEMS SO.
BUT BEING SHORT ONE PERSON
DOESN'T CHANGE THE FACT
THAT WE'VE GOT A JOB
TO TAKE CARE OF.
TODAY IS ONLY MONDAY,
WHICH MEANS WE STILL
HAVE A LONG WORK WEEK
AHEAD OF US, UNDERSTOOD?
- ( laughs )
- I MAY TAKE IT EASY
ON YOU GUYS,
BUT DON'T FORGET,
I OWN ALL OF YOU.
I MEAN, SWEET JEEBUS, LEHM,
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
THE LEADER OF THIS UNIT.
KEEPING EVERYONE IN LINE
IS YOUR RESPONSIBILITY.
- YEAH, I KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
GETTING AT WITH ALL THIS.
BUT SERIOUSLY, BOSS,
YOU CAN'T TELL ME
YOU DIDN'T KNOW
THIS DAY WAS COMING.
IT WAS ALWAYS
JUST A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE SHE WENT AFTER
HER PAST. RIGHT?
- WHERE'S JONAH?!
- NO LUCK, BOSS.
HE'S GONE TOO.
WE CAN'T FIND HIM.
- WE TORE THE SHIP APART.
- THINK HE MIGHT HAVE
LEFT WITH VALMET?
- PROBABLY.
- ARGH!
AHHH!
- R: CALM DOWN.
YOU MIGHT HURT YOURSELF.
- I AM CALM!
- Wilee: THEY'LL BOTH
COME BACK, BOSS.
I'M SURE OF IT.
- ARGH!  I KNOW THEY WILL!
NOW QUIT GAWKIN' AND GET BACK
TO WORK. NO MORE SLACKING!
AHH!
- ( laughs )
IT'S GONNA BE
ONE OF THOSE DAYS.
- JONAH, I WANT YOU
TO GO BACK TO KOKO
AND THE OTHERS RIGHT NOW.
YOU SHOULDN'T BE HERE.
- SORRY, CAN'T DO THAT.
- JONAH!  DON'T YOU SEE
THIS IS FOR YOUR OWN GOOD?
- LAST TIME I CHECKED,
I WORKED FOR KOKO, NOT YOU.
SHE'S THE ONE WHO TOOK ME IN
AND MADE ME PART OF THIS UNIT.
LONG AS I'M WITH THE CREW,
I DO WHAT'S BEST FOR HER.
IT DIDN'T LOOK LIKE
YOU EXPECTED TO BE
COMING BACK, EVER.
AND AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED,
THAT'S UNACCEPTABLE.
WE'RE A TEAM.
WE HAVE TO STICK TOGETHER.
- ( thinking ) THIS KID.
- YOU WANT REVENGE
ON THOSE PEOPLE WE MET
IN SOUTH AFRICA, DON'T YOU?
A C.I.A. TECHIE
NAMED SCHOKOLADE
STARTED HANGING AROUND KOKO
AFTER THAT TRIP.
I BET YOU HAD HER
DO SOME RECON FOR YOU
BEHIND THE BOSS'S BACK.
YOU WANTED TO KNOW WHO WAS
RUNNING THAT AFRICAN CREW.
- YOU'RE JUST FULL OF SURPRISES.
WHEN YOU GET RIGHT DOWN TO IT,
I DON'T KNOW YOU AT ALL, DO I?
- WHATEVER IT IS YOU'RE DOING,
I WANNA HELP YOU.
- YOU'VE ALREADY GIVEN ME
A LOT TO THINK ABOUT.
I'LL NEED TO GET BACK TO YOU
ON THAT PART.
AND I'M SORRY I PUNCHED YOU.
LET'S RUN SOME COLD WATER
ON YOUR FACE.
- MAN, THIS SUCKS!
DID YOU LOOK THROUGH THIS FILE?
- SURE DID!
- LIKE I THOUGHT,
BIG PAYOUT MEANS TOUGH JOB.
GONNA BE
A REAL PAIN IN THE ASS.
I'M IMPRESSED THIS CHICK
COULD PUT TOGETHER
SUCH A SERIOUS CREW.
DELTA FORCE?
FINNISH RAPID DEPLOYMENT?
THOSE ARE THE TWO HEAVY HITTERS.
WE'LL SAVE THEM FOR LATER.
WE ALSO GOT AN EX-COP
FROM AN ANTI-TERRORISM UNIT
AND A FORMER J.S.D.F. OFFICER.
- J.S.D.F.?  WHAT'S THAT?
- JAPANESE MILITARY.
- THERE'S A GUY WITH 'EM
WHO USED TO BE
WITH THE ITALIAN ARMY,
FOUGHT IN BOSNIA-HERZEGOVINA.
YOU KNOW WHO I MEAN.
THE ONES THAT LIKE TO GO AROUND
WEARING BLACK FEATHERS
IN THEIR HELMETS.
- WOW, BOSS,
YOU KNOW ALL SORTS OF SHIT.
- THESE GUYS ARE DANGEROUS.
WE CAN'T TAKE 'EM ALL AT ONCE.
HAVE TO BE ONE AT A TIME.
LET'S SPLIT
THE JOB INTO 10 PARTS.
- Gregoire: SOUNDS GOOD TO ME.
- ( gasps )
- ( laughs )
- WHAT'S WITH THE GIGGLING,
LILIANE?
- CHECK OUT UGO!
HIS BACKROUND, IT'S HYSTERICAL.
IT SAYS HE'S EX-MAFIA!
ALL THOSE ELITE SOLDIERS
AND HE'S A MOBSTER!
( laughing )
- THAT SETTLES IT.
OUR FIRST TARGET IS HIM.
- GENERAL, I'M SORRY.
I KNOW THAT I DON'T DESERVE
ANOTHER CHANCE.
BUT I'M BEGGING YOU.
TWICE WE'VE FOUGHT
THE HEKMATYARS.
AND TWICE, I'VE LOST.
I MUST RESTORE MY HONOR.
- KAREN, PLEASE,
IT'S "EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR."
PEOPLE IN THIS COUNTRY
GET TOUCHY
ABOUT THE WORD "GENERAL."
YOU WOULD THINK
THEY'D BE USED TO IT,
GIVEN THEIR CONSTANT STATE
OF CIVIL WAR
AND THE PERCENT OF INCOME
THEY SPEND ON WEAPONRY.
I'VE TOLD YOU, THESE MINOR
FAILURES DO NOT BOTHER ME.
AND WHILE I'M THE DIRECTOR OF
THE DA XINGHAI TRADING COMPANY,
AND ON PAPER, YOU'VE BEEN
DISCHARGED FROM THE P.L.A.
AND ARE ONLY
MY CIVILIAN BODYGUARDS,
THE CENTRAL COMMITTEE
LEARNED OF THE RECENT SLAUGHTER
AND INSIST I LET YOU GO.
THEY ARE THE VOICE
OF MY FATHERLAND
SO I MUST OBEY.
- NO. I CAN'T SIT BY AND WATCH
WHILE THE REASON
I FIRST FOLLOWED YOU FADES AWAY.
YOU WERE THE EMBODIMENT
OF POWER IN BATTLE.
WHEN YOU FOUGHT,
NOBODY COULD STAND BEFORE YOU.
WITH YOUR SKILLS, YOU BROUGHT
OUR COUNTRY GREAT HONOR.
THAT WAS THE MAN
I FELL IN LOVE WITH.
I WILL DO WHATEVER
YOU ASK OF ME.
PLEASE, JUST LET ME STAY
BY YOUR SIDE, GENERAL.
YOU CAN'T JUST WALK AWAY
FROM THE FIGHT!
WHAT WILL BE LEFT OF YOU THEN?
- THAT'S QUITE ENOUGH,
FORMER LIEUTENANT LOW.
- ( grunts )
- OH, I'M SORRY.
YOU SEEM TO HAVE SLIPPED.
- DAMN YOU.
I AM YOUR SUPERIOR, LI.
- NOT ANYMORE. I'VE BEEN
PROMOTED TO LIEUTENANT.
DO YOU KNOW HOW RIDICULOUS
YOU SOUND?
THE GENERAL WILL KEEP FIGHTING,
WITH OR WITHOUT YOU.
THE DA XINGHAI TRADING COMPANY
WILL CONTINUE TO EXPAND,
AND THE EXECUTIVE
DIRECTOR WILL BECOME
THE FACE OF CHINA IN AFRICA.
HE WILL BE PROTECTED BY
A NEW UNIT UNDER MY COMMAND.
- GENERAL.
I WILL RETURN TOMORROW.
- Schokolade: EXECUTIVE
DIRECTOR GUOMING CHEN
ISN'T AS OLD AS HE LOOKS.
HE'S JUST AGED FASTER THAN
USUAL SINCE INJURING HIS LEG.
HE HAD THE CRAPPY LUCK
TO STEP ON A LANDMINE.
- WHAT ELSE DO YOU KNOW?
- A LOT, ACTUALLY.
CHEN WAS THE ONE
WHO ATTACKED THE PATROL UNIT
AND THE UNFID SQUAD
COMMANDED BY MAJOR VELMER--
ER, YOU KNOW, VALMET.
I'M SURE OF IT.
SUPPOSEDLY, HE'S GOT
A UNIQUE FIGHTING STYLE.
HE PLOWS INTO THE MIDDLE
OF ENEMY FORCES
WITH CUSTOM BAYONETS
ON HIS SIDEARMS.
THAT ALONE TELLS YOU THIS GUY
IS A COMBAT JUNKIE.
IT'S NO WONDER LOSING FULL USE
OF HIS LEG AGED HIM SO QUICKLY.
ANYWAY,
HE DISTINGUISHED HIMSELF
AS AN ARMY OFFICIAL
IN CENTRAL ASIA
UNTIL, POSSIBLY ON ORDER
FROM MILITARY HIGHER-UPS,
HE STARTED SPENDING
TIME IN AFRICA,
AND THAT'S WHERE
HIS TRAIL GETS FAINT.
IT'S CONCEIVABLE THEY'RE
USING HIM AS A SCAPEGOAT.
DA XINGHAI IS
AN INDEPENDENT COMPANY
THAT WAS SET UP
TO PAVE THE WAY FOR CHINA
TO MINE FOR PETROLEUM
AND NATURAL GAS.
THEY HANDLE SECURITY
FOR REFINERIES AND PIPELINES,
NEGOTIATE BETWEEN THE LOCALS
AND THE WEAPONS INDUSTRY,
AND DELIVER REGIONAL ARMIES'
ORDERS TO THE MILITIAS.
THEY'VE GOT THEIR FINGERS
IN MORE PIES THAN YOU CAN COUNT.
THINK OF THEM
AS THE ADVANCE GUARD
SENT TO DO CHINA'S DIRTY WORK
AND UP THE COUNTRY'S
POLITICAL CAPITAL.
SCARECROW WAS LIVID
AND SWORE HE'D FIGURE OUT
HOW CHEN WAS DOING IT ALL, BUT--
- WHAT THE HELL?!
IT'S ALL LEGIT.
- HE WAS
PRETTY DISAPPOINTED.
NOW HE DOESN'T WANNA HEAR
ANYTHING ABOUT IT.
YOU KNOW, I WASN'T SURE
WHETHER I WOULD GIVE VALMET
THE RESULTS OF MY RESEARCH.
- ( chuckles ) WHY NOT?
ISN'T THIS EXACTLY WHAT SHE
WANTED YOU TO FIND OUT FOR HER?
IF YOU HADN'T FOUND ANYTHING
OF INTEREST
TO REPORT ABOUT MR. CHEN,
I WOULD UNDERSTAND
YOUR HESITATION.
- WELL, WHEN YOU CALLED ME
SAYING YOU WANTED TO TALK
ABOUT VALMET, I WAS TOTALLY
EXPECTING YOU TO CHEW ME OUT.
OH, BUT SHE SAID SOMETHING
STRANGE BEFORE SHE LEFT--
"THANKS TO KOKO,
I WAS FINALLY ABLE
TO UNLOCK THE WORLD."
- Valmet: IT'S ALMOST FUNNY.
I'VE TRAVELED ALL OVER THE WORLD
AS A MEMBER OF KOKO'S CREW.
BUT IN THE END, I'M BACK HERE
WHERE IT ALL STARTED.
- Man: IF YOU'VE ALREADY BEEN
HERE, WHY WOULD YOU COME BACK?
LOOK, I CAN TELL YOU GUYS
ARE NOT NORMAL CIVILIANS,
BUT LET ME GIVE YOU
A PIECE OF ADVICE--
NO MATTER HOW TOUGH
YOU THINK YOU ARE,
YOU'D BE SMART TO STAY WELL AWAY
FROM CHINATOWN.
IT WAS BUILT BY A COMPANY
MINING NATURAL GAS,
BUT FOR SOME REASON,
IT'S TURNED INTO A HANGOUT
FOR THE MILITIA
AND OTHER NASTY TYPES.
NONE OF THE LOCALS WILL RISK
GOING ANYWHERE NEAR THERE NOW.
SO WORD TRAVELS FAST
WHEN AN OUTSIDER STUMBLES IN.
- THANKS FOR THE WARNING.
THAT'S VERY HELPFUL.
AND I DO BELIEVE
WE'LL TAKE YOUR ADVICE.
LET'S FIND A HOTEL
IN THE NEXT TOWN.
SO WE DON'T REALLY PASS
FOR TOURISTS, HUH?
- NOT AT ALL.
YOU'RE SOLDIERS, AREN'T YOU?
IT'S YOUR BODY LANGUAGE
THAT'S THE GIVE-AWAY.
- Man #2: I LOOKED OVER
THE MERCHANDISE
YOU BROUGHT, MS. HEKMATYAR.
THOSE ARE SOME
GOOD QUALITY PIECES.
- I'M GLAD YOU FIND THEM
ACCEPTABLE.
NOW THEN,
YOU JUST HAND OVER THE MONEY
AND THE KEYS TO THESE
THREE TRUCKS ARE ALL YOURS.
UH-HUH, I SEE.
- WE ALSO BROUGHT
SOME HIGH-QUALITY STUFF.
SELL IT RIGHT,
AND YOU'LL MAKE A LOT MORE
THAN THE PRICE
WE ORIGINALLY AGREED ON.
- THIS IS EXACTLY WHY I DON'T
LIKE TAKING THIS TYPE OF JOB.
I SEE NOW WHY YOU WERE
RELUCTANT TO PAY IN ADVANCE.
- WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
THE PAYMENT'S ALL THERE.
- I TOLD YOU
TO HAND OVER THE MONEY.
DOESN'T LOOK LIKE CASH TO ME,
JUST WORTHLESS POWDER.
- YOU WHORE!
- Man: WHAT THE FUCK
ARE YOU DOING?!
- ( fires )
- SHIT!
- ( sighs )
GLAD I DIDN'T BRING LILIANE
AND GREG ALONG FOR THIS.
IDIOTS WOULD PROBABLY WANT
TO JUMP IN AND KILL 'EM ALL NOW.
SO THEY TOOK OUT
A GROUP OF TEN AMATEURS
WITHOUT BREAKING A SWEAT.
NO SURPRISE THERE.
LOOKS LIKE THE FINNISH
WOMAN'S NOT WITH 'EM.
WONDER WHY THAT IS.
THIS COULD BE
OUR GOLDEN OPPORTUNITY.
- Gregoire:
ROGER THAT, BOSS.
- ( humming )
- HE SAID TO MOVE OUT.
- FINALLY!  MAN, CAN'T WAIT
TO GET BACK IN THE FIELD!
WHAT SHOULD I WEAR?
- I'D SAY IT'S A BLACK-T-SHIRT,
BLACK-PANTS GIG.
- ROGER THAT.
( laughs )
- Lehm: HOW DID IT GO AGAIN?
"THE BOSS SHOULD ALWAYS BE
SMILING, NO MATTER WHAT"?
THAT WAS THE PROMISE YOU MADE,
WASN'T IT?
- UNFORTUNATELY, SOME PROMISES
AREN'T MEANT TO BE KEPT.
- YOU KNOW,
I'M PRETTY SURE I SAID
THE SAME THING TO YOU BEFORE.
( laughs )
- WHAT'S GOTTEN INTO THE BOSS?
THAT WAS BRUTAL.
- NOTHING'S GOTTEN INTO HER.
SHE'S ALWAYS LIKE THIS.
- YOU THINK SO?
YOU MUST BE BLIND.
- WHAT WOULD YOU HAVE DONE, R?
ACCEPT THEIR BLOW AS PAYMENT
AND GO SELL IT ON THE STREET?
SINCE WHEN
DID WE BECOME DRUG DEALERS?
THOSE IDIOTS
SIGNED THEIR DEATH WARRANTS
WHEN THEY DECIDED
TO SCREW WITH US.
I THINK THE LITTLE LADY
DID WHAT NEEDED TO BE DONE.
- HMM.
- HAVEN'T YOU NOTICED VALMET
ACTING DIFFERENTLY?
I GAVE JONAH ORDERS TO KEEP
A CLOSE EYE ON HER FOR ME.
AND TOLD HIM TO FOLLOW HER
IF SHE EVER LEFT
WITHOUT TELLING US.
I KNEW THAT DAY WOULD COME.
- WELL, AIN'T HE OBSERVANT?
CAN'T SAY I NOTICED
ANY CHANGE IN HER.
FAR AS I'M CONCERNED,
VALMET'S ALWAYS ACTIN' WEIRD.
I THINK SENDING JONAH ALONG
WAS A GOOD IDEA, THOUGH.
HE'LL HELP HER.
- I--
I CAN'T PRETEND VALMET
IS JUST ANOTHER SOLDIER
I PAY TO PROTECT ME.
IT'S NOT LIKE THAT.
I'VE SPENT MORE TIME WITH HER
THAN MY OWN FAMILY.
SHE'S MY SISTER, MY TEACHER,
AND SOMETHING EVEN MORE.
- THAT'S THE KIND OF THING
YOU'D BE BETTER OFF
KEEPING TO YOURSELF, KOKO.
SOLDIERS OUT IN THE FIELD
SPEND A LOT OF TIME
THINKIN' ABOUT STUFF LIKE THAT.
"IS MY COMMANDER
WORTH RISKING MY LIFE FOR?"
"WHAT AM I WORTH?"
IT'S NOT SOMETHING
I WORRY ABOUT TOO MUCH,
BUT THERE ARE PLENTY OF SOLDIERS
WHO FREEZE UP
IF THEIR COMMANDER JUST LAYS OUT
THE ANSWERS TO THOSE QUESTIONS.
SOMETIMES
ACTING LIKE YOU DON'T CARE
IS A NECESSARY PART OF THE JOB.
SUCKS, HUH?
( laughs )
- Koko: ALL RIGHT.
I THINK THAT'S ENOUGH TIME
WASTED.
WE'RE IN THE WIND!
- All: 'KAY.
- ( sighs )
OH, YEAH!
NOW IT'S BATH TIME.
- WE'RE UP FIRST.
YOU READY TO START OUR ROUNDS?
- YEAH.
- FULLY LOADED?
- ( humming )
- WHAT THE--
- DAMN IT!
TOJO,
GET TO THE LITTLE LADY'S ROOM.
- RIGHT.
LEHM, UGO, R!
- TWO MINUTES. LILIANE, ALL YOU
HAVE TO DO IS DISTRACT 'EM.
THAT'LL GIVE GREG
THE CHANCE TO KILL UGO.
BUT IN TWO MINUTES,
PULL BACK.
- ( laughs )
- AH!
OH, COME ON!
ANOTHER LITTLE GIRL?
GET DOWN!
- LUTZ, HOW MANY?!
- JUST A KID SO FAR.
LIKELY MORE.
DON'T COME OUT!
- WILEE!
- YEAH!
- UGO!
- R!
- YEAH.
- MAO!
- LEHM!
- ( grunting )
- UGO!  LEHM!
DAMN YOU.
- ( metal striking,
blood spurting )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ CONTROL, CONTROL ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS LOCO ♪
♪ I SAID, OH NO! ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS LOCO ♪
♪ I SAID, OH NO! ♪