- I DIDN'T KNOW
YOU HAD A FAMILY.
- YEAH, I'M A LUCKY MAN.
I'VE GOT A WIFE, A SON,
AND A DAUGHTER BACK HOME.
I WAS ASSIGNED
TO AN ARTILLERY UNIT.
MAN, THE GUNS I SHOT
WERE SO BIG,
YOU COULD STICK YOUR HEAD
INSIDE OF 'EM.
I WAS DRIFTING
AROUND AFTER THAT.
AND KOKO JUST SO HAPPENED
TO BE IN ASIA.
SHE WAS KIND ENOUGH
TO HIRE ME.
- IF YOU'LL TAKE A LOOK AT THE
INFORMATION IN FRONT OF YOU,
YOU'LL SEE IT'S TIME
FOR AN AIR DELIVERY!
- MS. HEKMATYAR, I WANT
TO TELL YOU HOW GRATEFUL WE ARE.
WE APPRECIATE
YOU TRANSPORTING US.
A MAN CALLED
DRAGAN NIKOLAEVICH
IS THE HEAD OF THE MILITIA
GROUP, THE BALKAN DRAGONS.
BOTH THE GROUP AND ITS LEADER
ARE ALSO KNOWN AS BALDRA.
- LET ME MAKE THIS EASY FOR
YOU--
I KNOW FULL WELL
YOU'VE GOT 10 DOCTORS
STASHED IN THAT AIRCRAFT
LIKE CARGO.
UNLOAD THEM IMMEDIATELY!
- ( groaning )
WELL, SON OF A BITCH.
THE BOYS IN BERETS
ARE MULTIPLYING.
- THIS ISN'T JUST ABOUT US.
WE'RE CAUSING PROBLEMS
FOR MS. HEKMATYAR.
I CAN'T SIT HERE
PRETENDING TO BE CARGO.
- YOU PATCH UP THE PEOPLE
I SHOOT.
AND THAT MAKES YOU MY ENEMY.
- WHATCHA WANT US TO DO NOW,
BOSS?
- WE'VE PRETTY MUCH RUN OUT
OF OPTIONS AT THIS POINT.
NEW ORDERS-- ELIMINATE
THE BALKAN DRAGON MILITIA!
- ( rap music playing )
- CLOSE ONE.
NICE TRY.
- WHA--
WHO'S FIRING?
- ( theme music playing )
-( singing in Japanese )
- ( gunfire continues )
- STAND DOWN!
BALKAN ELITE, REMAIN INSIDE.
MS. HEKMATYAR, PLEASE!
YOU MUST PUT A STOP
TO THE SHOOTING.
- YOU BITCH, I'LL KILL YOU!
AHHH!
( grunting )
- Koko: HOLD IT, JONAH.
DON'T FIRE.
- ( car stalling )
- SHIT!  SHIT!
- ( car turns over )
THAT INTERFERING HARPY.
I WILL NEVER FORGET
WHAT SHE DID TODAY.
SOONER OR LATER, SHE'S DEAD!
- ( gunfire )
- ( man grunts )
- ALL CLEAR.
- Mao: ALL CLEAR.
- OUR CASUALTIES?
- Lehm: ZERO.
- ( camera smashing )
- Captain: I CANNOT BELIEVE WHAT
YOU HAVE DONE ON MY AIRFIELD!
YOU ARE LEAVING
A MOUNTAIN OF BALDRA CORPSES
IN YOUR WAKE, MS. HEKMATYAR.
- THIS ALL COULD HAVE GONE DOWN
MUCH DIFFERENTLY, CAPTAIN,
IF THEIR BOSS
HAD BEHAVED LIKE A GENTLEMAN.
- PROBLEM NOW IS, HOW'RE WE
GONNA GET OUT OF THE COUNTRY?
BY PLANE?
THEY'LL SHOOT US DOWN THE
SECOND WE'RE IN THE AIR.
BY LAND?
AND BRING OUR "CARGO"
WITH US? NO WAY.
- Jonah: THAT BALDRA GUY
DROVE OFF WITH THE CHIEF DOCTOR,
WHICH WOULDN'T HAVE HAPPENED
IF I HAD JUST SHOT HIM.
WHY COULDN'T I TAKE THE SHOT?
- SORRY, THAT BASTARD
DIDN'T DESERVE
A QUICK, CLEAN DEATH
BY YOUR HAND.
A SWORD'S WORTH IS
MEASURED BY THE NOBILITY
OF THE LIVES IT TAKES.
I COULD NEVER LET YOU
DULL YOUR SHARP EDGE
BY TAKING DOWN
THAT USELESS PIECE OF SHIT.
- YOU USE WAY TOO MANY METAPHORS
FOR ME TO UNDERSTAND SOMETIMES.
- ( laughs )
BUT IT WOULDN'T SOUND AS PRETTY.
BESIDES, I HAD MY REASONS.
LETTING HIM GET AWAY
SUITS OUR NEEDS.
- WHAT KIND OF
IDIOT IDEA IS THAT?
YOU ARE NOT THINKING HERE.
- I'M NOT?
AND WHAT WAS YOUR IDEA?
YOU WANT US TO RUN OFF
WITH A TANK?
- BOYS, BOYS, LET'S KEEP THE
ARGUMENTS CONSTRUCTIVE, OKAY?
- BUT THIS SITUATION
DOES DEMAND SOME HASTE, BOSS.
- IF WE DON'T HURRY,
THAT CROOK WILL BE BACK
WITH A WHOLE MILITIA IN TOW.
- WHAT DO THEY HAVE
FOR AN AERIAL STRIKE?
- ROCKET LAUNCHERS,
ANTI-AIRCRAFT GUNS.
AND I WOULDN'T BE SURPRISED
IF THEY HAVE MISSILES TOO.
- THEY DEFINITELY WILL.
- WE COULD TRY USING FLARES.
- YEAH, THAT'S A GREAT PLAN.
AND WHAT DO WE DO AFTER THAT?
- ( all grunting )
- HUH.
WHAT ABOUT
THOSE CANNONS OVER THERE?
- HANG ON,
SAY THAT AGAIN.
- WELL, UH, I WAS THINKING
WE COULD USE THOSE 122s
TO DESTROY
THE MISSILE LAUNCH PAD.
- I LIKE IT.
LET'S DO IT.
THIS MAY BE AN ODD REQUEST,
BUT WE'D LIKE TO TAKE ONE OF
THOSE ENORMOUS CANNONS
OFF YOUR HANDS, CAPTAIN.
FOR A REASONABLE PRICE,
OF COURSE.
GIVE US THE ARTILLERY
AND 10 MORE MINUTES,
AND WE'LL BE OUT OF YOUR HAIR.
GONNA PLAY HARDBALL, HUH?
OKEY-DOKE, I'LL THROW IN
A TWENTY PERCENT DISCOUNT
ON YOUR NEXT ORDER.
- DO WHATEVER YOU NEED TO.
- UGO, GO GET US PREPPED
FOR TAKE-OFF.
- HA!  ROGER THAT.
- AS FOR THE REST OF YOU,
HELP MAO GET ONE OF THOSE BABIES
LOCKED AND LOADED.
HE'S IN CHARGE OF THIS OPERATION
SO LISTEN TO WHAT HE SAYS.
- All: YES, MA'AM!
- ( sighs )
- PLEASE EXCUSE ME,
BUT, UH, THE CHIEF DOCTOR?
- HE WAS SHOT TWICE
AND THEN ABDUCTED.
- OH.   WE'VE CAUSED YOU
SO MUCH TROUBLE.
- ( laughs )
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT, DOCTOR.
BALDRA AND I
ARE THE REAL TROUBLEMAKERS HERE.
( zipping )
YOUR HELMET.
WE'RE EXPECTING SOME NASTY
TURBULENCE AFTER TAKEOFF.
- Baldra: ATTACK AS SOON
AS THEY'RE OFF THE GROUND.
I WANT THEM TAKEN DOWN BEFORE
THEY ESCAPE THE CLOUDS, GOT IT?
AND YOU KNOW WHAT'LL HAPPEN
IF YOU FAIL ME, DON'T YOU? HUH?
- YOU ACT LIKE
A SPOILED LITTLE KID.
CAN'T EVEN BEGIN TO FATHOM
WHY ANYBODY WOULD FOLLOW YOU.
YOU MAY BE INJURED,
BUT I STILL HAVE USE FOR YOU.
LET ME EXPLAIN.
YOU WILL SHOOT A VIDEO
BEGGING THE WORLD
TO SAVE YOUR MISERABLE LIFE.
AFTER THAT, WELL...
- ( laughs )
UP YOURS.
- ( silent )
( silent )
- Koko: LET'S GO!
TAKE OFF.
AND GET BOTH
OF OUR I.R. JAMMERS TURNED ON.
- Lutz: DAMN, THAT WAS CLOSE.
THOSE GUYS
AREN'T SCREWING AROUND.
- YEAH, NO KIDDING.
- YOU GUYS FORGET WHAT I SAID
ABOUT FLYING WITH KOKO?
- DON'T BE RIDICULOUS.
THIS ISN'T KOKO'S FAULT.
- Koko: INCOMING!
- Man: THEY HAVE INFRARED
JAMMER. I CAN'T LOCK ON.
- GET ME THROUGH TO MISSILE
UNIT TWO IN THE SOUTHWEST.
- GO, CAPTAIN!
WE NEED ALTITUDE NOW.
- ROGER.
- Computer voice: WARNING!
- WARNING, INCOMING OBJECTS.
- THAT'S THE MISSILE ALERT.
- FIRE OFF THE FLARES!
- ( all grunting )
- SHE WASN'T KIDDING
ABOUT THE TURBULENCE!
- GO!
RELOAD NOW.
- DON'T LET THEM FIRE AGAIN.
- Ugo: 10,000 FEET.
MAINTAINING SPEED AND ALTITUDE.
- ROGER THAT.
COVER YOUR EARS!
SAY "AH!"
- All: AH.
- THREE, TWO, ONE!
- ( explosion )
- DIRECT HIT CONFIRMED.
I'LL LOAD THE NEXT ROUND.
- All: YEAH!
ALL RIGHT!
- ( thinking )
SO GLAD THAT WORKED.
ONLY THREW THE IDEA OUT THERE
TO CALM EVERYONE DOWN.
- YOU'VE STILL GOT IT, MAO.
A JOB WELL DONE.
6,000 IRON DARTS
SHOULD KEEP 'EM BUSY.
WE'VE GOT 'EM PINNED FOR NOW.
BUT KEEP YOUR
GUARD UP JUST IN CASE.
- UGH, SCHOKOLADE,
WHY THE HELL
ARE YOU SOLDERING IN MY ROOM?
COULDN'T YOU DO THAT
SOMEWHERE ELSE?
THAT SMELL IS DISGUSTING.
- TELL YOU WHAT,
IF YOU STOP BITCHING,
I'LL LET YOU TAKE ME OUT TO EAT.
- ( cell phone ringing )
- YEAH, SCARECROW HERE.
- Koko: SCARECROW,
MY OLD FRIEND.
- HEKMATYAR?!
HOW'D YOU GET MY CELL?
- THAT KOKO?
- DAMN BIMBO.
- I DON'T HAVE MUCH TIME.
PISS ME OFF AND I'LL HANG UP.
I HAPPEN TO BE IN BALKAN
AIRSPACE AT THE MOMENT.
I FOUND NIKOLAEVICH.
- YOU-- WAIT.
AS IN, LIKE, BALDRA?
THE MANIAC SHITBAG
WITH A $5 MIL PRICE
ON HIS HEAD?
GREAT!
I MEAN, YEAH, OKAY, WHATEVER.
SO WHERE'S BALDRA HIDING?
- THAT INFO WILL COST YA.
I'M WILLING
TO SELL HIS LOCATION
AND THE HONOR
OF APPREHENDING HIM.
FOR FIVE MILLION DOLLARS.
- FIVE MIL? KISS MY ASS.
I DON'T MAKE A HABIT OF
GIVING THAT KIND OF CASH
TO CRIMINALS.
- REALLY?
WELL, THAT'S TOO BAD.
YOU'RE EVEN STUPIDER
THAN I THOUGHT.
- ( phone goes dead )
- THE BITCH JUST HUNG UP.
ARMS DEALERS
HAVE THE WORST MANNERS.
- ( phone vibrating )
RUDE.
- HELLO?
- HEY, SCHOKOLADE, I FOUND
NIKOLAEVICH IN THE BALKANS.
AND I CAN MAKE IT REAL EASY
FOR YOU TO TAKE HIM IN.
CARE TO PURCHASE THIS INTEL
FOR $5 MILLION?
- YOU'VE GOT A DEAL!
- WAIT, NO-- OH.
- Koko: MAN, THAT WAS CUTTIN' IT
WAY CLOSER THAN I LIKE.
IF THE MORONS HAD USED
ONE OF THE MISSILES I SOLD 'EM,
THEY COULDA SHOT US DOWN.
- ( all laughing )
- Lutz: WE DAMN NEAR DIED,
AND THIS IS SOMETHING
TO LAUGH ABOUT?!
- MS. HEKMATYAR, I--
I JUST WANTED TO SAY
HOW MUCH WE APPRECIATE
YOU DROPPING US OFF
THIS CLOSE TO THE REFUGEE CAMP.
WE'LL TRANSFER THE REMAINDER
OF THE FEE TO YOUR ACCOUNT.
BUT WE CAN MAKE IT
ON OUR OWN FROM HERE.
- HOLD ON. WE HAVEN'T FULFILLED
OUR PART OF THE DEAL YET.
I JUST NEED TO ASK YOU
TO GIVE US A LITTLE MORE TIME.
YOU SEE, OUR CONTRACT
WAS FOR THE TRANSPORT
AND DELIVERY OF TEN DOCTORS.
SEEMS TO ME,
WE'RE ONE DOCTOR SHORT.
WE'D LIKE TO GET
HIM BACK FOR YOU.
- GREAT!
- Koko:
OKAY, SO YOU BOYS AT H.Q.
ARE TRACKING BALDRA'S MOVEMENTS
VIA SATELLITE?
- Man: YES, MA'AM.
WE'VE BEEN ACTIVELY TRACING HIM
USING SATELLITE IMAGES.
- JUST "YES" WILL DO.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
REPEAT EVERYTHING I SAY.
ANYWAY, I FIGURED IT OUT
ABOUT HALFWAY THROUGH,
BUT THIS WHOLE OPERATION,
IT'S ONE OF FLOYD'S SCENARIOS,
ISN'T IT?
- IF YOU WOULD JUST TALK
TO YOUR FATHER,
YOU WOULD ALREADY KNOW
THE ANSWER.
AT ANY RATE, YES.
YOU'RE CORRECT
ABOUT HIS INVOLVEMENT.
YOU DID A GOOD JOB WITH THIS.
YOUR FATHER'S OBJECTIVE
WITH THIS MISSION
WAS TO GET BOTH THE O.D.H.
AND THE C.I.A. IN HIS DEBT,
AND YOU SAW TO THAT.
YOU CAN KEEP ANY REWARD MONEY
YOU GET FOR BALDRA AS A BONUS.
SCARECROW HAS JUST SENT
A REQUEST
FOR THE U.S. MARINES
TO MOBILIZE.
THEY'RE SENDING IN
A SPECIAL-OPS UNIT.
THAT SHOULD WRAP
THINGS UP NEATLY. H.Q. OUT.
- HEY, LEHM.
- YES, MA'AM?
- TIME TO GO HUNTING.
- ( laughs )
I WAS HOPING YOU'D SAY THAT.
WILEE, WE'LL NEED THE
122 MIL ROUNDS FOR THIS OP.
MAO, GET 'EM LOCKED
AND LOADED, FAST.
LET'S GET THIS SHOW
ON THE ROAD, BOYS.
- IF A MAN KILLS ENOUGH PEOPLE,
HE'S NO LONGER A MAN.
HE BECOMES A DRAGON.
DRAGONS ARE TERRIBLE BEASTS
JEALOUSLY GUARDING THEIR HORDES
OF TREASURE.
THEIR NEED FOR VIOLENCE
GROWS WITH THEIR GREED
UNTIL THEY LOSE ALL VESTIGES
OF HUMANITY.
HUMANS CANNOT ALLOW DRAGONS
TO EXIST,
EVEN THOUGH THEY ARE MONSTERS
OF OUR OWN CREATION.
SLAYING A DRAGON
IS THE ULTIMATE HONOR.
SO IN A WAY, BALDRA,
I SHOULD THANK YOU.
- DAMN IT!
THIS HURTS.
CURSE THOSE MEDDLING BASTARDS.
YOU HEAR ME, DOCTOR?
YOU'RE NOT GONNA LIVE
TO SEE MORNING.
- Lehm: I GRABBED YOU GUYS
WITHOUT GIVING IT
A WHOLE LOT OF THOUGHT.
BUT THE THREE OF US
ALWAYS SEEM TO END UP
ON CLEAN-UP DUTY TOGETHER,
DON'T WE?
- Mao: YEAH,
NOW THAT YOU MENTION IT.
- ( laughs )
- Mao: CLEAR!
WILEE'S SCARY GOOD
WITH EXPLOSIVES.
HE TOOK OUT MOST OF 'EM.
- Wilee: I BURIED
A 122mm FLECHETTE ROUND
FOR THEM TO FIND.
JUST WAIT FOR IT.
- ( metal clanging
against car )
- WAIT, WHAT IS THAT?
- NOT SURE.
IRON DARTS?
- A FLECHETTE ROUND.
- WE GOT THE CHIEF DOCTOR
AND THE MANIAC IN CUSTODY.
THE DOC?
EH, HE'S HOLDIN' UP FINE.
IT'LL TAKE MORE THAN A COUPLE
BULLETS TO KILL THIS GUY.
( laughs )
- DONE. WE'VE SECURED
DR. RIVIERE.
- ( all cheering )
- WAY TO GO!
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
YOU'RE AMAZING.
- YOU SAVED HIS LIFE!
- I WASN'T SURE YOU'D BE ABLE
TO GET TO HIM.
WE CAN'T THANK YOU ENOUGH.
HONESTLY,
IT WAS A LITTLE TERRIFYING
TO SEE THE KIND OF POWER
YOU HAVE.
I WAS LISTENING
TO WHAT YOU SAID EARLIER.
AND I CAN'T HELP BUT WONDER--
MAYBE YOU'RE A DRAGON TOO.
OH, I MEAN, UH, NOT IN A BAD WAY
LIKE BALDRA OR ANYTHING!
I JUST, UM...
- ( laughs, coughs )
PRICELESS!
YOU'RE A RIOT, MAGGIE,
YOU KNOW THAT?
- SORRY, DID I OFFEND YOU?
- HEY, WHAT'S GOING ON?
DID YOU SAY SOMETHING AWKWARD
AGAIN, MAGGIE?
- ME, A DRAGON?
ONLY IF I GET TO BE A PEACEFUL,
FUN-LOVING ONE.
NO "BURNINATING" OR ANYTHING.
- ALL DONE?
- ALMOST.
JUST ONE THING LEFT.
- ( cell phone ringing )
- Scarecrow: HEKMATYAR!
- HELLO.
YOU'RE CALLING ME NOW.
HOW THE TABLES HAVE TURNED.
I TAKE IT THIS MEANS
YOU'VE RECONSIDERED MY OFFER.
- YEAH, $5 MILLION!
I WANT THAT INTEL.
- AS ALWAYS, IT'S A PLEASURE
DOING BUSINESS WITH YOU.
I'VE JUST SENT YOU THE G.P.S.
COORDINATES. CONGRATULATIONS.
TOMORROW THIS WILL BE
ON THE FRONT PAGE
OF NEWSPAPERS WORLDWIDE.
ADIEU.
- ( phone goes dead )
- SON OF A--
ONE DAY, I SWEAR,
I WILL TAKE HER DOWN!
HEY, BRING UP THE LOCATION.
- COMING RIGHT UP.
( humming )
OH, WOW! THAT KOKO'S
GOT A SERIOUS MEAN STREAK.
SHE SAID SHE'D MAKE IT EASY
FOR US, BUT HOLY CRAP.
- I'LL KILL YOU!
DO HEAR ME, BITCH?
YOU'RE A DEAD WOMAN,
HEKMATYAR!
- SEE YOU AROUND!
BYE, JONAH!  BYE, KOKO.
- MAN, THERE ARE
SOME CRAZY DOCTORS OUT THERE.
AM I RIGHT?
- YEAH.
- ONE OF THEM EVEN COMPARED ME
TO A DRAGON.
ISN'T THAT FUNNY?
HEY, JONAH?
WHAT'S A DRAGON'S ROAR
SOUND LIKE?
- RA-A-A-R.
LIKE THAT, MAYBE?
- ( laughs )
( Koko roaring loudly )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ♪ CONTROL, CONTROL ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS LOCO ♪
♪ I SAID, OH NO! ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS LOCO ♪
♪ I SAID, OH NO! ♪