- Lutz: JONAH, WRONG SPOT.
- OH, SORRY.
- RUN THE DRILL AGAIN.
- ( tires squeal )
- AW, COME ON.
- ( gunshot )
- Koko: R, YOU KNOW A C.I.A.
AGENT? PEOPLE CALL HIM BOOK MAN?
- YEAH, I'M FAMILIAR WITH HIM.
MET HIM IN BOSNIA
WHEN I WAS STILL ITALIAN ARMY.
DOES THIS HAVE ANYTHING TO DO
WITH WHAT THOSE HIT MEN SAID?
DIDN'T THEY MENTION
SOMETHING ABOUT THE C.I.A.?
- NO.  BOOK MAN CAME UP
IN SOME OTHER RUMORS.
I THINK THE HIT-MAN STUFF
IS A COINCIDENCE.
I CAN'T SEE SOMEONE AS
HIGH UP
AS THE EURO BRANCH CHIEF
PLAYING THAT CARD.
EVER HEAR OF ANOTHER AGENT
WHO GOES BY HEX?
A PARAMILITARY OPERATIONS
OFFICER? YOU KNOW, P.O.O.?
- SORRY.
DON'T KNOW HIM.
DOES HIS FACE HAVE SIX SIDES
OR SOMETHING?
- SHE'S A SHE.
HEX AS IN WITCH.
- R: I THINK HEX IS
THE ONE BEHIND
ALL THE RECENT ATTEMPTS
ON OUR GROUP.
ARE YOU OKAY
WITH SOME ROGUE AGENT
SCREWING OPERATION UNDERSHAFT?
- R, YOU ARE MY RIGHT ARM
AND HEX IS MY LEFT.
SHE'S STAYING.
FOR THE LONG HAUL.
ESPECIALLY SINCE THAT LEFT ARM
IS ATTACHED TO A FIST
THAT SMASHES TERRORISTS.
IF SHE WANTS A SACRIFICE,
WE MAY HAVE TO GIVE IT TO HER.
EVEN IF IT'S THE LIFE
OF A SINGLE CHILD.
- NO WAY.
I WON'T LET THAT HAPPEN, SAW.
I WON'T LET HEX KILL JONAH.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( cell phone ringing )
- Koko: HELLO?  HEY, R.
MM. MM-HM.
JUST WALKING AROUND
TOWN WITH JONAH.
YEAH.  YEAH.
WE'RE RIGHT BY THE HOTEL.
THANKS FOR CALLING
AND CHECKING IN, R.
YOU SOUND WINDED.
HAVE YOU BEEN RUNNING?
- YEP, MY MORNING JOG.
CIAO.
YOU REALLY WANNA GIVE JONAH
OVER TO HEX?
I WON'T DO IT.
DAMN IT,
YOU LISTEN TO ME, SAW.
IF YOU ALLOW THAT CHILD
TO BE KILLED,
YOU'LL BE FLUSHING OPERATION
UNDERSHAFT DOWN THE DRAIN.
- YOU DON'T SAY.
HOW DO YOU FIGURE?
- WHY DO YOU THINK KOKO
TOOK IN JONAH?
WHY INVITE A KID INTO A GROUP
OF ARMS DEALERS?
SHE'S ALWAYS LOGICAL,
CAUTIOUS.
BUT SHE'S TAKING
AN INTENTIONAL RISK WITH HIM.
SURE, AS AN EX-CHILD SOLDIER,
HE HAS HIS USES,
BUT THAT
DOESN'T MAKE IT SMART.
- ALL GOOD POINTS.
SO WHAT?
- HE CALMS HER.
JONAH ACTS LIKE A LIMITER
ON HER EMOTIONS.
- ( cell phone ringing )
WING COMMANDER SIMUNEK.
HOW ARE YOU THIS FINE MORNING?
THAT'S GOOD.
NO, THE PLEASURE IS ALL MINE.
I'M QUITE LOOKING FORWARD
TO OUR MEETING THIS AFTERNOON.
RIGHT NOW?
WELL, YOU DON'T WASTE TIME.
I MEAN I'D LOVE TO.
I'M REALLY NOT DRESSED
FOR BUSINESS, THOUGH.
I'M DOING THE TOURIST THING
AROUND TOWN.
SURE.
LONG AS YOU DON'T MIND.
HA.
HE JUST INVITED ME OUT TO TEA.
- YOU SHOULD
LET THE SQUAD KNOW
WE'LL BE LATE
GETTING BACK TO THE HOTEL.
- A "LIMITER," HUH?
- YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
THINK OF HIM LIKE A GOVERNOR
ON AN OLD CAR,
KEEPING THE LITTLE LADY
FROM OVERHEATING.
SHE'S GOT HUGE PLANS
THAT ONLY SHE KNOWS ABOUT.
BY BRINGING IN A BOY WHO'S
HAD TO FIGHT JUST TO SURVIVE,
SHE'S CREATED A PATH
TO RE-CONNECT WITH HER HUMANITY,
AND MAYBE A PATH
TO ABANDON THOSE PLANS
AND HER ENTIRE LIFE
AS AN ARMS DEALER.
BENEATH KOKO'S IRON MASK,
SHE STILL HAS THE SAME DESIRES
OF ANY GIRL HER AGE.
- STOP PLAYING SHRINK.
I EXPECT ACTUAL INTEL FROM YOU.
CLEAR?
SHE'S GOT YOU IN HER POCKET.
AT LEAST TRY TO RESIST
DANCING TO HER TUNE.
- HA, HA.  I'LL ADMIT, I HAVE A
GOOD TIME HANGING OUT WITH THEM.
HELL, RUNNING GUNS IS FUN.
BUT COME ON.
IF THERE'S ANYONE WHO WANTS
TO DANCE WITH THE LITTLE LADY,
IT'S TOTALLY YOU, SAW.
"I DON'T WANT TO SEE HER
BECOME A MONSTER," YOU SAID.
SO DON'T LIE.
PART OF YOU IS DYING TO SEE
EXACTLY WHAT HER PLANS ARE,
AND HOW THEY WORK OUT.
- ( elevator dings )
- HA!
YOU KNOW ME TOO WELL, R.
( laughs )
- Woman:
IS DIRECTOR BLACK LAUGHING?
- PLEASE, SAW,
YOU HAVE TO TELL ME
HEX'S LOCATION.
- I SUPPOSE I DO.
HEX IS 2.5 KLICKS
SOUTHEAST OF YOUR HOTEL,
IN THE PRAGUE B MARKET.
10 HEAVILY ARMED,
WELL-TRAINED MEN
SHOULD BE LYING IN WAIT THERE,
ALL OF THEM
ACTING UNDER HEX'S AUTHORITY.
THEIR OPERATION AGAINST KOKO
AND THE BOY IS ALREADY UNDERWAY.
THE CALL SHE GOT FOR A MEETING
WITH AIR FORCE OFFICER SIMUNEK
IS PART OF A TRAP
TO LURE HER TO THEM.
I'LL STOP IT.
I'M PLACING A CALL
TO THE LOCAL POLICE.
- ( dings )
- HEY, R,
YOU'RE UP EARLY.
WHATCHA BEEN UP TO?
YOU OUT JOGGING?
- YEAH, WHERE WERE YOU, LUTZ?
GOTTA STAY FIT.
- HEY, I WORK OUT.
I JOG.
- I'VE GOTTA HEAD BACK OUT
IN A MINUTE.
I'M OFF DUTY TODAY.
- ROGER THAT.
I ALWAYS WORK OUT.
- PRETTY NICE WEATHER
THIS MORNING.
- Man: TARGET IN SIGHT.
- ABOUT TIME.
LET'S GET THIS SHOW ON THE ROAD.
AND PROMISE YOU WON'T
GO EASY ON THE TARGET
JUST 'CAUSE HE'S A KID.
- ( thinking ) PRAGUE P.D. CAN'T
HANDLE A PARAMILITARY SQUAD.
DO I CALL THE LITTLE LADY?
TELL HER TO GET THE
HELL OUTTA THERE?
NO,
SHE'D FIGURE OUT I'M A MOLE.
- Black's voice: R, YOU ARE MY
RIGHT ARM AND HEX IS MY LEFT.
- BUT SHE'S A LEFT ARM
WHO DOESN'T LISTEN TO HER HEAD.
I WON'T GET A BETTER CHANCE
TO STOP HER.
AND IF I GOTTA BLOW COVER,
I'M GONNA DO IT KILLING HEX.
I'LL HAVE TO LEAVE KOKO'S CREW,
BUT SO BE IT.
- KOKO, THIS IS BAD.
CONTACT THE REST OF THE SQUAD.
TOO MANY EYES IN THE CROWD
ARE ON US.
WE'RE SURROUNDED.
- YEAH, I'M ON IT.
UNTIL LEHM AND THE REST
GET HERE, WE'LL HIDE BY THE--
- HIDING IN A CROWD ISN'T
ALWAYS THE SAFEST MOVE, GIRLY.
- WHO THE HELL ARE YOU?!
- HEAD'S UP.
- JONAH!
- ( gunshots )
- ( people screaming )
- WE HAVE SHOTS FIRED!
- ( all shouting )
- WHAT'D I SAY?
DON'T LET YOUR GUARD DOWN.
- JONAH.  JONAH!
- GET DOWN, KOKO!
- HA HA! YOU'RE PRETTY GOOD,
KID, TO DROP BOTTS LIKE THAT.
- YOU'RE NEXT.
- ( grunting )
- EXCUSE ME, MA'AM, YOU'RE--
- WHOOPS, YOU'RE IN MY WAY.
- R?
- YOU GUYS
GET BEHIND THE CAR!
- DAMN IT.
CAN SOMEONE THROW ME A WEAPON?
- JONAH, YOUR GEAR.
- WOW,
HER CREW MOVES FAST.
I WASN'T EXPECTING KOKO
TO HAVE BACK-UP HERE ALREADY.
- R: KOKO.
THIS WHOLE TIME
I'VE BEEN WORKING FOR BOOK MAN.
I'M A SPY.
I AM SO SORRY, LITTLE LADY.
AFTER I TAKE OUT HEX,
I'LL DISAPPEAR.
YOU'LL NEVER SEE
OR HEAR FROM ME AGAIN.
- THAT CAN'T BE.  R!
- Man:
A FIREFIGHT HAS BROKEN OUT.
- GOOD LUCK, RENATO.
- ( gunshots )
- DAMN IT, HEX,
I'LL KILL YOU!
- COME ON.
JONAH!
- SEAL THEIR EXITS.
NO ESCAPE.
- THAT GUY WHO JUST SHOWED UP,
IS THAT THE ONE KOKO CALLS R?
- YEAH.
THAT'S FUCKIN' HIM,
ALL RIGHT.
- THEN LET'S TAKE HIM OUT
RIGHT NOW
BEFORE HE CAN COVER
THEIR RETREAT.
SNIPERS A,
POWELL AND STYLES,
SNIPERS B,
GODUNOV AND RICKMAN,
YOUR TARGET, R.
HE'S--
- ( cell phone vibrating )
- AH!
- ( laughing )
YOU MORON.
- HE'S GOOD.
AND THERE'S EIGHT MORE
JUST LIKE HIM.
BUT I LIKE
MY FRIENDS' CHANCES BETTER.
BOSS, CALL FOR BACKUP.
- ( gunfire continues )
- Jonah: KOKO.  KOKO!
- JONAH.
- I-- I CAN'T FEEL MY LEGS.
MUSTA BEEN THAT SHOT.
FORGET ME, JUST RUN AWAY.
- JONAH!
- HEY, SAW,
WE NEED YOUR HELP.
- ABORT THE OPERATION
IMMEDIATELY.
THAT'S AN ORDER, HEX.
- ( Hex laughing )
SORRY, THAT TRAIN'S ALREADY
LEFT THE STATION.
IT'S A LITTLE LATE
TO STOP IT NOW.
IN FACT, I DON'T THINK
YOU EVER COULD HAVE STOPPED ME.
EVEN IF YOU CAME IN PERSON,
BEGGING ON YOUR KNEES.
UNDERSHAFT'S
ABOUT MAKING HER YOUR PUPPET.
BUT I'VE LEARNED SOMETHING
ABOUT KOKO.
NO MATTER HOW MUCH ENERGY
YOU SPEND
TRYING TO BRING HER
INTO YOUR FOLD,
EVENTUALLY
SHE WILL BECOME A MONSTER.
DO YOU REALLY WANT TO DANCE
WITH A MONSTER, CHIEF?
YOU MARK MY WORDS--
OPERATION UNDERSHAFT
WILL NEVER TRULY SUCCEED.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND
THE TERRORIST MIND.
- ARE YOU FINISHED?
YOU REVEALED YOUR TRUE LOYALTIES
TOWARD ME AND UNDERSHAFT
THE SECOND YOU DECIDED
TO TARGET MY RIGHT ARM.
WATCH YOURSELF.
- ( cell phone vibrating )
- R: SAW!
I NEED A REMOTE START
ON THIS SILVER SEDAN.
- SOMEONE HACK
THAT CAR'S AUTO-START.
- ( car starts )
- THANKS.
ONE MORE THING--
FIND A WAY TO GET LEHM
AND THE OTHERS HERE.
- DON'T WORRY,
I ALREADY TOOK CARE OF IT
BY WAY OF AN ANONYMOUS CALL.
- R-- R?
IT'S OKAY THAT YOU'RE A SPY.
I WON'T TELL THE OTHERS.
I PROMISE YOU.
- STOP THAT.
I NEED THE LITTLE LADY BACK.
GET IT TOGETHER.
FIRST THING I NEED YOU
TO DO IS GET JONAH
TO A HOSPITAL, OKAY?
- ALL RIGHT,
ARE WE TAKING HIM OUT OR NOT?
COME ON, BOSS, WHICH IS IT?
- JONAH, COME ON!
( grunting )
BASTARD!
- Man: SHIT, HE GOT ICO!
AND THEY GOT
THAT CAR STARTED.
WHAT THE HELL'S GOIN' ON?
- THERE WERE 10 TOTAL.
A FEW MUST BE
IN SNIPER POSITIONS.
HIT 'EM
WITH EVERYTHING YOU GOT.
- R, NO.
WHAT ABOUT YOU?
- WHEN THE OTHERS GET HERE,
I'LL TAKE ADVANTAGE
OF THE CHAOS AND HIGHTAIL IT.
SO THAT'S IT.
KOKO HEKMATYAR, SEE YOU SOON,
IN THE NEXT LIFE.
NOW GO!
- NOW I SEE
WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
YOU'RE A VERY BRAVE AGENT, R.
- ( tires squeal )
- R!
- WHOA, YOU'RE WAY HOTTER
THAN I EXPECTED.
COME ON,
LET'S DO THIS.
SHOW ME WHAT YA GOT!
- ( both firing )
- R: GUYS.
- THAT'S THEIR CAR.
OPEN FIRE!
- ( bullet zinging )
- SNIPER TEAM A,
NEUTRALIZED.
- ( tires squeal )
- SNIPER TEAM B, NEUTRALIZED.
- YOU GAVE THEM
MY GUYS' LOCATIONS?
HOW COULD YOU?
YOU DOUBLE CROSSED ME
FOR SOME TERRORIST SYMPATHIZER?
DAMN YOU, BOOK MAN.
DON'T THINK I WAS TRYING
TO KILL THEM OUT OF VENGEANCE.
I WAS ONLY TRYING TO DO WHAT
WAS BEST FOR THE COUNTRY I LOVE.
KOKO HEKMATYAR
WILL BECOME A MONSTER.
SHE WILL THREATEN OUR HOMELAND.
AND THE DAY SHE CHOMPS DOWN
ON YOU,
I HOPE YOU REMEMBER
I WAS RIGHT.
- HEY, BOSS,
WE'RE LOSING HERE.
JUST THREE OF US LEFT.
WHAT'RE YOUR ORDERS?  HEX?
- Hex: WE'RE RETREATING.
- Lehm: YOU DONE REAL GOOD
SAVING KOKO AND JONAH.
BUT DAMN, IT HURTS
LOSIN' A GOOD MAN LIKE YOU, R.
KOKO, R'S DEAD.
- UNDERSTOOD.
FOR NOW,
REGROUP THE REST OF THE SQUAD.
JONAH'S GONNA BE OKAY.
BYE.
- ( phone beeps )
- R.
- ( ringing )
- Man: H.C.L.I. HEADQUARTERS.
- PLEASE TELL ME
YOU'RE TRACKING HER.
- YES, MA'AM,
WE HAVE A LOCK ON THE TARGETS.
- DON'T LOSE HER.
IF YOU DO,
I'LL COME DOWN THERE
AND BLOW YOUR BRAINS OUT
MYSELF.
ECHO TOLD ME
I SHOULD ALWAYS BE SMILING.
BUT R ALWAYS SAID
HE COULDN'T TELL
WHAT I WAS THINKING,
THAT I WAS HIDING MY FEELINGS
BEHIND A CHESHIRE GRIN.
AND HE TOLD ME
THAT IT WASN'T NECESSARY.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I SHOULD DO.
- DOESN'T MATTER,
YOU'RE STILL A GOOD PERSON.
- I'M AN ARMS DEALER.
HOW THE HELL AM I A GOOD PERSON?
I'M SORRY, VALMET.
- YOU'RE RIGHT, YOU'RE
NOT GOOD. YOU'RE GREAT.
SOMEDAY IN THE FUTURE
YOU'LL REALIZE YOUR DREAM.
TRUST ME.
I CAN FEEL IT IN MY HEART.
R FELT THE SAME WAY
ABOUT YOU.
IT'S WHY HE GAVE HIS LIFE
IN BATTLE.
DON'T YOU SEE THAT?
COME ON, KOKO.
LET'S GET BACK TO THE OTHERS.
- OH, VALMET,
I'M GLAD YOU'RE ALL HEALED.
- THANKS,
IT'S GOOD TO BE BACK.
JUST ONE THING, KOKO,
IS THERE A REASON
WHY YOU'RE GROPING MY BOOBS?
I LOVE IT, OF COURSE,
BUT IT'S NOT YOUR STYLE.
- IN REMEMBRANCE OF R.
- WHY ME?
WHY SHOULD A PATRIOT
BE FORCED TO HIDE IN CAVES
LIKE THE SCUM SHE HUNTS?
WHAT KIND OF GOVERNMENT
TURNS ON THOSE
WHO WOULD DIE TO DEFEND IT?
I AM JUSTICE.
- WE'RE BACK
FROM THE SUPPLY RUN.
WE GOT YA SOME FRESH FOOD
AND CLEAN BANDAGES FOR YOUR EYE.
- WHAT'S THAT SOUND?
- ( jet hissing )
- IT'S A B52,
A BOMBER FROM OUR OWN COUNTRY.
I REALLY PISSED YOU OFF,
DIDN'T I, KOKO HEKMATYAR?
VERY WELL.
I LOOK FORWARD
TO OUR NEXT BATTLE IN HELL.
- THE DEED IS DONE.
- ( phone beeps )
- JONAH BROUGHT YOU FLOWERS, R.
- I REALLY CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU SAVED BOTH OF OUR LIVES.
SO BRAVE.
- HE SURE WAS.
- SO, THANK YOU, R.
- Tojo: KOKO.
- IT'S NICE TO FINALLY MEET YOU,
MISS HEKMATYAR.
I HOPE YOU UNDERSTAND ME
NOT BRINGING FLOWERS.
IN MY LINE OF WORK,
YOU LEARN NOT TO GET EMOTIONAL.
- WELL, IT'S CHIEF BLACK
OF THE N.C.S.'S EUROPEAN OFFICE.
YOU'RE HERE ALONE?
AND UNARMED, I HOPE.
- I'M UNARMED.
DO I LOOK LIKE I'M HERE
FOR A SHOOT-OUT?
CALL ME BOOK MAN.
ADEEB IF YOU PREFER,
OR BURRATINAIO.
IN FACT, YOU CAN CALL ME
WHATEVER YOU WANT.
BUT YOU
DON'T GET TO CALL ME SAW.
- BOOK MAN, THEN.
THANKS FOR YOUR HELP
WITH THE GUNFIGHT IN PRAGUE.
- SURE.
IT WAS MY PLEASURE.
BUT YOU CAN SKIP
THE FALSE GRATITUDE.
I'M IMPRESSED
THAT YOU COULD FIND THIS PLACE.
IT'S A REAL NICE SPOT.
R, REST IN PEACE.
LIMITER. HUH.
- WHAT'S THAT?
- THE BEST P.O.O.s MAKE
THEMSELVES IMPOSSIBLE TO FIND.
AS YOU CARRY ON WITH YOUR WORK,
I'D ADVISE YOU TO BE WARY
OF HEX'S SHADOW.
- THAT'S A GOOD POINT.
I'LL BE CAREFUL.
- I THINK IT'S TIME
FOR ME TO GO.
KOKO HEKMATYAR,
HOW MANY ROCKETS
HAVE YOU LAUNCHED?
- WHAT?  NO IDEA.
SAYONARA.
( laughs )
SO THAT'S YOUR PAL,
THE BOOK MAN.
SEEMS LIKE HE'S A REAL STICK
IN THE MUD.
I'M SURE YOU HAD WAY MORE FUN
WITH ME.
'SPECIALLY
THE DRINKING PARTIES.
THANK YOU,
AND GOODBYE, RENATO.
WE'LL MEET AGAIN.
- ( theme music playing )
- ( cell phone vibrating )
- THIS IS BLACK.  WHAT IS IT?
- Man: BOOK MAN, YOU ALONE?
YOU MIGHT WANNA
SIT DOWN FOR THIS.
- CALM DOWN, SON.
WHAT'S WRONG?
- THERE WAS AN AIR RAID
ON A MOUNTAIN RANGE
ALONG THE TURKEY-IRAQ BORDER.
WE THINK KOKO WAS BEHIND IT,
SIR.
SEEMS SHE USED
A RECONDITIONED HEAVY BOMBER.
IT DROPPED ENOUGH TONNAGE
THAT THE DEBRIS PLUME
SHOWED UP ON OUR SATELLITES.
THE GROUND TEAM
SAYS THEY FOUND TINY TRACES
OF THREE BODIES.
D.N.A.
MATCHED ONE OF THEM TO HEX.
- Black: I'VE LOST MY RIGHT
AND LEFT ARMS.
KOKO IS A MONSTER.
- SHE'S CREATED A PATH
TO RE-CONNECT WITH HER HUMANITY
AND ABANDON HER LIFE
AS AN ARMS DEALER.
- FROM ALL I'VE LEARNED
ABOUT HER,
SHE DOESN'T WALK AWAY
FROM ANYTHING.
- OPERATION UNDERSHAFT
WILL NEVER TRULY SUCCEED.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND
THE TERRORIST MIND.
- OH, YOU JUST SIT BACK
AND WATCH.
I'LL HAVE THE LITTLE LADY
DANCING TO MY TUNE
UNTIL SHE'S GASPING
FOR BREATH.
I'D ALWAYS PLANNED
TO JOIN THE MILITARY
AND GET MY HANDS DIRTY
IN THE FIELD, LIKE YOU.
- YOU DON'T SAY?
WELL,
KNOWING WHAT I KNOW NOW,
YOU CLEARLY
MADE THE RIGHT CHOICE.
- WELL, MY DREAMS
OF BEING A MARINE
WENT DOWN THE DRAIN FAST.
INJURED MY BACK
RIGHT OUT OF ANNAPOLIS.
THOUGH I'M BEGINNING TO SEE
THAT SOME OF THE METHODS
I USE IN MY CURRENT POST
AREN'T ALL THAT DIFFERENT.
AH, LISTEN TO ME
RATIONALIZING.
- R: HA HA! I THINK IT WAS
YOUR BODY WARNING YOU
THAT YOU JUST WEREN'T BUILT
FOR THAT KIND OF STUFF.
- ( laughing )
SHUT UP.
- ♪ CONTROL, CONTROL ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS LOCO ♪
♪ I SAID, OH NO! ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS LOCO ♪
♪ I SAID, OH NO! ♪