- I'M AFRAID THE DEAL IS OFF.
THOUGH I HAVE A FEELING
YOU'VE SURMISED THAT BY NOW.
- WH-- WH--
WHY AM I STILL ALIVE?
- YOU MEAN, WHY ARE YOU
THE ONLY ONE WE DIDN'T SHOOT?
WELL, IT'S LIKE THIS--
INSTEAD OF MONEY,
YOUR BOSS BROUGHT DRUGS
AS PAYMENT FOR OUR TRANSACTION.
WHEN HE OPENED THAT BRIEFCASE,
I NOTICED THAT YOU--
AND YOU ALONE--
HAD TURNED YOUR HEAD AWAY
WITH A LOOK OF
UTTER DISGUST ON YOUR FACE.
THAT INTRIGUED ME,
SO I SPARED YOU.
- YEAH, I WAS DISGUSTED.
WHY WOULDN'T I BE?
THAT STUFF
KILLED MY LITTLE BROTHER.
BUT IT'S NOT LIKE I COULD
SAY ANYTHING TO THE BOSS.
I'M JUST A DRIVER.
( thinking )
SHIT, I'M GONNA DIE.
SHE'S NOT GONNA LISTEN
TO A MOBSTER EXPLAINING HIMSELF.
- SO WHY DID YOU LOOK AWAY?
- I-- I'LL LEAVE THAT
TO YOUR IMAGINATION.
- ( coughing )
- ( Koko laughs )
ALL RIGHT THEN.
COME WITH ME.
ALWAYS WANTED A CHAUFFEUR.
UGO!  UGO!
- ( grunting )
DAMN YOU.
- ( metal clanging )
- ( theme music playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( grunting )
AW, SHIT,
BULLETPROOF!
- ( grunting )
AAH!
BEEN TWO MINUTES.
NEED TO GET OUT.
- UGO,
LEAVE THAT BASTARD TO ME.
- IN A MINUTE!
- YOU GET THE BOSS OUTTA HERE.
- ROGER!
- ( gunfire continues )
- GREG, TWO MINUTES ARE UP!
GREG?
DUDE!
YOU IN THERE?
AH!
WHA--
SHIT! ( grunts )
HYAH!
- All: DAMN.
- UGO, LET'S GO!
- ( tires squealing )
- THOSE TWO WEREN'T ALONE.
WHERE'S MY DAMN GUN?
- WHAT NOW?  SHAKE HIM
AND HEAD FOR THE SAFE HOUSE?
- NO POINT. THEY MUST KNOW
WHERE IT IS ALREADY.
THEY PLANNED FOR THIS.
RIGHT NOW, JUST HAUL ASS
DOWN ROUTE ONE.
- ( gun firing )
- NICE SHOT.  YOU HIT HIM?
- NO, I MISSED!
I CAN'T SEE.
- Dominique:
SHIT, THAT WAS CLOSE.
THAT CHICK
IS A PRETTY GOOD SHOT.
AND THAT WAS SOME SERIOUS
FIREPOWER. 50 CAL, I'D SAY.
THIS IS WHAT REALLY SUCKS
ABOUT TARGETING AN ARMS DEALER.
BUT I GOT 'EM SPOOKED ENOUGH
THEY'RE ACCELERATING LIKE MAD.
ALL I GOTTA DO
IS GET 'EM TO CRASH.
THAT'LL END
THIS DAMN CONTRACT.
- Ugo: WE'RE ALMOST THERE.
HEY BOSS, HAND YOUR PIECE TO ME.
THEN BRACE YOURSELF FOR IMPACT.
- OKAY.
- ( tires squealing )
- WHAA!
- SO, MOBSTER, YOU WANNA DANCE?
- HERE WE GO.
SOMETIMES I LIKE TO REMIND THE
LADY WHY SHE KEEPS ME AROUND.
- ( rap song playing )
♪ TIME TIME TIME TIME
TO ATTACK. ♪
- ( steam hissing )
- THIS SUCKS.
REALLY SUCKS.
NO SIGNAL, OF COURSE.
DAMN USELESS DESERT.
- ( tires squeal )
- USE MINE.
GO ON, "BOSS" DOMINIQUE.
YOUR LACKEYS
ARE ON THE OTHER END.
- Liliane: BOSS!  BOSS!
HELLO?  BOSS.
ARE YOU THERE, SIR? HELLO?
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
- LILIANE.
- OH, HEY, BOSS.
I GOT CAPTURED BY THE ENEMY.
I'M REAL SORRY.
- AND GREGOIRE?
- YEAH, HIM TOO.
WELL, SO MUCH FOR OPENING
OUR OWN RESTAURANT, HUH?
( laughs )
- THEY WERE SUPPOSED TO
HAVE GOTTEN THEMSELVES
OUT OF THERE BY NOW.
IF THIS SUCKED ANY HARDER,
I'D PROBABLY VOMIT.
- LOOKS LIKE YOU'VE
REACHED THE END OF THE ROAD.
UNLESS YOU WANT TO MAKE A DEAL.
I'LL LET YOU WALK AWAY.
AND ALL IT'LL COST?
THE NAME OF WHO HIRED YOU.
BETTER TO LIVE ON
AS A RESTAURATEUR
THAN DIE AS A HIT MAN.
- Valmet: I'M REALLY SORRY
ABOUT THIS, JONAH.
BUT IT WAS THE ONLY WAY.
WHAT COMES NEXT IS SOMETHING
I HAVE TO DO ON MY OWN.
THANK YOU FOR COMING THIS FAR,
THOUGH.
IT WAS KINDA SWEET.
TRY TO HIDE IT ALL YOU WANT,
BUT YOU'RE A GOOD GUY.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER, KIDDO.
IF I SURVIVE.
- IT WORKED.
SINCE I KNEW IT WAS COMING,
I WAS ABLE TO
FIGHT OFF THE DRUG.
20 MINUTES.
THERE'S STILL TIME.
I GOTTA GO.
- Man #1: HALT.
THIS IS PRIVATE PROPERTY.
DO YOU HAVE AN APPOINTMENT?
- Man #2: THE FACTORY'S NOT
EVEN OPEN YET. WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- YEAH, THIS IS DEFINITELY
THE PLACE.
- GO FIND OUT WHAT THE
PROBLEM IS AND DEAL WITH IT.
MMM.
- STATUS REPORT.
- Man: SHOTS AT THE GATE!
TWO DOWN, UNKNOWN INTRUDER.
- DEAD OR JUST WOUNDED?
- FATAL KNIFE WOUNDS.
- GET MOVING.
FIND THE INTRUDER RIGHT NOW.
- WHA-- A WOMAN?
HOSTILE IS A WHITE FEMA--
( grunts )
- ( gunfire continues )
- ONE WOMAN,
AND YOU CAN'T TAKE HER DOWN?
FORGET IT.
I'LL FINISH HER OFF.
JUST FLUSH HER OUT
INTO THE OPEN.
I'VE ALWAYS ENJOYED
A GOOD FOX HUNT.
HUH.
HOW COULD I HAVE MISSED
FROM THAT SHORT A DISTANCE?
- VALMET!
- JONAH?
NO FUCKING WAY.
HOW IS HE HERE?
THOSE PILLS SHOULD'VE
KEPT HIM OUT COLD FOR HOURS.
- YOU CAN MOVE FASTER THAN THIS!
GO TAKE THE BASTARD'S HEAD OFF!
JUST KEEP YOUR BACK TO ME.
RUN, VALMET!  RUN!
- SHE'S HEADED MY WAY.
THANKS, KID.
A BOY SOLDIER.
WASN'T THERE ONE OF THOSE
IN THE GROUP KAREN
AMBUSHED IN THE MOUNTAINS?
KOKO HEKMATYAR'S
PERSONAL GUARD, HUH?
INTERESTING.
- FASTER!  FASTER!
I AM RUNNING TOWARD VENGEANCE
FOR THE MEN I LOST
IN THIS DESERT.
THIS IS FOR THEM!
YES! I CAN ALMOST
HEAR THEM REJOICING.
THEY ARE SHOUTING OUT,
"THANK YOU, MAJOR!"
- ( laughs ) SORRY,
BUT DEAD MEN DON'T TALK.
- THESE DO.
THEY'RE MY MEN.
AND THEIR SOULS ARE ALIVE
AND WELL.
GUOMING CHEN OF THE DA SHINGHAI
TRADING COMPANY, YOU'RE MINE.
- YOU MUST BE SURE OF YOURSELF
TO CHALLENGE A GENERAL
OF THE P.L.A.
YEAH, I RECOGNIZE YOU NOW.
MAJOR VELMER,
FORMERLY OF UN-FID, ISN'T IT?
YOU'VE AGED FAST.
- FUNNY, COMING
FROM YOUR WRINKLED OLD FACE.
AND I GOTTA SAY,
I AM SURPRISED YOU REMEMBER ME.
- YES, WELL,
I COULDN'T POSSIBLY REMEMBER
EVERY PERSON
I'VE KILLED OVER THE YEARS.
HONESTLY, YOU ONLY STAND OUT
BECAUSE YOU'RE ONE OF
THE FEW I FAILED TO KILL.
YOUR PRESENCE IN THIS FACTORY
IS CAUSING SOME LONG-BURIED
EMOTIONS TO BUBBLE UP,
MUCH LIKE THE
NATURAL GAS BUBBLING UP
FROM THE FIELD WE'RE MINING.
THAT WAS ONCE
YOUR U.N. PATROL GROUNDS.
I REMEMBER THAT DAY.
I ONLY HAD A MINUTE
BEFORE
YOUR REINFORCEMENTS ARRIVED.
I KNEW I HADN'T KILLED
THE UNIT COMMANDER,
BUT I COULDN'T FIND YOU.
IT WAS HUMILIATING.
WHERE WERE YOU HIDING?
NO, LET ME GUESS.
ONE OF YOUR MEN FELL ON YOU AND
YOU LAY THERE UNDER HIS CORPSE.
- ( gunshot )
- I'VE BEEN TOLD WHAT A
DISGUSTING HUMAN BEING YOU ARE.
BUT THAT WAS
NO SURPRISE TO ME. I KNEW.
I TRAINED HARD SO I
COULD KILL YOU ONE DAY.
BUT THE MORE I TRAINED,
THE MORE MY STYLE
CAME TO RESEMBLE YOURS,
LIKE IT HAD BEEN BURNED
INTO MY BRAIN.
BUT THAT WILL CHANGE
AFTER TODAY.
I CAN ABANDON THE KNIFE
FOR GOOD.
OF COURSE, NOT UNTIL
AFTER I'VE USED IT
TO SLICE YOU INTO RIBBONS.
HAKKAA PAALLE!
ON YOUR FEET, GENERAL!
I'LL HAVE MY REVENGE.
AND I'LL TAKE FROM YOU WHAT
YOU TOOK FROM ME--EVERYTHING!
- LET'S NOT GET MELODRAMATIC.
ANYWAY, YOU SHOULD BE
GRATEFUL TO ME, MAJOR.
LOSING EVERYTHING
HAS ENABLED YOU
TO FINALLY REACH YOUR
FULL POTENTIAL AS A SOLDIER.
DON'T LET MY INJURY FOOL YOU
INTO UNDERESTIMATING ME.
I DON'T NEED TWO
GOOD LEGS TO KILL YOU.
- ( two gunshots )
- SO HOT.
- ( slow song playing
in Portuguese )
- WHAT IS IT?
- KAREN.  IT'S HORRIBLE!
THE EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR
AND EVERYONE.
GENERAL!
OH, NO.
( sobbing )
SHE WILL DIE.
- ( yawning )
- STILL KINDA SLEEPY.
VALMET?
- YEAH, SORRY ABOUT THAT.
WHAT IS IT?
- CAN WE GET BACK
TO THE OTHERS NOW?
- ( tires squeal )
- Jonah:
VALMET?  VALMET?
- I-- I--
I HATE THIS WORLD! YOU HEAR
THAT, WORLD? SCREW YOU!
- ( two shots fire )
- ( song in
Portuguese continues )
- ( gasps )
- Koko:
GOOD MORNING, SUNSHINE.
- KOKO?
GOOD MORNING TO YOU TOO.
( grunts )
- YOU SHOULD BE MORE CAREFUL.
YOU WENT AND GOT YOURSELF
ALL SHOT UP.
.45 CALIBER-- TWO TO THE BACK
AND ONE TO THE THIGH.
JONAH PATCHED YOU UP
ON THE SPOT AND SAVED YOUR LIFE.
YOU MIGHT WANT
TO SAY THANK YOU.
INTERESTING HAIR CUT.
IF YOU WANTED SOMETHING
DIFFERENT THOUGH,
YOU SHOULDA REALLY COMMITTED
AND CHOPPED IT OFF
LIKE THE OLD DAYS.
- UM, KOKO, I'M SORRY.
BUT AREN'T YOU MAD AT ME?
- UH-HUH.
I'M PISSED AS HELL.
WHY, CAN'T YOU TELL?
- ( laughs nervously )
- FOR STARTERS,
TAKE A LOOK AT THAT!
THE BED'S ALL MADE UP
AND EVERYTHING.
IT USED TO BE OCCUPIED
BY THE WOMAN WHO SHOT YOU!
LIEUTENANT KAREN LOW OF THE
DA XINGHAI TRADING COMPANY.
SHE DISAPPEARED.
VANISHED INTO THIN AIR.
WHAA!  THIS IS GONNA COST!
HUSH MONEY TO DOCTORS,
MORE HUSH MONEY
FOR ARMY HELICOPTER TRANSPORT,
AND EVEN MORE HUSH MONEY STILL
TO HIDE JONAH'S VERY EXISTENCE!
IF THAT'S NOT BAD ENOUGH,
I HAVE TO COVER KAREN
LOW'S HOSPITAL FEES TOO.
AND THEY'RE HIGH.
SO, YOU SEE, I AM MAD.
BUT MOSTLY ABOUT THE MONEY.
MAN, THE DOCTORS HAVE BEEN
BREATHING DOWN MY FRIGGIN' NECK.
BET THEY'LL BE HERE ANY MINUTE.
"CAN WE HAVE A WORD
ABOUT THE BILL?"
THIS WAS A SERIOUS INCIDENT.
TERRORIST ACTION.
AIDING A TERRORIST.
IT'S BAD.
I THINK WE'VE REACHED A WHOLE
NEW LEVEL OF EVIL WITH THIS ONE.
BUT YOU KNOW, MAJOR VELMER,
I AM OF ONE MIND ON THIS.
I BELIEVE THE SOULS OF THE
MEN YOU LOST IN THAT DESERT
ARE NOW RESTING PEACEFULLY.
YOU DID NOT FAIL
A SINGLE ONE OF THEM.
YOU HAVE MY ADMIRATION.
I HOPE YOU DON'T MIND HEARING
THAT FROM SOMEONE LIKE ME.
- COURSE NOT, KOKO.
- WHAT ON EARTH ARE YOU DOING?
- OKAY, NOW THAT MAJOR VELMER
HAS COMPLETED HER MISSION,
WHAT IS VALMET GOING TO DO?
- I BELONG TO YOU,
AND ONLY YOU, FOREVER, KOKO.
- THAT'S GOOD TO HEAR.
NOW HURRY UP AND GET BETTER.
AND DON'T FORGET THIS--
TOOL OF THE TRADE AND ALL.
YOU'RE GONNA NEED IT.
I SHOULD GO.
I'LL COME BACK TO VISIT LATER.
TRY NOT TO GO CRAZY ON 'EM HERE.
OH, ONE MORE THING--
ABOUT YOUR HAIRCUT--
I THINK YOU SHOULD
GROW IT OUT AGAIN.
THE MAJOR KEPT HER HAIR SHORT.
I DON'T KNOW, JUST THOUGHT
I'D THROW IT OUT THERE.
- Doctor: MS. HEKMATYAR,
IF YOU DON'T MIND--
- YEAH YEAH,
I'LL FORK OVER THE CASH.
- AND, UH--
- I SAID I WOULD PAY!
- Jonah: YOU WERE ATTACKED
BY ASSASSINS AGAIN?
- YEAH, NO BIGGIE.
- WHAT WERE THEY LIKE?
ANY CASUALTIES?
- THEY WERE LIKE
STREET PERFORMERS.
YOU SHOULDA SEEN 'EM.
TOTAL FREAKS.
AS FOR CASUALTIES,
LEHM HAS MINOR WOUNDS
AND LUTZ WAS KNIFED
IN THE BUTT.
- HEH.
LUTZ AND HIS BUTT.
- SO CLOSE.
I ALMOST CAUGHT YOU SMILING.
IN THIS CASE,
IT WAS MORE BENEFICIAL
FOR ME TO LET 'EM LIVE.
THEIR CLIENT, ON THE
OTHER HAND, NOT SO MUCH.
- HUH?  THEY TOLD YOU
WHO THEY WERE WORKING FOR?
- LIKE I SAID, TOTAL FREAKS.
( laughs )
WELL, ALL OF THAT'S OVER NOW.
I GAVE THE TEAM
SOME TIME OFF,
BUT WE'LL REGROUP
FOR THE NEXT JOB.
TILL THEN, I HAVE YOU
TO PROTECT ME.
SO I KNOW I'M SAFE.
YOU DID A GREAT JOB BACK THERE.
- I DIDN'T REALLY DO
MUCH OF ANYTHING THOUGH.
- YOU DESERVE A REWARD.
WHAT'S IT GONNA IT BE?
- I AM KINDA HUNGRY.
- Nurse:
OH!  DOCTOR!
THE G.S.W. PATIENT
IS DOING CRUNCHES.
- WHAT?  AGAIN?
- SHOULDN'T THIS BE
A PHYSICAL IMPOSSIBILITY?
- CALM DOWN
AND GET HER BACK IN BED.
- GORGEOUS MORNING, ISN'T IT?
- SURE IS.
- HEY, DAD,
DO YOU THINK YOU COULD
STOP DUMPING YOUR SWEATY
WORKOUT CLOTHES ON THE FLOOR?
- AW, GROSS!
- HA!
- ( groans ) MOTHER!
SAY SOMETHING, WILL YOU?
- WHY?  YOU TWO
GO THROUGH THIS EVERY MORNING.
YOU'RE JUST TOO MUCH ALIKE.
SAME APPETITES EVEN.
- ALL RIGHT.
I'M OFF.
- HEY, BOOK MAN.
- HI.
IMPECCABLE TIMING.
WE NEED TO CANCEL
OPERATION UNDERSHAFT FOR TODAY.
I'M HEADING OUT OF TOWN,
AND THERE ISN'T MUCH TIME
UNTIL MY FLIGHT.
WOULD YOU MIND PASSING THE WORD
ALONG TO EVERYONE?
- COME ON. THAT'S THE ONLY
REASON I GOT HERE SO EARLY.
- SORRY ABOUT THAT.
MORNING.
- GOOD MORNING, CHIEF BLACK.
HOW ARE YOU?
- THE TICKETS?
- GOT THEM.
- I'LL BE READY TO LEAVE
FOR DULLES IN A FEW MOMENTS.
- OF COURSE, SIR.
CHIEF, DO YOU MIND
IF I ASK YOU SOMETHING?
- WHAT'S THAT?
- WELL, I'VE BEEN WONDERING
THIS FOR A WHILE.
WHY DO PEOPLE
CALL YOU BOOK MAN?
- BECAUSE THEY
CONSIDER ME A SCHOLAR.
I SPEAK ARABIC.
AND I STUDIED
ANCIENT ARABIAN LITERATURE.
PEOPLE ASSOCIATE ME
WITH BOOK LEARNING.
MIDDLE EASTERNERS
CALL ME ADEEB,
WHICH MEANS "MAN OF LETTERS."
ORIGINALLY, I'D WANTED TO BECOME
AN ARABIC HISTORIAN.
ITALIANS CALL ME BURATTINAIO.
THAT ONE TRANSLATES
AS "PUPPET MASTER."
I GOT SO MANY NICKNAMES,
SOMETIMES I FORGET THE REAL ONE.
- ( laughs )
I DOUBT THAT.
- I'M NOT KIDDING.
IT'S HARD TO KEEP UP.
- WE'LL BE AT THE
AIRPORT SOON, SIR.
- ( end theme playing )
- ( singing in Japanese )
- ( thinking ) KOKO HEKMATYAR
IS CURRENTLY IN ALEXANDRIA.
DID HE SET THE MEET FOR PARIS
BECAUSE IT'S THE MIDPOINT?
MAYBE HE'S GROWN UP ENOUGH
TO KNOW
WHEN TO SHOW SOME RESPECT.
- ( door opens )
- R: SORRY.
DID I KEEP YOU WAITING
VERY LONG?
- YES.
FOR QUITE A WHILE.
- IT'S BEEN AGES, SAW.
- I'M GLAD TO SEE
YOU'RE DOING WELL, R.