- ♪ HER NAME IS KOKO... ♪
- DO YOU HAVE A MOMENT TO TALK?
IT'S AKIHIKO TOJO.
- DIDN'T THINK I'D HEAR YOUR
VOICE TODAY. IT'S BEEN AGES.
- I'D LIKE YOU TO PULL OUT
OF THE CONFLICT
CONCERNING KASPER'S
SOUTHEAST ASIAN TRADE ROUTE.
H.C.L.I. IS TAKING MEASURES
TO ELIMINATE THE S.R. UNIT.
- COLONEL HINOKI CALLED TOJO
LATE LAST NIGHT
AND EMAILED ME TO CONFIRM.
HE WANTS TO PARLAY.
THE LOCATION IS THE
PARKING AREA AT UMIHOTARU.
IF WE MISS THIS CHANCE, FINDING
THEM AGAIN WON'T BE EASY.
LET'S MOVE OUT.
- I REALLY DON'T CARE.
CAN I SEE THIS PROPOSAL?
- THANK YOU FOR YOUR
UNDERSTANDING, MR. KASPER.
THAT'S VERY GOOD OF YOU.
WE'LL MOVE RIGHT
TO THE DOCUMENTS,
AS YOU'VE REQUESTED.
- WAKE UP, SIR. YOU SPACED
OUT. SHE'S AN ASSASSIN.
THE S.R. UNIT'S
MOVING AGAINST US.
- ( laughing )
TOJO, YOU WERE WAY
OFF THE MARK ON THIS ONE.
BUT THIS IS NO STRIKE,
HE'S JUST TESTING ME.
COLONEL HINOKI NEEDS
TO STOP PLAYING
AND BRING ME A REAL FIGHT.
WHATEVER.
JUST MAKE SURE
YOU KILL 'EM ALL.
- ( theme music playing )
- TOJO, I GOT A QUESTION.
- HUH?
- YOU HAD SOME ELITE JOBS
WORKING FOR THE S.R. UNIT
AND FOR KASPER,
SO WHY'D YOU DECIDE TO QUIT?
- WHAT THE WHAT?
THAT SURE CAME OUT OF NOWHERE.
SO MUCH FOR THE
SILENT UNDERSTANDING
TO NOT GET PERSONAL.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL AT LEAST TELL
YOU WHY I PREFER KOKO'S SQUAD.
WHICH ONE DO YOU WANT--
THE AMUSING ANSWER
OR THE SERIOUS ONE?
- THE SERIOUS ONE.
- 'CAUSE AT THIS JOB,
I GET TO WORK
WITH TWO SMOKIN' HOT LADIES.
- ( all laughing )
- TOJO, YOUR SALARY
JUST DOUBLED FOR THIS MONTH.
- Lutz: SERIOUSLY?  FOR THAT?
- ( men laugh )
- AW, MAN. YOU'RE JOKIN' RIGHT?
- JONAH, GET THIS.
YOU KNOW WHERE WE ARE RIGHT NOW?
UNDER THE OCEAN.
- REALLY?
THAT'S AWESOME.
- YEAH,
IT'S CALLED THE AQUA-LINE.
- LIKES TUNNELS, BUT DOESN'T
CARE ABOUT HOT BABES?
KIND OF IRONIC.
- ( all laughing )
- LOOK AT THAT.
- IT'S LIKE A CASTLE
BUILT ON THE OCEAN.
- Koko: ALL RIGHT, GUYS,
WE'RE HERE.
- Lutz: 'KAY.
- LET'S PARK DEEPER INSIDE,
UGO.
MORE COVER.
- ROGER THAT.
- Koko: OKAY,
EVERYONE STICK TO THE PLAN
AND WE SHOULD BE JUST FINE.
JONAH, WE'LL BE COUNTING ON YOU.
- GOT IT.
I'LL LET YOU KNOW
WHEN I FIND HIM.
- KOKO, I STILL CAN'T GET A HOLD
OF COLONEL HINOKI.
- THEN KEEP CALLING HIM
TILL YOU DO.
Koko: JONAH, HAVE YOU REACHED
THE MEETING POINT YET?
I'M GETTING A BAD FEELING.
STAY ON GUARD.
- UNDERSTOOD.
I'M IN THE RESTAURANT NOW.
LOOKS LIKE
YOUR HUNCH IS RIGHT.
THERE'S NOBODY HERE.
- JONAH, GET BACK DOWN HERE.
HURRY.
LEHM, YOU COPY?
WE'VE WALKED
INTO THE COLONEL'S TRAP.
LEHM, REPORT.
WHERE ARE YOU?
- KOKO,
GET BACK IN THE CAR NOW.
WAIT, THAT'S--
- Man: OPERATION COMMENCING,
COLONEL.
- THIS IS IT.
GIVE THEM EVERYTHING YOU GOT.
THE JAKARTA MISSION
WAS A TOTAL SUCCESS.
NOW IT'S YOUR TURN.
- YES, SIR.
- ( phone beeps )
- WE ARE GHOSTS.
WE CANNOT BE STOPPED.
- GET MOVING!
HEAD FOR THE EXIT.
IT'S THEM.
- TOJO?
- SOMEONE'S GOTTA
GO GET JONAH.
- Man: KABURAGI,
THE TRAITOR IS HEADING YOUR WAY.
HEADS UP.
- I'LL HANDLE HIM TOO.
- Woman: WHAT'S GOING ON?
- Tojo: KABURAGI!
- Kaburagi: DAMN YOU.
DAMN YOU, TRAITOR.
DAMN YOU.
- Woman:
THEY'RE FILMING ON LOCATION.
- Woman #2:
WOW.
- I AM NOT A TRAITOR!
DON'T MAKE ME YOUR SCAPEGOAT.
YOU'RE THE ONES
WHO WENT BERSERK.
- Man: UM,
BUT WHERE ARE THE CAMERAS?
- JONAH, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- YEAH, I'M FINE.
- THE ATTACK'S ON.
WE'LL BOOST A CAR
AND CATCH UP TO KOKO.
- THAT'S A LOT OF BLOOD.
YOU OKAY?
- HURTS LIKE HELL,
BUT I'LL LIVE.
- Jonah: KOKO. KOKO!
- JONAH, YOU ALL RIGHT?
- TOJO'S BEEN SHOT.
- HOW BAD?
- Tojo: I'LL BE FINE.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
I SCOOPED UP JONAH
AND BORROWED A CAR.
WE JUST LEFT THE GARAGE.
WHAT'S YOUR 20?
- WE'RE STICKING WITH THE PLAN
AND HEADING TOWARDS KAWASAKI.
THERE'RE TWO ENEMY VEHICLES
ON OUR TAIL.
YOU'LL HAVE TO EVADE.
THE LOCAL POLICE
HAVE SET UP A BARRICADE
AT THE BRIDGE ENTRANCE
TO THE TUNNEL.  BE CAREFUL!
- Tojo: I GOT THROUGH.
TRY NOT TO SHOOT US
WHEN WE CATCH UP TO YA.
- THOSE DIRTY SONS OF BITCHES
ARE PUTTING HOLES IN MY BABY.
- SOUNDS LIKE THEY'RE
BREAKING THROUGH
THE BULLETPROOF PLATES.
- ONCE WE GET OUT OF THE TUNNEL,
WE'RE IN THE CLEAR.
HANG ON!
- COPY THAT.
- SON OF A BITCH, THIS HURTS.
- I'M SORRY, THAT RUBBER
TAPE WAS ALL I HAD ON ME.
- IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT, JONAH.
I'M THE ONE WHO GOT SHOT.
I'M JUST LUCKY WE WERE ABLE
TO STOP THE BLEEDING.
ANYWAY,
ARE YOU READY FOR ACTION?
WE'RE GONNA SLIP
PAST THE ENEMY CARS,
NAIL 'EM FROM THE SIDE.
- SURE THING.
- PICK UP YOUR PHONE, COLONEL.
YOU OWE ME AN EXPLANATION.
- ( ringing )
- TOJO'S READY TO MAKE HIS MOVE.
FORCE THOSE CARS INTO ONE LANE.
- TO THE RIGHT!
- Tojo: GOT IT.
- BULLETPROOF.
- Koko: SUPPRESSIVE FIRE!
- Jonah: PASS 'EM.
- WE'RE CLOSE!
TAKE THE BAYSHORE ROUTE.
DON'T LET UP.
WE CAN MAKE IT!
THAT'S HOW IT'S DONE.
- YES!
- Lutz: ROASTED EM!
- Koko: THERE COULD BE MORE.
DON'T DROP YOUR GUARD YET.
- YOU'RE NOT INJURED,
ARE YOU?
- I'M FINE.
HOW ARE YOU HOLDING UP?
- I'M GOOD.
- UM, YOU DO KNOW
THERE'S SOMEONE ON THE OTHER
END OF THAT LINE, RIGHT?
- Hinoki: HELLO?
HELLO? ANYONE THERE?
- YES, COLONEL HINOKI,
I'M HERE.
- YOU GOT AN ODD SENSE
OF PHONE ETIQUETTE, TOJO.
MOST PEOPLE TALK
WHEN THEY CALL.
I ALMOST HUNG UP.
( laughing )
- CUT THE CRAP.
WHERE ARE YOU, COLONEL?
- IF I TOLD YOU THAT,
IT WOULD
DEFEAT THE WHOLE PURPOSE.
- THE PURPOSE OF WHAT?
THEY'RE DEAD.
WHAT THE HELL WERE YOU TRYING
TO ACCOMPLISH HERE?
- H.C.L.I.'S FIREPOWER
VERSUS THE S.R. UNIT'S PROWESS.
THERE WAS ONLY ONE WAY
THIS COULD GO.
AND THIS IS
HOW BOTH SIDES WANTED IT.
I JUST GRANTED THEIR WISH.
( laughing )
COME ON, TOJO.
YOU KNOW YOU'VE
ALWAYS WANTED THIS FIGHT TOO.
- Tojo: HEY, WHERE ARE
THE CUBAN OPERATIVES?
WHY ON EARTH
ARE WE THE ONLY ONES HERE?
YOU GAVE THOSE AGENTS
A FALSE RENDEZVOUS POINT,
DIDN'T YOU?
IF THE ARMY FINDS THEM,
YOU KNOW THEY'LL BE EXECUTED.
- TOJO, THIS IS HOW
IT HAS TO GO DOWN.  LET'S GO.
- I WANNA HEAR IT FROM YOU,
COLONEL. AH!
- SORRY TO KEEP YOU WAITING,
BOYS.
I'M THE LAST ONE, RIGHT?
LET'S MOVE THE HELL OUT.
- SO YOU'RE OKAY
WITH THIS TOO?
- SHUT UP AND READ
THE SITUATION, TOJO.
LEAVING THEM
REMOVES A VARIABLE,
AND DISTRACTS THE HOSTILES
WHILE WE DISAPPEAR.
WHAT'S THE ONE THING
WE CAN'T DO ON THIS MISSION?
WE CAN'T LEAVE
ANY JAPANESE CORPSES
ON THIS BEACH.
IT WOULD UNDERMINE
EVERYTHING WE'VE DONE.
- Tojo: ELITE INTELLIGENCE?
THAT'S WHAT WE CLAIM TO BE.
WHAT A JOKE.
LOOK AT OUR OBJECTIVE--
INFILTRATE A COMMUNIST COUNTRY
AND ASSASSINATE
THEIR MILITARY LEADERS.
WHEN DID THIS UNIT
TURN INTO OMEGA OR GORGON?
- ( thinking )
KID'S GONE SOFT ON US.
- Man:
WHAT, ARE YOU SURPRISED?
HE CAME FROM CENTRAL SYSTEM
ADMIN. HE'S A GEEK WITH A GUN.
- Man #2: BEFORE THAT
HE WAS WITH ELECTRONIC WARFARE.
LIKE THEY GET
THEIR HANDS DIRTY.
- THAT'S ENOUGH.
CUT THE CHATTER.
( scoffs )
- Tojo: I'M SICK OF THIS.
I LEFT THE S.R. UNIT
THE SAME DAY WE REACHED JAKARTA.
I'VE OFTEN WONDERED
IF I GAVE UP ON THEM
TOO QUICKLY, THOUGH.
I WAS SURPRISED AT HOW
READILY COLONEL HINOKI
ACCEPTED MY RESIGNATION.
HE DIDN'T TRY TO STOP ME
LIKE YOU'D EXPECT
FROM A TOP-SECRET AGENCY.
WHAT THE HELL
AM I GONNA DO NOW?
FOOD'S A GOOD START.
THAT OUGHTA KILL SOME TIME.
ON PAPER, I HAD "DIED IN
AN ACCIDENT" YEARS AGO.
AND NOW
I'D QUIT MY UNDERCOVER GIG.
HOW DO YOU FIND
EMPLOYMENT AFTER THAT?
- YO.
- 20 MINUTES LATER,
I HAD A NEW JOB.
I FIGURED
SOME OF THE S.R. UNIT GUYS
WOULD ASSUME I'D BEEN DEALING
WITH KASPER ALL ALONG.
THIS IS WHAT YOU'D CALL
A TEXTBOOK CASE
OF "MISREADING THE SITUATION."
- DAMN YOU, TRAITOR.
DAMN YOU.
- A MAN CAN'T BE CHANGED
SO EASILY.
BUT A GROUP
IS A DIFFERENT STORY.
- KASPER WAS ONLY HALF RIGHT.
MEN CAN CHANGE QUITE EASILY.
WE BEND WHICHEVER WAY
THE WIND BLOWS.
THAT'S WHAT
I'M REALIZING NOW.
HE WAS THE BEST SPY
HIS COUNTRY'D EVER HAD.
HE'D SPENT YEARS OF HIS LIFE
DEVELOPING THAT AGENCY.
HE WAS AS SOLID AS A ROCK.
BUT AS SOON WE HAD HIM CORNERED,
HE ABANDONED EVERY ONE,
JUST TO SAVE HIMSELF.
- Koko: HELLO, BAHAMAS.
WHITE SAND, BLUE SKIES.
THE GUY HANGS UP HIS HAT
AND DISAPPEARS
TO A TROPICAL TAX HAVEN?
IT'S LIKE
A REAL-LIFE SPY MOVIE.
- SO WHERE IS HE?
- I DON'T KNOW. MAYBE A
SHARK ATE HIM OR SOMETHING.
EH?
- AH! DAMN IT, KOKO.
I'M HEALING
FROM A BULLET WOUND HERE.
- YOU MUST HAVE THE ONLY
FROWNY-FACE IN PARADISE, TOJO.
WE ACTUALLY TRACKED DOWN
JAPAN'S ONE AND ONLY SPYMASTER.
HAVE SOME PRIDE
IN YOUR ACCOMPLISHMENTS.
LISTEN, WHEN YOU SEE HIM,
I WON'T TELL YOU HOW TO REACT.
THAT'S YOUR CALL.
BUT THE CONSEQUENCES
WILL BE YOURS, AS WELL.
- YOU KNOW, KOKO,
THERE'S A GOOD CHANCE
WE'VE BEEN DANCING
TO THE COLONEL'S TUNE
THIS ENTIRE TIME.
- AH!
( whimpering )
- YOU DIDN'T CRY.
THAT'S A GOOD GIRL.
- WHY CRY?
THAT'S FOR SAD PEOPLE.
- ( Koko laughs )
LOOK AT THAT!
JONAH'S A PURE CHICK MAGNET.
HE MAY NOT LIKE GIRLS,
BUT THEY SURE LIKE HIM.
JONAH, GO PLAY.
BUILD A CASTLE OR SOMETHING.
- FINE.
- Hinoki: WELL, I'M IMPRESSED
YOU WERE ABLE
TO FIND ME HERE, TOJO.
CAN'T EVEN REMEMBER
HOW MANY YEARS IT'S BEEN
SINCE I SAW YOU LAST.
WHAT WAS IT, CUBA?
- PLEASE, COLONEL,
YOU REMEMBER EVERY HOUR,
MINUTE AND SECOND
OF THAT OPERATION.
YOU KNOW DAMN WELL
WHEN IT WAS I LEFT.
- KOKO HEKMATYAR,
IT'S TRULY A PLEASURE
TO MEET YOU.
I'M HINOKI,
THE FORMER S.R. UNIT DIRECTOR.
I'M SORRY MY SUBORDINATES
DEVIATED FROM THEIR ORDERS
AND ATTACKED YOU.
IT SEEMS THEY WERE TOO PROUD
TO NEGOTIATE.
I HOPE YOU DIDN'T SUFFER
LASTING DAMAGE.
- I ASSURE YOU, COLONEL HINOKI,
THE PLEASURE IS ALL MINE.
AND YES, WE'RE FINE.
TOJO TOOK TWO BULLETS
TO THE SHOULDER
AND ONE OF OUR CARS
GOT TORN UP.
OUR DRIVER
WASN'T VERY THRILLED.
BUT WE'LL GET HIM NEW TOYS.
NOW I KNOW
YOU HAVE CATCHING UP TO DO.
SO IF YOU DON'T MIND,
I'LL LEAVE YOU BOYS TO IT.
JONAH!
SAVE A TURRET FOR ME.
- WAIT, THAT'S ALL
SHE HAS TO SAY TO YOU?
YOU CAME AT US.
- YOUR BOSS IS PRACTICAL.
ALL SHE SEES
IS THE BOTTOM LINE.
I COULD HAVE DRAGGED THIS OUT.
BUT SIMULTANEOUS ATTACKS
WERE THE BEST WAY
TO BRING THIS
TO ITS INEVITABLE END.
I HOPE KASPER CALLED
TO THANK YOU.
ANYWAY, HOW'D IT PLAY
ON THE MEDIA?
- I WAS BUSY FLEEING JAPAN,
SO I ONLY CAUGHT
THE INTERNATIONAL NEWS.
THEY TOTALLY PLAYED DOWN
THE GUNFIGHT AROUND THE TUNNEL.
SAID SOME JUNKIES
WENT ON A JOY RIDE
SHOOTING THEIR GUNS IN THE AIR,
LOST CONTROL OF THEIR VEHICLES
AND WENT UP IN FLAMES.
BUT LUCKILY,
NO CIVILIAN CASUALTIES.
- MEANWHILE,
THE BODIES OF A BUNCH
OF LONG-DEAD J.S.D.F. OFFICERS
FINALLY TURNED UP.
AND THE INCIDENT IN JAKARTA
GOT A SIMILAR TREATMENT.
EVEN A MONKEY IN A SUIT
WOULD KNOW
NOT TO LET THE REAL STORY
GO PUBLIC.
- THE WHOLE S.R. UNIT,
GONE IN A DAY.
I'VE NEVER SEEN KASPER
SO HAPPY.
HE WAS PRACTICALLY DANCING
ON HIS DESK.
- I'M SURE.
- I MISJUDGED YOU.
EVERYTHING PROCEEDED
EXACTLY THE OPPOSITE OF
HOW I WAS EXPECTING.
SO WHY DID YOU
DESERT THE S.R. UNIT?
- BECAUSE IT WAS THE OPPOSITE
OF WHAT YOU EXPECTED.
I KNEW
WHAT YOU THOUGHT I WOULD DO
AND PLANNED ACCORDINGLY.
AND I DIDN'T DESERT THEM.
THEY WERE NEVER HAPPY
AS GHOSTS.
THEY WANTED TO GO OUT WITH A
FIGHT AND I MADE IT HAPPEN.
- AND YOU THOUGHT THAT BY
SURRENDERING THE TRADE ROUTE,
YOU'D MAKE KASPER'S AND KOKO'S
DREAMS COME TRUE AS WELL.
RIGHT?
- AND MY DREAM TOO.
YES.
IF I HAVE ONE REGRET,
IT'S THAT I COULDN'T STOP THE
ORGANIZATION FROM EVOLVING.
THE S.R. SURVIVED BY BUYING
AND SELLING WEAPONS.
BUT LIVING IN THAT WORLD
CHANGED US--
CHANGED OUR GOALS,
CHANGED MY MEN.
MAKES ME WONDER
HOW YOUR UNIT'S GONNA HOLD UP.
ENOUGH OF THAT.
JUST THINK OF THE OLD PROVERB--
"THE BIRD MAKES A CLEAN BREAK
AS IT FLIES AWAY."
MEANS YOU SHOULD LEAVE WITHOUT
CAUSING TROUBLE ON YOUR WAY OUT.
BUT IT NEVER WORKS
THAT WAY
BECAUSE THE BIRD THAT FLIES OFF
STAYS IN THE HEARTS
OF ALL THE OTHERS.
THOSE THAT CAN'T COMPREHEND
WHY THE BIRD LEFT
WILL VIEW HIM AS A TRAITOR
TO HIS FLOCK.
WHILE THOSE THAT WANNA FLY AWAY
BUT CAN'T
WILL ENVY HIM
WITH ALL THEIR BEING.
I HONESTLY THOUGHT
YOU WOULD COME BACK CRYING
20 MINUTES AFTER YOU
LEFT MY OFFICE THAT DAY,
BUT I WAS WRONG.
AND YET OF EVERYONE
IN THAT UNIT,
YOU'VE HAD THE MOST EXPERIENCE
WALKING IN THE TRENCHES OF HELL.
IT'S IRONIC.
YOU UNDERSTAND?
EVERYONE IN THE S.R. UNIT
WAS JEALOUS OF YA, TOJO,
BECAUSE YOU KNEW
WHEN TO FLY AWAY.
WELL, 'BOUT TIME I HEAD HOME.
THANKS FOR THE INFORMATION.
WHEN I SAW YOU'D FOUND ME,
I CONSIDERED MOVING AGAIN,
BUT THAT DOESN'T
SEEM NECESSARY.
COME VISIT AGAIN SOMETIME.
DRINKS ARE ON ME.
( laughing )
- THAT WON'T BE HAPPENING.
- MANA, TIME TO GO.
- OKAY!  COMING, DADDY.
- Both: OH!
- THANKS FOR PLAYING
CASTLES WITH ME. IT WAS FUN.
( laughing )
- Tojo's voice: HE'S GOT A SHAM
MARRIAGE WITH SOME THAI WOMAN.
HONESTLY, I DON'T KNOW HOW
HE KEEPS ALL HIS LIES STRAIGHT.
- BYE-BYE.
- MANA, DARLING,
LUNCH IS READY!
- OKAY.
- OH, DO WE HAVE GUESTS?
- ( laughs )
- ( laughs nervously )
- ( both laughing )
- HEY, TOJO?
I HAVE NO DOUBT
YOU WILL BE BACK SOMEDAY.
AND WHEN YOU DO,
I'LL TEACH YOU ALL I KNOW,
MAKE YOU A FIRST-RATE SPOOK.
- I TOLD YOU, COLONEL,
THAT'S NOT HAPPENING.
I'M NOT SPY MATERIAL,
I'M NOT WIRED LIKE YOU.
- OF COURSE YOU ARE.
ANY DECENT SPY
THINKS FIVE YEARS IN ADVANCE
WHEN MAKING HIS PLANS.
YOU'RE THE ONLY SURVIVING MEMBER
OF THE S.R. UNIT
FOR A REASON, TOJO.
BE SEEING YA.
- Tojo: KOKO, WHAT'S WRONG?
- I PROMISE, YOU'LL BE WORKING
FOR ME FOR YEARS TO COME.
- WHAT?  DON'T TELL ME
YOU TOOK HIS RAMBLING SERIOUSLY.
- ( groans )
YOU'RE MY BITCH, TOJO!
SAY IT.
- AGAIN WITH THE SHOULDER!
COME ON.
I'M YOUR BITCH!
JUST STOP.
- YOU BETTER MEAN IT!
- I MEAN IT!  I DO!
PLEASE, THAT HURTS.
- DON'T YOU LIE TO ME, MISTER.
I'M HOLDING YOU TO THAT!
I HAVE PEOPLE--
THEY'LL HUNT YOU DOWN!
- OKAY!  OKAY, I GOT IT.
- YOU'RE MINE FOREVER!
AND YOU'LL ALWAYS
THINK I'M HOT.
- I'M YOURS FOREVER.
I'LL ALWAYS THINK YOU'RE HOT!
- ( theme music playing )
- ♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS-- OH NO ♪
♪ NO NO NO NO NO
NO NO NO NO NO NO NO NO ♪
♪ HER NAME IS KOKO,
SHE IS LOCO ♪
♪ I SAID, OH NO. ♪