Ah, Okeanos.
I have to ask, what brought on this sudden outing?
Why are we going into town?
No reason, change of scenery, that's all.
You've been whining all the time about wanting
to see the amusement district, haven't you?
The joy of window‐shopping in
a foreign land is every bit
as wonderful as the thrilling joy of battle.
I feel really bad for the countries that got
themselves invaded for a stupid reason like that.
What is it, boy?
You sound like you actually
saw something like that happen.
Never mind.
I was just thinking out loud.
No way.
This is horrible.
We worked so hard to create this artwork!
How could they?
What kind of... What kind of inhuman
monster would so something like this?!
Dear Ryuunosuke,
only a very select few can fully comprehend the
immense importance of true beauty and harmony.
To the vast majority of common ignorant philistines,
beauty is but something to be
loathed and feared and destroyed.
It is for that very reason that we mustn't
become excessively attached to our creations.
All things given form and substance are
destined to one day break and fade away.
It is therefore absolutely essential that we find joy in
the process of creation instead of the creation itself.
So, whatever they break, we should just make another?
Is that it?
Precisely so!
As always, my dear Ryuunosuke, your understanding
of important matters is your best virtue.
Maybe we were just having way too much fun and so God
decided to punish us?
Listen carefully to what I say to you now, Ryuunosuke!
God does not punish humans ever!
He simply toys with them, cruelly.
B... big guy?
Once, long ago, I committed spectacular atrocities
the likes of which this Earth had never imagined.
Day after day, I murdered and defiled,
yet no divine punishment rained down on me.
Before I knew it, eight years had passed and my
exploration into the depths of evil had been ignored.
In the end,
it was not God that destroyed
me and took away my life,
but rather the selfishness of my fellow Man.
The church and the state executed me,
not for anything wrong that I had done,
but because they coveted my wealth and my land and
wanted to take them from me and make them their own!
What brought an end to my evil
deeds was far from judgment;
it was simple theft by a pack of criminals!
Uh, yeah, but, big guy.
There's... there's still a God, right?
Why ever would you think that? You, who are without
faith and have never in your life known a miracle.
Because the world seems like it's so boring.
But then, the more you look, the more you find
all kinds of neat and crazy stuff around you!
I've always thought that way.
A world filled with so many wondrous and amazing things
like this could never have happened simply by chance.
If you set your mind to enjoying it, there's no
better entertainment than this unbelievable world!
I'm sure there's a master entertainer somewhere writing
the story of all five billion people in this world.
If you wanted to describe somebody like that, what
other name could you possibly call Him but God Himself?
Then, Ryuunosuke, do you believe that
it's possible God loves humanity?
What do you mean?
He's head over heels.
I mean, if He's spending every minute
of every day writing our story,
well,
He could never do it if He didn't love us.
In fact, I'll bet you He's totally into it,
along with totally enjoying the results of His own work.
He also loves all the things that make humans look
good, like honor, courage, and hope,
and at the very same time, He loves screams and blood
and utter despair just as much.
If He didn't, there's just no way in Hell the guts of
living things would be as cool and colorful as they are.
So, I'm positive the whole world is filled
to the brim with God's love, big guy.
In this era of faithlessness when the state
has completely abandoned the true will of God,
I had no idea that such a vivacious new faith had
taken root and was beginning to bear amazing fruit.
You have my admiration, Ryuunosuke, my dear master.
Cut it out, I'm starting to blush.
But wait, according to your bold view of religion,
were not my blasphemies nothing more than a silly farce?
Not at all.
You know, the best entertainers
will sometimes get the most acclaim of their careers
when they play a really dark and disturbed villain.
I think when you get right down to it,
God probably loves playing against your
cruel and demented villain routine.
So both blasphemy and worship
are, in your eyes,
actually valid forms of Godly devotion?
Oh, that's marvelous!
Truly, you are the insightful bearer of
a brilliant and important new philosophy!
A God who makes me a puppet of man for His own sport,
and, at the same time, is Himself but another clown!
I see; His vicious ways finally make sense to me now!
Very well, then.
Let us go and paint the gardens
of the puppet master God
with even more brilliant despair
and terror and depravity.
We will show the author of this wicked world who
hides up in Heaven that God is not the only one here
who knows what entertainment is.
We're gonna do something awesome
again, aren't we, big guy?
Cool, cool!
All right, now.
I'll be in this bookstore for a while.
As for you, you can go do whatever you want,
but you're not to set foot outside this arcade.
If I'm attacked and kicked while I'm here,
it's curtains for you, too, understand?
Of course.
No conquering, Rider, means no plundering either.
Huh?
Pay attention to me, dammit!
There's to be no shoplifting
and no eating without paying!
If you want something, then pay for it with this money,
or am I gonna have to use a Command
Seal in order to make you behave?
Now, don't be rude.
Back in my day, Macedonian etiquette was the
mark of a man of culture in palaces everywhere.
I'm off.
Until later.
"The king gave control over
the lands he had conquered
and the rights to the taxes from
those lands to the local nobles.
He then mustered his armies and marched
off, taking them further east."
Just like in my dream.
"He continued on his campaign...
...because he wanted to reach Okeanos,
the furthest ocean."
Hey, boy, where are you?
Ah, yes, here you are.
You know, you're so tiny,
you're impossible to see between these bookshelves.
It was difficult to find you.
Normal people are smaller than bookshelves, idiot.
Man!
So, what is it you bought?
Feast your eyes!
It just so happens that the new Admirable
Grand Strategy videogame came out today.
First‐run, limited edition!
I suppose my luck must be pretty good today.
You know, there's no point is buying software
when you don't even have a game console.
Yes, I took care of that.
Come on, boy, let's go play in two player mode!
I bought us each a controller.
I'm not interested in low‐class entertainment like that.
It's stupid.
What's wrong with you?
Why are you constantly trying to
narrow your own horizons instead of
broadening them
to the fullest you can?
Don't you ever get the desire to seek out something fun?
Shut up.
If I had spare time to waste on that,
I'd spend it all on a search for truth rather than...
So, what was it you found so
interesting on this shelf over here?
Was it this one?
Well, I'll be, this is a book about me!
You are a strange boy,
I am right here in front of you every day.
If you wanna know something, just ask me.
All right, fine then, I'll ask you!
According to the description of this history book,
you were really short back when you were first alive.
So, how come you materialized
here in such an enormous body?
Huh, it says that I was tiny?
I've always believed that you should never
completely trust what's written in a book
when you don't know the person who wrote it.
Wait a minute, you mean to tell me
you're not mad they got it all wrong?
Huh, no, it doesn't really bother me.
That's strange.
Throughout history, the people in charge
have always tried their hardest to make
sure future generations remember them.
I suppose having your name recorded in the
history books is a kind of noble immortality.
But if that means my name and nothing
else gets passed down for two millennia,
I would have preferred to have...even
a hundredth of that added to my life.
So, then...it's true that
you died in your early 30s?
Hmm, yes, that one's true.
Oh.
Hey, big guy!
Get going out there and show us some cool
gig that's gonna shock even God, okay?!
You may look forward to it, Ryuunosuke!
It will be the greatest "cool!"
you have ever seen in your life!
Seriously?
All right, I can't wait to see it!
Uh.
Oh, yeah, something really awesome
is gonna happen here, I just know it!
Hey, why are you being so quiet, boy?
Hmm?
It's nothing, I was just thinking
about how boring you are.
What, you were?
See, you are bored, just as I thought.
Just quit whining and play this game with me.
That's not it!
You see, with a servant like you
who's practically guaranteed to win,
I couldn't take pride in winning the grail.
It would have been a lot better for both of us
if my pact had been with Assassin instead of you!
Mmm, I don't think that would
have worked out for you at all.
I think by now, you'd be deceased.
Well, that's fine!
If I'm going to die fighting in my own
battle, I'm not going to complain!
That's the reason why I decided to join the Grail War,
and now...
I really don't know what to tell you, boy.
If the wish you have for the Holy Grail was
something that impressed me in some form or manner,
I would be far more inclined to enthusiastically
obey your every whim and desire.
But if all you want it for is to add a few
centimeters to your diminutive stature...
You have no idea what you're talking about!
You don't need to be in such a hurry.
Nobody said that the Holy Grail War would be the
single most important event of your entire life.
There will be others.
What?
When the day finally arrives that you find a
way to live that you can truly be proud of,
you'll be forced into your own grand battle,
one that you will have to fight
whether you want to or not.
You will have plenty of time, then,
to look for your battlefield.
I'm saying that I'm not the only one here
who isn't satisfied with this pact.
Mmm?
You don't like it any more than I do, right?
Having me as your sworn master, I mean.
You'd have been able
to win this war easier
if only you'd sworn your allegiance
to a different master, right?
Probably, yes.
Take a look, boy.
You see, you're looking at the
real enemy that I'm facing.
Now, try to draw a picture of the two
of us standing alongside this enemy.
Draw it so you can tell the difference in our sizes.
Wait, what do you mean,
that's...  Impossible, right?
Compared to the enemy that we're about to take on,
you and I are the same, just little dots.
What point is there in trying to compare our sizes?
That is exactly why I'm excited!
The weakest and the smallest; that's just perfect!
With a body tinier than a poppy seed,
I will someday overtake and
even surpass the entire world!
Nothing can ever stop my quest,
for in my chest beats the invincible
heart of the King of Conquerors!
So, what you're saying is who your
master is makes no difference.
No matter how weak I am, it really doesn't
matter one way or the other to you?
Now, where did you get that stupid idea?
That miserable complaining nature of yours is a
sign that somewhere inside you is a conqueror.
No matter what you want me to believe,
you are acutely aware of how small you are
and yet, in spite of that,
you still struggle to reach heights greater
than you could ever begin to imagine.
It's not a compliment; you're making fun of me.
Indeed, boy.
Face it, you are a stubborn and incorrigible idiot.
Your deepest desires are far greater than yourself.
Like they say, glory lies beyond the horizon.
Back in the world that I lived in,
that was the fundamental rule of a full life.
Is that why you kept rushing towards the
east all the time like some kind of idiot?
Of course, that's right!
I wanted to see Okeanos with my own eyes, but,
alas, my glorious dream was never realized.
Huh?
You never saw the ocean like in my dream?
Even now, boy,
Okeanos remains the place I strive for.
It is a never‐ending dream.
That sea in my dream was really an image
of the heart that Rider has been dreaming.
Laugh if you like.
I, who after 2,000 years still dream the same dream
about a place he's never seen, am a great fool.
So, you see, boy, a pact with an idiot like you
is just perfect for me.
The river, I feel it.
Can you see what is happening?
Could it be him, Lancer?
It is Caster, indeed.
He is positioned on the river and is doing something;
however, I cannot make out what exactly.
It's the perfect chance to attack and put him down.
Agreed.
If I can defeat Caster, I can regain one
of the bonds with Lancer that I lost.
I will go and engage him, you stay here, Madam Sola‐Ui,
and bear witness to the deeds I perform.
What do you mean?
But I have to go, I'm a master now!
I'll be by your side.
You mustn't, Madam.
You do not understand military
matters as Master Kayneth does.
That river will become a deathtrap.
Please understand.
But, I...
Unless, perhaps, you still harbor doubts as to
where the true loyalty of Diarmuid actually lies,
that he would fight to serve his own ends?
Lancer, go fight as you will,
I leave field decisions to you.
Fight the battle freely and without any regret.
I am in your debt.
If you return victorious,
I hope you'll grant me a smile, Lancer.
Caster.
This incredible outpouring of
mana from him leaves me no doubts.
Caster is in the process of
casting some incredible magic.
Hmm?
Greetings and welcome, Holy Virgin!
I am incredibly overjoyed that
we find ourselves together again.
You just never
learn, you monster!
What is it you're trying to do here?
I'm terribly sorry, my dear Jeanne,
but you're not the guest of honor this evening.
But if you care to join us in our revelries,
it would give me the greatest pleasure
and fulfill the deepest wishes of my tortured soul.
At this banquet of death and decadence that
I, Gilles de Rais, have prepared!
You are welcome to come and eat your fill and be sated!
And now, once again,
we raise the blood‐soaked flag of salvation!
Unbelievable, Caster is being absorbed?
You who are abandoned gather here!
I shall lead you, I shall rule you.
The resentment and rage of we, the oppressed,
shall reach onto the lofty throne of God Himself.
God in Heaven, with words of condemnation,
I praise Your holy name!
What in the world?
Oh, eminent God!
Oh, cruel God!
We shall pull you down from your throne!
Hail, King of Knights.
King of Conquerors.
Now, just wait a minute,
we're calling a truce for the night.
We won't be able to have any kind of meaningful fight
unless we deal with that behemoth Caster created.
I have been going around informing everyone
and Lancer has agreed to come.
He should be here any minute now.
Understood, we will fight alongside you.
Our alliance will be short,
but let us pledge our loyalties.
Hey, Einzbern, you guys got a plan?
We haven't faced Caster yet and
Lancer told me you fought him already.
What do you think we should do?
Just defeat him as quickly as we can.
That horrid monster is maintaining itself
in this world by using Caster's mana,
but if it gets its own food source and
starts to become self‐sustaining...
We must stop Caster before then!
Yes, I follow you.
We need to settle this before it manages
to come ashore and begins to feed itself.
The problem is Caster's encased himself
deep inside those thick walls of flesh.
I'm not sure what to do.
Drag him out, that's the only way.
If we can expose his noble phantasm,
then my Gáe Dearg can destroy the spell with one strike.
Lancer, do you think you can strike
Caster's noble phantasm from the shore?
If I can just see it, it'll be child's play.
Then Rider and I will act as the advance guard.
Acceptable, King of Conquerors?
That is fine.
My chariot has no need of roads, of course.
But, Saber, how are you going to
attack the enemy in the river?
My body has been blessed by the Lady of the Lake.
Water cannot stop me,
however many fathoms deep it may be.
Oh, very impressive.
That is quite a rare skill.
I want for you to serve under my command even more now.
You will pay for your words
some other time, but for now,
we need to drag Caster out from
within that monster and destroy him.
Indeed, then I shall take the lead!
Let us begin!
Yah!
Saber, good luck.
Let's finish this, Caster!
Now!