Kiritsugu.
I'm not dreaming, am I?
You really came?
You really came to see me again.
Yes, that's right.
Thank you.
My last task
is to return this to you.
Take it.
From now on, you will be the
one who will be needing Avalon.
When you begin your final battle for the Grail,
I'm sure it will aid you.
You know what?
I'm really happy.
To love, to be loved.
To have a husband and daughter for nine whole years.
I'm grateful.
You gave me everything.
You gave me all the happiness in the world.
Something that was never meant for me.
I'm sorry, I wanted to show
you much more of this world.
No, it was enough.
If there's still any happiness left to experience,
I want you to give it all to our sweet Ilya,
to your daughter.
Our angel, our beloved Ilya.
I want you to promise
to bring Ilya to this country someday.
Promise me that you'll show her everything
that I didn't get to see, amazing things.
Blossoming cherry trees,
and the summer clouds.
I will.
Okay, I have to go.
Yes, you be careful.
I love you.
Saber is heading to Rider's hideout right now.
Is that correct?
Yes, she's on her way.
I'm going to kill Tokiomi Tohsaka.
If Rider and Saber engage in battle
there's a good chance Archer will also appear.
I'll hit him there.
I want you to stay here and watch over Iri.
I understand.
Um, Kiritsugu.
Finally.
You look focused.
Just like you used to.
I don't feel a servant's presence.
There's no barrier?
What's going on?
So, is that good?
Nope, it's awful.
Guess Japanese cuisine isn't that good after all.
Boy, you walked right by Okonomiyaki Shoki
in Newtown without even stopping to look.
Their modanyaki was a thing of beauty.
Too bad you didn't pick up any of that.
If you wanna eat there again, you're gonna have
to recover enough so that you can materialize.
Do you recognize this spot?
This is the place where I summoned you.
It's the Fuyuki location with the
leylines that suit you best, remember?
You should be able to recover much more quickly here.
I've decided that I'm staying here all day.
Just sleeping, that's all.
So take my mana, as much as you want.
Just don't kill me.
Maybe it'll help you feel a little bit better.
If you had already figured it out
you should've said something earlier.
Finding out afterwards that someone's been onto you the
whole time is... well, well, it's a bit embarrassing.
You idiot, you should've just told me about it!
If you aren't at full strength
at the exact moment I need you
I'll be the one who ends up in danger.
Why didn't you say anything, Rider?
I thought that maybe I could tough
it out a little while longer,
but the fatigue from the river battle
has hit me harder than I expected.
Yeah, well, when it's all said and done,
your Noble Phantasm consumes a ton of power.
At first, I didn't really notice.
Because it wasn't affecting me I thought it
was all incredibly efficient or something.
Rider, honestly, instead of using mana
that was supposed to come from me ,
you managed to use your own stored power, didn't you?
And not only that, you did it twice.
What's the big idea doing that?
Well, you know,
I mean, when you get right down to it, as a servant,
I'm a natural soul eater of sorts.
If I involve you when I expend mana at my maximum rate
it could put your life at serious risk.
Yeah, but I'm fine with that.
This is a battle that I got us into.
Unless I bleed or make sacrifices,
there's no point at all of winning this war.
Hmmm.
All I wanted was to prove myself,
that I could... that someone just like me
can take whatever it is he wants with his own two hands.
But boy, I hope you realize that all of
that only applies if the Grail truly exists.
You know, I once did something similar.
Fought ferociously for something
that might not have even existed.
Oceanus.
That's right.
I said I'd show them Oceanus,
and they were so swept up by my story that they
all followed me on my quest without a single doubt.
Many died along the way,
all dreaming of Oceanus until the very end.
When I gained this era's
knowledge, it hit my really hard.
I'd had no idea the world was an enclosed sphere.
What a bad joke.
But even so, when I saw the map,
I had no choice but to accept it.
It seems I've had my fill of
letting people die for fairytales.
If the Grail's existence was
certain,
I'd have no objection to you risking
your life in an effort to possess it.
But unfortunately, that is not the case.
Even so...
don't you forget, I am still your master.
Boy, learned to talk back now, have you?
Excellent.
It's true, your magic circuits
are more powerful than usual.
If I rest all day I should be ready
to go another round come nightfall.
Oh yeah, another round?
What exactly are you planning to do next?
Hm, good question.
I'm thinking that we should begin with Saber.
At the rate you're regenerating,
how much will you be able to recover by tonight?
If I only use the Gordius Wheel for flight,
there really shouldn't be a problem.
However, I'm afraid I'll only be able to
employ my Ionioi Hetairoi one more time.
I see.
We should probably save it for
the later fight with Archer.
Then Rider, I don't get it.
Why is it you wanna fight Saber first?
I must defeat her, and no one else.
As a heroic spirit, it is my responsibility.
What's that mean?
If I don't show that silly girl the right path,
the path to true kingship,
I fear she'll never learn.
That would be too sad to bear thinking about.
Whatever, have it however you want.
Boy, quit keeping yourself awake and just go to sleep.
Rest is the battle that you face right now.
Mmm.
I am the shunned, the scorned,
the despised.
Who the hell are you?
My name is unworthy of praise.
My body unworthy of envy.
I am the shadow cast by the heroic spirits' light,
the darkness born in the shadow of shining legend.
Thus do I hate,
thus do I resent.
I feed on the lamentation of those who sink into
darkness, and curse those who shine so brightly.
Her shadow is my shame.
Her honor remains forever unsullied.
Thus am I forever looked down upon.
You are the sacrifice.
Healing won't help me.
I'm going to die soon.
Damn it.
Really, what a sorry sight you are.
You look absolutely terrible.
Now I don't want you to get the wrong idea.
I'm not blaming you for your current condition.
To be perfectly honest, I never would've
imagined that you'd hold out for this long.
You've really surprised me, and so,
I shall give you the ace I've
kept hidden up my sleeve,
secreted away for use at
precisely this stage of the game.
Take it.
It works quickly, doesn't it?
The worm I just gave you is very special.
It was the first to feed on
Sakura's innocent purity.
How does it feel, Kariya?
For an entire year it has been
devouring the girl's life energy.
It's a magnificent mana source.
Now, go back and fight, Kariya,
and make good use of the precious life
force you've stolen from young Sakura.
Go and use every ounce of your flesh
and bone to acquire the Holy Grail,
if someone such as you is even capable of it, that is.
Hey, Maiya.
I'm curious as to why you fight for Kiritsugu.
Because I have nothing else in life.
I can't remember my family or
my own name for that matter.
Maiya Hisau was the name on the very first fake passport
that Kiritsugu made for me.
All I remember is that the place where
I came from was a terribly poor country.
The wars never ended,
even though there was no money to maintain the armies.
But day after day, they continued to kill one another.
Then one day, someone had an idea.
Rather than conscript and train soldiers,
it was cheaper and faster to abduct children
and send them out to fight the battles.
You mean, you were one of them?
Aim at the enemy and pull the trigger.
That was my sole function in life.
I threw everything else away.
As a human being, I'm dead inside,
but the outer shell continues to function.
Still working just like it did before.
That's always been my life,
but regardless, Kiritsugu took me in,
so however he wants to use me is fine by
me, and that's the reason I'm here.
To tell you the truth, madam,
it was your passion for all this that surprised me.
You've been secluded in the castle where you were born,
knowing so little of the outside world.
So I simply can't imagine why you would
fight this hard for Kiritsugu's dream.
To change a world you've never really seen.
Well, I... you're right.
I cannot truly understand Kiritsugu's ideals,
or why he holds them close to his heart.
It's as you say, I've been sheltered,
and I know practically nothing of the
world that Kiritsugu longs to change.
All the ideals I speak of are merely
words that I learned from him.
But please don't let him know that.
I've always told him that I thought
he was doing the right thing,
and also that those same ideals
were worth giving up my life for.
And I pretended that I understood him.
Then, madam, in that case,
have you no wish or longing of your own?
My wish?
Oh yes, I have one.
I wish for Kiritsugu and Saber
to prevail and win possession of the Holy Grail.
You mean, you support the Einzbern's desire
to attain the Third Magic?
No, what I desire is an end to conflict in the world.
If Kiritsugu's wish comes true and fighting everywhere
comes to an end,
the battles for possession of
the Holy Grail here in Fuyuki
will be no exception.
I want this fourth battle to be
the last of the Holy Grail Wars.
You mean, for your daughter?
If Kiritsugu and I fail to get the Grail,
then Ilya's next.
It's unfortunate, but that is the destiny
that an Einzbern homunculus must bear.
So my wish is to be the last one.
If that comes true she'll be able to live
out her life as a normal human being.
Maiya, what will you do after Kiritsugu
reaches his goal and saves the world?
I don't expect to survive that long.
And even if I do,
there'll be no reason for me to exist anymore.
I'm sure it will be that kind of world
once Kiritsugu changes it.
But you do have a reason to exist.
You think so?
You must look for your real name,
and then go out and find your family.
Those aren't things anyone should forget.
You must learn who you are and etch
yourself into the memories of others.
So live, Maiya,
for yourself and for me too.
I'll do my best, but all that has
to wait until after the battle ends.
Right now we must be cautious.
Both he and I
must stay on constant guard.
The one who died was Tokiomi Tohsaka.
Oh, Maiya, you really are stubborn.
Maiya!
Iri!
By my command seal, I order you!
Saber, go to the storehouse immediately!
Kiritsugu.
What happened?
Maiya!
Saber.
Don't try to speak.
Hurry, follow him.
Don't let him escape with her.
Rider took madam with him.
But if I leave...
Don't worry.
I'll be just fine.
And Kiritsugu will come soon.
So, hurry.
Maiya, you have to try and hold
on until Kiritsugu returns.
I shall bring Irisviel back safe.
Rider, I can't believe it.
It was Rider.
Yes, I understand.
You mustn't cry, not over me.
You need to save those tears for your wife.
You can't cry here.
Be strong, you have to finish.
So don't cry yet.
You can't break.
You can't.
Maiya.
You know, this morning, you finally
looked like Kiritsugu, like your old self.
Don't lose your resolve over this.
Promise.
Don't worry, Maiya.
Leave the rest to Saber.
Maiya, your task here
is finished.
Maiya.
Maiya?