Murdered?
I can't...believe it.
Why would anyone kill him?
It's unthinkable!
This cannot be allowed!
It must also be regrettable for you
to lose your father in this way.
It is.
Father Risei was very dear.
He was just like a second father to me.
It's been one unexpected
disaster after another.
I think it might prove necessary
to formulate a new plan right away.
Why did you not tell Tokiomi?
Tell him what?
I pity your father.
He died believing his son
to be a pious man of God.
Or...
perhaps that was his salvation.
Does your father's death arouse no feeling in you?
He was killed, after all.
You could at least attempt to appear a little upset.
I am.
I'm furious to no end.
Furious, you say?
Are you...
furious because you were unable to kill him yourself?
Saber?
Irisviel, how are you feeling?
It appears I've made you worry about me again.
I'm sorry.
No.
As long as you are truly fine.
That is all that really matters to me.
But then...
It's okay.
It's Maiya's presence you are sensing.
Tohsaka?
Yes.
He requests that we present a united front.
Wait, an alliance?
At this stage?
The thought of dealing with Rider and Berserker
must have Tohsaka feeling father uneasy.
And so, assuming that we would be the most amenable,
he has invited us to meet.
Meaning that he considers us the
weakest of the remaining teams.
Tohsaka said that he wishes to meet with
you tonight over at the Fuyuki church.
You should know that from the very start
Tokiomi Tohsaka has made elaborate preparations
to try and ensure his victory in this Grail War.
And it's also likely
that in total secret
he controlled Assassin's
master, Kirei Kotomine.
If that's true, and Tohsaka exerts
some influence over Kotomine,
then I believe it would be a mistake
if we choose to ignore this offer.
Yes, you're right.
Kirei Kotomine?
Remember this, Saber,
if there is anyone in this war who can defeat
Kiritsugu and claim the Holy Grail for himself,
it is the man named Kirei Kotomine.
Go and tell them.
We accept.
Father?
Hi, Father!
Rin, your father says that he
would like to speak with you.
Rin...
keep the Mage's Association
in your debt till you grow up.
After that, I leave the rest to your judgment.
I'm certain you'll be fine on your own.
The Holy Grail will appear one day,
it is the Tohsaka
family's duty to claim it.
Above all, if you wish to be a mage, Rin,
it's a path you cannot avoid.
Here, take this.
Oh!
I have to go now.
You know what to do, right?
Yes.
I'll see you soon.
Take care, Father.
First, allow me to thank you
for coming here at my behest.
I very much appreciate it.
Let me introduce Kirei Kotomine,
my long‐time apprentice.
While we were once honorable competitors
in this battle for the Holy Grail,
all that is now in the past.
He has lost his servant, and as a result,
has yielded his rights as a master.
This Grail War is rapidly heading toward its conclusion.
The one's remaining are, as anticipated,
the masters of the three great
houses along with one outsider.
Now, what is your appraisal
of the state of the war?
I have no opinion.
We control the most powerful servant, Saber,
and don't need to wait for the best time to strike.
We shall simply continue to win each battle.
Hm.
Unfortunately for the Matous,
it is my opinion that they
erred in their strategy.
They have imposed a draining servant upon a frail
master, thereby hastening his self‐destruction.
Rider is likely to be the victor between them.
The Grail must not be allowed
to fall into outside hands.
The two of us should be able to agree on that much.
Any alliance is out of the question.
However, if you wish to discuss the
order in which we approach our enemies,
we may be able to
come to some equitable agreement.
Go on.
We can settle things with the Tohsaka team
after defeating the other masters.
We are prepared to agree to such a proposal.
So a temporary conditional ceasefire?
That is a fair compromise.
We have two conditions.
The first is that you agree to share with us
any and all information you may have gathered
concerning Rider and his master.
Agreed.
Our second condition is
that Kirei Kotomine be removed
from the Holy Grail War.
Kirei?
I am not suggesting in any way he be killed,
but I insist that until this battle is over,
he be expelled from Fuyuki,
or better yet, from Japan entirely.
Immediately, before morning.
Would you explain why?
Because of the bad blood
between the Einzberns and the so‐called Inquisitor.
If the Tohsaka team continues to protect him,
we will find ourselves unable to
trust you under any circumstances.
What does she mean?
Kirei.
Well, Saber,how do you
like Kiritsugu's present?
Very much so.
It is more like a horse than a car is.
It seems to suit me much better.
I shall go ahead then
and scout out the route ahead for us.
We should go now as well.
Ma... madam, what's the matter?
Please drive, Maiya.
You sure?
Tohsaka will suspect something's wrong.
What's happening to me really isn't unexpected.
It was actually inevitable.
Honestly, the fact that I've been able to function as
a human for this long... is really quite a miracle.
Does Kiritsugu know about this?
Yes, but don't tell Saber.
She has a crucial battle
to fight ahead of her.
I don't want to distract
her with all of this.
But listen, Maiya,
there's something I need to tell you.
I am a homunculus created
specifically for the Holy Grail War.
You know about that, right?
Yes.
Grandfather Acht ingrained in the
vessel an instinct for self‐preservation
so that it would avoid all danger and
safeguard the Grail to its completion.
He disguised the vessel so he could hide
it in plain sight and called it Irisviel.
That is who I am.
But how?
Then that means that you are...
Very soon now.
I will revert back to what I originally was.
When that happens, I won't even be able to
talk to you or anyone else like this anymore.
That's the reason why Kiritsugu
gave me Saber's scabbard to keep.
Avalon, are you familiar with its effects?
It halts aging and provides an infinite healing ability.
Or so I'm told.
Its effects are what have prevented
the hollow shell that is me
from collapsing in on itself.
Of course, they stop working
as soon as Saber is away.
And I start to deteriorate.
Madam, why are you telling me all this?
Because, Maiya Hisau,
under no circumstances would you ever pity me.
You would accept me for what I am.
That's why I tell you.
Madam, Irisviel, I'm afraid I've always
thought that you were beyond my reach.
No, I'm not really.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Even if it costs me my life, Irisviel,
I will see you through to the very end.
And so please...
please die now for Kiritsugu Emiya
to make his dream a reality.
Thank you.
I really wish you had told me of your
troubled history with the Einzberns.
Unfortunately, I have no choice.
You must withdraw from the Holy Grail War
immediately.
Kiritsugu Emiya, who are you really?
Will I leave this place
never even learning that?
Still thinking about what to do even now?
Could you truly be so slow, Kirei?
The Holy Grail beckons to you still.
And even you yourself still long to
jump into the fight and claim it.
For as long as I remember,
I've spent my life in search of a single thing.
I've devoted every moment
and endured great pain for it,
but all of that has come to naught.
Yet I sense that the answer to my question
is closer to me now than it has ever been before.
After all of that self‐reflection,
why in the world do you still hesitate?
Because I fear
that when I've learned all the answers,
it will result in my utter destruction.
Understood, well done.
Ah, you've just received an
exciting bit of news, I take it.
We've finally learned the exact location of the
stronghold where the Einzberns have been hiding.
As I live and breathe!
You honestly amaze me.
You were planning to continue all
along, weren't you?
I did hesitate.
I was even prepared to give up.
But in the end,
it is just as you say, Archer...
I know no other way than to keep asking
the question until I find an answer.
What is that?
A gift from my father.
JN424.
The gospel of John.
"God is spirit, and those who worship Him
must worship in spirit and in truth."
However, Kirei,
there remains for you a rather grave problem.
Were you to participate in the Holy Grail War on
your own behalf, Tokiomi Tohsaka becomes your enemy.
In other words, you are in the
same room as an enemy's servant
with no real plan to actually
defend yourself from him.
A dire situation, would you not agree?
No, not at all.
I came with something to trade for my life.
Really?
Gilgamesh.
Let me reveal to you the truth behind the
Holy Grail War that has been kept from you.
And that is?
The magical ritual held here in Fuyuki
is an attempt by the winning mage to
open up a passage directly to the root
by the sacrifice of the souls
of seven heroic spirits.
The activation of the Holy Grail can only be
achieved by the killing of all seven servants.
That's correct, all seven.
You understand?
That's the reason my master has worked
so hard to avoid using his command seals,
because when all the battles are finally over, he will
require them to force his own servant to commit suicide.
So then the loyalty Tokiomi has shown me
has all been nothing but a lie from the very beginning?
To put it yet another way,
my master is first and foremost
a mage down to his very core.
He may worship a heroic spirit,
but he harbors no illusions about his idols.
Well, Tokiomi, at last you have
shown some hint of promise.
That dull excuse for a man will finally be able
to provide me with a measure of entertainment.
Now then, what will you do, Gilgamesh?
Will you now choose to remain loyal to Tokiomi
and then punish me for rebelling against him?
Ah, a fair question, indeed.
Regardless of his treachery,
Tokiomi still supplies me with the mana I require.
Were I to abandon my master,it would
hamper my ability to remain materialized.
Oh, come to think of it,
there is a partnerless master I know of.
One who is actively searching for a servant
that is free and unbound by a contract.
Hmph.
Now that you mention it, you're right.
But of course, there is a question
of whether that man is a worthy master
in the eyes of the King of Heroes?
He will suffice.
He is a bit stiff and humorless, perhaps,
but he has great potential for growth.
He may yet prove himself a fine
source of entertainment for me.
Hm.
I've been waiting for you, Kirei.
I came to say goodbye and thank
you before I departed Fuyuki.
First, I'd like to say that I'm still very proud
to have had you as my student.
I hope you will maintain good
relations with the Tohsaka family,
as throughout the years
your late father always did.
All right?
Your words honor me.
Once this Grail War has finally come to an end,
Kirei, I'd like for you to help train
my young daughter, Rin, to be a mage.
It's rather simple, but in essence,
this is a will I've prepared.
I thought it prudent to be ready in the event
the worst happened and I did not survive.
It leaves the entire wealth
of the Tohsaka family to Rin.
And names you as her legal guardian
until she comes of age.
Leave it to me.
I shall do all I can
to look after your daughter and
keep her safe from any harm.
Thank you.
Kirei.
What is this?
A little something for you.
A gift from me.
Open it.
An Azoth dagger.
It symbolizes your mastery of magic,
and marks the completion of your apprenticeship to me.
I am without words.
You are far too kind to me.
I am filled with gratitude,
my master.
It is I who thanks you,
Kirei Kotomine.
Now I can finish preparing for
the final battle of this war.
Oh my, look at the time.
I'm sorry to have kept
you here for so long.
I hope I haven't made you miss your flight.
No.
You needn't worry about it, my master.
You see, I never got around to buying myself a ticket.
Master.
How like my father you were.
Even at the very end, you never really
understood me or my inner motivations, did you?
Hah.
Such a boring end.
Look at that.
Such an idiotic expression.
He did have a dematerialized
servant at hand that he depended on.
It was natural for him to lower his guard.
So, you have learned to adjust already, have you?
I praise you for your studious aptitude.
Well, Kirei?
Do you feel a little better about not
having had the chance to kill your father?
So you have no qualms about this,
Gilgamesh, King of Heroes?
No, not so long as you continue to amuse me.
Otherwise, Kirei...
Well, you are the one who ought
to question your own resolve.
My will creates your body,
and your sword creates my destiny.
If you heed the Grail's call
and also obey my will and my reason.
Yes, I swear your offering will be my flesh,
Kirei Kotomine, my new master.
Now, Kirei,
let us begin.
Put an end to this farce,
and as a reward for your loyalty,
I shall give you the Holy Grail.
Very well then, King of Heroes.
May you have your fill of amusement from me.
Until such time I find the answer I seek,
I shall gladly play the fool for you.