I am Iskandar, the King of Conquerors!
In this battle for the Holy Grail,
I am of the Rider Class of Servants.
Wh... what the hell are you thinking
announcing yourself that way?
You idiot!
Ow!
Ow...
Fate has brought us all together in this place to
do battle for the possession of the Holy Grail.
But first, I wish to make a proposition and offer.
What think you of yielding the Holy Grail to
me and joining my glorious and invincible army?
You will be treated as honored
allies, friends, and brothers in arms!
Together we shall share in the glory of
battle and the joy of world conquest!
Hm.
I'm afraid that I must decline your offer.
As tempting as that offer may be,
I may give the Grail to but one man.
My new avowed lord and Master.
And not to the likes of you, Rider!
Tell me, Rider.
Did you come here and interfere
with our battle, rudely,
merely to proffer that ridiculous
and laughable plan of yours?
This is a grave offense against my honor!
Hmm.
I'd be willing to discuss compensation.
Enough!
Hm.
And further,
I am the rightful king of Britain
and not merely a knight of the realm.
I could never lower myself to mere
retainer, even to a mighty king!
Ooh, you are king of Britain?
That is quite a surprise!
I would hardly have expected the
King of Knights to be a little girl.
Then would you like to taste of this
little girl's blade, King of Conquerors?
I suppose negotiations have failed.
Such a terrible waste.
A truly awful shame.
Rider!
I can't believe it.
That moron nearly conquered the known world?
What the hell is wrong with you?
So, you were the one who did it, huh?
I'd been wondering what twisted madness had invaded
your psyche and compelled you to steal my relic.
I never even imagined that you yourself had
being planning to enter the Holy Grail War.
Waver...
Velvet?
Now I know you're not experienced in these matters.
How would you like me to offer you a private lesson?
What it really means for mages to kill one another?
I'll teach you all about the fear and
pain involved in such noble endeavors.
You should feel honored.
Hm.
Mage who is speaking now,
do I understand correctly that you believe you were to
be my Master rather than this boy I'm sworn to serve?
That whole idea is absurd and laughable!
Only one brave enough to openly
ride onto the battlefield
standing at my side could
ever hope to be my Master!
A coward who lacks sufficient courage to show himself
is nowhere close to being worthy of me!
Of course, there are also others!
They're out there skulking in the darkness, watching us!
What are you talking about, Rider?
Saber and Lancer,
the skills and bravery you showed were impressive!
Your duel was magnificent!
Surely the sound of your blades
and the fury of your battle
called other Heroic Spirits here to bear
witness and glean knowledge from your encounter.
Heroic Spirits,
born again through the Holy Grail,
gather here and now!
Those too craven and cowardly
to show themselves here tonight
will draw the vicious scorn of Iskandar,
King of Conquerors!
Kirei.
Yes?
This is not good.
Not good indeed.
Oh no, that's him!
The Servant that defeated Assassin?
So, two lesser beings dare to name themselves kings
even in my royal presence.
I fail to see where the problem lies, Servant?
For I am Iskandar,
the legendary King of Conquerors known
through all the lands of the world.
What nonsense!
You're deluding yourself!
I am the one true king of the world!
All others are mongrels!
Pretenders to the name!
If you are that insistent of your
claim, then why not name yourself?
No true king should be troubled by something as simple
as giving his name to those he wishes to challenge.
So, you would question me, you filthy mongrel?
Me, the one true king?
If you cannot now discern my identity
in the presence of my magnificent glory,
then your ignorant blindness
will serve to seal your doom!
I see now.
That is how he killed Assassin.
That is his Noble Phantasm.
Kill them all.
Berserker?
So, King of Conquerors,
are you planning to ask him to join too?
Perhaps not.
He doesn't seem terribly interested in
civilized negotiations of any kind, does he?
Hey there, boy.
How powerful a Servant is this monster, huh?
I don't know.
I can't really tell.
What do you mean, boy?
Are you not a Master chosen by the Holy Grail?
You're supposed to be able to sense all
their strengths and weaknesses, aren't you?
I can't tell anything.
That black thing is definitely a Servant,
but I can't read its status or anything else!
Hmm.
It appears you'll be facing another difficult enemy.
Yes, so it seems.
That spirit has some curse or other ability.
It fully conceals nearly everything about him.
But that isn't all.
With four other Servants present,
we have to be very careful.
Why did he materialize here?
No sane Master would ever choose
to send their Servant out here
under these circumstances,
certainly not right into the middle of all this chaos.
Maiya, keep watching Assassin.
I'll look for Berserker's Master.
Who gave you permission to look upon me?
You rabid dog.
May your death provide me some
modicum of entertainment, mongrel!
Good God!
Is that truly Berserker?
For a madman completely devoid of a soul or conscience,
huh, he is rather nimble.
Huh?
Come now.
Couldn't you tell what he did?
That black thing casually snatched the first
blade that was flying toward him out of the air
and used it to deflect the second spear.
You dare lay your filthy hands
on my precious treasures.
You must long for a painful death, cur!
No way, that's impossible!
All right now, mongrel.
Let us all just see how long your parlor tricks
can keep you alive now!
Fool...
I belong among the heavens,
yet you would have me trod upon the ground?
Your impudence has guaranteed your death!
Mongrel!
When I am through with you,
nothing will remain of your corpse!
Gilgamesh is serious.
He plans to open the Gate of Babylon even further.
Repeatedly exposing his Noble
Phantasm to all the others.
Very rash of him.
Your decision, my Master.
By the power of my Command Seal.
King of Heroes, quell thine anger and withdraw.
You dare to order a king to
withdraw, to leave the fight undone?
You have much nerve, Tokiomi!
You were fortunate, mad dog.
You mongrels!
By our next meeting,
see that you culled your numbers!
Only a true hero is worthy to
look upon my glorious presence!
Hm.
It would seem that Archer's Master has much less
fortitude and is far less courageous than he is.
Irisviel!
Get back!
What?
So that's what it is.
Whatever he grabs onto with his
hands becomes his Noble Phantasm.
Saber!
Hey, Maiya,
have you gotten any visual on Berserker's Master?
No, I haven't.
This looks bad.
Damn.
What are you, monster?
That's quite enough messing around for now, Berserker!
You see, Saber has a prior engagement.
If you insist on interfering with that obligation,
you'll have to face me.
Lancer...
What are you doing, Lancer?
This is your chance to defeat
Saber and take her out of play.
My Master!
I, Diarmuid,
will defeat Saber!
I swear it upon my honor!
If you insist I kill her here and now,
then I will first defeat that mad dog Berserker!
Please, my Master, let it be so!
With my Command Seal, I order you.
My lord!
You are to help Berserker kill Saber!
Now!
Lancer!
Sorry, Saber.
Irisviel, listen!
I shall hold them here!
While I do that, you must leave
this place as quickly as possible!
Run!
Get as far away as you can!
Irisviel, please!
Run away!
It's all right, Saber.
Please believe in your Master!
Kiritsugu is here?
Kiritsugu, I know that you can
still turn this to a victory!
All right, I'll kill Lancer's Master now.
It's the only way out of this situation.
Maiya, proceed with your attack of Assassin on my mark.
Suppressive fire.
Right, acknowledged.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Rider?
Ah, this Servant is quite a tough one, isn't he?
Well, as you can see, our dark malevolent
friend will be retiring for the evening.
Master of Lancer!
I know not from whence you are watching,
but do not sully a battle between
knights with your petty tricks!
Have Lancer withdraw.
If you insist on humiliating him further,
then I shall join Saber against him.
And I assure you that together the two
of us will annihilate your Servant.
What will it be?
Fine; Withdraw, Lancer.
That's enough for tonight.
My thanks, King of Conquers.
It was nothing.
The flowers of a battlefield must bloom.
I must know.
What was your purpose in coming here,
King of Conquers?
Well, honestly, I try not to
think too hard about such things.
Saber, first settle matters with Lancer and battle.
And then, I shall face the victor of your contest.
Be it you or Lancer.
Well, King of Knights, goodbye for the moment!
It was a pleasure,
and I sincerely hope to enjoy our next meeting
as much as I did this one.
Hey, boy, don't you have
anything nice to say to the lady?
Hm?
I really do wish he'd man up a little.
Oh, well.
Fare thee well!
Saber!
Your left arm!
Yes, it was a painful blow.
It is as Rider says.
If I fail to deal with Lancer first
and undo the curse on this wound,
it will damage my chances against the other Servants.
Thank you, Saber.
I survived thanks to you.
The reason I could focus on the battle before me
was because I had you to stand behind me.
Saber.
The battle is only beginning, Irisviel.
Tonight we saw the opening gambits have an epic
battle that is only just beginning to unfold.
I know.
They were all powerful adversaries.
Not one of them was a conventional enemy.
So this is the Holy Grail War.
He turned and ran like a cowardly
rat away from my Berserker.
And I also got to embarrass that stupid arrogant ass.
Tokiomi, how I wish I could
have seen the look on your face.
That damn Berserker broke free of my
control and started fighting Saber.
Bastard!
If he keeps doing that, my body won't last long.
But if I can
control him,
I can win.
Just hold on, Sakura.
Begging your pardon, Master Kirei.
What is it?
Master, I've come to report that I've found
something of interest outside the church.
A familiar?
Yes.
It was outside the barrier.
But it was clearly sent here for the
purpose of monitoring this church.
Awesome!
That was so awesome!
Hey, Bluebeard!
That was all real, right?
Right?
It was for real!
Not some kind of cool special effect, right?
So awesome!
So, about this Grail War,
you're gonna do it, aren't ya?
Right, big guy?
Ah...big guy?
My wish has come true.
What do you mean by, uh,
wish come true?
Look at her!
The answer to my prayer!
Her extraordinary face,
her strong and noble bearing!
She is none other than the maiden of my dreams!
The one perfect woman in the world!
You know this chick?
Yes indeed!
She was forsaken by God!
Died in abject shame and terrible loneliness and now,
at last, she has come back to life!
It is such a miracle!
What else could it be
but the fulfillment of all my hopes and dreams!
Oh, maiden.
My holy virgin!
Soon I will come for you!