[NAGISA] Having gotten our
hands on some juicy intel,
we took it upon ourselves
to investigate.
At least that was our story.
To be honest, we'd
infiltrated this café
a good ways from school
just for the heck of it.
Wow. He looks
just like a prince.
[door opens]
Hi. Welcome.
Ah, yes. Good to
see you both again.
Mrs. Harada, Mrs. Ito.
Li'l Yuma. How are you?
Now, you realize we come here
more for you than the coffee.
Now, now. If the manager
hears you say that,
he's bound to get
his feelings hurt.
So, the usual?
Mocha for Mrs. Harada,
double espresso for Mrs. Ito?
Care for a slice
of chiffon cake?
It's our special of the day.
[HARADA] Ooh! Yes, please.
We'll take two.
Indeed. Very good, ma'am.
[MAEHARA]
Our leader's not just a man.
He's a prince among men.
Ugh. I want him to die.
[ISOGAI]
You're really nursing that tea.
Sure you don't want
somethin' else?
Actually, yes.
Might as well get the most
out of keeping your job secret.
[ISOGAI] Ah, I get it.
Good old extortion, huh?
This one's on me. Enjoy.
[BOTH]
He's Prince Charming!
[MEG] Look how much
he can carry at once!
[BOTH]
He's Prince Charming!
Sweetheart, don't tell me your
poor mother's taken ill again.
[ISOGAI]
Well, you know.
It's just the two of us,
so sometimes I have to help out
in the financial department.
[NAGISA, KAEDE, MEG, OKAJIMA]
He's Prince Charming!
Yeah. The only negative thing
you could say about
him is he's dirt poor.
'Cept somehow makes
even that look cool.
Guy keeps his clothes
so neat and tidy,
you'd never know they're
fresh off the bargain rack.
[NAGISA, KAEDE, MEG, OKAJIMA]
He's Prince Charming!
[MAEHARA] Oh, and did I
mention he let me eat some of
the goldfish he caught
at the Summer Festival?
Let me tell you,
that boy can cook!
[NAGISA, KAEDE, MEG, OKAJIMA]
He's Prince Charming!
Oh, yeah. And I went to
the bathroom after him once.
He'd folded the toilet
paper into a triangle!
[BOTH]
He's Prince Charming!
I fold toilet paper into a
triangle. Every time I go!
[BOTH]
That's disgusting.
[MAEHARA]
Check him out.
Even middle-aged
women dote on him!
[KAEDE, MEG]
He's Prince Charming!
[NAGISA] Uh, middle-aged
women in my neighborhood
dote on me sometimes.
[KAEDE, MEG]
Who cares?
[MAEHARA] Did you know
Isogai gets love letters
from the girls on
the main campus?
[NAGISA, KAEDE, MEG, OKAJIMA]
He's Prince Charming!
[MEG]
Um. I get them, too, actually.
[NAGISA, KAEDE, MAEHARA,
OKAJIMA] Forbidden love!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Alas, some things are only cool
when done by a cool person.
Like Isogai, or me, of course
[NAGISA, KAEDE, MEG, OKAJIMA,
MAEHARA] He's Prince Cha--
What are you doing here?
[KORO-SENSEI] Their honey
toast! It's absolutely divine!
Enough so that I
turn a blind eye
to Isogai's illicit
part-time job.
[KORO-SENSEI]
I'm rather surprised.
You're not the least bit irked
at his being such an ideal man?
[ALL]
Uh? No.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Care to explain why not?
I don't get it.
He, uh, he's too good
a guy to be upset with?
Do we need a better reason?
[door opens]
[ISOGAI]
Hello! Welcome!
[ARAKI]
What's this? Uh, oh.
Looks like the rumors about
a student working here
are true after all.
Isogai, you're
such a bad student.
This is your second
violation of school policy.
I expected better. Oh, Isogai.
[NAGISA] It's Asano.
This couldn't get any worse.
[GAKUSHU] The last time you
were caught holding down a job,
they punted you to E-Class
without a second thought.
Such a shame. Have you done
no soul-searching since then?
Asano, I'm begging you.
Keep this on the down-low.
It's only for the month.
I need the money. Please.
I don't know.
Well perhaps we can be
gentlemanly about all this.
[NAGISA]
You can tell when Asano's
up to something sinister.
He becomes the spitting
image of his father.
Very well, then. I'll keep
your dirty little secret.
On condition that you show
me your fighting spirit.
My what?
[GAKUSHU]
I think you heard me.
Our school has a proud
tradition of revering those
who can hold their
own in class and life.
Ample fighting spirit
earns enough respect
to forgive a flagrant
conduct violation.
And to show that spirit...
[SUGINO] Pole-toppling
at the Sports Festival?
Yep.
If we can beat A Class,
they'll let Isogai off the hook.
[ALL groaning]
Tch. You do know it's a trap.
They're obviously just
out to humiliate us.
What're we supposed to do?
We say no, Isogai'll
get penalized again.
Not a slap on the wrist either.
He could get expelled.
So what? I don't want
you guys getting involved.
Terasaka's right. Asano's got
something up his sleeve.
Besides, I'm the one
who made this choice.
I'll take responsibility
for it myself.
Let them expel me.
Nothing says I can't stage
an assassination off campus.
[ALL]
Wow what a...
...terrible idea!
[ISOGAI]
Huh?
[MIMURA] You impoverished,
cow-licked bastard!
What d'you mean cow-licked?
[MAEHARA] You're overthinkin'
it, man. Knock it off.
Look, only thing we gotta do is
beat the nerds at pole-toppling.
We got this in the bag!
'Course we do!
Hell, I'd say we're lucky the
jerks caught you workin'.
Golden opportunity.
We can payback some of the crap
they're always
dishing out on us.
[YOSHIDA] Topple 'em?
We'll friggin' destroy 'em!
[SUGINO]
C'mon, Prince Charming.
You guys, I...
All right! Let's do it!
[ALL]
Yeah!
[KORO-SENSEI]
How very typical of him.
Always putting the needs of his
classmates ahead of his own.
This is personal
magnetism in action.
Perhaps the single most
important attribute of a leader.
Heh. As a prince among men
myself, I ought to lend a hand.
[KARASUMA]
Pole-toppling, huh?
Reminds me of my
days at the academy.
It's not so much
assassination as war.
The relative size of your team
can be a major setback.
These kids may be well-trained,
but A-Class' team has them
outnumbered two to one.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Woo-hoo! Great job, Kimura!
Show 'em how it's done!
That's the way!
Smile big for the
camera! Go, Justice!
Might as well be water.
No problem.
[ALL]
That's so cool!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Indeed.
Assassination has improved
overall fitness, equilibrium,
hand-eye coordination,
and depth perception.
And this extraordinary
competition
will showcase them all!
[STUDENT A] Holy crap,
that pipsqueak can move!
[STUDENT B]
Her body's so... aerodynamic!
[KORO-SENSEI] You move to
the beat of your own drum,
an important advantage.
Remember that when it comes
to pole-toppling, my boy.
Victory is entirely up to you.
Something wrong?
Koro-sensei, the fact
of the matter is,
Asano is very talented.
I-I'm no match for him.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Huh...
Look at it this way.
However talented someone is,
however gifted or well-trained,
the world is a mighty big place.
There's always someone better.
What do I do? I can't win.
The guys are gonna get
crushed because of me.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Talent or not,
one person alone can
only accomplish so much.
[OKAJIMA]
Yeah!
[KORO-SENSEI]
You've got Asano beat
in one very important
respect already.
The ability to inspire
confidence in your comrades.
Should you find yourself between
a rock and a hard place,
there'll be quite a few
people rallying to help you.
You have the gift of
personal magnetism.
And between you and me, I'd much
rather have a fellow like you
as a student than Asano.
All right!
Guys, like always, we're
goin' into this guns blazing!
[ALL]
Yeah!
Next up, we have an
exhibition match!
E-Class must be
feelin' lucky, folks
'cause they've challenged
A-Class to a battle!
Something tells me
Kunugigaoka's elite
will make 'em live to regret it!
[NAGISA]
Who are they?
[OKAJIMA]
No way can that be regulation!
[ARAKI] In the spirit
of cultural diversity,
this exhibition
match will feature
our foreign exchange students.
All of them.
Asano's scared.
He brought in outsiders
to cover his butt.
Must be a lot riding
on this for him.
[TAKADA]
This is gonna be hilarious.
What'cha gonna do,
E-Class? You got nothin'.
[GAKUSHU] If they expect to
win with so few team members,
they'll have no choice
but to break formation
and go on the attack.
At which point,
our ironclad defensive
line will eat them alive.
Hey, uh, do the End Class
dorks even wanna win?
None of them are
on the offensive!
[ARAKI] Okay, apparently
E-Class' strategy
is to go all-in on defense.
Are they cowed by
the gap in skill?
[ARAKI] Whatever they're
thinkin', let the games begin!
[ISOGAI]
Bring it on, Asano.
[GAKUSHU] If you think
we can be lured out,
you underestimate us.
Offensive line, go Plan F!
Roger that!
[GAKUSHU] Our objective isn't
to bring down the pole, per se.
No, we intend to crush
you once and for all.
Uh, guys.
[yelling]
Dammit!
We're not just gonna
roll over and take this!
[ARAKI]
Two men down!
And not just down,
flung to the bleachers!
Sir, this is already a disaster!
It doesn't matter how
tight the defense is
if all they do
is get picked off!
[KEVIN] How 'bout instead
of tryin' to hold the line
like a bunch of turtles,
you step up and fight?
Hmph. Or don't you know
the meaning of the word?
[KARMA]
Hey, partner,
why don't you stop yammerin'
and follow your own advice?
Hmph. Bring it on, man!
[ALL yelling]
Okay! Now!
Operation: Tentacles!
[ISOGAI]
Pin 'em down!
[ARAKI]
Unbelievable!
The E-Class team is pinning
down A-Class' offensive line
with the weight of the pole!
They're playing dirty!
Tough luck, big guy,
there's no rule against us
using the pole as a weapon.
[KEVIN]
Get the hell off of me!
Shut up and stay down.
[GAKUSHU]
A splendid tactic.
But you've only got
seven teammates
to create a defense with,
and two of them are
down for the count.
You've just given us
more of an advantage.
Guerilla team, Plan K!
Both flanks, move in!
[ISOGAI]
There's a gap dead center.
If we're going to attack,
is has to be now
while they're separated.
All right, let's do it!
Look alive, men!
Operation: Runny Nose!
[ALL]
Yeah!
I've got you now.
[ARAKI]
Oh-ho! Classic bait and switch!
They pulled an
offensive fake-out!
[KARASUMA]
It's like a chess problem.
The kids have made their
defensive line airtight.
But the tide of battle is
turning against them quickly.
[KORO-SENSEI chuckling]
[KARASUMA]
We should do something.
The Ministry of Defense
isn't gonna like it very much
if the students get injured.
[KORO-SENSEI chuckles]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Not to worry, my good man.
I gave Isogai some helpful
tips during Social Studies.
On the subject of defeating
an enemy twice your size,
history provides an excellent
example in Hannibal of Carthage.
Ah, yes, called "The
Scourge of Ancient Rome."
[KORO-SENSEI] He led his troops
off-road, time and again,
popping up where the opposing
forces were least prepared.
His defense strategies were
clever, his weapons innovative.
The lesson here is that
a good tactician
thinks unconventionally.
Successful schemes
are often guided
by a touch of the eccentric.
[TAKADA]
Ooh! Ha!
The E-Class dorks are about to
get the net closed in on 'em.
Yeah, it's beatin' time!
[TAKADA, TANAKA]
Whoa, what the--?
[TANAKA]
Look out!
[ARAKI] The E-Class team
has fled the playing field
and is running amok among
the spectators! Total chaos!
[KARMA] Hey, there're no
rules about boundaries.
Come on. What'cha waitin' for?
The whole school's
a battlefield.
What're you doing? Damn it!
Quit screwin' around, guys!
[GAKUSHU] The most dangerous
part of pole-toppling
is that even with only
a handful of teammates,
you can clamor to the top.
Their strongest are...
[GAKUSHU]
Akabane. Kimura. Isogai.
Those are the three to watch.
[GAKUSHU]
Yuma Isogai.
Should E-Class lose this
friendly little match,
I'll report your infraction
and you'll be out in the cold.
Order your team to attack
unless you care to be expelled.
Fall alone or drag your
friends down with you.
The choice is yours.
Not ideal, but those are the
stakes of leading the underdogs.
Isogai! It's about that time!
[ISOGAI]
Yep!
And so far, it's
all going to plan!
[gasps]
[ARAKI] What? Where'd
those two come from?
Weren't they out of commission?
[YOSHIDA]
We practiced takin' punches
till we were blue in the face.
[MURAMATSU]
But the hardest part of it all
was acting like we got
flung off the field!
[GAKUSHU]
You're kidding me!
These are the goons we
pummeled in the beginning?
Right, we're done running!
E-Class, go Sonic!
[E-CLASS]
Yeah!
[GAKUSHU]
Of course.
The scuffle was only to
distract our attention.
After those two clowns
were knocked to the seats,
they regrouped.
Why didn't I see it coming?
Now they're taking advantage of
the chaos to rush our main unit!
That's their game!
[KORO-SENSEI]
That's our game!
[ARAKI] Oh! They got
right up in their grill!
[MAEHARA]
How you like that, Asano?
[YOSHIDA] There may not
be that many of us.
but it only takes one to
reach the top of the pole.
Don't tell me this punk
knows martial arts.
[GAKUSHU] We happen to be
standing on the same stage,
you and I.
Tell me, are so big a fool you
don't expect to be kicked off?
[NAGISA] Strong Final Boss vibe.
Definitely his father's son.
Uh-oh. A-Class is closing in.
Anyone else feel like we're
about to watch a massacre?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Make no mistake.
Asano is a singularly
fearsome leader.
Provided they follow his
command, A-Class can't lose.
Not the sort of adversary
you can trifle with, Isogai.
Fortunately... you don't have
to take in on all by yourself.
[GAKUSHU]
What?
[ARAKI]
Wait a minute!
The E-Class offensive has
called in reinforcements!
[SAKAKIBARA] What the hell?
That's their defensive unit.
[KOYAMA]
Which means...
[TAKADA] They only have two
guys left at the pole?!
[TANAKA] How are they
even holdlin' 'em down?
A little thing called leverage.
[TAKADA]
Heh?
Oh yeah. Physics and stuff.
Ha-ha! Nice one, man.
They're totally
buyin' that answer.
It's simply a play for time.
The two of us can't
really hold down
this many people by ourselves.
Lucky for us,
these poor souls don't dare
do anything without orders.
Could be your boss still
has an ace up his sleeve.
And of course,
in times like these
it's better to wait and see
than take the initiative, right?
Stupid four-eyes!
Asano! We need orders!
[GAKUSHU]
I can't give you any!
[ARAKI]
Looks like the A-Class team
is assuming a defensive
posture, too!
If they can hold, E-Class
will be out of options!
Itona! Now! Do it!
Yeah, okay.
[chuckling]
[KORO-SENSEI] A secret weapon is
best saved for the last minute.
[GAKUSHU]
I can't lose!
[thud]
[ARAKI]
Uh... The... A-Class is, uh...
Team E-Class...
for the win!
[KORO-SENSEI] Outstanding!
My students are so cool!
Aren't they cool?
Look this way, please!
That's right! They're mine!
[ASANO]
Well, well, well.
It would appear that
by some miracle,
the underdogs have gotten
the better of you again.
You were owned.
I believe that's how the kids
are putting it these days.
Worse still, Isogai turned your
strategy to his advantage.
You hadn't the foresight to
account for a secret weapon.
This was a war of information,
gentlemen, and you lost.
Because of incompetent
leadership.
Uh, Mr. Principal.
Please, sir, your son
did the best he could.
[GAKUSHU]
Shut up, Kevin!
Ya can't win 'em all.
You're his father, tell him
defeat can be a valuable lesson.
Yes, of course.
You're absolutely right,
Kevin. Well said.
Perhaps you could teach
me the value of defeat.
Your words would carry
a great deal more weight,
if I knew what it was
to lose, yes? Well, then.
Come. Fight. All four
of you, please. At once.
[ALL grunting]
[GIRL A]
There he is! Isogai!
[GIRL B]
You were incredible!
Oh, thank you!
But it's pretty dangerous stuff.
[SUGAYA, KIMURA]
Yeah, yeah, prince among men.
Everything's different now.
It's like the mood's changed.
They don't treat us like
the untouchables anymore.
What d'you expect, man?
Our nothin' little team
rocked the boat today.
People are gonna talk.
[OKAJIMA]
Think about it, guys.
Officially, we're now even
cooler than Team Asano.
[FOREIGNERS groaning]
[KEVIN] I'm sorry, sir. Please.
Please accept my apology.
[ASANO]
Did you know...
...I once took down a black belt
on my third day
of karate lessons.
The first day, I was soundly
beaten, you understand,
by some 30-something.
There was so much
pain, I vomited.
I'd never known a more
agonizing defeat.
What do you suppose
I did on day two?
I observed.
Inwardly consumed by
flames of my humiliation,
certain were I to lose again,
I would be mortified
to point of insanity.
That I would, in effect,
die of madness.
On day three,
I crushed my sensei
without him landing
a single blow.
That is the lesson of defeat.
[ASANO]
Incidentally, Asano.
Aren't you mortified?
Losing hurts.
One would think the pain
is eating you alive.
[GAKUSHU]
You're a monster.
[NAKAMURA]
Hey. Check it out.
[SUMIRE]
Oh. It's Asano.
[MAEHARA]
We had a deal.
You gonna hold your
end of the bargain?
You're not gonna rat Isogai
out for having a job?
You may take me at my word.
Unlike some people I know,
I'm not one for
underhanded tactics.
But next time I won't
just take you down.
I will chase you into oblivion.
Hah. Someone's a poor loser.
Yeah, what a jerk. Let him
talk all the smack he wants.
We're totally above it.
[MAEHARA]
Don't pay any attention to him.
He doesn't even know you, man.
Doesn't understand what
you have to deal with.
Except, that's not being fair.
I don't know him either.
His life could be really tough.
Plus, I've got super
awesome classmates.
If being broke led me
to you, then I'm glad.
[NAGISA] Isogai may not
look as cool as Asano.
He's not on top or out front,
but before you even realize it,
he's right there next to you.
[ISOGAI] Whoa! Leftovers from
the bread-eating contest!
[NAGISA] That's the president
of E-Class for you.
A prince among men
and assassins.