[KORO-SENSEI]
Listen to me, class.
There's something I neglected
to mention in my earlier lesson.
A clever assassin may avoid
confrontation for a while,
but sooner or later,
the fight will come.
And when it does,
every last ounce of strength
will be put to the test.
In my case, that would be now!
[REAPER howling]
[NAGISA]
Koro-sensei!
[KORO-SENSEI yelling]
[NAGISA] For every attack,
a corresponding sonic boom.
Clearly, this was not your
garden-variety battle royale.
We couldn't make
out their moves,
but there was no mistaking it,
Koro-sensei was losing ground.
Big time.
Koro-sensei!
Sufficiently hopeless
yet, guinea pig?
A little math theorem.
Square the inverse of your
tentacles and solve for genius.
Factored by the
power of hatred.
And you get superiority!
[KORO-SENSEI groaning]
[REAPER] Please!
Teach me to kill like that!
You're sure about that?
I did just murder your father.
You're not at all upset?
Who cares about him?
You. You're an artist! I'd give
anything to do what you do!
Nothing in my life
has any meaning.
Take me in. Teach me
what you know. Please!
I'm willing! I'm willing
to risk my life!
[KORO-SENSEI] The child had
no concept of right and wrong,
but his eyes,
his eyes shone with
an intelligence
and a singular determination.
There was the fork in the road,
the point where I might've
steered him differently,
spared his sanity.
[KORO-SENSEI grunting]
[NAGISA] They're in
totally different leagues.
[NAGISA]
This is a one-sided fight.
All our hard work,
down the drain.
Everything we'd done the
past year... meaningless.
We were barely a distraction,
too stunned even to run away.
Not just failures...
Koro-sensei's failure.
[gasps]
[KORO-SENSEI grunting]
He's dodging them.
Am I seeing things?
Heh! Let's see
you deflect this!
[KORO-SENSEI]
What the--?
[KORO-SENSEI grunts]
[roaring]
You're kidding me!
Koro-sensei's using evasive
moves with minimal energy,
throwing handfuls of
soil to block the light.
That closes the gap
between them significantly.
He's analyzing and adjusting for
his own weaknesses mid-battle.
I'm not surprised.
That's our Koro-sensei.
[KORO-SENSEI] You may chalk
this one down to experience!
[KORO-SENSEI yells]
[KORO-SENSEI] I am the teacher.
You are the student.
I take full responsibility
for your lapse, but first...
Yanagisawa, I'd
like you to leave.
This is a place of
learning, not a warzone.
You have no business being here!
[sighs]
[SHIRO] You just won't
let go of this fantasy
of being an educator, will you?
Deranged little guinea pig.
Answer me this, teacher!
Why do you suppose we
chose this of all moments
to launch our final offensive?
[gasps]
[SHIRO]
You will protect them, right?
That is what a
teacher's meant to do.
[STUDENTS gasping]
--What the hell's goin' on?
--Where're the children?
Are you all right, sir?
[gasps]
[STUDENTS]
Koro-sensei!
[STUDENTS shouting]
[SHIRO] Well, well, aren't
you the model protector?!
You could easily dodge these
blows if you had a mind to,
yet you stay for the sake of
your poor defenseless charges.
I believe it's time.
Another, please.
[KORO-SENSEI grunting]
[SHIRO]
And another.
And another. And another.
I don't think I've ever
seen hatred more intense.
When fueled by bloodlust,
there's no emotion
more destructive.
Killing won't satisfy
a man like that.
He won't stop until his
target is obliterated.
Mind, body, heart, and soul.
[KORO-SENSEI retching]
[KAEDE]
Koro-sensei...
[SHIRO] Coral the guinea pig
with his precious students
and this was all but
a foregone conclusion.
Sorry, boys and girls.
You chose poorly.
Showing up here tonight only
increased the likelihood
of his dying by our hands.
[KARASUMA]
Shut up, Yanagisawa.
I think we've all heard just
about enough out of you.
[KURASAMA]
Huh?
[IRINA]
Karasuma!
[SHIRO] Make yourselves
comfortable and enjoy the show.
I'm afraid at this juncture
there's really nothing
else you can do.
[growls]
[NAGISA]
We'd seen it. All along.
We'd seen, but...
we looked away.
[SHIRO] Optimistically,
I'd say seven or eight.
Surely you can't just leave
these poor young people
to drown, can you?
[KORO-SENSEI groaning]
[SHIRO]
How does it feel...
...watching your student's
quake with despair
as they realize how much
of a hindrance they've been?
[groaning]
[SHIRO]
Do you understand now?
They are your greatest weakness!
[NAGISA]
He's absolutely right. It...
It's u--
[KORO-SENSEI]
That is preposterous!
[gasps]
[KORO-SENSEI]
You're a fool if you think
I'll believe it's
that cut and dry!
These children, they've risked
life and limb to save me.
What they've gone through
just to be here tonight
is extraordinary!
Their determination,
their unflappable spirit,
students like these
are the greatest gift
a teacher could ask for!
They are not a hindrance!
They are not a weakness!
They are my class!
And I am proud of each
and every one of them!
Call it what you will,
but when the chips are down,
I will give my life
to protect them!
[REAPER growls]
Yes, that's all fine
and good. So dutiful.
And yet, I'm afraid, we have to
deny you even that satisfaction.
See, your strength
will run out soon,
at which point the children
you're protecting...
...let's just say their
future won't be as bright
as you'd hoped.
Everything you've gained
over the last year
you've gained by
destroying our lives.
I will ensure that it
was all for nothing!
Then and only then will
my revenge be complete!
Now then, let's continue.
Where were we?
Yes, of course! Mind that
you pay close attention.
[grunts]
Idiot!
What the--?
Make a run for it, sir!
Find a place to hide.
You need to recover.
I'll buy you some time!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Kayano, what're you doing?
[gasps]
Ah-ha.
Even with the tentacles excised,
your kinetic vision remains.
[KORO-SENSEI]
No, Kayano! Stop this at once!
[KAEDE]
It was all my fault.
[gasps]
[KAEDE]
I brought us down.
Because of me, everyone
had to face the truth.
We'd been like a
family and I ruined it.
So, please, just let me do this.
As your student, I owe you one.
[KORO-SENSEI] You can't put
this on yourself, Kayano!
Sooner or later we all
would've had to face reality!
Your actions simply made us
take stock and regroup--!
[sighs]
What do you say, 2.0?
[KAEDE]
Don't worry, Koro-sensei.
I've got this.
All I have to do is try.
My sister taught me that.
So did you!
[yells]
[SHIRO laughing]
[SHIRO]
Unbelievable!
What're the odds of
having both sisters
die right in front of me?
[laughing]
[SHIRO] Tragic ends must
run in the family, eh?
Ha-ha!
Can you imagine if I'd kept her
around as a back-up wife?
Too bad for me.
It looks like I have a thing for
women destined to be impaled.
[SHIRO laughing]
[yelling]
[SHIRO]
There it is!
Oh, but you are a
devastating creature
when your emotions twist
past the point of endurance!
Black indicates well-nigh
unimaginable power.
At last, your true colors
are on full, glorious display!
Isn't it liberating to shed
that ridiculous façade?
All year long, you've
been a smiling hypocrite!
How wonderful to see
you as you really are!
But alas,
considerable though your
power may be in this form...
...the new and improved you
will negate it effortlessly.
Thank you for playing.
Behold his final attack.
[REAPER roaring]
[NAGISA]
We need to get out of here!
Are you for real?
C'mon! We're wasting
time! He's distracted!
If we stick around, it'll
only make things worse!
You can't be serious!
Living to fight another day
is a perfectly reasonable
battle tactic!
[yelling]
[SHIRO] This has been the
year from Hell, hasn't it?
Well, fortunately
it's all over now.
[roaring]
[SHIRO]
What? A white light?
But, he-- His tentacles
are still black!
[NAGISA]
No. He's gone back to yellow.
Nuh-uh. That's red!
He's green!
And blue!
[NAGISA]
And white!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Every color.
Every emotion.
Every element of my past.
My entire life...
..mixed together...
...into pure white energy.
Treasured pupil...
...may your graduation...
help you find peace!
[SHIRO] Shit! No, no! The
barrier liquefies tentacles!
Damn you!
[KORO-SENSEI]
What're these flowers for?
[REAPER] Uh. I just thought
they looked pretty is all.
Figured making arrangements
might, I don't know,
come in handy one
day or something.
Sorry, master, I can move them.
[roaring]
No. Leave them here.
You've got a keen eye.
Nicely done.
[chuckles] You really
mean that, sir?
I can make a fresh
bouquet every morning!
I suppose you could...
But I'd rather you
study chemistry.
With what you know now, you'd
be lucky to kill a mosquito.
[groans]
[chuckles]
[KORO-SENSEI]
If I'd only seen that smile,
I might've led the poor boy
down an entirely different path.
[REAPER]
The tentacles spoke to me,
asked me what I wanted.
And I said... to be
acknowledged by you.
To be like you...
To be... like... you.
[KORO-SENSEI]
But you are.
You are and you
always have been.
More than you understood.
If by chance we meet again...
on the other side...
...let's pick up
where we left off.
[NAGISA]
The fight was over...
...but none of us
were shouting for joy.
[NAGISA]
Koro-sensei, Kayano's...
[STUDENTS crying]
[HINANO]
Oh, Kaede.
Why don't we lay her down?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Not so fast. One moment, please.
Sorry, I'd rather her cells not
come in contact with the soil.
But, sir--
[KORO-SENSEI]
Children,
I've made mistakes,
more than I care to count.
What's done is done.
The past can never be
regained or revised.
If, however,
we attend carefully,
it can teach us how
to move forward.
What is... that?
[KORO-SENSEI]
You're looking at Kayano's blood
and somatic cells.
I gathered as much as I could
before she fell to the
ground and stored them
in a sterile membrane of
compressed air for safekeeping.
You-You did all of that
in the middle of a battle?
[KORO-SENSEI]
I set a few tentacles aside
for protecting you.
Of the rest, I used some for
fighting and some for this.
Okey dokey, then.
Time to string these cells
together one by one.
Faster. And more accurately
You see, class,
I've been improving my skills
for some months now.
If what happened to
Aguri repeated itself,
I was adamant about
being prepared.
Now, some cells
couldn't be recovered,
so I'll leave strategic gaps.
Those I'll fill in with
tiny bits of mucus.
In a few days, what cells
there are will have regenerated
in sufficient quantities
to replace them.
I'm a little low on blood.
Type AB donors, if you please.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Nakamura! The birthday cake!
Collect it and stuff it
in my mouth immediately!
Do what?!
You realize it's been one with
the dirt for the past half hour,
right?
[KORO-SENSEI]
That doesn't matter!
I have to replenish my energy!
Besides, I can't stop
thinking about it!
Thirty-minute rule!
Thirty-second rule!
[NAGISA] I think the wound's
starting to close up!
He didn't use a single stitch;
didn't leave so much as a mark!
[KORO-SENSEI sighs]
[KORO-SENSEI] In a moment,
her heart will start beating
and she'll come back to life.
According to my handy-dandy
"What to Do for a
Gut-Shot Student" manual,
from here on out it
should be smooth sailing.
[ALL] But who thinks
of writing a manual
for something like that?!
[KORO-SENSEI]
I didn't mention this earlier
for fear of sounding ghoulish,
but if ever your bodies
were torn to shreds,
I was ready and able to put them
back in order piece by piece.
The ultimate student-teacher
relationship, really.
[KORO-SENSEI] Because it
requires, above all else,
that I properly acknowledge you.
[ALL gasp]
[KORO-SENSEI chuckles]
[sighs]
What did you--? You saved
me again, didn't you?
[KORO-SENSEI]
As many times as necessary.
After all, your sister
would've done the same.
[STUDENTS gasp]
--[KAEDE screaming]
--[STUDENTS laughing]
[KORO-SENSEI]
The important thing
is that you not make
the same mistake twice.
Aguri, thank you for
giving me this past year.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Such a beautiful gift.
I hope against hope
I've been worthy of it.