[STUDENTS]
One! Two! Three! Four! Five!
--Six! Seven! Eight!
--[KORO-SENSEI] Ahhh...
The sounds of a
choreographed exercise regimen
echoing across the fields
on a golden afternoon.
So peaceful. So militant.
[STUDENTS]
One! Two!
Make those knives sing.
Treat every move
like a legit kill strike.
[STUDENTS]
Seven! Eight! One!
You're in the way here, pal.
Phys Ed is my department now.
[KORO-SENSEI]
But... But I'm lonely.
Find something else to do
then, like, I don't know.
There's a sandbox.
Have a field day.
[KORO-SENSEI sobs] You don't
have to be so insensitive...
The kids liked it better when
I was their gym coach anyhow.
[sighs]
Yeah, not such much.
No offense or
anything, it's just
when it comes
to exercise, you...
...set the bar kinda high.
[KORO-SENSEI] All right,
let's try a simple jumping
side-to-side maneuver.
Watch closely and I'll
show you how it's done.
Are you kidding me?!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Once you've got the rhythm,
throw some cat's-cradle
into the mix.
Wow, he is seriously good!
Like we could keep up with that.
We're human beings, y'know.
I, for one, think our
coach should be, too.
[KORO-SENSEI whines, sobs]
[KARASUMA]
Right. Back to work, people.
Can I ask an obvious
question, sir?
If there's an actual point
to this training, should, uh,
should we be practicing
right in front of our target?
Whether killing or studying,
it's the same principle.
Drill the basics and
they'll serve you well.
[NAGISA]
Okay.
[KARASUMA]
Isogai, Maehara, step up.
I want you to try to
tag me with those knives.
Wait. Like as a team?
Do you think
that's a good idea?
The blades are harmless.
They weren't designed
to injure human beings.
Tell you what, manage to hit me
and you can go home for the day.
Uh, okay. Well,
here goes nothin'.
[ISOGAI grunts]
Come on.
[MAEHARA growls]
[ISOGAI grunts]
[MAEHARA]
[KARASUMA]
See that, kids?
Even with the
bare minimum know-how,
I can practically dodge
their attacks in my sleep.
They've got no technique.
[BOTH growl]
[NAGISA]
Whoa...
[BOTH growl]
[KARASUMA grunts]
If you can't land a hit
against a guy like me,
you haven't got a prayer
against a target
whose top speed is Mach Twenty.
See?
We've been sparring for
half a minute and look.
He's had time to change
clothes, make tea,
and build a model
of Osaka Castle.
[MAEHARA]
That is so irritating!
[KARASUMA]
That's why we drill.
When the whole class can
hit me, you have a shot.
Do what I tell you as
often as I tell you to do it,
you'll become assassins.
This isn't recess, kids.
From now on, gym class
will be about the basics.
Stabbing correct
use of firearms,
everything
you need to succeed.
Wow. Okay.
[KARASUMA] All right.
That oughta do it for today.
[STUDENTS]
Thank you, sir!
[KARMA sighs]
This is so intense!
He's terrifying but
cool at the same time.
--[KORO-SENSEI growls]
--[HINANO] I know!
He wants you to hurt him
but he'll pat you on the head
if you do it right.
He's a good coach.
[KORO-SENSEI]
I know what this is!
You're trying to take my place
as their favorite teacher!
[KARASUMA]
Really?
I'm here by assignment.
Like it or not, as per your
contract, and I quote:
"all new hires regarding
E Class are solely
the prerogative of
Kunugigaoka Academy."
And, either way, this is
not a popularity contest.
It's my job. I'm here
to help them kill you, pal.
[KORO-SENSEI] Could you not
call me that, please?
I prefer the name
my students gave me.
So that's Koro-sensei to you.
[school bell chimes]
Ugh. We've got a quiz
in sixth period.
Right? They should just
let us go home after gym.
[KARMA]
Nagisa. 'Sup?
It's been a while.
[gasps]
[NAGISA]
Karma... You're back?
[KARMA]
Hm.
Oh, hey.
That must be the
notorious Koro-sensei.
Wow. He really does
look like an octopus.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Ah. Mr. Akabane, correct?
I understand your
suspension ends today.
Welcome back. That said,
tardiness is a no-no.
[chuckles]
It's kinda tricky gettin'
back into the swing of things.
Oh. Feel free to call me
by my first name.
Anyway, I've heard some good
things, Teach. Nice to meet'cha.
[KORO-SENSEI]
The pleasure's all mine.
Should be a fun
and educational year.
[KORO-SENSEI gasps]
[KARMA]
Hah!
Ah. You are fast, aren't'cha?
[KARMA laughs]
[KARMA] And who'da thought
these knives actually work?
I just cut one up into
strips and tacked 'em on.
Pretty elementary stuff, chief.
I'm disappointed that's all it
took to catch you by surprise.
But good jump.
If you don't mind comin'
off like a 'fraidy cat.
What, are you scared of me?
[NAGISA] He hurt him.
He actually hurt him.
That makes him the first.
I heard they call
you "Koro-sensei"
'cause you're s'posed
to be unkillable.
[KORO-SENSEI mumbles]
Oh, come on.
No way you can be
this big of a pushover!
[KORO-SENSEI growls]
Hey, Nagisa, what kind of
person is this Karma guy?
Uh. He and I were in the same
class our first and second year.
He was violent, so violent
they finally expelled him,
shipped him here.
E Class is where they
send you when they don't know
what else to do with you.
Thing is, under
the circumstances,
he may end up a star student.
[KAEDE]
Huh? What do you mean?
[NAGISA] Weapons and
blood are his passion.
Trust me, if anyone can kill
our teacher, it's Karma.
[KARMA] Stick around
next time, Koro-sensei.
I'll show you what it's
like to be assassinated.
You won't want to miss it.
[rhythymic squishing]
[STUDENTS sigh]
[squishing continues]
[MIMURA]
Um. What is he doing?
I dunno, I think
he's punching the wall.
[ISOGAI]
No, you're right.
Karma's smack-talk seems to
have really touched a nerve.
But what's the point
of punchin' a wall
when his tentacles are
too soft to do any damage?
Okay, that's enough!
Could you maybe stop that?!
We're trying to
take a quiz here!
[KORO-SENSEI]
S-Sorry! Yes, absolutely.
You sure you know what you're
gettin' yourself into, Karma?
The jellyfish is sincerely
pissed off at you.
You can't pay me enough
to be in your shoes.
If I was you, I'd stay at home
with my head under a pillow.
'Course he's pissed.
Who wouldn't be if someone
made an attempt on their life?
'Less the would-be
assassin screwed up
and pissed himself
in the process.
[growls]
I didn't piss myself!
That attitude's gonna
get your ass kicked--
[KORO-SENSEI]
Quiet, please!
No noise during a quiz!
[MAEHARA]
Tell that to your tentacles.
[KORO-SENSEI] Continue
to talk, and I will assume
--that you're cheating!
--Sorry, Koro-sensei, my bad.
No worries, though.
I've already finished.
I'm just gonna eat this
gelato if that's okay.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Not so fast! No eating in class!
Hey!
That's the gelato I brought
back from Italy yesterday!
[STUDENTS]
Uh-oh.
Huh? Sorry.
My bad, I just saw it chillin'
in the faculty lounge.
[KORO-SENSEI]
This won't do, young man!
I flew through the coldest
layer of the stratosphere
to keep that delicious
treat from melting!
Yeah? So? Whaddya gonna do?
Hit me?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Of course not!
I'll simply have it back
and finish what's left,
thank you very much.
[KORO-SENSEI gasps]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Anti-me BB's?!
[laughs] Wow. That's
twice in one day, Teach.
[KORO-SENSEI whimpers]
I'm gonna keep pullin'
the same old tricks.
Class'll get interrupted,
our grades'll slip.
Let's be straight-up, though.
If you want this to stop,
you can just kill me or
anyone else in this class
for that matter.
You just gotta let go of wanting
us to see you as our teacher.
Give us a taste
of your ugly side.
Or you can make
peace with all this.
Accept that I'll be
the one to kill you.
Here's my quiz. Easy peesy.
Peace out for now, Teach.
Whaddya say we
play again tomorrow?
[NAGISA]
Karma's not afraid to go there,
he knows exactly
what buttons to push.
Case in point.
He drew a line in the sand
Koro-sensei couldn't cross
without changing the
way we all saw him.
It took nerve.
It also took honing in on
his target's weakness.
[KORO-SENSEI sighs]
[NAGISA] He's clever. He's
manipulative. He's ice cold.
He sees what makes you tick
and how to exploit it.
If anyone can do this, it's him.
[KORO-SENSEI]
That boy...
He's left me with no choice
but to go buy another gelato.
He's sharp. Deviously clever.
Mustn't let him bait me.
Mustn't give him
the satisfaction
of losing my temper
and killing him.
I am the teacher,
he is the student.
Yes, indeed.
I'll have to be exceptionally
careful with that one.
[SUGINO]
See ya later, Nagisa.
[NAGISA]
Bye! Have a good one!
[TANAKA] Are you kiddin'
me? Is that actually Nagisa?
Look at the guy all cozy
with the E Class dumbasses.
Ew, gross. Gotta hand it to him,
he's adapted to the crowd
he's gonna spend
the rest of his life with.
Hey, did you hear the news?
Now that his suspension's over,
they shoved that Akabane
nut over to E Class.
Ooh! Dude! No kidding?
I'd rather be dead than stuck
in a classroom with that freak!
[TANAKA, TAKADA gasp]
Seriously? Because I can
help you out with that.
It'd be messy, but real quick.
I'd rather live,
thanks! Run away!
Like I'd actually
do anything, right?
I'm not gonna risk
another suspension
with the once-in-a-lifetime deal
they're giving me in E Class.
Uh, hey.
Yeah, hey, Nagisa.
Is it cool if I pick
your brain for a sec?
[KARMA] Word is that you've been
keepin' notes on the octopus.
[NAGISA]
Um, well. Yeah, I kinda have.
Does he hate
that nickname?
Us callin' him
"octopus," I mean?
[NAGISA]
Now that you mention it.
Whenever he draws himself,
it's always as an octopus,
and that's the skin he
picks for his characters
in every video game.
[KORO-SENSEI]
And there's this thing
he does in the sandbox.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Octopus trap.
So, no, I don't
think he minds at all.
In fact, I think it's like his
personal avatar
or whatever, y'know?
He loves it.
Does he?
That's good.
Oh, this is gonna be
friggin' epic.
I know that look.
You're cooking up
something really dark.
I might be. It's fun, right?
I was into this when I thought
he was just a monster,
but... now that I know what
his personality is like.
[train horn blares]
[KARMA] I finally get to kill
an honest-to-goodness teacher!
[laughs]
I've been dreaming of this.
Ever since my last
teacher up and died.
[gasps]
[KORO-SENSEI sobs]
My gelato funds...
Gone, pinched right out
from under my nose.
And with payday
an eternity away!
Guess I'll have to
make my own now.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Good morning, boys and girls!
[STUDENTS sigh]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Uh? Why the long faces?
Has something--
[KARMA]
Oops! That's on me.
Yeah, totally thought it
was you, innocent mistake.
I stabbed it, so I s'pose
I should get rid of it?
[KORO-SENSEI sighs]
Yes, you should.
[KARMA]
Bring it on, Koro-sensei.
No worries, I don't plan on
killin' you physically, yet.
It's more fun to watch
your spirit die first.
[STUDENTS scream]
[KORO-SENSEI] Observe,
if you will, Karma m'boy,
the versatility of
these tentacles,
and the firepower of
this missile yoinked
from the Self Defense Force!
[gasps]
[KORO-SENSEI] If you think
I'm gonna let the new kid
get away with murder,
think again.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Don't you know breakfast is
the most important
meal of the day?
Your complexion tells me
you haven't eaten.
So, please, help yourself to
some of this delicious takoyaki,
I insist.
[KORO-SENSEI]
You see...
I'm a giver...
I take care of things.
Hungry students, would-be
assassins, troubled teens.
Every attempt on my life
is an opportunity for me
to play my part.
So, by all means, keep at it.
[KORO-SENSEI] By the end of
the day, if your body and mind
aren't aglow with
health and knowledge,
I haven't done my job.
[KORO-SENSEI]
As you can see,
whatever we do,
this number remains.
Now, I know the concept
of indivisibility is a beast.
But, if its fangs frighten you,
I have a surefire method
for taming it.
See if you can get the gist as
I write it out on the board.
Karma.
It takes an anti-me BB
far too long to reach its mark.
[gasps]
[KORO-SENSEI]
I had time on my hands.
Hope you don't mind
if I prettified yours.
[KARMA growls]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Let's see now.
How'd the two of you do, Fuwa?
I'm... not totally sure.
It's got a bizarre tangy flavor
to it for some reason.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Let's give it a taste.
[KARMA] Probably easier if you
just start over from scratch.
Why not toss it out?
[KORO-SENSEI] We wear
an apron in Home Ec, Karma.
[KARMA gasps]
[KORO-SENSEI] Oh, and
don't worry: the soup is fine.
I siphoned it out of thin air
and put it back in the pot.
I also added a dash of sugar.
[gasps]
That's exactly what it needed!
[TERASAKA laughs]
Cute outfit.
[KARMA growls]
[NAGISA]
It's no use.
[KORO-SENSEI
"Over that little pool..."
[NAGISA]
Koro-sensei has weaknesses.
We all do.
He screws up
every now and then,
and his speed drops
to human levels
whenever he's flustered, sure.
But...
Karma's been so relentless
with his surprise attacks.
[KORO-SENSEI "Even as I was
thinking this, the red frog,
having failed again,
was making its way back.
I was starting
to get bored with it...
[NAGISA] He has
Koro-sensei on high alert.
--And that means... No dice...
--[school bell chimes]
[NAGISA] C'mon, man.
I'm tellin ya not to sweat it.
We'll do it
together as a group.
You could have the sneakiest,
most foolproof plan in the world
ready to go,
but if Koro-sensei's
got his eye on you, forget it.
He's not like other teachers.
Other teachers, huh?
No.
[TEACHER ONO] I'm with
you a hundred percent, Akabane.
Yes, you've had problems.
Yes, you have issues
respecting authority.
But you're absolutely
in the right.
Not a question.
And I stand by you.
[KARMA]
Hm.
You don't understand.
I wanna do it on my own.
Let me ask you,
would it tick you off to die
in some random place?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Oh, Karma?
I feel like I've taken
exceptionally good
care of you today.
Keep trying to kill me
if that tickles your fancy.
I certainly don't get tired
of spiffing you up.
Just so we're on
the same page here.
You pretty much consider
yourself a teacher
above all else?
[KORO-SENSEI]
That's right.
[KARMA]
Cool.
And you wouldn't
think twice about
putting your life on the line
to save a student?
[KORO-SENSEI] What sort of
teacher would I be if I did?
[KARMA]
That's awesome. Good to know.
So I can kill you.
Knew there had to be a way.
[gasps]
[KARMA]
What's it gonna be, Teach?
You gonna swoop down to save me
and get blasted in the process?
Or you gonna be
the sort of teacher
who lets one of your kids die?
Ha, ha! Whoa!
That crap they say
about your life flashing
before your eyes is true!
I think he's learned
his lesson.
Three-E? The one
out in the sticks?
Dude, that sucks.
Still, don't let anyone
give you lip over it.
What?
I'm not the bad guy here.
All I did was put
a bully in his place.
Little jerk had it comin'.
No! Damn it, Akabane!
Any way you slice it,
you're clearly in the wrong!
[KARMA gasps]
Are you out of your mind,
or just stupid?!
What possessed you to think
attacking your class's star
pupil like a mad dog
was something I'd let slide?
[KARMA]
But... Sir, he was...
What? Talking badly
about the dregs?!
Good for you, injuring
someone on principle!
This young man
happens to have a future!
If this interferes with
his exams, it's on my head!
[KARMA]
He said he'd stand by me.
So much for that, I guess...
Damn.
I'm totally gonna die.
I've been willing
to turn a blind eye
on account of your grades.
But you've tried my
patience once too often.
Throw a monkey wrench into
my career and all bets are off.
I'm not saving you anymore.
[KARMA] This is it.
This is how it's gonna go down.
[TEACHER ONO] The good news is
I filed the paperwork
for your transfer
just this afternoon.
Best thing for all
involved, really.
But the bad news is,
you'll be commencing
Third Year in E Class.
[TEACHER ONO screams]
[KARMA]
Son of a bitch screwed me over.
So that's it.
He's dead to me now.
[KARMA] What are you
waitin' for, Koro-sensei?
Let's do this!
You either die for real,
or I kill your reputation.
[KARMA grunts]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Well done!
A splendidly premeditated
assassination attempt!
Full marks! Neat, huh?
I knew your body couldn't take
being plucked out of freefall
at the speed of sound,
and had I moved any slower,
you would've shot me.
What a tangled and
sticky web we weave, eh?
What the hell?!
Is there anything these
tentacles aren't capable of?!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Can't shoot me now, can you?
[KORO-SENSEI laughs]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Oh, and for future reference:
Students do not
die on my watch.
--Ever.
--[KARMA gasps]
[KORO-SENSEI] Take that to heart
for the next time you jump.
[KARMA] I got nothin'.
Un-friggin'-believable.
He won't die. The teacher
in him especially.
I don't get it. How were you
so calm the whole time?
[KARMA]
Meh. No big.
What really sucks is
that was my best bet.
Nothing else I can come up
with even touches it.
[KORO-SENSEI] Aw!
Run out of ideas already?
But I have an entire beauty
regimen lined up just for you!
"C'mon. No way you can be
this big of a pushover!"
[KARMA] I still feel
like killing something.
Except... it's different
this time, somehow.
No worries, Teach.
You're still dead meat.
[KORO-SENSEI] That's
the spirit! Never give up!
Seems my tender loving
care has paid off.
[NAGISA]
Hm.
[KARMA] Welp.
Let's head back, Nagisa.
We can grab some
food on the way.
[KORO-SENSEI yells]
Excuse me! That's my purse!
Come on, teach.
You've gotta stop
leaving stuff unattended
in the faculty lounge.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Give it back!
Here you go.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Gimme-gimme-gimme!
Uh, hey, uh, this is, uh, empty!
There wasn't much
there to begin with.
Call it a donation.
[KORO-SENSEI screams]
[KORO-SENSEI]
A donation? A donation?!
[NAGISA] Every time one of us
goes in for the kill,
we miss the mark,
but somehow end up better off.
That's the way it goes in
our Assassination Classroom.
I can't wait to see how we try
to kill our teacher tomorrow.