I'm not even sure it's possible.
But instead of
killing Koro-sensei,
I think we should
try to save him.
[MIMURA]
Save him?
By like, finding a way to keep
him from self-detonating
come March, or what?
Where do we start?
Well, I don't know. Yet.
But...
Totally! I'm game!
Koro-sensei's way too good
of a bug-hunting buddy
to let explode!
Kurahashi...
Thank you for bringing it up.
If you hadn't said
something, I would've.
Saving him's
the least we can do.
So you're on board?
[SUMIRE]
Seems appropriate.
It is what this class
has been leading to.
Damn right. I'm in!
Far as I'm concerned,
it's a whole new challenge!
Like a new show, sort of.
I really don't wanna
live with the guilt.
I mean we're obligated
to at least give it a shot.
Guys, you...
[NAGISA]
Thank goodness...
They feel the same way I do.
[SUGINO]
Amen to that, Okano!
[STUDENTS murmur, laugh]
I really hate to be the one
who spoils the mood...
...but I'm against it.
[ALL]
Huh?
[NAKAMURA] We're assassins.
He's the target.
That's our bond.
Koro-sensei said so himself.
I don't know about you,
but I cherish that bond.
Think about it.
Not killing him would
defeat the purpose.
Nakamura, I...
You're against it?
We get wantin' to
save him and all.
but how do we know
it's even doable?
Well, I...
You act like you're the only one
who's been thinkin' about this.
Also, what happens if
the clock runs out on us
before we find a way?
Did you consider that?
Seriously. You want the
Octopus's last thought to be
"Damn, my students
are a bunch of half-asses"?
No! But--
We owe it to him!
Always the talented ones, huh?
Figuring whatever the odds,
in the end, things
will always work out.
Wow. Listen to you.
Getting a tad full of
yourself there, chief.
Granted, you're the most
gifted one in our class.
But seriously.
We should just up and scrap
the whole assassination plan?
What about the underdogs?
Those of us who work ourselves
sick just to squeak by
on what little talent we have.
How're we supposed to feel?
You're like a hot chick
tellin' her homely friends
there's no point
trying to find a man.
'Course you don't have a problem
with changing the rules.
You've already won the game.
That... That's not
what I'm trying to say...
Besides...
I'm not the gifted one.
Between you and me,
you're the better assassin.
Okay, hearing you talk like that
just pisses me off even more.
You know what your
problem is, Nagisa?
You've got no respect for how
hard this is for everyone
who isn't you.
Whoa, whoa!
Where is this coming from?!
I'm just telling you how I feel!
Do you have an axe to grind
with Koro-sensei or something?!
He took us to the movies!
He's made learning fun!
That's my point! Why do you
think he bothered?! Huh?!
He didn't want us to
end up like a bunch of
whiney, half-assed jerks!
And look at you!
Assassinating him is what
this entire class is based on.
You're just trying
to find a loophole!
You wanna undermine
what Koro-sensei's done?
Or do you have the mind and
the body of a ten-year-old?
[KARMA]
Ah. What's with that look?
Aw, the itty-bitty mouse
wanna roar?
Feel like he could
take on a lion?
No, I...
[KARMA]
Got somethin' to say?
Kick my ass for once and
you can say whatever you like.
Oh, don't be shy.
What're you afraid of?
Let's settle this like men.
C'mon! Ha!
[gasps]
A flying triangle hold!
[NAGISA] I am not...
a whiney, half-assed jerk!
Well, all right then.
When did Nagisa learn that move?
Um...
[KIMURA] He's still no match for
Karma in hand-to-hand combat.
You little...!
[MAEHARA]
Knock it off!
[ISOGAI] What the hell are the
two of you trying to prove?!
[MAEHARA] Okay! I don't
think I can hold him back!
[MAEHARA] Damn it, Karma!
Will you chill out already?
[KORO-SENSEI] A good
old-fashioned schoolyard fight?
Outstanding!
However, you're the
Assassination Classroom!
This is how we settle
our differences!
[STUDENTS]
What kind of mediator are you?!
Oh, these are just
red and blue paintballs.
[KORO-SENSEI] Red for those who
feel I must be liquidated.
Blue for those
who beg to differ.
Before we begin, I want each
of you to state his or her
position clearly and
choose a color.
Then, after battling it out
on the mountainside
like civilized human beings, the
winning team's opinion prevails.
[gasping]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Absolutely no grudges allowed!
Seem fair?
[KORO-SENSEI]
For the record...
Whatever the outcome,
I'll respect your decision,
provided you defend it
with everything you have.
You are all a family.
I can't abide for my students
to be at odds with each other.
If you truly care about me,
promise what we've built here
won't crumble into discord.
Well, guys?
Right. Let's do it.
[ISOGAI]
To kill or not to kill.
'Kay, then. So, guess
I'll choose a side.
Me, too.
[RYUNOSUKE] The insta-kill
shot's almost there.
We've put a lot of work into it.
[RYUNOSUKE] And, as for who,
or what, got us this far...
[HAYAMI] ...I'm sure he'd want
to see us take it all the way.
We keep our eyes on the target.
Chiba... Hayami, you...
[KAEDE]
My mind's made up.
I've already tried
to assassinate him once,
and I regret it.
I want Koro-sensei to
live as long as possible.
My sister felt the same way;
must run in the
family or something.
[KAEDE]
No more death.
He's entitled to our protection.
[KAEDE]
Having a thing for assassins
runs in the family, too...
[OKUDA] The power
of science is limitless!
If it can sow
destruction, then surely
it can find a way to save!
Right. And it's not
as though hope is slim,
we can do anything together.
I know we can.
[OKAJIMA]
Sorry, but us hands-on types?
We kinda see this assassination
as our big final project.
[OKAJIMA grunts]
If Koro-sensei's
gonna die anyway,
showing him our masterpiece
will be his going away present.
[KIMURA] Justice is a tricky
concept for a kid like me,
you're the one who
taught me to respect it.
My choice is clear:
Gotta live up to my name.
[KANZAKI]
I suppose I'm selfish.
I want him to keep
giving us good advice.
[KIRARA] Save the planet
or save our teacher?
Blah, blah, blah.
We're just goin'
around in circles.
I'm more of a cut-to-the-chase
kind of gal.
[TOKA] If you can't be true
to your own feelings,
what hope is there in life?
I want him to live, that's that.
[MAEHARA] Couldn't have
said it better myself.
We're simple guys at heart,
the two of us.
We wanna save him 'cause we
wanna save him, y'know?
Right?
Sure. As long as I can
still be sensitive
to everyone else's needs.
[ITONA] I'm a simple guy.
I joined this class to kill him.
I've learned a lot.
Even made a few friends.
Coming up with ways
to kill him has been fun.
So, yeah.
More of that, please.
[RITSU]
It may be my prime directive,
but after several attempts to
assassinate Koro-sensei,
I'm at a loss.
The protocol has changed.
I've thought about this, and
I've come to the conclusion
that the target's death would
be an immeasurable loss to us.
The right course of
action is unclear.
My current specs are unable
to make an informed decision
on the matter.
So in the spirit of cooperation,
I'll remain neutral.
[OKANO] Not gonna lie--I was
in the no-kill camp.
But hearing everyone's
thoughts... now I'm not so sure.
I have a question.
If we do this, does killing you
necessarily mean we hate you?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Of course not, Okano.
Quite the opposite, in fact.
It's when you're killing me
that I feel the most loved.
Well, in that case,
Nagisa, I'm sorry.
Pretty sure my feelings
are more in line with
where these guys stand.
[NAGISA] Guess it was
a little arrogant of me
to think I spoke
for the whole class.
[SUGINO]
Aw, man.
This is gonna be one
hell of a showdown, huh?
Uh, hey, I've been kinda
wondering about something.
So Nagisa and Karma...
They've been friends
for a while, yeah?
Oh, sure, been in the same class
since they were First Years.
They hang out all the time.
Huh. But look how they act.
There's always this
polite distance.
You can hear it in the way
they talk sometimes.
Like they don't really feel
comfortable with each other.
[ISOGAI]
All right.
Looks like everyone's
picked a side.
[KARASUMA] The object is to the
steal the opposing team's flag,
or to wipe them out entirely.
It's my job to referee.
I'll be watching from midpoint.
If I see zombies or any other
illegal moves, I'll call 'em.
Don't worry. For all
intents and purposes,
I'm blind to your
respective positions, got it?
[KARASUMA] Even if the
pro-kill team wins this thing,
odds are an assassination
at this stage won't succeed.
These kids are just
too conflicted
to go through with it.
Who wouldn't be?
[KARASUMA]
Here we go. Are you ready?
Let the intra-class
assassination survival game--
Begin!
[BOTH]
Right out of the gate?!
[TAKEBAYASHI]
Ugh!
Shot just as we were
getting into position!
[MEG] It's hard to establish
a BB's trajectory
beyond 50 meters.
Chiba and Hayami's super
long-distance sniper shot
is incredible!
[IRINA]
Holy crap.
The killing machines you've
made out of those two!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Indeed.
Though, as you'll see,
they're far from the only ones.
Nice job: Keep your sights
trained on the enemy.
[gunfire]
You're kidding me! Wow.
Did not see that one coming!
I should've known.
Kanzaki: Undisputed champion
of the online war game.
[KANZAKI] Started playing to
help with assassination
and got where I mastered it.
What?!
[KANZAKI] I'm glad I did. The
hours it took really paid off.
Yukiko. She's been
keepin' a low profile.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Hasn't she, though?
And her battle style
is so classical!
A frontal breakthrough on
this field is quite difficult.
Normally, the best strategy
would be to circle around
and attack from the outside.
And yet...
[KANZAKI gasps]
[KARMA]
Oh, that's right.
You cut your teeth on a virtual
battlefield, didn't you?
Trouble is, once I realize
you're making a beeline
for a key position,
all I have to do is be patient
and wait for you to jump.
Red Team, it's Karma.
I'll be taking the lead.
Mimura, there's a highpoint
to Mr. Karasuma's right.
You should have a visual.
Go for it.
[MIMURA]
Copy that.
[KARMA]
Make sure no one sees you.
Terasaka and the other stooges,
I want you on defense
at Face Rock.
We're screwed if they make it
past there, so play it tight.
Man, why are we
always pawns?
Shut your hole!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Ah! Very well done out there!
[MEG]
I was careless.
We were only two minutes in
and I got killed...
[KORO-SENSEI]
By Karma's orders, most likely.
[IRINA]
Incredible.
The red-headed one's
so organized.
What else does he have
up his sleeve?
[MIMURA]
Karma, I'm at the highpoint.
[KARMA]
Perfect.
You should have a clear view
of the enemies' movements.
Anyone shows up, give me
their positions and I'll order
our team to mobilize.
[KARMA] Mimura always blends in.
Makes him ideal for covert ops.
Plus he's got a producer's
eye for the field,
which translates into a real
knack for reconnaissance.
Not that anyone else
in class has ever noticed.
[MIMURA]
I see Sugino and Fuwa, I think.
Forest, right flank.
Nice. Keep it up.
Hazama, this is
your cue to advance.
[chuckles]
[SUGINO]
Where'd she even come from?!
Stop being one with
the shadows, dang it!
[grunts]
Rat bastard used me as a decoy.
You'll be paying
for that, Karma.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Why move Hazama into such
a compromising position?
He had to have known she'd
be hopelessly outnumbered.
[TAKEBAYASHI] Well, Hazama
is a terrible fighter,
but she did manage
to take down two enemies.
Not least of which was Sugino,
the close-combat superstar.
[KARMA]
Their ranks are in shambles.
Now's the time
for a surprise attack.
Okano?
On it!
--[HINANO groans]
--Oh no!
I lost the Battle of the Hinas.
I'm sorry...
Ha! Well done!
You've been holding out on us!
[KAEDE grunts]
I'm gonna assume you didn't pick
these moves up in gym class!
I'm an actor, I take training
for a role very seriously!
Now that I don't have to mask
the pain of having tentacles,
I can actually focus!
[OKANO]
Aw, crap...
[KAEDE] Koro-sensei...
I'll keep you safe!
--[gunshots]
--[grunts]
I'm impressed.
But I sure wish we could've seen
this side of you before now.
[OKANO] You weren't the
only one working hard in secret.
We've all been training.
Honing our skills.
However this business ends up,
we'll face it
together as a class.
No masks.
No more secret agendas.
Sound good?
[gasps]
Okay, then.
We'll see you later!
Oh-ho, hey! Remind me
to get your autograph.
[KIMURA]
Ee-hee-yeah-ha!
Let's keep up the momentum
and tag someone else!
You sure? But Karma's orders
were to hit and run!
Yo, look! It's Hara
and she's wide open!
Tonight's rations
belong to me!
[BOTH yelp]
Uh-oh! Ha! Little
homemade trap of mine.
Mama is fierce.
An unarmed girl
alone in the woods
must seem like
a pretty easy mark.
I suppose looks
can be deceiving, huh?
Hey, no butt-cutting, pervert!
Stupid idiot got
ahead of himself.
Seriously, why the hell
can't people just do
what I tell them to?
Yeah, it's a tragedy.
Well, looks like it's time
for your lieutenant
to finish this off.
Isn't that why you left
the stooges over there?
Not bad. You get me.
Have fun.
[OKUDA]
Ah-ha! Over there!
Ugh, I figured our
formation was leaked.
Mimura can see us!
[KARMA] As of now,
both sides are down by half.
Okay, I think it's time
we start focusing
on flag-capturing tactics.
[SUMIRE grunts]
[KARMA]
Strategic maneuvering is key.
We were bound to
get here eventually.
It's why we took out Kataoka
and Takebayashi first.
To deprive the enemy
camp of options.
To that end, Hayami's
lookout position
was absolutely crucial. Couldn't
have done it without her.
[HAYAMI] I'm gonna need you
stand guard, Itona.
[gasps]
[KARMA] Chiba can shoot farther
and hit the target more often,
but her balance and kinetic
vision are way better.
Give her an active
battlefield like this,
and she really shines.
[ISOGAI grunts]
She's not gonna be an easy one.
Gotta go in carefully.
We could try attacking
from the opposite side,
but then we'd have to
break through Terasaka's
defensive line,
and he's too solid.
And the area around their flag
is well within Hayami's range.
We've no choice but
to take Hayami out first.
Hayami, Itona, they'll be coming
in droves any second now.
Do whatever you can
to slow 'em down.
If you can take 'em out,
take 'em out.
[HAYAMI, ITONA]
Roger.
[KARMA] Nakamura,
when the fight starts,
I want you to step
in and finish it.
[NAKAMURA]
Gotcha.
That means we're counting
on you, Meat Wall!
--[TERASAKA] Excuse me?!
--Shut up.
Everyone else'll be
occupied with Rinka.
I'm gonna rush in while you
play the part of my shield.
Once you three are dead, I'll
have time to capture the flag.
Good strategy, right?
Of course it is.
So we're being
sacrificed, then?
That is some
serious ruthlessness.
[NAKAMURA] Duh! We have
to do whatever it takes.
I wanna win this...
so we can kill Koro-sensei.
[sighs] I know what this is.
You wanted us all
to think you were stupid,
so you did stupid stuff.
But be honest,
you joined the pro-kill camp
because you feel
you have a sense of duty.
In reality, out of everyone
here you're the one who
takes things the most seriously.
[KARMA] The plan's as ready as
it's ever going to be I suppose.
There's just one hitch: Nagisa.
Not even Mimura can
figure out where he is.
[ISOGAI] Okay, guys.
Forget about defense.
Take out Hayami and
Itona no matter what!
Tag those two, and Karma's
the only one guarding the flag.
Let's settle this now!
[guns firing]
All right...
Let's get over there, guys!
[yelps]
[ISOGAI]
Surround them from the left!
[gasps]
Isogai's in the lead.
If I can take him down,
we'll have this game in the bag!
[TOKA]
I sincerely hate conflict,
and never once have
I managed to shoot
anywhere near as good as Rinka.
But this isn't for me.
It's for Koro-sensei!
Yada...?
I got her!
And I'm out, too...
[grunting]
Cool, huh?
I had a feeling I was more
of a knife guy, y'know?
I mean, there's no way
I'm worth a damn with a gun.
[TERASAKA]
Son of a--
Did they get you?!
It doesn't matter.
The flag's unguarded either way.
It's time.
Nakamura, get in there now.
[NAKAMURA]
Yes, sir!
[gasps]
[NAKAMURA screams]
[grunts]
[NAKAMURA] From behind
at point-blank range...?
Like a bolt of lightning
out of the clear blue sky!
Where in the world
has he been hiding?!