[KORO-SENSEI] Thank you
for the help, children.
I really appreciate it.
[MEG] You may have more hands
than the rest of us,
but it'd still be
a stretch for you to carry
all this lab equipment
by yourself.
[KORO-SENSEI] Exactly.
Now, it's a one-trip job!
No wonder you were both
elected class officers.
So reliable!
Thanks, but you really
could've done this without us.
Couple of quick trips
back and forth.
[KORO-SENSEI]
I supposed I could've, yes.
But the more the merrier, eh?
I have a question, sir.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Yes?
Are you starting
to feel at home?
Like, with all of us?
Wow. I can't believe you're
really asking him that.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Put in those terms,
I'd say I feel incredibly
at home as your teacher.
That's strange.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Really?
[ISOGAI]
Well, yeah.
A creature like you taking
any interest whatsoever
in a group of junior high kids
isn't exactly something
you see every day.
[MEG] I mean, you actually teach
us, so it's borderline cool.
Just takes getting used to.
Yeah, no kidding.
[growling, grunting]
Then there's the whole
assassination thing.
[KORO-SENSEI laughs]
[KORO-SENSEI] A vital part
of my role, I'd argue.
Target, teacher. We ought
not separate the two.
Did he seriously just
dodge three knives
while prepping lab?
--[school bell chimes]
--Hey, Maehara. You okay?
Eh.
--[KORO-SENSEI laughs]
--They should know by now
that was too obvious.
Am I right, Teach?
[KORO-SENSEI] All right,
boys and girls, let's begin!
[OKUDA whimpers]
[STUDENTS gasping]
[SUGAYA]
Whoa! It's bright red!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Ta-da!
And that's how we extract the
coloring from processed foods.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[KORO-SENSEI]
I'll, uh...
I'll just take the leftover
samples, thank you.
Excuse me.
[STUDENTS scream]
[SUGINO] Wait! We bought
those for ourselves!
Is it me, or did he
just use this lab
to support his junk-food
habit between paychecks?
My question's why a
super organism has to
live on a teacher's salary
in the first place.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Eh?
I, uh...
Well, uh...
[KORO-SENSEI]
Go on, speak up, Okuda.
What can I do for you?
Umm!
Poison, sir! Would you
drink it, please?!
[STUDENTS gasp]
Well, she doesn't
beat around the bush.
[OKUDA]
I'm sorry. Is this weird?
[KORO-SENSEI] It's certainly
a very straightforward
assassination attempt,
I'll give you that.
See, the thing is, sir, I'm not
very good at being sneaky.
I mean, everyone else
is so good at this stuff.
But, me? What I'm good
at is chemistry!
And I put my heart and
soul into this mixture!
--[STUDENTS murmuring]
--[MIMURA] All righty, then.
[SUGINO]
Um, Okuda?
Points for throwing in,
but no one's that stupid.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Your heart and soul?
Don't mind if I do, then!
[STUDENTS gasping, chattering]
[KORO-SENSEI retches]
[KORO-SENSEI]
This-This is!
Is it really gonna work?
[MAEHARA]
This might be it!
[KORO-SENSEI squeaks]
[STUDENTS groan]
[ISOGAI]
Or he could just grew horns.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Quite a kick.
Sodium hydroxide, I believe?
Good try, Miss Okuda.
If I were human, I'd most
definitely have bought the farm.
[OKUDA]
Oh, I see.
[KORO-SENSEI] Shall I try the
other two we have here as well?
[OKUDA]
Yes, please!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Right! Down the hatch!
[KORO-SENSEI retches]
[KORO-SENSEI groans]
[ISOGAI]
He grew wings this time?!
[MAEHARA] Wow, he's starting
to look kinda fancy.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Thallium acetate. Interesting.
Let's see what
the last one does.
[KORO-SENSEI retches, grunts]
[MEG]
Uh-oh!
[SUGINO]
Not sure I wanna see this!
[KORO-SENSEI growls]
[KAEDE]
That's boring.
[SUGINO] This just keeps
getting weirder and weirder.
[ISOGAI]
I don't like this look.
It's creeping me out.
[MIMURA] So poison
turns him into an emoticon?
[KORO-SENSEI]
If you hate me, I understand.
But please, don't
hate assassination.
[OKAJIMA] What's that
even supposed to mean?!
[KORO-SENSEI] Also, young
lady. As your teacher,
I can't overlook the fact that
you handled toxic substances
unsupervised.
[OKUDA]
Yes, sir. Sorry, sir.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Don't worry. I have an idea.
Why don't we work
together on a poison
that has a little
bit more of a kick?
[OKUDA gasps]
Uh, sure!
Doesn't seem like that's gonna
end in success if you ask me.
Might get some good
notes out of it at least.
[STUDENTS chattering]
--[MEG] Heads up!
--[KORO-SENSEI sputters]
[SUGINO]
I got it!
[KAEDE]
Yeah!
[MEG] All right, that's
what I'm talking about!
[STUDENTS chattering]
[IRINA] Hey there,
big boy. How's tricks?
[KARASUMA]
Hmm?
[IRINA]
It's an absolute sauna in here.
Ugh. Aren't you on fire?
That's not the word
I would use, no.
[IRINA growls]
Look, save this act
for the target. Back off.
Ugh, I swear,
you're such a killjoy.
If you're gonna cut it here
as a teacher, pull it together.
I thought we had discussed this.
For your information,
it's not an act.
It's hotter than hell
in this dump.
How do they expect these kids
to function without AC?
I've tried to put in several
requests for renovations,
but the funds aren't there.
Or so I'm told.
[IRINA]
Seriously?
--[SUGINO] Damn it!
--[HINANO] Everyone saw, right?
That was a clean hit!
[KARASUMA] Can't be helped.
It's how things are here.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Okey-dokey.
We're ready to add it
to the ethanol, I think.
Now, be extra careful.
Don't breathe in the fumes.
[OKUDA]
Got it!
[KORO-SENSEI] It's a shame your
enthusiasm for chemistry
doesn't extend
to other subjects.
Heh. Everything else
seems to go over my head.
Especially when it comes
to language arts and stuff.
That's why I'm here, I guess.
I never know
the right thing to say.
The words don't come out or
I get 'em all turned around.
Tell me to express
myself and I seize up.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Hmm...
[OKUDA] It's okay.
I don't mind so much.
At least with math and science,
there's always a right answer.
Everything's
spelled out for you.
They're concise.
No double meanings,
no weird feels.
No worrying that someone'll
take your words the wrong way.
It makes perfect sense.
[KORO-SENSEI]
I see the appeal.
Tell you what, Okuda.
I have a special homework
assignment just for you.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Remember, though. Safety first.
[school bell chimes]
[KAEDE]
Um...
Okay, so he really asked you
to bring the poison to class?
[OKUDA] Yeah! He said
the stuff in this flask
should work like a charm!
He even drew a manga of
the safety guidelines
for proper use and storage.
I'm impressed.
Going the extra mile yet again.
[SUGINO] I know he's
unconventional and all,
but giving us the goods on
a poison that'll kill him?
Nice, right?
I think it's his way
of encouraging me.
I'm good at chemistry,
not words.
He says to focus
on my strengths!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Good morning, everyone.
--[KAEDE] Here's your chance.
--Take your seats, please.
--Go give it to him!
--[OKUDA] Here it is, sir.
Just like you asked.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Ah! Nice work.
Well, here's to
your health, children.
Salud!
[KORO-SENSEI gulping]
[STUDENTS gasping]
[KORO-SENSEI retches]
[KORO-SENSEI laughs]
Thank you, Okuda.
Thank you very much indeed.
This concoction is precisely
what I needed to level up.
[OKUDA]
Wait, you... I don't--
[KORO-SENSEI roars]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Pyuu.
[STUDENTS]
He melted?!
[KORO-SENSEI] You didn't think
that was a poison, did you?
On the contrary. I had you
whip up a special tonic
designed to increase
my fluidity.
[MEG gasps]
[KORO-SENSEI]
In liquid form,
I fit comfortably into the
tightest nooks and crannies.
[MEG]
What are you doing in there?
[KORO-SENSEI] Best of all,
I lose none of my speed!
Go ahead! Try to
beat me! Come on!
[OKAJIMA]
This is messed up, dude!
[KAEDE] What in the world
did you give him?!
[OKUDA]
You tricked me! That's not fair!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Hmm... Fair?
Verbal deception is a vital part
of the successful
assassin's toolkit.
[OKUDA]
Huh?
What are you
talking about, sir?
[KORO-SENSEI] Approaching the
target so naively
is a good way to
fail in your mission.
Even the deadliest
of poisons is useless
if one can't persuade
the mark to drink it.
Nagisa. Say you
wanted to poison me.
How might you go about it?
Huh? Well, lemme think.
I'd probably put it
in something you liked.
--[NAGISA] For you!
- [KORO-SENSEI] For me?
[NAGISA] Then I guess I would
offer it to you as a gift.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Excellent.
You see, to deceive someone you
have to get inside their heads;
know what they respond to.
Use language creatively.
In poisoning, as in life, the
key to success is communication.
[BOTH gasp]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Imagine that one day, you make
an Earth-shattering
scientific discovery.
How can it benefit mankind if it
stays locked inside your head?
Knowing the right thing so say
can make all
the difference, right?
Right! Thank you, sir!
[laughs] Nice move, Teach.
Turn the tables, huh?
No kidding.
[NAGISA]
Leave it to Koro-sensei.
To him, even a student
trying to poison him is still,
first and foremost, a student.
We're a long way off
from being able to kill him.
He's just that good.
[ISOGAI]
Quit dragging your feet.
We show up late again,
there's no telling what kind
of messed up stuff
they'll make us do.
[OKANO] Yeah. Last time we had
to clean out the flower beds.
[MAEHARA]
Heh. Man, that blew.
Those friggin' things
are the size of a house.
[ISOGAI]
What are you bitching about?
We did all the work.
[MAEHARA laughs]
I was moral support!
[OKANO growls]
This sucks!
Somebody explain to me why we're
the only students in school
who have to put up
with this crap!
[KUNUDON]
Surprise!
[BOYS &amp; GIRLS]
Hey! Is that Kunudon?
[KUNUDON]
Hello! It's me, Kunudon!
[BOYS &amp; GIRLS]
Hooray!
[KUNUDON] Today, we're going
to talk about underachievers!
Here, we like to give them a
special place all their own!
A place called E Class,
where they won't bother
the good boys and girls!
[BOYS &amp; GIRLS]
Wow! What a great idea!
[KUNUDON] Now we don't normally
like it when E Class students
set foot on the main campus.
But we do make exceptions
for school assemblies,
when we invite them
to take a stroll down the
mountain on their lunch break.
[OKAJIMA]
Ahh! The stupid bridge is out!
[MIMURA]
No way!
Who's the genius who
told us this was a shortcut?!
Okajima!
[OKAJIMA screams]
Discipline is key!
'Specially for E Class slobs.
And nothing instills
discipline like lining up
inside the gymnasium for
special assemblies, kids!
[BOYS &amp; GIRLS]
Discipline!
[SUMIRE, FUWA, TOKA]
Why are there snakes?!
Look out, Okajima!
Come on, maggots,
get in gear!
Give me a "sir, yes sir!" Now!
[BOYS &amp; GIRLS]
Sir, yes, sir! Hooray!
[KIRARA, MURAMATSU, TERASAKA]
Why are there falling boulders?!
[KIRARA, TERASAKA, YOSHIDA]
Crap! Look out, Okajima!
[screaming
[SUGINO] Whose big idea
was it to poke the beehive?!
[CLASS]
Look out, Okajima!
[SUGINO] He's, uh, not having
a very good day, is he?
Hope the poor guy's all right.
[NAGISA]
Me, too.
[KAEDE] Ugh. Can we
be done with the rocks
and the bees and the things
trying to kill us, please?
I'm glad Okajima was around
to take the brunt of it for us.
Hey. Anyone hurt?
I think we're mostly okay.
Good. No rush.
In fact, at this rate, we're
making fairly excellent time.
[IRINA]
Wait for me!
[IRINA growls]
Way to ditch me, jerks!
[KAEDE]
Hey! Professor Bitch!
[IRINA] No one said anything
about a class trip during lunch.
Yeah, no offense, Professor,
but you look wrecked.
You try running through
nature in heels!
Mr. Karasuma?
Where's Koro-sensei?
[KARASUMA] We told him to
wait back at the old campus
for security reasons.
It wouldn't do for the other
students to see him.
[KORO-SENSEI]
I'm all alone. A shunned Sensei.
[Well. The main campus
isn't much further away.
Are you ready?
[IRINA, STUDENTS]
Yeah...
[STUDENTS panting, groaning]
That sincerely sucked.
Well, at least we're not late.
No idea how that happened.
Hurry up, people!
We've got to get in line
before they start!
[STUDENTS]
Okay.
[TAKADA]
Hey, Nagisa!
--[NAGISA] Uh?
--Wow, look at you guys!
I'm surprised you made it!
Must've been a heck of a trek
rollin' down the mountain!
[TAKADA, TANAKA laugh]
[NAGISA] Once a month,
there's an all-school assembly.
And even here we get treated
like the lowest of the low.
Not something
we look forward to,
but... not a lot we can
do about it, either.
[DEAN]
You are the cream of the crop.
This nation's shining elite.
Never forget that.
I am proud to be your dean.
But!
Don't get too comfortable.
No. Let E Class remind
us of the perils in that.
--[E CLASS STUDENTS sigh]
--[A-D CLASS STUDENTS laugh]
[DEAN] Now, now! It's unkind
to laugh at their expense!
Hey, Nagisa.
Why isn't Karma here?
Because he's ditching.
What?
Is he out of his mind?!
[NAGISA] It's not like he
doesn't know he'll catch hell
for blowing off assembly;
he just doesn't care.
Wish I had the grades
to get away with that.
They'd probably
just throw me out.
Yeah, ain't that the truth.
[INSTRUCTOR A]
If I may say so, sir,
this method is
remarkably effective!
It shows in the percentage of
students from our academy
who go on to top universities.
E Class aside, of course.
[PRINCIPAL]
We are pragmatists here.
Realists. Young people must be
prepared for the world as it is.
Sadly, the best way to
ignite their potential
is to let them see it
extinguished in others.
Very sound reasoning.
[PRINCIPAL]
Yes, of course it is.
Whether in school
administration or assassination,
I pride myself on
adherence to logic.
[STUDENT ANNOUNCER A]
Now we'll have an address
by the student council.
Student council members,
--come up to the podium, please.
--[BOY STUDENT A] Who's that?
Never seen him before.
[GIRL STUDENT A] He looks way
too cool to be a teacher!
[KARASUMA] ...take this
opportunity to introduce myself.
--Oh. Hello.
--[HINANO] You too?
Wow! Cool!
Yeah.
[KARASUMA grunts]
Hey. Check it, Mister K.
We decorated the thing
we keep our knives in!
So stylish.
They're "totes adorable," yes!
Now put them away!
We're supposed to
keep this on the DL.
The other students can't know!
[HINANO, NAKAMURA]
Oh, sorry.
[BOY STUDENT B] I think he's
the new E Class teacher.
Looks like he's big on
the hands-on approach.
No fair. Why can't the regular
teachers be that hot?
I mean, seriously, is there
some kind of rule?
[BOY STUDENT C, D growl]
[STUDENTS gasping]
[STUDENTS gasp]
[BOY STUDENT F] Whoa!
Who's the boobalicious
foreign-looking chick?!
Five minutes ago she was
down on all fours,
but damn,
look at 'er work it!
[IRINA pants]
Slow down. I'm dying!
[NAGISA]
Quick recovery, huh?
[BOY STUDENT G] Don't tell me
she's an E Class teacher, too?
[GIRL STUDENT C]
So jealous...
What are you doing here?
Don't even try
to pull rank on me.
I'm an educator
just like you are.
So you're finally
embracing your role?
Or, I just need an excuse
to scope out the student body.
Me-ow. Said nobody ever.
Oh. That's right.
Nagisa. The octopus
isn't around. Talk to me.
Gimme some intel.
You're still keeping a record
of all the ooey-gooey bastard's
vulnerable points, right?
Let teacher peek
at your notebook
and I'll make it
worth your while.
Uh. I, uh, haven't
added anything to it
since the last time you looked.
Please, sweetheart.
You and I both know
you're keeping the good stuff
all to your lonesome.
Actually, I've shared every--
Ugh. Come on now, kid.
Dish. Or I'll smother you.
[NAGISA]
Stop it, Professor Bitch!
I can't breathe through
your enormous ta-tas!
[TANAKA]
What a teacher.
[TAKADA]
What a... bitch.
[BOY STUDENT H] What the
hell? Are you kidding me?
[BOY STUDENT I]
The End Class douche bags
aren't supposed to
get any special perks!
[IRINA]
Oww!
[ARAKI] Okay. All the upcoming
student council events
are detailed in the handouts
you've just been given.
Uh. Hang on. How come
we didn't get any?
[OKADA]
Ionno.
[ISOGAI]
Uh, excuse me, sir?
E Class didn't get the handouts.
Oh. Wow, really?
That's kind of bizarre.
Huh. I'm so sorry.
I thought for sure we printed
enough for everyone!
Guess E Class will just
have to memorize it
off their neighbors'.
[STUDENTS laugh]
[ARAKI] That works out
for the best, really.
I mean, you people could use the
mental exercise I'm guessing.
What a little prick.
Somebody ought to punch--
[KORO-SENSEI]
There you go, Isogai.
Seriously?!
[KORO-SENSEI] That should
take care of it, I think.
All of you have a copy of
the handout now, correct?
[ISOGAI] Yes, Sir!
Never mind. We have some.
My mistake, sorry.
You what?! But, I--
How did you--?
Okay, who's the wise guy?
Who killed our fun?
Er, I mean. Ahem!
As I was saying before.
Um, if you'll take a closer look
at the events schedule,
you'll notice we have quite
a few things packed...
I thought we agreed we couldn't
let the other students see you.
What part of "state secret"
do you refuse to understand?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Relax. My disguise is flawless.
No one suspects a thing.
Looks like somebody
got a little lonely.
Can't say I blame the guy.
[BOY STUDENT A] Hey. Was that
teacher standing there
a second ago?
[BOY STUDENT B] I dunno,
what's with him bein' all big
and, like, wriggly?
[BOY STUDENT A] Yeah.
And what's with the hot one
trying to stab him?
[BOY STUDENT B] Is that a
thing? Can she do that?
--I can get him, let go!
--Come on!
The other one's got her
in some kind of hold.
That class is crazy.
Oh well. I'll say this much
for her, she never quits.
[TANAKA, TAKADA growl]
[SUGINO] We're gonna
run on ahead, Nagisa.
[NAGISA] Cool. I'll grab a
drink and catch up with you.
[TAKADA]
Yo, Nagisa.
[NAGISA]
Uh?
You proud of yourselves?
Acting like you're havin'
the time of your lives?
Laughing during assembly.
Not cool.
You bums ever hear of respect?
If I was in E Class, I'd keep
my head down and my mouth shut.
Yeah, and I sure as hell
wouldn't have a reason to laugh.
[TAKADA] Hey. Watch it with
that look, I'm warnin' ya.
[KARASUMA]
Hmm?
[TANAKA growls]
This whole stupid
system is a travesty.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Easy does it.
The boy can handle himself.
My students know how
to deal with bullies.
[TANAKA] Something
you wanna say, scumbag?
You want me to kill your ass?!
[NAGISA]
Kill? You're kidding, right?
You're really gonna kill me?
--[NAGISA] Heh.
--[TANAKA gasps]
Like you've got
the balls to try.
Go right ahead.
[TANAKA, TAKADA gasp]
[TANAKA] Dude, what...
What was that all about?
[TAKADA]
Damn. He's a psycho.
[KORO-SENSEI]
What did I tell you?
They have more self-respect
than to roll over for a bully.
[KARASUMA]
Huh...
[PRINCIPAL]
Interesting.
An E Class reprobate
presuming to shove his betters?
Hmph. What nonsense.
This behavior is unacceptable.
It would appear
a few tweaks are in order.
Assassination can wait.
For now, my priority
is the status quo.