[KUNUDON]
Surprise!
[CHILDREN]
Tell us, Kunudon!
Well hello there, boys 'n girls!
Fall's here at last!
And you know what that means!
Food, studying, and festivals!
Kunugigaoka Academy's Fall
Festival is the real deal!
[CHILDREN] With a great
return-on-investment ratio!
[KUNUDON] Head-hunters
from top tier corporations
come to scout out
potential hires,
so be sure you make
a good impression!
[CHILDREN] Unemployment
is at an all-time high!
[KUNUDON]
Don't be like those students
whose poor business sense
makes them a laughing stock
of the upper class!
[CHILDREN]
Nouveau riche!
Hurray!
[EMPLOYEE A] Our franchise
is happy to lend its support.
Kunugigaoka's Annual Festival
is extraordinarily popular.
Projected sales of our
product is one thing,
but the publicity would be huge.
Mr. Asano.
These are very impressive
figures you've drawn up.
I believe we have a deal.
A pleasure doing
business with you.
[ALL] Uh! What Junior High
kid gets a corporate sponsor?
[GAKUSHU]
No blind spots.
E-Class will be blown
out of the water.
[MAEHARA]
Wow.
The main campus
is really goin' nuts
over this year's festival, huh?
The hype is insane.
Probably 'cause they think
we're up to something.
Word is Asano made a deal with
some big restaurant chain.
Yeah, well. I wouldn't
put it past the guy.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Then we will go for the jugular.
Figuratively, of course.
This competition will
be decided by skills
not assassination related.
I really don't wanna lose
to the A-Class jerkwads.
But what are we supposed to do?
[NAGISA, KAEDE]
Mm.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Asano has the right idea.
This all about providing
something unique.
Give people a bargain
and you'll draw them in,
even on a shoestring budget.
[MAEHARA] Sounds nice,
but how we gonna do that?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Come now, children!
The answers are all around you!
E-Class can give customers
a one-of-a-kind bargain.
On this baby!
And this!
And these.
And these!
Ingredients that have a
lot in common with you!
You're all tucked away
in the mountains
where your value tends
to go unnoticed!
I get it!
We'll hit our customers
where they least expect!
What a cool idea!
An assassination restaurant!
[KORO-SENSEI]
In a manner of speaking, yes.
Now brandish these secret blades
like you're going
in for the kill!
[CROWD chattering]
[TOKA]
Don't miss out!
Genuine acorn noodles,
made from genuine acorns!
The brand new taste
sensation straight from
the mountain's natural
goodness to your mouth!
Ah! Upperclassmen!
You know value for money
when you see it,
but you've never had
anything like this!
[RYUKI] Yeah? Can it
seriously be all that?
Oh, yes!
Come experience the
fresh-picked taste!
[PUNKS laugh]
[RYUKI panting]
[RYUKI]
Hey. Cool place you got here.
[SUGINO] Uh! The high school
thugs from our class trip!
What the hell are
you doing here?!
Hey, guys.
Huh, come to kidnap
another girl?
Yeah, 'cause I'm an idiot.
You think I want your freak
show of a teacher on my back?
No thanks.
'Course, I don't gotta get
physical to wreck your day.
Not at all. I could just
start tellin' everybody
your food tastes like crap.
Maybe write a bad review online.
[SUGINO growls]
C'mon, bring out the grub, son.
[OKUDA]
Our signature dish...
Acorn noodles!
Whoa! This looks great!
Uh, hey, Ryuki?
Would it be okay if
I get a Mont Blanc!
Dude! I gotta try
the smoked fish!
Pretty please!
Knock it off!
Your stupid is showing!
[RYUKI]
Heh. One bite and I'll puke.
Only a Junior High kid
would cook this up.
[RYUKI gasps]
It's delicious!
Originally we were gonna do a
more impressive reaction shot,
but sadly there's already
another cooking anime
that's called dibs on that.
Do what?
Not bad, right? I spent
like a solid week
researching and
refining the recipe.
The noodles are
made from acorns,
thickened with grated yam.
The flavor was super
earthy, though,
so I went with a rich
dipping broth.
Turned out to be
the perfect balance.
It was hard work,
lemme tell ya.
but the end product is tonkotsu
soy-sauce acorn noodles
fit for a king!
No kiddin'.
I ain't never tasted
nothin' like it.
For Muramatsu, it's
kind of a miracle.
Well, so much for blandness
being a selling point.
Hey, Itona!
Shut up and get back to work!
[PUNK A] This stuff is da bomb!
We should try everything!
[PUNK D] Let's do the "Slender
Caesar Mushroom" next!
It sounds awesome!
[RYUKI] We're supposed to say it
tastes like crap, dumbasses!
[IRINA]
Oh... oh, dear.
Aw. You boys don't
like any of the food
my students have
prepared for you?
[PUNKS]
What a hottie!
No, no! It's amazing!
[IRINA]
Really?
Then might I recommend the
persimmon-loquat gelatin?
The texture is as
soft as my skin!
[RYUKI]
Yes, ma'am!
And why stop there?
Try the whole menu!
It would make me so very happy.
[RYUKI chuckles]
I need more cash.
There's an ATM at the station.
You can pull out all
the cash you need.
[RYUKI]
Be right back!
[IRINA]
Okay! I'll be waiting!
[NAGISA] Not ideal,
but I guess it's a start.
Yada's at the bottom of the
mountain drawing in customers.
And Professor Bitch
is at the top.
That's a sharp
combo right there.
[KORO-SENSEI]
With Sugaya's beautiful signage,
Okajima's superb
food photography,
Hazama's mouth-watering
menu descriptions,
and Mimura's sleek
website design,
we have everything we need to
pique our customer's interest!
Remember, it's only day one.
The battle is just
getting started.
[ITONA]
If my recon is correct,
A-Class is better at
pulling in customers.
[POP IDOL A] Welcome to our
school festival debut!
[GIRL A]
Oh!
Hey Asano!
Hello, glad you could come.
Now you ladies enjoy yourselves.
We have events every
hour on the hour.
My idol singer friends
and some comedians I know
are performing for free.
The cover charge includes
unlimited food and drinks.
When whatever's playing on
one side of the stage ends,
the next show begins
immediately on the flip side.
The entrance fee is only good
for half the performance space,
so people will
keep going around,
shelling out their hard-earned
cash for each new act.
Before long, their
stomachs'll be full,
and E-Class high and dry.
Right, gentlemen. Let's do this.
I'll start hammering
out a few power riffs.
You guys get ready.
[AUDIENCE chattering]
[AUDIENCE cheers]
No, seriously.
Is there anything he can't do?
[ARAKI]
I know!
To be honest,  it's rather
disgusting how good he is.
[ARAKI] He's good.
But remember:
he's not infallible.
Well he sure isn't going
to lose to E-Class,
I guarantee you that!
That'd be a nice change of pace.
I'm sick of seeing our
leader get his butt kicked
by those friggin' nobodies.
He's not the only Chosen
One at this school.
I mean, after all,
we learned our instruments
between study sessions, too.
Whaddya say we get out
there and back him up?
[SEO]
Yeah!
[CUSTOMER A]
This, please.
[SAKURA]
Ah-ha! There you are, Nagisa!
Look who I've got in tow!
Hey, Sakura!
You brought Mr. Matsukata
and the gang!
Aw, that's sweet,
Nagisa you kept in touch.
Yeah.
I help her study sometimes.
I had to show up!
When your personal tutor asks
you to try out their restaurant,
you really don't have a choice.
Good business strategy.
With this bunch, we'll make
bank on volume alone!
Sorry we don't have deeper
pockets, but we're here.
[slurping]
Oh, my now!
Now this is superb!
Something so tasty is bound
to sell out before long.
[NAGISA] It's been kind
of a struggle, actually.
Cooking it is one thing, getting
the word out there is another.
Really?
I wouldn't worry
too much, though.
You guys have like this
mysterious power, y'know?
Of course.
Keep doing what you do
and word'll get out.
Let your customer base find you.
[SAKURA]
Thanks again!
[CHILDREN]
Bye!
[MATSUKATA]
Come along now, Sakura.
[NAGISA]
Huh.
Keep doing what we do
and word'll get out.
It'd be great if people
started talking.
We just have to be patient.
I'm just gonna come
out and say it.
I, uh, heard all about your mom.
And why your hair's long.
I'm sorry I teased you so much.
Honestly, I never meant to
hurt your feelings, Nagisa.
No, no. We're all good.
I can take a little ribbing from
you and Karma. It's no big deal.
Oh, good.
But I'll go a little easier
on you from here on out.
[YUJI]
Wassup?
[NAGISA]
Oh crap, I know that voice!
Nagisa! Long time no see!
No! No! Not Yuji!
We know him?
Oh, wait.
That guy from Summer vacation!
The one who thought
you were a chick
and totally had a thing for you!
How... how'd you find out
where I went to school?
It was easy,
I just looked up the
island's guest registry.
Uh, I've been kinda
stalking you online
and I saw the big
Autumn Festival.
[NAKAMURA humming]
[NAGISA]
Um, okay.
Hey Nakamura!
What the--? Stop!
[NAGISA growls]
Okay, I promise this
is the last time for real.
We just had a conversation
about this!
The kid is loaded, isn't he?
So, c'mon, don't be shy,
we have to raise our customer
average any way we can.
[NAGISA grunts]
Take one for
the team, Nagisa!
Like it or not, the fate
of this enterprise rests
on your skills as a hostess!
[NAGISA yelps]
[YUJI] Man, did I pick the
right time to come or what?
Pretty lucky I got you
as a waitress, huh?
Yeah. Great spot, too.
Thanks for bringin' me here.
I'm lovin' the privacy!
[NAGISA]
And I'm lovin' that fact
that no one else can see us.
Huh?
[slurping]
[NAGISA]
Cue cards? Really?
So, um, you know what I want?
I, uh, "want you to eat
all of my favorites."
Sure thing, babe!
Just ask and I'll get
everything on the menu!
[NAKAMURA laughs]
This idiot's a total goldmine.
And a big eater.
Rake in the cash, Nagisa!
Did I tell you I stopped smokin'
those sketchy cigarettes?
You were so worried about me,
it got me thinkin'.
[NAGISA]
Ah....
Here we go.
[YUJI]
Oh! This looks amazing!
Lemme get a pic!
[NAGISA]
I feel bad about it,
but if I don't keep it up
things'll get more awkward
than they already are.
[NAGISA] Okay, that is
definitely crossing a line!
[RED EYE] Hey! Brought
you a gift, Karasuma.
[NAGISA]
Uh!
[RED EYE] The colors up
here are breathtaking.
I heard some rumors that
the Reaper took you out.
He tried, it was rough
there for a while.
But hey, I aint
no spring chicken.
[KARASUMA] I'm gonna need
you to conceal that gun.
Who the heck is that?
And is he packing?
Want me to call the police?
Whoa! Whoa!
It's okay, uh...
We know this guy.
He's...
"Mr. Yoshioka from
the local hunt club."
Yoshioka?
What kind of name is
that for a foreigner?
[NAGISA]
Oh, he changed his name.
Big anime fan.
Oh. Guess that makes sense.
Uh.
Well enough about this Yoshioka
dude, or whatever.
Nagisa. Can...
Can I...
Like...
Ask you what you think--
[screams]
[NAGISA sighs]
Lovro.
The Octopus extended invitation.
Yes, of course.
I'm just glad to see
you're still alive.
Your protégée's been worried,
you should talk to her.
[LOVRO]
Indeed.
Wha... what's with
the creepy old dude?
He step out of a horror movie?
He's Mr. Mild Yagyu.
He's kind of a big deal on
the Asakusa theatre scene.
That guy's a comedian?!
He and Mr. K were talking
about a, uh, a bit!
Yeah. His protégée used
to be on the circuit,
but retired and
became a teacher.
[YUJI]
Mm-hm...
[GASTRO]
Ooo-hoo!
My gun's never tasted so good!
Oh wow!
I wouldn't turn down a bowl of
this stuff if it were poisoned.
Fellow comedians from Asakusa!
Ha, ha!
The one eating wasabi
Mont Blac is building up
his tolerance for an
extreme-eating sketch!
What can I tell you, huh?
We get to know all
sorts of people.
Give it a rest.
Huh?
I can tell you're lying.
My old man's a big
name in the industry.
I've been seeing
burnouts and wannabe's
suck up to him since
I was a little kid.
I know a front when I see one.
I can spot phonies
from a mile away.
The girl I met on the island?
Let's just say a fake
smile doesn't suit her.
You got me there.
Some talent, Yuji.
If you wanna use that word.
Not a lot of good about
the baggage you take
from a skeevy childhood.
Look, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to lie to you.
It's not your fault.
I've essentially
looked like this
ever since I was a little boy.
It's kind of a pain.
"Little boy"?
[NAGISA]
Lately,
I've learned that even a
talent you're ashamed of
can be a source of confidence
if you used it to
help someone else.
So I'm starting to make peace
with how girlie I look.
I'm a guy.
Is the point I'm trying
to get across here.
Well that's another lie.
[NAGISA]
No.
Well that's another lie.
[NAGISA]
It's not. I promise.
[NAKAMURA]
Show him the goods already!
[NAGISA]
What?!
Look at me and say this
is the face of a liar.
This is for real...?
[NAGISA] From the right angle,
our flaws can be weapons.
If I've learned nothing else
from this classroom, it's that.
It's what we do.
It's how this café
came together.
It's what brought
everyone here today,
what made us a part of
so many peoples' lives.
This may sound weird, but, the
thrill is out of this world!
Hey! Hold on!
I'm sorry I tricked you!
Here, I'll give you
your money back!
[YUJI]
Whatever. I just...
I feel like a total
idiot is all.
Peace out.
What? Aw, why's he leaving?
I was gonna see what
he'd be willing to pay
for a cosplay shoot!
Exactly how much money d'you
expect to make off me?!
[NAGISA]
Sorry, Yuji.
Bad move on my part.
[HINANO] Well, I suppose our
first day went sort of okay.
[MIMURA] They posted
the sales report earlier.
Honestly at this
rate we don't have
a snowball's chance in hell
of catching up to A-Class.
Uh?
[REPORTER A]
Pick up the pace!
We'll miss the morning
broadcast!
[STUDENTS]
Wha...?
Is that a TV crew?
I don't get it,
what're they covering?
The only thing up there's
the E-Class building.
[MAEHARA, MIMURA]
What the hell?!
Look you guys!
Somebody posted an online review
that's spreading like wildfire!
I did a little digging to try
and track down the source,
and you'll never believe this.
It's by Yuji Norita!
Who happens to be,
wait for it, the biggest name
in the food blogosphere!
[FUWA]
Since he grew up rich,
he's tried everything
from caviar to crocodile,
so the boy's palate, annoyingly
enough, is highly developed.
He's got a money-is-no-object,
I'll-try-anything approach.
People love it!
Okay, then.
[YUJI] Of all the places
to find great food,
you wouldn't think a school
festival would be one of them.
But let me tell you: this place
was "out of this world."
The menu changed
my whole outlook.
Sustainable, organic.
They've turned a poor location
into a big advantage.
"From the right angle,
our flaws can be weapons."
Those words come from a buddy
of mine who works there.
When I heard them,
I thought to myself: wow.
I've been so spoiled
all my life.
Living in the shadow
of my big-shot dad.
The privilege I've grown up in?
That's my weapon.
I can use it to help people.
Which is exactly what I'm
trying to do with this blog.
Trust me.
You've only got one more day,
so cut a beeline up
that mountain now.
You won't be disappointed.
Taste it while you can and
it'll change your life!
[NAGISA] After that,
we ran ourselves ragged.
With every new order,
we foraged.
Cooked.
Served.
And sold.
Just about everybody
we knew showed up.
People from school.
People from other places.
Everybody.
Uh-oh, guys!
This isn't good!
We're almost out
of acorn noodles!
We sold a heck of a lot more
than I thought we would.
Doesn't change the
fact that A-Class
will have made
more revenue.
[SUMIRE]
It's okay,
the side menu have been
selling like crazy, too.
I say in the time
we've got left,
we should just stick with them.
We can go a little deeper
into the forest if we need.
Pad our ingredient reserves?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Hm...
[HINANO, NAGISA]
Huh?
[KORO-SENSEI] No, I think
it best to stop here.
But, sir, if we do
that we won't win.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Perfectly all right.
Any more foraging and we
run the risk of upsetting
the mountain's
delicate ecosystem.
[HINANO]
Hm....
[KORO-SENSEI]
We're all interconnected.
Every action resonates
through the web of life.
Can you feel it,
boys and girls?
The intricate bonds
of shared fate,
of lives that have been touched?
People who've taught you.
People you've helped.
People who've caused
you trouble.
People you've caused
trouble for,
unlikely friendships,
bitter rivalries.
We're all part of one another!
Ah-ha.
So today was just
another lesson all along.
Aw, man, I really wanted
to win this thing.
[TOKA sighs]
Oh, I'm very sorry.
We're all sold out-- [gasps]
[HIROMI]
Really? Well, you are popular.
Uh!
Mom.
[NAGISA] Here you go: our last
crimson-glory-vine juice.
It's good.
[HIROMI]
Thank you.
I have to say, this class
is really something.
I can see why you're
passionate about staying.
Yep.
So, uh, about all
the unpleasantness
the other evening...
Looking back at it now, I knew.
My boy's grown up.
He's ready to cut
the apron strings.
That business about
graduating from me,
you meant every word.
I don't know where you found
the strength to say it,
but somewhere along
the way, you got tough.
Just, please, for right now,
stay with me a little longer,
till you're of age.
That's all I'm asking.
The world'll be
yours soon enough.
I'm not ready to let go of
my baby just yet, Nagisa.
Whatever else I may be,
I'm still your mother.
[KORO-SENSEI] Every connection
we encounter in this world
teaches us a little something
about ourselves.
So please,
as a friend, let me give
you a proper birthday.
[KORO-SENSEI]
The connection we had.
Am I doing right by
what it taught me?
[KARASUMA]
Hey.
[KORO-SENSEI]
You?
[KARASUMA] Nagisa's mother
just apologized to me.
Apparently she tried
to start a fire?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Oh, that.
Water under the bridge.
Good enough.
Now maybe you can explain
what she whispered in my ear.
She promised she would
keep my toupee a secret!
What does that mean?!
[whistles]
[yelps]
[STUDENT A]
A-Class is amazing!
They even beat out
the high-schoolers!
[STUDENT B]
Well, it is Asano.
[STUDENT C]
Yeah, but check out E-Class!
They managed to come in third,
and that's after shutting down
halfway through the second day!
If you ask me, that's an
even bigger accomplishment.
So did you actually visit?
After all the hype they
were getting on TV?
How could I not?
I don't get it, man.
I thought bein' in Class E was
supposed to be punishment.
But, they're all like doing
really well for themselves.
I'm actually a little
bit jealous.