[KORO-SENSEI]
Phew!
Talk about Helter Swelter,
am I right, boys and girls?
Quite a heat wave we've got!
Yeah.
Hey, so why are we hiking
down the mountain again?
To swim, maybe? The main
campus has a pool.
In the opposite direction.
Yeah.
[KARMA]
Hey, Nagisa.
I heard you were a real
badass the other day.
Sorry I wasn't around. I'd have
loved to see the guy's face.
[NAGISA]
He means my "assassination"
of Coach Takaeko.
Which was cool, sure.
But it's relatively easy to take
a normal person by surprise.
Besides, we're down to the wire,
and it's still anybody's guess
how we're going to
assassinate him.
[KORO-SENSEI chuckling]
[KORO-SENSEI] All right, class.
Feast your eyes on this.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Your very own swimming hole,
compliments of moi!
[STUDENTS]
Woohoo!
[NAGISA] It's weird when
he does stuff like this.
It makes him awesome,
and, honestly,
hard to wanna kill.
[sighs] Not to be ungrateful,
but this is kinda sad.
First of all, I can't even
swim, and second of all,
this bathing suit makes
me feel self-conscious.
[OKAJIMA] You got nothin'
to worry about, babe.
Take my word for it. Plenty
of people go for your body type.
Gee, thanks.
And plenty of people
wouldn't find it creepy
that you're using
a long-range lens.
[NAKAMURA]
Nagisa? Oh, snap.
You're really a dude!
You didn't know that?
[OKANO]
We had our doubts.
[whistle blowing]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Kimura!
Absolutely no running
around the edge of the pool!
That's how accidents happen!
[KIMURA]
Oh, sorry.
[whistle blows]
[KORO-SENSEI] What do
think you two are doing?!
Absolutely no holding
your breath underwater!
How am I supposed to tell the
difference between horseplay
and drowning?
Absolutely no sneaking pictures!
Put down that book and enjoy
the water, for heaven's sake!
[whistle blowing]
[SUGINO]
Wow. What a pain.
[NAKAMURA]
Huh.
I guess being a lifeguard really
goes to some people's heads.
Brings out their inner
Type-A personality.
[KIMURA]
No kidding.
Someone tell him he needs
to dial it back a notch.
[KORO-SENSEI chuckling]
[KORO-SENSEI] I've gone
through a great deal of trouble
making sure this
pool is in harmony
with its natural surroundings.
Proper enjoyment of it must
be disciplined and orderly.
[HINANO] Aw, c'mon! Don't be
such a stick in the mud!
You need to loosen up!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Eek!
[HINANO]
Uhh...
[NAKAMURA] Um, did he just
scream like a chick?
[KORO-SENSEI giggles]
[KORO-SENSEI yelps]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Karma, what are you doing?
Stop it! I'll fall in!
Are you listening to me?
I said stop! Please!
[MAEHARA]
Whoa.
[ISOGAI]
Are you okay?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Don't read too much into it.
I just don't feel like taking
a dip at the moment, that's all.
It's certainly not as though
water causes my fingers
to swell up or anything.
[NAGISA]
Wait a sec.
He can't swim!
Interesting. This might be his
most promising weakness yet.
If you were never intending
to get in the pool,
why even bother bringing
that kickboard along?
[KORO SENSEI]
This? This isn't a kickboard!
It's my afternoon snack!
[MIMURA]
Naturally.
[TERASAKA]
Hmph.
[TERASAKA] Excuse me? You're
happy your grades are up?
No, say that again! Don't
think I heard you right!
C'mon, these are the highest
scores I've ever got.
It's 'cause of the octopus
and the "Right Before
the Practice Exam
Afterschool Slithery
Study Session" thing.
Whoa, whoa.
You sayin' you actually
showed up for that crap?!
Yeah.
The three of us agreed no
slithery anything, remember?!
But that's the thing!
It wasn't all bad, in fact,
it really helped me out.
[TERASAKA]
Are you kidding me?!
Fine, care about your grades if
that gets you off, you traitor.
[TERASAKA]
Fantastic.
Now Muramatsu's fallen for
that "you can do it" B.S.
Am I the only one
with half a brain?
[YOSHIDA]
That is awesome!
Holy crap, you even got
the flair sides right!
The hell you so stoked about?
Oh. Hey, Terasaka.
So, you know how
we always thought
I was the only one here
into bikes and stuff?
Well, turns out Koro-sensei
knows as much as I do about 'em.
[KORO-SENSEI]
I may be an adult,
but I'll never outgrow
the need for speed.
I've dabbled in manly hobbies
like this for years.
Did you know this
particular model
can reach up to 300
kilometers per hour?
What I wouldn't
give to burn rubber
on the genuine article someday.
Are you kidding?
You could get this puppy to
Mach 20 without pumpin' the gas!
[STUDENTS laughing]
[growls]
[KORO-SENSEI yelps, screams]
Come on dude, what the
hell is wrong with you?
Apologize immediately!
Koro-sensei worked very hard on
that to showcase his manliness
and you've just
reduced him to tears!
[MEG, MIMURA, FUWA]
Yeah, what she said!
[TERASAKA]
You're talkin' to me
and all I hear is a swarm
of freakin' locusts.
I think it's time for
some pest control!
--[KIRARA] Hey! What the--?
--[OKAJIMA] Is that a bug bomb?
[KORO SENSEI]
That does it!
I enjoy a good prank as
much as the next--
Get those disgusting
things the hell off.
You're a monster, you hear me?
A freak of nature!
Anyone who falls for your
nice-guy act is stupid!
That's right!
I don't know what's got
your jock in a tangle today,
but if he's such a monster,
why not man-up and kill him?
I mean, last I checked that is
what we're supposed to do here.
You aimin' to start something
with me, tough guy?
'Cause I wanted to bash
your stupid head in
since the moment you w--
A little advice. You got
this backwards.
You gotta bash my head in
before you can run your mouth.
[TERASAKA]
Let go of me!
You're all a bunch of freaks!
Wow. What crawled up his butt?
I dunno, maybe he just
does it for the attention.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Hmm.
[TERASAKA]
Earth on the brink.
Students training
to be assassins
like we're in some kinda
self-improvement camp.
Give me one good reason why
I should care about any of this.
I'm not gonna just smile and
fall in line with the herd.
I do things my way.
[SHIRO]
Nicely done.
Here. You've earned it.
Phase One of my
plan is complete.
[TERASAKA] Now these guys
have the right idea.
[SHIRO] The octopus has
an excellent sense of smell.
Hence why we dare not
lay the groundwork
for Itona's return ourselves.
Had he picked up even
a trace of our scent,
the game would've been spoiled.
I sympathize with your feelings
on the matter, Ryoma
Terasaka, believe me.
And I advise you to relax.
You have but to follow
my plan to the letter.
The freak of nature
will be dead,
and E Class restored to
its former insignificance.
[TERASAKA]
Hm?
I know you.
You're weaker than the
red-headed one by far.
Your physique says
otherwise, but I see.
Those eyes are a dead giveaway.
You have sight, but no vision.
The only thing you see is
the path of least resistance.
The wolf has eyes for prey.
The cow has eyes for hay.
One of them's a killer,
the other his buffet.
What the hell is that
supposed to mean--?!
[SHIRO]
There, there.
Calm yourself. We're
counting on you tomorrow.
[TERASAKA grunts]
[KORO-SENSEI sniffling]
Okay, could you please stop?
This crying business
is ridiculous.
[KORO-SENSEI]
'Scuse me.
For your information,
these are my nostrils.
I'm not crying,
my nose is running.
[IRINA] How am I
supposed to know that?!
[KORO-SENSEI]
For some reason,
my sinuses have been
running amok since yesterday.
Terasaka, thank heaven!
I had this awful feeling you
abandoned our class for good!
[TERASAKA growls]
[SHIRO] The so-called "bug bomb"
you set off in class was in fact
a canister of concentrated,
pollen-like allergens,
specially designed to
blunt our foe's senses.
Now we move to Phase Two.
So, octopus.
I think it's time we
stopped messin' around
and killed you for real.
Come by the pool after class.
We all know you're big weakness
is water, don't we now?
Hey, 's all right.
You guys can come, too!
You can watch while
I shove him in!
You can even help me out!
Where's this coming from?
You always make fun
of our attempts
and now you expect us
to be on board with yours?
Dude, you pride yourself on
having the worst attitude
in this class.
Give me one good reason why
any of us should help you.
Ha. Whatever.
Suit yourself, man.
I didn't want to share
the prize money
with you dead-asses anyway.
The hell is his deal
all of a sudden?
The guy's mood swings
are too much for me.
Exactly. Count me out.
Yeah, me too.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Let's all go! It'll be fun!
What the--? His snot's hardening
and locking us to the floor!
[KORO-SENSEI] Terasaka's
finally showing some initiative.
We have to be supportive!
I realize he's been rather
difficult in the past,
but this is everyone's chance
to kill and make up!
[KIMURA]
Why are you so gross?
[NAGISA]
Terasaka, hold up!
[TERASAKA]
Huh?
Are you for real
about this, or what?
You tell me, man. Does it
look like I'm joking?
I'm just sayin'.
If you've got a plan,
let the rest of us in
on it and we might be able--
Shut up!
Damn! You people make
me sick, you know that?
Always huddling together,
terrified to make
a move on your own.
I ain't like the rest
of you, I have vision!
A wolf's got eyes for prey,
a cow's got eyes for hay!
[NAGISA] All right, then.
Guess he knows what he's doing.
Still, it seems like he's
more confident in his plan
than in himself.
I mean, "the wolf's got
eyes for prey"? Seriously?
No way he came up
with that on his own.
[TERASAKA]
Yeah, there we go!
Everybody stay spread out
like that! Nice and far apart!
Yeah, we get it. Thanks.
I'm not so sure about
this plan of yours.
It's highly unlikely we'll get
Koro-sensei in the water--
How unlikely is it that
I get you in the water
--against your will?
--[TAKEBAYASHI yelps]
Look at 'im. We cooperate
and the jerk goes power mad.
Yeah. Sorta reminds
me of the way
he used to push people
around back in Second Year.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Ah-ha.
So I assume the idea is
to push me in the water
and have everyone converge
on me with their knives?
Have you worked out how
to actually push me in?
It's only good sportsmanship
to tell you
that fancy pistol of
yours won't do the trick.
[SHIRO]
This is not a gun,
but rather a special transmitter
that will alert us to when
all the pieces are in place.
Once your classmates are in
position, pull the trigger.
We'll take it from there.
Best say your prayers,
monster. This is it.
[KORO-SENSEI]
I'm ready when you are.
My sinuses have
even been cleared.
For the record I've always
hated you with a passion.
I couldn't wait for you
to up and disappear.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Oh, I'm well aware.
Methinks we should have
a little sit-down after this.
Talk out our differences.
[TERASAKA] This'll wipe
that smile off his face.
Itona, you're up!
[STUDENTS screaming]
[TERASAKA]
What?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Uh! Children!
[ISOGAI]
Help!
[SHIRO] Surely you can't just
leave these poor young people
to drown, can you?
What the hell, man?
They never told me.
They never told me about this.
[STUDENTS screaming]
[KORO-SENSEI]
There's a waterfall up ahead.
If they go over it,
they're doomed!
[SHIRO] He can't rescue
them without getting wet.
and by the time
he saves them all,
his fingers will be swollen.
Normally he'd use his mucus
as a protective barrier
against water.
[SHIRO]
Normally, yes.
In fact, his mucus
can gelatinize water,
modifying the
permeation pressure.
But alas, his mucus
stores have run dry.
[KARMA]
This can't be good.
[TERASAKA]
I-I didn't do it.
This wasn't part of the deal.
Itona was just s'pposed to help
me push him in, that was all.
You never had a plan, did you?
Just let yourself be strung
along by someone else.
A pawn in a game you
don't know the rules to.
Uh! Listen to me, damn
it! It's not my fault!
Come on, you know I'd never
sign up for something like this!
I-I was played for an idiot!
I'm not the one who
swept them all away!
Hey idiot, the only person who
got swept away here is you.
You've got two choices:
keep making excuses
to cover your ass,
or find a way to fix this.
[YOSHIDA yelps]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Last one! Thank goodness!
[KORO-SENSEI yelps]
[SHIRO] Lovely to see you
again, Koro-sensei.
Ordinary water is bad
enough, isn't it?
Worse still is water treated
with a chemical agent
designed to slow you down.
Your own student saw to it
that things went swimmingly.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Itona.
How's it goin', brother?
I believe you an' me are slated
for a friendly little rematch.
[TERASAKA] I always thought
of myself as strong.
I singled out the wimps and made
sure to put 'em under my thumb.
Great way to feel like a boss.
But at this school,
none of the usual tricks
landed worth a damn.
[TERASAKA]
Yo, let's ditch next period
and hit up the
convenience store?
Yeah, no.
I'm sorry, man. I've gotta
study up for my English exam.
Lighten up. Skipping one class
ain't gonna matter that much.
[STUDENT A] Does the ape not
wanna play hooky by himself?
What?
[TERASAKA]
Here, no one ever caved.
No one respected me.
You need to get with
the times, bro.
The alpha male crap might've
worked in middle school,
but it's a different story now.
Once you're pushed to
E Class, you're nothing.
And nobody's as scared
of you as they are of that.
[KOYAMA] Your grades have been
in a downward spiral all year.
One of these days, you're
in for a rude awakening.
People like me will be throwing
rocks at people like you.
[TERASAKA] That's when
the reality of it hit me.
When I realized my tough-guy act
was a joke to these people.
I was through. No one would
ever take me seriously again.
All the dweebs and jerk-offs
I used to push around
would grow up to be big shots.
They'd run the show,
and shiftless dumbasses like me
would be under their thumb.
When I first got put
into E Class, I figured,
"Hey, no prob, Everyone's
the same as me.
I can afford not to care."
But then he showed up.
Out of nowhere,
things changed again.
Suddenly we had
a goal, a purpose.
And now here I am.
A lazy, good-for-nothin'
chump with no future,
caught up in someone
else's master plan.
Dammit!
[KORO-SENSEI]
He's fast!
And rather stronger
than I recall.
[SHIRO] We reduced
the number of tentacles,
focusing the speed and
power in those remaining.
Now even a simple child
can master them.
[KORO-SENSEI yelping]
[OKAJIMA]
This is unreal!
That's maybe a foot of water.
Can it seriously throw
him off that much?
The water ain't
his only problem.
You've got some nerve!
Look, he just saved
you from drowning.
He can't go all out
'cause he's spent.
And his attention's
still divided.
[OKAJIMA]
Oh, no!
That branch can't support
Hara's weight! She's gonna fall!
[OKUDA]
He can't focus on the fight
because he's too
worried about them!
[TERASAKA] 'Specially her.
That fatty'll be toast soon.
[NAGISA]
We have to help!
[OKUDA]
How?
Wait, hold on a sec. This
wasn't even your plan, was it?
You got roped into this.
[TERASAKA]
Hmph.
Like a head of cattle, but
hey, that's what happens
when you got sight
and no vision.
Some smartass wolf comes
along and, before you know it,
you're on the menu.
Thing is, though.
If I'm gonna be played,
I pick the tune.
I've had it up to here
with these jerks,
and the idea of them
gettin' the prize money?
Don't get me started.
You're a smart dude, Karma.
You be the puppet master,
and I'll be the puppet.
[KARMA]
Hm?
Come up with
something awesome.
If you"re the brains, then I'm
the brawn, you got it?
Give me a plan and I'll
save every one of 'em,
fatty and the monster included!
I don't know. Sure you
want to be my lackey?
I'm pretty devious.
[TERASAKA]
Huh?
You might get killed.
Ooh, big deal.
Devious I can handle, just make
sure you've got a vision.
[SHIRO] Now, Itona.
Strike the killing blow.
What's up?
[SHIRO]
Can I help you?
So, bet you jerks think
you played me pretty good.
[SHIRO]
Does that wound your ego?
There's something to be said
for being the perfect
foil, my friend.
Or are you suddenly upset
we endangered the classmates
you care nothing for?
Laugh it up, man.
Payback's about
to be real bitch.
Itona! You an' me,
one-on-one, right now!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Don't be ridiculous, Terasaka!
He'll throttle you!
I wasn't talkin'
to you, Tentacles!
[SHIRO chuckles]
[SHIRO]
He's tapped into his inner hero.
Shut him down, Itona. For good.
What've you done?
No worries.
They're not gonna
to kill a student.
We're too valuable alive.
As long as we're in danger,
Koro-sensei can't
concentrate on the fight.
Even Hara isn't that bad off.
If she falls, either he or
Itona is bound to catch her.
It may look like he's
in over his head,
but Terasaka knows
exactly what to expect.
Tentacle Boy will try
to knock him unconscious,
but if he grabs on and
rides it out, we're good.
[SHIRO] That's an impressive
grip you've got there.
Let us see if it holds up
under another lashing.
[ITONA]
Uh.
[sneezes]
[grunts]
That's yesterday's shirt.
The one he had on when
he bug-bombed the class.
Unless he did
laundry last night,
there's still some residue on it
from whatever weird
chemical was in that can.
I figure if it affected
Koro-sensei, it'll effect Itona.
And there you go.
Now Tentacle Boy's distracted
and the Octopus has
a chance to rescue Hara.
You gotta love a good plan.
Yoshida! Muramatsu!
Give us a nice big splash, okay?
He's out of his mind.
I like it.
Logically, the two of them
have the exact same weaknesses.
Easy, turn the kid's own
tactics against him, and voila.
[gasps]
[STUDENTS yelling]
Well, that escalated quickly.
Looks like you've got a problem
with water retention there, pal.
[growling]
All right, here's the deal.
We're not okay with you
hogging all the prize money,
or with the fact that
your plan revolved around
putting our lives on the line.
Slapping one of our own around
doesn't sit well either.
So if you wanna keep at this,
you're going to have
to face all of us.
[grunting]
[SHIRO]
Well played, children.
We withdraw.
The slaughter of innocents
was never our intention.
Who can predict how his
anti-matter organs would react?
Come along, Itona.
[growls]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Ah!
Wasn't that a fun way to while
away the afternoon, class?
And there's always
room for one more.
[SHIRO]
Itona.
[sighs] I thought we'd never
get rid of those two.
We saved your bacon, didn't we?
It's a good thing we're quick on
our feet or you'd been a goner.
[KORO-SENSEI chuckles]
[KORO-SENSEI]
That's adorable.
I still had a few tricks up
my sleeve, just so you know.
Hey, Terasaka.
In case you're wondering,
I heard your cracks
about my weight.
We "fatties" prefer
the termc "full-figured."
Oh, uh. Didn't mean
to be a dick!
Just sizing up the situation
all objective-like.
Sizing it up?
I may be on the hefty side,
but I can still kick your ass!
Wow. Awkward. A little tact
goes a long way, man.
You should try it next time.
Kinda hard to run
from the wolves
with your foot in your
mouth, just sayin'.
Why don't you get
down off your perch
and say that to my face,
you little turd bucket!
How 'bout that?!
[KARMA]
Hey!
I'm s'posed to be your
puppet master, remember?
Don't even go there! That was
a temporary arrangement
and you're not the one who
took a tentacle to the gut!
That's right! I was down
here taking all the hits
'cause you don't have the balls
to do your own dirty work!
True, you sorta kept your
distance the whole time.
Oh, don't like getting
your hands dirty, huh?
We can fix that.
[STUDENTS laughing]
[KORO-SENSEI]
I think we can all agree
Terasaka isn't exactly
cut out to be a mastermind,
but when tasked with putting
someone else's plan into action,
he's invaluable. On the field,
his confidence shines through
and things get done.
It's as simple as that.
No self-respecting assassination
squad should be without him.
[NAGISA]
Definitely.
Terasaka may be hot-headed,
but he belongs here.
I'm glad he's finally
adjusting. We all are.
Trouble is, we're so
caught up in the moment,
we've overlooked something.
Something major, actually.
Koro-sensei's biggest
weakness yet.