[NAGISA] Itona's tried
to kill Koro-sensei
a total of three times.
It took some convincing,
but in the end he finally
joined our class.
And so, about a week later...
[KORO-SENSEI] Well that just
about does it, boys and girls.
See you tomorrow.
Payday today, at long last,
so I'll be treating myself
to some mouthwatering
Shanghai crab.
Yi, er, san, GO!
[MEG]
You could treat us to some.
[MAEHARA sighs]
Is it me or has our
workload gotten crazy hard
now that it's second term?
Yeah, well you can't
exactly blame Koro-sensei
for trying to get our grades up.
Guess not.
It's just that it's been forever
since I picked up a chick.
[chuckles]
[NAGISA] Hey, Itona. Are
you stickin' around? Hm?
What'cha working on there?
What's it look like I'm doing?
I'm building a
remote-control tank.
[NAGISA]
How come?
[ITONA] The Octopus. He made
me cram all day yesterday.
Stressed me out.
[KORO-SENSEI] Focus on the
material, please. Next question.
[ITONA] I'm pissed. So I'm
gonna use this to kill him.
It's like the idiot said.
What's his name? Terasaka.
If I fail a hundred times,
so be it. Who cares?
Only gotta kill the
task master once.
Good way of lookin' at it.
Wow, this stuff, it's,
like, stupid high tech.
[MAEHARA]
I mean, is it even for real?
Kudos.
This puppy's using modified
camera phone parts.
[ISOGAI]
Wow, Itona.
You came up with all
these tweaks yourself?
It's not really a big deal.
I picked up electronics
workin' for my old man.
Anybody could do this
stuff. Except Terasaka.
[TERASAKA grunts]
[NAGISA]
What a change.
Compared to how he was when
he had tentacles, I mean.
Still has a sharp
tongue, though.
[STUDENTS gasping, chuckling]
[STUDENTS]
Wow.
Are you kidding me?
That thing barely
even makes a sound.
When it moves or when it shoots.
I used electrical parts
instead of gears.
Noise cancellation is paramount.
[MURAMATSU whistles]
[ITONA] The camera feed is
linked to the controller.
I've got it lined up with
the sights on the main gun.
Wow. Cloak and dagger!
Okay, suppose you
could sneak up on him.
Where're you gonna aim?
[ITONA]
Where else? That's right.
I'll let you guys in on
a little secret, you see.
Koro-sensei has a
single weak spot.
[NAGISA]
This is news to me.
[ITONA]
His heart.
It's located directly
behind that necktie.
If we hit it, we can take
him out in one shot.
[KORO-SENSEI chuckling]
[KORO-SENSEI]
No doubt he's telling the others
about my heart this very moment.
Clever child that he is.
Assassination promises
to be a good deal more fun
now that Itona's
thrown into the mix.
I'm thinking this could work.
Yeah. All right.
Let's give 'er a test drive.
Get a feel for how she handles.
It is better to test it now than
watch it break when we need it.
[OKAJIMA]
Let's make it happen!
[NAKAMURA]
See ya later, Professor Bitch.
[TOKA]
Bye! Have a good one!
[IRINA] Straight home, ladies.
No detours, understood?
[HINANO]
Yes, ma'am.
Cool. Snack run?
[HINANO]
Um, yeah!
[TOKA]
Wait. Didn't you just say--?
Do ya see anything?
Not a lot. Ugh, this
camera totally sucks.
Its field of vision
is way too narrow!
So? It's not the
end of the world.
We'll fit it with a bigger one.
But that would increase the
weight, compromise mobility.
Target acquisition
would be more difficult.
[TAKEBAYASHI]
In that case.
We'll just install
a fisheye lens
on the camera we already have.
[OKAJIMA, MAEHARA]
Takebayashi!
[TAKEBAYASHI]
If we write a program
that can correct image
distortion in the data feed,
even a relatively small lens can
give us a wide field of view.
That's good.
Right. Fisheye lens
with a big viewing angle.
I've got it taken care of.
[TAKEBAYASHI]
Ritsu.
Hello!
[TAKEBAYASHI] Can you build an
image correction program for us?
Of course!
I have no idea what you're using
it for, but I'm on the job!
Takebayashi, you're a genius.
[TAKEBAYASHI chuckles]
[MAEHARA]
We need to be able to record.
[OKAJIMA] Absolutely.
We'll wanna analyze the upgrades
as effectively as we can.
[NAGISA] Weren't we all just put
off by an underwear thief?
[MAEHARA]
In the name of assassination,
onward--! Uh, Prototype Zero!
[STUDENTS grunt]
[KIMURA]
I'll flip it over!
Yeah, sure. Thanks, man!
There's not much in the way of
a suspension system, apparently.
[YOSHIDA]
Leave it to me.
I know a thing or two about
drive mechanics and metalwork.
[OKAJIMA] Doesn't the
paint job on the chassis
stand out like a sore thumb?
[TAKEBAYASHI]
That's combat camouflage.
Unless we want our target seeing
the tank from a mile away,
we need it to blend in
with the school.
[SUGAYA]
I got this.
Classroom camouflage.
Consider it done.
[MAEHARA] We should chart out
the territory at RC scale.
In the name of
better maneuvering...
...I'll draw us a detailed map.
[ISOGAI]
They, uh,
really get into it when
smut's on the line, huh?
[NAGISA]
It's kinda creepy.
[YOSHIDA]
S'up?
Transmission's ready.
I finished it last night.
[MURAMATSU]
Oh.
And I made us all breakfast.
[SUGAYA]
Hey. Think it'll stand out now?
[ALL gasp]
This is great and all,
guys, but, uh,
you do get that this is for an
assassination plan, right?
Yeah, yeah. Whatever you say,
President Poverty. Sure.
Okay! Let's give this
sucker a proper field test
before all the girls show up!
[ALL]
Yeah!
Funny how nobody's tardy
on a day like today.
[TAKEBAYASHI]
Ritsu won't boot up
until precisely
eight o'clock.
You see, I didn't want her
to see what we were doing.
[NAGISA]
Oh. Yeah.
[BOYS chattering]
Step aside! I wanna take a shot!
[NAGISA] Turns out there
was no reason to worry
whether Itona would
fit in with us.
He did better than
most, actually.
[NAGISA]
Smut, killing, making stuff.
Talk about hitting all
the right buttons.
All of a sudden, he was
the center of attention.
Itona. This thing should
have a codename.
Seems only fair it
should come from you.
I'll give it some thought.
[ITONA] The tentacles once
asked me what kind of person
I wanted to be.
I told them I wanted
to be strong.
Soon, that was all
I could think about.
My mind raced with images
of fighting, winning.
[ITONA'S FATHER]
Over time, you can spin
even the weakest material
into good, strong thread.
"Itona" means "becoming thread,"
you know. Remember that.
[ITONA]
How did I forget my roots?
It's in my name.
[MAEHARA]
Aw, dammit! It crashed.
Watch what you're
doin', Terasaka.
[TERASAKA]
Shut up! It's not my fault...
[ITONA]
"Becoming thread."
This is where I'm finally
gonna live up to it.
It's a monster!
--[SUGAYA] Pull out!
--[MAEHARA] No, fire!
[OKAJIMA] Crap! The main
gun's not strong enough!
[MAEHARA] It's okay.
We'll tweak that, too!
[BOYS screaming]
Well, damn. Outdone by a
squirrelly little weasel.
Next time, we need to
designate who's what.
Which means, first off,
we need a gunner. Chiba?
Yeah. Sure.
It's all right. Screw-ups
are a part of the process.
[ITONA] We all agree
Itona One was a dud.
So, we'll just keep spinning
till it's gets stronger.
I might fail a hundred times.
But I'll be sure to kill him
before it's all said and done.
You've got my back, right, guys?
'Course we do!
[NAGISA]
Nothing binds like bloodlust.
I think this is going to be fun!
Okay! Back to the
drawing board, men!
We put our heads together,
this baby'll be lookin'
up skirts by March!
[NAGISA]
When did that become the goal?
Uh, what's all this
I hear about skirts?
Kataoka, it's not
what you think!
We were talking about the kind
of skirts you put on cars!
[OKANO]
Yeah, sure.
[TOKA]
Boys suck.
[MEG] Uh-huh. And who's
big idea was this?
Itona, perhaps you'd
care to tell me?
Okajima.
[OKAJIMA]
What?
Ah! Good morning, everybody!
Oh, hey, Okajima, about
that program you wanted
for correcting fisheye
lens distortion,
I finally have it ready.
Hang on. It wasn't me,
all right? Tell 'em!
Tell 'em what? Don't try to
pull me into this, ya perv.
[OKAJIMA]
You have got to be kidding me!
Guys, we really oughta 'fess up.
Whether you do or don't,
it's clear you're all involved
in this disgusting scheme!
[ALL]
Boys make me wanna puke!
[KARMA]
What's going on in here?
Why don't we just call
it a crime of passion.
[ALL chattering]
So it's true. Boys really do
only think about one thing.
Karma, I'm gonna
ditch class today.
Where's a good spot to go?
Wow, so you can talk. Follow me.
[OKAJIMA, MAEHARA]
Hey! Where you goin'? Hold on!
[NAGISA] Apparently, Itona's a
cooler customer than we thought.
[KAEDE] Huh. So that's what
"Itona" means in kanji.
Well, I think it's awesome!
Yeah!
"Becoming thread." Pretty cool.
It is what it is. Lots of kids
in the class have weird names.
[sighs]
[KAEDE]
Hang on a sec!
"Justice"? I thought your
name was "Masayoshi."
Yeah, if you write
it out in kanji,
but my parents insist
on saying "Justice."
Koro-sensei's just nice
enough to say it my way.
When they called you
at opening ceremonies,
I got nervous hearing
them yell "Justice."
[OKAJIMA]
Yeah, no kidding.
I know. And when they do it
again at closing ceremonies,
it'll be even more
public humiliation.
[NAGISA] Kimura's parents
are both in law enforcement.
Apparently they're very
passionate about the fact
that they're cops.
When I was a kid, I'd complain
about having a weird name,
but mom and dad would
just get all upset at me.
They didn't put a whole lotta
thought into the kind of hell
they were setting me up for
once I started going to school.
You can't expect parents to have
your best interests at heart.
Does a cute name like "Kirara"
go with this face? Seriously?
My name makes me sound
like a sparkly princess.
[KIMURA]
I-I... yeah.
[KIRARA] My mom lives in her
own little fantasy world.
When the least little thing
threatens to break the illusion,
she goes into
full-blown hysterics.
You have any idea what it's lik
growing up in a house like that?
Well it doesn't make living up
to a ridiculously adorable name
any easier.
Getting' saddled
with a weird name?
How do you poor
bastards manage to cope?
[KARMA]
What? Oh, c'mon.
What's not to love about
being named Karma?
Both of my parents have
pretty bizarre taste,
and I guess I inherited
that from 'em.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Come to think of it,
I'm far from satisfied
with my name.
Hang on, I thought you liked
being called Koro-sensei.
Kayano gave you that
name, didn't she?
[KORO-SENSEI] It's because I
like it that I'm not satisfied.
There happen to be two
people in this very room
who refuse to address
me accordingly.
At best, Mr. Karasuma talks
to me using nothing but,
"Hey. Hey, you."
What are we, a
middle-aged couple?
[IRINA]
We're adults.
We don't say things
like "Koro-sensei"
because it makes us
sound like idiots.
Here's a thought.
We could call each other by
specially chosen code names,
couldn't we?
Are you serious?
Yeah!
I mean, codenames are
actually kind of appropriate
for this classroom.
The assassins we met on the
island all had one, remember?
They used them to keep
their real names a secret.
Personally, I think
it made them sound
really polished
and professional.
[KORO-SENSEI] Yes, of course.
That's an excellent idea!
Here's what we'll do, then.
Write down a suggested codename
for each of your classmates
and place them in the box.
We'll call each other by
whatever codenames I draw out.
Sounds like fun, but won't we
have to do separate drawings?
I'm writing down the first
thing that pops in my head.
[KIRARA chuckling]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Also, I should mention this.
For the rest of the day,
real names are forbidden!
[STUDENTS]
What?
[SUGAYA] Baseball Geek.
Come in, Baseball Geek!
Can we confirm that the
target's on the move?
Sorry, Lanky Artist,
that'd be a negative.
Codename Da Densest is still
hiding out there somewhere
in the pine trees.
President Poverty's team
will come up from the rear
and chase him toward the swamp.
When he's out in the open,
Hot-n'-Cold Sniper
will take the shot.
[MAEHARA]
All right. Let's do this!
[KARASUMA]
Congratulations!
You just let your target
slip away from the scene.
Shape up, Womanizing Scumbag!
I told you! Always hold
your gun at firing height!
I'm not letting you get away!
Director Mushroom! Mistress
Kanzaki! Fluffy Stag Beetle!
He's headed your way!
Don't worry, we've got him!
[gasps] He pulled a fast one!
[TERASAKA] Home Plate!
Loofah! Picture-Book Graduate!
I'm on it!
[TERASAKA chuckles]
[TERASAKA] That's right,
keep those eyes on the ground.
[KARASUMA]
Nicely done, Pseudo-Takaoka.
Don't get comfortable!
Scoring a hit on me
doesn't mean anything.
It certainly doesn't mean
you can get him!
Poison Specs! Forever Flat!
If I can see your positions,
I can dodge your shots!
[gasps] He spotted us.
Dignified Didact, take over!
All right!
English Lass, Gender!
You two get a move on!
[BOTH]
Roger, that!
[KARASUMA]
Nice shooting.
They didn't give
away their position.
That has to be thanks to
Dignified Didact's leadership.
Keep your distance back there.
Wait for your chance.
Terminal Perv and This Manga is
Amazing aren't too bad, either.
[ISOGAI] Semi-Senioritis has
blocked the escape route.
It's all on you now,
Dating Sim Emo Character.
[gunshot]
[gasps]
Dating Sim Emo Character!
I told you, a sniper has
to assume his target
is always on high alert!
[RYUNOSUKE] I know, but
the one taking you down...
[RYUNOSUKE]
...is Justice!
[gunshots]
[KORO-SENSEI chuckles]
[KORO-SENSEI]
How'd it go?
Using those codenames
felt pretty great, huh?
[STUDENTS]
Actually, it was kinda painful.
[TOKA]
"Scrunchies and Boobs"? Really?
[OKANO] Try being called
"Amazing Ape" all day.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Ah, yes. Well, I see.
Could someone explain
what "Box o' Moe" means?
Uh, isn't it pretty obvious?
Excuse me, sir?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Yeah?
My codename was just the
same thing as my real one.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Correct.
Because I knew what
you'd be doing in P.E.
Given your agility,
it was all but certain you'd
have a special role to play.
And considering the moves
you showcased out there
this afternoon, I'd say
"Justice" fits perfectly.
You bet it does!
[KIMURA groans]
[KORO-SENSEI] Now, now.
Rest assured, Kimura my boy.
If you don't like it,
requesting a name change
is simply a matter
of filling out the
right paperwork.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
[KORO-SENSEI] You should
bear in mind, however.
If you wind up being the one
to actually assassinate me,
I'm certain people are
going to be quite gracious
about your name.
"Justice indeed," they'll say.
"Why, what else do
you call the man
who saved the entire world, eh?'
Honestly there's very little
significance to the names
our parents give us.
[BOTH chuckle]
[KORO-SENSEI] We don't choose
what we're called,
but we can choose what people
come to associate with it.
Names don't make us who we are.
They're merely part of
what we leave behind
as we walk through life.
Footprints in the sand.
That said, cherish them.
If nothing else,
for their potential.
"Justice," for example.
Why not hold on to that until
after the assassination?
What do you say?
[KIMURA]
Hmm...
Yeah! I think I will.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Now then!
Since everyone got to use
their codename today,
it's only fair that
I divulge my own.
From this point forward,
kindly refer to me as follows:
"Prince of the Fateful
Eternal Wind."
[SUGINO] Why do you get to pick
one that's all fancy-schmancy?
[TOKA] And wipe that
smug look off your face!
[KORO-SENSEI] Aw, c'mon!
Just for one day, then! Please?
[NAGISA]
And for the rest of the day,
Koro-sensei was referred to
by a very different name.
[STUDENTS] "The Octopus of
the Idiotic Perverted Chicken!"
[KORO-SENSEI]
Octopus?!
Well, that was fun.
[NAGISA]
The codename thing was a blast!
Maybe he'll let us
do it again sometime.
Hope so. Right,
Picture-Book Graduate?
Shut your face, Baseball Geek.
[SUGINO chuckles]
Call the burn unit!
My codename doesn't
even make sense.
Yeah! And while we're at it,
who's brilliant idea
was "Forever Flat?"
Like that means anything!
[MURAMATSU whistling]
So it was you.
Well, I'll see you tomorrow.
Hey, I could go for a bowl of
that disgusting ramen. Let's go.
Not cool, man.
He's fittin' in with
Terasaka's group pretty well.
Sure looks like it.
[NAGISA]
And so time marched on,
all of us determined to give
Second Term everything we had.
Of course, being E-Class,
it was more or less a given
that the good times
wouldn't last forever.
[ASANO] Dare I ask how
things are coming along?
Of course, I trust you realize
any response short of
"exceptionally well" would be
unacceptable for A-Class.
[GAKUSHU] Things are
going exceptionally well.
Any student who lags behind
gets left behind. Period.
I have no patience
for slackers.
None. I rule with an iron fist.
And when it comes to midterms,
the bar has been raised.
[ASANO]
That is encouraging.
However, it appears you
are still the subject
of much derision
among the student body.
Letting E-Class get the better
of you in the First Term.
It's not a stain
that washes out.
[GAKUSHU gasps]
[GAKUSHU] Let people say what
they like. I'll crush them!
[ASANO]
Will you now?
At its most basic,
this institution
is divided into two groups:
The weak and the strong.
Which group you belong
to is, on principle,
of no consequence to me.
[ASANO]
That being said,
allow me to offer
you a little guidance.
True leadership requires
an aptitude for winning.
And on top of that...
...to triumph, a leader
must first consider
the where and when,
and the how soon will follow.
Should a loophole
present itself,
it is to be exploited
mercilessly.
[ASANO]
Good word, "aptitude."
Something without which you
haven't a prayer in the world
of besting me, Asano.
[GAKUSHU]
Very well.
Then my aptitude will be on full
display, Mr. Principal, sir.