[MEG] Hey, Nagisa. You figure
out who all's in your group?
My what?
[MEG] It's mine and Isogai's job
to keep track
of who's with who,
so let one of us know.
--[NAGISA] Hm?
--You look confused.
She's talking about
next week's trip.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Of all the--
Who in their right mind
schedules a class trip
this early in the year?!
Unbelievable!
I cannot say that I approve.
Then why are you
dressed like that?!
Geisha? Really?
[OKAJIMA]
It's actually kinda hot!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Guilty as charged.
Yes, all right, I'll admit it.
I'm as excited about
this excursion as you.
[NAGISA] First midterms,
and now a class trip.
We have a pretty full calendar.
I mean, for assassins at least.
[KARASUMA] Everyone's aware
next week is our big,
overnight field trip
to Kyoto, yeah?
Well, not to put
a damper on the fun,
but you're still on the clock.
So, are we supposed to
try to kill him there?
That is the idea.
Kyoto is a very large city,
a lot more cosmopolitan
than this area.
For your safety, you'll be
touring in designated groups.
Koro-sensei will divide
his time between you.
[KARASUMA] There are
a lot of good sniper nests
in the big city.
We plan to have sharpshooters
posted just about everywhere.
Lead your target into
the crosshairs,
and the reward money
will be parsed out
between you and
the lucky marksman.
So stick to the
sniper-friendly routes
and keep those eyes peeled.
[STUDENTS]
Yes, sir.
[school bell chimes]
[NAGISA] So we're splittin' up
into groups, huh?
Hey, Karma. Do you
wanna be with us?
Count me in.
Uh, you're gonna
behave yourself, right?
No funny business?
No gettin' into fights
and all that stuff?
Yeah. Sure.
Don't worry, dude.
When I stir up trouble out
of town, let's just say...
...I know how to keep
witnesses from reporting it.
Oh, great! And now
he's part of our group.
Way to go!
Eh. What can I say?
We've been friends for a while.
So... Who else?
There's me, you, Sugino,
Kayano, should be two more.
Yep. Got it covered!
Okuda's in!
Still one shy.
You think our number six
should be a girl, too?
Heh-heh! No sweat. I foresaw
this and took the liberty
of enlisting
someone very special.
Ladies and gentleman,
class idol, Kanzaki!
Ohh! I'm totally for it!
[NAGISA]
Nice girl, Kanzaki.
Doesn't exactly
stand out in a crowd,
but everyone in E Class
is nuts about her.
Good addition to
the group, I think.
Thank you for letting me join!
I'm flattered.
Uh, yeah.
[KAEDE] Cool. So where
in Kyoto do we wanna go?
[SUGINO]
Good question.
Oh! You're all so cute.
Excited to walk the city
streets, boys and girls?
Ah, so young and naïve.
Yeah, well, you can just
stay here, Professor Bitch.
You can water the plants
while we're gone.
[HINANO]
Where should we go on day two?
[MEG]
I vote Higashiyama.
[ISOGAI] Remember, we have to
think about assassination.
[MEG] But there's so much
cool stuff on this route.
Oh, no! If you bastards think
you're gonna deal me out of
this trip, think again!
What?!
You know, you're kinda
giving us mixed signals here!
[IRINA] Oh, I'll show you
mixed signals, copper top!
[STUDENTS]
Huh?
[KORO-SENSEI]
One for each of you!
What are those, sir?
[KORO-SENSEI]
They're field trip guidebooks!
--[grunting]
--[MIMURA] What the hell?
They're more like dictionaries!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Just a little something
I threw together last night!
Included are: illustrations of
every major tourist attraction,
the top 100 local souvenirs
and where to find them,
travel self-defense techniques
from basic to advanced,
oh, and best of all: the
first edition comes with
a model of Kinjakuji!
[OKAJIMA] You are WAY too
excited about this trip!
[NAGISA] Koro-sensei likes
E Class to be prepared.
If the way things have been
going lately is any indication,
this is going to be
an educational trip.
I'm actually kinda stoked!
[SUGAYA] Whoa. Man, look
at those lucky jerks,
gettin' to ride first class.
And as always,
we're stuck in coach.
Yay for us, right, guys?
Now, now, boys and girls.
Try not to look so sour.
Rules are rules,
you know how this works.
The student handbook
states those of us
with the highest grade-point
average get dibs
on school funds.
Oh-ho! Is that the putrid stench
of abject poverty
filling my nostrils?
[IRINA]
Pardon me, boys.
[IRINA] Everyone having a
glamorous day so far?
[MAEHARA]
Um, Professor Bitch?
Why are you dressed like the
paparazzi should care
who you are?
[IRINA laughs]
When it comes to womanly wiles,
a femme fatale
pulls out all the stops.
Besides, travel is
no excuse not to look
devastatingly fashionable.
[KARASUMA]
You stick out like a sore thumb.
Go change. You're a chaperone,
not a runway model.
Oh, come on, lighten up!
What's wrong with
a little style?
These kids are
going to the city.
Shut up. Get changed now.
[IRINA sobs]
[MEG] She's a more
of a child than we are.
[ISOGAI] Maybe killing
rich dudes for a living
disconnects you from reality.
An excellent
place to corner him.
Yeah!
[STUDENTS chattering]
[SUGINO] Huh. Has anybody
seen Koro-sensei?
Was he even at
the train station?
Holy--!
Not to pry, but is
there some reason
you're stuck to the window?!
[KORO-SENSEI] Uh...
I was stocking up on munchies
at the terminal and
lost track of time.
It's all right,
I'll just stay here
till we reach the next stop.
Cloaking engaged!
Nothing to see here. Just some
random clothes and luggage
stuck to the side of a train.
[NAGISA]
Worst. Camouflage. Ever.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Whew...
Who knew traveling incognito
would be so exhausting?
Goodness me.
Might be a little easier
if you didn't bring
such a big suitcase.
No offense, but you
weird people out as it is.
And while we're
on the subject,
broadcasting that you're
in disguise defeats the purpose.
[KORO-SENSEI gasps]
[TOKA] Truth? It's a
lame disguise anyway.
Nobody's buyin' it.
Hey, Koro-sensei.
Try these.
Can't have your nose going
AWOL all the time, right?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Wow! A perfect fit!
Custom carved to complement
the contours of your face.
You're welcome.
It's whatever, just a little
hobby of mine, no big.
Whoa! That's cool, Sugaya!
[KAEDE giggles] Isn't it awesome
how when you travel together
you see a whole
other side to people?
[NAGISA] Mm-hm! I don't know
what we'll learn about
each other on this trip but
I'm ready to be surprised.
Hey, guys, I'm gonna make a run
to the main car
and get us some drinks.
Anybody else feeling parched?
Uh, can I come with you, please?
[KAEDE]
Me, too!
--Isn't this cool?
--I love how space age it feels.
[KANZAKI]
Sorry. Excuse us.
[GIRLS giggling]
[PUNK A] What school
you s'pose they're from?
[RYUKI]
Kunugigaoka, probably.
How'd you like that?
A train full of smarties
from one of the best schools
in the country.
Tell me another.
Come on, her?
She don't look smart.
[RYUKI]
Hey. I have an idea.
Once we're in Kyoto,
whaddya say we have some
fun with these dweebs?
Nice!
[KORO-SENSEI sighs]
[MIMURA] So, bullet trains
actually give him
motion sickness?
You'll probably feel better
if you lay down
in our room for a while.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Perhaps later...
I need to pop back over
to Tokyo for a moment first.
Koro-sensei forgot
his favorite pillow.
How is everything you
own not in that bag?!
Any luck?
It's gotta be in there, you
worked so hard on it, too.
[KANZAKI]
Mm-mm...
[KORO-SENSEI] I admire your
going through the trouble
of putting together an
itinerary, Kanzaki,
but if you can't
locate it, don't fret.
I have just the solution.
These handy dandy guidebooks
contain everything
you could possibly need.
[MAEHARA, OKAJIMA]
She made the itinerary
so we wouldn't have to
lug those things around!
I distinctly remember
putting it in my handbag.
I wonder if I
dropped it somewhere.
[MALE TEACHER A] So, uh,
tomorrow is your free-study day
in Kyoto, everybody got that?
Hey! Shut your traps
and listen for a second!
[RYUKI] Heh! Those jerks
from Kunugigaoka
are really gonna try to
squeeze all this
sight-seeing into one day?
[SUGINO] Nice spot.
For assassination, I mean.
Don't you think, Nagisa?
[NAGISA]
If the snipers can see it, sure.
[KAEDE] What a bizarre
field trip, right?
[NAGISA] Maybe.
But you gotta admit it's fun.
[KAEDE sighs]
Whatever we do,
we have to get green tea
warabimochi dumplings!
--[NAGISA chuckles]
--[OKUDA] That's a great idea!
We could put poison in them!
That's twisted!
[OKUDA] Not for us, silly.
For Koro-sensei.
Not too shabby.
We could take advantage
of his sweet tooth.
[KAEDE] That'd be a waste of
a perfectly good local treat!
Now if only we could
find a poison
that didn't give him
special powers.
[SUGINO] Not to be that guy,
but I gotta tell ya:
I was sorta hoping we could put
the whole assassination thing
on hold while we were here.
We're in Kyoto, people!
What do any of these sites have
to do with assassination?
[NAGISA]
You'd be surprised.
[OKUDA]
Hold on, the Ryoma Sakamoto?
[KARMA] This is where
Omiya used to be.
The inn where Sakamoto was cut
down by assassins in 1867.
That's right.
And just a little further
down is Honnoji Temple.
Though it's moved a few
times since they built it.
Oh, yeah. Oda's death
counts as an assassination.
[NAGISA] Just think,
in these few city blocks
a slew of high-profile
assassinations went down.
Sure, Kyoto's always been the
heart of Japan,
but it's also a Mecca
for professional killers.
[SUGINO]
I never thought of it that way.
Guess you could say we're on
an "assassination vacation."
[NAGISA] Throughout history,
tons of targets have been
neutralized here, targets
whose lives the world
still feels the
repercussions of.
As far as that goes, Koro-sensei
is definitely in good company.
[OKUDA]
Cool! Next up is Yasaka Shrine!
[KANZAKI]
Uh-huh.
[KARMA sighs]
Mind if we take a break first?
I could really go for some
sugar-loaded Kyoto coffee
right about now.
[KAEDE]
Yay, sugar!
[KAEDE] Talk about off
the beaten path.
Gion is a ghost town
this far in.
[KANZAKI] Yeah. Places like
this put a cap on the number
of visitors they allow,
so you don't catch many people
just wandering around.
Secluded, lots of
good hiding places.
That's why I made sure
to put in on the itinerary.
It's ideal for assassination.
[KAEDE] Good job, Kanzaki!
You really do your homework!
I vote this is
where we do the deed!
[PUNK A]
"Ideal" is right.
[gasping]
It's also a great spot for
kidnappers to ply their trade.
[KAEDE]
Huh...?
[PUNKS laughing]
[RYUKI chuckles]
[PUNKS chuckling]
I hope you don't take
this the wrong way,
but, something tells me
you gentlemen aren't tourists.
Don't try to be
a hero, carrot top.
Hand over your
lady friends and wa--
[PUNK A grunts]
Y'see that? What did I tell you?
To hell with 'em.
Without any witnesses,
it's basically a
free-for-all, so go nuts!
--Hey!
--[KARMA] Hm?
I'm gonna gut you like a pig!
[PUNK B grunts]
[KARMA] Strong words for
a guy kissin' the sidewalk.
[KAEDE]
Let go of me!
[KANZAKI]
No! Stop!
[RYUKI]
What did we tell you?!
--[KARMA grunts]
--[KANZAKI gasps]
[KARMA grunting]
Leave him alone!
[NAGISA grunts]
[RYUKI]
Bring the car around.
Yeah, that's right.
Don't mess with us, dweebs.
[NAGISA] They crawled out of
the shadows like monsters.
Only these thugs are something
far worse than monsters.
They're high schoolers.
[PUNK B growls]
[OKUDA]
Nagisa! Sugino!
[NAGISA grunts]
Oh, thank goodness!
Are you two okay?
You all right, Okuda?
Those guys didn't do anything
to you, did they?
It's okay, I'm fine.
Sorry, I didn't know
what to do, so I just hid.
[KARMA] Don't sweat it.
You did the right thing.
[OKUDA]
Huh...?
[KARMA]
I think it's safe to assume
those guys are pretty hardcore.
We could go to the cops,
except they're the type who know
their way around the system.
Which is fine.
'Cause I'm the type who
likes to handle these things
personally, if you
know what I mean.
[SUGINO] Okay. Dude,
how do we even find them?
[RYUKI] I gave our buddies
a call and they're in.
We're gonna have ourselves a
li'l commemorative photo shoot
with you gals.
Feel free to scream.
No one'll hear ya 'cept for us.
[RYUKI] You. I seen you
somewhere before, right?
Sure I have.
Last summer in Tokyo.
Saw ya in that arcade.
Don't deny it.
[BOTH gasp]
[RYUKI]
My boys spotted you first,
told me to be on the
lookout for a party girl.
We was gonna
kidnap you then, but...
I guess you lucked out
and gave us the slip.
Who'd 'a thought
you were gonna go
to the school for geniuses?
No judgment, though.
I get it.
The higher you are
on the ladder,
the more you wanna
take a swan dive.
[KANZAKI gasps]
Don't worry about a thing.
Professor Ruin's gonna take
all night teachin' you
to dive like a pro.
[SUGINO "When a Group Member
has Been Abducted?"
I'll just say it, what kind of
"guidebook" covers this stuff?
[NAGISA] The sort of guidebook
an insanely thorough teacher
writes, apparently.
There's even a section
on how to deal with
seeing overpriced Kyoto
souvenirs for cheap
in boutique shops back home.
It's like he's walking us
through every possible scenario.
"Cheering Up Your Lonely Self
After Seeing a
Lovey-Dovey Couple."
Specifically "On the Banks
of the Kamo River."
But that's not even a thing!
[OKUDA giggles]
Well, at least reading
this calmed us down.
I for one feel pretty
confident about what to do.
[PUNKS laughing]
[KAEDE]
So that picture...
Not gonna lie, it's kinda
comforting to know
even you went through a phase.
Never would've imagined.
Yeah.
My dad was crazy strict.
Always on me about doing well
in school and
building up my resume.
It was so suffocating, you know?
I just couldn't deal.
So I'd ditch the uniform,
glam myself out, and hang
where no one knew who I was.
Felt like therapy.
So stupid. Where did
I expect to end up, right?
It's E Class for me.
But now, I don't even know
where I belong anymore.
[RYUKI] Sounds to me like you'd
be right at home with us.
Grades and all that pointless
bullshit don't mean jack here.
We eat elitist scum
for breakfast.
Nothin' sweeter 'n knockin'
stuffed shirts down
a peg or two.
The only thing that matters
is having a little fun, right?
You're a jerk.
[RYUKI]
I see how it is!
Little Miss Perfect
thinks she's better than me!
This is exactly what I'm talkin'
about, you uppity bitch!
When we're done here, you go
back to whatever fancy hotel
you're in and tell whoever asks
that you were just out
singin' karaoke and
lost track of time.
Stick to that story,
and no one gets hurt.
Once we're all
back home in Tokyo,
we can all hang out together.
Maybe we'll scrapbook,
do something artsy
with the "vacation photos"
we're about to take.
[RYUKI laughs]
Ah. Speak of the devil.
My photographer
buddies are here.
[RYUKI gasps]
[PUNK G groans]
[NAGISA] School Trip
Guidebook, page 1,043
"What To Do When a
Group Member Has Been Abducted."
"If there are no leads
on the perpetrators
think back to any
colloquialisms, accents
or linguistic quirks
that might indicate
whether said
perpetrators are local.
If not, and the perpetrators
were wearing school uniforms,
refer to page 1,334."
Here we are.
If the perpetrators are in
school uniforms, you might be
dealing with a rival school
out causing trouble.
You found us!
What the hell?! How'd you
even know where to look?!
[NAGISA]
"Being unfamiliar with the area,
the culprits will opt to stay
within a narrow perimeter
after the initial kidnapping,
somewhere secluded
but not far from
the scene of the crime.
If this is the case,
consult page 134."
"My Mach 20 bird's-eye-view map
of popular and or likely
abductor hideouts may help."
[KANZAKI gasps]
[SUGINO] That guidebook
is straight-up amazing!
There's nothing
Koro-sensei didn't think of!
[KARMA] No kidding, right?
Definitely worth lugging around.
We should take one
with us everywhere.
[PUNKS] You're getting
all this from a guidebook?!
[KARMA] All right.
So what's it gonna be gentlemen?
Fight or flight?
We'll go easy if you back
down now,
but after all you've put us
through,
you're not gettin'
out of this unscathed.
That's a promise.
[RYUKI]
Heh...
[OKUDA]
Uh...?
[RYUKI]
Actin' all badass.
You Junior High kids
crack me up.
Why don't you say hello
to some friends of mine.
See how far that attitude
gets you with them?
[groaning]
They... [screams]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Say hello to them if you like.
Be advised, though, they
probably won't to hear you.
It's Koro-sensei!
[KORO-SENSEI] Sorry I'm a little
late to the festivities.
I figured it'd be best to let
you handle this on your own
while I searched elsewhere,
just to cover all the bases.
[NAGISA] Um. Sir? Why exactly
are you wearing a veil?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Violence is always regrettable.
I'd rather you not associate my
face with what I've just done,
or what I'm about to do.
[KORO-SENSEI] Good work
following the instructions
in the guidebook, Nagisa.
I'm glad I had the foresight
to provide them.
[OKUDA gasps]
Hold on! This freakazoid's
your teacher?!
That's the biggest load of
bullshit I ever heard!
[PUNKS yell]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Such language.
I'll thank you not to use it
in front of my students.
[PUNKS groan]
[RYUKI] I, I didn't even
see what he just did!
[KORO-SENSEI] And unless
you can move faster than me,
you'd be smart to keep your
filthy hands off them, too.
[RYUKI groans]
Wow.
So even the teachers they hire
at that damn school are special.
Prolly get off by lookin' down
on us like the other kids do.
Well, look down on this!
--[OKUDA gasps]
--[PUNKS yell]
[KORO-SENSEI] I think you
have the wrong impression.
[PUNKS grunt]
[KORO-SENSEI] The school
these boys and girls attend
is special, yes.
[PUNKS grunt]
[yelling]
[KORO-SENSEI] But they're
considered the outcasts.
[KORO-SENSEI] Their class is
the target of merciless scorn.
[KORO-SENSEI] Even so, bleak
as their situation may seem,
they stay commendably positive.
[RYUKI growls]
[KORO-SENSEI] Never would
these children dream
of pulling others down to
their "level" out of spite.
[RYUKI growls, grunts]
[RYUKI grunts]
[KORO-SENSEI]
They're not privileged,
they simply work hard.
And there's the moral for you.
As the old saying goes,
in clear waters or murky,
fortune favors the fish
who swim upstream.
[KANZAKI gasps]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Okay, boys and girls,
let's take
care of business.
These misguided young rascals
are in desperate need
of a lesson in proper field trip
etiquette, wouldn't you agree?
[PUNKS gasp]
[PUNKS grunt, groan]
[RYUKI] How are they
behind us all of a sudden?!
What the hell did they just
whack us upside the head with?
[RYUKI]
You know...
I'm starting to think we picked
the wrong kids to mess with.
[SUGINO]
Man, for a while there
I didn't know what
was gonna happen.
[KARMA] Should've just left me
alone with the ringleader,
I'd have taken out the trash
before the bastard
knew what hit him.
[SUGINO]
We get it, you're a scary dude.
[OKUDO laughs]
[KAEDE sighs]
I'm just glad we're okay.
How you holdin' up,
Kanzaki? You good?
[KANZAKI]
Sure. All things considered.
[KAEDE giggles]
[KORO-SENSEI] I must say,
you're handling this quite well.
[KANZAKI]
Huh?
[KORO-SENSEI] Most folks
would've been traumatized
by what you just experienced.
Yet, you've shaken it off
without batting an eye.
In fact, I daresay the whole
ordeal has empowered you.
What do you know?
I guess it has.
Thanks for coming to the rescue!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Don't mention it. [giggles]
Why don't we carry on with
our field trip, boys and girls?
[SUGINO]
Aw, dang it.
We never got to try out
our assassination plan.
[OKUDA] Well, it really isn't
the time or place for that now.
[KARMA] Whatever.
We'll just try it tomorrow.
[KORO-SENSEI giggles]
Best of luck to you.
[NAGISA] When your target is
also an outstanding teacher,
it's the definition of "between
a rock and a hard place."