[KORO-SENSEI] ♪ First,
you take the planet Earth, ♪
♪ round and blue and green. ♪
♪ And floating over Tokyo,
you drop a giant bean. ♪
♪ Put another one in Sichuan,
China--what a sheen! ♪
♪ Taking off from Dubai to
Hawaii at Mach Twenty, ♪
♪ leave contrails as you fly. ♪
♪ Double back across
the Southern Hemisphere ♪
♪ over the Philippines once
again to ol' Dubai. (And then)♪
♪ Back to Hawaii,
drawing lines of latitude ♪
♪ every 25 degrees
along the way. ♪
[KORO-SENSEI]
And there you have it:
♪ Koro-sensei! ♪
See? Simple! Now you try it!
[STUDENTS]
Are you kidding?!
[KARASUMA]
Here's the hitch,
your target is a
junior high school teacher
chaperoning students
on a field trip to Kyoto.
As you're probably
aware, he's not human.
Now, I don't mean to call
your skills into question,
but on this assignment,
be ready for anything.
[RED EYE]
They call me Red Eye.
I'm a hired gun.
A sharpshooter.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Wowza!
The open-air design really
lets you feel this baby move!
This is how you
travel by train!
Zipped along at a bracing
25 kilometers per hour,
and no queasiness!
[MAEHARA] Says the guy who
can break the sound barrier.
[PASSENGERS chattering]
[ISOGAI]
Just a little more.
And we'll be right in
the sniper's line of sight.
Incidentally.
It's a popular tourist stop
on the Sagano Tram line.
[ISOGAI]
The Hozu River Bridge.
[TRAIN ANNOUNCER]
All right, folks.
Now's the time to
snap those pictures.
[HINANO] Hey! Check out
the boat, Koro-sensei!
Coolest thing ever, huh?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Ooh, let me see!
Nice!
[ISOGAI]
He's waiting on the banks.
Our high sign is when
Koro-sensei leans forward
to get a better
look at the boat.
[RED EYE] One time,
in the Middle East,
I shot a man at twenty clicks
during a sandstorm.
Beautiful day,
clear line of sight.
Easy mode. Yeah.
If that wasn't a headshot,
I'm a monkey's--
He blocked my bullet
with a piece of yatsuhashi?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Oh dear.
There seems to be a sliver
of bone in my om-nom.
That could've turned out ugly.
[RED EYE]
Urgh! Impossible!
A high-spin round stopped dead
by a tiny piece of local,
ooey-gooey goodness?!
How fast do they
expect me to be?
[RED EYE]
Hmph. Okay.
Now I understand the price
on this guy's head.
Mr. K was serious we he said
my target wasn't human.
[RED EYE]
This is gonna be fun.
[ACTOR A]
Be gone with thee, foul wastrel!
Your presence doth
desecrate mine eye!
[ACTOR B growls]
How dare you address me thus?!
[ACTOR C] Let us teach
this man humility, brothers!
[yelling, grunting]
[OKAJIMA]
Awesome!
Their swords move so fast
you can barely see them!
[KORO-SENSEI]
These men are highly trained
in the subtle art
of stage combat.
Did I mention that I'm an
aficionado of Edo-era swordplay?
[MIMURA]
Whoa!
[NAKAMURA]
Heads up!
Watch out, sir!
Don't stand so close!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Okie dokie.
[RED EYE] The actors are
guiding the target nicely.
Good. Everything's going
according to plan.
That's right,
eyes on the show.
Huh?
Where the hell?!
Oh, come on! Really?!
--How's everyone okay with this?
--[AUDIENCE screams]
[KORO-SENSEI]
I come to thine aid.
Blood-soaked sakura blossoms
are an evil flower.
I will not abide them.
[RED EYE]
He even knows the lines?!
I can't hit him like this!
The actors are in the way!
Gah, I hate actors!
[KARASUMA] He's been
clocked at Mach Twenty,
and his defensive techniques
are unconventional.
But don't let that
throw you off.
[RED EYE] Yeah.
Unconventional. Moving on!
This son of a bitch is dead.
I stake my name on it.
[SUMIRE]
You're late, sir.
What took you so long?
[KORO-SENSEI]
So sorry!
I got swept up into
a samurai drama.
I was the star!
[MURAMATSU]
I totally believe it.
[YOSHIDA] Y'know,
we finished Kiyomizu Temple
like forever ago.
[KORO-SENSEI] Then what
do you say we scope out
Ninehnzaka Street for souvenirs?
Yeah, right. Like you'll buy
anything except junk food.
[RED EYE]
Okay.
[RED EYE] Perfect place
to draw a steady bead on him.
From Yasaka's five-story pagoda,
it's a straight shot.
[SUMIRE] Here, Koro-sensei,
try this blotting paper!
It's super cool.
[KORO-SENSEI]
I'm not sure I care for you
to see what it'll pick up.
[SUMIRE]
C'mon, it's supposed to be fun!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Okay, guess we're doing this.
[RED EYE]
He pores over his tchotchkes
at the foot of Sannenzaka.
And while a student
distracts him...
[RED EYE]
Booyah! Smack dab in the temple!
[RED EYE] This is ridiculous!
A piece of paper?!
[KORO-SENSEI] See?
This is exactly what I meant.
Look at all these secretions.
There's enough mucus here
to stop a bullet.
--[phone ringing]
--[KORO-SENSEI] Hmm?
Ah. Nagisa's group is calling.
Excuse me. Hello?
[gasps] Tell me where you are.
[RED EYE] Damn. What in
god's name is this thing?
His speed's insane,
his defenses impregnable.
It's like he's factory-made with
the express purpose
of being un-friggin'-killable.
[phone vibrates]
Red Eye here.
[KARASUMA]
It's me.
Oh, hey Mr. K.
[KARASUMA] I'm afraid you'll
have to pack it in for today.
No more attempts.
[RED EYE gasps]
[WALLA: STREET]
[KARASUMA] The next group you
were supposed to work with
has run into some
unforeseen issues.
Something about a gang
of high school thugs.
Target is disregarding the
itinerary to go to their aid.
[RED EYE]
Yes, sir. Understood.
To be honest...
...this bastard makes we wanna
throw in the towel anyway.
[RED EYE] I've been
a sniper for eight years.
And not once have I failed to
see a mark's blood in my scope.
Not once. That's how
I got the name Red Eye.
Kinda strange when
you think about it.
Nothing particularly
red about my eye.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Here you go.
It's a special blend
of spices from Sannenzaka.
Thank you. 'Preciate it.
You really shouldn't have--
What in the hell?!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Sorry to disrupt your plans;
some of my students
were in a pickle.
Not to worry,
it's taken care of.
Everything's shipshape now.
So I thought I'd take this
opportunity to drop by
and say hello.
[RED EYE]
So you knew the plan
and you were just
playing along for kicks?
You're one scary customer,
you know that?
No wonder the government's
paying a fortune
to keep you secret.
So, uh... Let's cut
to the chase, huh?
If you're gonna kill me,
go right ahead.
Death's an occupational hazard.
I know what I signed up for.
[RED EYE]
Just eat it!
[KORO-SENSEI] You don't really
think I'm going to kill you?
When you've gone
to so much trouble
making this an enjoyable trip?
On the contrary,
I'm here to thank you.
[gasps]
[KORO-SENSEI] My students did
some very impressive research
on this region. Yes,
as a means of pinpointing
an ideal spot for
assassination, but still!
They steeped themselves
in geography, local customs,
tourist highlights,
history, all of it.
[KORO-SENSEI] As a matter of
fact, their efforts brought them
closer to this city's
charms than a teacher
might otherwise dare to hope.
They've really come
to understand another place
and its people; to expand
their minds with travel.
What ultimately brought them to
that milestone? Assassination.
Here you go.
Under the circumstances,
I'm as proud as punch
to be their target.
[RED EYE] I'll be damned.
You're as crazy as you look.
Still. I can tell you
care about those kids.
Wish I'd had a teacher
like you back in the day.
[KARASUMA] Wait, what do you
mean you're quitting?
[RED EYE]
Yeah, sorry.
I suddenly feel like just
being a tourist for a while.
Life tends to pass you by
in the sniper's nest, ya know?
It's time I expanded
the ol' color palate.
Eye's gettin' tired of red.
Now, let me see.
What hue should I set
my sights on tomorrow?
[SUGINO]
Hot damn!
How the hell are you
dodging all of those?!
[KANZAKI] This is actually
starting to get embarrassing.
Look at the way she
handles that joystick,
smiling like it's no big deal.
Oh, wow! I had no idea.
I mean, who knew you'd turn out
to be such a video game pro?
I've kept it secret.
My family's super strict.
They don't approve of me
wasting time on stuff like this.
Lately, though, I feel like
I'm over caring so much
about what they think.
Well what anybody
thinks, really.
I used to get so stressed
about how other people saw me.
I always second-guessed myself.
[KANZAKI] But then
Koro-sensei made me realize.
It's all about doing
the best with what you have.
Being true to the person
you are on the inside.
[NAGISA] Not a side of
Kanzaki I expected to see.
I wonder what she and
Kayano talked about
while those creeps
held them against their will.
It's like, I dunno,
like they've bonded.
--They blew you up!
--Yeah, that'll happen.
[MIMURA]
A-ha!
Hey, good save, man.
[KARASUMA] Almost every
sniper who saw the specs
on this mission
turned it down.
The one guy we thought was a
shoe-in quit halfway through
the assignment. Damn.
So much for our
Kyoto gambit, I suppose.
[MIMURA]
Who else wants some?!
Hey, Mr. Karasuma, quick game?
[KARASUMA]
Aw, what the hell.
No more horning in
on their field trip.
This is supposed to be
their time, after all.
You got it,
but I'll warn you.
I'm pretty good.
[OKAJIMA] I'm just gonna say it.
This place is a dump.
Why we gotta sleep in two big
dorm rooms separated by gender?
The kids in all the other
classes get put up
in their own fancy suites.
[NAGISA] Personally, I think
it's more fun this... way...
Hey. What are you guys doing?
[FUWA]
Shh!
What does it look
like we're doing?
Tryin' to sneak a peek!
[NAGISA]
What?!
Wait, that supposed
to be our job!
It's nobody's job.
[NAKAMURA] Either way,
who can resist?
[NAKAMURA] Look at the way
that outfit is hung.
That can only mean one thing.
You're a clever guy.
You get what I'm saying.
We wanna see what
he looks like naked.
This may be our
only opportunity.
Does he have a proper body or is
it tentacles all the way down?
And it's not creepy
'cause we need all the intel
on Koro-sensei we can get.
[OKAJIMA] Can we all agree that
this isn't the least bit sexy?
[NAKAMURA]
Is he a chick?!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Oh, hello, children.
Are you taking a bubble
bath in a public restroom?
We're not s'posed to add
anything to the water, sir.
[KORO-SENSEI] Worry not.
This is just my mucus.
[NAKAMURA]
Huh...?
[KORO-SENSEI]
On contact with water,
it works up a nice lather
and acts as an exfoliate.
[SUGINO]
So is that a pro or a con?
[NAKAMURA giggles]
Yeah. Fascinating.
But you let
your guard down, sir,
and we're blocking your exit.
You'll come slopping
out of that tub eventually.
And when you do,
you'll have to walk by us.
We may not kill you,
but we'll see you naked!
[KORO-SENSEI]
This simply will not do!
A-ha!
[NAKAMURA]
What the hell is that?!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Jellied broth, my dear!
Now, if you'll excuse me.
[KORO-SENSEI giggles]
All righty, then.
Well, that was lame.
Can we peep on a woman
next time, please?
Travel sure brings out
another side of people.
I know I'm learning a lot.
[OKAJIMA] Sucks we still don't
know what Koro-sensei
looks like under his
clothes, though.
[SUGINO]
Can we go back to the room now?
[MAEHARA]
Kanzaki's in the top spot.
No surprise there.
[MIMURA]
Well, yeah. Everybody likes her.
[MAEHARA]
I know.
Pretty slick of you to pull her
into our group, Sugino.
I was hoping me an' her
would have a chance
to talk a little on this trip?
But with all the crap
that went down, no dice.
[MAEHARA]
Sucks to be you, man.
Better luck next time, I guess.
Dudes, you're killin' me!
Can we just focus on
who has the hots for who?
[OKAJIMA]
Don't ask me to choose!
I can't do it! No! No!
You're exempted.
What about you?
Which of the class shorties
is your top pick?
[NAGISA]
Huh? Uh... I don't really know.
Ah, c'mon, Maehara.
You gonna ask you gotta tell.
Sorry. No can do.
A gentleman keeps
his secrets, fellas.
Bitch move, man!
When I think how popular
dillweeds like you are,
it drives me crazy!
Sounds like a party in here.
[ISOGAI]
Karma! Great timing!
[MAEHARA] Which of the girls
in our class do you like?
[KARMA]
Hmm...
I believe I'll have to
go with Okuda.
Dude, you're kidding. Really?
Huh. Interesting. But why Okuda?
[KARMA]
She's a demon with chemistry.
Think of all the concoctions
she could brew up
to enhance my shenanigans.
It'd be a match made in heaven.
[MAEHARA]
Yeah, heaven. Sure.
Hey, guys.
We're agreeing to keep these
ratings just between us, yeah?
[MAEHARA]
Of course. We're not stupid.
So absolutely none of what
we're saying leaves this room?
If this information got out,
we'd have a real problem.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Don't mind me. Just passing by.
[SUGAYA]
Oh, no he di'n't!
[MAEHARA]
Kill him!
[KORO-SENSEI cackles]
If I can't get the low-down
on juicy gossip like this,
what's Mach Twenty good for?!
Ew. Who wants
to talk about boys?
Ugh, c'mon. That's what girls
talk about on trips like these.
Don't be a party pooper.
I'll start! I have a
huge crush on Mr. Karasuma!
Honey, there's no one here
that doesn't have
a thing for that man.
I'm talking about boys in our
class that we think are hotties.
Aww...
Whatever, I'll get
the ball rolling.
Isogai and Maehara are
half decent, I guess.
Gross. You don't
seriously like them?
[NAKAMURA] Why not? Maehara
plays the field, though,
so I'd never actually go out
with him or anything.
Isogai's class monitor, so
he's, like, upwardly mobile.
I don't know. Karma's the cutest
of the bunch if you ask me.
[OKANO sighs]
Too bad he's such a psycho.
[GIRLS]
True...
Come on.
I don't think he's that bad
when you get to know him.
Hey, 'least he's quiet
most of the time.
Yeah, so are wild animals.
[KAEDE]
Who'd you pick, Kanzaki?
Uh... I don't really think
about it. No idea, sorry.
[KAEDE]
Oh, please! Liar!
Don't be a prude! Spill it!
[NAKAMURA]
You know you have your choice!
--They all worship you!
--Who would you go out with?
--Seriously, you guys!
--Tell us!
Knock it off!
[IRINA]
Okay, girls. Settle down.
I'm supposed to tell you
lights out, so, I dunno,
at least pretend to be asleep?
Wow, way to chaperone there.
[IRINA] We all know you're
gonna stay up jibber-jabbing.
Just keep the antics
to a dull roar, okay?
Hang on, how come
you get to drink beer?
Meanie!
I'm an adult, sweetie.
Adults get to drink beer.
[TOKA]
Why don't you stay up with us?
You could tell us
some "adult" stories!
Huh?
We'd probably get more out
of 'em than your usual classes.
--Why, you trashy li'l ginger--
--Now, now.
Don't get bent out of shape.
[GIRLS]
Huhh?!
[NAKAMURA]
No way! You're only twenty?!
[MEG] You look great, it's just,
you're so... "experienced".
[OKANO]
I know, right?
And the whole black widow vibe.
Ladies.
I wouldn't have gotten far in
this line of work if I wasn't--
Who the hell just
called me a black widow?!
[NAKAMURA]
Delayed reaction much?
[IRINA] Whatever. Point is,
if I teach you nothing else.
You should know
sex appeal is skin deep
and by the time
you get it, it fades.
In a place like
the one I was born in,
you learn that all too quickly.
--[GIRLS gasp]
--[OKANO] Professor Bitch
actually said something
profound for a change.
Feels like B.S.
[IRINA]
I heard that, you hussy!
Oh, just ignore her.
Tell us about all the rich men
you seduced and killed!
That's what we're dying to hear!
[HINANO] Yeah!
I totally second that!
[IRINA]
Hmph. Well, if you insist.
Be warned, my life story
might be a bit spicy
for girls like you.
It all began at the tender
age of seventeen.
--I don't think so, pal!
--[screams]
You got a lot of balls helping
yourself to our girl-talk!
[KORO-SENSEI] Aw! But I
wanna hear your stories, too!
Why can't an impartial observer
get in on this action?
Ha! You never tell us
about your love life!
You wanna sit there and listen,
fine, but give us the goods!
[HINANO] She's right.
It's only fair, you know.
[OKANO] We know you've got a
romance in there somewhere!
[NAKAMURA]
You like giant boobs!
You must at least
have a crush on somebody!
[KORO-SENSEI whimpers]
[NAKAMURA]
Oh no, he didn't!
[IRINA] Catch him, make him
sing, and cut his throat!
--[OKAJIMA] There he is!
--[KORO-SENSEI gasps]
--[MAEHARA] Come on!
--[BOYS yelling]
[GIRLS yelling]
[KORO-SENSEI] Rats!
Caught in a pincer attack!
[STUDENTS yelling]
You guys still
trying to kill him?
Assassination doesn't
have a curfew, huh?
[STUDENTS screaming]
[KARASUMA]
Hm?
[KORO-SENSEI] That was
a little too close for comfort!
[KARASUMA]
Would you mind telling me
what all that racket was about?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Nothing.
The students wanted me to
open up about my love life.
[KARASUMA]
Your what?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Oh, I assure you,
my past is positively riddled
with romantic encounters.
I haven't enough fingers and
toes to keep count of them all.
[KARASUMA]
Fingers and toes, huh?
I assume you're
referring back to a time
when you had hands and feet?
Sorry. I didn't
mean to go there.
I wouldn't want to talk about
the past in your shoes.
[KORO-SENSEI] A wise
observation, Mr. Karasuma.
It's bad manners to ask after
the number of one's appendages.
Even while traveling together.
[KAEDE] This has been
such a great trip, right?
It's like we've all really
gotten to know each other.
[NAGISA]
That's true.
[KAEDE]
Hm? Is something the matter?
[NAGISA sighs]
I was just thinking.
You know how our
trip's mostly over?
Even though it feels
like we just got here?
I'm kind of starting to feel
the same way about life.
We're just learning about the
world, and it may be over soon.
[KAEDE]
Yeah...
[NAGISA] And even if the world
isn't over by March,
this class will be.
[KAEDE]
Right...
I wanna live big,
to experience everything,
to be a top-notch assassin.
I just want my life
to have purpose, you know?
[KAEDE]
Hm. I hear you.
For now, I'd settle for just one
more school trip like this one.
[NAGISA]
Me, too.
Tonight, the curtain falls
on our adventures in Kyoto.
What a trip.
Tomorrow, it's back to life
at Kunugigaoka Junior High.
Back to our
Assassination Classroom.
[MALE AGENT A] So,
no luck neutralizing him
on the field trip to Kyoto
either, I take it?
This is most unfortunate,
Mr. Karasuma.
[KARASUMA] The fault lies
entirely with me, sir.
I will redouble my efforts.
[MALE AGENT B] Need I remind
you that May is almost over?
Our deadline is
fast approaching.
It will be here
before we know it.
[MALE AGENT C]
Precisely.
Why not just fire
a missile at the school
and flatten the whole
confounded thing?
[MALE AGENT D]
We've been through this.
Far too much collateral damage.
And there'd be no guarantee
he wouldn't escape the blast.
You recall what became
of our trying to hit him
over the Pacific, don't you?
He reassembled the missile
fragments and handed them back.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Hey, nice try!
[MALE AGENT E]
So what are you saying?
That there's no surefire
way to kill him?
[MALE AGENT F]
Worry not, gentlemen.
Several allied nations have
pooled their resources
to arrive at a solution.
The fruits of their labor
are most interesting.
In fact, we've already
received consent
from the Ministry of Defense.
Joining the so-called
Assassination Classroom
will be two very
special additions.
Cutting-edge science
has vested both
with veritably
superhuman abilities.
One still has a few kinks
that need to be worked out.
The other was put on standby
while you were in Kyoto.
Oh, yes, Mr. Karasuma.
There is quite a surprise
waiting for you back at school.
[KARASUMA growls]