[NAGISA]
November: maturity month.
Everyone's really started
thinking for themselves.
Which is good.
Because we only have four months
left to assassinate Koro-sensei.
[STUDENTS gasp]
[footsteps]
[IRINA]
Is the Octopus for real?
He's giving you kids
career counseling now?
[STUDENTS gasp]
Wow, look at you!
In a normal outfit!
Yeah.
Thought I'd go for
cheap and plain.
Just tryin' to fit in to your
regular old world, that's all.
[BOTH gasping]
Oh, come on.
Don't tell me all of a sudden
you wanna see more skin?
[OKAJIMA] No, leaving
more to the imagination
is somehow even sexier.
You've really grown as a person!
[NAGISA]
Uh.
[NAKAMURA laughs]
[NAGISA] Uh! Nakamura!
Did you write this?!
That's my future
you're messing with!
Sorry, sweetheart, men's
work just doesn't suit you.
[KARMA]
Hey, Nagisa.
[NAKAMURA, NAGISA]
Huh?
Which would you prefer,
Thailand or Morocco
after graduation?
I'm kinda partial
to Thailand myself.
[NAGISA]
Why do I get the feeling
everyone's dead-set
on neutering me?
[NAGISA sighs]
[SUGINO]
Careers? Seriously?
Why're we talking
about this stuff
when the Earth's on the
verge of being destroyed?
[NAGISA]
Hm. What do I wanna be?
[KORO-SENSEI]
A bureaucrat, eh?
Interesting choice.
If I may say so, administrative
duties seem rather, um,
restrained for someone
of your temperament.
Well, remember the last quake?
How the politicians were
completely useless?
[KORO-SENSEI] I won't
disagree with you on that.
[KARMA] The country should've
been paralyzed, but it wasn't.
Everything kept functioning.
Who do we have to thank?
Behind every talking
head at a podium
is some bureaucrat
pulling the strings.
That's what real
power's all about.
Does that make sense?
[KORO-SENSEI]
You know, I take it back,
that's a good fit for you.
[KARMA]
Take my advice, Terasaka.
Don't be a politician.
Huh?
I mean, sure: people love
seeing a big-mouthed,
impulsive idiot on the ballot,
don't get me wrong.
It's just that making you
a puppet'd be way too easy.
Huh.
You're delusional, man.
Like I'd be somebody's puppet!
Who the hell said I
wanna be a politician?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Nakamura.
You aspire to be a diplomat?
Oh, to aim so far above
one's modest beginnings.
[laughs]
You don't have to put
it like that, sir.
Believe it or not,
back in primary school
they said I was a
certifiable genius.
In first grade,
I actually tested at
a sixth-grade level.
I always placed in
the top of my class.
The thing is...
it really sucked.
I just wanted to be normal.
Not caring about grades,
goofing off with your friends:
that's normal.
So, when I made it to
Kunugigaoka, I played dumb.
After a while it wasn't an act.
Then I saw how disappointed
my parents were,
and the importance of what
I'd thrown away really hit me.
I still wanted to joke around,
but I knew I needed
to apply myself, too.
[NAKAMURA] This class is
the best of both worlds.
What I mean is... Thank you.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Aw...
[HINANO]
Miss Irina! Miss Irina!
Can I hear more of
the story, please?
[NAGISA]
To look at them,
you wouldn't believe anyone's
thinking all that hard.
But they are.
[KAEDE gasps]
Uh-oh.
Miss Irina's top.
The tag's still on.
[KARMA] She's not used to
buying stuff off the rack.
You think maybe we
should tell her?
[NAGISA]
I'll take care of it.
Believe me, I earned that car.
Putting the moves on the
CEO of a tech company
is challenging to say the least.
Oh, yes.
For one thing, the hours
are atrocious...
...if Karasuma hadn't forbidden
me to drive the damn thing here.
He says I won it by
defrauding a man.
"I'm Karasuma and I hate fun!"
[HINANO, TOKA laugh]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Okey-dokey.
Last but not least.
So, have you decided
on a prospective career,
Nagisa m'boy?
Sir, I... I think, well, uh.
I think I have a talent
for killing people.
I'm pretty sure I could get to
where I do what the Reaper does.
We all know I don't have
any other strengths.
So, I mean, what else can I
reasonably shoot for, right?
[NAGISA]
Koro-sensei, should I...
Should I become an assassin?
Please, sir. What path
should I follow?
'Cause I don't know.
[KORO-SENSEI] You're a
sensible young man, Nagisa.
And a good student.
I'm sure you would've
weighed the risks
of becoming an assassin
before coming to me with this.
For the record, you have
a gift for the work.
No one who's seen you in
action could doubt that.
Whether facing an
otherworldly monster,
an unhinged teacher, or an
evil genius, you prevail.
Your attacks are thought-out,
well-timed, and without fear.
All indispensable qualities
for a master killer.
[KORO-SENSEI]
That said, of course.
While you are courageous,
there's a tinge of desperation.
[NAGISA]
Uh!
[KORO-SENSEI] You never
give your safety, or dignity,
a second thought.
You strike without fear
because you feel you
have nothing to lose.
To what end should your
talents be put to use?
More importantly, for whom?
Reexamine those
questions more closely.
We'll talk again after you've
done a bit more soul searching.
I give you my word,
if you still wish
to be an assassin,
I'll support that decision
wholeheartedly.
[NAGISA sighs]
[BOY A] Whoa! You beat it?
Even the secret boss?
Not my first time.
I had to play it twice before
I got enough experience.
Oh, I see, I'll
start over. Cool!
[BOY B laughs]
--[door opens]
--[NAGISA] I'm home.
[HIROMI] Welcome back, Nagisa.
Have a seat, please.
[NAGISA]
Sure, mom. What's up?
[HIROMI]
Not your grades, certainly.
Fifty-fourth on midterms?
The cutoff for being
permitted back
onto the regular campus
is fiftieth place.
I'm disappointed,
but don't lose hope.
Tanaka's older brother
was once sixtieth.
Of course, this was
three years ago now,
but he managed to bounce back.
The school made an
exception for him
on account of his family's
rather generous donation.
The same gesture
should work for us.
Whatever gets you out
of that dreadful E-Class.
The sooner the better.
[gasps]
I'll be scheduling
an appointment
with Mr. Ono of D Class
very soon and I expect
you to come with me.
[NAGISA]
No, wait! You... you can't!
Please! You gotta let me stay
where I am for right now!
I know you don't like it,
but honestly,
I'm bringing my grades up,
and it's a lot of fun!
Look, I'll go to whatever
college you want, I swear!
But for junior high
I really, really--!
[gasps]
[NAGISA]
Uh-oh.
She's in one of her
moods, not good.
Here it comes.
[HIROMI growls]
[HIROMI] Shut that filthy,
ungrateful mouth!
I did not raise my son to be
driftwood, do you understand me?
Do want to live the rest of your
life in the shadow of failure?
You have no idea what it's like!
I work and slave to spare you
the fate of your poor mother
and this is that thanks I get!
Do you think money
grows on trees?!
You think I just pulled this
donation out of thin air?!
Well I've got news for you!
I put myself through hell
to secure your future!
Who do you think you are?!
[NAGISA] There's no talking
to her when she's like this.
It's my fault for not
bringing this up
when she was in a better mood.
I'm sorry, mom.
I was being selfish.
I wasn't thinking.
[HIROMI grunts]
[NAGISA] Dad doesn't have
the stomach for confrontation.
This is why he walked out on us.
[HIROMI]
Now, then.
You listen to me.
You're a child.
You have no earthly idea how
to make your way through life.
But mother knows all
the twists and turns.
I won't let you end up
like your father and I.
See, I have it all planned
out, just trust me.
The long-term goal is to get
you into Keisetsu University.
[NAGISA] One of the top
schools in the country.
Mom didn't make the cut.
It's a great alma mater.
Big companies take notice.
In the real world,
it's not what you know,
it's who you know: school
ties are everything.
A Keisetsu graduate could
even have a shot at working
for an elite corporation
like Hishimaru!
[NAGISA] They're a famous
company, who didn't hire her.
[HIROMI sighs]
Have I ever told you
how badly I wanted
a little girl?
[NAGISA]
Only about a million times.
[HIROMI] Your grandparents
discouraged me
from being too feminine.
It was always studying
and hard work.
That's why Hishimaru
didn't want me.
They're all about looks.
I promised myself
if I had a daughter,
she'd get to wear are the frilly
things I was never allowed to.
Ah!
See how nice this looks with
your beautiful, long hair?
[NAGISA]
Yeah. Looks great.
Except I'm a boy.
It's chilling how
determined she is.
I don't think I'll ever be able
to get out from under her.
Koro-sensei saw right
through me.
I'm not, and never will be,
the hero of my own life.
Not even close. It's her RPG.
I'm just her new play through.
[HIROMI]
Oh, and by the way.
Just so you know, I'll be
dropping by the school tomorrow
to meet with your
teacher for a transfer.
[NAGISA]
Huh?!
That's a little out
of the blue, mom!
I think he might be busy!
It's for the best,
Nagisa dear.
Now, if I were you, I'd say
goodbye to my E-Class friends.
[NAGISA]
She's gone dark again.
Nothing I say will
make any difference.
[KORO-SENSEI]
I see.
Your mother seems to
be rather single-minded.
[NAGISA] Yeah, I know.
What do I do now?
She won't listen
to a word I say.
Mr. Karasuma's out
of town on business.
I can't ask one of
his subordinates
to meet with her on his behalf.
I'm just... I can't.
I'm not ready to
leave E-Class yet.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Now, now.
Don't you worry about a thing.
I'm a super being capable
of destroying the planet,
after all.
A simple parent-teacher meeting
should be a walk in a park!
[NAGISA] Uh... I'm
not so sure about that.
[SUGINO]
Wow, seriously? Your mom?
She's one tough cookie.
Koro-sensei seems pretty sure
he can handle her, but...
I see no reason I couldn't
play your teacher.
[NAGISA]
Uh?
Problem is, officially
it's Mr. Karasuma.
His name's on file.
If our parents talk to each
other it won't add up.
Mm. Yeah. Good call.
[KORO-SENSEI] Ha, ha, ha.
There's a simple solution.
Yours truly becomes
Tadaomi Karasuma.
[NAGISA]
Koro-sensei?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Ha!
Why, no!
I'm Karasuma!
[OKAJIMA, SUGINO]
Worst cosplay ever!
[NAKAMURA] Did you draw lines
on your face with a marker?!
[KORO-SENSEI]
It's a furrowed brow
to accentuate his
bleak worldview.
Details!
[MIMURA] Why do your arms
look like summer sausages?!
[KORO-SENSEI] These are
Karasuma's bulging muscles!
[MIMURA]
You look ridiculous!
[NAGISA] All I can do
at this point is pray.
With any luck, mom will
fall for the charade.
Please just let me
stay in E-Class.
[MIMURA]
That's Nagisa's mom?
[OKAJIMA]
She's a knockout.
[MAEHARA]
More like she'll knock you out.
[HIROMI]
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm Ms.Shiota, Nagisa's mother.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Yes, yes. Please, have a seat.
Good to see you.
Trekking up the mountain
is quite a journey,
you must be tired.
Might I offer you a
refreshing beverage?
[NAGISA]
I...
I guess it's kinda convincing?
[KORO-SENSEI]
If I may say so, madam,
you're quite stunning.
I see where Nagisa
gets his looks.
[HIROMI gasping]
[HIROMI]
Why, thank you!
You know, if only this one
had been born a girl,
I'd have groomed her
to be my ideal!
Not quite sure I follow you.
Well, you see.
I wasn't allowed to
wear my hair long
and a girl is ever so much
prettier with flowing locks.
Oh, Nagisa,
what I wouldn't give to have
had lovely, full-bodied hair.
I was so mad when he
started tying it back
for school this year.
But it looked so good,
I just had to let it slide as
long as he wouldn't cut it off.
[HIROMI]
Ah.
But we're here to
discuss his future.
We can't afford to discourage
them at this age.
They're far too impressionable,
in my experience.
You're familiar with Kei U?
They've accepted
several graduates
from Kunugigaoka High School.
I'd very much like
Nagisa to go one day,
but I'm afraid being so far
off track in Junior High
will hurt his chances.
So I've come here,
with all due respect,
to talk about what we can do
to get him out of E-Class.
And I trust you spoke
with Nagisa on the matter?
Oh, he's too young to
understand what's at stake,
believe me. And at any rate,
it's my job as a parent
to steer him clear
of the mistakes
I made at his age.
[NAGISA]
Mom. I, don't--
[HIROMI]
Hush up now, sweetheart,
the adults are talking.
Uh.
[KORO-SENSEI exhales]
Yes, well...
I believe I'm starting to get a
clearer picture of how Nagisa
became the person
he is today.
[NAGISA]
Huh?
[BOTH]
Ugh!
[KORO-SENSEI] Yes. Indeed.
I, Tadaomi Karasuma,
wear a toupee!
[KORO-SENSEI] High schools,
colleges, and hairstyles.
Ma'am, forgive me for saying so,
are decidedly not a
parent's prerogative!
I'm sorry.
Nagisa must be permitted
to live his own life.
You'll get nowhere foisting
your complexes onto him.
Ms. Shiota. Let me
be perfectly clear.
Unless Nagisa so desires,
he will not be allowed
to leave E-Class.
Uh.
[HIROMI] What's the hell
is your problem?!
Since when does a teacher
talks like that to a parent?!
How dare you?!
"Foisting my
complexes onto him"?!
If you think I'll sit by--
[OKAJIMA]
Whoa.
[MAEHARA]
Holy crap!
That is one seriously
pissed of lady right there!
Of course! That
explains your attitude
at home lately, this bald
idiot's been giving you ideas!
Well, watch this!
When I'm done with you,
your eyes will be wide open!
Koro-sensei.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Hm.
That was a bit more
tactless than I'd planned.
Still, though...
There's a lesson
to be learned here.
You need to communicate
your intentions
more clearly from now on,
speak your mind.
It's not that easy.
Mom won't listen
to anything I say.
She only sees me as her
second play though.
[KORO-SENSEI] It's not as
though you're powerless.
If assassination is your
forte, what can't you do?
The first round of your
own RPG started here
in this classroom,
remember that.
[NAGISA]
My first. My first round.
Looks great, thanks.
[HIROMI]
Sorry for earlier, darling.
I ought not have blown up
at your teacher like that.
It's just that I'm so invested.
Yeah.
Well, anyway.
I've been doing quite a
bit of thinking today.
And I've decided I simply will
not have someone who thinks
they know better than me
interfering with my life.
Period.
All obstacles must be removed.
It's time I gave you
a new outlook on life.
Nagisa.
[NAGISA]
Wha... What the...?
Mom?
[HIROMI] This is where it all
started going downhill.
When you started disobeying me.
This place turned
into a monster.
[NAGISA groans]
Burn it to the ground.
With your own hands.
Get your life back on track.
Mom, please.
What're you doing?
Calm down!
[HIROMI]
Mother knows best, honey.
Listen to me.
Burn it down and the guilt will
keep you from being able to face
any of these people again.
Plus, with the building gone,
the main campus
will have no choice
but to take you back in, yes?
[NAGISA]
No! I don't want to!
I brought you into
this world, Nagisa!
I scraped to send you to cram
school, then private school!
You have no idea
what it cost me!
I do everything for you!
Every night dinner's
on the table,
no matter how exhausted
I am from work!
Does E-Class do that for you?!
I made you who you
are! You owe me!
You will do what I tell you!
[NAGISA]
She's wrong.
But she's right.
How do I tell her,
what do I say?
[KORO-SENSEI] You need to
communicate your intentions
more clearly from now on,
speak your mind.
Mom, listen. I--
[BOTH gasp]
[ASSASSIN A] How 'bout you
quit shrieking, you old bag.
Sit back and enjoy the
show like a good girl, hm?
[NAGISA] That bloodlust.
He's an assassin!
Actually, it's you
who's in my way.
It's Wednesday night.
He comes here to watch
his favorite TV shows
on the Autonomous Artillery.
He'll shoot through here
at the speed of sound,
and when he does,
I'll split his head open
with my whip and kill him.
[HIROMI]
Kill? Oh, dear.
I have to call the police--!
[gasps]
Wouldn't do that if I were you.
The bounty's void
if I kill the kid,
but nothing in the rules
says I can't take out
a whiney old hag.
[HIROMI whimpering]
[NAGISA]
Okay. She's afraid.
Which probably means the
assassin has his guard down.
Mom.
I've spent my whole life
learning how to read you.
It's given me a very
specific set of skills.
Maybe not the ones
you'd prefer me to have,
but they come in very handy.
Especially in E-Class.
[KORO-SENSEI] The first round
of your own RPG started here
in this classroom,
remember that.
[HIROMI whimpers]
[NAGISA]
Mom. Believe it or not,
I'm giving this class
everything I've got.
Before I graduate,
I'll get results.
And when I do,
I'm cutting my hair,
and paying back every scrap
you've spent on me.
[whimpers]
[NAGISA] If you can't find it
in your heart to forgive me...
What is this?
[NAGISA]
...then I'll graduate again,
from you.
[clap]
[ASSASSIN A gagging]
[gasps]
[NAGISA]
Mom.
I'm grateful that you had me.
Grateful that you raised me.
It may be asking a lot,
but if you can just be happy
that you have a child.
That, all things considered,
turned out relatively okay,
that's all I need to be happy.
Who are you, Nagisa?
What in the world have you done?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Certain unsavory types
have made this their
after hours hangout,
I recommend you give the
area a wide berth at night.
Koro-sensei.
[KORO-SENSEI]
For the record,
you just vowed to kill
me before March.
No takesies-backsies!
[grunts]
You heard all that, huh?
[KORO-SENSEI]
Now, then, ma'am.
Nagisa has quite a bit of
growing left to do, I agree.
What he needs more than
anything is a loving mother.
Don't take his stubbornness
so personally.
Every little birdie needs to
leave the nest at some point,
that's the way of things.
[HIROMI]
My baby is...
pulling away. He's leaving me.
Mom, no!
[KORO-SENSEI]
It's all right.
The adrenaline rush
got the best of her.
Why don't I take the two
of you back to her car?
I'll drive you home.
[KORO-SENSEI]
So tell me, Nagisa.
If you did manage
to assassinate me,
would you marshal your talent
toward becoming a
full-fledged professional?
Good question.
I don't know.
Probably not.
I mean, when we're
talking about talent.
It's not like it's only for
one thing or the other.
I'd be good at killing,
but I'd be good at
protecting people, too.
But definitely not by
being an assassin.
Way too dangerous for me.
I'd rather find a career that
wouldn't worry my folks.
[KORO-SENSEI] No rush.
You have plenty of time.
Ah, and keep in mind:
with your parents,
communication is key.
[NAGISA]
Right.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Ugh! Come on,
there's no cross traffic!
How long does it take
to get a green light?!
[NAGISA sighs]
[HIROMI]
And what's all this?
[NAGISA] I'm making
breakfast from now on.
So, uh, you can take it
easy in the mornings now.
I'll start taking
out the trash, too.
And hey, I promise to
get into a high school
every bit as good
as Kunugigaoka!
Just please, mom.
Let me stay in E.
If that's what you want, fine.
I really couldn't care less.
[NAGISA]
Ha!
I'm an assassin!
Holding my head high
till graduation!