[SHIRO]
Now then, Koro-sensei.
Let your final
death match begin.
[ITONA]
So strong, but compared to me...
...so weak.
[ALL]
It's Itona!
[SHIRO] I'm afraid drastic
changes to the playing field
were in order.
You understand, I'm sure.
Ensnare first, strike
second. Very effective.
As you can see, we've taken
a page from their tactics.
You dirty--!
I should've known it was
you behind all this!
[SHIRO]
Indeed.
When the trust of his
students is on the line,
this creature panics.
If something seems a
bit fishy, no matter,
the fool plunges in headfirst.
Ugh! Dammit! The bastard's
stealing our kill!
This totally counts as fighting
dirty, in case you didn't know!
[SHIRO] Also commonly
referred to as being an adult.
Note the gloves on
Itona's tentacles.
The edges are sharp
and constructed of
anti-Sensei material.
Each defensive stroke
by your teacher
results in ever increasing
damage to his limbs.
Though that won't be quite
enough to finish him off.
[ITONA] I've won, big brother.
Give up already.
This is just how it is.
I have one problem
to solve. You.
At last, I will
prove my strength!
[KORO-SENSEI yelps]
[KORO-SENSEI chuckling]
[gasps]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Bravo! Well done, Itona!
If we were in the
First Term right now,
this might've actually
cooked my goose!
One criticism, though.
Your attack pattern
is rather transparent.
However fast you are,
however strong,
however many schemes
your guardian thinks up,
however prone I am to panic,
by our third bout,
I can adapt to
the idiosyncrasies
of your fighting
style with ease.
[growls] No way.
It's not possible!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Dear boy.
I study too, you realize.
How could I mold young
minds if I didn't?
A true teacher misses
no opportunity to learn.
Now then, let's get rid of
this dangerous cage, shall we?
Incidentally, trying out my
Absolute Defense Form
over the summer break taught
me a very valuable skill.
How to release a burst of energy
by compressing not my body,
but only the tips
of my tentacles.
[SHIRO]
What?
[ITONA growls]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Remember this, Itona.
Assassination is
education, I say.
And in an
Assassination Classroom,
the teacher grows stronger
with every lesson!
[yelling]
[ITONA]
Why? Why can't I ever win?
I'm supposed to be
stronger than this.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Well there you have it, Shiro.
I suggest you go quietly
and leave him to E-Class.
Also...
I'd appreciate it if you'd
spread the word that I'm not,
in fact, an underwear thief!
And tell people I'm a
B-cup! Got it? B-cup!
[screaming]
[ITONA]
It hurts.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Itona!
[ITONA]
It hurts!
Feels like my head's
gonna burst!
[SHIRO] That would be
the agony of defeat.
His tentacles are
gnawing away at his brain.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Hang in there, Itona!
[SHIRO] Seems losing to you a
third time was quite the blow.
Failing to carry out this
little scheme of mine
is clearly more
than he can bear.
[NAGISA]
Huh? What does that mean?
[SHIRO]
Itona.
If this is the best
you're capable of,
the Organization
will stop paying.
I feel for you, I really do.
But I have to cut my
losses at some point,
focus my attention
on your successor.
This is goodbye,
Itona. I'm sorry.
You're own your own from here.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Uh. Hey! Where're you going?
How can you call
yourself his guardian?
[SHIRO] Asks the monster
playing classroom.
Why feign concern when all
you can really do is destroy?
Mark my words.
I will not tolerate
your existence.
In the end, I'll kill you.
No cost is too high,
no sacrifice too great.
[KORO-SENSEI growls]
[SHIRO]
Come to think of it, actually.
How do you suppose your dear
students feel about that?
[screams]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Look out!
What was wrong with him?
[KORO-SENSEI groaning]
[ALL gasp]
[STUDENTS]
Koro-sensei!
[KORO-SENSEI chuckles nervously]
[KORO-SENSEI]
Don't worry. I'm just pooped.
Nothing a little rest won't fix.
[SHIRO] Your immune system
sees the tentacle grafts
as foreign objects.
An intensive adaptive regimen
must be adhered to daily.
Otherwise the body takes
nightmarish defensive measures.
Once maintenance
is discontinued,
the tentacles begin to painfully
corrode the nervous system.
The average person dies
of madness in three days.
[REPORTER]
The first incident was here.
Officials don't yet
have any suspects
in this bizarre string of
cellphone shop attacks,
but aren't ruling out terrorism.
Businesses in the area have
been told to be on high alert.
[RITSU]
This has to be him.
No kidding.
Who else would it be?
Yeah, but why cellphone
shops, though?
We can't just let
him run loose.
[KORO-SENSEI] The burden
of reining the boy in
now falls on me.
I have to find Itona
and protect him.
[KARMA] I've seen guys
like Shiro before.
This is a game to him. People
are pawns to be sacrificed.
You can never really know what
someone like that'll do next.
Yeah, I vote it'd be better
if we just leave the kid alone.
[STUDENTS]
Uh?
[KORO-SENSEI]
No. I am his teacher.
[KORO-SENSEI] A teacher never
turns his back on a student,
no matter what.
When I took this job,
that was my solemn vow.
To never let go.
[ITONA'S FATHER] There are no
shortcuts, son. Believe me.
So if you want to get stronger,
it takes work, heart,
and integrity.
That's the only way.
Yeah right.
[PEOPLE whispering]
[ITONA] No more lip service.
No more beating around the bush.
The only thing you learn from
losing is how to be a loser.
I wanna win.
I wanna be strong.
[KORO-SENSEI] Your human side
is finally starting to show.
That's a positive sign.
[ITONA]
Big brother.
[KORO-SENSEI] I prefer
Koro-sensei, if you please.
A much more appropriate
name, I think.
Promise not to go all
nuclear on us, okay?
We've been through a lotta
crap tonight because of you.
But if you come quietly we're
and willing to let it slide,
so just, you know...
Shut your face.
We fight. Come at me. Right now!
[KORO-SENSEI] We can battle
if that's what you really want.
There must be a
vacant lot nearby.
State Secret
versus State Secret.
When the smoke clears, we
can study ways to kill me.
I've got all the fixin's
for a study-buddy-barbeque!
He's a very persistent Octopus.
Take my word for it.
Once you're in his class,
he'll go to Hell and back to
make sure a lesson sticks.
[KORO-SENSEI chuckles]
[KORO-SENSEI]
You bet I will!
Put a student in front of
me and I'm in my element.
The instinct to teach them is
so powerful, I can't help it.
[KORO-SENSEI chuckling]
[NAGISA]
What is this stuff?
[KAEDE]
I can't see!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Oh dear. This is anti-me powder!
[SHIRO]
Casting my ward adrift
was all part of the
plan, Koro-sensei.
[KORO-SENSEI]
I was so preoccupied
with the boy's bloodlust,
I didn't even notice!
[SHIRO] Come along, Itona.
You've one last duty to fulfill.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Don't you dare!
[SHIRO]
Rescue him. You are his teacher.
[KORO-SENSEI growls]
[STUDENTS coughing]
[NAGISA] Koro-sensei.
[KORO-SENSEI] No one's hurt,
are they? Everyone okay?
Uh, sure, more or less.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Good.
I'll go after your
classmate. Away!
You noticed that, right?
Protecting us slowed
his response time.
Oh no.
Damn that Shiro.
He sure as hell made
us his pawns, all right.
[KORO-SENSEI]
Itona!
Blast!
They're using pressure
rays to slow me down!
[SHIRO] Not that I'm
the least bit surprised,
but you really are a fool.
Itona is mine.
[SHIRO]
Remarkable.
You grow exponentially weaker
when the target is
anyone but yourself.
Are you certain you won't go?
[KORO-SENSEI]
I am his teacher!
[ITONA]
I... I'm weak.
Why else would my
partner abandon me?
[SHIRO]
Good eyes.
They radiate an insatiable
hunger for victory.
Crucial for anyone
hoping to fully utilize
the cells I've created.
[SHIRO] I can help you
carve a path to dominance.
Let us review some simple
arithmetic, you and I.
Your tenacity plus
my cutting-edge tech
equals the power
to seize victory.
Indeed, you can become the
most powerful creature on Earth.
[ITONA]
I wanted it so badly.
I could endure the
agony of those cells.
I was so dead-set on winning,
I could throw myself
into whatever it took.
Except... I lost.
I lost and now I'm being
protected by the thing
I was supposed to kill.
How? How did I lose
to a bunch of nobodies?
[UNDERLING A]
What the--?
You guys really shoulda
seen this comin'.
That crap might be anti-Octopus,
but it sure ain't anti-us.
[ISOGAI]
Hey, Terasaka,
can you grab those lights
up in the in tree?
All over it.
[UNDERLING D]
Damn kids! Huh?
You're doing this for me?
[HAYAMI]
Don't read too much into it.
This isn't about you, we're
just pissed at your boss.
And if Koro-sensei
hadn't bolted,
we'd have left you
behind in a heartbeat.
You hear that, dude? I love
how she pretends not to care.
[TAKEBAYASHI]
The girl runs hot n' cold.
Wouldn't look this way
if I were you, Shiro.
[KARMA]
You need to pay attention.
Stop shootin' and the net'll
come right off at the base.
[KORO-SENSEI] Excellent
timing. Nicely done, children.
[ISOGAI] That stuff's
melting his tentacles.
[MAEHARA] It's okay,
we'll get you out of there!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Step down, Shiro.
We're taking Itona with us.
You're a meticulous man,
that much is apparent,
but once you involve
my students,
there's no telling
what lengths I'll go to.
The sooner you home
in on the obvious, the better.
[chuckles]
[SHIRO] A class taught by a
monster swarmed with gnats.
How infinitely irritating.
Though, I begrudgingly grant
you my approach is in need
of a radical overhaul.
[SHIRO]
Keep the boy if you like.
He'll only live another
two days or so.
You kids play nice, now, hmm?
[ITONA]
Hard work, heart, integrity.
What a joke.
At the end of the day, it all
comes down to who's stronger.
[KORO-SENSEI] As long as
the poor boy is gripped
by this pathological
need to win,
the tentacle cells will cling
too tightly to be extracted.
So, can't we just cut
'em off, or whatever?
[KORO-SENSEI] Not until
he can break the fixation.
Some dreadful thing
brought him to this pass.
We must find out what.
Okay.
Easier said than done.
I mean, he's not just
gonna spill his guts.
[FUWA]
I was thinking, actually.
His little rampage.
Aren't cellphone shops a
weirdly specific target?
I had Ritsu do
some digging to see
if she could come up with
a possible connection,
and guess what,
one company's president
had a son named Itona.
A parts supplier.
Pretty modest, but they
used to have business
all over the world.
They declared bankruptcy
a couple of years ago.
The president and
his wife skipped town
and left the son behind
with relatives.
[NAGISA] Suddenly, we had
a clearer picture of Itona.
Why he was so bent
on power at any cost.
[TERASAKA]
Heh. Lame.
That's all it took to make
this punk a delinquent?
Like we don't all have
a bag o' rocks to carry.
Kid needs some perspective.
We'll handle things from here.
Take him in, care
for him, yadda yadda.
If he dies, he dies. We tried.
[ITONA'S FATHER]
Look around you, son.
We don't look like much
next to the big boys,
but if we work hard,
stay strong,
and let integrity be our guide,
we can give 'em a run
for their money.
[ITONA]
Yeah, sure. Whatever you say.
[ITONA'S FATHER]
Don't leave!
You're this company's
nerve center.
We can't function without you!
[ITONA]
Integrity is meaningless.
Against superior force,
it isn't worth a damn.
[ITONA'S FATHER]
I'm sorry, Itona.
I'm sending you to
live with your uncle.
Welcome back, Sleeping Beauty.
We used the anti-Sensei
netting to make a bandana.
For our own protection.
We need to keep those
tentacles in check.
How come we're lettin'
this jerk eat ramen?
'Cause he's bound to be hungry.
If we expect him to feel better,
he's gotta eat properly.
[MURAMATSU] What do you think?
Totally disgusting, right?
I keep tellin' my old man, but
he won't change the recipe.
I agree. It is disgusting.
Ugh, MSG doesn't hid the fact
the bones are stale.
And somebody needs
to tell your old man
this fishcake topping
is out of style.
This recipe you've got is
four generations too old.
[MURAMATSU]
Crap! He really knows his stuff.
[ITONA]
What a joke.
This dive'll go belly up the
second a competitor moves in.
Just like what happened to dad.
That's what integrity gets you.
Hey, c'mon, let's hit
up my place next!
What I got's the bomb!
It's totally modern.
This fossil ain't even
remotely in the same league.
[MURAMATSU]
Dude!
[YOSHIDA]
Pretty badass, huh?
Really takes your
mind off things.
[KIRARA] You know he doesn't
have a license, right?
[TERASAKA]
Relax. His folks own the track.
[YOSHIDA] Tell me this isn't
the most awesome thing ever.
[ITONA]
It's all right.
[YOSHIDA] Oh yeah?
Check out my brake turn!
Idiot! The hell you doing?
Help him! The shock's
gonna set him off again!
Relax, man! That wasn't
enough to hurt him.
[NAKAMURA] Way to fly by
the seat of your pants, guys.
[YOSHIDA]
See? He's fine.
Well, they're a
couple of morons.
What did we really expect?
Hey, no worries.
At least Hazama's got
a brain in her head.
[KIRARA] You wanna get
back at Shiro, am I right?
This novel oughta inspire you.
Seven volumes, 25 hundred pages
full of delicious revenge.
Read and let your
soul be nourished
by the darkness within.
Toward the end the hero
learns to forgive,
so you don't have to
bother reading that far.
[TERASAKA]
Seriously?
No! Way too dark!
And no one has the time
to read a damn book!
Oh, come on.
Evil has to be nurtured
properly, too, you know.
We're supposed to be
cheering him up!
You gotta think
of your audience!
He's probably not the sharpest
tool in the shed. Uh...
Uh, he's gettin'
all twitchy again.
Hell, I'd be twitchy too if
Terasaka called me stupid.
Oh no. It's the tentacles!
He's about to flip out!
I am not one of you losers!
I'm strong!
I'm strong and I win!
[YOSHIDA]
What're you doing?
[TERASAKA] Take it easy.
We all wanna kill the Octopus.
Matter of fact, I was just
thinking about it earlier today.
Look, you're not gonna get
him right outta the gate,
so get over yourself.
You need this too bad, man.
Just let it go. You gotta
chill the hell out.
Ugh! Shut up!
Hah. Second time today.
And you're weaker now,
so it's way easier.
Don't get me wrong, it still
hurts bad enough I wanna puke.
And speaking of puke, this
reminds me of Muramatsu's ramen.
Hey!
[TERASAKA] You see, the Octopus
told him it'd be a good idea
for him to study business.
Sure, his dad's ramen is crap,
but one of these days,
he'll take over.
And with what he's learned
he can push new flavors.
The joint'll be hoppin'.
The Octopus said the
same thing to Yoshida.
It's about bein' patient,
pickin' your moment.
So snap out of it.
You can't let a couple
losses blow you off course!
You don't have to win
now, just someday!
Slow and steady wins
the race, right?
Well, it kills the Octopus, too.
Doesn't matter if we screw
up a hundred times either.
As long as we kill him once
before March rolls around,
we win.
Use the reward money to get your
dad's factory runnin' again
so him and your
mom can come back.
That's somethin' to
shoot for. Why not?
I can't handle this.
The hell am I supposed to do
while I'm waiting to win?
How... How do I pass the time?
[TERASAKA]
Huh?
You act like an idiot,
like we did tonight.
Don't worry, we got you
covered in that department.
Isn't that heartwarming.
And who but an idiot could've
said it with a straight face?
I gotta say, sometimes
the word of an idiot
is exactly what
you need to hear.
[ITONA]
So I was... being impatient?
[TERASAKA]
Hah.
A little bit, yeah.
[KORO-SENSEI] I do believe
the fire in your eyes is out.
In a good way.
Those painful tentacle cells
can finally be excised now.
But don't fret too much.
What you'll lose in power,
you'll more than
make up for in friends.
You will come and kill me,
won't you? Starting tomorrow?
Whatever you say.
I'm sick of this power anyway.
And this whole brother thing.
Hey, look who's here.
Bet it's nice not to have to
bust through a wall, huh?
Good morning! That bandana's
lookin' pretty sharp!
[KORO-SENSEI]
Well, hello there! Welcome!
How are we feeling today?
Not so hot.
Sucks not having
my power anymore.
Still, guess I don't
feel any weaker.
I will kill you before it's
all over, Koro-sensei.
[KORO-SENSEI chuckles]
[NAGISA] And that's how
the textbook problem child
Itona Horibe finally
joined E-Class.
Muramatsu, hey. I'm broke.
Give me some of your ramen
and I'll try not to puke.
Huh?
[NAGISA] By being part
of Terasaka's group.