♪
(Japanese theme music)
I know you're hiding,
you can't fool me,
so come on out.
♪
What brings you back?
We just want to make certain
that you stay away from Katsu.
♪
Listen to me,
don't make trouble,
or you'll jeopardize the lives
of many innocent people.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
But if I hear that
Mr. Katsu is in harms way,
I'm not gonna sit
by and ignore it,
I'm going to do all
I can to defend the man.
♪
If you were a smart fella,
you'd listen to my advice.
Stay clear of Kaishu Katsu.
I'm not listening to anybody
that refuses
to give me his name.
I suggest you leave and
stop wasting your time.
I don't need to
tell you my name,
you should know by now.
What do you mean?
Don't pretend to be ignorant.
Surely, you're familiar
with the Beni Aoi.
Beni Aoi?
This is very strange indeed.
Didn't Mr. Katsu
tell you about us?
It's very possible
that we made a mistake.
We thought that you were
someone that Katsu hired.
We certainly wouldn't
want to kill anyone
that didn't deserve it.
♪
So don't go snoopin' around
if you want to survive.
♪
Beni Aoi?
(grunting)
Hey, Daigoro, if this piddly
stuff makes you tired,
you're never gonna
make it as a sensei.
You're right.
(grunting)
♪
Huh?
(smack)
(panting)
♪
Well, I'm pretty impressed.
The wimp's putting in
a mighty good effort.
So, what do you think,
does he have potential?
Huh, he's not bad, I guess.
I didn't give it
a lot of thought.
Is something wrong?
Tell me now.
Nothing's wrong,
I was just daydreaming.
Hey, everybody, come inside.
I hope you're all
nice and hungry.
Dinner's on the table.
Mmm, I'm starving to death.
♪
Hey, watch it,
Sano, there's now way
you're gonna eat before I do!
Get out of the way
you little squirt!
♪
That man didn't let down
his guard for a second.
That's strange,
I have no idea who he is,
and what involvement
he has with Mr. Katsu.
♪
It's possible that he may be
another samurai with a grudge,
but why?
♪
Come on, Kenshin, get up
and have something to eat.
Wait, let me help
you with that.
I'll be fine, now go ahead
and get yourself some food.
Cleaning up's
part of the training.
It builds character.
It's also a pleasant
form of meditation.
Huh?
♪
I'm assuming
Mr. Katsu wants us
to keep them for a while.
Right?
Mm-hmm.
That's the idea I got.
He feels that
the two of them
would be a lot
better off here.
Hey, that's my egg,
give it back right now!
Mmm, tasty.
Oh, disgusting,
you drooled all over it!
Hey, let's see what it
looks like on your face.
Oh, how am I
supposed to eat it now?
You wear that egg better
than egghead Daigoro!
Cut it out, Sano!
I don't know, maybe
you should go back home.
Wha?
No matter what
your father says,
he's going to be
worried about you.
I'm afraid that you
could be making a mistake
staying with me.
Besides, I'm not much
of a warrior type.
Daigoro.
Anyway, your
father's probably
going to go hungry
while you're gone.
Who's going to cook
his meals for him?
It'll be good for my father
to spend a little time alone.
He'll be fine, I think.
(chimes tinkling)
I hope it takes you a long
time to become a swordsman.
I'll tell you how come.
Until you become a
more skilled fighter,
Itsuko will have
to stick around
and cook us some
more decent meals.
You have no idea what kind
of garbage we have to eat
when Kaoru tries to cook.
It's awful to say the least.
Believe me, we are in no hurry
for you and Itsuko to leave.
Kaoru's food is so disgusting
that even a starving cat
would say, "No thanks."
Yeah, she's the sorriest
cook I've ever seen.
It's funny, she can
kick like a banshee,
but she sure can't cook.
All right, this is
getting ridiculous.
What is this, story time
at the Kamiya dojo?
Everybody's got their
face in a damn book.
Ah, zip your lips, not
everyone's a dumb fighter
like you, Sano.
What's that?
Hey, what's that story about?
It's too advanced for you.
Yoshi said he was
interested in science,
so I let him borrow my book.
You're welcome
to borrow it too
when he's
finished with it.
I don't know about that,
he's got to learn
how to read first.
(growling)
(thundering)
Tell me about Mr. Katsu.
Like what?
I've been told that
Mr. Katsu financed
Saigo's army
during the Seinan War.
Well, he's been
accused of that.
Tell me about it.
♪
Uh, all right.
(chime tinkling)
(thundering)
That would be
a criminal offense.
Why would he make a stupid move
like that and ruin his name?
He felt that he owed Saigo
for helping him save
the people of Edo.
Saigo planned to
attack Edo Castle,
but after meeting
with Mr. Katsu,
he was persuaded
to cancel the assault.
It's been said that the reason
the town of Edo
avoided a bloody conflict
was because those two
men negotiated a deal.
Many innocent
people were saved.
♪
After the meeting, Saigo
took Kaishu Katsu aside.
He knew that this decision
would trigger violent debates,
because certain people would
be unhappy with the outcome.
The sensei's life was left
in a precarious position.
Saigo made a promise
that he would take care
of any troublemakers
that threatened sensei
if he received
support in kind.
♪
This collaboration was a
double-edge sword for sensei,
but the town of Edo
was saved and, well,
that's what mattered.
Some government officials
who examined sensei
heard him say that Saigo was
a man that deserved honor.
(thunder clap)
Sorry I couldn't help,
but I'm afraid it
wasn't my time to die.
I was not afraid to lose my
life, that is not important.
There are so many
things left to do,
so much more I
could give the world.
I hope you understand
my position, Daigoro.
Until I accomplish
the goals I've set,
the past will
haunt me forever.
♪
But I am old and
my dreams are passé.
I'm just a relic of the past.
Young men like
you and Tetsuma
have the fate of
the world in your hands.
You need to spring ahead
and forge your way.
The Tokugawa era
is finally over
and now you have
the opportunity
to accomplish whatever
you set out to do.
I'm pretty impressed
with what he said.
Me too.
Both sensei and Itsuko
have taken care of me,
and I'm sorry to say
that I haven't been
able to repay them.
Don't beat yourself up.
The fact that you've
come here to the dojo
to continue your training
should make Mr. Katsu happy,
don't you think?
I suppose.
♪
He gave me this book
as a gift before I left.
It means a lot to me.
That's right,
that book talks about
going to the moon.
Mm-hmm.
I'm really interested
in scientific study,
and this book's filled
with valuable information.
It's a treasure to me,
and I want to
thank him properly.
I must succeed in
the art of kendo.
If I can master it,
I'll be able
to live with myself.
Well, you're very dedicated.
And just think,
if you get strong,
you'll be able
to protect the old man.
But you'll have
to really pump up
if you want
to fend off an attack
like the one we
had the other day.
Oh, yeah, them.
Who were those thugs anyway?
Oh, I can't tell for sure,
but I've heard some rumors.
Someone was talking
about a former samurai
who had a grudge
against sensei.
It has to do with the
fact that sensei gave up Edo
to the Satcho army
without a fight.
Unfortunately, I have
no idea who's behind it.
Well, judging by
their performance,
I can't say they have
very much in the way of guts.
(punching)
They didn't look like
they could kill anyone.
Then the strangest
thing happened.
This upper crust guy
appeared out of nowhere.
The thugs took one look
at him and they all ran away.
♪
(thundering)
(lightening striking)
♪
(carriage wheels rolling)
(thunder clapping)
(neighing)
It's Tetsuma.
Come in, the door's open.
I'm here.
♪
You come here often
these days, why is that?
(clears throat)
It's simply because I'm
worried about you, that's all.
The government
still has its doubts
about your involvement
in the misappropriation
of army funds.
Hah, that's a laugh.
Do they think I'm rich?
Where in blazes would
I get that much dough?
Don't worry about it, Sensei,
I'll take care
of the government.
Just leave it to me.
I took care of those
brawlers as well.
This should soon be over.
Thank you for your concern.
This place isn't safe.
Perhaps you
should move someplace
that's not so conspicuous.
Once I manage
to clear the air,
it will be all right
to come back here.
It's not necessary
for me to leave.
If they want to kill me,
they will, no matter what.
Here, you're a sitting duck.
Please leave with me.
It will be easier for
me to protect you.
No, but thanks for offering.
I'm going to
take my chances.
Mmm, are you sure?
Yes, I'm certain.
(bird chirping)
I consider myself
to be extremely lucky.
It's comforting to have
a pupil I can count on.
I've never had anyone
like you before.
You've succeeded
in understanding
everything I've taught you.
Not very many can truly
understand my ideas.
But, Sensei,
you also have Daigoro.
He's a man who has many
ideas, what about him?
Understanding comes from
having an intuitive sense.
Daigoro doesn't possess that.
He thinks when he should act.
(wings fluttering)
And he's obsessed
with his dream,
which isn't necessarily bad.
♪
Well, I've been told
that Itsuko's
been staying with him
ever since you
asked him to leave.
♪
That's true.
Apparently she
likes it there.
She's mad.
I'm going to pick her up.
There's no need.
I think it's better for her
to get a taste
of the real world,
so leave her alone.
All right.
I'll abide by your wishes.
I think you'd
better be going.
You could get in trouble
for goofing off here.
Perhaps you're right, Sensei.
I'll check on you again.
Tetsuma!
Hmm?
Wait a moment,
I have some advice
I'd like to give you.
Don't be too
confident in yourself,
or you could lose sight.
I believe you are talented
in everything you attempt,
but don't become so
enthralled with yourself
that you forget all
the beliefs you were taught.
Remember that God
knows everything.
Be one with him and you
will know what to do next.
♪
What!
You want me to match up
with that nutcase?
Come on.
I'm not ready
for a match yet.
The best way to
learn how to fight
is to jump right
in and go for it.
Yes, but I think that I--
Quit making excuses.
This isn't about thinking,
it's about doing.
Come on, you don't
have time to waste.
We realize that this
is your first attempt.
Yeah, but I've been
watching him practice.
You better watch
your back, Yoshi.
Kenshin, are you
trying to tell me
I'm gonna lose
to this yahoo?
No way!
That won't happen
till pigs fly!
He's right, I'm not even
close to Yoshi's level.
He'll make
chop suey out of me.
And besides,
I'm so exhausted--
Quit doubting yourself.
Huh?
I'm willing to bet that
you have what it takes.
Mm-hmm.
Yeah.
Right!
Whose side are you on?
Huh?
First match.
Eat my shorts!
(sticks banging)
(yelling)
Fight him back now.
Huh?
♪
Aahhh!
Ugh.
Daigoro, are you all right?
It's, uh, my back.
(crashing)
Uh.
Oh, my, he's hurt.
Daigoro, oh, you poor thing.
Let me help you.
Stay still, don't
die on me, please.
He made a move that
was not a very good move,
and he froze up so bad
that he looked like
a statue standing there.
But then as he
fell to the ground,
he sure was lucky
to be comforted
by a beautiful girl.
I bet she tried to
bolster his confidence.
Let's just hope for his sake
that he listens to her.
And that, my friends,
is what can happen to
you if you try to fight
the mighty Yoshi.
Hey, I just made that
story up about the fight.
What do you think?
You know I should
really write this all down
so I could send
it somewhere.
Yeah.
Hey, is anybody
listening to me?
You know all this
talk about writing
sure is making me hungry.
Daigoro, tell me,
does it still hurt?
A little, but
I feel better now.
I hope you'll forgive me.
I'm just
hopeless as a fighter.
You're making
yourself feel awful.
You did great.
(sigh)
Hey Kaoru?
Huh?
Is your pupil
having a comfy nap?
What do you mean?
Why don't you beat
him up a little,
I bet that would make
a fighter out of him.
Shh.
I can't, he'd
never let me do it.
He'll forgive you.
I'm just not sure it's the
right thing to do, that's all.
Well, you're
the one who said it.
Ah, he's having
second thoughts.
Hey Kaoru, what
are you doing here?
Why don't you just go in?
Shh.
What the--
It would be useless for me
to leave and go back to Sensei.
At the rate I'm going,
it would take me
10 or 20 years
to become
a master swordsman.
Oh, come on.
I don't believe
that for a second.
You're a lot better
than you think.
You can do it,
I'm sure of it.
Well, I hope you're right.
(struggling)
Hey, stop acting
like a stuffed pig.
So, what are you guys up to?
-Shh.
-Huh?
Yeah, would you be quiet?
I can't believe how
insensitive you are!
Huh?
Would you put me down,
you big behemoth!
You two were eavesdropping,
I saw you!
Come on, you're taking
me against my will!
I know my rights!
I want a lawyer!
I've decided what
our next move will be.
Time we put our foot down.
We've been too easy on him.
We may have to get brutal
if we want to
accomplish our goal
and show them that
we mean business.
That's not a problem.
I'll do anything if
I get paid for it.
Don't be an idiot.
Remember, we're not
doing this for the money,
or have you forgotten
the true principles
of the Beni Aoi?
Mmm?
♪
We move tonight.
(gong strike)
♪
Oh, Kaoru, forgive me.
I didn't mean to start
preparing dinner without you.
Honestly, it's
quite all right.
I was just observing
how skilled you are
in the culinary arts.
It's not really
that hard to learn,
I can teach you
if you'd like.
I'm ashamed to say that
cooking's just not my thing.
I'm sure it would take me
at least 10 or 20
years to learn.
I'm sure it's not
as hard as all that.
If you can run this dojo,
I'm sure you can learn.
Huh, you really
think I could?
Oh, boy, I'm going
to show that big oaf Sano
I'm a good cook
once and for all!
Now you've got the spirit.
Yeah, you bet I do!
I'll shower him with
fish balls and sukiyaki.
He'll turn into a blimp!
I think the one you really
want to impress is Kenshin.
Hmm, what?
Oh, that's silly.
But what's the deal
with you and Daigoro, huh?
Tell me.
No, Daigoro is
my father's pupil.
We're not
romantically involved.
I'm not so sure
I believe that.
What about Tetsuma?
Is there something going on?
Tetsuma is my
father's best student.
He's very busy
most of the time.
He seems to be
a little stuck up.
(dog whining)
Huh.
(crickets chirring)
♪
I'm not so sure I like him.
Tetsuma's not really stuck up,
but sometimes he
comes off that way.
He's just very focused
on what he's doing.
He's actually very smart
and skilled at his job.
After studying
with my father,
he went on to work
for the government.
He's a very serious man.
He's concerned with
the future of our country.
He always has my father's
best interest at heart.
But tell me, Itsuko,
do you prefer
a man whose dream
is to shoot himself
to the moon in a cannon,
or the more somber type?
I never gave it much thought.
Oh, my goodness,
I forgot the daikon radish.
I have to go get some.
Wait!
I don't know what I'm doing.
Oh, my gosh, I think the
dinner is starting to burn!
Help, don't leave
me here alone!
♪
You must be Katsu's
daughter, Itsuko.
It's too bad you're
such a beautiful girl.
So, what if I am?
What do you want from me?
Shut up, you're coming
with us right now.
♪
(laughing)
Somebody come quick,
it's an emergency!
Huh?
(footsteps running)
Help, I'm having a problem.
What!
Are you trying to burn
down the whole dojo?
I can't help it
if I can't cook!
Yoshi, hurry
and fetch some water.
Okay.
No, water will make it worse!
It's really smoking a lot,
what the heck do we do now?
Don't panic,
we have to smother
it with something.
Where is Itsuko?
She stepped outside.
She went to get some radish.
Hey cut it out, you're
scorching my eyebrows!
We need something
to use as a cover.
♪
What's this?
Itsuko!
(fireworks)
♪
(singing in Japanese)