♪
(theme song)
Please save him.
Yutaro, you have to protect
the formula for the medicine.
Don't let those men get
their filthy hands on it.
What men?
Well, you're a sight
for sore eyes.
Please tell me your name.
They call me Misanagi,
leader of the ninjas.
I'm sorry, I hope
you'll forgive me.
♪
I've almost got it.
This was his notebook.
Hey, what's that thing for?
It looks like
an ordinary rock.
Are these two items
all that we have to go on?
Yes, they're the only
things that Hans left me.
♪
I don't get it.
Why would the Germans
want to attack that doctor?
I have no idea what
could have provoked it.
It doesn't make
any sense at all.
The German government's
policies wouldn't be served
by that type of move.
So that makes me wonder
if it was
a political decision.
If their government didn't
have anything to do with it,
why would they bother?
Maybe they had some
other kind of motive.
I bet they wanted
the medicine.
That medicine must
pack a big wallop.
The notebook
could be the key.
Open it and see what it says.
Yeah, let's see.
Whoa, that doctor's
handwriting's awful!
It's not as bad as you think.
It's written in Latin.
What's that?
I'll explain.
Dr. Hans used
a complex language
in the event that
the notebook was stolen.
He didn't want the formula
to be deciphered.
That was a smart
move on his part.
(crickets chirping)
"I'm leaving this notebook
to my beloved pupil,
Yutaro Tsukayama.
Forgive me.
The reason that I did not give
you this information before
is because I didn't want
to put your life in danger.
Be careful, Yutaro.
You are only
reading this now
because something terrible
has happened to me.
Several years ago, while
studying Eastern culture,
I happened to obtain
a map and small stone.
They were
artifacts from Japan.
♪
I was told that these items
were brought to Germany
by a Portuguese missionary
about 300 years ago.
The missionary
also left a diary
detailing a legendary
miracle cure.
It was heralded as
a magic elixir for life.
♪
An allusion
to this same elixir
was called Nectar
in Greek mythology...
♪
...and Amrita
in Indian mythology.
♪
Of course, it's hard
to imagine that any medicine
could be a cure
at the present time,
but Yutaro, as you know,
the progress that we
have seen in microbiology
may make it a
definite possibility
in the near future.
We have discovered
the presence
of a pathogenic bacteria
that is thought
to be the cause
of many
communicable diseases.
So far, we have not
come up with a way
to immunize ourselves
against them.
The wisdom of the ancients
may be the clue to
our ultimate survival.
After extensive research
on the ingredients
in the miracle elixir,
I have come up
with a hypothesis.
This formula will
strengthen the immune system
and fight bacteria.
It could extend our lives far
beyond our wildest dreams.
This elixir could change
medicine as we know it."
Wow, if we find it,
we could
revolutionize medicine.
But how do you know
that stuff isn't snake oil?
He wouldn't lie to me.
But we need to prove
that he's right.
If he is, just think of
all the millions of lives
that we could save.
There wouldn't be
any more diseases.
Could you imagine what
that would be like?
We'd be selfish
if we didn't try.
Tell me, Yutaro, is this
map supposed to tell us
where the formula
for the medicine is?
I bet those Germans
are looking for this map
and they're gonna go after it
with everything they've got.
It's frightening
to think about.
What will they do with
it once they have it?
(crickets chirping)
Huh, there's some more.
"There's a group of evil men
that have been after
the medicine for a while.
They call themselves
The Black Knights."
-What?
The Black Knights.
♪
(galloping)
"The secret society
of The Black Knights
has existed since
the Middle Ages.
Their center of power has
been primarily in Europe,
but is rapidly expanding into
other areas of the globe.
Their members include
many prominent scientists,
politicians, leaders
of industry, and soldiers.
All are said to be
the best in their field.
Their main goal is
to control the world.
They are planning
to amass a huge fortune
by securing the financial
rights to the medicine.
By controlling
its distribution,
they will have power
over life and death.
We must not let them get
their hands on the medicine.
It is supposed to save lives,
but in the hands
of The Black Knights,
it will only become
a vehicle for disaster."
If that's true, we could
have a worldwide catastrophe.
The German soldiers
that attacked Dr. Hans
must be members of
The Black Knights.
Well, that would
certainly explain
why they traveled all
the way over here to Japan.
But taking over the world,
that seems pretty
horrifying to me.
The Black Knights
sound like whackos.
We can't let those sauerkrauts
take over the world.
That would be
absolutely insane!
How are we supposed to
find it without the map?
This may be it right here.
There's some weird
Japanese writing
at the end of the notebook.
I don't know if I can
figure out what it means.
Kenshin, mind helping me out?
"Heaven will begin to flow
backwards and you will find
yourself looking at Suwa.
There you'll see
four dragons flying
-straight to the moon.
-A god will cross by
and lead you to
the gates of Heaven.
You will enter through
the path of the tiger.
It is very dark and
if you're not careful,
you may get lost.
Follow the path where the
Goddess of Mercy's hand is
pointing and it will lead you
to the bottom of Mount Fuji.
♪
These instructions have been
passed on by my ancestors
for hundreds of years.
If you dare to call yourself
members of The Black Knights,
then you should be able
to understand what they mean."
♪
Whoa, how are we supposed
to figure out what all this
gobbledygook means anyway?
I'm not sure, and
to make matters worse,
the rest of the instructions
have gotten wet and blurred.
It's hard to read.
Yeah, but the book gave us
some good clues to go by.
The instructions said, "When
heaven begins to flow backwards,
you will find yourself
looking at Suwa."
Well, that's simple enough.
Let's start at
the Sea of Suwa.
So Misanagi, your
family seems to be
very knowledgeable
about medicine.
Let's stop with the riddles,
give me the formula.
We were very knowledgeable.
Unfortunately,
all the documents
that pertain
to the medicine
were scattered during
the chaos of the war.
Some were even destroyed.
Now even we are unable
to solve the mystery.
That is why
we want to work
with The Black
Knights' organization.
You will enable us
to communicate
through a global network.
It's not such
a bad deal, either.
You'll come closer
to achieving your goal,
and we'll get
what we want as well.
What do you mean,
achieve our goal?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Don't play coy
with me, Meldars.
If you feel that
you can't trust us,
then it may be a bad idea
in the first place.
In that case,
the deal is off.
Why, you little tramp!
Quiet, Lentz.
Please forgive us.
We don't want
you to leave, miss,
and we didn't mean
to be offensive.
We understand your
position perfectly,
and from now on, we intend
to be straight with you.
We have been searching
for this miracle medicine
for many years.
When we learned that you
could provide us with it,
we were elated.
Now, we will finally be able
to create our ideal world.
At first we thought it would
take at least ten years,
but our dream will
now become a reality
much sooner than
we had planned.
But I must be assured
of something first.
The medicine has been
in your family for centuries.
It's obviously
very important to you.
So there's a question
that needs to be answered
before we can go any further.
Why would you risk
all that you have
and give the formula
away to strangers?
Why?
I don't have a problem
giving the formula away.
You must want
something in return.
That's right.
I thought so.
We didn't expect
anything less of you.
What is it that you want?
Control of Japan.
Suwa is the Sea
of Suwa, of course.
You're right!
Hey, how come
I never thought of that?
And tenryu is another
word for Heaven.
That must mean
the Tenryu River.
It would be a good assumption
that we would need to go
where the Tenryu River
and the Sea of Suwa meet.
Once we arrive there,
maybe the other clues
will fall into place.
What do you think,
Kenshin, huh?
The Black Knights must
be halfway there by now.
We'd better hurry.
We have to find
the medicine first.
Then come on.
♪
Hey, last one
there's a rotten egg.
What, wait for me!
They're gonna
wear themselves out
before we get there.
♪
Just smell that ocean air.
That means we should
be arriving soon.
♪
(galloping)
Steady, easy, boy.
We're here, gentlemen.
There it is.
♪
Misanagi has returned.
Hurry, open the gates
for her immediately!
Who are those foreigners
she brought with her?
They could be trouble.
It sure beats me.
(horse trotting)
So, these are
Misanagi's ninjas, huh?
They all look like a bunch
of filthy monkeys to me.
They are supposed to
be the best in Japan
from what I've been told.
Have you noticed, they
haven't taken their eyes
off us since we arrived.
Shut up, both
of you, right now.
Ya.
Listen now.
From now on, our Sanada
ninja organization
will be working
hand in hand
with The Black Knights.
Every one of you will
be under the command
of Lieutenant Meldars.
(grumbling)
Just calm down.
You will obey
my orders, or else.
Have you forgotten
what will happen to you
if you rebel against me?
I will not tolerate
insubordination.
♪
That is one big lake.
It sure is, Sano.
I guess that's why they
call it the Sea of Suwa.
Great, now what
are we gonna do?
That's a good question.
The only clue that we have
is that it's here somewhere.
This will be like finding
a needle in a rice paddy.
It's gonna be
next to impossible,
if you ask me.
Hey look, there's
the Shrine of Suwa.
The shrine's been here
since the beginning
of the Japanese Empire.
I bet it's just full
of helpful information.
We may find out about
the medicine's whereabouts.
Hey, maybe we fly like crows,
we'll catch something, huh?
I don't know, Yoshi,
I'm not real partial to worms.
Huh, what's that thing?
I don't know, it must be
some sort of ancient symbol.
♪
Well, let's not
stand around.
There may be
some food inside.
♪
You want
the miracle medicine?
Well, uh, I'm sorry
but I've never even
heard of that before.
Thank you for your time.
That was useless.
Oh, knock it off,
you don't all have to sulk,
we'll just have to try
someplace else, that's all.
♪
Come on, Kenshin,
let's get a move on.
Wait, Mr. Negi,
what's that pillar?
It's owned by Shira.
There was another one
that's exactly the same,
I saw it when we arrived.
That's one of
our holy pillars.
We have a total
of four all together.
There's one,
and there's another.
They're hard
to see from here,
but those pillars are
very sacred symbols.
These pillars
were once shrines.
There's the upper main shrine,
the upper front shrine,
and then below.
There were some smaller ones.
They were called the spring
shrine, the autumn shrine,
and during that time,
the ancient people
called them suistasha.
The pillars that remain
are all that is left
of the original
four shrines.
They are very holy.
In our Shinto religion,
they are a stepping stone
for the gods' descent to Earth.
How were they made?
Sixteen giant trees
were cut down
from the tops
of the mountains.
They were dragged
over hills and valleys
and erected at
the Suwa shrine.
It was extremely hard work,
but it was a way to bring
the gods closer to Earth.
We celebrate them yearly
at the Ombishira Festival.
It's a huge Shinto ritual.
Lots of people come out.
If there's a party,
I'm ready.
There are four pillars,
four dragons.
Huh.
You may have
a point, Kenshin.
Take a good look at
those pillars, everybody.
Use your imagination,
they look a lot like dragons.
♪
He's right!
Hey, according to this,
in some regions people
worship these giant trees
or pillars as dragon gods.
It's part of their religion.
In this particular case,
the four pillars that
remain at the shrine
could represent
the four dragons
that Dr. Hans wrote about.
Hey, I'm sorry to
burst your bubble,
but they look like a bunch
of oversized logs to me.
What, you come here!
Well, they do.
Yoshi!
(laughing)
Don't mind him, he's a
little sick in the head.
How are we supposed to
solve the rest of the puzzle?
The dragons fly to the moon
and then some god
crosses by in heaven.
That's simple enough.
It's the tale of Omiwatari.
-Ah.
-Grrr.
One dark cold night,
a male god from the upper
shrine, Takimikiaka,
went to visit his lover
like he did every night.
She was a goddess
from the lower shrine.
Her name was Sosaketumi.
The two of them were
very much in love.
But that particular
evening, it was freezing.
It had been
snowing all evening
and the lake
was frozen solid.
The god crossed over on
the way to his sweetheart,
but all of a sudden,
the ice began to crack.
Crack, crack!
(splashing)
He fell into the icy waters.
And that is the
legend of Omiwatari.
It means a god
has crossed the sea.
See?
That makes good sense.
Lake Suwa must
be where all of
the medicine's
been packed away.
But the lake's humungous.
How are we ever
gonna find it?
Let's wait for
Omiwatari to happen again.
Then we can narrow it down.
Hey, yeah!
That's a good idea, Kori
Let's do it!
(grumble)
I--whoa, wait!
Omiwatari happens in winter.
Oh, yeah?
(birdsong)
Yutaro, quit moping and have
something to eat with us.
I understand how
the little twerp feels.
Everywhere we look, we just
run into a roadblock.
I guess we'll go back
to the drawing board.
Start all over again.
(menacing laugh)
Ha, thanks, Yutaro.
I'll eat it if you won't.
Huh?
Hey, come on, what's wrong?
Don't be such a party pooper.
Huh?
Watch out!
♪
Who's that guy?
-Help!
-No.
♪
Agh!
I never knew that such a
skilled swordsman existed.
Don't make any sudden
moves, do you hear me?
Heads up!
(yelling)
♪
Don't mess
around with Misao.
I'm the leader
of the Oni gang.
Yeah, she's right.
So watch out!
♪
(kicking and clanking)
Huh?
♪
The Oni gang, huh?
It's hard to believe.
Don't think we're gonna
turn the other cheek.
You turned against us
and we're never gonna
let you get away with it.
We will soon
give you a lesson
in the ninja's
code of conduct.
Hmm?
♪
What made you come here?
I heard rumors that
the Sanada ninja force
built a stronghold
in the Shinano Mountains.
It was Toyotomo's dream
of an independent country.
Even before he died
at the Battle of Osaka,
the Oni gang has been keeping
an eye on Toyotomo's group.
We've been checking
them out recently
because their movements
have become suspicious.
That's when we saw Himura.
Not bad, right?
Hey, you did a good job.
Who are you, anyway?
My name is Yutaro Tsukayama.
Right now, I'm a student
at the Kamiya dojo.
That's right,
he's actually a doctor.
Not a full-fledged doctor.
I'm just hoping
to be one.
Well, I'm Misao Makimachi.
I know on the surface I look
like a beautiful woman,
but in actuality I'm the
leader of the Oni gang.
Pretty awesome, huh?
You can call me
charm girl if you want.
Uh...
Don't get your
pants on fire,
she's a below
average ninja.
Her real name's Weasel Woman
and she's a screaming lunatic.
Who's a screaming lunatic,
you big freeloader?
Okay, you're just
a weasel woman.
Ooh, if anybody's
a weasel, it's you!
Well at least I accept
my shortcomings.
That's because that's
all you got, oh!
You almost killed me!
What makes you think
you can put our lives
on the line for the
pleasure of foreigners?
I don't care if you are
the leader of this
group, Misanagi,
I'm not about to take
orders from these men,
and above all, I won't
let them take our medicine.
I've been sworn to protect
it and I'm going to do that.
It's a promise we made
to our ancestors
that I'll obey.
Times have changed, Kaita.
It's a mistake!
He's more trouble
than he's worth.
We should eliminate
him and move on.
The ninjas must
have attacked us
because they know something
about the medicine
and wanted to keep us away.
Perhaps they could
lead us to it
if we could somehow
infiltrate their hideout.
It seems like that
might be our best chance.
Hey, that's the best idea
you've come up
with so far, Sano.
Could you please
tell me something
before I go
absolutely crazy?
What is this stupid medicine
you guys keep harping about?
(punching and clanking)
♪
That man put up quite a fight.
Yes, it's too bad.
That ninja had some potential.
♪
Misanagi, I'm very sorry
that you lost some
great warriors,
even though they decided
to turn against you.
I'm not looking
for your sympathy.
I'm much more concerned
about a group of swordsmen
led by the red-haired man
that injured Kaita.
He told me they were asking
questions about the medicine.
Ya, we've already
obtained some information
about that particular group.
One of them is
the pupil of Dr. Hans.
The fact that they've
showed up in Lake Suwa
means they might
know something.
It's possible that they
found some more clues,
which could help us
solve the mystery.
Let's capture them.
No, I have a better idea.
We'll make them
find the medicine
and then we'll make sure
they never make
it back home again.
Hmm, good idea.
♪
Be very careful, Misao.
I will, Shirojo.
Tell Okina not to worry
when you make it back
home to Kyoto, okay?
Sure.
Come on, it's time
to get some ninjas.
Yeah, let's get a move on.
♪
He has red hair with a cross
mark scar on his cheek.
♪
That's him, all right.
He's the one I'm after.
♪
(theme song)