♪
(singing in foreign language)
Thanks to Kenshin,
my life was spared
by the Sea Dragon's captain,
a mysterious woman named Shura.
(thunder)
Kenshin fought to
protect me from the pirates,
but a poison dart
proved to be his undoing.
The pirates were
going to kidnap me.
Kenshin, what's wrong?
But Kenshin talked Shura
into letting him take my place.
Take care of Kori!
♪
I love you, Kenshin!
Oh...
Awake at last, I see.
You were out cold for
quite a while, my friend,
but then that was
a strong dose of poison you got.
Shura, it is almost time.
All right, Iwazo.
All hands.
We're almost home.
Prepare to dock and go ashore.
(cheering)
Yeah, we took
everything Mr. Yohi had,
but it's still small potatoes.
We need a big haul.
What's our next target?
How about that copper
mining village near Nagoya?
Yeah, that's a good idea.
There's just
women and kids there.
The place isn't defended at all.
Oh yeah, easy pickin's,
and besides, with
all those women around,
why, we could...
Forget it, we're not
just a bunch of thugs
who go around beating up
women and children.
Have you forgotten who we are?
We were poor once.
My father taught you
to be worthy survivors.
Cowards and crooks like Yohi
deserve what they get from us,
and there's plenty like him
to keep us fat and sassy.
I don't want to hear
any more talk out of you
about attacking that
little mining town.
Now I want you all to go rest
up for the next real battle.
(clapping)
Shura, you know what?
I think that our hostage friend
deserves a little more attention
than we've been giving him.
After all, shore leave usually
includes a little recreation,
doesn't it?
♪
Maybe some harmless
amusement like...
chopping up a captive.
How about startin'
with this one?
There ain't much to him,
but we can busy ourselves
for a little while at least.
♪
I think I'll just
finish him up alone.
♪
The only question is
where to begin cuttin'.
At the hands or the feet...
(grunting)
♪
You had better
change your tune, Geki,
or prepare yourself
to take me on.
♪
(grunting)
Hey, listen up, all of you.
I'll take care of
executing this guy.
Gather up your
belongings and go home.
Shura.
-What?
-We've been talking,
and some of the men
aren't really happy
with that arrangement.
Hey, listen.
Have you decided to start
questioning my orders now?
Answer me.
Stop it, both of you.
Huh?
Everybody go on home.
But, you know,
she is the captain.
Let her take care
of it in her own way.
Come on, boys.
Huh, she's startin' to annoy me.
Just because her father
was captain before her...
Aye, orderin' us
around like that.
Bring me the prisoner's sword.
Thanks a lot, kid.
Now you go on home.
This is a job
I have to do myself.
Let my assault be noble
and therefore worthy.
Why didn't you kill me?
You could have easily,
and we both know it.
But you chose not
to finish me off.
Ah!
Why?
You could have easily beaten me,
but you did not.
Fight me now.
Go on!
What?
What are you grinning at?
Forgive me.
For some reason,
a thought just occurred to me.
If only we could have met as
friends instead of adversaries,
I would have preferred that.
How odd that fate
should bring us together
only to be enemies.
I guess you'd call this
one of the ironies of life.
♪
Take your sword and fight me.
Pick it up and fight!
♪
No, Shura.
Why not?
♪
Because you saved
my friend Kori's life.
To repay you,
I now offer you my life.
♪
(angry grunt)
Huh?
♪
(angry grunt)
(grunting)
(gasps)
Hm.
Maybe I'll feel like
killing you tomorrow.
Sarujiro, take him up
to the clearing on the cliff.
Make sure he's secured.
Take charge of these.
Guard 'em well.
I want you to watch
the prisoner tonight.
Mm-hm.
Don't let him out of
your sight for a moment.
I have a feeling that Kori
is looking up at the moon
and wondering where I am.
I've got to escape somehow.
♪
Sarujiro, you're a good guard.
You take your work
pretty seriously, don't you?
Hm.
So, does Captain Shura
treat you well?
Huh?
Mm-hm.
Well, it's obvious
that she cares about you.
You like her too?
Mm-hm.
(gasps)
Mm.
Oh.
(laughs)
♪
(footsteps)
Shura, I want to talk to you.
Ginjo, I thought you went home.
What is it now?
What's so important?
Hey, I'm just curious.
So why didn't you kill him?
Don't tell me that you might be
falling for that skinny reject.
What?
You've gotta be kidding.
Why would I do that?
Why not?
You could have.
After all, you're still a lady.
Huh?
I never even thought
of myself as female.
Hold it right there, princess.
You're a girl, all right.
All you need is to spend a
little time with a man like me.
(grunts)
Ha.
(grunting)
Ginjo, I swear I'm
going to kill you
if you ever touch
me like that again.
You're a member of
the crew and nothing more.
I am the captain
of the Sea Dragon.
Pig.
(winces)
You're gonna
freakin' regret that.
Ginjo, I could have
told you that little bitch
was a handful.
Hey, forget about it.
Come with me.
I got somethin' to show ya
that'll pick
your spirits right up.
♪
I figured we could make
some money with the silk
we got from Yohi.
But some of the crates
didn't feel like silk,
so I dug around,
and guess what I found
underneath in one of 'em?
So Mr. Yohi deals in opium.
And there's more.
Look under that.
I think maybe we've stumbled
into that big haul you wanted.
I believe you're
right, my friend.
This will make us wealthy.
This is only one
shipment of the stuff.
There must be a whole lot
more wherever this came from.
♪
I'll pay a visit to Yohi,
and I think life is about to
change for our beloved captain.
You know, the best thing
about drinking alone
is you get more to drink.
(laughs)
There's no more in this one.
This one's empty.
I know there's some
more in one of these.
Yep, it's this one, I think.
They stole 20 pounds of opium
and all those rifles from me.
Oh boy.
Ah!
Why did those pirates have to
pick on me anyway, the chumps!
Yohi!
Ah!
Where are you?
I'm in here.
♪
That voice sounds familiar.
Ah!
♪
Ah...
(trembling)
I'm so glad I
caught you at home.
We have a lot to
talk about, partner.
I'm disappointed.
You don't look
very happy to see me.
Oh, why, yes, of--no.
I would like you to
continue your trafficking
in opium and
firearms, old friend.
I'm even gonna help.
Now you're probably wondering
what I get out of this deal,
aren't ya?
Say yes.
Uh huh, uh huh.
I knew you were gonna say that.
Okay now, here's what
you're gonna do for me.
♪
I know you're worried, Kori,
and I think about it too,
but you can't let it
spoil your appetite.
You gotta eat.
Keep up your strength.
But it's all my fault
that he's on that ship.
If I hadn't got
so upset about money,
Kenshin would be
here having supper.
(gargling)
(muffled yelp)
(dazed muttering)
Sano, I'll thank you
not to gargle sake
while I'm worrying.
But, Kori, don't you see
you're not gonna help Kenshin
by worrying and starving
yourself like this?
Besides, what good
is a dead hostage?
They gotta feed him.
To tell you the truth,
I think he jumped into it
because he was lookin' for
a little change of scenery,
some excitement.
He's like that.
I feel responsible.
Kenshin knew what
he was getting into.
Anyway, tomorrow
something's bound to turn up.
Hey guys!
Come on, I think I got a lead
where they've taken Kenshin.
They were comin'
out of Yohi's place.
Who was?
Pirates, who do
you think I meant?
(grunting)
♪
Yep, those are
the pirates of the Sea Dragon.
♪
Anybody got an idea?
The only way to find Kenshin
is to follow them
back to their ship.
That won't be
a walk in the park.
-Are you up to it?
-Mm-hm.
Then I guess we've gotta go
and find ourselves a boat.
Mm-hm.
♪
Yohi really came through.
Now that Yohi's
our business partner,
we'll be able to
get the provisions
a big ship like
this really needs.
Smile, Yohi.
Fellas, you'll have to
excuse our guest of honor.
He's still upset over
a shipment of his weapons
that fell into our hands.
But we'll put them
to good use sometime.
Weapons?
Why didn't you tell us?
Let's see 'em.
Calm down, all in good time.
I wanted it to be a surprise.
See?
Look at those.
With these, nobody
can stand up to us.
New lever action
repeater rifles,
enough of 'em to arm
every man on the ship.
And as if that weren't enough,
our pal Yohi here is gonna
buy us a brand new boat,
isn't that right, pal?
And he's gonna buy it for us
with the profits from
selling all that opium.
But there's still a fly
in the ointment, Ginjo.
(sips)
Yeah, a fly by
the name of Shura.
Yeah, what about her?
So how does Shura
figure into these plans,
or does she?
You bet your hat she does.
But since Shura doesn't
like our choice of targets,
I plan to eliminate her.
(screams)
(slam)
Hm?
Huh?
Hm.
It's just a little bitty rodent.
A little bitty rodent,
ain't that cute.
♪
Yeah, a rat.
(soft snoring)
If I could only have one wish,
it would be to be
back at the Kamiya dojo
with all my friends.
I hope they're safe and sound.
I trust Kori has
recovered from her injuries.
(footsteps approaching)
♪
Huh?
It certainly is
a beautiful night.
Hey, listen.
Tell me something.
What is it you want to ask?
This--this friend of yours,
the girl you call Kori?
I would like you to
tell me something about her.
But what's the reason you ask?
I want to know!
Humor me.
Tell me what it is
that makes that person
someone that you would
give up everything for.
Please enlighten me.
I would really like to know.
♪
What shall I tell
you about her?
My friend Kori
has enormous courage.
She's generous
and compassionate,
and she has no idea
how special she really is.
She's far better at caring
for others than for herself.
♪
And deep inside,
she's very lonely.
Now that I think about it,
you remind me of
her a little bit.
Can you cook?
(gasps)
Huh?
You don't know me well enough.
(soft snoring)
♪
Then please tell me
about your background, Shura.
Maybe then I'd
understand you better.
I'd really like to know.
♪
When I was a child,
this village was hideously poor.
Rather than see us
all starve to death,
my father stole from
the provincial robber barons.
♪
My father did what he had
to to keep us all alive.
♪
The children he fed are
the crew that serve under me.
He was a thief with
an iron code of honor.
♪
Is it set?
I'm gonna miss this old tub.
(snickering)
Why, those lousy pirates--huh?
Sano, you know we've got to
get out of here right away.
I think they knew we were here.
Actually, Kori, I think
we need to jump off this ship
right away.
But why should we abandon ship?
Well, let's just
say I have a feeling.
♪
This way.
No, stop.
I can smell something burning.
♪
Gunpowder!
(explosion)
An explosion on my ship.
Don't go down there, Shura.
Ginjo wants to take over.
Your crew just
blew up your ship.
They would never do that.
Your crew isn't as grateful
as you think they are.
It isn't gratitude.
My crew counts on me
for their very survival.
They don't need you
for survival, Shura.
(grunting)
And their pirate code
is the code of cutthroats.
Don't you understand?
You don't know what you're
talking about, swordsman.
As they served my father,
my crew will
serve me to the end!
I bet her crew will sooner
serve her to the sharks.
It's up to me.
(grunting)
♪
I've just gotta break
out of these ropes.
♪
I heard an explosion.
What happened?
♪
Hey, what's the matter with you?
Shura!
(grunting)
♪
Shura, get Sarujiro.
Did you hear me?
Shura!
Sarujiro needs you.
You must take care of him.
Huh?
Oh, yes.
Ya!
(laughing)
♪
Ya!
(grunting)
♪
Ah, quit foolin' around, boys.
Hey, I mean, if you
want to get rid of him,
blast him.
Uh, but, men...
♪
(gunshot)
(grunts)
♪
Shura!
(gunshots)
(panting)
♪
Well, would you
look at that now?
♪
Hm.
Well, how 'bout that?
We got two pests
out of the way
at the same time.
(laughing)
(whimpering)
(roar of waterfalls)
♪
(singing in foreign language)