♪
Who will buy my wares?
Hold it, wait!
♪
Come on, Kenshin,
I'm really counting
on you here,
let's make this one.
We need an 11.
Come on, six-five!
Two-four!
It's all ours, baby.
Sano, my friend, it's
just not your day, is it?
Considering the loss,
you're taking this
pretty well, Kenshin.
Damn, I thought for sure
we were gonna win that last one!
So, tell me, what happened
to your Flying Sword
intuition, huh?
I don't even think you won
a single roll of the dice.
First of all, gambling
and swordfighting
are two different things.
Second of all,
you said you had
something very
important to tell me.
Oh, and by the way,
did I mention that
gambling is completely
against the law?
Ah, come on, this isn't
real serious gabling here.
We're just betting
with some of our friends
for what amounts
to pocket change
and besides, it's not
like we're drawing blood.
I've known these guys
for years and they're
all good buddies of mine,
even if you all are goofy.
Hey, watch what you're
calling us, loser!
Yeah, mister, we're
the good-looking ones!
You're the only
goofy one around here!
You mean goofy and broke!
(laughter)
So, you think you're
pretty funny, huh?
Is that right, Mister "I Could
Care Less While I Sip My Hot Tea
And Lose Every Round"?
I oughta teach you a lesson.
♪
Where is she?
Where did she go?
There she is, let's go!
Get her!
♪
Come on, baby.
Two-six, now, come on!
Hot dice!
Come on, come on,
come on, come on!
Ugh!
Two-five, yes!
Come to papa!
(laughter)
You lost again, you idiot!
How can you just sit there
drinking your stupid tea?
You couldn't roll a winner
if your life depended on it!
Every single time?
What's the matter
with you, Kenshin?
Hey, Sano, relax, will ya?
Why are you so serious today?
I'll tell you why,
'cause for the past
two weeks I've owed
that candy seller Yoita
some money and he's
been really bugging
me about it,
so I thought
I should pay him back.
You know, come to think of it,
I haven't seen
Yoita in a few days.
So, where is my buddy?
He's always hanging
around here somewhere.
(groaning)
Hey, what's with
the long faces?
It's Yoita, he-he died.
What do you mean, "He's dead"?
How?
I mean, I just saw him last week
and he seemed perfectly fine!
So you tell me
what happened to Yoita!
Well...it...it was opium.
No.
He overdosed.
He didn't know
what he was taking.
He thought it was a medication,
but it was opium,
a dangerous drug.
♪
Wait until I get my hands
on whoever did this to him.
They are going to pay.
Huh?
Oh, please help me!
There's a group
of men after me,
please save me from them!
You'll protect me, won't you?
Huh?
We got you, Megumi!
You haven't got a chance
in hell now, do ya?
I don't remember
inviting you two.
What's all the yelling about?
Shut up and mind
your own business.
We came for the girl.
Now get out of my way!
No!
♪
You guys really picked
the wrong time to come
barging in here
telling me what to do.
Believe me, you'll
never get away with this!
You don't even know
who you're dealing with!
We're members of
Mr. Takeda's group
and you'd better
watch your back!
You'd better watch your mouth!
You can take that
to Henry Takeda.
The Oni gang could
be serious trouble
for you, Sano.
So, who's Henry Takeda?
Well, on the outside,
he appears to be
a hardworking businessman,
but he's really
a seedy racketeering boss
whose operations
include all sorts
of crooked deals
to bring in money.
So, how did you get
mixed up with this guy anyway?
I didn't get involved with him.
I don't know why
they were after me.
Don't lie, Megumi.
Huh?
What?
Where did you come from?
What a conniving
little fox you are,
acting so innocent
and helpless
so these men protect you.
Remember, they're not
the only two after you,
you mustn't forget that
I will always be close
on your tail
watching your every move.
You go back and tell
that slimebag that I
will always get away from him.
No matter what he tries,
I'll always get away!
That's what I like about you,
your feisty little attitude,
but you're not going anywhere.
♪
Kenji!
Tomo!
Next, I'll hit both
your legs with these
flying spikes.
That should teach you, my dear.
♪
I'm not sure I understand
what's happening here,
but I won't let this
young lady get hurt,
no matter what the reason.
Why don't you shut up?
'Cause the next one's for you!
You freak!
Don't you talk
to my friends that way!
♪
Kenshin must be winning!
Hiya!
How many times
do I have to tell you?
Gambling is for delinquents!
Don't you ever gamble
when you get older!
Got it?
Okay, already!
Gee whiz.
Kori!
Huh?
They're back!
Me not gamble?
Ha, don't bet on it!
Kenshin, you're back!
Yeah, well, sorry we're so late.
What a rundown place.
Is this really a dojo?
Kenshin, who is that?
Oh, how rude of me.
This is Megumi Takani.
She got in some trouble,
so we decided to help her out.
Oh, much more than that,
Kenshin saved me.
He saved you?
So, in other words,
you met this beautiful girl
and you wanted to show
her around your new pad.
Ha, Kenshin, you sly dog you!
No, that's ridiculous,
it's nothing like that!
Then start talking, Himura!
Let me explain...huh?
He came to my
rescue like a hero.
He's so wonderful.
Kenshin...
I am so disgusted with you,
it's not even funny.
How dare you treat me like this?
You no-good, lousy pig!
Oh, you make me so mad!
♪
Oh, my goodness.
You're so violent.
Kenshin, darling.
Hey, would you mind
explaining to me
what your relationship
is to Kenshin, please?
Well, he is very important
to me because he's going
to protect me from
those evil men.
And what is he to you?
Uh, I, uh--
Well, you couldn't
possibly be his girlfriend.
I mean, no way would
a strong swordsman like him
go for a sweaty,
underdeveloped
tomboy like you.
How dare you call me a tomboy?
Why, you've got a lot of nerve?
Take it easy, Kori!
Please, watch your mouth
when you're talking to Kori.
She's naive and not
as hardened as you,
so don't pick on her.
She's an innocent girl
with an enthusiastic spirit.
Hmm?
What?
Sweetie, you like me
a lot more than that
violent girl,
don't you my strong,
handsome Kenshin?
Kenshin!
Well, you don't understand,
we tried our best!
No, don't do it!
Don't kill us,
we'll do anything!
Come on!
Please, Boss, we won't
fail you next time, I swear!
Just give us another chance!
Please!
Please, let us go!
Have mercy!
It wasn't our fault!
Please, don't do it!
Wait, wait!
(screaming)
I don't know
what it is about me.
Maybe it's my
good business sense?
But I feel I just have
to get rid of things
I have no use for.
I now it's
your territory, Boss,
so please excuse
my butting in.
Yes, I would prefer to handle
the discipline
of the men myself.
Don't undermine my
authority by doing my job.
Of course, I understand.
In any case, I'll be happy
as long as I get Megumi back.
You'll handle that?
Of course I will.
Hannya, where is Megumi Takani?
In a dojo near town.
Good, I want you
to go find Hoko
and then go with Beshimi
and bring her back here.
Yes, Boss.
Beshimi, you understand
the consequences if you
were to fail?
I understand completely.
Just make sure there aren't
any mistakes this time.
If we play our cards right,
she's the hen that will lay
the golden eggs.
This is our last chance
and we can't afford to lose her.
Takeda has about 60 warriors,
the leader of all the warriors
is known as the Boss.
Who's the Boss?
He's second in command
below Takeda, but considers
himself independent
from the operation.
He's formally
a top government spy.
At the age of 16,
just prior to the Restoration,
he became the head spy boss
to protect the Edo castle.
His name is Aoshi Himmo,
he's one of the top spies
in the world
and very dangerous,
but as long as you're here,
I have absolutely nothing
to worry about.
Well, gee, I don't
know about that.
If the spies decide to attack,
even he won't be able to stop
all of them.
I'd better not stay here long.
Megumi, I'm just
a little curious,
why are you running away
from Takeda and his thugs?
I guess you must've
done something
really horrible, huh?
Come on, why won't you tell me?
Because I don't want to.
Don't you know
how rude it is
to ask about a woman's past?
I think I have
a right to know.
(chuckles)
Caught in the act.
You know, Kori,
eavesdropping
isn't very ladylike.
I never thought
a woman like you
would stoop so low.
I can't help it,
I've got to know
what's going on!
Can't you see I'm
a nervous wreck?
How can he spend so much time
alone with her in his room?
I think he likes her a lot!
You know how he is,
Kenshin's very strong
when it comes
to fighting with a sword,
but when it comes
to everyday life
with regular people,
he can be a real pushover,
especially with
women and children.
That's what I'm afraid of.
To be honest, right now,
I really wish he wasn't
that big of a pushover.
What?
Huh, what?
Nothing, nothing, you have
nothing to worry about!
Kenshin thinks she's ugly!
Really ugly!
No, she's beautiful!
Sanosuke, is everything
all right out there?
Just peachy.
I've been doing
some thinking
about the situation.
Since we're dealing with spies,
they probably know
exactly where we are,
so we have to stay
on the lookout
at all costs.
Underworld spies, huh?
Is he talking about ninjas?
This is gonna get dangerous.
♪
I don't wanna scare you,
but we might have serious
trouble headed our way.
I don't know how
many there will be
or when they might get here,
but all of us need
to be prepared.
Kaoru, you've got
nothing to worry about.
You can handle yourself.
Thanks a lot.
No need to fear, Yoshi's here!
What?
Gotcha!
Did I hear the word "trouble"?
Yoshi!
Hey, did you plan
on leaving me out of this?
I'm a member of the Kenshin
Peace Force, too, you know!
The Kenshin Peace Force?
What's that?
That's us!
Let them come with everything
they got, I'm ready for 'em!
I'll take every one
of those slimy ninjas
and turn them
into hamburger meat!
They aren't that tough!
Quit with the hamburger,
you're just a little kid.
Who ya callin' a little kid?
Take it back!
Yoshi, get off
of him right now!
Good grief,
internal discord already?
This Kenshin Peace Force
is more like a bunch of stooges.
-Hmm?
-Huh?
Here they come.
Whoa.
I came here for
a girl named Megumi.
So, hand her over now
or I'm going to get physical
with all of you.
First, tell us
who you are and who sent you.
Demanding, huh?
Well, the Boss sent me
and my name is Hoko.
Now, who's going to try me?
He's huge!
You know what they say,
the bigger they are,
the harder they fall.
Hey, I've got an idea,
leave this one to me.
Just remember,
he works for a top spy.
He's smarter than he looks.
I don't think he's too smart.
His brain is probably
the size of a mustard seed.
Besides, I always
enjoy the chance
for a good bite.
♪
So, you're gonna be first?
You may have very large muscles,
but you're also
a slow clumsy ox!
(chuckling)
♪
Sanosuke!
Huh?
A human flamethrower!
You somehow dodged my
famous Breath of Flames,
but with that
wound on your leg,
you're not going
to get very far!
♪
Indeed, he is
Master of the Flames.
His full written name, Hyottoko,
means "The Man of Fire."
He can burn
anything he wants to.
Didn't your mother
ever teach you not
to play with fire?
My mother?
Yeah, didn't you ever
listen when you were a kid?
Or were you too busy
burning the house down?
I'm gonna barbecue your brain!
You fool.
You don't think
that little sword
is gonna stop me!
It'll melt,
and so will you!
Kenshin!
Where are you going?
That giant is way
too strong for Kenshin.
He'll never win
against those hot flames.
Kenshin is risking everything
for your safety, Megumi.
How dare you walk out
on him when he's fighting
for your freedom?
Believe me,
I'm extremely grateful
for what Yoshi has done for me,
but I'm realistic
and I know that these guys
are merciless.
They might even go
after you and Yoshi.
Well, at least I'm not
going to be a coward
and run away.
Besides,
you underestimate
his great skills.
Kenshin will protect me.
Have gave me his word.
Now, let's stop
playing with fire.
He's dry!
I don't believe it.
I'm not finished yet!
Wait, Kenshin!
What?
I told you I wanna
take care of this joker.
You've forgotten how tough I am.
This small burn won't stop me
from taking this
oversized furnace.
One last mouthful of fuel.
You are gonna get it,
you freak of nature!
I'm gonna burn
you good this time!
♪
The Great Breath of Flame!
No one can withstand it!
♪
I see, Sanosuke.
He's going straight in
quickly and aggressively
to minimize the burn.
This is the best chance
against his flame.
♪
Sano!
So, Hoko, this is how
you did your stupid
little trick.
Huh?
So, what's next?
Is your brain gonna blow up?
I'm not through with you yet!
An easy win.
Ha, take a look in the mirror
and say it was easy.
♪
My gosh, they are so strong.
Who are these
incredible warriors?
Most important of all,
they're my friends.
Are you guys all right?
Oh my, you look terrible!
You're burnt to a crisp.
I'd say he looks medium-rare.
Get lost.
"Friends"?
Megumi, don't forget
I'm one of them, too!
Damn, that stupid idiot
was beaten and defeated
way too easily!
I can't believe we've
blown it a second time!
Yoshi, do you rally
think we have a chance?
Sure, there's no reason
to worry about it.
But how can you be so sure?
It'll all work out.
These problems
are because of that witch!
She'll pay!
No!
Die!
♪
What the...?
Yoshi!
How did you like
that diving move
to stop the spike?
Pretty good, huh?
I told you I was
part of the group,
just like those two!
You don't have
to act so tough for me.
Let me see your arm.
No, don't touch it, it's just
a little scratch anyway.
It'll heal.
Yoshi!
He-he, that was
a very poisonous spike!
That's what the brat deserves
for getting in the way.
That spike is called
the Flying Deadly Spiral
and that kid is going
to be dead within one hour
and there's nothing
you can do to stop it.
He was just for
starters and now...huh?
♪
Huh?
I would never have believed
that in this day and age,
there would still be
a swordsman like you.
Seems I underestimated
your abilities, but one
day soon, I'm sure
we will get to fight.
Until then,
pleasant nightmares!
(cackles)
♪
He'll be trouble.
Yoshi, come on!
Yoshi, wake up,
snap out of it.
I'm going to try
to suck out all the poison.
No, wait a minute.
Why don't you just try
to stay out of things?
It's too late,
the poison has already
entered his bloodstream
and if you suck out
the poison into your mouth,
it could end up
killing you as well.
I know about this
stuff, now move over
and leave this to me!
He's unconscious with a fever,
rapid heart rate,
dilated pupils,
and perspiring.
I think this is poison
from the mandala leaf.
Kori, I'm going to write
you a list of medicine.
I want you to find
the nearest doctor
and have him bring
them here quickly.
Kenshin, get me
a bucket of boiling water,
towels, bandages,
and a first aid kit
as quick as you can.
And you, Sano,
go to the ice shop
and get two large
buckets of ice.
Hurry, don't just sit there!
Stopping this poison
from killing your friend
is a race against time!
Now move!
Okay!
Right away!
Huh?
♪
Hang in there, Yoshi!
Don't die on us,
I'm almost there!
♪
I wish she would hurry
with that medicine.
♪
I'm not sure how much
longer he'll last.
"He thought it was a medication,
but it was actually opium."
♪
I don't trust her.
Why would she be
carrying opium around?
Maybe she's the one
we should be careful of.
♪