♪
(singing in Japanese)
Kaishu Katsu, we are holding
your daughter Itsuko captive.
At the moment, we have no
intention of harming her,
but that may change depending
on your response to this letter.
If you don't do as we ask, we
may have to take drastic action.
We want the money you hid away
just before the
fall of Castle Edo.
And we want you to
deliver it personally.
Signed: Beni Aoi.
♪
Huh?
Any luck?
Did you find Itsuko?
She's disappeared completely.
Without a trace, we've checked
everywhere in the neighborhood.
Huh?
Daigoro!
(panting)
She's not down at
the produce shop.
I'm worried, I can't
imagine where she went.
Something really awful must have
happened to her, I can sense it.
Calm down just a minute.
For all we know, she
went home to her father's.
If that's true, it would
have been nice of her
to tell us where
she was going.
(groans)
I will give it one more try.
Wait a minute, you
can't just run off
when you don't have the first
idea what happened to her.
Take it easy!
Listen, she could
be in big trouble!
Where's Kenshin?
He'll know what to do.
I'm afraid he hasn't
made it back yet.
Now I'm getting worried
about what's happened to him.
(clock ticking)
(ticking echoes)
(beating drums)
We should fight.
That's suicide,
we should negotiate.
It's too late for that,
the army is closing in on us.
We still have options, why
don't we ask France for help?
And have them take over?
That's a stupid suggestion.
Are you calling me stupid?
Watch your tongue,
before I rip it out!
One more word and you won't
have to face the Satsuma army,
because I'll kill you myself!
Stop all this senseless arguing,
it's not going to
solve the problem!
We need to come up with a
plan to marshal our forces
and neutralize
the army's advance!
(clicking)
♪
Katsu.
Yes, my Lord?
♪
What's the situation
in the city of Edo?
There's a general atmosphere
of fear and panic since
the population heard
the news last night
that the Satsuma
army is closing in.
The streets are filled with
people determined to evacuate.
So many loyalists are
trying to escape in boats,
all order has broken down,
and the dock area
is in total chaos.
It's worse than I thought.
Thank you, Katsu.
The Tokugawa era, the world
we knew, is about to end.
That is reality.
We are outnumbered
by our opponents,
and further resistance
would be futile.
I cannot cause more
bloodshed for Edo.
I have failed my people.
Not so, my Lord!
I must end this conflict,
even at the risk
of my own life.
Sire.
I am overwhelmed by
your commitment, Shogun.
I will do everything in my power
to help you carry out this
last noble act of leadership.
Thank you, Katsu.
♪
(crickets chirring)
Mr. Katsu?
Yeh?
Mr. Himura.
♪
"We'll expect you
at 2:00 A.M.
at the Ryougen
temple in Shinagawa."
Beni Aoi.
I'm very sorry, Mr. Katsu.
I guess I didn't
take them seriously.
Don't blame yourself,
I didn't take them
seriously, either,
but I am puzzled.
How did these men
know about the money?
As far as the
government knows,
after the war,
it disappeared.
You mean you do have money
hidden away somewhere?
Quite a bit.
I trust you, and I'm willing
to tell you the truth,
but no one else
knows about this,
including my pupils
and my daughter Itsuko,
and no one must ever know.
♪
This money represents
the personal fortune
of the shogun.
He gave it to me himself.
The last shogun?
Yoshinobu Tokugawa?
Yes, my boy.
We were always
told it was stolen.
Course you were.
Just imagine what would
have happened otherwise.
Master Yoshinobu would
have been tortured
until he told the army
commanders where it was.
So we put out a false story
about thieves breaking in
during the chaos,
and I hid it away.
Events moved
quickly in those days,
and people's
loyalties were suspect.
But the shogun knew
I could be trusted,
and I've never
betrayed him since.
I've been waiting
for the right moment
to put that money to use.
♪
It's been 10 years since
Master Yoshinobu voluntarily
abdicated his
position as shogun.
♪
All during that time,
he's been a prisoner,
kept under house arrest
by the Meiji government.
They're still afraid of
the power his name carries,
and they've made sure
he has no base of support.
And they're right to
fear his influence.
There are many
who would join him
if he were allowed
to reclaim his position.
I want to use that money
to make sure he
is safely released.
The remainder, I'll give back
to him to use as he wishes.
My final act of loyalty.
I understand.
♪
Why don't you let
me come with you?
I might be able to help.
I have to do this alone.
They have taken my
daughter hostage.
Simple honor requires that I be
the one to go in and rescue her.
I thank you for
the offer though.
I can see from your sword
that what it represents,
that you would be
a formidable ally.
I made a vow to never
again be the instrument
of another person's death,
and I've been
true to my oath.
I respect your
refusal to do the same,
although I imagine
the temptation is great.
Overwhelming, but
I'm a stubborn old man.
♪
Better go, just
a few hours left.
Do you have
a plan in mind?
(laughs)
The broad strokes
aren't formulated yet,
much less the details.
But it won't involve
giving them the money
or allowing them to
kill me or my daughter.
That doesn't leave much room
for negotiation, does it?
Not really.
By the way, please don't
say anything to Daigoro.
He's not a brave boy,
but he's very emotional,
and he might decide
to do something rash.
I'm not sure how
this will end,
and I don't want
him to get hurt.
Goodbye.
Hey, Kenshin.
The Kamiya dojo is
the other direction.
You're right,
I was dreaming.
Kenshin, I really wish you'd
taken the time to tell us
you were coming over here.
We were very worried!
Was Miss Itsuko at
home with her father?
We haven't been able to find
her anywhere, is she all right?
Why aren't you answering me?
Something bad has happened
to Miss Itsuko, hasn't it?
But Daigoro,
I can explain it,
but we can't talk here.
Come with me, let's
go sit down somewhere.
♪
Seriously?
She was kidnapped?
Why abduct her?
Her father has no money.
♪
Come on, would you get
a hold of yourself?
This doesn't look good.
I know, I'm just weak.
Well, you could try
a little harder.
The truth is, Mr. Katsu asked me
not to tell you what occurred.
Still, I thought
you ought to know.
He figures I'm powerless
to do anything about it.
I don't think so, Daigoro.
He seemed more concerned
about what could happen
if you tried to do something.
Kenshin, we have to
help get Itsuko back
before something bad happens.
I think we should
go tell the police.
Well, if you want my opinion,
I think that's a bad idea.
How so?
The police train
for matters like this.
Yes, but they're
not impartial.
They've been keeping
an eye on Mr. Katsu.
If they think he's been
hiding the Tokugawa money,
they'll come in
and arrest him.
I think that is the single
reason he is determined
to handle this
problem by himself.
No one's going with him?
Come on, that's suicide!
He's willing
to take that risk,
and it's not our
place to interfere.
For all we know,
he could pull it off.
Or be killed!
Gotta think!
Hey wait, we
still have Tatsuma
if the police are no good.
Yes, but can he be trusted?
He's working for
the Meiji government.
The politicians are
worse than the police.
No, he's been protecting
Mr. Katsu from the government.
He's loyal to the family,
he'll do whatever it
takes to help them.
Believe me, I know he will!
♪
It will all be
over by sunrise.
Trust me, Tatsuma can take
care of this problem without
tipping things off
to the government.
Ugh, I really don't like the
idea of owing a politician
a favor in return.
At this stage, what
other options do we have?
Are you all right with this?
What?
How do you feel
about stepping aside
and letting somebody else go
in and save Itsuko's life?
Well, I...
♪
If we want to reach
Shinagawa by 2:00 AM,
we're gonna have to
leave pretty soon.
What do you think, Kenshin?
Mr. Katsu said for me
to not get involved.
But you've always had
a hearing problem when
it comes to helping
out the underdog.
Oh, well, I guess I'm ready
to be scolded by Mr. Katsu
for interfering
in his business.
I thought you'd feel that way.
Well, you're not going
alone, we're coming too!
I don't suppose I can
talk you out of this.
Don't even think about it!
Wait for us at the dojo,
I'm not gonna miss the fun.
Anyway, I owe this to Itsuko,
she cooked a good meal
for me last week.
You think dry rice
is a good meal.
Aw, what do you know?
You can't even boil water!
Yes I can!
Wait!
I want to...
I want to go with you.
You should give this
some more thought,
I'm not sure
you can handle it,
especially if it turns
out we have to fight.
I'm gonna be all
right, don't worry!
I want to make sure my
friends get home safely.
That's very brave.
Look, I know I don't have
the power of a politician
or the sword skills
of any of you,
but I can't let someone else
fight my battles for me.
It's just wrong!
It's a matter of honor.
I'm ashamed of
the way I reacted.
A friend of mine
is in great danger,
and I don't think about
rescuing her myself,
I think about getting
someone else to do it.
I can see why you wouldn't
want me to come along with you.
♪
We mistakenly assumed we
were doing this to protect you.
We were wrong, we should
have given you more credit.
You just demonstrated
how brave you are.
Please come with us.
Thank you, Kaoru.
Yeah, let's go!
We'll rescue Itsuko together!
Yes!
Well, then, there's
no time to waste.
Kenshin, you wait here,
I'm going to go to the dojo
to change clothes and
pick up some weapons,
I'll be right back!
Hey, I need some stuff
too, come with me Daigoro!
I'm right behind you!
♪
Come on, Satsuma, let your
hair down a little bit.
Why don't you have
a drink and relax?
Thank you, I think I will.
There you go,
it's strong stuff,
but it looks like
you can handle it.
By the way, how is
Mr. Katsu doing?
He is doing very well.
That's good,
I imagine the recent incident
regarding the military fund
for Saigo must have been
very upsetting for him.
I know you were
pretty shaken up by it.
You're right about that.
By the way, thanks so much
for helping us out that time.
You don't have to
thank me, my boy,
it was a pleasure
to be of assistance.
I was convinced it was
nothing but a big mistake.
Mr. Katsu is
a very wise man,
and here you were,
studying under him.
You must have gotten quite
an education, you lucky dog.
Yes.
I'm glad to see you've become
a student of
governmental procedure.
We need more young bucks like
yourself to give the system
an overhaul, and bring
us into the modern age.
I have great
expectations
for you, my boy.
That's kind of you,
I plan to work very hard
to meet those expectations.
I believe you will.
I want you to meet some people
who would be very helpful.
I think we should put
you on the fast track
as soon as possible.
Can I quote you on that?
Officially?
I can see you're
already learning
to swim with the sharks.
That's good.
It shows you're not a fool.
♪
Innkeeper!
Bring more sake
for my friend, here.
♪
Daigoro, Daigoro!
Oh, Daigoro, sleeping
on the job again.
♪
I see you haven't
gotten very far.
Don't be too hard on him Itsuko,
he was studying
pretty late last night.
Tatsuma!
Good morning, Itsuko.
It's good to see that Daigoro is
applying himself to his studies,
but he's taking a long time
to get with the program.
I hope he'll be a credit
to the sensei someday.
I'm certain he will.
With time, he will mature and
he will take his place here.
But I must admit, I am
enjoying his exuberance.
The best thing about this era
is that young people are free
to live their lives to
pursue their own happiness
without interference.
And even if I'm
not here to see it,
that's a very good sign for
the future of our country.
Hearing you speak
like that, Father,
you'd think you were
about to pass away.
The truth is, you're in
the prime of your life.
You're active and vigorous!
She's right, you know.
Now, don't you
two worry about me,
I plan to live for
a good long time.
Daigoro?
I see you're awake.
Who are you?
And where are we?
I am the leader
of the Beni Aoi,
a group you're
not familiar with,
and this is
a temple in Shinagawa.
Why did you bring me here?
What do you want with me?
(whimpers)
We have no intention
of harming you,
as long as you
don't try to escape,
you will not be tied up.
Once you've served
your purpose,
you will be released.
What purpose is that?
To bring your father...
Kaishu Katsu.
Why are you trying to
bring my father here?
To kill him.
Why?
♪
All the people here used
to be vassals of the shogun,
proud warriors,
masters of the land,
now reduced to pitiful beggars.
Without hope, we simply
exist, waiting to die.
It's the Meiji legacy.
♪
They took away
everything we had
and threw our families
into the street.
♪
We were exiled to the
most desolate outposts,
and our family members either
escaped to other countries,
or died in despair.
♪
We all knew who was
responsible for our adversity,
and we swore revenge.
♪
One man, more than any other,
talked the shogun into
giving up without a fight.
He forced us to surrender.
Are you blaming my father?
How can you?
The man was
trying to save them!
He knew the army was
going to kill everyone!
Your father
accomplished his goal.
We followed the order
because we were told
that this was what
the shogun wanted.
As a result, Edo was saved.
Then why are
you doing this?
Because we found out
later that this was not
what the shogun had wanted.
What?
We were able to
discover the truth,
that Katsu misled
us out of greed!
In order to save his own life
and gain control over
the Tokugawa fortune,
he lied to master Yoshinobu
and convinced him to surrender.
That's a filthy lie,
you have no proof!
Then why does Katsu control a
secret stash of Tokugawa money?
Huh?
The Meiji government
is about to move in
and find the cash
and confiscate it.
Oh my God.
There's no choice now.
For our honor and for
the future of our movement,
Kaishu Katsu has to be killed.
And what will you
accomplish by doing that?
We'll be able to reverse
the Meiji restoration.
Killing my father will
topple the government?
Before he dies, he will
turn over the Tokugawa fortune
and we will use that money
to start a revolution.
♪
We will put our
master back in power.
Then we will take
revenge on our oppressors!
♪
That is the ultimate
goal of the Beni Aoi.
Your father should
arrive here very soon.
♪
What do you think?
How about launching
a surprise attack?
Are you crazy?
How about finding out how
many people are in there,
first of all?
Worried you can't handle it?
I can handle you!
Quiet you nincompoops,
you're gonna give us away!
You know, I don't see
Mr. Katsu anywhere.
First thing we should find out
is what part of he shrine
they're keeping Itsuko in,
and how many men we're facing.
♪
I can do this.
Calm down, now.
When things get
going, you'll be fine.
Okay.
♪
(shrieks)
Daigoro, don't!
(yelling)
Don't touch her!
Daigoro, come back!
Leave her alone, you brute!
Daigoro!
Stay balanced!
(screaming)
(groans)
♪
(shrieks)
No, you cowards!
Daigoro, no!
♪
Daigoro!
(singing in Japanese)
♪