♪
(singing in foreign language)
It's time for you to
meet your next opponent.
Do you have any idea
who's behind that door?
No, gimme a hint.
I believe it's Sojiro.
There's nobody else left.
I knew it was only
a matter of time.
He's the one who split
my Reversed-Edge Sword.
You better be on guard.
I wouldn't worry,
I know his moves.
Are you ready, gentlemen?
This new Reversed-Edge Sword
and the obstacles
I have overcome
will give me the leverage
I need to defeat him.
I will not let him
get the best of me.
Open up the door.
Sojiro's an adept assailant
and I'm looking forward to
the opportunity to be
able to compete with him.
♪
Kenshin, how nice
it is to see you again.
♪
It's been a long time,
I must say, but I'm glad
you made it here safely.
What a surprise.
I thought he'd be
a big monster of a guy,
but he's just
a dinky little kid.
He isn't even as big as Kenshin.
That was a gracious welcome,
but I don't have time
for idle nonsense.
So, let's just forget about
exchanging idiotic pleasantries
and get down to the
business at hand, shall we?
What do you have in mind?
Are you planning to fight
or would you like to retreat?
Relax, if you're worried
about getting back in time
to help your friends in Aoiya,
there's no need to rush.
I've just been informed
that the Juppongatana
has been completely
defeated over there.
What was that?
I'm sorry to say
that it's a fact.
Hoji and Shishio were as
astonished as any of us.
It seems that your allies
apparently caught
us by surprise.
So, in actuality,
I'm the one that doesn't
have any time
to waste sitting around.
The reason is
they're counting on me.
I'm the one that's
left to do the work
of all 10 Juppongatana and I'm
going to carry out my mission.
First, I'm going
to take care of you,
then I'm going
to decimate your comrades.
Let's get started, shall we?
♪
This is just like
what happened back
at the Shingetsu village.
♪
They're going to fight.
Go, Sojiro.
♪
He's even faster
than the last time,
but luckily,
my new Reversed-Edge Sword
has performed up
to my expectations.
I have to
concentrate my hardest.
Sojiro may look like a kid,
but he has the fighting ability
of a giant.
He's cracked his sword!
It's only a small crack.
That thing won't
make any difference.
Just keep fighting!
That's strange.
My sword has never
been cracked before.
It is obvious that I am
at a distinct disadvantage.
I'm afraid my old standby
won't be capable of matching up
to your much more
superior weapon.
Sojiro, your sword
is just as efficient as his.
It's probably better.
In order to determine
a sword's performance,
it depends on which
person is using it.
One small crack
in the sword's blade
can ultimately mean
the difference between
a glorious victory
or an agonizing defeat.
I wasn't there at your
last battle with Kenshin,
but one thing I do know
is when it comes
to Batto technique,
absolutely no one
surpasses Kenshin.
Yeah.
Ah, Kenshin,
your technique
has improved quite dramatically
since the last time we met.
I have to admit,
I'm very impressed,
and yet, I am perplexed.
It makes me wonder
how someone like you
can have so much power.
It just doesn't make
a whole lot of sense.
Oh well, I can't be distracted
by these petty details.
Maybe, if I put my mind to it,
I can get lucky
and win this little spat!
♪
Huh?
That's amazing!
His footwork is
so lightning-fast
I can't even see it!
I'm beginning to believe
that that's why Sojiro
was able to assassinate Okubo
while his carriage was still
in motion.
How come he got away from me?
I must've made a mistake.
That's all right.
I'll try a little harder.
Sojiro is very fast.
In fact, I think he's
almost as fast as Kenshin,
but it's hard to tell.
Unless my eyes
are deceiving me,
I think that he
could be even faster.
That would certainly
be an astounding feat
if it were true,
but it can't be!
There's isn't anyone
on this Earth that's
as fast as Kenshin!
It's not possible!
This has gotta be an illusion.
How do you think he does it?
Huh?
I don't know, don't ask me.
Ugh, you've been going on
and on about how
incredibly strong he is!
How the hell could you not know?
I'm telling the truth.
I said that because Shishio
was bragging about the runt,
but this is the first time
I've seen Sojiro fight.
Well, I don't believe you!
I think you know
a lot more than you let on!
Oh, yeah?
Why don't you go suck an egg?
Shukuchi.
Huh?
What you were practicing
just now is Shukuchi.
It's an even faster
technique than Shinsoku,
am I correct?
So, you're aware of
the Shukuchi technique?
Well, I've gotta say,
I'm very impressed.
Shishio told me
about this method.
Before then,
I'd never even heard of it.
Shukuchi, huh?
That sounds very interesting.
Evidently, that's Sojiro's
third element of power.
The first two being
his Heavenly Sword
and, of course,
his complete lack of emotion.
Yes, that's right.
The Shukuchi technique
requires powerful footwork.
Sojiro is able
to reach maximum speed
from the very first step,
similar to how a magician
goes about creating an illusion.
Each time he steps,
he disappears into thin air.
He can jump from one point
to the other without ever
being seen.
So, what you're saying is
Shukuchi means speed
that cannot be detected
with the naked eye,
is that right?
Not exactly.
What you're thinking of
resembles Battousai's
Shinsoku technique.
Sojiro's ultra-fast movement
cannot be detected period.
That's what makes
a far more superior method.
It's quite simple:
Battousai fights
by reading emotions
and when those
emotions don't exist
or don't manifest themselves,
it's impossible to detect them.
So, there's just about nothing
Battousai can do about it,
no matter how much he tries,
because Sojiro will always have
a big advantage.
Sojiro may be a kid,
but his lightning-fast speed
will win out, you'll see.
That means Battousai's chances
of surviving
this competition are--
Absolutely zero.
(cackles)
Do you know what, Kenshin?
The move I made
wasn't really Shukuchi,
it was actually a bit slower.
That's probably why you were
able to detect my motions
and avoid me.
Huh?
I obviously
underestimated your capability.
I must do better next time.
You see, I was remembering
your speed when we met back
in Shingetsu village.
You didn't seem
to be that fast at the time
and I wanted to save
my energy for the fights ahead.
I thought it would
be sufficient,
but I was wrong.
You've improved
significantly since then.
However, I feel I'm able
to live up to the challenge now.
This time, my feet will be
even faster than the speed
of light!
♪
Concentrate, Kenshin!
Otherwise, you're gonna die!
♪
Ouch!
I really think he is moving
as fast as the speed of light.
His technique is not
limited to his footwork alone.
His body is able to move
equally fast as well,
and he shows no
emotion whatsoever.
That makes it hard
to determine his next move.
He just appears to be quicker,
but I can't get distracted.
I have to counteract
by intercepting him
when he least expects it.
That's the only way
I'm gonna overtake him.
Hakuji!
Nine-Headed Dragon Light!
♪
He made it out!
No, the kill is yet to come.
♪
This can't be happening.
How do I get out of this?
Think, Kenshin, think!
♪
How do I get out of this?
Think, Kenshin, think!
(grunting)
♪
He dodged my countermove.
Is it possible that
Sojiro's technique
is indeed faster than
the Hiten Mitsurugi style?
I must congratulate you,
my friend, your move was
successful this time,
but I'm giving you fair warning
that I'm not gonna
let you beat me!
You hear me?
Kenshin!
That kid's quick,
I hope Kenshin knows
what he's doing.
You ready?
I hope Kenshin
has enough strength
to finish him.
Sojiro definitely has
the upper hand over Battousai.
What a stroke
of luck for our side!
All it would take
is one good blow.
That should be
enough to kill him.
Then, we will be rid
of that scourge forever.
That's weird,
I thought I had you.
Something must've
gone terribly wrong,
but what was it?
♪
Oh, I'm not quite
sure what to do next.
(gasps)
I realize that I messed up
the first time, but then,
the second time, I was certain
I had you under my grasp.
I just don't understand
what it was I did wrong.
This is really confusing.
I'm at a loss.
Kenshin, go get him now!
Pop that little weasel
before he comes to his senses!
Come on, Sojiro, do your
analyzing later, will ya?
Get off your cloud
and get the job done!
This is odd, I'm positive
I did it like I was supposed to.
Hmm.
It's simply a basic
rule of human nature,
the meek shall perish
and the strong will survive.
It's vital that Kenshin Himura
reveal his true nature
as Battousai the Slasher
and we must see that he does.
Battousai is extremely complex.
There's more to his character
than just strength alone.
Sojiro!
This is no time to sleep,
what are you doing?
Stupid fool.
What?
How dare you call
me a stupid fool?
You have some nerve
calling me names!
Oh, would you calm down?
You're not the person
I was talking about, Yumi.
Then who were you talking about?
I was just remembering something
that a man named
Senkaku once said to me.
Senkaku?
What's this about Senkaku?
Who's that?
Speak up, Sojiro!
What in the world
does he have to do
with this anyway?
Tell us about it.
♪
It's up to you to stop him.
May I be so bold
as to ask you something?
When you were
fighting with Senkaku,
why did you display
your secret weapon?
What are you talking about?
You displayed your move
in front of Shishio
and almost gave it away.
What is the matter
with you, Sojiro?
Are you dumb or
you just don't get it?
This is gonna be hard
for a squirt like you
to understand, but Shishio
threatened Senkaku.
He told him that if
he lost the fight
without getting
Kenshin to display
at least one
of his techniques
that he would kill him
and that's why Kenshin
showed it to him.
Kenshin showed compassion even
though the man was an enemy.
I guess you might say
he's just that kinda guy.
Sano.
I don't know, I think you
should have killed Senkaku
right then and there.
When you spared his life,
I'm afraid you did him
a major disservice.
After you left him,
he began speaking
very strangely.
He almost seemed like
he was heading towards
the brink of insanity.
Tell me more about it.
I'm sorry, Kenshin, I don't
have any more time to waste.
This time, I'm not
making any mistakes,
so be prepared.
Kenshin, watch out!
You better slaughter him
this time, you hear?
I'm gonna be faster than ever.
♪
He's quick, but he's not
as stable as the last time.
I wonder what could
be distracting him?
Huh?
You should have killed
Senkaku, Kenshin.
That was your job
and you failed miserably,
so now, you must pay the price.
The fact that you
didn't kill him
doesn't make any
sense to me at all.
That's why you're going to die.
♪
(chuckling)
Is that you, Sojiro?
Right here in
the flesh, Senkaku.
♪
Have you come here to kill me?
No, I have not.
Shishio said that since
you know nothing about us,
there would be no need
to eliminate you,
although I find it
rather hard to understand.
Senkaku, I am puzzled.
Why are you still
alive after you lost
to Kenshin Himura?
Huh?
Come on, let's hear it.
I really wanna know.
I was surprised myself
that he didn't attempt
to finish me.
If it hadn't been
for Kenshin's kindness
and mercy, I would've
been dead by now.
Shishio would've killed me
and I would've found myself
floating around on
a river full of blood.
But this whole experience
has taught me something
about the value of life.
It's been an extremely
important lesson.
I'm glad I'm alive.
Battousai's not merely
physically strong,
his mind is powerful as well.
He doesn't force others
to follow him by using fear
or threats like Shishio
and I really respect him
for that.
Kenshin's inability to kill
is a sign of weakness to me.
I find it hard to understand
this concept of compassion.
What keeps him from doing it?
Why won't he kill?
(gasps)
♪
"The meek shall perish
and the strong will survive.
It's just human nature."
Shishio is right.
Sympathy and compassion cannot
exist in this vicious world.
You are the one
who is mistaken, Himura.
♪
Kenshin!
Come on!
Missed him again!
Oh, no!
Kenshin, are you all right?
Sojiro, I see that your
concentration is off.
What's causing you
to become distracted?
Something is bothering you
deep inside, isn't it?
Whatever it is, it's
preventing you from killing me,
so it has to be
of some great importance.
♪
And just who are you
to tell me how I feel?
Are you a fortune teller?
I really don't understand.
Why is it that you spare
the lives of all your opponents?
It doesn't make sense.
How can you expect
to survive with that philosophy?
You have to be tough
to make it in the world.
That's life, get used to it.
I've had enough of this!
What's there to understand,
you bloodthirsty little creep?
You are an excellent swordsman,
but in the real
world called life,
you're a fool!
You don't even know
what it means to be tough!
There's a lot more
involved than brute force,
but you wouldn't know
about that, would you?
And Kenshin made those kinds
of decisions because he wanted
people weaker than himself
to have the chance to live
happier lives!
That's why he fought
so long risking his life!
What's the point
of fighting for the weak?
They'd be happier dead.
I think the whole
philosophy is stupid.
Sojiro!
What do we need weak people for?
They will always
be crushed by stronger powers.
I'm never gonna figure it out.
Not killing, that's weak.
I think you're insane.
What's that?
Why you--
The concept
of not killing people
seems to bother
you a lot, Sojiro.
I believe that it must
be eating you alive inside
and that's why you've lost
your ability to concentrate.
It can't be anything else.
A man who can cause people
to suffer and die without
any hesitation wouldn't be so
interested in talking about it.
Deep in your heart,
you know this is true,
but you won't allow
your real feelings to come out.
I think you're afraid to.
Sojiro's eyes
have changed color.
Could it be anger?
No, that would be impossible.
He doesn't have the ability
to register emotions.
But could it be that Kenshin's
breaking him down and making him
realize that he's a human
being like the rest of us?
If he succeeds in his efforts
to turn Sojiro around,
then our side will be lost.
Kenshin, don't worry yourself
about how I'm feeling.
You have the problem.
Get ready to meet your doom.
I am going to kill you.
♪
What's the matter now, Sojiro?
Sorry, it's my shoelace.
I hope you don't mind
if we take a little break.
I have to see if I
can find a replacement.
I'll be right back.
-Huh?
Don't worry, there should
be one around here somewhere.
Kenshin, why didn't
you attack him?
Come on, what are
you waiting for?
Are you gonna let that little
pipsqueak get away with this?
Sano, would you calm down?
You sound exactly like Saito.
I do not, do I?
I needed a break anyway.
Besides, the poor kid
really needs to get
his head together.
Sano, why don't
you cool off a little
and help me dress my wounds?
Yeah, sure.
Ow, Kori, would you stop that?
It really hurts!
Knock it off!
Hold still!
It's exactly right,
now don't get yourself
worked up.
You're gonna be fine.
It's pretty pitiful
when you have to be
taken care of by the enemy.
It's embarrassing;
I've never been so humiliated.
No, that's nonsense.
Anyone that's hurt
in battle deserves first aid
and you needed help.
I guess I should
appreciate your help,
but it doesn't get rid
of the pain of defeat.
I'll never convince Shishio
to make me his number one
person in battle because
I've lost all his respect.
♪
Sojiro is definitely
an excellent fighter.
Anybody else besides yourself
would have collapsed trying
to face him.
Lemme ask you something, Sano.
What?
It's about Sojiro.
Do you really think
it's possible for him
to be incapable of expressing
or feeling emotions?
Can anyone be that inhuman?
It's possible,
but very unlikely.
Besides, I really believe
that you got to him this time.
It's kinda difficult to explain,
but when I looked into his face,
I could tell something
was troubling him somehow.
Well, it's just that
I was remembering
when I was in battle
with Saizuchi.
At one point, I dropped my guard
and returned to being Battousai.
I think that Sojiro's having
a similar experience as well.
How so?
Perhaps Sojiro's not
the monster he appears to be.
You just may be right.
I think that something
must have happened to him
a long time ago
that's caused him
to keep his emotions
from coming to the surface.
He's gonna have
to face his fears.
He can't keep them
sealed up inside of him.
When he realizes this,
he'll become
an even better fighter.
Hopefully, Sojiro will be able
to understand that, Kenshin,
and then somehow, his feelings
will gradually come back.
Why didn't you kill him
when you had the chance?
And what are you
doing down there?
This is no time
to tie your shoes!
It's really funny.
I never expected
this fight to go so badly.
But I'm sticking to my guns:
I refuse to believe
that Kenshin is right.
Oh, come on, Sojiro.
I'll never forget the words
that Shishio told me:
"If you're strong,
you'll survive,
and if you're weak,
you will perish."
♪
My only wish is to go back,
back to where it all began.
If only it were possible.
Yes, if only it were possible.
♪
(singing in foreign language)