♪
(singing in foreign language)
(rapid firing)
♪
What is it?
His speed's the same,
but he's different.
It's his attitude.
He's never been like this.
So intense.
There's a truth I have
accepted all these years.
If you're strong, you live.
If you're weak, you die.
It's a simple philosophy
Mr. Shishio taught me,
along with my sword technique,
and it has protected me.
It is my strength of will
that'll defeat Kenshin.
You're wrong about me.
I have no doubts,
and I'll prove it.
♪
He's letting his emotions show.
Kenshin can read his moves.
Sojiro.
♪
He's lost.
Why are you hesitating, Himura?
Let's face it, you can't win
unless you've finished me off.
I don't wanna hurt you,
and you know what?
I don't think that you
wanna hurt me either, really.
You try to cover it up,
but underneath all that bluster,
I think you're just
a scared little kid.
Bullies like you aren't born,
they're made.
I can see you've been influenced
by the wrong teacher,
but it's not too late.
If you wanna change, I can help.
Just try to keep an open mind.
First you have to accept
that you're on the wrong path.
Then you have
to face your fears.
You've used your
anger as a weapon,
when, in fact, you never really
wanted to hurt anyone
in the first place.
Sojiro, am I getting
through to you?
Sojiro?
(rain falling)
If you're strong, you live.
And if you're weak, you die.
Is it possible that this lesson,
which is the basis
of Mr. Shishio's philosophy,
isn't really true?
According to my sensei,
any uncertainty or sympathy
when facing an opponent
is a fatal error.
That's why I never
questioned any of his orders
and just carried
out my missions.
The truth is, though,
Himura's right.
I killed people when
I didn't really want to.
But I can't stop now.
I have nowhere to go
and nobody to guide me.
How can I function?
I feel like I'm being
ripped in half by two horses.
(screaming)
♪
Sojiro.
He's falling apart.
(crying)
♪
I reject you!
I know your game.
♪
You're trying
to confuse me.
You know I can beat you
so you're messin' with my head,
hoping I'll slip up
and make a mistake.
It's not gonna work,
I see through your plan.
♪
You almost had me fooled.
Very smart.
(panting)
Now, no matter what you say,
I'm gonna kill you.
♪
You ready to die?
This is it.
Say goodbye.
Your time is up.
♪
I sure hope Kenshin
can handle him.
This boy has
an unorthodox technique,
but more than that
I'm very concerned
about his lightning speed.
I'm going to take pity
on you, Mr. Himura.
I'm going to kill you fast.
I'll use my
Quick Heaven technique.
I assure you,
you won't feel any pain.
How polite of you, Sojiro.
I suppose you
expect me to thank you,
but you'll pardon me if I don't.
You see, I have
a plan of my own,
and it doesn't involve my death.
In fact, I'm even wondering
if you can carry out your plan,
considering how well
you'll need to perform.
I don't plan to just
stand here, ya know.
Yeah, so what?
I'm not worried.
Whether you fight or not,
the outcome will be the same.
I don't know how
Kenshin stays so cool.
He's the best
warrior I've ever seen.
But this kid, Sojiro,
moves like he's possessed.
If it was me standing there,
I don't think
I could act so confident.
He must see something I don't.
To me, this kid's
as lethal as a snake.
You're supposed to be good,
but I'm younger
and my reflexes are faster.
That's life,
or, in your case, that's death.
No one maintains
their edge forever.
It's time to retire,
you old man.
I see.
Well, in that case.
I won't be needing this.
♪
He's not giving up.
He's positioning himself.
Yes, he's going to pull
his sword Batto style.
(unintelligible).
There's only one strategy
he could be planning.
He's gonna try and
fake the kid out.
♪
So come on.
That's it?
Why are you surprised?
You're right.
I can't live forever.
All I can say is,
whatever you're gonna do
make it quick.
Let's see if you're
really as good as you claim.
Believe me, I am.
I respect your courage
in accepting the inevitable.
He really thinks
Kenshin's giving up.
He's got to learn.
It's the only way.
There is much about
Mr. Himura that I admire,
but the old must
make way for the new.
His oath not to kill again
proves that he's weak.
It's just as Mr. Shishio says,
only the strong survive.
Himura's death will prove
he was right all along.
♪
It's showtime.
His speed's amazing.
I can't follow him.
Himura's just as fast.
I knew Kenshin would fight back.
I only hope
his strategy pays off.
(screaming)
♪
(sharp ringing)
Are you all right, Kenshin?
(gasping)
What about Sojiro?
(grunts)
I guess my technique
isn't as good as I thought.
Perhaps my philosophy
is flawed, as well.
I can't believe that
a man devoted to nonviolence
could be this strong against me
in a face off, one-to-one.
Apparently, I've been
wrong about everything.
Don't say that.
It's not true.
A building's only as
strong as its foundation,
and mine is real defective.
I see it clearly now.
Real strength doesn't come
from your ability with a weapon.
It comes from being true
to your inner voice.
I ignored that inner voice
all these years,
and now I have to pay a price.
I guess I'll have to find
the path to start over.
Will you act as
my guide, Mr. Himura?
♪
I'm sorry, Sojiro.
It's not as simple
as having someone tell you
this is right or that is wrong.
That's how you got in
trouble in the first place.
You see now that the toughest
warriors in this life
are not necessarily the ones
with the greatest strength
or even the ones
with the fastest reflexes.
The toughest warriors
are those who have the willpower
to put down their swords
and find a more
constructive answer
to life's challenges.
I can't provide that answer.
You'll discover it for yourself
as you make your way
in the world.
♪
Like you did.
I understand, Kenshin.
♪
You will be my role model.
(whimpering)
I promise I'll do my best.
Someday I hope
you will be proud of me.
But more than that,
I hope I'll be proud of me.
I have a feeling you will.
♪
(panting)
(grunting)
Hey, you don't
look so good, Aoshi.
Who's there?
Saito?
♪
I haven't seen you since
that time at the Kamiya dojo.
Just what do you want?
Battousai isn't here,
he left a long time ago.
That's a filthy habit.
I thought you were
going to fight him
in a final confrontation.
Oh, I will fight him
and beat him.
In fact, everything's
proceeding according to plan.
What do you mean?
♪
Why, this is a blueprint
of Shishio's hideout.
How did you get this?
Oh, come now, Aoshi.
I have my ways.
The Oni gang isn't
the only organization
with intelligence-
gathering capabilities.
It's our business
to know what's happening.
That's why I'm a member
of the secret police.
Once Battousai leads us
to the location
and eliminates Shishio,
we'll move in and destroy
what's left of his gang.
So you're going to use Battousai
to do your dirty work,
so you can step up
and claim all the glory.
Yeah.
That's pretty much how it'll go.
There's only one problem.
You've wanted to have
a final confrontation
with Battousai yourself.
How will that ever get resolved
if he loses the fight
with Shishio and gets killed?
Hmm...in that case,
I suppose I'll have
to beat Shishio myself,
and as the last man standing,
obviously I'll be the winner.
Thanks to your continuing
battles with Battousai,
I'm in a position to take
advantage of that opportunity
if and when the time comes.
See you around.
What a slime bucket
you are, Saito.
You know you can't defeat
Battousai head-to-head,
so you set it up for
someone else to step in
and take care of him for you.
It's just the kind
of low-life strategy
I'd expect from the former
head of the Shinsen patrol.
But you may have
outsmarted yourself.
I'll put my money on
Battousai against Shishio,
and when he finally
does face you,
we'll see what kind
of man you really are.
(footsteps pounding)
You think Sojiro
will be all right?
Yeah, those were
superficial wounds.
His life's not really in danger.
I'm not talking
about his wounds, Sano.
I know, I really think
you did the kid
a big favor, Kenshin.
He would have
ended up as a street thug
if you hadn't stepped in.
♪
At least now he has a future
if he can resist Shishio.
That's the question, isn't it?
Does he have the strength
to cut those ties?
♪
Sojiro, I have to go.
Are you feeling well enough
to get along by yourself?
Yes, I'm all right,
but I want you to do me a favor.
Go through the secret
passage in back,
and give Shishio
a message from me.
It's about the way Himura
sets up for an attack.
I hope it saves his life.
It's the least I can do
after what he's done for me.
It's an easy tip.
When they fight,
tell him to keep an eye
on Himura's left foot.
I'm sorry, Sojiro,
I don't understand.
♪
The left foot?
Yes.
It's so obvious.
I wish I'd reacted faster.
Oh, well.
♪
-He led with his left foot?
-Mm-hm.
The Batto fight technique
can be very complex,
but there's
a reason for every move.
When pulling your sword,
you usually put
your right leg forward,
so you don't
accidentally cut yourself.
But Himura put his
left leg forward instead.
And he added a little twist,
so that not only would
he avoid cutting his leg,
he would also increase
his acceleration and weight.
It's a brilliant improvisation.
It must have taken him
years to perfect it.
It increases his speed
by a factor of ten.
No way.
In just one step?
Oh, yes.
But that one step
is hard to accomplish.
The correct state of mind
is very important.
If you don't have a
positive attitude about life,
you won't be able to do it.
Believe me, I know
what I'm talking about.
I tried for years
to incorporate that move,
but something inside of me
just kept resisting it.
Deep down, I never
had enough confidence.
Really?
But you were able to determine
when Himura was about to do it.
So you're warning Shishio?
(grunts)
Just think of it as
my farewell gift to him.
I don't want him to get hurt
when he fights Battousai.
So listen,
Himura's eyes and arms
are not important here.
He can't make this move
without first putting
his left foot forward.
When Shishio sees
that happening,
he should be able
to anticipate the maneuver.
I'd better go warn Shishio now.
Hold on a minute, Yumi.
I know you're in a hurry,
but I have one more
favor to ask of you.
It's beautiful.
♪
It's the sword Mr. Shishio
gave me a long time ago.
It's precious to me.
It's been my treasure
for the last ten years,
but now it's time
to return this sword
to its rightful owner.
Sojiro.
He'd want you to keep it.
When I was about to be
killed a few years back.
Mr. Shishio stepped in
with this sword to protect me.
I'll never forget that.
He gave me my life.
♪
Now I'm about
to betray that loyalty
by deserting him at the moment
when he needs me most.
I'm going off to find
the truth of my life,
just as Mr. Himura suggested.
Do you understand, Yumi?
I can't keep this sword.
I can't.
I have to be free.
♪
I see.
I'll tell Shishio.
For now, this is something
you have to do.
♪
Thank you for understanding.
Don't let anyone hurt him.
It's all right, don't worry.
He really doesn't
need protection.
He's stronger than both of us.
That's not what I meant.
Ah.
I get it now.
♪
Goodbye.
Take care of yourself.
(door sliding)
♪
Goodbye, Mr. Shishio.
(rain falling)
That's what he said?
It's a farewell gift?
He must have been
too ashamed to face me
after he lost to Himura.
I should have anticipated this.
Ah, it's obvious
I'm the only one
who can defeat Battousai.
All right, I'm
ready to face him.
If I hadn't done
this in the first place,
we wouldn't be in this position.
I don't know how
Battousai does it,
since he's vowed
not to kill anyone.
But I'm not restricted
by such an oath.
And when this battle's over,
nothing will stand in the way
of our complete domination
of this country.
We'll be the masters of Japan.
Facing Battousai
has got me as excited
as taking over this government!
Yes, I share your enthusiasm,
but we have practical problems.
Most of our soldiers
have been arrested.
And the Juppongatana
has almost been destroyed.
In assessing the damage,
it appears that our timetable
has been set back
by a number of years.
Don't be so concerned.
Yes, we've lost a few battles,
but as long as I'm alive,
we're in business.
Ahhh!
He's right.
I don't know why I let
myself get so depressed.
He's the most brilliant
tactician I've ever seen!
Always a step ahead
of his enemies.
If he said he could make
the sun rise in the west,
I'd believe it!
This country needs
a strong leader,
and no one is more
qualified than Shishio.
I'll do whatever it takes
to put him in power.
I swear it!
(running and panting)
It's a dead end!
This must be
Shishio's stronghold.
Stay with me, Kenshin,
'cause I'm breaking on through
to the other side.
(screaming)
Huh?
I've been waiting for you.
What was the big delay?
Ah, how'd you get here so fast?
Mr. Shishio says he'll meet
you both in the fighting room.
Come along with me.
Well, that's perfect, lady,
'cause that's
exactly why we're here.
You ready to face him?
Yeah.
All right, then.
(groans)
What's that?
I'm okay, don't worry.
Let's go get him.
Maybe you'd like
to meet some other time?
What?!
After all, you've had
a couple of major fights today.
I'm just saying that you
might not be at your best.
He's all right.
I'll make you a deal.
You can leave if you want to,
just promise me you'll
leave Mr. Shishio alone.
I'll tell him you
couldn't find the hideout,
got discouraged, and went home.
Think about it.
It's not a bad offer.
Everyone saves face,
and you can fight later
if you're up to it.
Thank you, Yumi.
You're a very caring person.
♪
I can see you're worried
about the outcome
of this battle.
After all, Mr. Shishio could
very well lose his life.
He's a very lucky man.
Not everyone has
a guardian angel
so vigilantly
watching over them.
Hm, you're shortsighted
and stupid, Himura.
You could lose, you know.
♪
-You ready?
-Uh-huh.
Don't forget what I said.
This is gonna be
a fight to the finish
between me and Shishio.
No matter what happens,
I don't want you to interfere.
You understand?
♪
-All right?
-All right.
Whatever you say.
You're a good friend.
♪
But no matter what I promised,
I'm not gonna let you die here.
I wouldn't be able to live
with myself otherwise.
Yoshi and Kori
need you too much,
and they're not the only ones.
There are a lot
of people in this country
who depend on you
for guidance and protection.
Call me what you like.
If I feel you're in danger
of losing your life,
I'm gonna step in and save you.
There's too much at stake.
That's my vow, Kenshin,
and I will put everything
I've got behind it.
♪
(pocket watch ticking)
(echoing thud)
This is as far as I can go.
Behind this door
is a fighting arena.
It's where Shishio's
been waiting for you.
A final warning, once you
pass through these doors,
there's no escape.
Ready?
♪
(chain rattling)
(laughing maniacally)
♪
(singing in foreign language)