♪
(roars)
Now I'm gonna kill you!
Ahh!
Huh?
Hi-ya!
(laughing)
Hiten Mitsurugi style!
Ahh!
(yelling)
Ugh.
♪
Whoa.
I know Himura's martial arts
are really special,
but what he just did
to Senkaku was super.
Here's my idea:
It's best we stay put here
until we can help the situation.
It's a better idea
that you two come
out into the open.
Wha-ahh!
Oh!
Now, you two are able
to see things a lot better.
What are you two doing here?
Really, they're merely
a distraction, Battousai.
Let us review your choices
during this little skirmish
with Senkaku, shall we?
When you countered his attack,
you chose to use
the back of your sword
against his jaw.
If you had used the sharp end,
you would've taken
him out forever!
♪
That's not my aim.
I must say that's disappointing.
I thought battling
Senkaku would bring out
the bloodthirstiness
that you have inside you.
My spies told me that
you now fight like this.
But I didn't want
to believe them.
♪
You were as good a
slasher as there was,
now look at you.
(sliding)
♪
Your skills have been dissipated
and you've completely
bastardized yourself.
I've discovered how
precious life can be.
(laughs)
No!
(whirling)
Finish the job, Sojiro.
It's obvious that Battousai
no longer exists.
Thank you very much, sir.
It is an honor to be allowed
to do battle with your sword.
You're right.
If you can rekindle
the warrior fire
inside you, Battousai,
I'll be in Edo, waiting.
(snickers)
His fire is about
to be put out.
I salute your wisdom,
Master Shishio.
Now, Master Himura, shall we?
♪
You know that I
don't believe in mercy.
If you give me an opening,
then I will kill you.
♪
How different.
I've never fought anyone
who possessed such
a pure, childish joy
for killing.
I can't read his mind
or predict what he'll do.
Himura, why are
you just standing there?
I want you to take this
Sojiro kid out completely!
Get to work!
This is a different kind
of challenge for Kenshin.
Even though Sojiro is young,
he has such confidence.
♪
This boy's got
the characteristics
of a great slasher.
He's in no hurry to rush in
and force the issue,
he's very disciplined
and focused.
He reminds me of Saito or Akita,
first-class swordsmen
who never allow
emotion or ego
to get in the way of
their pure fighting spirit.
By never showing their feelings,
their opponents can't know them
well enough to predict
what they might do next.
And hence, the mind of a reptile,
the enigmatic face of a sphinx.
I can't feel any
bloodthirstiness from him,
and yet he's a
ruthless killer.
He's very hard to understand.
He acts like a child at play,
and yet I suspect he's the one
who was the hitman
when Okubo was murdered.
If he was capable of that,
then I must fight him
using all my ability.
It won't be easy for me,
considering he's a child.
Why aren't you doing something
besides standing there,
looking like a statue?
This is no time to daydream!
♪
Huh!
Oof, uh!
What do you think you're doing?
You're distracting him!
Well, I guess I was just
trying to help out.
Well, don't.
Misao, we're not playing
Chinese checkers here,
Kenshin's about to fight
in a match to the death.
That's why he just
used his chi energy
to sit you down.
Just what is chi?
It's an energy force
that can be channeled
and it can have
the force of a punch.
When we arrived here,
we thought we would be able
to attack Shishio,
but Sojiro created
a problem for us.
I sensed his chi was strong.
So, because of him,
we were pushed
into a stalemate.
After we'd come
so far to face him,
we couldn't attack Shishio
without being sure
our attempt to eliminate him
would be successful.
♪
(hooves clomping)
So, what were you thinking
leaving Sojiro
to fight Battousai?
Battousai has a tragic flaw.
He's discovered life
amidst beauty.
You do have to admit,
he has the skills
of a great swordsman.
The match against Senkaku
was merely a test.
I had to see if he still
had the killer instinct
of a slasher.
And of course, he proved
that he doesn't.
(horse neighing)
♪
Sojiro's sword skills
are equal to Battousai's,
and the fact that he's
younger and trains so much
should give him
the decided edge
in reaction time.
But what really gives
Sojiro an advantage
are the things that
he hasn't learned.
Sojiro lacks emotions in the way
most people experience them.
As a result, there's no way
to gauge his fighting spirit.
For example,
Saito was ready to attack me,
but his inability to read Sojiro
made him hesitate
in his chance was lost.
It's as if Sojiro were
an indecipherable puzzle
instead of a human being,
so I know that Sojiro
will triumph against Himura.
It's time for me to be going.
I really don't mean
to rush this match,
but to catch up with
Shishio I must hurry.
(swish)
Then let's begin!
♪
What's going on?
Well, he's certainly made
an interesting choice.
If you cannot use
a counterattack
as your means of succeeding
against an opponent,
then you must resort
to other methods
or employ unusual strategies
to be effective.
Say that one more time
in plain English?
Since Himura can't predict
what his opponent's going to do,
he's decided the way
to beat Sojiro
is to take the risk of
making the first move instead.
I see.
My move, Battousai?
Then I'll mirror you.
I know battojutsu, too.
♪
I wish I could be there.
Seeing the result
would be interesting.
(gasp)
♪
He's too smart to just guess
and risk a counterattack.
(clink)
(gasp)
It would be decided man-to-man.
(whooshing)
Speed will win.
(clang)
If their speed is equal,
Battousai will lose.
Huh?
(swishing)
Oh.
Ahh!
Oh!
♪
You see, since Sojiro
has no comprehension of pity,
he feels nothing
when he kills.
But Battousai's feelings
will keep him from reacting
intuitively
when it's necessary.
It's wondrous that
by just taking
the time to think,
a man can lose his life.
Since Battousai refuses to kill,
his chance of surviving
against Sojiro is slim.
Very slim, indeed.
Looks like it's all over,
I'm gonna die.
♪
Well, from the look of things,
you're through.
Not really.
I think it's a tie,
because neither one of you
have a sword in shape
to finish this.
Huh?
(chiming)
Oh no, it's ruined!
Oh...
Yeah!
That's the way to go, Himura!
I can't believe it's
completely disintegrated.
It doesn't seem possible
after so few hits.
Well then, it seems
your friend is right,
we'll have to call
this match a tie.
(clink)
I suppose that
it's about time
I got my own sword
for fighting, anyway.
So, we will just
have to meet again
in a rematch.
You need to find
a replacement sword,
and I'll have one
crafted for myself.
Goodbye, I must be going
to catch up with Shishio.
(footsteps)
(clink)
Himura, your precious sword.
Your most prized possession!
Your sword's broken
and Shishio escapes us again.
and just what the hell
did you do to stop him?
All you did was stand there!
I'll get another sword made.
Once that's accomplished,
then the three of us
can go after Shishio together.
Huh?
Well, look on the bright side.
At least we drove Shishio out
of that village forever!
And now, we've got
him and Sojiro
on the run!
Hmm!
Mm-hmm.
♪
Ugh...
So, the bastard's breathing.
He's still alive.
(gasping)
♪
You son of a bitch,
you were responsible
for the murder of my brother,
and because of
your reign of terror,
my parents are dead!
And now you are
going to die, too!
-Huh?
-Hmm?
You will not live, Senkaku!
Now, for my revenge!
Please, somebody stop him!
(clink)
He killed my brother!
(struggling)
Ahh!
You need to
calm down a bit, Eiji.
He might be very valuable to us
in terms of giving us
important information.
He killed my family
and I'm entitled
to avenge them!
That's where you're wrong.
I won't allow you
to snuff out
our only source of knowledge
about Shishio and
his secret group.
Besides, why should
you rot in jail
for the rest of your life
for a vendetta?
Why?
There's a lot of injustice
in our world,
but your killing him
won't do any good.
Remember, the authorities
will execute him
only after torturing
every answer
they can get out of him.
If you really
want him to suffer,
that reality will
serve your vengeance
better than you killing
an unconscious man.
He's right.
No!
I wanna make him suffer myself!
But, Eiji,
that's not the best way
to serve justice.
You must accept
the authorities
will do what's right.
You don't know
what you're saying!
You mean the same authorities
that allow Shishio
to rule our village?
If I leave it to them,
Senkaku could live
or be set free!
That won't happen.
Don't lie!
I have to get revenge
on this guy personally.
He killed my brother
and made me an orphan!
Now!
♪
(grunting)
Please let go of me,
I have to do it!
Eiji, wasn't this
your brother's sword?
You know he gave his life
so you wouldn't be hurt.
Huh?
He did everything he could
to avoid bloodshed.
This sword was
stained with blood
to save your life,
and now you want
to soak it in blood
for a selfish reason?
Do you think
your brother Ei'Ichiro
would really want
you to kill needlessly?
(grunting)
I'm sure your brother
doesn't want vengeance.
People that have passed on
want the loved ones
they left behind
to experience happiness,
health, and peace!
How could your brother be happy
knowing you used
all your energies
to kill someone
instead of rebuilding your life?
You have to stop this!
You're doing the
right thing, Eiji.
As time rolls on,
these hands will grow
and you'll be filled with pride,
not bitterness,
about the decision
you just made.
Don't ever allow yourself
to be bitter,
or you'll become
like Shishio
and his gang,
oppressors of people,
heartless and cruel,
living a hate-filled
life with no hope.
The best way to honor
your brother's memory
and his courage
is to live your life
as he did.
When he was alive,
he believed
life was precious.
♪
(evil laughter)
Who are they?
Don't worry about
these men, Eiji.
They'll never hurt you
because they have
to go through me first!
I'm certain that
I could arrange something!
If I were you,
I'd be very scared, kid!
Yah!
(yelling)
(grunting)
Get them!
The older one's
half dead already,
but I want you three
to chase them down
and make sure that
you kill both of them!
(group hollering)
(footsteps, grunting)
♪
(group yelling)
No!
♪
Ugh.
I'm starting to feel weak, Eiji.
After I promised to protect you,
I don't feel I'm going
to be able to keep that promise.
I guess I failed you.
♪
Forgive me, Eiji.
No matter what happens,
you must save yourself.
(grunting)
(clanking)
♪
My poor brother...
(sobbing)
♪
I understand you're still sad,
but at least now
everything's settled.
How can you seriously say
that everything's settled?
Hmm?
♪
After his sword tip broke,
I was going in for the kill
when I saw your sword was
too damaged to finish him.
So I apologize deeply
for what happened, sir.
But your sword was
in no shape to continue,
as much as I wanted to.
I never imagined
his reverse-edged sword
could do this kind of damage
to a Nagasone Kotetsu.
I must admit, I underestimated
his strength and ability.
Nagasone-what?
You can't be serious
that you don't know
what a Nagasone Kotetsu is.
-Hmm?
-Well, at least
you're a good fighter.
A Nagasone Kotetsu
is a handcrafted sword
made by one of
the master craftsmen
of Nagasone!
It takes six months
to craft one!
(chime)
Now, Sojiro, I want you
to do something for me
that's very important.
As long as it's not
replacing your sword,
I'll do it. sir.
I want you to contact
all ten of the Jupponta
Swordsmen of death
and have them meet us in Edo.
And what has made you
want to call in
your special attack force?
I believe doing this
may be the only way
I have to bring
Battousai the Slasher
out of Kenshin Himura.
He's not about to give up
and let us get away.
♪
What a sight!
After years of living
under Shishio's thumb,
the Shingetsu village
has a chance to make
a change for the better.
(crowd chatting)
I know these people may feel
they've reclaimed their town,
but if you hadn't saved them,
they'd still be cowards!
You don't know human nature
very well, do you?
When people are oppressed,
it brings out the worst in them.
People turn on each other
and endure almost anything
to survive.
Most people are spineless beings
having less courage
than a flea.
You know, I can't
believe I agree with you,
but I'm thinking of
changing my opinion
just because you're such
an obnoxious jerk!
Even though I've lived
my whole life in Shingetsu,
I'll never go back.
I forgive them,
but I couldn't live
with them again.
♪
Let's find you a new sword.
Then, we'll head to
Edo to crush Shishio
once and for all.
Sounds good.
But, there's someone else
we have to take care
of first, Eiji.
I think I have an idea
that would put Eiji
in a good situation.
I know of a safe place
where you would be welcome
to stay and live in peace.
Tokio will take care of Eiji
as if he were our own.
Tokio?
She's my wife.
(blaze roaring)
You never said
Mr. Personality
had a wife!
That's because
Saito never told me
he was married before right now!
My wife's sweet,
warm-hearted and reliable.
She'll be happy to
take care of him.
Tokio would be thrilled
to have someone like Eiji
at home with her.
If that woman can stay
married to this jerk,
she must be an absolute saint!
I'd say only a person
who's a boddhisattva
could live with Saito.
(gong ringing)
Ahem.
Well, I'd better
take Eiji and get going.
While I'm gone,
I want you to become
Battousai again.
Without his fighting spirit,
we'll never defeat Shishio.
Hmph!
I look forward
to rejoining you
again in Edo.
You're lucky Sojiro's sword
got damaged when it did.
It gave you another
chance to regain
your slasher instincts.
♪
It was a good thing your
reverse-edged sword broke.
Now, you can obtain a sword
that will take care
of business.
Well, until I see you next time,
get yourself ready.
(footsteps)
♪
Hey, Eiji, I know
you're gonna grow up
to be a really good man,
and you're going to do
some great stuff!
Many thanks for
all your support, Misao!
You and Mr. Himura
convinced me
there's more to life
than getting revenge.
Goodbye, Eiji!
Take care of yourself!
Bye!
Hello, Himura?
Hmm?
Hmm.
I don't understand
why Shishio ran off,
maybe he doesn't do
his own dirty work.
He left a boy,
albeit a talented swordsman
to do a slasher's job.
We should enjoy
the fact we're alive
before the parade passes by.
I regret that I have
but one life to give
for my country,
but while I'm still alive
I refuse to be sad and mope.
Instead, we should celebrate!
You should always turn
your eyes up like this.
Sometimes you try to look cool.
Other times you just look crazy.
Or really lonely.
Or just close-minded.
Or you just cannot
see eye-to-eye.
But I like your happy eyes!
Okay?
Misao, you should really
come out of your shell
so you can learn how
to express yourself.
Well actually,
I've been working
on that a little.
(growls)
Am I getting the impression
that you're trying
to reach me with sarcasm?
You know I'm just
starting to like you?
After all, you
saved my life
when I jumped a chasm
and I'm falling for you
and then you pull this crap?
♪
Huh?
Oh.
So, you do like me, after all?
Well, we've wasted enough time,
we better get going to Edo.
I don't think Shishio
will attack us
until we get to Edo,
so I really need
to pick up a sword
between here and there.
I can't believe he's
regarding my affection
so lightly that
he's just walking off!
I'm through being calm!
Ugh!
(yelling over each other)
♪
I could feel there
was a fierce battle
going on inside me.
Was I destined to be
Battousai the slasher, again?
Or Kenshin,
the peaceful wanderer?
I would find the answer in Edo.
♪