♪
♪ (singing in Japanese) ♪
(laughing)
Today's the day.
♪
And now it's white.
-So white!
(laughing)
♪
Rise and shine!
Let me sleep,
I was up late drinking
and losing at dice.
Up.
Hey!
You and your six
five sake binges.
Don't you remember
what today is, you lout?
Yeah, today's May 14th.
Today's the day that Kenshin's
supposed to give the
Okubo guy his big answer.
I just hope he doesn't
bring that Kawaji.
Yeah, he's a real pompous jerk.
Let's stop talking
and go find Kenshin.
♪
Come on, let's try
to find some frogs.
I see.
And so today's the day, huh?
We've let Kenshin know
we're here to help him.
No matter what kind of pressure
Okubo puts on Kenshin
we won't allow them
to force Kenshin to go.
So what does Kenshin
say about all this?
He's not going to go.
♪
This is where we saw
them, right, Grandpa?
Hm?
This is the spot where we
see fireflies every year.
Where are they now?
By next week you'll see them.
Fireflies.
I guess I wasn't
here last summer.
Oh, they shine as
bright as a candle.
They sure do.
So have you ever
seen them before?
Mhmm.
When they get here that's
where they'll see us.
They'll shine for
me and you, too.
They're shiny buggy bugs!
Seems like Kenshin's
been here forever.
Even though he's been
with us less than a year
he sure has become
a part of the family.
He is one of us and I love him.
And I'd do almost anything
to keep him a
part of our family.
Let's go find some frogs.
Let's come back
here tonight, okay?
For the fireflies?
It'll be fun.
Yes, and all of us will come.
Yeah, promise, promise!
♪
Uh...
Hey!
He can't make any
promises for tonight
until he tells Okubo no, right?
We all know you couldn't
possibly be stupid enough
to accept his crazy offer.
I know you wanna help,
but there's only
one logical choice.
Yeah, those guys could
care less about you.
All they want is to get
their dirty work done.
Okubo wants you to risk it all,
and the Meiji
government is so rotten
that it's sure not worth
putting your life on the line
for those jerks.
Boy, you must really
hate the Meiji government
to talk about it that way, Sano.
Wrong again!
It's not as black
and white as that.
I'm sure Okubo was
really greedy or corrupt
Saito would've already
killed him by now.
That's why this
decision's so tough.
Saito?
Isn't he that phony policeman?
Slash evil now.
The Shinsen group
and slashers of honor
are the only protectors of
righteousness in our society.
He still believes the
philosophy of idealizing
what's truly right,
even in this mixed up Meiji era.
He acts like a lone wolf,
defending justice and
protecting the righteous
from evil.
Of course, that doesn't mean
that it's any easier
to get along with him.
You're right.
He's a real pain.
-We hate him.
-We hate him, too.
(sneezing)
How crass.
You are a pig.
Why, thank you.
Stupid people like you
judge everyone by what you see.
But so what?
As a member of
the Shinsen Group
I'm used to being despised
no matter what I do.
Today's May 14th?
Battosai, today's
your decision day.
If you'll excuse me.
Where are you going?
Are you leaving?
Mhmm.
Kenshin?
I need to go and
give Sir Okubo my answer.
But wait a second.
He said he was
going to come here.
I'm sure he has
more important matters
than to waste time
traveling here.
It will also show
how much I respect him.
You're not going to leave.
Ahhhh!
There's only one
way to keep a man,
and that's to make sure he knows
just who's in control
and keep him on a short leash.
And I give him some
of my pleasure balm
to keep him totally satisfied
and help seduce him.
(laughing)
You stop that kind
of talk, Megumi.
Women, they are scary.
So just where can
I get some of that
for my lady friends?
Oh, Dr. Gensai.
Really, now.
Thanks for the thought.
But I really have
to get going now.
But, Kenshin, how
can you expect to find
just where Okubo is anyway?
He mentioned that today
he would be visiting
the county administrator in
Akasaka so I'm walking there.
If that's the situation
then we'll all go.
No.
I think it's best
that I go there alone,
it'll make things a lot easier.
♪
Don't worry, Kaoru.
Kenshin knows this
is where he belongs.
When he's finished with his
business he'll come back.
This dojo's his home.
He'll be back tonight.
He's not gonna kill anybody
for any government.
I still can't believe
I couldn't convince him
to stay put here.
Where did Kenshin go, Grandpa?
And when's he coming back here?
Well, I hope he'll be
back with us very soon.
Me, too.
♪
I still need to talk with Okubo
and ask him if killing Shishio
would really mean
peace for everyone.
I know from the candid way
he spoke when he visited
he'll give me an honest answer.
♪
Will this day never end?
My meeting with the county
administrator may take hours.
After that I still
need to travel to Ito
and meet with Himura
to hear his decision.
There's only one answer
that's acceptable from him.
He has to do it no matter what.
He simply must say yes.
Without him we're
really done for.
You know something?
You worry too much.
Okubo, why concern yourself
with what might
happen in the future?
Besides, you're
going to be dead.
Shishio wanted me
to tell you this.
Now listen.
Enlisting Himura's a good idea,
but it won't stop me
from taking over the country.
He wanted you to know.
Too bad for you he's
not here to bail you out.
♪
Hold your horses!
Huh?
Whoa!
Stop, you're being commandeered
by Ito radicals.
Come out now, Okubo.
We're coming in after ya!
(shouting)
The coachman's dead!
(cheering)
You can't hide, Okubo.
Dammit!
Someone's assassinated him.
Who would have done this?
That's not our concern.
The question is what
are we going to do now?
This really messes things up.
I say we pretend
that we're responsible
for what just happened.
Are you sure?
It helps our cause.
Agreed?
That sounds right, Shimada.
Count me in.
Agreed!
We're all in!
(laughing and cheering)
♪
Sir Okubo murdered?
Who would have killed
our Home Minister?
Everybody get back.
Stand back, I said back.
(gasps)
It's Okubo.
The same thing
could happen to you
if you try to stop
Shishio, buddy.
I'd think twice before
you try anything.
♪
Shishio.
He's responsible.
♪
Extra, extra.
Home Minister assassinated.
Read all about it.
All provinces mourn
murdered statesman.
Are they kidding?
Just who else could they mean?
Read this, it seems
Okubo's been murdered.
"Earlier today in Akasaka,
our country lost a
renowned statesman.
A man considered by many
to be the central pillar
of the Meiji government
has been assassinated.
Toshimichi Okubo is dead".
♪
This is the way
Shishio does things.
He takes the truth,
which is that he was responsible
for Sir Okubo's untimely death,
and he distorts the facts
so that the people
of our country
think this heinous act
was committed by
some other group.
He keeps out of sight,
but he kills our
greatest statesman
and keeps slicing
away at the fabric
that holds our fragile
country together.
It can't be.
(knocking)
I hope I'm not interrupting.
Welcome, Yamayoshi.
You were the last one
to talk with Sir Okubo.
Please tell us about it.
I met with him just before
he left in his carriage
heading to Akasaka and
he seemed very tired.
The enormous pressure he
was under was getting to him.
I mean, he was doing his best
to keep our government afloat.
It's been ten years
since the restoration
and we have been so busy
trying to suppress internal
strife and organize things
that we have very little
to show for all our work,
it's disheartening.
The real restoration will
take place in the next 15 years
and the only way we
will achieve our dream
is to win the people over
to our way of thinking.
Without the common
man we are lost.
Now it's time to expand
and by beginning to
deal with domestic issues
the people will see
we are worthy of their trust.
I only wish I
were a younger man.
Then I'd feel sure I'd be here
to see my ideas implemented.
I know you can do it.
You have my confidence, Sir.
The only way the
restoration will work
is to enlist the people.
By building a national unity
and organizing
our nation's states
the people will join our cause.
Once the people find
they are a vital part
of the process of government,
we can't help but succeed.
When people feel empowered
instead of thinking a handful
of men decide everything
then we will have the chance,
the chance to be a
truly great nation.
He was a man for the people.
But he was just too idealistic.
But he was right.
He was the only one
who could do it.
His ideas were right,
now he's gone.
One other thing.
Sir Okubo was usually quiet
and reserved when we spoke.
But when we spoke
yesterday he was passionate
in the way he
related his thoughts.
It was almost as
if he somehow knew.
It was as though he wanted
his philosophy and his ideas
to keep on living.
I, for one, will
never forget the man.
He was the greatest statesman
of our time and, maybe,
the greatest of all time.
(crying)
♪
Kawaji certainly seemed to
take Okubo's death pretty hard.
Sir Okubo was like
a father to him.
He taught Kawaji
everything he knows.
But Kawaji isn't the only one
that will be affected
by Okubo's death.
Our entire country
will be in confusion.
This could put the
restoration flat on its back.
With all three of
the great statesmen
of the restoration dead now,
all we have left are
third rate politicians.
And you know what that means.
Shishio was licking his chops.
He won't let this
opportunity pass him by.
Saito.
Where are you going?
What are you planning to do now?
There's only one thing to do.
Go to Ito and see to it
that Shishio gets stopped.
See ya.
♪
Sir Okubo murdered
by dissidents!
Ishikawa Royalists
claim responsibility
for Home Minister's death!
What's gonna happen now?
(crowd talking)
It's like the turmoil
of the Tokugawa era
is starting again.
What have we done
to deserve this?
They should hang those
dissident bastards.
How can Uta allow this
to happen to us?
War might break out
among the rival factions.
When is Sir Okubo's funeral?
No one will ever be
able to replace him.
Once the people feel
they are a vital part
of the process of government,
we can't help but succeed.
We don't want your opinion.
He could save our country.
Shut your mouth.
Shishio is licking his chops.
He won't let this
opportunity pass him by.
I see, the only
viewpoint that's valid here
is your own corrupt
government's viewpoint.
I would rather be executed
than go along with
your blackmail scheme.
I don't know much about
your Meiji government,
but I have figured
out one thing.
If the situation was
just a little different
you might be hiring
us to kill Kenshin.
We will not allow Kenshin to
go to Ito and risk being killed.
Battosai, I told you.
The real you is a slasher
and will always be a slasher.
A slasher cannot
be anything else
until someone kills him.
The only time
you're really alive
is when you're fighting.
Or killing people.
Deep down you know
what I say is the truth.
Your bloodthirsty hands
cannot let go of the sword,
no matter how much
you try to fight it.
You should give
in to your destiny.
(laughing)
I know he's right.
The slasher still
lives in my heart.
I've been trying
to get rid of him,
but maybe that's not possible.
I really tried to do
what I think is right,
but maybe what's right
is being true to myself
instead of fighting the part
of me that lives as Battosai.
To find out who I really am
I must confront my own fear.
The only way to know which
Kenshin is the real me
is to give Battosai a
chance to live again.
Then I can choose which
life is best for me.
♪
Oh, isn't it just my luck
to get an emergency patient
on a night like this?
Come on, Grandpa
said we need to hurry.
I was hoping to
stay here tonight
and see if Kenshin
decides to come home.
Well, I sure can't allow
Dr. Fox and two little girls
to walk home alone at night.
Come on, ladies.
That sounded
awfully patronizing.
Kaoru, if Kenshin
comes back while I'm gone
you can tell him
where my sake jug is.
Okay.
And be careful.
We'll be careful and quiet.
Sh, quiet!
Kenshin.
Aw, come on, Kaoru.
You know that he's probably
gonna come back here.
I know it's not nice to say,
but since Okubo's dead
there's no reason
for him to go to Ito.
He'll come back home.
Then I'll run down the
road and welcome him home.
Hey, Kaoru.
Nice move, Yoshi boy.
Maybe I shouldn't
get my hopes up.
Maybe he decided to
start wandering again.
Those fireflies
really are beautiful.
Kenshin!
♪
What is it?
Sir Okubo was
assassinated yesterday.
I know, we heard.
I'm pretty sure about one thing.
Shishio and his gang did this.
I couldn't live myself
if I let Shishio
get away with this.
That's why I came to tell you
I have to go to Ito.
Kaoru, did you hear what I said?
Kaoru?
Ito?
I have to ask.
Are you going back to
being the old Kenshin again?
I wish I knew.
It's been a long time.
But when I was fighting
Saito I had a strange feeling.
I could feel the old
warrior Battosai coming back.
There's still a
slasher inside me
and he's fighting to get out.
Battosai still lives
somewhere inside me
and he just won't
allow me to ignore him.
I must give him a
chance to live again.
But it's not fair.
Your life's so much better
without that killer
running your life.
Can't you see I want
what's best for you?
The one you shouldn't
give up on is Kenshin.
At least we know he's good.
If I stay here any longer
than you'll all be
pulled into this mess.
The best thing I can do
is let Battosai out again
and see what happens.
♪
I'll never forget the
first time that I met you.
And I remember you told me then
that you didn't care
about my past, Kaoru.
That made me very happy
and I knew I found a new home.
You've been great.
I've had so much peace,
so many fun filled days
being part of this
wonderful family,
feeling the love we all share.
♪
Thank you, Kaoru.
Thank you for
everything you've given me.
♪
I just have to go to Ito.
But that doesn't mean
that I don't love you.
Goodbye, Kaoru.
(crying)
♪
Oh, Kenshin.
♪ (singing in Japanese) ♪
♪