(theme music)
♪
I'm up here!
You're through,
let Iori go.
I think I've heard of
you, you must be him.
That X on your cheek,
you've got to be
the renowned assassin
Battousai the Slasher.
Let me guess, you've
come here to battle
for the right to own
the last sword of Shakku.
Actually, it's
not the sword
that made me
follow you here.
You can have the sword.
I'm more concerned with Iori
being returned to her
parents, understand?
So I'm telling
you, let her go.
♪
If you think you're
getting this baby back
without a fight,
you're wrong.
And I've never
been defeated.
Now I know
you're at a loss
without your
reversed-edge sword.
I heard you broke it
dueling with Sojiro.
But as much as that sword
is your weapon of choice,
I'm afraid you'll have to
make a stand without it.
Personally, I'd
rather battle you
when you're at your best,
but Shishio might not
understand if I have
this opportunity
and let you live.
Whoa!
And, besides, getting
the coveted last sword
of Shakku Arai without
having to fight for it
just wouldn't
seem right to me.
(crying)
So, are you
going to fight?
Or should I slice
that baby in two?
So my threat got
your attention,
now let's begin
our little game.
I do feel sad for
you being unarmed.
But you're obviously
not sad enough to make
this a truly fair fight,
one where you don't
have a huge advantage.
But I'll still
find a way.
Sure, a quick and
easy way to die.
♪
Get ready to taste steel!
Even with such
an obvious edge,
you still underestimated
my skills enough to try
gatotsu on me.
(thunderous rumble)
(grunting)
Thanks for your
help, mister!
(grunting)
If you think
that's all I've got,
you've got another
thing coming.
You're better
than I thought.
But I think I've
just figured out
a way to double my
chances of winning.
(clanging)
This technique
is called "renbato."
The twin blades
create a wound
that's almost
impossible to survive.
And even if you do
survive my initial attack,
you'll probably die a
slow and agonizing death
from the massive infection
these blades would cause.
(yelling)
Shakku taught me how to
defend against renbato.
(grunting)
(yelling)
(crashing)
Huh?
You did it!
I hope you had
a nice little nap.
Now, it's time to get
you down from there.
You were right.
It's time to get serious.
Uh oh!
I'm really scared.
Don't worry, Iori.
Take my word for it,
he won't be hurting you.
Stop jawing with that runt
kid I'm going to kill!
Turn around
and face me now
so we can finish this
duel to the death!
♪
Now that I finally have
your attention again,
let's get on
with our business
so I can kill you, gut
that child like a fish,
and get my new sword.
♪
Hurry up before we're
too late to save Iori!
My little baby!
We must save our
baby from that fiend!
I just know that Himura
will be able to stall Cho,
but he can't stop him
with just his bare hands.
That bastard Cho
is so heartless.
He'd sooner kill you
than talk to you.
I hope Himura's alive.
Ooh, oh!
It looks like they're
squaring off for a showdown,
but I didn't see
Iori anywhere.
Hmm, from the
looks of things,
Himura has somehow held on.
Look around his waist.
Be aware what Cho's got
around his waist, Himura!
My father Shakku created
that flexible sword
that Cho's got after years
of experimenting
with the idea.
What?
So we've got
an audience.
That's just fine,
I don't mind witnesses.
So let's rumble.
Be careful,
he's full of tricks!
Watch out!
This is my favorite killer
sword, Hakujin no Tachi.
You better move, you've
got to dodge that blade!
♪
(grunting)
(laughing)
That's why it's
my favorite blade.
Shakku designed this sword
and there's no
known defense for it.
He's right, by
designing the blade
to be so thin and flexible,
the Hakujin no Tachi sword
is the most
impossible to avoid!
And since he's
been wounded,
his chances of
living are slim.
I hate to agree, but
with his leg slashed,
he won't be able
to move quick enough
to avoid being killed.
From the look of things,
I'd say your friends
won't get a chance
to cheer for you,
but I'll do my best to keep
your death short and sweet.
It can't be, why did
I sell him that sword?
Seiku.
My irresponsibility
will kill our baby.
-Hey, I'm up here!
-Quiet, kid.
Time to finish this.
He hasn't got
a chance now.
Cho's gonna end
Himura's life
and he'll kill anyone
who tries to rescue Iori.
Oh, why did I do it?
It's my fault!
(crashing)
You've got
to help him!
(grunting)
Hang on, Himura,
we're trying to come up
with a plan to
help you win!
Ha, I don't think
there's going to be
any winning
in your future.
For God's sake, move!
(grunting)
That was good.
I wish someone would slap
my face so I'd wake up.
What can I do?
(growling)
♪
We've all got
to work together
to see if we can't
help Himura out.
The trouble is we
haven't got much time
before Cho slices him as thin
as paper with that blade.
Do you have any
other swords, Seiku?
No!
Watch out!
(grunting)
You know, I have something
terrible to admit.
For a man of honor, I was
really telling an awful lie
when I promised you
that I'd kill you quickly.
♪
What's honorable about
wanting to kill a child?
Where's the honor
in fighting a man
with no sword?
You possess no honor, Cho.
You're nothing
but a gutless worm.
Without our children,
our country has no future.
I will defend
Iori to the death!
So you, a slasher, are
trying to moralize me
on just how
valuable life is?
Isn't it true you killed
hundreds of people
during the Tokugawa era?
You've got a lot
of room to talk,
but don't worry,
you'll be leaving us soon
and won't have to
ponder how ironic
your thought sounded.
I made mistakes
in the past,
but now I've learned
to do what's right.
Oh, yeah.
When I was a slasher,
I never killed children.
I killed real men
who had honor.
Violence will only beget
more violence, wisdom--
I've had enough
of your philosophy.
(spitting)
I'd say your time's up!
(thundering)
No!
-Don't!
-Seiku!
Please, stop!
I hate interference!
♪
(grunting)
Hurry, Seiku,
rescue your son
while there's still time.
You've got to
do something!
Move!
Don't be nervous, Iori,
I'll be back
to save you soon!
I just have to give
Himura a hand first!
I'll cover your back!
(laughing)
I've just got to make it
all the way back
to the workshop.
If I don't, then
all of us will die!
(yelling)
Himura has stopped
Cho, thank Buddha.
Now I've got a chance
to help him save my baby.
(yelling)
♪
It is ironic,
here I am giving a man
who believes in peace
a weapon of war.
And he will use it to
help keep the peace.
(yelling)
All right!
Your friend Himura is
certainly resourceful.
He's obviously studied
Tang Soo Do and he's good.
Well, it looks like
that elbow strike
has made Cho a lot more
reasonable to deal with.
It's becoming
pretty clear
I'm going to have to
give you some more space,
because when I try to
get in close to you
and try to finish,
you're not cooperating
with my plans.
It's over.
Now he'll just slice
Himura to death.
Kenshin doesn't
stand a chance.
If only he
had a sword.
Himura, here at last is
the sword of my father!
Please use it
to save Iori!
♪
(audible sigh)
Well, looks like you've
got yourself a sword.
That's actually the last
sword Shakku ever made
and I mean to add
it to my collection,
even if it's over
your dead body.
Well, you look much
more serious now.
Go on, kick his ass!
♪
(audible sigh)
Just what is
he waiting for?
Good, he's smart enough
not to rush his first move.
That's one of the traits
of a truly great fighter,
they never rush into battle.
Besides, Himura's decided
that he doesn't want
to use that sword.
What?
Are you nuts?
If he doesn't, he'll die.
I really don't know
much about his past,
but this is no time
for him to worry
about protecting Cho's life.
Don't you realize if
he uses that sword,
all that he's worked
to change in himself
will be destroyed?
He doesn't want to return
to the murdering life
of Battousai the Slasher.
Oh my God, you're
absolutely right.
♪
Hey, you finally got your
wish and the odds are even.
So now what are
you waiting for?
Come on.
I heard Shishio
tell stories
that the great Battousai
never hesitated in battle.
Oh, well, I guess
you've forgotten
that slashing
people is exciting.
It's really
delicious fun.
Perhaps you just
need an example.
(laughing)
Iori!
Don't do that!
Allow me to demonstrate
by eliminating our
country's future!
No!
(gasping)
(shouting)
♪
Ha, finally , he's been
pushed out of his hole.
He shouldn't have let
Cho bait him like that.
You made a fool of me and
now I'm returning a favor.
(crumbling)
It's a little late
to watch your back!
Ah!
(shouting)
What the hell just
happened to him?
It's as though he
became the devil himself!
I'll show him Hiten
Mitsurugi-ryu style close-up.
(yelling)
(exploding)
♪
He did it.
I didn't think
he'd be able
to go back to
being Battousai,
but Cho really
left him no choice.
♪
He's dead.
I can't believe it.
Kenshin Himura
actually killed someone.
♪
Cho forced me
to attack him.
If I hadn't
killed him,
I really believe he
would've killed Iori.
I tried to wait,
to hold back,
I didn't want this
to end this way.
Why did he do it?
♪
Now what will happen?
Will he become
a fugitive?
Will he have to
run from the law?
(exploding)
♪
Perhaps I just
should've let him
kill me in one of our
earlier skirmishes,
then he might
have been satisfied
and left without
harming anyone else.
I would've sacrificed
myself gladly if I
could've been sure
what he'd do
afterwards,
but I couldn't be sure.
It doesn't matter now.
He forced me
into the decision
I didn't want to make,
the decision to
become Battousai again.
♪
You really did it.
Now that I've
killed again,
do I have to go back
to being Battousai?
Oh, no.
Himura?
That's incredible!
Mr. Himura, take a good
look at your sword!
What?
♪
I can't believe it,
a reversed edge!
Huh, so the last sword
Shakku ever created
he designed to hurt,
but not kill.
A reversed edge.
If it's a reversed edge,
Cho should be alive, right?
(grunting)
So you really didn't
kill him, did you?
Oh, Himura.
I just don't understand.
Dad made killing swords.
A reversed edge?
Maybe he'd seen
too much killing
and wanted to create
a sword of peace.
(crumbling)
(clanging)
What happened?
Why would Shakku use
a pine-wood handle
that he knew
would break, heh?
What?
The hilt is engraved.
It's written in
classical Japanese.
Look, "I forged
swords for many years,
my son hates that I
never have time for him.
This sword is for
my grandchildren."
He's saying that all
his life his passion
was creating
swords for killing,
to build a new era.
But in the end,
he realized
there was more to life
than promoting death.
So, he fashioned this
very special sword
to reflect his
change in thinking,
he found a
better way
to view his
grandchildren's future.
I'll bet he
engraved that
knowing it would
be his death poem.
I guess he knew this was
going to be his last sword
and he really put
his best into it.
Even after he changed
his thinking about using
killer swords to
build a new era,
he knew that for our
family to survive,
he had to keep
making them.
And so he put
his regret
and hope for a peaceful
future into this sword.
He designed a reverse-edge
shinuchi to help peace.
Shinuchi?
Yes, when you forge
this type of sword,
two pieces are
incorporated
to make one blade.
It takes literally weeks
of working the metal
before it melds to
become the strongest,
sharpest blade possible.
So what you're saying is
this particular piece
of metal is the finest,
strongest sword blade
that's ever been made.
For saving my child's
life, it is yours.
I know it would
make my father happy
to know you have it.
It is good to see
you again, Battousai.
Well, maybe I
shouldn't call you that.
After all, you are wanted
for your slasher crimes
by the state,
even though they
were the ones
that ordered
you to kill.
I was happily surprised
you left the royalists,
but what have you
done with your sword?
Mr. Shakku,
I have decided
that I must change
the way I live my life.
I want to find a way
to protect people
without killing others.
Huh, I admire
your optimism.
If there is such a way,
I'd certainly embrace it.
So, now, after killing
so many, you've decided
the way of the
sword is wrong,
you'll still need
one to survive.
I want you
to have this.
It's not my best, but
it will serve you well.
You will always
be a swordsman,
and at least this way
you will have
something on your back.
Someday you'll realize
that no matter how good
your peaceful
intentions are,
the world's not
ready to accept peace
as a way of life.
And when the sword that
I've given you breaks,
if you're still preaching
peace towards your fellow man
and I'm still alive,
then come back here,
and I'll be happy
to give you another.
♪
Shakku, I still
believe that in our time
the world is ready
to accept peace
as a way of life.
I only wish you'd
lived longer to see it.
In your father's memory,
I am proud to accept
this great gift.
Mr. Himura!
Go bye-bye.
Have a safe trip!
Goodbye, Iori.
(giggling)
(birds chirping)
(indistinct chattering)
Kaoru, we've been searching
for Kenshin for three days
and so far,
we haven't found
any sign of him here,
this is depressing, really.
Well, keep your chin up.
I had no idea that Edo
was going to be so big.
Hiya!
(cracking)
So do you want
to go back home?
I won't give up!
I'm here to find him
and I'll find him,
and then you can
kiss your man Kenshin.
Why did you have to
say that about kissing?
But you shouldn't feel
bad about him leaving you,
you're not
why he left.
He didn't want us
hurt so he deci--huh?
(gasping)
♪
It's Aoshi.
And he's alive.
Oh my God, he did survive
the massacre of his Oni gang.
Hey, where'd he go,
he was just here!
-Yoshi, wait!
-Don't worry,
I'll find him!
He might know where
to find Kenshin.
Just stay where you are!
Hey, come back!
I turned in Cho
to the police,
just like you suggested.
It turned out he was wanted
for other crimes as well.
And here's the address
of Seijuro Hiko.
We weren't aware that
he'd been using an alias,
so it made it harder
to track him down.
Thanks for all
your help, Okina.
So I guess this
means farewell.
I know you'll take
good care of Misao.
And would you please
tell her I'm sorry
I didn't tell her
anything about Aoshi?
Of course I'll tell her.
Thanks.
Oh, Himura, remember this,
no matter what happens,
I will always be on
your side, my friend.
Thanks, and we
all thank you
for making
Misao so strong.
Hi, Himura,
breakfast's almost ready.
Hey, wait, where are
you going anyway?
Let me guess,
you're leaving us,
and you weren't even
gonna say anything.
I told you
a long time ago
that some pretty vicious
people are after me.
I just can't have
you risking your life
just to be my friend,
it's too dangerous, but I--
And just who are you
to tell me what to do?
You've got a lot
of nerve, Kenshin.
Real friends stick together
through the tough times,
and as for creeps,
I can take care of
myself, you know?
Now listen carefully,
I don't care about
your life as Battousai.
I know Kenshin Himura and
he's the one I care about.
Hey, what's so funny?
Well, a lady friend
of mine in Kyoto
said almost exactly the same
thing when I left there.
I would've never thought
anyone in my hometown of Edo
would ever say something
that kind to me if I
hadn't heard it myself.
♪
Oh, yeah, well I'm
gonna go with you!
Misao!
Oh, Okina.
I realize that you have
feelings for Mr. Himura.
And I'm sure he
cares about you, too.
In fact, he cares enough
to want you to be safe
while he finishes
his mission.
Trust his judgment
and let him go.
If he loves you,
he'll come back.
Misao, don't!
Hey!
I swear, I'll
find you, Himura.
I'm not afraid to share any
challenge you might face.
After all, why should
men be the only ones
to fight and have fun?
♪
(panting)
(yelling)
Oh!
You dumb half-pint,
watch where you're going!
Hey, you're the one
who ran into me,
you overgrown forage queen!
Don't you talk to that
lady like that, Yoshi!
I'm sorry, are
you all right?
Oh, it's nothing.
It's just that
Mr. Kenshin Himura
has just decided he
wants to go off alone
and he's got
another thing coming!
You said, "Kenshin Himura."
Himura, what can you
tell us about Kenshin?
Huh?
We are old friends
of his from Kyoto.
We're trying to find him,
that's why we came here.
This can't be one
of those evil types
that are after Himura.
But, wait, she just might be
that old friend from Kyoto.
(theme music)
♪