(rock and roll music)
♪
(singing in foreign language)
(bird tweeting)
Oh, Kenshin!
Kenshin, where are you?
Kenshin?
♪
Hey, you guys, I'm outside.
It's a beautiful
morning out here.
What are you doin' out
here enjoying yourself?
How can you be so relaxed
when you know a fighter's
on his way to challenge you?
Kenshin, I don't think
you should fight this guy.
I mean what if he's some
crazy lunatic or nut?
Believe me, I wish
I didn't have to fight him.
But with Sanosuke, I may
not have much of a choice.
You're not thinking about
going through with it, are you?
What do you think?
Of course he's gonna
go through with it,
and I'm gonna be the one
to help him train
to win, aren't I?
Who asked you anyway?
Why don't you just
stay out of it?
Don't tell me what
to do, you spaz.
How dare you call your teacher that,
you ungrateful--
Spaz!
-Ow, ow, let me go!
-Little punk!
Oh, you're gonna get it!
I've had it with your big mouth.
I wonder what he wants.
He's done.
I'm gonna take
that legendary Slasher
and show him who's boss
once and for all.
I'll bury him
and the restoration!
I wish I knew why
he holds a grudge
against the royalists
from the restoration.
Kenshin, will you
please wake up?
-You're daydreaming again.
-Huh?
I told you, you're not
going to fight him.
Good morning, Kaoru.
Dr. Gensai.
Hi, Yumi and little Susie.
-Oh, boy, Kenshin!
-Kenshin, yay!
(giggling)
How are my two favorite
kids in the whole world?
Oh, boy.
I'm worried about him.
But he doesn't
even seem to care.
(drumming)
♪
(dice tapping)
Captain Sagara.
♪
(soldiers marching)
Listen very carefully, Sanosuke.
Very soon
300 years of Tokugawa
control will be over,
and a new era will start.
We will say goodbye
to a society, where
people had no power
and were told what to do,
whether they liked it or not,
and say hello to a new society
where everyone is equal.
And all due to us,
the Sekiho Force.
I have been told
about the sacrifices
I must make
to help the movement.
If we all work hard
to build the society,
then our dream can come true.
(snow crunching)
Hey, Captain, when
the movement is over
and everything has calmed down
do you think I could
have a family name, too?
Sure.
Well, then, in that case,
do you think it's possible
that I take your
family name for my own?
Then I'll be a Sagara.
Sanosuke Sagara?
I don't know.
That kinda sounds
like a circus performer.
(chuckling)
(horse cantering)
Whoa.
So you must be Sagara,
the number one captain
of the Sekiho Force.
I am Tatewaki Shindo,
the staff officer
of the Imperial Army.
I came here from
the headquarters in Shimosuwa
to give you an order
from the government general.
The government general?
What does he want, Captain?
(fast zoom)
(pained scream)
(groaning and gasping)
Just what are you
trying to do, Sanosuke?
Maybe I should ask you
that same question, my friend.
I see you snooping around,
trying to follow me.
Oh, well, it's
no big deal, really.
I just wanted to see how
the fight ends, that's all.
Let me tell you
something, Gohei,
this was my decision
to take up this fight,
and I don't want you or anybody
else butting in my business.
Do we understand each other?
All right, all right.
Just calm down for a second.
I'm not buttin' in here.
I mean, don't get me wrong.
It's not that I think
you can't handle him,
but if you knew
Battousai like I do,
you'd be happy to have
a little help close by
in case you got into any trouble
that you couldn't
get out of, all right?
Hey!
Well, I appreciate
the concern, Gohei,
but since this challenge
was my own idea,
I'll handle it myself.
And don't worry,
I'll take care of him.
(birds singing)
Ha-ha, come on!
-Two, three...
-Ha ha, woo!
♪
Kenshin, who's that?
Tell me, you heard
what about the rumor?
This morning, my patient
said he heard some news
about a fighter who's
looking for Kenshin.
And it seems that
he's a former member
of the Sekiho Force.
What is that, Dr. Gensai?
A group of hoodlums?
No, it's a fake Imperial Army.
An army?
The Sekiho Force was
an army that was created
by ordinary citizens
during the restoration.
Just regular people,
like farmers and merchants,
decided to form
their own special unit
of the Imperial Army.
But the leaders of the group
misled the people, lying about
free taxes and other things.
Then later, they were
all punished for that
by the restoration government.
So that's why the fighter's
coming for Kenshin,
because he's mad at anyone
associated with the royalists.
So why should he come
here picking a fight?
It's not Kenshin's
fault that they lied.
It's their own, and besides
he's swinging that zamba sword,
and it makes me very nervous.
That guy better not
hurt my Kenshin,
or he's gonna get it.
I'm hungry, Kaoru.
Me, too.
Yumi, I thought you two
were with Kenshin?
Kenshin told us
to come back here,
because he had to talk
with a strange man
who had really funny hair.
Yeah, he had really funny hair.
(giggles)
Oh, no!
Kaoru, I think
Kenshin's with the fighter.
Come on.
Wait!
(water burbling)
♪
Well, Battousai,
the moment has arrived.
So what do you say
we get started?
My name is Kenshin Himura.
♪
Enough talk, let's
get this over with.
♪
Oh, come on, Kenshin.
Where are you?
Kaoru, a farmer said
they passed through
this way about
ten minutes ago,
and they were headed
towards the riverbank.
Let's go!
(cackling)
A reverse, dead sword, huh?
You mean to tell me that
you're still gonna use that
against this mighty
and powerful sword?
I'll never understand your style
of only knocking
people unconscious.
♪
You fool!
(screaming)
Look, they're both over there!
Kenshin!
♪
Hey, Kenshin!
(grunting in pain)
(explosive crash)
(growling)
(sizzling)
Way to go!
That zamba sword is just
a big oversized hunka steel.
You showed him, Kenshin.
Kenshin, what is it?
(shouts)
(grunts)
But how could he possibly get up
after that kind
of a knockdown?
This man's pretty powerful
and really
proficient with a sword.
He knows how
to take a hit
and bounce right
back unscathed.
Well, now I completely
understand why
they call him a legend.
I'm very impressed, I must say.
Kenshin has defeated every
opponent with only one blow,
using his Hiten Mitsurugi style.
But now it's not working.
What'll he do?
You look upset.
As you can tell, one blow
will not win this fight.
But rather the most skilled
swordsman who refuses to quit
and who has the most
stamina will win.
So, do you think
you can go the distance?
You know, you're doing
an awful lot of talking
for a man who's just been hit
and slammed to the ground.
That's it, I've
had enough of you.
♪
You're history now!
(wind blowing)
Think again.
Your skills are not bad,
but you're limited by the
zamba's huge size and weight,
and you only have
two moves with it anyway:
the log split or
the mid-section slash,
and both of them are
easy to anticipate.
Sorry, party's over.
♪
If one blow won't do it,
then take this.
(rapid swishing)
♪
(gasps)
(groaning)
That was the
Hiten Mitsurugi style,
the Dragon's Nest Dodge.
Yeah, well it worked.
Hey, listen, I don't wanna
be forced to kill you,
so let's end this
meaningless fight.
Face it, you lost.
I can't lose to the restoration.
(fire roaring)
What?
Who says the Sekiho Force
is a phony Imperial Army?
You'll have to explain
yourself, Mr. Shindo.
I will repeat it again.
You have discredited
the restoration government
by promising a tax reduction
without any permission to do so.
Since you have
lied to the people
with false incentives,
the government has decided
to execute all of you
for the problems
you have caused.
This will give credibility
back to the restoration.
That's absolutely ridiculous.
The government told us
what to promise the people,
so we did.
Now I see.
The royalists needed some way
to get more people
to join the army,
but then the royalist
government found out
that they could not
live up to their promise
of the 50% tax reduction.
So like sly cowards,
they decided
to find a scapegoat:
Us.
They could blame it
on all the Sekiho Force
and then execute them.
Then the problem would go away.
That's what's
happening, isn't it?
Right, Shindo?
I only hope that isn't true.
When we started out,
we fought very hard
for the new era,
because we trusted
the restoration government
and believed they
were truly righteous.
And now, like dogs,
they turn their backs on us.
Captain, let me tell
you something about life.
A war is never
a beautiful thing.
There are no rules,
and life is treated
with little or no value.
May I remind you,
life is not fair.
Many sacrifices are made,
and yes, most of them unjustly,
like the sacrifice
that you and your men
are about to make
on behalf of the restoration.
What do you mean?
Riflemen, take aim.
(rifles clicking)
(panicked shouting)
♪
(fire crackling)
(panicked whispering)
I'm sorry I must do this,
but I have to carry out
the orders I have been given.
Captain.
Ah!
(grunts)
Fire!
(rapid gunfire)
♪
Oh, Captain!
(gunfire and shouting)
♪
(panting)
(rifles clicking)
(gasping)
(gunfire)
♪
(grunting)
Run for your life.
Get away.
I will not leave
you here to die.
There he is!
Quick, get up.
God bless you, Sanosuke.
(screaming)
Captain Sagara!
♪
The royalists of the restoration
used the Sekiho Force,
and then slaughtered
every one of us except me.
I lost my best friend,
Captain Sagara.
Sekiho Force?
Oh, that's right.
He must be
the one living survivor.
Sanosuke.
In that case, I'll
take care of him myself.
Die, Battousai.
(gunshot and steel ringing)
No!
This can't be happening!
(growls)
(cracks)
Huh?
-Ha-ha!
-Kenshin.
Ya, ha-ha-ha.
Battousai, don't even
try to come towards me,
or I'll take this claw
and cut these two
into little slivers.
You're really
an evil monster, Gohei,
and I wonder how you
ever got out of jail.
♪
Say goodbye, Battousai.
(gun clicks)
(pained screaming)
I thought I told you
to stay out of my fight.
I don't need
anyone to interfere.
Sanosuke.
I can handle
this fight on my own,
and I refuse
to be beaten by you.
But you've already lost.
It's over.
Accept it.
All right, you freak.
Let's see you stop a bullet
from this close range.
Hiten Mitsurugi style,
the Dragon Dodge!
(sonorous explosion)
(screaming)
Sanosuke Sagara.
I had no idea you were
the survivor
of the Sekiho Force.
Let's have one last round.
What do you say,
Mr. Legendary Swordsman?
Why don't you just give up?
Can't you leave
the past behind you
and quit blaming Kenshin?
You think Kenshin's
responsible for that decision?
He had nothing to do with
what you were talking about.
You people think the royalists
of the restoration were saints?
You have no idea
what they did to people.
They used us like chess pieces
on a game board.
I guess we were
human sacrifices.
What's he talking about?
I'm afraid he's right.
(together)
Huh?
The Sekiho Force was
used to recruit people
for the Imperial Army
who gunned them down.
So, I understand why
Sanosuke wants revenge
against the royalists.
But tell me one thing.
Don't say it.
Captain Sagara trusted
the restoration.
He was a good man.
They never told him
to betray the others
or lie to anyone.
Never.
For that I will never trust
you or any other royalist.
I understand.
Let's have our final match.
He knows what
Kenshin's gonna do!
(wind blowing)
(screaming)
Every day since the massacre
I have been training,
and now I will destroy
the best fighter
of the royalists.
Battousai!
I'm afraid your
revenge towards me
will work against you.
♪
Hiten Mitsurugi style.
This is the Dragon Hammer Dodge.
♪
You have incredible stamina.
You're the first
person I've seen
who could stand up
after such a blow.
♪
But you look
a little dizzy to me,
and you're shaking like a leaf.
So stay there,
and I'll get you a doctor, okay?
Not yet.
This thing isn't over.
I haven't lost.
Don't you turn your back on me.
I am not not gonna
let down Captain Sagara
and the rest
of the Sekiho Force.
No way!
Hey, come on.
Finish it!
(thud and grunt)
(gasping)
Well, you asked for it.
What did you learn
from the Sekiho Force?
That the restoration
was worth fighting for?
Or how to hold a grudge
for the rest of your life?
Shut up!
You and the rest
of the royalists
are phony liars who
deceived the people
and crushed anyone you felt like
in the name of
the restoration.
Just a second!
If there are any royalists
that lie and cheat people,
I'm sure there
aren't many of them.
And I can guarantee that
Kenshin is not one of them.
Can you get that
through your head?
So, don't you dare
compare Kenshin
with a few bad
apples in government.
He just turned down
a high ranking position
in the Imperial Army,
and now he's using
his sword to protect people.
That's right.
You got Kenshin all wrong.
You've heard too many fables
about Battousai, the legend.
And if you can't
get it straight,
I'm gonna have
to fight you myself
and teach you a lesson
you'll never forget.
Sanosuke, the restoration
is not over yet.
Huh?
Old habits die hard.
Unfortunately, there
are still many people
who are still being oppressed.
The people are the ones who
must carry out the changes
and make sure there's
peace throughout the land.
That is why I choose
to live my life as a wanderer.
Whenever possible, I uphold
the principles of the new era
and use my sword
to protect people.
Battousai the Slasher's
protecting people?
It's my way of giving something
back to those who have suffered.
It's not a bad life.
You might wanna think
about doing the same.
Come on, you guys.
Let's go get Dr. Gensai.
He reminds me of Captain Sagara
who fought for what
he believed in,
his faith that there
will be peace someday.
And Kenshin continues
to fight for the new era
by standing up
against oppression.
I, on the other hand,
had given up.
I became bitter,
and the only thing
I wanted was revenge.
I totally lost sight
of what I was fighting for.
Oh, Captain Sagara,
how did I get
so far off track?
Sanosuke!
♪
(echoing thud)
(crowd chatter)
Children, over here--
(rickshaw wheels rolling)
You sure gave Sanosuke
one heck of a beating.
I'm sure it's
going to take a while
for him to heal from all
those cuts and bruises.
Dr. Gensai said
it was a miracle
that Sanosuke didn't die.
I tried not
to hurt him too bad,
but he's a good fighter
so I had to give
him my best stuff,
and then he kept
asking for more.
I couldn't believe it.
He wouldn't quit.
Well, I'm glad this
thing is finally over.
Why don't we eat
a hot beef pie?
(crashing and shouting)
Oh, no.
What this time?
There are those two
rowdy trouble makers
we saw the other day.
(footstep)
I have never seen anybody
talk so much about being tough
and then trying
to pick a fight
when they had no idea
how to defend themselves.
Sanosuke.
I thought you had orders
to stay in the hospital?
Are you kiddin'?
I'm not stayin' in that place.
Besides, this little scratch
really isn't anything.
(poking and knocking noises)
You know somethin'.
You two are startin'
to get on my nerves.
All right, that's enough.
Why don't you cut it out, 'kay!
♪
Oh, Sanosuke.
Why don't you take
the Sekiho Force symbol
off the back of your coat?
Because they will
always be a part of me.
I've been thinking about
all those things
you said yesterday.
They're much easier
to say than do,
but I've decided
to let go of my anger
towards the death
of my fellow comrades.
I think it's time to forget
the past and start living today.
Besides, you were right.
Our work isn't finished,
and I know Captain Sagara
would want me to do
the same as you.
Huh?
So, if it's all right with you,
I'd like to hang around
and help you protect
people for a while.
I'm a new man.
Thanks to you, my friend.
I don't look it,
but I feel better
than I have in years.
♪
This way you won't be wanderin'
around by yourself anymore.
I'm hopin' you'll show me
some of those cool moves.
Oh, well.
It looks like
we can add one more nut
to this crazy group.
What do you mean
by one more nut?
Watch who you're calling
a nut around here, wise guy.
Sanosuke, oh, I hope
he comes back soon.
(gasping)
It sure makes
things a lot easier
now that he's fighting with us
instead of against us.
There he goes.
The latest member of our group:
Sanosuke Sagara.
♪