(theme music)
♪
Oh, yeah?
Is it true you know
where Kenshin is?
Take me to him, please.
I've come all this way,
I have to see him.
This must be the girl
Himura was talking about.
The one he left
behind in Kyoto.
She must have
come to find him.
♪
I can't believe it.
You're saying
Kenshin was here?
So, I guess we just
missed him then.
Oh.
♪
I had a feeling something
like this would happen.
I sensed Himura
left someone behind
that was very
special to him.
I can see it
in your eyes.
You must care
a great deal about him
to travel all this way.
I wish there was something
I could do to help you.
It's just I really
wanted to see him.
All right, so let me
ask you something,
are you aware that
Himura is preparing
for the biggest
fight of his life,
and that fight could decide
the future of this country?
Well, are you?
Well, yes.
You also understand
that your presence here
could undermine
Himura's concentration
and jeopardize
your own safety?
Knowing this, do you
still want to see him?
♪
I came all the
way from Kyoto.
I traveled a long
distance for the chance.
I'm really not here
to disturb him.
I only want to see
him again, that's all.
Ah.
I know how she feels.
I would do anything.
I would travel anywhere,
all over Japan and back
just to see
Aoshi again.
I miss him so
much it hurts.
All right.
I will take these
two to the place
that Himura
is staying at.
Is it all right?
Will you tell me
how to get there?
Hmm, take the map.
Yeah?
All right, Kaoru!
Let's go.
Well, do you two
want to go or not?
Yes, thank you.
And...
Thank you very
much for your help.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
(fire crackling)
(clinking)
(whooshing)
How impolite of you to attack
an ordinary ceramic artist.
Your mother should
be ashamed of herself.
Seijuro Hiko is no
ordinary ceramic artist.
It's been awhile...
...Master.
Oh my God.
Okina, Okina?
You have a visitor,
someone's at the gate.
I don't feel very well.
Tell him to
just go away.
Not a him, it's a
woman at the gate.
Hmm?
I changed my mind!
I thought you
didn't feel well.
I feel just
great now.
What a weirdo.
Ooh.
Here, I was asked
to give this to you.
It was given to
me by some guy.
Thank you very much.
And what did this
guy look like?
Well, he was a tall,
good-looking gentleman.
Actually, he was
very good looking.
Hmm.
(indistinct chattering)
Mom?
Mom, could you buy me
some of these, Mom?
Oh, I like the kind where
the heads go up and down.
I think we're gonna
have to ask your father.
Oh.
Hey, come over here.
♪
It's been a long
time since we talked.
Maybe I shouldn't
sit down before you
since you are the leader
of our organization.
Protocol is
not necessary.
Why didn't you
come to Aoi-Ya
to say, "Hello,"
since you're in town?
It just wasn't possible.
You know that Misao
has been asking a lot
about you lately.
She really
wants to see you.
After all, she's the
precious granddaughter
of one of our
previous great leaders.
I'm sure you want
her to remain safe.
That's why I
brought her to you.
I need to find someone.
Battousai Himura?
♪
(chiming)
Where is he?
I don't want
to tell you.
He's in training right now.
I'd say you need
to wake up, Aoshi.
I mean, don't you know
what's been going on lately?
You need to
heal your mind.
I don't need
advice from you.
Even though you are
a former Oni gang member,
you can't
understand how I feel.
Wait, Aoshi.
Let me tell you this,
I was responsible for
making you our leader.
If you lose the
pride of the Oni gang,
behave like a renegade,
and become a
liability to us,
I will personally
come after you
and destroy you with
everything in my power.
Do I make myself clear?
♪
Hmm?
What a surprise.
I'm glad to see
that you are in town.
What a coincidence.
Yes, is it also
a coincidence
that someone's
been following me?
Really?
Why are you
asking me?
I just got into
town myself.
Well, isn't
that interesting?
And I'm certain
you know nothing
about those
people watching me.
(chuckling)
Ah, yes, but I didn't
mean anything by it.
All right,
I sent them.
I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, see?
I hope you'll
accept my apology.
Let me make it all
up to you, my friend.
We're on our way
to see Mr. Shishio,
won't you join
us, please?
I told you before.
I'm not a joiner, I don't
want to pair up with anyone.
I didn't necessarily
mean to join us.
You didn't have any luck
finding Battousai, did you?
Well, I happen to
know where he is.
If you decide
to come with us,
I'll be happy to share
any information I have.
All right, I'll go.
Just take me there.
It's been 15 long years.
Why return now?
What is it that
you want from me?
I didn't know that
you'd changed your name
and that you're living
quietly as an artist.
Can you tell me why
you're living like this?
Being a ceramic artist is
a very good thing to be
if you want to avoid
meeting other people.
Besides, true genius can
excel in any occupation.
I see that you're
just as humble as ever.
Are you trying to
change the subject?
You have something very
important to tell me
and you're having a
hard time saying it.
Remember that I
was your master.
It's easy for me to
feel your anxiousness.
All right then.
I'm asking you to teach
me the secret principle
of the Hiten
Mitsurugi style,
which you were going to
teach me 15 years ago.
It's very important.
♪
I won't.
(gasping)
You were the one who left
without my permission
15 years ago, so why
should I teach you now?
♪
Hmm?
Teach me.
I beg you.
I can see that
this training
is very important
to you, Himura.
This guy's
Kenshin's master?
I can't believe
there's such a person.
Yeah, Seijuro
Hiko is his name.
I understand that
he is the master
of the Hiten
Mitsurugi style.
He has studied this
technique for 20 years.
So are you saying
Kenshin doesn't know
certain techniques of
the Hiten Mitsurugi style?
Maybe there are certain
aspects of the technique
he doesn't know, that's why
he went to see the master.
So, if he would master
those techniques--
Then he would be even more
powerful than he was before.
Wow, that's incredible!
As it is, he's
not even human!
This will make
him a monster.
(laughing)
I can't believe I'm going
to see Kenshin again.
I can't wait.
Every second seems
like an eternity.
I see, so Mr. Shishio
is back in town
and you have to go back to
being Battousai the Slasher
in order to
defeat him,
but you don't want to
kill him, is that it?
And in order to defeat
him without killing him,
you have to become
more powerful.
You want to develop
more strength and power,
and that's why
you've come to me.
But that's impossible.
Why is that?
Remember when you
were my student?
Remember what
I taught you?
A sword is
a murder weapon.
Swordsmanship is
a murder technique
no matter how you try
to look at it, Himura.
And no matter how you try to
make it clean and beautiful,
those are the real facts.
It's impractical to maintain
your optimistic ideas
in the face of death.
This mistake began
15 years ago.
(water whooshing)
What do you mean,
you're leaving?
-Yes.
-You fool.
You should concentrate
on your training
and not pay attention to
what's going on outside.
But how I can
ignore it, Master?
More and more people have
been dragged into the mess.
They're being killed
even as we speak.
Isn't the motto of the
Hiten Mitsurugi technique
to protect people
from the pain of life?
And so you think that
you're going to do that?
You're pompous.
Oh, yeah?
Go ahead if you
want to leave.
But you have to
defeat me first.
(shouting)
You didn't hold back at
all when you just hit me!
That's 'cause you don't
understand a thing!
You're the one who
doesn't understand!
Listen to me, Himura,
the Hiten Mitsurugi style
brings victory for the
person who masters it
because of its power.
It is a way to kill
efficiently, understand?
No, sir!
People are dying right
in front of my eyes!
I can't leave them like that
no matter what the reason is,
and I won't be like those
murdering pigs either!
You were such
a wild kid back then.
♪
And what happened when you
left me and your training
and went out
on your own?
You helped to cause
what's going on now.
Your sword technique was
superb but you were only
14 years old, a stupid
self-righteous pupil
who was immature.
You had a big heart
that was deeply wounded
and a scar on your cheek
that will never go away.
You are a swordsman
caught between killing
and not killing.
As a result, your
Hiten Mitsurugi style
ended up helping
to generate a ghost.
That ghost was at the
end of the Tokugawa era
and his name is Shishio.
♪
That's right!
The motto of the
Hiten Mitsurugi style
is to protect people from
the pain of time and of life,
but that's as
a free sword
which doesn't belong
to any authority.
You don't
understand that!
And so you are not
qualified to learn
the secret principle of
the Hiten Mitsurugi style.
Well, according to
the map, this is it.
Kaoru, want to go in?
Hmm?
What's the matter?
Are you frozen
or something?
Yeah, Himura is
on the other side
of that door right now.
-Go home.
-Huh?
It was a big
mistake for me
to teach the Hiten
Mitsurugi style
to a fool like you
in the first place.
Who are you
calling "a fool"?
What's that?
(grunting)
Hey, you!
Who do you think
you're calling "a fool"?
Who are these children?
This is Misao, Yoshi...
(gasping)
♪
It's Kaoru.
You're here.
♪
They're your friends?
-Uh huh.
-A lot of guests.
I didn't plan on having
a lot of people dropping
by unexpectedly today.
Kenshin, I would like you
to go down to the valley
and fetch me
some water.
-Water?
-Yes, go right now.
Why should I go?
Because I'm
out of water.
I don't understand,
why don't you go
and get the
water yourself?
You want the great
gift that you seek?
Fetch me water and
I'll consider it.
Mm-hmm.
Kenshin?
Himura?
What the--
Kaoru, why are you standing
there just like a statue?
Go talk to him!
You finally found him
after all your searching,
tell him how you feel.
Mm-mm.
Wow.
Kaoru, what in the
world's with you?
Hmm.
So, this is the master that
taught Kenshin how to fight.
He may be a master
but there is something very
strange about this guy.
Will you answer
some questions?
-Yes.
We have a question for you.
So how old
are you anyway?
Old?
I'm 43.
What difference
does it make?
(shouting)
He's a master
at that age?
Yeah, well,
Kenshin's only 29!
Is that right?
That's what I
said, didn't I?
Hey, don't
get so angry,
I'm just asking.
So, how's his
training going?
Oh, is that the reason you
came here, to find out?
Not really.
I came to Kenshin.
Oh, yeah?
Huh?
You see him and then
what do you want to do?
You want him to go back to
Kyoto with you, is that it?
Do you want to
open your heart
and tell him
how you feel?
Or maybe you just
want to fight with him.
Uh, no.
I just wanted--I just
really wanted to see him.
Just one more time,
that's all I wanted,
to see him again.
Huh?
I really don't
know what it is
that you all see in that
foolish student of mine,
but he certainly seems
to be very popular
with you strangers.
Now, hold on!
You don't know
anything about Kenshin.
You haven't seen
him for 15 years!
And that's exactly the reason
that I want to
talk to all of you.
Huh?
It's been 10 years
since the beginning
of the Meiji era.
What I want to know is
what Kenshin has been doing
with the knowledge that he
learned from me so long ago.
How's he been utilizing
that sword technique
that I taught him?
I don't want to hear
about it from him,
but rather from the
people that know him.
You've been
with him recently.
Kaoru.
The fact that Kaoru
and Yoshi came to Edo
probably means that
Sanosuke is here, too.
♪
This fight with Shishio
is all I must think about.
I can't allow anything to
divert my concentration.
♪
Mr. Shishio,
sorry to interrupt,
Sojiro is here.
Yes, it's nice
to be back here.
I brought you a
little something.
I sure hope that
it's good news
that you bring
me, Sojiro.
Great news, I brought you
the Ten Swords of East Japan.
Mm.
It's been awhile, Anji.
Have you finished
your training?
I have.
Nice to see you, I
hope you're not rusty.
No, sir.
Iwanbo, you look
as stupid as ever.
Who's this?
♪
Someone extra
added to the mix?
♪
Hmm?
Hmm.
Your friends here tell me
that you've been traveling
all around Japan as a
wanderer helping people.
It sounds as though
you've finally learned
the meaning of the Hiten
Mitsurugi style's motto.
Or is it possibly the
guilt of all the people
that you killed in the
war that made you do this?
That has something
to do with it.
If I happen to
be in a situation
where someone's
in trouble,
I can't look away.
I have to help them!
Yes, it seems you are still
blathering the same things.
I guess you'll
never change.
I've decided to teach
you the hidden secret.
You'll have the
whole technique.
No matter how we
feel about the past,
we can't let Shishio
run around, can we?
No, sir.
You will have to stop
Shishio on your own, Himura,
but you will do it
with my assistance.
♪
Come on, let's
get started.
Yeah, right!
♪
Uh, Kenshin?
Are you mad at me...
...for coming to Edo?
Part of me is.
Huh?
But the other part of me
is glad that you're here.
Let's go.
♪
Be very careful,
we don't know where
Shishio's group is hiding.
Take care of yourself.
It was good seeing you.
Kenshin?
What's wrong with him?
He won't even look me
in the eye anymore.
Does he wish that
I'd never come here?
♪
I have to tell
you one thing
before we begin, Himura.
Once you learn the
secret principle
of the Hiten Mitsurugi style,
you will possess powers
that are equal to mine,
but don't ever get cocky
'cause you might
end up dead.
Even with this
additional technique,
you'll still have to be
on your toes all the time
so that you don't sacrifice
yourself to save the world.
And the same thing
can be applied
to your individual happiness.
If you sacrifice yourself,
that woman and your friend
who came all the way
from Kyoto just to see you
will definitely be unhappy
if some harm comes to you.
Don't forget this.
No matter what
happens to you,
you're just a human
being, not a god.
You don't have
to become Buddha
or a fatality to win.
All right then, Himura.
Let's begin.
♪
From here to Shirobako?
There's no reason to go
at this hour of the night.
What are you
crazy or something?
Kenshin has started
his training to learn
the secret of the
Hiten Mitsurugi style.
Our presence here may
be disturbing him.
-I see.
-Are you all right, Kaoru?
I'm fine, really.
I came all this way to
see Kenshin and I saw him.
I have an idea, you two
could stay at my place
for as long
as you like.
Thanks a lot.
I wonder what the secret
of the Hiten Mitsurugi
style is anyway.
I don't know
but I understand
that it's a very
closely guarded secret.
Ah, really, I hear it's
the most powerful one.
That's really exciting.
Dang, there was something
I meant to tell Kenshin
but I forgot
what it was.
I can't believe how
lame my memory is lately.
I know, Aoshi!
That's right,
Aoshi's in Edo!
He's here to go
after Kenshin,
we have to warn him
about it right away!
Hey, I'll run
back and tell him!
Wait!
Misao!
Why'd you do that?
Is it true, what
you just said?
Is Aoshi really
here in Edo?
Aoshi?
He is!
Get away!
Yoshi!
Stay back!
This girl's one
of the Oni gang.
-Huh?
-What?
Why did you get
close to Kenshin?
Was that your orders?
Aoshi tell you to?
Or were you revenging
Han'nya and the others?
Revenge?
Han'nya?
What are you saying?
Please, I want you to
tell me what happened
between Himura
and Mr. Aoshi.
What happened to
everyone in the Oni gang?
Please tell me.
Don't act so innocent.
Just a minute,
Yoshi, calm down.
Kaoru, you don't
know what she is.
All I know, Yoshi,
is that because of her
I was able to see
Kenshin again.
Hey there, Kaoru.
You must know everything
about Mr. Aoshi, don't you?
Please tell me!
I'm begging you!
Ah, Kaoru,
don't tell her.
She has to hear this.
I'll tell you what
you want to know,
but I warn you,
it's a painful story.
♪
(theme music)