♪
(singing in foreign language)
(pendulum clicking)
♪
Thank goodness his fever
has finally gone down.
Will you get me some
fresh water, Yoshi?
All right, mm.
♪
Yoshi, tell me,
is Sanosuke doing any better?
Well, his fever's
finally broken,
and Megumi says he'll be okay
as long as he rests up.
Hey, great, that's good news.
I was worried about
him for a minute there.
I guess what I'm wondering about
is what kinda guy
did that to Sano?
He's a very good fighter.
This guy must have
been unbelievable.
Why did he do it?
♪
I wonder if this guy wanted
to settle a score with me?
But why did he have
to hurt Sanosuke?
What could he have possibly
gained by doing that?
I'm gonna have to find this guy,
and the sooner the better.
♪
Here's your ichiban.
Thank you for waiting.
Enjoy.
Thanks a lot.
I remember the noodles
are very good here.
Oh, you're only gonna have
one little bowl of noodles?
That doesn't seem quite
filling now, does it?
Isn't that right, Mr. Saito?
It's enough for me.
And the name is
Fujita now, all right?
I believe your name
is Akamatsu, right?
So what brings you here?
We have to talk.
This job was
originally my assignment.
(slurping noodles)
But Mr. Shibumi gave it to you
just because you're
a former member
of the Shinsen group.
Well I don't care
spit about that.
All I know is I was cheated.
Maybe that guy will kill you.
I hear he's one of the greatest
swordsmen in all the land.
He might hang you out
to dry like a Peking Duck.
I really don't like you.
I wouldn't care one bit
if you got killed or something.
Then the assignment
would revert back to me,
where it was
before you came along
sticking your nose in
where it doesn't belong.
(Fujita chuckles)
What's so damn funny?
I'm sorry.
I understand why you're upset.
I think it would be a good idea
if we did the job together.
You're right about this guy,
he is an excellent swordsman.
And don't forget,
two heads are better than one.
What?
You think for one second
that I would work with you?
You have to be
drinking some bad sake.
Please, just hear me out.
I found out where
Battousai lives
and left some clues for him.
Plus, I sent him a letter.
He doesn't have to be a great
detective to figure it out.
I did quite a lot of damage
to his friend and to his dojo.
He's got to know
it was me who did it.
He's just trying
to figure out why.
Believe me.
At this point,
he's more than eager
to fight me any place.
You're gonna trick him
into coming after you.
Is that it?
That's right,
I'll lure him into a trap
and you can have the honor
of finishing him off.
How's that sound, Akamatsu?
Sounds all right.
But I don't know
if I like this idea.
Battousai is the Shinsen group's
number one enemy.
Why would you
allow me to kill him?
It doesn't make sense.
Because if you
wanna know the truth,
I don't care about
that stuff anymore.
I just want to enjoy
the rest of my life.
If you can kill him
and get him out
of the way for me,
so much the better.
It makes it easier for me.
Understand?
Besides, I'd rather
make a little easy money
than risk my neck
making hard money.
Mr. Shibumi knows exactly
how I feel about that.
♪
(laughing)
I still don't trust you,
but now that you've
explained your plan
I understand.
Count me in.
Just don't forget,
I'm the top dog in this outfit.
Not you.
I'm the one calling the shots.
(laughing maniacally)
I'm glad you enjoyed your meal.
Come again.
(chuckling evilly)
He thinks he's top dog,
but not all
his dogs are barking.
(pendulum clicking)
(high-pitched echo)
Kenshin!
Kenshin, Kori wants
you to go into town
and get some tofu right now!
I'm sorry, Yoshi,
I'm goin' to run some errands.
I might be back late,
so be sure to lock up.
Tell Kori I'm busy
and that I'll make it up
to her another time.
Bye, Yoshi, see you later.
(door sliding closed)
Oh.
What!
That means that I have
to go and get the tofu.
That's great.
You expect me to flap
my wings and fly over there?
I got things to do!
Fish!
Get your fish!
Mom, I'm hungry.
♪
Saito, here I am.
You asked me to meet
you here in your letter.
Why don't you show yourself?
♪
(grass rustling)
(thunderous explosion)
That was a pretty
impressive move for a kid.
Or should I call you Battousai?
Why not?
Who are you?
I'll introduce myself.
I'm Yujin Akamatsu,
and I'm here to kill you.
(cackling)
Kenshin?
He went where?
He said that
he had things to do.
-So I went and got us the tofu.
-Thank you.
So, did he say anything else?
No, just that he'd be late.
Really?
I do remember
he was reading a letter.
A letter?
That's it, a love letter!
No wonder he didn't wanna
tell us where he was going.
Now I know why
it's a big secret.
Ha ha, that's the reason
he's gonna be late.
(shouting and gasping)
Phew.
Hey, don't you dare
drop this tofu.
It took me a lot of trouble
to go in town
and get it for you.
Kori, I was just
pulling your leg.
Besides, you really think
Kenshin would run
around with girls
knowing that Sano's so hurt?
Hey, snap out of it!
Huh?
I didn't believe
it for a second!
(laughing)
That was a good one, Yoshi.
I just can't believe
how gullible I can be.
(laughing nervously)
Excuse me, anyone home?
Huh?
I'm sorry to be disturbing you,
but I understand that Battousai
is staying right
here in this dojo.
Ah, Battousai, yeah.
So what do you
know about Kenshin?
Sorry, I should
introduce myself.
My name is Officer Fujita,
and I have only been
recently assigned to this area.
I heard all about Mr. Himura
from the police chief.
Oh, so you work for the chief?
Kenshin is not
at the dojo right now.
Is there something that
I can, ah, help you with?
No, thank you,
that's all right.
I was hoping to find him in.
Actually, I just stopped by
to ask him a few questions,
because we've
been getting reports
that someone is trying
to attack Mr. Himura.
Huh?
Would you mind terribly
if I waited here for him,
until he got back?
Uh, sure, but he might
be back very late.
It might take a while.
That's fine.
Kenshin.
(gasps)
♪
I don't know what
this is all about.
I don't know who you are
or why you wanna kill me.
But I have no intention of
giving up my life for nothing.
I think perhaps you need
to fill me in on a few things.
The reason?
Well, you want answers, huh?
Well, you can read all about it
on your tombstone!
(echoing explosion)
Hah, you think you would
escape that easily, Battou?
Huh?
I'm over here, Akamatsu.
You know, for a hired assassin,
you move pretty slow.
As a matter of fact,
that time I wasn't
even moving that fast.
(shouting)
(grunting)
You should give it up.
There's no way on Earth
that you can beat me, Akamatsu.
Huh?
(growls)
I want answers.
Who are you really?
Who are you working for?
And what is
your connection to Saito?
♪
Please forgive me.
Please don't hurt me, Battousai.
I didn't mean to hurt you.
It--it wasn't my idea.
Saito put me up to it.
It was his idea.
He threatened to kill me
if I didn't try to kill you.
This guy's pathetic.
Why is Saito using
a guy like this?
It's embarrassing.
I don't really believe
your story, Akamatsu,
but hopefully you
learned your lesson.
I won't hurt ya.
Oh, thank you.
Thanks for nothin'.
This guy doesn't give up.
♪
That was pretty slick
the way you got your hand up
in time to avoid being choked.
But what can you do now?
Both your hands are tied.
You can't move.
So there.
Who's laughin' now?
(shouting and groaning)
I may not be as light on
my feet as you, Battousai,
but I'm a hell of a lot
more powerful than you are.
(cackling)
♪
Somebody is after Kenshin?
Yes, and something tells me
that it's the same person
who injured Sanosuke.
Well, whoever it was
who attacked Sanosuke
is extremely ruthless.
I can only hope that
for Kenshin's sake
this lunatic doesn't
catch up with him.
Hmm.
Kenshin left earlier today,
and I don't know where he went.
Don't worry about Kenshin.
He can handle himself.
And as long as
that officer is here,
we should just stay
and wait for him.
I don't think the chief
would send this man here
if it wasn't dangerous.
We're safer staying with him
than running around
looking for Kenshin,
especially with
this madman loose.
You're right.
♪
Hey, I thought the police
were only supposed
to use a saber,
but that's not a saber you got.
That's a Japanese sword.
A saber is too brittle
and unreliable.
♪
I had to get special permission
to carry this Japanese sword.
The Japanese sword is the best
and has never let me down.
(echoing thud)
Huh?
(bird tweeting)
(sighs)
(laughs)
Huh, finally he's dead.
He sure lasted a long time.
I don't know who
you are, Battousai,
but you're one tough customer.
I don't know why a contract
was taken out on your life,
but Saito and I were hired
by a government official.
I think some politicians found
out about your whereabouts.
They were afraid
their evil deeds
from the end of the Tokugawa era
would become public.
You know how politicians are,
always afraid of some nasty
skeleton in the closet.
They were afraid you'd talk.
So they hired Saito
and me to get rid of you.
They wanted you silenced.
I see.
(gasping)
♪
I had heard that Saito
was one of the main assassins
of the Shinsen group.
I figured he would come for me.
This guy's unbelievable.
He's not human, I tell ya.
I can't believe that they
still harbor these fears.
They should get on
with their lives
and forget about what happened.
Oh, yeah?
(chains clinking)
I'll kill you!
(echoing thud)
This guy won't die.
♪
(bird calling)
(footsteps)
Hmm?
Ah, Kenshin!
Hi, Kori.
I was so worried about you.
How come?
Did something happen?
Just do me a favor,
Kenshin, and please stay home.
I don't like the idea
of you being out alone
when someone is after you.
Kori, who told you
someone is after me?
Why, the police did.
The chief sent over
an officer who's been here
waiting for you all day long.
This is the police officer I
was telling you about, Kenshin.
His name is Officer Fujita.
(gasps)
♪
Your swordsmanship must
have really deteriorated
if it took you this
long to defeat Akamatsu.
♪
I think it's been ten years,
Battousai, since I fought you.
It was at Toba-Fushimi.
Kenshin, do you know
Officer Fujita?
I know this person.
He has changed
his name to Fujita.
Yes, my name is now Goro Fujita.
Ten years, Battousai.
That's quite a long time,
don't you think?
Yeah, it's enough
time for someone
to become really
corrupt and evil.
Kenshin, what do you mean?
Jinei Udo was crazy
from the start,
but you were not.
You were always a man of honor.
You always fought face to face.
In the past, you'd never
injure the friend of an enemy,
be malicious, or hurt
some innocent bystander
just to bait an enemy.
You were above such
reprehensible behavior.
You are no longer the head
of the Shinsen group,
the man I knew as Saito.
(gasping)
(shouting)
Because that man was a samurai.
That man had honor.
That man was a man.
(laughing maniacally)
You can laugh,
but in your heart
you know that what
I'm saying is the truth, Saito.
You have sunk to new depths.
You disgrace the memory
of the Shinsen group.
He's after Kenshin.
Kenshin get out out!
♪
This is the guy
from your past, Kenshin,
and he wants to kill you!
♪
I thought that your
swordsmanship skills
had become dull,
but what I didn't realize
was that your mind has
become dull, as well.
I don't know what all your
ridiculous gibberish means.
All I know is that
the Battousai I knew,
the one we in the Shinsen
group called "The Slasher,"
would have dispensed
with Akamatsu quickly.
But he wasn't that
easy for you, was he?
No, as a matter of fact,
it took you some
time to defeat him.
You're slipping, Battousai.
♪
This new lifestyle
has obviously
slowed you down
and made you weak,
hasn't it?
He's not weak.
Be quiet!
♪
I don't need
to kill people, Saito,
to prove that I am strong.
I use my skill to protect
the people I care for.
I use my power
for positive things,
not to destroy.
I don't use it to hurt people.
Oh, that's touching.
Really heartwarming.
You don't deserve to live.
♪
Let me tell you something.
I've been waiting
here for you all along.
I told your friends
that I was a policeman,
and the fools believed me.
I was here the whole time
you were fighting with Akamatsu.
At any time, I could
have killed them.
I thought about slicing them up
and leaving them
for you to find.
But I thought it would be better
for them to watch you die.
I also know that
when they're here,
your concentration is shattered.
Just like with Jenai
and with Kanryu.
It's a definite edge
to keep them around.
That way you're
so concerned with them
that you're liable
to make some stupid mistakes.
Just like you did with Raijuta.
You made dumb mistakes that
allowed him to get to you.
♪
He must have been after
Kenshin for a long time.
He seems to know
everything about him.
Your great strength
has become mediocre.
You're nothing but a hypocrite.
Your simpleton ways sicken me.
Who do you think you are?
You can't say
that about Kenshin!
He's a masterful swordsman,
and all of us, all of us
are alive and well
because of him.
Do you really think so?
What about your
friend, Sanosuke?
(blood spurting loudly)
(echoing crash)
(metal snapping)
♪
I could have easily
killed him if I wanted to.
You're the one who
attacked Sanosuke!
Where was Kenshin when
I attacked your friend?
Just like you said, ten years
is enough time for someone
to become really
corrupt and evil.
You think you're satisfied
with your self-righteousness,
a wanderer who
doesn't want to kill.
But how can
Battousai the Slasher
protect anyone
without killing someone?
Have you forgotten?
♪
Evil.
Right now.
Murder.
That was us, remember?
The Shinsen group.
And slashing people
was the one thing
that made life worth living.
I can't stand
seeing you like this.
You've become a cowardly,
pathetic shell of yourself.
I don't really care
what you think.
You can say what you want,
but I have no intention
of killing anyone.
I see.
♪
Too bad.
First I will destroy you.
Then your friends.
♪
We'll just have to see
if your friends are
worth fighting for.
(gasps)
It's all right.
He won't stop
unless I fight him.
I'm scared.
I am, too.
But there isn't
any other alternative.
I have no choice
but to fight this guy.
♪
Kenshin,
don't go.
I don't want to lose you.
♪
(footsteps)
(gasps)
(drums echoing)
♪
(pendulum clicking)
(screaming)
♪
You're the best, Kenshin!
You beat that guy!
Kenshin's not weak.
He's still the best.
I anticipated that move.
Say goodbye to life, Battousai!
(blood spurting loudly)
(screams)
(cackling)
Ah, Kenshin!
♪