♪
(theme song)
In our last episode,
Yutaro deciphered an
ancient Japanese script
that told of
a revolutionary medicine
that could cure all diseases.
We set out to find this
incredible discovery.
We had to solve
several riddles
that were given to us
by the ancient writings.
We had discovered
the four dragons
that were symbolized by
four huge shaved logs,
when suddenly we were
attacked by Misanagi's ninjas.
What we didn't know
was that the ninjas
had joined together with the
secret deadly German order
called The Black Knights.
Together, they would
find the medicine
and use it for their
own evil purposes.
♪
Misao, where is the fortress
of the Sanada ninja force?
I'm not exactly sure,
I think it's
a little further on.
(groaning)
Kenshin, they must know
about the medicine.
Yes, but I'm
concerned about
the moves of
The Black Knights group.
I can't believe those
people who got the map
would stay quiet.
(groaning)
The Black Knight group.
So the reason why Sanada ninja
force's move was strange
was because they learned
about The Black Knight group
who wants the medicine.
(groaning)
What's wrong, Yoshi?
You tired already?
What's going on
with you, Yoshi?
(groaning)
No, it's, it's my stomach.
Huh?
Yoshi, what's wrong?
Yoshi!
It's a high fever.
He needs help.
Hey, who's that?
Is that guy Sanada?
What do you people think
you're doing here?
Take it easy.
We're just passing through.
We really didn't mean
you any harm, sir.
Our friend here has become
sick all of a sudden.
Hey, come on, Yoshi.
You'll all have to
come with me, then.
Huh?
Here, you should eat
some of this, Yoshi.
Maybe it's because
he drank that water.
I told him to be careful.
Yoshi was excited
about the spring water.
Maybe he had too much
and it made him sick,
you think that's it?
Don't worry about a thing.
You're friend
will be all right
as soon as he
takes that medicine.
He'll just need some rest.
Thank you very much,
thanks a lot.
There is no need
to thank me,
I'm sorry that
I frightened you.
Sometimes bad people
come here in search of gold
and in their greed,
they destroyed the hillside.
So tell me, have you lived on
this mountain for a long time?
I was born and raised here
and lived here all my life,
as did my fathers and
their fathers before them.
But tell me, my friends,
what is your business here,
what are you doing here
so deep in the mountains?
We've come here to
search for holy medicine.
We followed these words and
checked out the Suwa Shrine,
but I guess it's just
not the right place.
So tell me, have you
heard of it before?
I really can't
say that I have.
That's too bad.
But, uh, listen,
Suwa Shrine is a holy land
that is known to everyone,
and not only in Shinshu,
but all over Japan.
However, there is a
holy place, a secret place
that is known only
to the people of Suwa.
This place has been feared,
coveted and respected
for many generations.
Where is it, then?
There is a shrine
by Lake Riujin.
Where exactly
is this Lake Riujin
and just how
do we get to it?
If you must know, it is hidden
deep inside this mountain.
Sounds to me like
it's worth checking out.
I'll say.
I would urge you
not to do so.
Those of us who live here
are afraid of
this forbidden land.
It is cursed.
Oh, please, don't
call it a curse.
It's just superstition.
It's not superstition.
It's all true.
Very late at night, I myself
have heard the horrible howl
of a dragon coming from
the direction of Lake Riujin.
If you're smart,
take my advice
and stay away from
this forbidden place.
Thanks for everything.
You've been very kind.
Yoshi, come on, can't you
do any better than that?
Ow, I've been sick!
You didn't have to hit me!
Kori, that really hurt.
Just be thankful I didn't
hit you very hard.
Thanks a lot!
Well, it sounds like
Yoshi's feeling better now.
If you're going,
you must be careful.
The lake is very treacherous.
There is danger
at every single turn.
Thanks, you take care
of yourself, too.
Well, I guess we
should be on our way now.
Thank you again, sir.
♪
Well, they say
there's kindness
to be found everywhere.
That gentleman was
certainly proof of that.
He scared me at first,
but I have to admit,
that he was helpful.
Now if we could just find
some clue at Lake Riujin,
that would be
extremely helpful.
But his warning.
What was that
you said, Kenshin?
Nothing, just
thinking out loud.
Who are you, let me go.
I suggest you
forget about this.
That is, if you want to
continue to go on living.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
♪
You see, once they're
trapped in that mountain,
there's no way
they will ever escape.
♪
How much further
do we have to walk?
I don't see any lake.
There's not even
a puddle around here.
Will you please stop
complaining for once, Yoshi?
Yoshi, if you can't
walk anymore,
we'll just have
to leave you behind.
Hey!
Huh?
Oh, yuck, leeches, ew,
get em off, ew, gross!
Leeches, ew!
Oh, yeah, this mountain
is teeming with 'em.
(water lapping)
Finally, this has
got to be Lake Riujin.
That's right.
Well then, that
means the shrine
must be around
here somewhere.
(water lapping)
(sighing)
Well, it's a lot
smaller than I expected,
but it's definitely a shrine.
"When the four dragons
climb the moon,
and God crosses, it connects
to the tiger entrance."
Hmm.
The four dragons
must be the pillars,
but what does
"climb the moon" mean?
What do you think, Misao?
I don't understand that part
about God crossing either.
I think I know that one!
"God crossing" is a term
the locals use on Lake Suwa.
It means that when
the lake is frozen over,
sometimes you can hear
the ice crack really loud,
especially at night.
They call it
God crossing the ice.
But that's in
winter, isn't it?
Yeah, that's the
part I don't get.
Anyway, we should check
out those pillars first,
don't you think so, Sano?
Right, that much
I can agree with.
(insects chirping)
Hey, what's with the stone?
I don't know, looks like
a traveler's guardian deity.
Hey, Kenshin!
Look, guys, there's
another one over here.
Four pillars around a shrine.
That must be
the four dragons, right?
Do you really
think these things
are the four dragons?
I don't get it.
So tell me, how do
they climb the moon?
Moon...
(waves lapping)
Hey, this stone
is really loose.
Uh!
(water rushing)
What's happening?
I don't know.
Yoshi, are you crazy?
Why did you do
that, you idiot!
The curse, this
is the curse!
No.
It's got to be
the moon's gravity.
The moon's
gravitational pull
also causes
high and low tides.
Gravity?
Yes, as in Newton's
Law of Gravity.
Newton?
Which means--
Huh!
(water gurgling)
The water's draining out.
Ah!
(water spouting)
♪
Dragons climbing
to the moon, get it?
Wow!
Sanosuke?
Move!
♪
The whole lake is receding.
(footsteps running)
Will you look at that?
This must be
how God crosses.
♪
Well, come on, everybody,
what are we waiting for?
♪
That's incredible.
I can't believe my eyes.
You saw it, the lake
just drained away.
That's supposed
to be a miracle, right?
I'm not sure it's a miracle.
But somebody went to
an awful lot of trouble
to keep this place private.
Yeah, but who?
Don't fall in.
Hey, cut it out!
♪
Secret door.
Tiger entrance.
♪
Uh-oh, what in
the world's happening?
♪
Yutaro, wait!
Kenshin, are you
certain it is safe
for us to enter there?
Uh, well...
What else can we do,
we can't go back now?
♪
Yutaro!
Yutaro.
Look, you guys, you can
stay if you want to,
but I made a promise
and I have no intention
of breaking it.
Wait for us, will ya?
Great, now what?
I could never forgive myself
if anything awful happened.
All right.
(screaming)
♪
(stone sliding)
(water rushing)
♪
(water dripping)
According to the legend,
to get to a tiger's baby,
you have to go
into a tiger's lair.
Aw, Kenshin, it wasn't
all that difficult.
Yeah, well I wouldn't say
it's been very easy either.
Remember, we have been
pretty lucky so far.
Yeah, that's true.
Hey, Kori, you're getting
really scared now?
Get a move on and don't
be such a big fraidy cat.
Don't you push me!
(struggling)
Hey, you guys.
Yeah, well he started it!
(rock sliding)
Whoa!
-Kori!
-Yoshi!
Look out!
Oh great, Kori, now
we're trapped in here.
Ugh, why can't you think?
Ow, I could have
really gotten hurt,
no thanks to you.
Is everybody certain
they're okay?
Uh, Misao, do you mind?
Huh?
Oh.
Just what in the world do
you think you're doing?
Kenshin, you pervert!
There's something weird
about this cave.
I hear something big
and it's moving.
It's moving right for us!
What do you mean?
Something's coming
right at us!
(rumbling)
Ah, it's a big boulder!
It's gonna crush us,
we've got to run!
There's no way out of here,
that thing is
coming right at us!
Hmm.
I'll handle this.
(yelling)
(crashing)
Wow.
There, no problem.
Behind you!
What, behind me?
Get out of the way,
I'll take care of this.
(yelling)
(crashing)
Yeah.
That was really
an amazing move, Kenshin.
Maybe not.
Hello, the roof is caving in.
Oh.
You really should learn
to control that power.
Misao, stop pointing out
the obvious and run!
Oh, great, the path
goes in two directions,
so which way do we go?
Just follow me.
My instincts
won't let you down.
This way!
♪
(rock echoing)
It's bottomless.
One false step and I'm
afraid it's adios, amigos.
And there's no
other way across.
Maybe we should have
just gone right instead.
I say next time we do
the exact opposite
of Sanosuke's instincts.
I guess I should
have let that boulder
flatten you like
a pancake, huh?
I ought to flatten you!
All right, that's
enough out of you two,
let's just get outta here.
He's right,
let's keep moving.
(footsteps)
Ah!
Yutaro!
(panting)
Have a nice trip,
see you next fall, Yutaro.
Thanks.
Hey, what were you thinking?
It's just a worthless
rock, you idiot!
This isn't just a rock.
It's an important stone
that Dr. Hans gave to me.
Really, well I guess that
explains why it's much more
important to you
than your life.
You're really
pushing me, you know?
How about I push you right
off the edge of this bridge?
I just dare you to--
Shut up, both of you.
Would you two knock it
off and quit arguing?
Come on, let's
get out of here.
-Hmmm.
-Grrr.
Kenshin?
Huh, what is it, Kori?
I can't, I can't, I can't
walk any further, I'm scared.
Huh?
All right, Kori,
here, climb aboard
and I'll give you a piggy
back ride, all right?
Say, Kori?
What, Kenshin?
Do you mind if
I ask you a question?
Of course, Kenshin, anything.
Good.
Haven't you put on
a little weight?
Grrr, how dare you say
such an awful thing!
I haven't gained
any weight at all!
Are you sure about that?
I'm just as light
as a feather.
Huh?
(yelling)
(rocks tumbling)
♪
I certainly hope that
we can locate the place
where this medicine is soon
because I'm really
dead on my feet.
Don't give up
just yet, Kori,
it can't be too much
farther from here.
There's something up ahead!
Yutaro!
(footsteps running)
That's what
I call a dead end.
Oh, that's great,
now we'll have to go back
in the other direction.
Just try to
remember the legend.
"Though you may find yourself
lost in the darkness,
if you locate the Goddess
of Mercy's hand,
it will point to a road
at the bottom of Mount Fuji."
It's some kind of riddle.
This cave is the darkness,
that much I understand,
but, uh, tell me,
what does it mean
by the hand
of the Goddess, huh?
That's the part of the riddle
that completely escapes me.
I just don't get it.
I really don't
know what it is,
it must be
some kind of clue.
What are you doing?
What's going on,
were you able to figure
something out, Yutaro?
What are you
doing with that?
I'm certain that this stone
has some kind of meaning.
I wonder what?
Be very careful, Yutaro.
You never know
if this place
has been booby
trapped or not.
Oh, come on, Yutaro,
we're waiting here!
I guess that stone doesn't
mean anything at all, right?
(laughing)
(water dripping)
Oh, wow, just take
a look at this!
What?
Look at the face,
it's amazing!
Hey, Yutaro, you might
be onto something.
There are arms carved
in the back of this thing.
(roar of flame)
♪
Look, the whole cave
is lighting up.
♪
Listen, you guys.
What is it, do you
see something, Kori?
That shadow.
♪
It's the Goddess of Mercy!
If you locate the
Goddess of Mercy...
There!
Yutaro!
Look out!
(yelling)
(crashing)
♪
Wow, look at that!
"Though you may find yourself
lost in the darkness,
if you locate the
Goddess of Mercy's hand
it points to a road at
the bottom of Mount Fuji."
In other words,
it's a good thing you
kept that stone, Yutaro.
I think you just
led us to the medicine.
Hey, congratulations.
Yes, all right!
Then it looks like that
medicine's as good as ours!
(laughing)
Well, it certainly
took you long enough.
Want your medicine?
(laughing)
Who are you?
♪
The Black Knights.
Just look and see
who's with 'em.
It's the head of
the Sanada ninjas.
It was my plan
to trap you here.
However, I'm impressed
that you were able to
open up that final door.
And I sincerely
congratulate you.
Just what is this
all about, lady?
Yeah, you better start talkin'
and I mean right now!
Hey, you better watch your
temper, you little peon.
Just who do you think it was
that cured your illness
in the first place?
Uh?
So I guess you
disguised yourself
as that old man.
It certainly did the trick.
But why, why do that?
Disguised as that fisherman,
she tricked us into coming.
You knew we'd come
for that medicine
the whole time.
But for some reason,
you got here before us
and must know
something we don't.
I want some answers and
I want 'em right now.
Hey, Yutaro, any idea what
she could know that we don't?
She must know
the final sentence
from the doctor's notebook.
How right you are.
"Though you will find yourself
lost in the darkness,
if you locate the
Goddess of Mercy's hand
it will direct you to a road
at the bottom of Mount Fuji.
But the path is deadly
and leads to an abyss."
We're on an abyss!
Look out!
(yelling)
♪
(theme song)