♪
(singing in Japanese)
I hit it high!
Here you go!
Up it goes!
Is that right, Sanosuke?
Kenshin and Kaoru
went to the theater
this afternoon together?
Yeah, Tae from
over at Lenny's
had two extra tickets
and gave them to them.
It's really good
that they got to
go out and see
a show together,
after everything they've
gone through recently,
they deserve
a good time out.
Right, Yoshi?
What are you saying?
Ever since Kenshin
and Kaoru left,
I have to do all
of his work, too,
and I have no time to
practice my sword work!
Hey, you shouldn't
be complaining--
you should just
think of it as
a different
kind of training.
Right, Yoshi?
Training?!
If you ask me,
this is nothing more
than slave labor!
Sanosuke,
could you please
play with us?
Eh, sorry, girls,
I'm really busy
right now.
Aww, that's
really too bad.
I wish that
Kenshin were here.
Hey, wait
just a minute,
I have a great idea.
What?
How would you
like something
good to eat?
Yeah!
Hey, Yoshi?
Huh?
We're hungry,
we want a snack.
Why don't you make some
sweet potatoes for us?
What?
I'm busy!
We want sweet potatoes!
See that?
The children
are very hungry.
I haven't finished
the laundry yet,
and I still have
other work to do!
I have to
clean the dojo!
Oh, come on,
just knock it off,
quit being
such a whiner.
Can't you see
they're hungry?
(coughing)
That darn Sanosuke!
Who does he
think he is?
I'll get even
with him if it's
the last
thing I do!
One day, Sano!
That was a
wonderful show,
did you enjoy it?
Oh yes, but it's
very late now.
I think we should
get back to the dojo.
Oh, I can't even
remember the last time
I had so much
fun, Kenshin.
I had a real nice
time, too, Kaoru.
You sound as though
you didn't have
that great of a time.
Is there something else
that's bothering you?
Well, to tell
you the truth,
I couldn't completely
relax because I was
thinking about dinner,
and all the chores
I have to do.
What?
Let me get
this straight.
You weren't having
a good time because
you were thinking
about all of your chores?
So, you're saying
you weren't thinking
about me at all!
That wasn't what I--
Huh, oh...
Kaoru, look there,
isn't that a really
nice carriage?
It's very nice.
Hey, Kenshin,
are you trying
to change
the subject?
Well,
actually, I was...
Hmm?
Huh?
What's that noise?
Hey, where
are you going?
You thieves won't
get my carriage!
Come on,
let's get him!
Oh!
He'll get killed!
We should stay
out of this.
He's good.
He's very skilled
with his sword.
Uh-oh...
He's outnumbered
by all those thugs!
(commotion)
And just
who are you?
I'm someone who
doesn't like the odds
three to one.
You should back off
and leave this man alone.
Sticking your nose
in other people's
business will
get you killed!
Get him!
Ahh!
Who is this guy?
Let's get
out of here!
And don't come back!
Are you all right,
my old friend?
I don't know
you, young man,
but I appreciate
your helping me.
There's someone
in the carriage.
Oh no,
the Prince...
Oh, Your
Highness...
(groans)
Huh?
Yoshi, what are
you doing in those
strange clothes?
What are you trying
to pull this time?
Oh...
You'd better
answer me right now!
Stop it!
What's the matter
with you, girl?
It's all right, sir,
I know this young man.
Get away from him!
What do you think
you're doing, anyway?
Do you have
any idea who
this young man is?
He is Prince Shin
from the Kingdom
of Jagarata.
Huh?
Just what is he
talking about, Kenshin?
I don't know, Kaoru.
This kid isn't Yoshi,
he just looks amazingly
like him.
Hmm?
Oh...
He looks exactly
like Yoshi.
How could they
possibly blame you
at all for
thinking it was him?
I feel really terrible.
I went up to
a complete stranger
and started
slapping him.
How could I do that?
Sorry, please,
forgive me.
We come from the
Jagarata Kingdom.
It's a very
tiny kingdom.
Prince Shin here
is our ruler.
He came to Japan to
improve the relationship
between our
two countries.
Dr. Gensai, tell us,
is Prince Shin doing
any better?
Well, actually, his
injury's not that bad,
but he is very weak
and dehydrated from
his journey.
He needs lots of fluids
and plenty of rest.
We would be happy
to let you stay here
while he recovers.
That's very
kind of you,
thank you
very much.
It's nothing.
Recently,
Prince Shin's father,
the King,
passed away.
Since then, the
Prince has been
carrying the
entire country
on his young
shoulders.
He is so young for
such a responsibility.
I don't know what will
become of our kingdom.
Why did this
have to happen?
Are you the Prince's
grandfather or something
like that?
I apologize, I forgot
to introduce myself.
I'm Marcus Murakami,
and I've served
the Prince
since his birth.
My ancestor was
a very great samurai
who built a Japanese
town in Jagarata.
Oh, your ancestor
was a samurai?
So that's why you
carry a sword with you.
That's right, I am
the Prince's protector.
I realized that I am
old and that I needed
your help earlier.
But when it comes to
the safety of our Prince,
I will give my
life to protect him.
If anyone dares harm him,
he will have to deal with me
and the sword
of a samurai.
I'll give him
this and this!
Watch it--put
that thing away!
Are you sure that
it's entirely safe
to keep this old
guy around here?
Huh?
Sorry about that.
By the way,
Mr. Murakami,
do you have any
idea just who those
thugs were that attacked
your carriage today?
I have no idea
who they were.
Who'd want to
hurt the Prince?
Times are very
tough right now,
and a lot of
the old samurai
have become
criminals in order
to get money to eat.
It's sad, but
true, I'm afraid.
I wonder if that's who
those guys were today.
I have no idea.
Oh, what am I
gonna do now?
Why, what's
the matter now?
We are here because
Prince Shin has been
invited by your
country as a guest
of honor to a very
prestigious dinner.
It would be
a great sign
of disrespect for
him not to attend.
He's not well
enough to go!
I was afraid of that.
Gee, this guy's
really upset about this,
isn't he?
Hmm?
Hi guys,
I'm glad to see
you finally made
it home tonight.
Ahh!
It's impossible!
This kid looks
like the Prince!
That's right,
this is our friend,
Yoshi.
Who is this
guy, anyway?
Hmm, his resemblance
to Prince Shin
is truly astounding.
Wait a second!
I think I know what
you're thinking, Kaoru.
We have an idea!
Hold on a second,
I just had a great idea!
♪
Your Highness,
I respectfully request
to borrow
your clothes.
What's going
on in here?
Hold it right there.
-What's that?
-Easy.
Yow, what in the
world are you doing?
Get off me,
crazy old man!
Just relax, Yoshi.
Let go of me,
you big baboon!
Ugh!
What are you
gonna do with that?
Ahhh!
I can't believe it,
it's as though
they're identical twins!
These are real
goofy clothes.
(laughter)
Haven't you heard
that expression,
"The clothes
make the man"?
You look very nice
in that, Yoshi.
You look
like royalty!
Well, I hate
these clothes.
Why do I have
to dress like this?
I feel like a clown!
Mr. Yoshi, I beg
you to help us out.
Huh?
I've never asked
a favor of any man,
but I'm asking
a favor of you.
You're the only one
who can help Jagarata.
It's a matter of
national consequence!
Jagarata?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Kenshin,
what's he saying?
What's going on here?
Would somebody
please answer me?
That man was darn
good with a sword!
He ruined our
assassination attempt
with the Prince.
Yeah, I don't know
when we'll have another
chance like
we had tonight.
That sure was
a weird sword he used.
Hmm?
I thought for sure he
had sliced my hand off,
but look,
it's still here.
He could have
sliced it off
if he wanted to.
Don't worry, sir,
the Prince won't
get away
from us again.
We'll make
sure of that!
See that you do
and be certain
that you don't
screw up again!
Uh...uh...
Now take a
look at this.
The Prince
will be here
at a dinner
party tonight.
Now, the dinner
party is tonight,
that doesn't leave
us very much time
to transform you
into a royal person.
I still don't
see why I have
to go through
with this.
I feel completely ridiculous
in this stupid outfit!
I've explained it.
We have been all
through this already.
If the Prince
doesn't attend,
Jagarata will lose
face in Japan's eyes,
and we could be
devoured by other
powerful countries.
The very existence
of our country rests
on the Prince going
to this party tonight.
Do you understand?
All right, already,
I'm sorry that I asked.
I'll go
through with this,
just tell me
what I have to do.
The first thing
you have to do
is to learn
some manners
so you behave
like a Prince.
Manners?
What is that?
Does that mean
I have to put on
some other
stuff or what?
Stop that!
Ow, hey, what's
the big idea?
Now, listen,
if you behave
inappropriately
at the party tonight,
it'll be an
embarrassment
to our country
and I won't have it.
Do you understand?
Yeah, I understand that.
Good.
What is it with
this old guy?
I try and
do him a favor
and this is how he
decides to repay me?
Now pay attention, Mr. Yoshi.
We've a lot to do
and little time
to do it in.
I've asked your
friends to help.
All of my friends
are gonna help us out?
Yes, and as a
matter of fact,
they're coming now.
Oh, well
dressed, too.
What do you
think, Yoshi?
Hey, Kaoru,
why in the world
do we have to be
dragged into this
thing anyway?
We have to go
as his entourage
and make sure nothing
bad happens to Yoshi.
You look great.
Yeah?
Thanks, I'm...
I'm not used
to wearing nice
clothes like these.
For royalty, I mean.
Well, I think you
look very handsome
dressed like
that, Kenshin.
In fact,
in these outfits,
I think we make
a beautiful couple,
don't you?
Kaoru, this isn't
the time or place
for this!
Ooh, you do make
a lovely couple.
Knock it off, Sano!
Why do I always
have to wait forever
when there's
a woman involved?
Keep quiet!
All right,
now pay attention.
We will now work on our
proper dining etiquette.
Good, 'cause
I'm starving!
Let's eat!
Thank you,
we shall now eat.
(slurp)
This soup sure
tastes different
than the one
at the dojo.
That isn't soup,
it's puree you're eating.
And always remember
to use the proper
spoon when eating it.
I'd say the proper
spoon is this one.
It's tasty.
Mmm, it's too thick.
Mmm, and it could
use some more salt!
Mmm, it tastes good,
but the texture's
a little
soft for me.
(groans)
Next course.
Now that's a steak!
Wow, that looks nothing
like the steak we get
at Lenny's.
You can say
that again,
but where are
the chopsticks
to eat it with?
I don't see
them anywhere.
Where did
you put them?
They don't
use chopsticks.
You should be
using your knife
and fork to
eat a steak!
Sanosuke,
he means these.
Oh, yeah,
here they are.
Oh, this
thing is tough!
I can't get
a bite out of it!
You knucklehead!
Put it back
on your plate
and cut it
into pieces.
I just can't get it!
Huh?
Hmm?
Just what does
Kenshin think
he's doing?
I don't know.
Very nice.
Way to go, Kenshin.
Hiten Mitsurugi
style of eating.
Just a flick of
the wrist, really.
I hope this works.
Go here and
here and there.
That's right,
Susie, very good.
Ayame, it's
your turn now,
you give it a try.
Go here and
here and there.
That's very
good, Ayame.
You are doing it right.
Great!
What is the
Prince teaching you?
He's teaching us
how to say "hello"
in his native Jagarata.
He also knows
how to speak
very good English.
I learned how
to speak English
from my protector,
Mr. Murakami.
Mm-hmm,
mm-hmm.
My back itches
from sitting in
that chair
all day long!
Himura.
Huh?
Mr. Yamagata.
If anyone
talks to you,
don't say anything.
It's acceptable
to bow politely
and listen silently.
Smile but don't
speak, or everyone
will find you out.
Huh?
It looks like
Kenshin disappeared
and took off
on his own.
The most important
thing for you to
remember is to
maintain your dignity
at all times.
So, you're saying
that tonight I should
act important?
In a manner of speaking,
you are correct, sir.
Hey, you, you big
dumb roosterhead!
Huh?
Get over here
and shine my shoes!
Why, you little rat!
Don't do that!
You must be
subordinate
to Prince Shin.
Yeah, have some
respect for your Prince!
That's right, Sano,
you must treat Yoshi
like a prince, and
have respect for him.
Hey, dogface,
don't just stand there,
my back aches.
Give me a backrub.
Why, you little
smart-ass!
Please, Miss Kaoru,
to help Jagarata,
you must
remain patient.
I'm depending on you.
Please don't
let me down,
I beg of you.
Let's go, snap
to it, you two,
I don't
have all day.
(humming)
♪
Yeah, this is great,
I could really get
used to this.
This royalty
thing ain't so bad.
There's a spot
on this one.
Do it again.
You little rat!
Hey, dogface, this
isn't a coffee break,
get into it!
Why you,
I oughta!
I could show that
Prince how it's done!
Ha-ha-ha!
I'd like to speak to
you about Prince Shin,
who is visiting Japan.
He is an important
diplomat to us.
What do you
know about him?
According to our
army reconnaissance,
some assassins have
been hired to try
and kill the Prince
while he is here
visiting our country.
His country,
Jagarata,
is the only country
between many European
countries and Asia.
For any country
trying to expand
their way East,
Jagarata is an easy target.
Why are they
trying to kill him?
With the Prince dead,
the country would have
internal turmoil,
and the Europeans
could colonize
their nation.
Inajiro, a dangerous
double agent, is behind
an assassination
attempt on Prince Shin.
And that is why
I need your help,
Battousai.
Would you agree to
protect the Prince?
We can't afford to
have any kind of
international incident.
Hmm.
If the Prince
is assassinated,
it would be the
end of Jagarata,
and it could spark
a civil war in
our own country.
You don't want
any trouble, huh?
Well, even if you
hadn't contacted me,
I would have
protected the Prince.
What?
♪
I'm extremely honored
to meet you, Prince Shin.
Ah, yes,
my friend.
Ow, what'd you
do that for?
Uh, quiet!
(clears throat)
We were just
goofing around.
♪
And just where do you
think you're going?
Yeah, Yoshi,
you better stay here.
Take your hands
off of me!
I have to go
to the bathroom,
is that
all right?
(gasps)
I've got a bad
feeling about this.
He'll be back,
he's just gonna go
to the bathroom.
Ahhh.
I'd rather be back
cleaning the dojo
than attending
this party.
This is perfect.
(whistles)
Umm...huh?
What the...
Ahh!
♪
Miss Kaoru,
Mr. Sanosuke!
Hmm?
I don't see
Yoshi anywhere,
have you seen him?
Do you know
where he is?
Last time we saw him,
he said he was going
to the bathroom.
But actually,
that seems like
quite a while ago.
Yeah, you're right.
I just hope
that nothing bad
has happened to him.
Why would you
say such a thing?
I'm concerned
for the boy!
All right, now I've
had enough of this.
If Yoshi's in danger,
we want to know,
so start talking!
We want to
know everything!
Uh...all right.
Here's the truth.
I think someone
is trying to kill
the Prince.
Those samurai yesterday
weren't there to rob us.
I believe they were
there to assassinate
Prince Shin.
You put Yoshi
in danger knowing
all this about the Prince
and you didn't
even say anything?
I'm so very sorry,
I wanted to protect
my Prince
and my country.
Please,
forgive me!
Well, we can't
stand around here,
we gotta
find Yoshi.
Come on!
Yeah, we better
find him right away!
I'll help you!
Who are you guys?
That doesn't matter.
We've come for
you, Prince Shin!
Leave me alone,
I'm not Prince Shin,
you've gotta
believe it!
See that,
I'm speaking
English right now!
Ha!
You can't fool me.
I know Prince Shin
can speak English!
Come on,
let's get him!
That's a bad idea!
Don't let
him get away!
You can't escape!
Yoshi!
Ahh!
Sanosuke!
Ahhhh!
Yoshi!
Now you're mine!
Ugh!
Huh?
♪
Kenshin!
Hey, it's that
guy from yesterday!
Now you're gonna pay!
Prince Shin, catch!
All right then,
let's see how
you handle
that thing.
Let's show
these guys
how to fight.
Oh, you got
us shaking
in our boots, kid.
I'll kill the Prince,
you two take care
of the intruder!
-Yes, sir.
-Right!
(commotion and yelling)
♪
Yoshi, look out!
(gasps)
♪
Mr. Murakami!
Stay still.
I'll do everything
that I can as a protector
to keep you safe,
just as I would
for the Prince.
That's the only way I
can repay your courage.
Ah!
Prince Shin
of Jagarata,
they will say
you died in Japan
at the hands of thugs.
The party's over.
-Not yet!
-Huh?
♪
(shouting)
Ahhh!
♪
That's it!
Give me that.
♪
Give it up, pal!
Huh?
Officers,
arrest those men!
Yes, sir!
Do you think you
can try to stand up?
It's only
a flesh wound.
Murakami!
Oh, are you
all right?
Himura.
Hi, Mr. Yamagata.
You see,
you really had
nothing to worry
about, after all.
Mr. Marcus Murakami
saved Prince Shin
of Jagarata.
Thank you, sir.
Here comes the Prince!
Hurry, everyone, outside,
the Prince is coming.
He's coming!
Look, look!
There he is!
He's handsome!
I never thought
I'd see him!
There he is,
there's the Prince!
So impressive!
How are you feeling,
Mr. Murakami?
How's your injury?
Fine, it was
only a flesh wound.
Mr. Yoshi,
thanks for your help.
Jagarata owes you
a debt of gratitude.
I'm sorry I caused
you so much trouble.
Thanks for
pretending to be me.
That's okay,
we do look alike,
and I kind of
enjoyed being
prince for a day.
Although, I'm happy
to be my old self again.
Hey, Your Highness?
Yes?
Go here and
here and there.
Right!
♪
Susie, Ayame,
what was that
you were doing?
We won't tell you.
It happens to be
a secret between
the Prince and us.
What?
(laughter)
Good bye!
See ya!
Have a safe journey!
Thanks so much!
I wonder if
we'll see him again.
I don't know,
I hope so.
He really did look
just like Yoshi,
didn't he?
I think Yoshi
and the Prince
look exactly alike.
Oh, yeah?
Actually, I think
I look better!
You are a vain
little twerp!
Who are you
calling a twerp?
Now, now!
Roosterhead?
Why, you little rat!
You runt!
♪
(singing in Japanese)
♪ It's gonna rain ♪
♪
♪ It's gonna rain ♪♪