♪
(singing foreign language)
(indistinct conversations)
♪
Hey, let's go in there and
see the two-headed snake!
Let's pick a show that
we all agree on, okay?
-Okay, that one!
-This one!
(chuckles)
You guys are impossible
when it comes to decisions.
Whoa, what a crowd.
Why do we always have
to do what you want?
We better hurry up or
we won't see anything.
You're stupid.
And you're a punk whose got
a little pea for a brain.
Hey, would you two
please stop arguing?
Oh, hey, let's go there.
(together)
Huh?
Japan's scariest haunted house.
I'm really not interested
in the haunted house.
That's 'cause you're afraid.
-Uh-uh.
-Is too!
(growling)
♪
So, how do they make sure
that it won't come and get us?
What's that?
A creature with
a seven-foot head.
(screaming)
(together)
Help, a vampire!
Ah, a beheaded queen!
(together)
Get off us, you goblin!
Those three are spooked
out of their minds.
Yeah, what a bunch
of wimps they are.
Hm, take a look, Yoshi.
The scary monster
reveals itself.
(laughing)
And look at this, it's just a
rope tied to each of the wings.
They just yank on it
a couple of times.
Oh man, this place will
scare ya to the bone.
Yeah, Japan's most
haunted house.
Maybe we should go find
the girls before they run
all the way to Tokyo.
Or dive straight into the sea.
Are you okay?
-Hey, we're sorry about that.
-It was an accident.
Our friends scared
us half to death
as some kind of stupid joke.
Are you okay?
(groaning)
♪
(indistinct conversations)
Wow!
Just look at all the people
waiting for this show.
Magnificent Marimo,
the Human Cannonball.
That's unbelievable,
let's check it out.
Yeah, you and everybody else.
♪
(bull growling)
(grunting)
♪
(panting)
(crying)
It's okay, shhh.
That damn cannon girl is
messing with my business.
As a matter of fact, it's
a very impressive show
they've got there, you
should go see it, boss.
I have, and it's
making me really mad.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we welcome you
to the greatest show on Earth.
Thank you for joining
us this afternoon.
And now without further delay,
allow me to introduce to you
the one, the only,
the Magnificent Marimo,
the Human Cannonball!
♪
Wow, isn't she
absolutely beautiful?
I hope she knows
what she's doing.
Ta-da!
Thank you, thank you, thank you!
(applause)
♪
-I'm kind of scared for her.
-I wouldn't worry about it.
After all, they're
professionals.
Besides, I'm sure
they've done this act
at least a thousand
times before.
Begin the countdown!
Three, two, one!
(cannon blasting)
(cheering)
♪
Ta-da!
Ladies and gentlemen,
my daughter,
the Magnificent Marimo!
Did you hear that?
They're a father
and daughter team.
-Isn't that fantastic?
-Yeah, they're great performers.
(cheering)
Thank you!
-Thank you!
-Ta-da!
That's it, the show's over.
Yeah, you heard
him, cannon girl.
Did you hear that?
Kenshin, why is it
you're stopping him?
Because I wanna hear exactly
what they have to say.
Hello, Sumidaya.
Just what are you up to?
Hello there.
Quite a big audience
you've packed in here
for your show today, Jiro.
And make no mistake about it.
You owe me big time for all
your success and good fortune.
We've been independent from you
Sumidaya, and you know it,
so your threats
and intimidation
are not about to scare me.
Think again.
You forget you owe
me plenty of money.
I built you up, and
I can bring you down.
You'll either meet my
demands or you'll burn.
Okay, I'll listen.
I'll give you what you want,
just don't hurt my daughter.
I don't know if I can do that.
It all depends on how
much you cooperate, Jiro.
By the stroke of midnight
tomorrow you must pay off
the remainder of
your debt to me,
or surrender your
act to my operation.
-Let's go, Hooka.
-Yes, sir.
♪
-Ah!
-What the hell are you doing?
No one messes with me.
Quickly, we've gotta put it out!
Did you see that
look on his face?
Yeah, as frightened
as a circus mouse!
-I just don't like those guys.
-Huh?
They shouldn't intimidate
people like that.
Come on, let's get 'em!
-Hey, where's Yoshi?
-He's right down there.
(grunting)
-Ah!
-Oh, hi.
I didn't mean to bump you.
Yoshi is my name, and I just
want you to know that was
absolutely incredible when you
got shot out of that cannon.
Thanks, I'm Marimo,
and thanks too
for helping me put
out the fire, Yogi.
It's Yoshi!
(laughing)
So, you've fallen for the
cannon girl, huh Yoshi?
It's always obvious when
your cheeks turn red.
Her real name is Marimo,
and she's just
a new friend of mine.
Why you old
cannon-kissing Romeo.
-I smell love in the air!
-Mhm, mmm.
-Hey, wait, where are you going?
-Out for a walk.
Yeah, and that
full moon outside
might make you feel
even more romantic.
Poor Yoshi.
He's gotta learn to take
a joke a little better.
Do you think he's all right?
He must be worried about Marimo.
He really hates it when
people get pushed around.
Don't worry, Marimo,
everything will be all right.
-Oh, hey!
-Hey!
Watch where you're going!
Huh, my wallet!
(panting)
Hey, come back here you thief!
(crashing)
Father, are you all right?
It's going to be okay.
Help, he--
Who are you?
What do you want?
Guess.
(screaming)
Huh?
♪
Hey, let go of me!
It looks like you won't be
able to make tomorrow's show.
Tough luck, my
little flying friend.
Hey, back off!
(together)
Huh?
-Oh, help me, Yogi!
-You mean Yoshi!
♪
That's it, punk.
This punk will kill
you if necessary.
♪
Come here!
-You'll pay for this.
-I'm out of here.
Come back here, I'll--huh?
Please help me,
my father is hurt.
Then we must hurry.
All right, there.
That will protect your
wounds, and help you heal.
Good.
With this sling, at least I'll
be able to perform tonight.
Father, you have to rest.
You were hurt very badly.
I know that Sumidaya
is to blame for this.
I'm going to the police.
I am not going to the
police without any proof,
and we need the money from
tomorrow night's show.
But what should we do?
I'm not about to stand by
here and watch these goons
try to pressure you into
losing your business.
Yoshi, you don't understand.
I am legally obligated to pay
the debt I owe to Sumidaya.
You see, with the money we
could make from tomorrow's show,
we might just be able to pay
off the balance of our loan.
When I get a hold of these
guys, I'm gonna make them pay!
I've got to get up
and make sure that--
Sir, you must stay still.
Listen, Father.
I've decided I'm going to put
the show on all by myself.
No, you're not.
-Wha--wha--how come?
-Because I said so!
If you make the smallest
mistake, it's possible
you may never be
able to walk again.
-But--
-I know my way's the best,
and you must believe
and trust what I say.
Sir, I can help out,
I'm smart and brave.
I'm sorry but using gunpowder
is much too dangerous.
Hey, you know what,
I'm a pretty good cook.
(together)
Huh?
Just show me the exact recipe,
and I'm sure I
can bake it right.
♪
-I smell blood.
-Doesn't it smell sweet?
Even sweeter than cotton candy.
Yeah, and it's even
better if it's the blood
of someone I just murdered.
-Are you sleeping?
-Not anymore.
I was having a
dream about death,
about breaking someone's neck,
about twisting it slowly
until I feel it
snap in my hands.
And then hanging
them from a tree
for me to slice
their guts out.
-No business again!
-Don't worry, boss.
Jirokichi is in real bad
shape, he'll never be able
to do the show
in his condition.
Watch, you'll see.
He'll come crawling
back begging,
"Please take us
back, I'm sorry."
Just like that, and we'll
be back in business.
I hope you're right,
but I can't be sure.
It's impossible for the girl to
do the show without her father.
She's a stubborn girl who might
attempt it all by herself.
You must make sure
she doesn't pull it off.
Yes, sir.
Why don't you
put me in charge,
and give us a chance
to handle the situation?
Because you'd kill them
at the first opportunity,
and I need them to
make me my money.
(laughing)
Ladies and gentlemen,
step right up!
Step right up, the show will
begin in just five minutes!
The Magnificent
Marimo flies again!
Damn, I knew it.
We'll just see
how far she'll fly.
What are you doing
up there, my friend?
Hey, guys, bad news.
Marimo's father got
mugged last night.
Oh, really?
So does anybody
know who did it?
I'm really sure
it was Sumidaya.
And let me guess, you're
here to save the day,
and win the heart
of your fair maiden.
I'm sorry, but that was funny.
Can you two stop teasing
Yoshi for a minute?
But we're just having fun.
It's a good thing her
father's okay, or I might--
Decapitate me with
a spinning back fist?
-You better run!
(laughing)
-Yoshi, we've got a problem.
-What's wrong, Marimo?
Help me, it's disappeared.
-They stole the gunpowder!
-What?
What do we do?
Well, we'll just have
to find some more,
because the show must go on.
-I have an idea.
-Huh?
We can get the gunpowder you
need from a fireworks shop.
This area of town has
a whole bunch of them
that might help you out.
Come on!
We have to hurry!
I'm right behind you!
I hope they make it back
or all these people
are gonna get very impatient.
Then we'll have to stall
them until they get back.
-Uh-oh.
-Huh?
We'll just put on our own show!
I, uh, think I've
got stage fright.
Are we getting
paid for this?
(indistinct remarks)
Hey, come on,
let's start the show!
Hey, why don't you just
give us back our money!
-Are you guys ready to go on?
-Well, if you say so.
Just don't make me dance.
Ladies and gentlemen, thank
you very much for coming,
and welcome to the
greatest show on earth!
Magnificent Marimo
the Human Cannonball
will perform in
just a few minutes!
-I really hope this works.
-It will.
-Or we'll blow sky high.
-Don't worry, Yumi.
♪
Before we get to
the main attraction,
we have a surprise for you.
Please give a warm welcome
to Kenshin and his ball!
Oh, yeah, this should
be a piece of cake.
Here, maybe this
will help for balance.
What am I supposed
to do with this thing?
Here goes nothing.
♪
Hey, use the umbrella, Kenshin!
Yeah, just open it up!
Help me, somebody help me!
Here, try this
ball, it might help.
(shouting)
♪
-Oh, that must have hurt.
-Ouch.
That was absolutely
amazing, Kenshin.
Good, can you help me
stand up Manipuki?
(applause and cheering)
-Thank you!
-Yeah, thanks!
-We can make it.
-Let's go!
(birds chirping)
Marimo.
♪
Okay, just aim at the target,
and make 'em all count.
Hold it, what's gonna
happen if she hits me?
That's not a problem, Sano.
Then I'll just have
to mop up the blood.
This is show business?
Go ahead, Kaoru,
he's just scared.
I am not scared!
Now, Kaoru, you have
done this before, right?
♪
No.
(gasping)
I'm gonna kill you!
(yelling)
(whimpering)
Oh man, Sano, you're bleeding!
(grunting)
Kenshin, go get him!
-Sano, get back here!
-The show must go on!
(crowd laughing)
Let's see the cannon girl!
Yeah, we wanna see
the cannon girl!
I just hope Yoshi will hurry.
We're almost there.
Yoshi!
I'm extremely sorry about
tripping you, my little friend.
Yeah, I bet.
I want that bag of
stuff right now.
Then come and get it.
I'll just take that.
Hey, give me--
(grunting)
-Come on!
-Ha, see ya!
You idiot, go get those kids!
♪ I dream of Genie
with the light
brown hair ♪♪
(singing gibberish)
♪
Hey, get off the stage, loser!
Hey, you, give us back our money
or we'll set this tent on fire!
(crowd yelling and boo-ing)
We're in trouble now.
I don't get it, I thought this
audience would love some music.
-Kenshin!
-They're back!
Oh my gosh!
Kenshin, take 'em!
It's Sumidaya.
Yeah, and he's brought
four stooges along.
That's it, I've had it.
I'm sick and tired
of you gang of morons
messing around in
my personal business,
and putting your fat heads
in where they don't belong!
And I've decided
I'm going to make sure
that none of you
ever walk again!
Kill 'em!
Can't you do better than that?
I got it.
Don't worry.
-Nice save, Sanosuke.
-No problem.
I'm going to slice
you to pieces.
After I've poked
him full of holes.
And I've pulled
off his damn head.
If you guys fight as
well as you threaten to,
then you're the ones
who should worry.
I don't think you're getting
the message, here it is.
I wouldn't underestimate these
three assassins if I were you.
-That's because I--
-Shut your mouth!
Well, we'll see who
has the last word.
Hold it.
Just remember what
you did before,
and take this umbrella.
Okay.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Shabubula and his secret
hit-and-miss dance style!
(cheering)
You heard her.
Observe, you just
might learn something.
-Oh, man.
-Just what's he gonna do?
(yelling)
The umbrella spin!
That was close!
A hit-and-ball toss!
(yelling)
(cheering)
(grunting)
♪
-Oh, my cannon!
-Get this thing off me!
-Nice try, baldy!
-Almost, bird brain.
I said kill 'em!
Watch the pretty umbrella,
ya stupid buffoon.
Hey, Sano, catch!
Hi there!
-Yoshi, some rope!
-Got it!
Don't just stand there.
Draw your sword,
and prepare to die.
This umbrella is enough.
That arrogance will
make you a dead man
with your bleeding
heart in my hand.
We'll see.
♪
-I'm--
-Hey, I'm right up here!
(groaning)
(cheering)
All that with an umbrella?
(yelling)
I got him, he's all mine!
♪
(speaking gibberish)
Sumidaya!
You go get him, Marimo!
All set?
Yes.
(cannon blasting)
♪
Bullseye!
(cheering)
♪
Just listen to that crowd, huh?
Well, they loved me.
Yeah, but not as
much as they loved me.
They loved the
whole performance.
♪
This time, Sumidaya, you're
going to have to pay for all
your crimes, and go to jail,
ya miserable scoundrel.
♪
They'll be locked up
for a really long time.
Hey, how about if all you guys
become a permanent
part of my show?
Well, I could become a
professional knife thrower
if Kenshin and Sano
would volunteer.
(laughing)
Hey, you two, where
are you going?
I'm retiring from show business!
I've got a train to catch!
♪
Aw, come on guys!
(singing in foreign language)
♪