♪
Kamiya Dojo had
begun rebuilding.
♪
In addition to our
guest swordsman,
Kenshin Himura,
we have also welcomed
our first student,
Yoshi Myojin.
Well then, this is our
third day of practice,
so let's start
with deep breathing,
as usual.
Oh!
Close your eyes.
(heavy breath)
This is the first step
of the Kamiya Kasshin style.
(grunting)
Yoshi!
♪
Come back here!
I'm sick of the Kasshin style
and all this breathing stuff,
I want to know how to
really beat up an opponent,
not all this boring junk!
That's the wrong
way of thinking!
The Kasshin style
is to protect people,
it takes discipline!
Protect people?
Ugh?
(crash)
Kenshin, I came here
because I want to learn
to be good with swords,
not to protect other people!
I really want to learn how
to beat an opponent from you!
I don't have any plans
to leave my sword technique
to the next generation.
What?
Besides, Yoshi,
Ms. Kori is your teacher,
not me.
Wait, hey!
Ugh!
Have a rice ball.
Rice ball!
(bird chirping)
Kenshin, what a great cook!
Outrageous!
Really!
He's the one who told me
to be good at swords!
He's the one
that forced me
to deal with this
out-of-control little kid!
(munching)
How come you're not
eating those chewy ones
that you made?
Because the rice balls
that Kenshin made
are a lot better,
and you know it.
You're just like me,
with your feisty
and competitive attitude.
I feel like I have
a bratty little brother
who could really be good
if he'd only listen
to his big sister.
I can't help it.
I know you're talented
and very good at swords,
but since I saw the
way Kenshin fights--
♪
(chime)
(slam)
♪
But it just doesn't
make any sense.
How come a guy who
can fight like that
is wasting his time
goofing off in
this no-name dojo?
Huh?
Sorry, Kori,
who is Kenshin, anyway?
I don't know.
It's like the
way he fights,
it seems like he's killed
so many people.
I've got it!
He must have been living
secretly as some kind of...
...renegade bandit!
What?
He must have been chased
by police everywhere!
How cool is that?
(marching)
I still don't know
why he's a wanderer.
It's hard to imagine
he was a royalist samurai
before the Meiji Era began.
After the violent
disturbances
in the last days
of the Tokugawa government,
Kenshin walked out
on his life
as a legendary samurai,
and to this day,
it still remains
a mystery why he left.
There were many rumors.
Some say that
he killed someone
he shouldn't have.
Or that he knew too much.
Others say
the Meiji government
is still after him.
(whooshing)
I...
...oh.
(humming to self)
What the--
(mumbling)
Hey, that's my lunch!
Give it back to me right now!
(meowing)
Ow!
(growling)
This is stupid.
Why don't you ask him
about his life?
I'm too concerned not to know!
I just can't stand it,
I want you to tell me the truth!
Huh?
I know it's not
a good thing to snoop
into the past of other people,
but I--
(hooves clomping)
(clears throat)
Maybe I,
maybe I shouldn't
really be asking you this,
but I'm very curious.
So, would you mind telling me--
Kori, what is it?
Ah!
Where is Kenshin?
He just went out to get tofu.
We're going to have
a feast tonight.
He's making all of us dinner.
That's nice.
(sighs)
Hello, who are you?
Huh?
I need to talk to
the representative
of this dojo.
Why don't you tell me what
this is all about first?
You there!
I am the owner
and swordmaster,
Kori Kamiya.
What is it exactly
that you want from us?
Lady, we're the police!
Gee, really?
I almost couldn't tell
by those uniforms
that you're wearing.
Sir!
I know Kenshin Himura,
known as Battousai
is here.
Huh?
Battousai the killer?
Are they talking about Kenshin?
Huh?
Many people who are
impersonating Battousai
have confessed
the real one
is in this dojo,
and may I say
that if you don't
tell us the honest truth,
you will be prosecuted
for resisting the government.
Kenshin?
Just what do you mean?
What did Kenshin do?
That's classified top-secret
and the only one who knows
is waiting for him out front.
Huh?
I need to search your house.
Wait!
Battousai's helper,
do you want
the death penalty?
Huh?
Oof!
Yoshi, tell Kenshin
that if he comes back here
he'll be caught!
Right, okay!
-Hurry!
-You got it!
-Get him!
-Come back!
Oh, Kenshin.
(horse neighing)
I'm very close now.
I finally found him,
and this time,
Battousai is mine.
(marching)
Come on, hurry up!
Yeah, hurry!
If I run, I might
spill the tofu,
you silly kids!
Lookit, that
guy's got a sword!
Huh?
Oh...
You seem to be pretty brave
totally ignoring the decree
abolishing the wearing
of swords in daylight!
And right in front
of the police, too.
Why don't we have
a little fight?
I'll tell you what,
I'll let you go if you win!
I've got kids here.
Please, let's not fight.
Plus, my sword has
a reversed edge.
Reversed edge?
(laughs)
That kind of sword
couldn't kill a lousy flea!
You dummy!
(smash)
Ridiculous sword.
(laughs)
Kenshin, oh...
No need to worry,
Susie, it's okay.
I can't believe how
rude those men were.
I think they should apologize
for spilling our food.
Yeah, that's right, they should!
You're right,
they certainly should.
Get out of my way!
Police swordsmen coming through!
Look out, you people!
It's the swordsmen police.
(background chatter)
Do you know what
I do to thieves?
(smack)
Ugh!
Please, I'm sorry,
I won't do it again.
Please!
Shut up!
Please, please officer,
let him go!
Don't hurt him anymore,
it was only a little towel!
Excuse me,
but why don't
you let us handle this matter.
You're only going to make things
more complicated around here.
Listen, you third-class nobody
of a town officer,
you better watch your step.
You're still talking
to us even knowing that
we're from Satsuma?
No, I was just,
I mean I was--
(smack)
Oof!
Get out of here.
Ah, got something to say?
We are the elite
swordsmen police,
we are in charge
of the situation.
We are permitted
to carry swords,
unlike you wannabes,
and if we have to,
we are permitted
by the government
to kill people,
so do not interfere.
Challenge us!
I'll kill you all!
Kenshin, Kenshin!
Where are you?
Huh?
(footsteps)
(grunting)
Wait, please,
my dad has done nothing!
Yeah?
He tried to help out
a criminal, lady!
Oh, father...
Sit down!
Go on!
Please, somebody do something!
Can't somebody help?
My dad is innocent!
He's done nothing!
Arrest his daughter as well.
Stop it!
Hmm?
I don't know exactly
what's going on here,
but you guys are all crazy!
Ahh!
Gah!
(grunting)
Ugh!
Oh my gosh...
Let this be a strong warning
to you and others.
Huh?
As swordsmen police,
we may execute
any of you as examples,
just so that we
don't lose our touch.
(laughter)
(growling)
Dang, let go!
Oof!
Execution?
No way!
But they're innocent!
Hmm?
We need to nip
the bad ones in the bud
if we're gonna prevent
crime around here.
Hey, we're just doing our job,
eliminating the troublemakers,
that's all.
You're the troublemaker!
Hush up,
or they'll kill you too!
(growls)
What happened to all
that spirit you had?
Damn you!
Do it.
Yeah!
(clang)
No!
Don't!
What's going on?
(crowd jeering)
Huh?
Hmm?
♪
Kenshin!
No, Kenshin,
run for your life!
These guys are crazy
and they'll kill you!
Ugh!
♪
Who are you, anyway?
Kenshin Himura.
♪
If all these people
have committed a crime,
transfer their punishment to me.
Take me and let them go.
So, you don't like
what we're doing, huh?
Well, I see,
you're wearing a sword.
You must have a lot
of confidence in yourself
to wear it out
in public like that.
He's just a big coward!
Huh.
I'm not so sure about this guy.
I smell a rat.
(chimes)
♪
I found him, he's over there!
And it's him all right,
he's got red hair
and a cross scar on his cheek.
It looks like he
was trying to attack
the swordsmen police force.
(smack)
-Ugh!
-Oof!
Stop her!
(whoosh)
(smack)
Ugh!
(whoosh)
I won't let you take Kenshin!
Wait!
Come on, take out your sword.
I won't.
Hmm.
Execute one by one.
Yeah!
You coward!
This is police brutality!
(crowd jeering)
Huh, you got a lot of nerve
to call the swordsmen police
bad names,
arrest them!
Arrest all of them
for gathering
to incite a riot
against the police!
Draw your swords!
(clang)
Kill anyone who resists us.
Go.
(whooshing)
(clang)
I won't let any of you police
abuse these innocent people,
so think again.
If you want a fight,
it'll be with me.
So which of you
wants a quick trip
to an early grave?
Now we can say
this was legitimate
self-defense.
(licking)
Kill him!
(whoosh)
(clanging)
Ugh!
(men shouting)
♪
(thud)
Ah!
Looks like you're the last one.
Ugh...
♪
Now you're going to promise
the people of this town
that you will
never act violently
against them again.
Then, I'll allow
you to arrest me
for the injuries I inflicted
on the others.
Eh, shut up!
You know I won't do that!
Ugh!
♪
Kenshin!
Get away, look out,
get out of my way!
Oh my god, it's him!
Battousai Himura!
(hooves clomping)
(shouting)
It's the posture
of Jigen style
of Ni no Tachi Fuyo!
It's the strongest
sword of Satsuma!
A powerful technique.
(shouting)
(whoosh)
But against the Hiten
Mitsurugi style of Himura,
it's totally useless.
Huh?
Agh!
(grunting)
(clank)
Ugh!
You took care
of all those guys
without killing them!
Kenshin, come on now,
you've got to get out
of here really fast!
Hurry, the police
are after you, also!
Ahh!
You are wanted
by the government
for various crimes
and for fighting
the swordsmen police force.
Now, take him away!
Yes sir!
No, stop it!
Enough.
Huh?
(crowd murmurs)
Who's this?
Can you tell me...
Your Excellency.
From the reaction
of these townspeople,
it is very clear
who was righteous
and who was not.
Let them go at once.
Ugh!
I want the swordsmen
police punished severely
for their violence.
Yes sir!
♪
Himura, I finally found you.
For ten long years
I have been looking for you.
I see you grew a mustache,
Yamagata.
You show him respect!
Don't you know who he is?
He knows very well.
What?
During the restoration,
Himura was a valiant hero
who saved many lives
with his quick thinking
and his sword.
You show him respect!
Yamagata?
Yamagata!
Aritomo?
What, so you mean
this guy's some
big important man
around here?
You don't know?
He's the Meiji government
army lord,
Aritomo Yamagata!
He's one of
the top leaders
in Japan today!
Oh.
My carriage is waiting for me.
Himura, may I have
a word with you in private?
Why can't we talk here?
You haven't changed.
Himura, the Meiji restoration
would have never happened
without your help.
Because you helped
to build this country,
I'd like you to be a top officer
of the imperial army.
Yeah?
Indeed, all the royalists
of the restoration
have been waiting
for your return.
Won't you pledge yourself
to the Meiji government,
Himura, please?
♪
Thank you for your offer.
However, I don't intend
to take a high-ranking job
for my reputation
of killing people.
Hmm?
♪
So now it becomes clear to me
that the reason you disappeared
is your determination
not to kill again,
and I admire your values.
Even though you
found it necessary
to kill people,
it was a part
of the restoration effort,
and those people
who don't recognize you
-should be--
-Should be punished
by your police?
What?
When people think like
that, they become corrupt,
like your police force,
and they abuse their power.
When you and I
fought with the sword,
it was not for power,
but to create
a better world
where people could live
in peace and harmony,
and not live in fear.
That's why it's
important to remember,
we need to give peace a chance.
♪
But Himura,
today is a different time.
There is a decree
abolishing the wearing
of swords,
and the samurai
have been overthrown!
In this Meiji era,
you unfortunately
can't do any good
with one sword
unless you have some power!
♪
But with this one sword,
I can protect everyone
in my community.
Especially those
I really care about.
♪
I won't give up, Himura.
(footsteps)
♪
But with this one sword,
I can protect everyone
in my community.
Especially those
I really care about.
A sword that protects, huh?
What?
What's the matter, Yoshi?
♪
Kenshin!
What you need to learn
is not the sword technique
to kill people,
but the sword technique
to protect them.
Master it.
Learn the Kasshin style.
Use it to protect people.
♪
Well, I guess Kori will have
to do if I want to learn the--
Watch it, big mouth,
before I give you a lesson
on how to respect a teacher!
Betcha can't do that again!
(smack)
Whoa!
Would you like some more?
Today, I understood
a little better
why Kenshin is a wanderer.
It helps him forget his past,
by not being tied
down to anything.
This way,
he can live in harmony.
The swordsman who is
the protector of peace.
That's our Kenshin.
♪