♪
(theme song)
(leaves rustling)
Maybe this is
my only way out.
(leaves rustling)
♪
(groaning)
I don't have
anything against you,
but you, Battousai,
are a symbol,
a legendary symbol of
the Restoration Royalists.
So, you must die.
That's what this is about?
Then it probably
goes without saying
that you're working
for a larger group,
not just Henry Takeda.
Let me explain.
If the Imperial Army
and the Tokugawa faction
had battled
at Edo Castle instead,
just imagine what
could've happened.
We would've burned
all of Edo and killed
all the Royalist leaders
in the Imperial Army,
then we could've
joined the Tokugawans.
With no one to lead
the Imperial Army,
the Tokugawan hoards
could've overwhelmed
the imperialists.
Victory would've been ours.
Hey, you didn't
make all of Edo
a sea of fire!
But I wish we had.
And besides, it's never
too late to try again.
We could burn all of Tokyo.
(gasps)
All of Tokyo?
♪
But past opportunities
mean nothing today,
we must prove how
powerful we are now.
Our mission statement
is that we,
the Oni syndicate,
will control all of Japan.
We are all-encompassing
and must show the people
we are all-powerful as well.
Power destroys
even criminals like you.
Regardless of which
side they fought on,
many people put
their hearts and minds
into the war.
They all sacrificed
what they had in hopes
of a unified Japan.
But you aren't like them.
You're heartless.
You can talk about
burning cities
without any conscience.
Even now you wanna rob
people of their very souls
by addicting them to opium.
Then all they
will know is despair.
I will not allow
this to happen!
Fight.
(swords clink)
Dammit.
How dare Aoshi insinuate
that I'm no longer the boss.
He treated me like garbage,
and I won't forget it.
Wait.
Wait a minute.
I know a way
to make him pay.
♪
Well?
What power
that guy's got.
As powerful as Kenshin is,
you think he'd be able
to find a way to break
through to him.
(growls)
♪
(grunts)
Kenshin.
It doesn't matter
how hard you try,
you just can't break
through my defense.
He's so expressionless.
He doesn't even
enjoy winning.
I can't stop shaking.
Oh no!
Huh?
I understand it.
I finally figured out
a way to defend myself
against your kodachi.
Oh, really?
Well, that's what
I've been waiting for.
I was hoping you'd
make some adjustments
and turn this from
a one-sided route
into a true challenge.
Please show me just
what changes you think
can save you.
So how about
a demonstration?
How did he--
(struggling)
Yeah!
The quickness
of your kodachi
was too much for
a longer sword like mine,
so I shortened my
sword by grabbing it
down on the blade,
which seems to
have made things
a little more even.
Good adjustment,
but your hand seems
to have paid a price.
You can let your
opponent cut your flesh,
but never break your bones.
(clears throat)
You really are
a good slasher.
Now it's my turn
to show you
what I do best.
(gasps)
That attack was
too slow for him.
Huh?
♪
Now he will experience
how I really fight.
Jissen Kenbu style.
The battle sword dance.
Even Battousai
won't be able
to handle the alternating
speed of these moves,
based on watching
a river flow.
Now, Battousai, die!
(grunts)
Kenshin!
(groaning)
My spinning sword dance.
There's nobody
that can beat me
when I use that technique.
♪
He's dead.
The end of Battousai.
It's all over.
No, it can't!
(whimpers)
Kenshin!
No matter what, you bastard,
you're gonna pay for that.
You may think you're
the greatest fighter ever,
but I swear I'll make
sure to kill you!
You've got me convinced,
but I'd rather
see you stay alive.
Don't push it, kid.
Why not?
Don't, Yoshi.
You're an important part
of the Kamiya Kasshin
School of Swordsmen.
Besides, I would
never allow you to die
while I'm alive.
He's alive!
By the way, Aoshi,
I'm not ready
to die here either.
Huh.
I felt my slashes
cut you deeply.
What you felt
was this.
(breaks)
That was smooth.
He used the hilt
of his sword
to block and absorb
most of the energy
of Aoshi's slashes.
I must admit something
that I never thought
I would have to.
You're living up
to your reputation.
The fact that you're
so skilled has made me
even more hungry
to beat you and earn
the title of most
powerful fighter.
Keep your eyes open!
Watch out for
his spinning move.
I will not fall
short this time.
You won't fool me again.
Plus, the blows
you've taken
have weakened you,
slowing you down.
(grunts)
♪
Fortunately, there was
a short but vulnerable moment
when you switched
to the spinning sword
dance maneuver and
I was able to catch you.
What a move!
Huh.
Aoshi.
I know that you still
want the title of being
the most powerful fighter,
well, it's going
to be yours,
For me, having a friends
and a life where you're
not always looking
over your shoulder
is more important,
you understand?
But first I gotta survive!
(growls)
(choking)
(grunts)
I'd rather die
than lose.
Relax, buddy.
I think it's really best
that you back off for now.
Kenshin!
I hope he's all right.
(groaning)
You all right?
I feel fine,
oh, maybe not.
Kenshin's flown the pagoda!
Come back, buddy.
I feel fine...
I think I finally got to him.
Is he dead?
No, Yoshi,
he's just passed out
from lack of air.
But I'll bet he'll
have a sore throat
when he wakes up.
He was so stubborn
about having a complete
victory that his
repeated efforts
gave me a chance
to figure out his strategy.
Ultimately,
he defeated himself.
Wha--
What you did when
Aoshi knocked me down
really showed
a lot of courage.
Thanks for giving
me time to recover.
(chuckles)
(laughs)
All right, now
let's go to Takeda
and free Megumi!
So, let's head out!
Maybe not.
(growling)
♪
So, why didn't
you kill me?
Because I'm a wanderer,
not a killer.
That's probably hard
for you to believe.
You see, I'm no longer
obsessed with what drives you.
The idea of fighting
to prove my worth
isn't important to me.
I've learned to validate
my existence in more
peaceful pursuits.
You can do a lot
of good if you changed.
That's easy for you to say.
Some of us would like
to try something else,
but all we know is
the life of a fighter.
Old habits are hard to break.
Those that live life
by the sword are resigned
to end our lives
that way as well.
You know how
rough it can be.
The only genuine kindness
we've ever experienced
has been from Aoshi.
He turned down
a chance to be a captain.
Instead, he kept us all
busy and well taken care of.
I created the Oni gang,
but I always wanted
the title of most powerful
as a symbol
that we've arrived,
so I searched out
the most talented fighters
I could find
and trained them
so we really
would be the best.
But you are the
best, Battousai,
so kill me.
I want you to end this.
That's enough!
It's all right.
You boys have
been my family,
but I can't live
knowing I'm second best.
All right,
let's get it over with.
Now's the time.
'Cause if you don't,
I'll attack you over
and over until you do.
I will not kill you.
Feel free to attack me
as often as you'd like.
Don't say that!
What I mean is,
you and I can battle,
but I won't allow you
to ever involved my friends.
Understand?
Huh?
What is it?
(evil laughter)
Enough of this talk.
Allow me to finish you
both in one fell swoop.
I hereby volunteer
to rid the world
of Aoshi and you
too, Battousai.
Just what is that?
It's called
a Gatling gun.
It's the latest in
firepower from America.
It shoots out hundreds
of bullets a minute,
just as fast as
you can crank it.
What are you doing?
I decided to show you
who's the real boss!
(gunfire)
That sounds like gunfire.
♪
What is that?
(gunfire)
♪
This is just great!
I wish I'd had
one of these
when the in-laws
visited last year.
(maniacal laughing)
(bullets ricocheting)
He's trying
to scare us to death
by missing on purpose.
Damn!
Takeda, just why
have you decided to--
Call me Mr. Takeda!
That's it, Han'nya.
(gunfire)
Don't do it!
Ah!
(gasps)
(groaning)
Boss!
Oh no!
Boss, you've been hit.
(groaning)
(chuckles)
Well, you shouldn't
have got in the way.
Did you really think
my biggest ambition
was to peddle opium for
the rest of my career?
Not on your life.
♪
I've got a new, better
scheme figured out.
I'm taking the profits
from our opium sales
and investing in weapons!
Everyone wants guns.
So now he's become
a death merchant.
Takeda!
You're just not satisfied
with wrecking people's lives
with dope!
Now you wanna bring
weapons to Japan
that will kill millions.
Hmm.
Overpopulation.
It's a problem
both here and abroad,
and the best remedy is
to eliminate some people.
So, I'm really
helping everyone
with this handy-dandy device.
The famous Gatling gun.
That's right!
I could care less
what happens
to the human race,
as long as I have
enough money!
(maniacal laughter)
♪
Since you had the gall
to insult me, Aoshi,
I will eliminate you first.
(laughing)
(gunfire)
Oh no!
(gunshots)
(screaming)
Shikijo.
Boss.
That sad expression
really doesn't suit
your face very well.
I'm glad, just glad that
my well-trained muscles
could save you.
Goodbye, Boss.
♪
(grunts)
Shikijo.
So, who wants to be
the next to die?
You're the one
that's gonna die!
(gunshots)
Hyotto!
♪
Just for you!
(gunfire)
♪
Well, you gotta admit it,
at least we tried.
We did well.
We did our best to
try to save the Boss.
We were good for something.
(groans)
♪
Well, now I feel relaxed.
That's it.
Huh?
Ah!
Take it easy.
I just wanted
to tell you
Megumi is up
on the third floor
locked in the observatory.
♪
Thanks.
Now I need your help, Battousai.
I want you to retrieve
your reverse-edge sword.
♪
I will take memories
of fighting you with me
to the nether world.
The rest I leave up to you!
Don't do it!
Sano, take care
of Yoshi and Miss Kori.
Kenshin!
Han'nya!
(growls)
(gunfire)
♪
You are the only
warrior left, Battousai.
Looks like this is
the end for you.
All of them wasted
their lives trying
to kill me and none
of them even got close.
And if you're dumb
enough to try it,
neither will you.
(maniacal laughter)
♪
You die right now!
Kenshin!
♪
Huh?
It's jammed!
(nervous laugh)
Huh?
(bang)
(metal clank)
(panting)
♪
Wait, I need help.
If you need help,
why not call for
your friend, Mr. Money.
(shouts)
All right!
(grunts)
(gurgling)
He deserved that.
Come on.
We've gotta go
and collect Megumi.
Sure.
Let's get her!
Yeah.
Huh.
I know what you're thinking,
but their deaths
were not a waste, Kori.
Thanks to their
courageous sacrifice,
there won't be any
Gatling guns here
for a long time.
Kori?
♪
It--it's over.
(struggling)
♪
(wind blowing)
Kenshin, Yoshi,
and Sanosuke,
I am so saddened by
your untimely deaths.
And to think,
we were almost a family.
Now, I truly have nothing.
Ugh!
(gasps)
What were you
trying to do?
Huh?
(heavy breathing)
I couldn't live
with myself
and all the lives
my opium-making ruined,
so I decided to end it all.
What?
How can you say
such nonsense?
All of us have
risked our lives
to save you from
your personal demons,
and you'd let all
that go to waste!
You're a lot stronger
person than to do
something like that.
But I was sure that
all of you were dead
and my life felt worthless.
Megumi, even if
you were to die,
it wouldn't bring
anyone else back.
Instead of hurting yourself,
you should try
to help other people,
people that need you.
That's the best way
to make up for
some of your mistakes.
Battousai the Slasher's
still alive and that's
what he does.
♪
(cries)
I'll try.
♪
(birds chirping)
Megumi, I hope you'll visit the dojo
whenever you get a chance.
Thank you, Kori.
You know I will.
You gotta visit us every day.
Well, I'm going
to be very busy
studying under Dr. Gensai.
I want to be
a really good doctor.
Yeah, maybe you can give
some aid to Kenshin
the next time Kori
really lets him have it.
Oop.
(laughs)
(chuckles)
Well...
we have to go now.
I'll walk with you.
♪
Well, Kenshin, you did
a good job of helping
that lady,
saving her life,
and you managed to
keep her out of jail.
Say, Sano,
if I were you,
I think I'd take
a little of the credit myself.
You really did
a great job
of helping out Megumi, too.
(chuckles)
I wonder whatever happened
to that gang boss, Aoshi.
I heard when the
police finally arrived,
all they found
was Takeda.
Aoshi and all four of
his henchmen's bodies
had disappeared.
So, I suppose
it's possible
that he still might
be alive somewhere.
♪
If he's still alive, Kenshin,
you think he's plotting
some kind of revenge?
Who knows?
I would hope that
after all the pain
his life of crime
has given him,
he'd find something
better to do with his life.
(animal chattering)
Rest well, my friends,
knowing Takeda paid
for his treachery.
And once I regain
my strength...
I'll make the others pay.
I swear it.
(animal chattering)
♪
(theme song)