♪
(singing in foreign language)
Progress sometimes
seems to take forever,
but if you wait
around long enough,
it does happen.
The first railroad
ever built in Japan
was completed and ready for use
in the summer of 1872.
The first route
that was opened
was between
Shinbashi and Yokohama.
Riding this train,
trade merchants,
and the rest of us,
could get from
the capital of Japan
to the port of Yokohama
in the unheard of time
of only an hour.
The steam locomotive came
all the way from England
traveling on a steam ship.
It had incredible power
and could pull eight train cars
filled with people and cargo.
Its top speed was over
40 kilometers an hour.
Some people feared
this new invention.
They thought that fire
from the locomotive
would explode and set
the whole countryside ablaze.
So most of the tracks
were built near the coast.
What a view, Mount Fuji
and the coast in the same trip!
♪
(crowd murmuring)
Hurry, chop chop!
Come on, we've got to hurry
or we'll miss the train!
And who took so long
getting packed
that we all had to take
time waiting for her anyway?
Wait a minute!
You're complaining
even though I'm the one
that bought your ticket?
I coulda slept in all day
but you insisted I come along!
So that's the thanks I get
for trying to be nice to you?
I save for weeks
so all of you can have
a relaxing ride
on the new train
and all you can do is look
a gift horse in the mouth,
you nocturnal nitwit!
We should have left you!
But we're really
glad you came along.
Can the bunch of you just stop?
You're acting like such babies.
I think I'll just meet up with
you at the loading platform.
And try to grow up!
(grunts)
Hey kid, keep your nose
out of my business.
Sorry, mister.
What a crowd.
I can't believe how
many people are here.
They can't all be here
to ride the train.
(crowd murmuring)
I don't know who they are
but they must have
a lot of money
to charter an entire train car.
Huh?
I hear those chests of theirs
are filled with gold.
(murmuring continues)
You see that train car
they're loading?
A rich English businessman
reserved that car
all for himself.
-Hey, watch it.
-What?
(gold coins clattering)
What was that?
What happened?
I just lost my grip.
Well, be more careful.
Last call, everyone.
All aboard!
♪
Don't you think being on
this train is just incredible?
I'm happy!
Happy that I decided
we should be pampered.
From time to time,
it's a good thing
to have a treat like this.
There is one thing
I want to do right away.
When we arrive in Yokohama,
I want to have
our photograph taken
and I wanna try something
called chocolate.
(laughs)
And I wanna see this
cloth from the West
called printed cotton.
It's supposed to be beautiful.
This trip is going
to be wonderful.
Sounds stupid.
What did you just mutter?
I heard that, Yoshi!
All you think about
are girl things.
There's nothing stupid
about a woman talking
about girl things!
Your attention please!
If you do not have a ticket,
please leave the train now.
Well, it's too bad
you're going to miss
this trip to Yokohama, Yoshi.
Huh?
One of those stupid girl
things is to plan ahead.
And it's pretty smart.
So I'd say your
cracks about girls
are something you better keep
to yourself, smart mouth.
Or here's an idea,
you can pay me the 11 yen
your ticket to Yokohama
cost me, Yoshi.
(laughing)
I'm leaving!
-Huh?
-I'm gonna go home!
But I was just teasing, Sano.
(grunting)
You're not gonna
wreck my good time
by getting off this train!
(hissing)
(whistle blows)
(train chuffing)
(groaning)
What I see just isn't possible.
How can the train be moving
with no horses pulling us?
But then again,
my stomach's moving
and no horses are pulling it.
Open the window.
I don't want my picture taken.
Nah, nah, nah!
I hear that the camera
can suck your spirit
right outta your body!
Well, that's not right.
You're right, that's not right.
-You're dead wrong.
-Well, if you know so much
then explain to me just
what makes this train move!
It's steam, it's using
the power of steam, Sano!
How can steam from a teapot
move a whole train?
You're making that up
because you won't admit
you don't know how
it really works!
You're the one that's
a little mixed up.
I know all about what
makes this train run.
Then explain it,
Ms. Know-It-All.
Okay, allow me to explain.
When water is boiled into steam,
its volume increases
hundreds of times.
Brother...
I'll see ya.
Hey, where ya going?
I'm gonna go see the engine.
(train wheels clacking)
(train chuffing)
Huh?
(muffled struggling, laughing)
(whistle blows)
Hm?
-Whoa.
-Hey, where are you going?
Huh?
Uh, I just wanted
to see the engine.
Listen up, kid,
you got no business
being up here.
Now get back to
your seat and stay there!
Yeah right.
(chuckles nervously)
(laughs)
(grunts)
Phew.
-Hey, buddy!
-Huh?
We've got a big
problem in the back
and we need you
to stop the train.
What?
I said, you need to stop
the train right now!
Ah!
Is he nuts?
Why would he wanna
stop the train?
-(soft thud)
-Huh?
--has an insulated engine and
a separate condensing chamber.
-Oh yeah?
-That's right!
Well, just maybe
I see your point!
(panting)
I bet Kenshin believes that
everything I told you is right.
Right, Kenshin?
What?
I wasn't listening closely.
(grumbling)
You know what?
I think I'll hop up front
and see what Yoshi's up to.
The man in the special
car requested we stop.
That just doesn't sound right.
Hey there, what's
your name, mister?
Come on now, give me an answer!
Hm.
(both gasp)
Now you stop the train.
-Don't do it!
-Huh?
This guy's nothing but a fake.
He knocked out
the real conductor.
So don't stop the train!
So it's you again.
I should have thrown
you off the train
the first time, you nosey bum!
(grunting, yelling)
Huh?
(laughing)
All right, now stop the train
or I'll drop this
kid on the tracks.
Sure, but why don't you
just tell us what you want.
He's trying to steal
those gold coins
that are on the train!
Be quiet!
Maybe this'll button your lip.
(laughing)
Okay, that's enough.
Huh?
-Just who the hell are you?
-Kenshin.
I'm just one of the
regular passengers onboard
but if you were
to drop that boy now,
then they'd have
to stop the train,
make reports, and we'd probably
never get to Yokohama today.
-That'd be disappointing.
-Huh?
Now let go of him so we
can all enjoy our trip.
(growls)
Stop right there.
(train chuffing)
(yelling)
Hold it!
♪
Yoshi, go tell Sano!
Right!
(heavy breathing)
(passengers murmuring)
♪
Looks like you're near
the end of the line, mister.
♪
Don't you think it's time
you gave this bad idea up?
♪
Before I give this up
I'll see you die first.
♪
Kenshin!
Ha!
Huh?
♪
I blew it.
What is it?
I'd say the tables
have turned, Wanderer.
Huh?
Move!
(laughing maniacally)
♪
(train chuffing, clacking)
Even though this robbery hasn't
gone exactly as I planned it,
I have to say I've got
the upper hand here, right?
So just what do you
want me to do?
To disappear.
You stand in the way
of our mission.
Goodbye.
Huh?
(yelling)
♪
Don't even think about it,
unless you want me to
blow his brains out.
(yelling)
♪
Hey, you're not bad,
but I think I've seen enough.
♪
Kenshin!
Yeah.
♪
(yelling)
Nice job.
Hey!
Huh?
Come back here!
We don't have time to
bother with that brat.
-Yes, sir.
-If we're gonna make
this plan work, then we
can't have any more delays.
(knocking)
What is it, my good man?
(chuckles)
(gun cocks)
Now look what you've done.
Kenshin and Yoshi
have wandered off
because of your
constant complaining.
Well, Kori, if you hadn't
bought these tickets
in the first place,
we wouldn't have this trouble.
You've hit it right on the head.
Kori, Sano, you've
gotta come quickly!
I was, you know--
and then this guy--
and if we didn't--
Try to calm down, Yoshi.
But I--ow!
Calm down!
-What?
-Huh?
(grunting)
(train chuffing, clacking)
Well, we're uncoupled
from the train.
Now we'll just roll to
a stop and bide our time.
Idiot.
What a dumb idea it was for you
to put your gold on this train.
And by loading it in plain view,
we knew just how
much gold you have
and we knew that there
are no security guards
tagging along.
Huh?
Hey, if we're disconnected
from the train...
then how come we
haven't slowed down yet?
I'll go check it out.
Hey!
Huh?
(Sano laughing)
You guys really need
to live by the proverb
"Don't count your chickens
until they're detached."
You!
Careful!
(exclaiming)
♪
Just what have you
got us into?
Hey, you coulda
just stayed up front
dreaming of chocolate.
Hey, I'm not just
some bon-bon eater,
I can be as tough
as nails when I need to.
(grunting)
♪
I warned ya!
To hell with your Chopsocky.
♪
Huh?
Ah!
I'll take my
Kamiya Kasshin style
over your crappy Colt any time!
(groaning)
You know, maybe I misjudged
you about being too soft.
You better give up!
♪
You're in more trouble
than you can imagine.
What does he mean?
(rumbling)
Hey!
Uh-oh.
(yells)
(brakes squealing)
(crowd commotion)
(grunting)
(crowd murmuring)
Huh?
What the hell?
Look!
-What's going on out there?
-Look over here!
(murmuring)
Pirates!
♪
♪ Danger zone ♪
Get ready to weigh anchor!
♪ Yeah ♪
Ouch.
I shoulda stayed at home.
-Huh, what the--
-Look at all those ships.
♪
Now listen up.
Any more trouble from you three
and I'll see to it that
you all wind up serving
as cabin boys
for my pirate friends.
Now just stay put while
we transfer the gold.
I'd say your plans are sunk.
He said freeze, you twit!
-Hey--
-Shut up
or I'll see to it
I give you a lot worse!
(pirates yelling, muttering)
♪
(laughing)
If you cooperate, everything
will turn out just fine,
but if you get
any other ideas,
I'll ventilate your head
and stain your suit.
Stain your suit,
that's a good one, boss!
(laughing)
(hooves clopping)
Hey, what's that?
(crowd murmuring)
Go get that guy!
It's Kenshin!
(horse whinnies)
At last I caught up
with you guys.
That's great.
It's just too bad
you're too late
to help anyone here.
♪
Huh?
(yelling)
That's impossible!
Whoa, how the hell'd he do that?
Huh?
(yelling)
Hey!
♪
(pirates exclaiming, muttering)
Whoa!
♪
I'm warning all of you,
leave now or you'll regret it.
You're the one that's
gonna be dead meat.
Get him!
(yelling)
♪
Hey guys, how's it going?
-Real good.
-Just doin' a little cleanup.
What's next?
We've gotta get
this train outta here
before there's
any more trouble.
Sano and Kori,
you two take care
of reconnecting that car.
Yoshi, get up front
and help the engineer.
-Right!
They think they can escape
with the track blocked.
I've gotta get this
out of my way.
All right then,
Hiten Mitsurugi style.
Ya!
(loud rumbling)
Impossible!
(splashing)
All right, let's roll!
Sure!
(train whistle blows)
♪
Full speed ahead!
We'll catch you!
♪
I'm not too worried about them.
There's not a ship on earth
that could catch this train.
♪
Tell me, what happened?
There was only four of them.
I betcha they must
eat a lot of ginseng.
♪
-Oh, Kenshin!
-So as I was saying--
I wanna kiss you all day,
you big hero--oh!
Whoa, I think you need
a cold bath, Kori!
Be quiet!
(laughing)
♪
(train steam hissing)
And he gave us
this piece of gold
as a token of his gratitude.
Thanks to you
and your brave friends,
my shipment was safe from
those thieving pirates.
This is my way of thanking you.
Since Kori's so generous to us,
she will decide how to use it.
But this is an
awful lot of money.
I bet I can spend it all.
No, I've got it,
we'll save most of this,
but now we can have
our picture taken.
(Sano clears throat)
Sano, what's the problem?
I'm not gonna do it
'cause it sucks up your spirit!
How can you still believe that?
Don't you know that
it's an old wives' tale
that's just full of bunk?
It's an absolute fact!
Next you're gonna try telling me
that touching frogs
won't give you warts,
little Ms. Know-It-All!
Please give all of us a break.
Can't you two stop arguing
at least for a minute?
Yeah, if I didn't know better,
I'd say you two act like
you're married to each other.
♪
I can't have my picture
taken in this outfit!
You look great.
Besides, it's
the only one you own.
Well, I'm ready.
Don't squint, Kenshin,
and try not to let your face
break the camera, Kori!
Say "soy cheese"!
Soy cheese!
(Kori giggles)
♪
(singing in foreign language)