♪
(singing in foreign language)
He's a strange one.
How come he smiles
all the time?
I don't know.
♪
I have a feeling there's
something different about him;
that something's changed.
Whatever he's going through,
he's having a
problem handling it.
Interesting that his
strap broke when it did.
I suspect that the timing
wasn't merely a coincidence.
Hurry up.
Is something wrong?
What's up?
You know, that Mr. Himura is
a lot better than I thought.
-Huh?
-Now I can see
why Battousai the Slasher
became such a legend.
But it doesn't really
matter how good he is.
There's no way he can
beat me or Mr. Shishio.
You know why?
He uses his sword
to protect the weak
and that makes him a loser.
♪
Protecting the weak
isn't what nature intended.
♪
(crickets chirring)
You little brat!
(crashing)
I ordered you
to take 100 rice sacks
over to the granary
before sunrise!
I don't care how tired you are.
Get up and do as I tell you.
(groaning)
(grumbling)
What are you smiling about,
you little bastard?
(yelling, glass shattering)
You know the rules.
You're not allowed
back in this house
until you've gotten
all your chores done.
(heart pounding)
Sleep outside tonight.
He's such a
horrible little thing.
Don't forget your kitchen chores
or you'll be sorry, kid!
And then you can
massage my back.
♪
I wish my father
had never brought
that little bastard
into this family.
He's nothing but trouble.
Sojiro's not a real
member of the family.
He's our lifetime slave
and we don't have
to pay him a cent.
He doesn't deserve to be
a member of this family.
He's just a spineless weakling.
We only gave the kid our name
to save grandfather's reputation
so no one would know
Sojiro was a bastard.
He'll never get a penny
of the profits from this place.
Our kids are gonna
inherit everything!
♪
(grunting)
(sobbing)
♪
(metal clanging, man yelling)
(yells)
♪
(man yelling)
(yelling continues)
♪
(branch snaps)
(whimpering)
♪
Tough luck, kid.
You're history.
♪
After what you've seen,
I have no choice.
♪
You're dead.
(whimpering)
♪
(giggling)
I said you're gonna die,
why are you smiling?
You want to die?
Is that it?
If it's quick, uh-huh.
(shuddering)
-Get up.
-Huh?
Show me where I can
hide out for a while.
Bring me some bandages
and some food
and I'll spare your life.
♪
Good.
Now it doesn't hurt so much.
Um...
excuse me?
-Hm?
-Mister?
Don't call me "mister," kid.
I have a name, you know.
Shishio Makoto.
You can call me Shishio.
♪
Um, Mr. Shishio?
Don't call me "mister."
Uh, well, I was just wondering,
since you killed a policeman,
does that mean that
you're, you know,
a bad guy?
The bad guys are
the Meiji government.
I worked for those guys
until they didn't need me.
That's when they tried
to burn me to death.
In that case,
you're a good guy, right?
No, kid.
There's no one worse than I am.
Huh?
Don't be frightened.
I told you I'd spare
your life, didn't I?
Yes.
I'll be safe here as long
as you'll keep silent
and tell no one about
what you've seen tonight.
♪
You found me
a pretty good hideout.
I think I'll stay for a while.
He's an outcast, a renegade.
He's pretty scary.
♪
But...
he didn't kill me
even though I know his secret.
He's the only person
who's ever trusted me.
What happened?
There are cops
all over the place.
What are they doing here?
I heard a couple of cops
who were on patrol around here
were killed last night.
They're searching
the area for the killer.
They think he might
still be in this area.
Well, I sure hope
they catch the guy.
He sounds like
a real lunatic.
Hey, Sojiro!
Yeah?
I saw you near the barn
the last couple of nights.
You been sleeping
out there, haven't you?
What's goin' on?
What are you doin' out there?
Kid, you better tell us if
you see any strangers around.
If I find out you're
hiding anything,
you're dead.
I hope I'm the one
who finds that traitor
'cause this is what
I'll do to the guy!
Will you cut it out, Gonzo?
When you draw your sword,
we never know
what's gonna happen.
You usually cut yourself.
Put it away now, all right?
(exhales)
(laughs)
Oh...Sojiro, it looks
like an another bag of rice
has been ruined thanks
to your clumsiness.
What a pity.
Now you're gonna get it.
Who did that?
Let me guess,
it was Sojiro again.
Listen, kid,
before he died,
my father told me I had
to take care of you,
but one more mistake
and you're history.
You got that?
Hmm, I see.
They seem like a bunch
of pretty nasty people,
your family, and I gotta
hand it to you, kid,
you took a beating
and you haven't shed a tear,
but what I don't understand
is, why are you smiling?
(giggles)
Uh, I don't know.
I smile whenever I
get nervous or upset.
I've been doing it for so long,
it's become a habit.
Now that I think about it,
I suppose it does
seem kinda weird.
I didn't use to be that way.
When they bullied me,
I get really upset
and when they hit me,
I cried my eyes out.
One day, they were
all yelling at me
and suddenly, they all
looked so stupid
I couldn't help smiling.
And they were so surprised
they stopped yelling.
So I just kept smiling.
Pretending I'm enjoying
whatever terrible things
they're doing to me
is how I get them to stop.
Even when that doesn't work
and they keep beating me,
smiling seems to
make it hurt less.
It's as if, somehow, if I
can keep smiling, I've won.
I don't really blame them
because I'm not a real member
of the family.
I'm an illegitimate
child, a bastard.
I don't deserve the
respect the others get.
You're wrong.
Huh?
The circumstances of
your birth aren't important.
They don't respect you
because you're weak.
The most basic
law of nature is
that the strong shall live
and the weak shall die.
Survival of the fittest.
The strong shall live
and the weak shall die.
Never forget that.
If I'm strong, I'll live.
If I'm weak, I'll die.
♪
(gasps)
You've earned my
respect and my trust.
And in return for your loyalty,
I give you my sword.
Take it, Sojiro, it's yours.
♪
How long are you going
to go on doing that?
He shows no emotion
at all, Kenshin.
Why is that?
I'm not really sure, Sano.
♪
But I think he met
the wrong person
at the wrong time
and it really twisted him.
Survival of the
fittest, he said.
Betcha Shishio's the one
who taught him that.
♪
Shishio gave him
what he'd never had.
Advice and guidance,
the kind that would
help him to survive.
Sojiro's heart was a void
which got filled with
Shishio's anger and hate.
If he had been lucky
enough to have met
another kind of teacher,
the way I did,
his life would
have been different.
♪
I give you my sword.
Take it, Sojiro, it's yours.
♪
The survival of the fittest.
The strong will live
and the weak will die.
♪
Survival of the fittest,
the law of nature.
It seems like a cruel law,
but nature isn't cruel.
That's just the way it is.
♪
Gonzo, got any idea
where the bandages are?
I don't know.
I know that we
have some somewhere.
But I've searched
the entire house
and can't find any!
So Sojiro must be the one
who stole the missing rice.
It's amazing how much
that kid can eat.
But bandages too?
We do knock the kid
around almost every day.
Only natural he'd
need bandages, I guess.
But all of them?
We had enough to
last us six months
and the entire supply is gone.
Nobody needs that many bandages.
Hey, wait a minute!
I heard the cops
say that the killer
they're looking for
was badly burned
and to be on the lookout
for a guy who's wearing
a lot of bandages.
-Huh?
-Bandages?
(collective grumbling)
That bastard Sojiro.
(thunder rumbling)
A lot of pain tonight.
That means there'll be a storm.
(wind blowing)
(exhaling sharply)
My hands hurt too.
And that's just
from carrying rice.
Mr. Shishio's must really hurt.
Mr. Shishio needs his sword
a lot more than I do,
so I'll return it tonight.
(wind blowing)
I'd better go find him.
Yeah!
I may not be strong
the way Mr. Shishio is,
but I'll learn to be
strong in other ways.
Sojiro!
Sojiro, where the hell are you?
I know you're
out here somewhere.
I wonder what they could
want at this time of night.
(panting)
(lightning crashes)
Ah-ha, so there you are!
You bastard!
You're helping that
traitorous killer, aren't you?
(yells)
You stupid kid!
If the government
finds out what you've done,
they'll put every
one of us to death.
Understand?
Unless we find the traitor
and kill him ourselves!
Tell us where
the traitor is hiding!
Tell us or we'll
beat you to death!
(crying, choking)
I've had enough.
I say he dies right now.
(gasps)
Wait a minute.
I don't know if killing him
is such a good idea.
We could go to jail.
No, now's the perfect time.
Think about it, there's
a dangerous criminal,
a bloodthirsty villain
on the loose,
so all we have to say is
that we found the poor kid
with his throat cut.
He'll be just another victim
of a murderous traitor.
Good idea,
and to top it off,
if we can find and kill
the traitor who supposedly
committed the crime,
the government might
even give us a reward.
Let's get rid of
the little brat right now!
He's a traitor himself
for betraying our family
and deserves only
one thing: death!
I think we should chop
his head right off.
Of course, that's what
they do to traitors!
I know, we'll call the police--
And get a nice fat reward!
He'll get exactly
what's coming to him.
He betrayed our family!
♪
(yelling, lightning crashing)
Don't let him get away!
Kill the little traitor!
Please help me, please!
(crying)
Help!
(yelling)
Help me, somebody!
(thunder rumbling)
Damn, we've searched everywhere.
Where the hell did he go?
Eh, he couldn't
have gotten far.
Hm?
(heavy breathing, sighing)
(heart pounding)
They're gonna kill me.
Please, Shishio,
I really need your help.
There you are.
Did you really think
you could get away
by hiding down here?
(yelling)
That's a pretty
expensive-looking sword, kid.
Where'd you find it,
the rice warehouse?
Why don't you hand it over?
The strong shall live,
the weak shall die.
Survival of the fittest.
(yelling)
Hagi, where are you?
Hey, what is he screaming about?
When he comes out
from underneath there,
we'll know.
(thudding)
Well, Hagi?
(screaming)
(whimpering)
♪
Eh?
The strong shall live
and the weak shall die.
(growling)
♪
-You murderer!
-Bastard!
What?
♪
(screaming)
(lightning crashes)
♪
(screaming)
(door creaking)
Sojiro, are you crying?
No, sir.
Are you coming with me?
Yes.
Mr. Shishio?
Yes?
Do you think I
can be strong too?
I mean, strong like you are.
Well, almost.
I'll always be the strongest,
but you'll be
my protégé, all right?
♪
Survival of the fittest.
Kenshin can't win
because he doesn't realize
that the laws of nature
are unchangeable.
He thinks he can use his
sword to protect the weak.
But the law of nature
is survival of the fittest.
You can't live in
harmony with nature
and fight it at the same time.
Huh?
I know he can't protect the weak
because if he could,
he would have protected me
and he didn't.
♪
His very existence
irritates me.
♪
He's still smiling.
But something's wrong.
He isn't focused.
-Sojiro.
-Hm?
Shishio is counting
on you to get rid
of his other enemies as well,
so concentrate
on killing Himura
as quickly as you can.
Don't worry, Yumi,
it won't take long.
I'll take one step,
then use the Shukuchi
style to finish him.
One step first?
What are you talking about?
I told you, Yumi, there
is nothing to worry about.
But killing Mr. Himura
isn't enough.
I've gotta do it in a way
that destroys his pride first
because he deserves
to be punished.
He's gotta be shown
that it's wrong
to defy the laws of nature.
♪
Survival of the fittest.
-He's ready.
-I know.
Say, are you all right?
♪
If you mean am I ready to fight,
I am.
It's simple,
I have to beat Sojiro
in order to get to Shishio.
That's the only way
I'll ever get to see Kori
and the others again.
I hope I don't have to kill him,
but I will if I have to.
♪
One step and then Shukuchi.
Right or left?
♪
A multi-direction aerial attack
lateral and vertical
at the same time.
Concentrate, Kenshin,
you gotta concentrate!
♪
Survival of the fittest,
the law of nature.
♪
The strong shall live,
the weak shall die.
♪
(grunting)
I was one of the weak ones.
♪
When I was desperate
and cried out for help,
you didn't lift a finger.
Huh?
If you believe
that you are right,
and that the weak and helpless
should be protected,
then why didn't you protect me?
Could I have protected him?
Could I have helped him?
♪
Hey, Sojiro!
I cried out
and no one was there.
Hey, Sojiro!
♪
One more step and then
the Shukuchi strike.
♪
Sojiro!
(singing in foreign language)
♪