♪
You think Aoshi
Shinomori is in there?
Kenshin, what do
you suggest we do?
We can't stop now.
Aoiya is becoming more
dangerous every minute.
We don't have time
for a grudge match
between Kenshin and Aoshi.
Kenshin!
Before we left Aoiya,
I promised Misao
that I would
bring Aoshi back.
And I promised Aoshi that
he could have a rematch.
This is my chance.
The only chance I'll ever have
to honor those two promises.
♪
I know what you're
thinking, Sano,
and I'm sorry, but I
don't have any choice.
I have to go in there.
I gave my word to Aoshi
and to Misao as well.
♪
(door creaks)
It's good to see you
again, Kenshin Himura.
Finally.
♪
I've been searching
for you for a long time.
But I knew you couldn't
hide from me forever.
Kenshin Himura has
never hidden from anyone.
He's a man of honor!
You, on the other hand,
the former leader
of the Oni gang,
wanted to defeat
Kenshin so much
that you teamed
up with Shishio
and almost killed Okina,
your own stepfather.
Shut up, Sano.
This has nothing
to do with you.
♪
I swore we'd fight again
someday, Kenshin, remember?
For that I gave up everything.
My pride, compassion,
the friends I had.
This is the only thing
that matters to me.
You can't put it
off any longer, Kenshin.
Your time's up.
♪
Agreed.
You've changed so much.
So much that it's
hard for me to believe
that you're the same
Aoshi Shinomori
that I used to understand.
You're right.
I have changed a lot.
I've learned how to focus all
my energy on this one goal.
And now...
the moment I've waited for
so long has finally come.
(metal scrapes)
♪
It looks like he's using
the Nitokatachi style.
Go on.
Draw your sword.
♪
Kenshin.
What are you
trying to do?
If you're planning to breach
the promise you made me
and refuse to fight, I'm
afraid that's unacceptable.
Aoshi Shinomori, that's
who I swore to fight,
and I will when I see him.
But you are not
that man at all.
The Aoshi I knew was
the head of the Oni gang,
not loyal to Shishio.
I promised to fight
a man, not a flunky.
Just what do
you mean by that?
We're wasting time!
Every minute we spend
makes things more dangerous
for the folks back in Aoiya.
You aren't going to
change Aoshi's mind
by talking about it.
You're going to have to fight
him, even if it's to the death.
No, Sano.
If I were to kill him,
I wouldn't be able
to keep the promise
I made to Misao.
I promised both
her and Okina
that I would find
Aoshi Shinomori,
the man we all knew as the
renegade leader of the Oni gang,
and that I would bring
him back to Aoiya alive.
But I haven't
found him, not yet.
This Aoshi's different.
So, even if I could convince
him to go back with me to Aoiya,
I'd be bringing back
a stranger, not Aoshi.
(scoffs)
That's enough talk.
Draw your sword and fight.
Kenshin, you have no choice.
Do it, now!
No.
Just what are
you trying to do?
You want to get
yourself killed?
I know of only one way to
honor the promises I've made.
I have to change this Aoshi
back into the one I once knew,
and at the same time,
it's my solemn duty
to convince him that
it doesn't matter
who's best and we
don't have to fight.
♪
Wait a minute.
So, you're
facing a guy
whose single reason for
living is to fight you,
and the only
plan you've got
is to convince
him not to fight?
Hmm.
Even if you can pull
it off, which I doubt,
we won't have the time.
It'll take too long.
I hope not.
Good luck.
Of course, I think
that it's the most
ridiculous plan
I've ever heard,
but if anyone can pull
it off, you can Kenshin.
♪
(grunts)
(growls)
♪
I know it's
here somewhere.
Ah, there it is.
The telegraph key.
Anji is of no further use, and
there's been no word from Usui.
We just received
this from Ayumi.
Oddly enough, it was sent from
the telegraph line in my office.
She's there with
Kenshin Himura,
Aoshi Shinomori
and Sanosuke Sagara.
It looks like Shinomori and
Himura are going to fight.
♪
Good news.
Very good news indeed.
Sanosuke won't be 100%
after his fight with Anji,
and even if
Saito beats Usui,
I'm sure Usui will
have injured him
and Himura, even if he wins
his fight with Shinomori,
will probably be exhausted,
and when they get here, they
won't put up much of a fight,
and Sojiro and I will be able
to take care of them easily.
You're right,
sir, as usual.
Finally, Shinomori is going
to get the rematch he wanted.
♪
I think Kenshin would
need quite a long time
to recover after
a fight like that.
Unfortunately for Kenshin,
he's going to have to fight
as soon as he gets here.
Yes.
He won't be here
for a while.
That fight's going to
go on for a long time.
♪
That was one hell of a
move you just pulled off.
That's Kenshin Himura all right!
So, throw the
book at him again!
♪
(grunts)
A long fight?
How do you know that, sir?
It's simple, Sojiro.
Aoshi Shinomori and Kenshin
Himura are almost equal
in their sword technique.
Though Kenshin should win,
Aoshi has the strength,
stamina and cunning
to make this
battle memorable.
♪
He pulled his sword out.
This is really serious.
♪
Ah, you finally
pulled your sword.
Good, now we can
have a real fight.
♪
(grunts)
(breathing heavily)
♪
Kenshin!
Ryukansen tornado flash!
(groans)
Time for duel
sword style.
Ying yang
double strike.
(groans)
(sighs)
♪
(shouting)
(giggling)
(snickers)
Come on guys,
let's do it!
Angle shuriken.
Brown shuriken.
-Circle shuriken.
♪
(grunting)
-Ha!
-We did it.
(gasps)
♪
(giggling)
The throwing knives could
not penetrate his fat!
He isn't even scratched.
What do we do now?
(grunts)
Oh no!
If I were you, I'd
stop worrying about them
and start worrying
about yourself.
Hi, I'm Kamatari, and
I'm gonna kill you.
♪
Stand up,
Battosai.
What's wrong with you?
The Kenshin Himura I knew
would never have given up.
Not now.
Not like this.
Perhaps you've changed
even more than I have.
Perhaps this new
Kenshin Himura
isn't as concerned
about honor
as the one I used to know.
In order to become the
most powerful fighter,
the man that I must
conquer in battle
is the one called
Battosai, the slasher.
I thought that
you were that man.
But he would never give up,
not Battosai, the slasher.
What a shame.
To have worked so hard
and searched for so long.
Being so close to regaining
my own personal honor.
You are robbing
me of the chance
to avenge my fallen comrades
that died because of you.
♪
(yells)
I gave up everything in order
to become the most powerful.
Because I knew that
attaining that goal
was all that I
would ever need.
I gave up control
and conscience,
for carnage and chaos.
I turned on those who
were once my friends.
They all hate me now, and
would kill me if they could.
♪
Aoshi.
Defend yourself,
Kenshin, now.
This is the chance for
me to annihilate you,
and finally achieve the goal
I've been trying to reach
for such a long time.
And when we're finished here,
no matter which of us wins,
I'll have the
satisfaction of knowing
I did everything I could.
I want to be the
most powerful, Kenshin.
Now get up.
I said, stand up.
And pick up your sword.
You have no choice,
either fight or die.
♪
Okina and Misao
were right about Aoshi.
He has absolutely
no conscience.
He's a cold-blooded killer
and he's so obsessed with
becoming the most powerful
that he's lost
his moral perspective.
He has no true sense
of right and wrong.
All he has now is some
twisted notion of honor
that's destroying him,
and everyone around him.
I hope Kenshin realizes
how dangerous he is,
and that for now,
at least, he can't afford
to worry about his
promise to Misao.
He's got to fight hard and
take Aoshi out if he can,
cause if he doesn't Aoshi's
going to do it to him.
♪
(gasps)
It's you who feels you
deserve to die, no one else.
You feel guilty
because you couldn't
protect your
four comrades
and you think by
punishing yourself,
you can atone for
what you've done.
None of your friends,
Misao, nor Okina,
nor Han'nya, Shikijo,
Beshimi, not even Hyottoko,
would want you to die.
So, don't use them to
justify your self-destruction.
♪
Alright, Aoshi,
I'll grant your wish.
I should have known that I
would need to defeat you again,
but considering what
you've been through,
the tragic death
of your four friends,
I wanted to spare you
any further indignity
or disappointment.
But now I realize that
you won't be satisfied
with anything less than a
full out effort on my part.
So, from here on, I'll
fight you with all my power.
(grunts)
But I will fight
you as Kenshin Himura,
not Battosai,
the slasher.
You say you're going to
fight, and give it your best,
but your sword is
reversed edge forward, right?
Right.
♪
That is unacceptable.
How can anybody totally
commit himself to a battle
while worrying
about his enemy's life?
♪
This fight's got to
be a fight to the death.
Only the most powerful one
will live when we're done.
It's the only way to decide
who's the best fighter.
I didn't spend all those
long days and nights
searching for you in
every city and village,
only to be denied
my satisfaction.
We will fight
to the death.
Be ready, Kenshin, because
I will kill you if I can.
♪
You really don't
understand, do you Aoshi?
Because you
kill so easily.
♪
I don't, but I've
learned something
you don't know
anything about yet,
which is how to use all
my power on an opponent
while staying in
control of myself.
What?
♪
You're a liar.
So you think I'm
lying, do you?
Well, then guess I'll just
have to prove it to you.
Hmm?
Sorry to disappoint
you, Mr. Shinomori,
but it looks like you don't
have any choice in the matter.
You're going to have to fight a
guy who refuses to kill you.
But look at it this way,
at least you're gonna
get to fight him
if the two of you ever
stop talking that is.
Make it quick, Kenshin,
or else we won't
get to Aoiya in time.
I know that this
fight has to happen.
The question that has to
be answered right now,
is which one of you is
the more skillful fighter.
So, go on, let's find out.
But before you do.
Huh?
Why didn't I hear
anything until now
about this control
secret of yours?
Well, uh.
That's all right.
Even if I don't understand
exactly what you're doing,
I'll finally be able to see
Kenshin Himura at his best.
Too bad Kaoru and Yoshi
couldn't be here to see this,
but hey, that's
their tough luck.
Yep.
♪
Ha.
Are you ready?
Let's do it.
♪
(grunting)
(yells)
♪
With my katachinito style, he
doesn't stand a chance.
Now you will die, Kenshin.
♪
First, dragon flash.
(shouts)
♪
Flying dragon flash.
(grunting)
♪
(groans)
(breathing heavily)
It's not over.
So, a liar, hmm?
Well, do you still
think that I'm lying?
Proud of yourself,
aren't you?
Well, Kenshin, I wouldn't
get too cocky if I were you.
It would have been your
blood on the floor, not mine,
if I'd turned just
a half second sooner,
and I'm not going to
let that happen again.
No, you're wrong about that.
What happens
here is up to me,
you have no choice
in the matter.
Huh?
♪
That slight difference of a
quarter second will be there
the next time and
the time after that.
Do you know why?
Because I don't fight from
a place of desperation,
because I fight to
live, not to kill.
That's the difference
between you and me, Aoshi.
That's the secret.
I trained with Master Hijo for
years before I understood it.
Still think
I'm a liar?
♪
No.
There's something else
you must understand.
The one that you call Battosai,
the slasher, no longer exists.
But when I was
known by that name,
I committed so many crimes that
it would be impossible for me
to atone for them
all in one lifetime.
However, the
one thing I can do
is fight on
the side of life,
and do my best
never to kill again.
Aoshi, you told me you
sacrificed everything
in order to become
the most powerful,
but true sacrifice isn't based
on desperation or obsession.
♪
You see, true sacrifice comes
from a place of love, not hate.
You're stronger
than you ever were.
With your sword, but
your mind has become weak.
My mind?
Aoshi, there
are two things
which have been controlling
you for a long time.
The first, to become
the most powerful.
The best
swordsman in Japan.
Second, to honor
your dead friends.
But you can't!
Not this way.
Not by killing me
or anyone else!
Death is not the answer.
The only way to find what
you're really looking for
is to look inside yourself,
and find out what
silenced your heart.
♪
Aoshi, you say you
want to honor the dead,
but you're not doing that.
You're just using them as
an excuse to go on killing.
♪
Beshimi.
Hyottoko.
Shikijo.
Han'nya.
Their friendship
meant so much to me.
How could I dishonor
them in death?
♪
(telegraph clicking)
(machine clacking)
♪