♪
(singing in foreign language)
In our last episode,
Kenshin defeated Sojiro
but was badly wounded
during the fight.
Combined with the
wounds he received
in his earlier
fight with Aoshi,
he's not at full strength
but is nonetheless on his way
to face the strongest
opponent of them all:
Shishio Makoto.
♪
Now I understand why Shishio
calls this place the heat room.
I wonder what that
horrible smell is.
Must be all those pools
of that black, stinky water
that we saw back there.
It's not water.
What do you mean by that?
It's a substance called oil,
what we used to call
burning water.
It's been used in lamps
for hundreds of years,
but other countries have
used it to replace coal.
It's also used
in a new machine
called an internal
combustion engine.
Shishio plans
on utilizing oil
so he can make Japan
a great world power.
Ha, you'd think Shishio
would've learned by now
that his plans to
take over the country
aren't going to amount
to a hill of beans.
Shishio's a stubborn fool,
he should've given up
a long time ago.
But fanatics like him are always
gonna fight to the last gasp.
(sighs)
You're the fool, Sano.
What did you say?
Sano.
Shishio is brilliant,
he's not to be taken lightly.
You're right, Mr. Himura.
I'm glad that at
least you understand.
Shishio isn't the type
to ever give up.
His belief in his
destiny is too strong.
One other thing.
This fight is extremely
important to Shishio.
Almost as important as his dream
of taking over the country.
♪
Ha, there's only one reason
Shishio is looking
forward to this fight:
Because it's an opportunity
to get rid of Kenshin
once and for all.
But Kenshin's not gonna lose,
and you can bet on that!
Everybody knows that
Shishio's a raving maniac
who's gotta be stopped,
lady, except you,
'cause you love him!
I know what a great man he is.
♪
I'll help Shishio lead Japan
to an honorable
and glorious future.
I'll be remembered
as the greatest woman
in the history of Japan.
♪
The time has finally come
to get rid of Himura forever.
True, we can't allow him
to interfere with our plans.
He's caused quite
enough damage already.
But that was your fault
as well, wasn't it, Hoji?
You refused to
recognize the threat
posed by Himura
and his allies.
That's why you hate him so much,
because of your own failures,
and why you're so
eager to see him die.
It wasn't my fault, sir.
No one could have predicted
the effects of a wildcard
like Himura.
I hate him only because
he stands in the way
of your final victory.
Ever since I met you,
I was inspired
by your strength
and determination,
your willingness to
sacrifice anything and anyone
in order to fulfill
your glorious destiny.
(chuckling)
But as you know, we've been
forced to delay our schedule
because of what Himura
and his cronies have done.
But once Himura's eliminated,
our schedule can be accelerated,
and within three years,
I'll have created
an organization
strong enough to ensure your
complete domination of Japan!
Excellent,
the sooner the better.
You're about to see the end
of Battousai the Slasher.
A truly historic moment,
don't you agree?
Yes.
♪
Kenshin's hurt.
He hasn't had a chance
to recover from his fights
with Aoshi and Sojiro.
He isn't strong enough to fight
a powerhouse like Shishio.
I've got to fight him,
and Sano mustn't interfere.
This is between me and Shishio.
There's more at stake here
than Kenshin's victory.
The people of Aoiya
are depending on him.
Without his protection,
they don't have a chance.
I can't let Shishio win.
I'll die before
I let that happen.
♪
There, that's better.
Careful, will ya?
This wound I got
is painful enough,
but what you're doing's
making it even worse!
Will you stop being so silly?
It's just a scratch,
a little cut that's
hardly more than skin-deep.
Stop acting so heroic, will you?
All right, but it still hurts!
♪
I can hardly believe it's over.
Aoiya isn't in danger
anymore, isn't that right?
-Kori?
-That's right.
I showed 'em!
Didn't I, Kori?
Sure did, I'm proud of you.
You kept the promise
that you made to Kenshin
that you would defend Aoiya.
I had no choice.
It was a promise
made man to man.
♪
But, I wonder...
What?
Do you think we'll ever be able
to tell Kenshin what happened?
Do you really think
he'll come back?
Yes, with all my heart.
♪
(watch ticking)
Shishio will show no mercy.
He'll kill me if he can,
because he believes that
only the strong should survive.
(screaming)
♪
Survival of the fittest.
The fundamental law of nature.
That's the way it's always
been and always will be.
The strong will live
and the weak shall die,
and I am the strongest of all.
♪
At the end of the Tokugawa era,
I chose one path
and Shishio another.
After so many years
of fighting,
the country was
finally at peace,
and I devoted myself
to protecting those
who wanted a peaceful life.
Shishio wants to
destroy all that,
and he and his followers
have created a new atmosphere
of terror throughout Japan.
♪
Hello there, Governor.
I'm terribly sorry to
disturb you like this.
But I'm afraid
you have to die!
(muffled screaming)
♪
What a shame.
I'm going to start
a revolution
which will tear
this country apart.
And then I shall rule Japan.
I'm the only one strong
enough to lead our nation
to its rightful place as the
greatest power in the world!
♪
The price of your
dreams of conquest
will be the blood
of the innocent,
the ones that
you call the weak,
who want nothing but to
live their lives in peace.
♪
The people you speak of
are nothing but sheep.
They'd be lost without
a leader like me to guide them.
Shishio Makoto,
I can't allow you to
slaughter the innocent.
I can't allow a madman
like you to rule Japan.
♪
Stop wasting time.
Draw your sword and fight.
♪
Are you ready, Kenshin?
I am.
♪
You have one weakness,
Hiko Seijuro.
You are afraid of death.
♪
And that's my advantage.
I've taken so many lives,
seen so much death,
that I've accepted
my own mortality.
Yes, I'm ready,
and if my time has come,
so be it!
Come on, start the lesson!
(screaming)
♪
When my father died,
I thought it was up to me
to defend my family,
but I was just a weak little
boy and couldn't protect them.
Shinta, from now on,
all I want you to think
about is how to survive.
You won't have anyone
to guide you now,
to show you what path to take,
so you're going to have
to find it all on your own.
You are meant to do
great things, Shinta.
I know it in my
heart, I know it.
Find the path!
I've been looking for
that path all my life.
Will I ever find it?
♪
(screaming)
Battousai.
You've been a thorn in
my side for a long time,
but I never took you seriously.
I thought of you
as a mere amusement,
someone I would
enjoy eliminating
when the time was right.
But now I realize
that you pose a threat
I can no longer ignore.
♪
So I'm going to destroy you.
Tomorrow, I'll begin the most
important battle of my life,
a battle that has to be fought
not only to protect the lives
of these wonderful friends
who are depending on me,
but to preserve the
freedom and security
of all the people of Japan.
Kenshin!
After you've won the battle,
you and I will go back together.
I'd like that, a lot.
♪
The last battle...
is about to begin.
(doors creaking open)
♪
Ah, Battousai.
I've got to admit,
you're better than I thought.
Sojiro was my most efficient
killer, but you beat him,
and didn't even have
to kill him to do it.
Impressive.
I was sure that you two
would fight to the death.
Imagine my surprise to learn
that you're both
still among the living.
Though I'm afraid you
won't be alive for long.
Don't you understand the
Juppongatana is history?
You're the only one left,
so what good are your plans now?
Mr. Shishio no longer needs
the Juppongatana group.
He can achieve his goals
without help from anyone.
But whatever happens,
neither one of you
are going to get
out of here alive!
After what you did
to the Rengoku,
I should kill you myself!
Yeah?
Hit me with your best shot.
♪
Miss Yumi.
In case we don't have
a chance to talk later,
thank you for showing
us the way here.
Yeah, same goes
for me, sweet thing.
Thanks for your help.
♪
You said the fight
would start...
at five o'clock.
♪
That's three minutes from now.
Please, Shishio.
Take care.
Kill him quickly.
♪
It'll all be over
in 15 minutes.
(departing footsteps)
Ha!
It'll be over, all right.
Over for Shishio, that is.
Sano.
No more talking
until we're finished.
Good luck.
You're wounded
all over your body.
Do you really think you're
strong enough to fight me?
Look who's talking,
you don't look like
you're in such
great shape yourself.
Yes, I see your point.
Then I suppose it's time.
Let's begin, shall we?
(ticking)
(loud whooshing)
(screaming)
(swords clanging)
♪
Come on, Kenshin,
you can do it.
I know you can.
♪
(screaming)
You're still pretty strong.
Winning this fight is going
to be more fun than I thought.
♪
That's it, flame technique!
Now move in and finish him off!
(flames crackling)
What the hell was that?
♪
How did he produce
so much flame and heat
from the tip of his sword?
♪
It couldn't be friction alone
or my sword would've
burst into flame as well,
so he must be using
some sort of substance,
but what is it and
where is it coming from?
(shouting)
Fireworks are a trick
to distract me.
The flames won't hurt
me, his sword will.
I've got to concentrate
on his sword, nothing else.
(shouting)
♪
Kenshin!
That's incredible!
(groaning)
♪
So, what do you think of
the Homura Dama technique?
Being slashed and set
aflame at the same time.
It's really quite
an experience, isn't it?
Yes, it's very unpleasant,
but the wound
isn't that deep
and I've learned
something interesting.
Now I understand how you create
the Homura Dama flame effect.
(gasps)
Really?
Care to elaborate?
The friction caused
by the tip of your sword
creates the heat
which starts the fire,
but the sword itself
isn't what's burning,
it's some sort of substance
that you're coating it with.
The substance is
stored in the hilt,
gravity draws it
down onto the blade
where it can be ignited.
It must be some sort of oil,
but not regular oil.
What is it?
The smell of burning bodies
is all too familiar to me.
It's oil refined from the
bodies of those you've killed.
It's human oil, isn't it?
Human oil?
A brilliant deduction.
Your powers of observation
are quite amazing.
I assume that's a result
of your training
in the Hiten Mitsurugi
technique.
Himura figured out the basis
of Mr. Shishio's secret
Homura Dama technique
after receiving
just two blows.
He's a lot more clever
than I realized.
But there's a great deal
more to the secret
than you imagine, Battousai.
In a way,
our swords are brothers,
for they were created by
the same master swordsmith.
Shakku.
But that's where
the similarity ends.
You see, any sword,
including yours,
loses its edge with use,
and the metal
becomes more brittle.
But this sword is different.
Shakku called it
the Ginzuto,
the Constant and Everlasting,
and it was his
greatest creation,
for it can never lose its edge
and will always remain
as flexible and resilient
as the day it was made.
The blade is lubricated
by the oil of its victims,
which is absorbed through tiny
openings on the reverse edge,
and its steel is retempered
and strengthened by the flames
of Homura Dama.
So you see, my sword
feeds upon its victims
the same way I do.
Once again, the law
of nature is seen
in the survival of
the fittest sword.
♪
They both lived through
the bloody end of an era
and use swords made
by the same man,
yet their philosophies
are worlds apart.
♪
You thought
if you knew my secret,
you might be able to beat me,
but the fact is, Kenshin,
you're going to die anyway.
Kenshin!
Stay out of it, Sano!
I was hoping that neither
of us would have to die
in order to prove
which of us was right.
I was able to accomplish
that with Sojiro.
But...
in your case, I've got
to do whatever's necessary
to stop you or you'll
devour the entire country.
Yes, but not until
I'm finished with you.
Defend yourself.
(shouting)
Watch out!
Hiten Mitsurugi style!
♪
Incredible.
(grunting)
♪
You already showed
me that technique
in the Shingetsu Village.
It's useless trying to attack me
with a move I've already seen.
You shall be consumed
as well, Battousai.
You'll make a delicious meal.
♪
(laughing)
(screaming)
(biting)
♪
Kenshin!
(salivating)
♪
Kenshin!
(singing in foreign language)
♪