♪
(singing in foreign language)
In our last episode, after
sharing a moment with Yumi,
Shishio begins his
battle with Kenshin,
who finds himself
fighting for his life.
♪
(yelling)
(fire roaring)
(whimpering)
♪
Survival of the fittest,
it's the only way.
So I've heard.
The strong will live,
the weak will die.
To Sojiro, this meant merely
being the strongest fighter,
but in fact, it means a
great deal more that that.
It's fundamental.
It's a law of nature.
♪
The weak exist only as
fodder for the strong.
But throughout history,
there have been times
when great multitudes of
weak men have banded together,
and with the strength of their
numbers, they've subverted
and suppressed
the laws of nature,
and now it's happening again!
The Meiji government
is an obscenity!
But soon I will take control
and lead Japan to glory.
You are a killer
who lived through
the bloody end of
the Tokugawa era.
You understand
that we must abide
by the fundamental
law of nature.
The strong will live, the weak
can be used, then discarded.
The strong cannot be
subservient to the weak.
You agree, don't you?
No, I don't.
♪
No human being in a free society
should be regarded as less
valuable than any other.
The people of this country
that you call fodder
are the ones that give it
stability and its strength.
All they ever asked
for was peace,
and now after living
through the bloodiest era
Japan has ever seen,
they've got it,
now you wanna destroy them,
and I'll do whatever
I can to stop you.
But you cannot stop me.
I must fulfill my destiny.
Your destiny is to lose.
♪
No matter how brilliant
Shishio's arguments are,
Kenshin's beliefs
are too strong.
He won't budge an inch,
but Shishio already knows that.
The reason he wants
Kenshin to keep talking
is because Kenshin's
already weak from his wounds,
and the longer they talk
the weaker he'll get.
♪
You're lying to yourself,
Kenshin Himura.
I know that deep within
your heart you agree with me.
I know all about you, Kenshin.
Your reputation as a merciless
slasher was well-deserved.
I wonder what you
find more embarrassing.
The fact that you killed
all those people,
or your pathetic attempt to
try to deny who you really are.
♪
You're a warrior,
Kenshin, I know you are.
The question is,
are you a better
warrior than I am?
Unfortunately for you,
the answer is no
which means that
you're going to die!
Yeah, I'll die,
but I won't die today.
Not at the hands of
a maniac like you.
I want the fighting to be
over, I want to live in peace.
(grunting)
Oh no, he's losing.
Hm.
(laughing)
So you think you're hot stuff?
Stop kidding yourself.
The truth is that there are
countries all over the world
who are at war with each other.
The European countries
are setting up colonies
wherever they can.
The British control India,
a country 12 times
the size of their own,
and other powers are
establishing colonies
in the China Sea which could
choke off our trade routes,
and could be staging
areas to attack Japan.
And what has our
government done about it?
Nothing, the only
thing they care about
is political maneuvering
and making certain
that they remain in power.
The other military powers
of the world are well aware
of our government's weakness,
and if Japan continues
on its present course,
we'll end up as a
colony, not a country.
Our so-called leaders
have to be replaced
in order to preserve
the honor of Japan.
♪
Kenshin's getting
weaker by the moment.
First he was wounded
in his duel with Aoshi,
and before he had a chance
to recover he fought Sojiro
who cut him up pretty badly
before Kenshin finally won.
If Kenshin waits any longer
he might not be strong enough
to beat Shishio.
♪
(groaning)
Sojiro told me all
about your law of nature,
the survival of the fittest.
You warped and twisted that poor
kid into an inhuman heartless
monster without the ability
to feel anything for anyone.
♪
The strong will live,
and the weak will die.
It's the natural
order of things,
yet you go on trying
to protect the weak.
I can't understand
why you would do that.
Why waste time on people
who aren't relevant?
Mr. Shishio taught me to
concern myself only with people
who were strong enough
to be dangerous,
how to recognize who they were,
and how to eliminate them.
Mr. Shishio gave me this sword.
Without it I wouldn't
have survived.
I never wanted to kill anyone.
It was Mr. Shishio who taught me
that I didn't have any choice.
If I hadn't killed them,
they would've killed me.
But still, the truth is,
I never wanted to kill anyone.
You used Sojiro
like everyone else.
You knew he couldn't win.
You had us fight in
order to weaken me.
Yes, exactly.
I'll do whatever
it takes to win.
In this case, I used
Sojiro's fanatical loyalty.
I knew he would wound
you badly enough
to drain most of your strength.
He even gave me the
ultimate farewell gift.
He told me how
to protect myself
against your secret
sword-strike technique.
A farewell gift?
I'm glad to hear it, there's
hope for Sojiro after all.
Huh?
I wouldn't expect you
to understand, Shishio,
so I'll explain it to you.
For the first time in his life,
Sojiro has given something
to someone simply
because he wanted to,
not for his own benefit.
He's not under your
control anymore, Shishio.
He's realized that
there's more to life
than being the strongest,
and now he'll find
his own answers.
I want an answer too,
Kenshin, remember?
I asked if you were
strong enough to beat me,
and that question can only
be answered with action.
You can't hide behind
your words any longer.
All right, Shishio,
make your move.
Yes, I think it's finally time
to say goodbye
to Kenshin Himura.
(shouting)
♪
No, it's too soon
for you to die.
♪
I know that smell.
At least you'll die
having the satisfaction
of a glorious death.
Gunpowder.
No!
(laughing)
♪
Kenshin!
No, dead?
♪
Poor Kenshin, I
can't believe it.
♪
What's this, dead already?
And I was going to
make him suffer.
I'm disappointed, I thought
you'd provide a lot more
entertainment than this.
Ha, it's really a pity.
Nine minutes and
fifty-three seconds.
There was no need
to worry after all.
I would never have believed
it if I hadn't seen it
with my own two eyes.
Gunpowder hidden in
the glove of his armor,
and he set it off just
as he struck Himura.
A brilliant strategy,
Mr. Shishio.
Absolutely brilliant.
Enough of your
compliments, Hoji.
See to it this
mess is cleaned up.
Yes, sir.
A wise warrior once said that
it's dangerous to let down
your guard until all of your
enemies have been defeated.
(screaming)
Saito!
(yelling)
-Mr. Shishio!
-Ahh!
He's got ya!
(shouting)
Ha!
Great.
Saito hit him perfectly.
How could Shishio
have even survived
a killer blow like that?
♪
I knew you would
come eventually.
♪
I know how clever
you are, Saito,
and that somehow you've managed
to learn many of my secrets,
but you didn't know
about this one, did you?
A steel crown.
Ten years ago, when
agents of the government
tried to assassinate me,
they knocked me unconscious
with a blow to the head.
It caused permanent
damage to my skull.
So I have made certain that
it will never happen again.
I'm afraid you didn't
do you research
quite well enough, Saito Hajime.
You lost the only chance
you had to destroy me.
♪
You must have received
that wound on your leg
when you fought Usui.
At least he did something
right before he died.
Actually, considering the
severity of your wound,
I'm surprised you were able
to mount such a strong attack.
It really was quite impressive.
Shame you have to die.
(flames hissing)
But look at the bright side.
When you get to the other world,
you and Battousai will
have a lot to talk about.
Perhaps, but I haven't
finished with you yet, Shishio.
I am going to kill
you or die trying.
Your dedication is admirable,
but what I don't understand
is why a former member
of the Shinsen group
would fight for the sake
of a corrupt government.
They don't deserve your
loyalty, and you know it.
I think you're fighting
for some other reason,
some lame sense of righteousness
like your friend Kenshin.
Is that it?
The reason I fight
is because I believe
in a very simple philosophy.
Those who are evil
must be destroyed,
killed immediately.
♪
Good.
Finally a man with a philosophy
that's easy to understand.
Unfortunately, a man
who's also about to die.
♪
That's enough talk.
You're not as strong
as you used to be.
I'm afraid your wounds
have taken their toll.
♪
You see, your fight with Usui
was part of my master plan.
I assumed you would win
and that you would
probably kill him,
but I also knew that
he would dissipate you.
You must admit my
plan worked perfectly.
Yet even if you'd been at full
strength you couldn't have won.
I've seen you fight often enough
to know all your techniques.
Huh?
♪
Saito knows he doesn't
stand a chance,
but he won't give up.
Now that Kenshin
has been taken out,
he feels that he and his
Gatotsu are all that remains
to keep Shishio from
completing his plan
to destroy the government
and become dictator of Japan.
♪
That's enough.
We are wasting time, come on.
You know the end is inevitable,
so why put it off any longer?
It's time to say goodbye.
Attack while you can.
Quickly.
Fang Thrust Two!
♪
Flying Fang Thrust!
(gasping)
(grunting)
♪
Like I said, Saito.
I know all your secrets,
all your tricks.
Can't you see it's hopeless?
All I see is an arrogant bastard
who I'm going to kill now!
Fang Thrust Zero!
♪
(laughing)
It's the end, my friend.
♪
You're not feeling so well.
I must admit, you lasted
longer than I thought you would.
For a government man, you fought
very well, and honorably.
I promise, when historians
write about my rise to power,
I'll make certain they
mention how well you fought.
Farewell, Saito Hajime.
You were a worthy opponent.
(screaming)
♪
(laughing)
Ohh.
♪
You?
You're still here?
Lucky for you, I'm
feeling generous.
I won't kill
cowards, you can go.
I don't accept your generosity,
and I'm not going
anywhere, not quite yet.
I don't mind dying as long
as I take you with me.
(laughing)
The only way you
could kill me, Sano,
is in your dreams,
that's the only way.
I can't believe that even
you would be foolish enough
to want to fight me after
what you've seen here today.
The secret sword technique
of Kenshin Himura,
the legendary Battousai
the Slasher wasn't enough.
Neither was the
Gatotsu of Saito,
the most formidable fighter
of the Shinsen group.
Their perseverance and bravery
did them no good in the end.
The strong live,
and the weak die.
You mean survival
of the fittest?
Exactly.
You're like a cannibal, Shishio.
You devour other human
beings in order to survive.
What's for lunch?
No human can be like that!
Kenshin was right.
You're a freak of
nature, an abomination.
The Meiji Restoration
started 10 years ago,
but there's still so much to do.
Right now, the weak are
still being oppressed
all over our country
by the strong,
but I know that
the future of Japan
depends on the beliefs and
principles of the Restoration
being accepted by all the
peoples of our country.
The old ways won't work anymore.
That's why Shishio has to go.
Guys like him would rather die
than live in a world
of peace and justice.
♪
You know, Kenshin used
his sword to protect people
who couldn't protect themselves.
He was trying to
build something,
not destroy everything
like you're trying to do.
And the result is he's dead.
Go away, Sanosuke Sagara.
There's nothing more
you can do here.
I'm not through with you yet!
(yelling)
♪
Let's not waste time.
(groaning)
♪
Hoji, you can kill him
now or just let him die.
He won't last very long,
almost all the bones
in his torso are broken.
Shishio, wait.
Not yet.
What?
(grunting)
Kori, I'm sorry that I
couldn't protect Kenshin.
But this I swear.
I won't give up.
I'll fight this battle to
the end, to my last breath.
♪
(shouting)
I can't believe it!
♪
Ha!
That's the best
you've got, Sano?
Sorry, but it's just
not good enough.
♪
You should've left when
you had the opportunity.
♪
(laughing)
He's unstoppable.
No, he's more than that.
Mr. Shishio is invulnerable.
No one is as powerful.
No one has his
indomitable will.
He's the only one who can lead
Japan to the glory it deserves.
Finish him off now, Shishio.
What are you waiting for?
He's helpless, kill
him, kill him now!
Silence, Yumi!
I've won a great victory
today, and I wish to savor it.
You must learn to
have patience, my dear.
(laughing)
You're wrong.
(gasping)
The day isn't over.
You haven't won yet.
♪
Aoshi, you must leave at once.
She's right,
you shouldn't have come, Aoshi.
Your friends won't be
able to lend a hand,
but you'll be joining
them shortly.
(laughing)
♪
(singing in foreign language)