(theme song)
♪
It's the Meiji government
I want to get even with.
♪
I want to return honor
to the Sekiho troop
and the name of Captain Sagara.
See you later.
Wait a minute.
I can't let you do this
all by yourself, you know.
Yeah?
♪
All of my new friends
are really important to me,
but for some reason I just
can't let go of my past.
♪
A party?
That's right.
I thought it might be nice
for all of us to get together
and celebrate.
So what do you think?
It's a wonderful idea.
It's wonderful!
I have no objections
to having a party.
Just one question.
Money.
But we're deep in debt.
How are we supposed
to come up with the money
to have a good time?
See, there's always
a party pooper.
Oh, well, we'll
think of some idea.
Yeah, we'll think of some idea!
I have a feeling something
just might turn up.
Oh?
So, do you know something?
Hm, I hope you're not thinking
that I'm gonna supply the money.
You can forget about it.
I hardly made enough
money in this dojo
giving hours of
sword fighting lessons
just to feed all
of you freeloaders,
so don't count on me.
There's absolutely no
extra money in this house.
And that's all.
Hey, Kori, don't have
a conniption fit, all right?
I will take care
of the money, okay?
Just leave it to me.
You're going to get
credit from Lenny's?
That's a terrible plan.
We'll still have
to pay that off,
and that'll leave
us further in debt.
Don't worry, we'll do it here.
At the dojo?
Yeah.
We can have a great time here,
and we won't be bothering
anyone else, all right?
That's okay with me.
We can have it right here.
Then it's settled.
I'll go get some money.
Oh, Kori, do me a favor
and ask Megumi if
she would join us.
You want me to invite Megumi?
Yeah, if you wouldn't mind.
She's been a good
friend for a long time.
Besides, the more the merrier.
See you later.
Wow, that was incredible.
What was that all about?
I never thought he'd
invite Megumi for anything.
Every single time
they get together,
all they do is fight.
You know, you're right, Yoshi.
Sanosuke's not himself tonight.
I certainly hope he's not
sick or anything like that.
-Huh?
-Ah!
I know what he's so happy about!
He's excited that
the Sekiho troupe
has just been cleared
of any wrongdoing.
You just might have
something there.
Maybe that's it.
In that case,
we should party down.
(giggling)
Party down, party down!
Oh yeah!
Wonder if this does
have anything to do
with the Sekiho troupe.
(high-pitched grunt)
(grunting)
Take that!
You'll have to do
better than that.
Out with a bang.
(explosion)
So?
Katsu, always nice to see you.
Listen, I was wonderin'
if you could loan me some money.
I'm a little short of scratch.
Wow.
You're givin' me
your whole wallet?
Well, I guess that
you famous artist types
must really be loaded.
Sano, you'd better hurry up
if you plan to spend it.
Oh?
♪
I'm planning the attack
for this evening.
It's going to be
a new moon tonight.
I'm going to destroy
the centerpiece
of the new Meiji government.
I've decided I'm going to level
the Ministry of Home Affairs.
I was thinking
that if we can stop
all of their operations there,
then we can move on and take
out their other offices.
Uh, does it have to be tonight?
Yes, it does, why?
Oh, nothin'.
Tonight's fine.
Thanks for the dough.
I'll pay you back.
Hey, thanks very much.
Have a great time.
(giggling)
Look at all that!
Looks fantastic.
Wow, what an incredible feast.
I've never seen
so much delicious food
in one place before.
I'm gonna carry this one.
Suzi, be careful
with that tray.
It's very heavy, okay?
All right.
Ah!
Oh...
(crying)
You come back here!
Hey you two, stop that!
You're making me dizzy
and I haven't even
drunk any sake yet!
(laughing)
Hey, what do you say
we start the party now?
Oh, Sanosuke,
this is quite a spread.
You really outdid yourself.
What I'm wondering is
where did you get the money
for all of this stuff?
You didn't do anything illegal
that would get us all
in trouble, did you?
Huh, I should have expected you
to say something
nasty like that.
You're still as
charming as ever.
Yeah?
Well, you have as
much charm as a snake.
You guys do this
every time we get together.
You're just birds of
a feather, you know that?
You know what you both act like,
like you're married.
(laughing)
(thud)
Hey guys, take it easy,
this is a party!
We're supposed to have fun.
Let's not punch Yoshi for once.
It's a little late,
but you're right, it's a party.
Let's celebrate!
Yay!
Yeah, sake!
Kenshin, let me do that for you.
All right, that would be
very nice of you, Kori.
Kori, you don't even know
how to correctly pour the sake.
How embarrassing for you.
Here, let me.
I'll demonstrate
the proper way of doing it.
Just butt out!
I'm going to pour it for him.
Oh, just be quiet.
Watch and learn.
Here you are, Kenshin.
Allow me to pour it.
Well, you really are
good at pouring, Megumi.
(angry grunting)
What do you mean by saying
she's very good at pouring sake?
I'll never offer to
pour for you again.
(nervous laughter)
Yoshi, slow down.
Here, have something
to wash it down with.
Oh!
All right.
He's a little boy.
Don't give him sake
to drink, Sano!
(grunting)
Will you stop treating me
like I'm a little child?
I'll have you know, Kori,
that I can take care of myself
without any of your help.
If I want to drink some sake,
then I'll drink it!
Do you understand that?
Here, watch this!
(gulping)
That was easy!
What the?
Whoa...
Maybe you should
sit down, Yoshi.
Oh, I don't feel so good.
Ugh...
See?
What did I tell you?
I guess you were right, Kori.
He can't hold his sake.
You should stick to eating.
Kenshin, the polite thing to do
is to offer me some sake.
Sure, I'm sorry.
What?
I can't believe it!
She's drinking
from the same cup!
It's unsanitary!
Ah, delicious.
(giggles)
You drink like a sailor.
Perhaps you need to
grow up, little girl.
Women do things differently.
Who are you calling
"little girl"?
(distant howling)
♪
Hey sweetheart, would you
mind pouring me some sake, hm?
Oh!
That sake's got a punch.
Well, I'm going to have
some sake like everyone else.
(gulping)
Hey Kori, be careful with that!
It's not water, you know!
Mind your own business.
Uh, Kori...
Kenshin, she said for you
to mind your own business,
so just leave her alone.
Are you hungry?
Would you like
some nice bean curd?
Wow.
Oh!
(high-pitched sound)
(hiccups)
♪
Hey, come on now, Kori,
don't overdo it.
Hey there, Kenshin!
Uh, yeah?
Huh?
I may not be very good
at serving you sake,
and I'm a bad cook
and I know I'm not very sexy.
The only thing I really know
about is using a sword.
(hiccups)
Come on now,
Kori, don't be sad!
You have a lot
of nice qualities.
Oh no, she's right.
She does have shortcomings.
Listen, Kori, that's
just the alcohol talking.
There's one--there's one--
there's one thing that
nobody can beat me at.
I still have one thing,
and that one thing is...
Yeah, what is it?
It's just that I...
(crying)
(maniacal laughter)
♪
That I can't tell you,
it's too personal.
It's too shamefaced to mention.
(maniacal laughter)
Uh, don't give
her any more sake.
I don't know, should I tell?
I don't know,
should I really tell him?
Tell us already or shut up.
You're drivin' me crazy
with that idiot rambling.
Hey, she doesn't have to
tell us if she doesn't want to.
Hey there, Kenshin,
I want to make sure you
hear what I have to say here,
capisce?
She's losin' it.
Let go of him.
No!
(slap)
Ow!
Hey, you hit me.
Bingo!
Uh, ladies, please?
(weak laughter)
Huh?
Kenshin,
let's you and me have a contest.
They look like Halloween.
(giggling)
(gulping)
Ah!
My stomach's on fire.
I can't drink any more.
Aha!
I'm the winner of the contest!
It's nice to know I
can beat you at something!
(laughing)
That's my sword...
(soft breathing and snoring)
It's time for me to go.
Hm?
Looks like the Last Supper.
I hope you had
a real good time, Sano.
That wasn't the reason
that I did this.
They're a nice group of people.
It was just my way
of thanking them.
Are you sure that you still
want to go through with this?
You'll lose everything.
My mind's made up,
there are some things
that are more important
than sentimentality.
This is what I'm
committed to do.
This is my destiny and I
have to go through with it.
That's good.
You are now being more
loyal to the Sekiho troupe
than your new friends.
I'm glad you chose
the past over them.
Let's get started.
We have a lot to
do before morning.
Hurry up.
I'm sorry, you guys.
I can't expect you
to understand.
The Sekiho troupe is
a part of my past.
It's still a part of me.
We've known each
other a short time,
but all of you are
like my family.
I'm glad I met you
and that we've spent
this time together.
After tonight I don't think
I'll ever see you again.
I'm sorry.
Don't think bad of me.
I'll miss every one of you.
Kenshin, I'll miss you the most.
♪
There it is.
This building is
the command center
of the Meiji
government's administration.
♪
And tonight, it's coming down.
Stay alert, soldier!
Yes, sir!
(fizzing)
♪
Here we go.
It's show time.
(explosion)
Huh?
What was that?
Alert the guard!
Yes, sir!
Call for reinforcements!
Right away, sir!
♪
(blowing whistle)
Let's go, come on!
Keep moving, those bombs should
keep 'em busy for a while.
We've gotta get over the fence.
Yeah, once we get inside
we'll destroy the building.
Their ministry will
be nothing but rubble.
Come on, let's hustle up!
♪
(grunting)
Help me up.
♪
Kenshin!
Sano, who is that man?
That, my friend, is
Battousai the legendary Slasher.
That guy is
Battousai the Slasher,
the pig guard of the royalists?
♪
You Meiji patriot.
You still think you can stop us?
The Sekiho troupe will
defeat you this time, Slasher.
See these?
Yeah, they're explosives.
Very good.
I'm going to blow this
government building
to smithereens,
and eventually extinguish
the Meiji government,
and anyone else
who gets in my way,
and that includes you,
Battousai the Slasher.
♪
Adios!
(grunts)
What? That's impossible!
Nothing is impossible for him.
There is nothing
that he can't do
with that reversed
edge sword of his.
He somehow defused the bombs.
Only he could do that.
He's nothing.
Just a government dog.
Take it easy, Katsu.
Kenshin feels the same way
about the government as we do.
What are you,
on his side or something?
When I first met him, I felt
exactly the same way as you do.
I thought he was nothing
but a lousy royalist.
I turned on him
and wanted to fight him.
Sano, you were right
to want to fight him.
He's the enemy.
No, he is my friend.
I remember when we did fight,
he blew me away.
He even made me believe
that he was one of us,
but now I have to turn
my back on my friendship.
I have to remain loyal
to the Sekiho troupe.
There's no turning back now.
I have to make my stand.
There are some things
that need to be righted.
You have always been
a good friend to me,
but tonight you'd
better stay out of my way.
I'm warning you, Kenshin,
I will kill you.
Sano, I know that
you feel that the Sekiho troupe
has been treated
unfairly in the past
and that this is
your way of rectifying it.
I don't intend on
talking you out of this,
but I have to do
what I have to do.
So do I.
♪
Sano, take
a weapon with you!
This is suicide!
(grunting)
♪
Come on, Kenshin, let's see you
draw your reversed edge sword.
What are you waiting for?
I never draw on an unarmed man.
You should know that, Sanosuke.
We'll see about that.
(grunting)
The dragon hammer flash.
Huh, where'd he go?
Ya!
♪
Sano!
Now that's it!
You'll be sorry you did that.
(grunting)
♪
(explosion)
Yeah, take that!
You didn't have a chance
to react that time,
did you, Battousai?
I put shorter fuses
on those bombs.
Where is he?
You won't get him
that way, my friend.
Hold it right there, Tsukioka.
If you use these explosives,
a lot of innocent people
are gonna get hurt
or worse yet killed.
What you're doing is wrong.
I won't allow you to
create anarchy and chaos.
(snickers)
(explosion)
(grunting)
You see, I really don't care
how many people get killed,
just as long as my goal to get
revenge for the Sekiho troupe
is fulfilled,
and I won't stop until
my captain's name is cleared.
But I can't expect
a Meiji patriot like you
to understand that.
You won't clear
your captain's name
by murdering innocent people.
The only thing you'll accomplish
is to bring further shame
upon your Sekiho troupe.
You're a former Slasher!
You've got nerve
talking like that!
Katsu, knock it off.
You've got work to do.
Kenshin, I am your opponent.
Come over here and fight me.
Sano.
Katsu, leave Kenshin to me.
Go and take care of
the building already, will ya?
Just go on and execute the plan
before all of those guards
come back here and find us.
Kenshin, come on.
Sano!
(grunting)
(piercing thud)
(pained grunting)
No!
Sano.
Katsu, get out of here!
Go on!
Ah!
You're risking
everything for the sake
of a fellow
Sekiho troop member,
even your own life!
Katsu, what are you doing?
Hurry up and get out of here.
No, I won't.
I won't leave you
here all alone.
(pained grunting)
♪
Stay away from him, Sano!
(panting)
What are you doing?
This Battousai will kill you.
-Get away.
-Don't do it.
Sano!
♪
(panting)
Sano!
(thud)
No!
♪
Sano.
I'm sorry.
No.
Katsu, I want you to
take care of Sano for me.
♪
Why did you do it?
You said he was your friend.
How could you do this?
Don't think this is over.
This is far from over.
You haven't won anything.
I won't sacrifice
Sano for nothing.
We have a score to
settle, do you hear me?
Battousai!
We will not stop until
we have settled the score,
do you understand?
You're the criminal
here, not us.
You're the one who killed
in the name of
the Meiji government.
You're nothing more
than an assassin.
You're the one
who's dirty, not us.
You. You're the killer.
♪
(gasps)
How strange.
He seems so
at peace with himself.
But how can he be
knowing what he knows?
Sano!
Kenshin...
Let's get out of here.
I've got to take
care of your wounds.
Kenshin...
I thank you.
(gasps)
Thanks to you,
we didn't end up being
dishonorable soldiers.
♪
Battousai the Slasher.
Maybe you're right.
Captain Sagara,
I wish you could
tell me what to do.
I feel so lost.
♪
(grunting)
Huh?
I lost to Kenshin again.
Katsu, where are you?
Oh no.
(panting)
Huh?
(grunting)
Hm.
♪
Sano, what the heck
happened to you?
You knucklehead, you probably
got so drunk last night
you wandered off and fell
into a sewer, didn't you?
Shut your yap, you're not
so great with sake yourself.
Is that bruise on his
ribs made from your sword?
There was a misunderstanding,
but it's over now.
Like you do!
(laughing)
Sano, you'd better
take a bath right away.
♪
So what happened to Tsukioka
after you saw him burying
all of his explosives?
I don't really know,
but I think he's out
of the bomb business.
You're the ones who asked
me about those pictures.
I've got somethin' for ya.
Come on, don't be shy.
All right, my friend.
You've got our attention.
What do you have anyway?
A Mr. Tsukioka left
this here for ya.
He said this is
his last woodblock print.
I think it's a shame.
He was one of the best
artists that I represented.
I don't know what got into him.
I heard he started
his own newspaper.
He said he was gonna
write all about the atrocities
in the Meiji government.
Personally I think
he's stickin' his neck out,
not to mention it's a shame
to lose an artist like him.
Yep, he was one of a kind.
♪
(theme song)