♪
(theme song)
In our last episode,
Yoshi was hit with
a poison dart by
an Oni gang member,
but made a full recovery
thanks to Dr. Gensai.
Kenshin brought
a troubled young lady
named Megumi
into our lives.
Everyone liked her,
but I had my
suspicions about her.
It turned out that one
of Sanosuke's friends
died from some opium
that Megumi made.
Even though Megumi
had been forced
to make the opium by
gang leader Henry Takeda,
Sanosuke couldn't
forgive her
for causing his
friend's death.
Megumi went back to the
evil gang leader, Henry.
She knew she was
risking her life
to protect us from
him and his gang.
This showed us all her
truly courageous nature.
After witnessing
her self-sacrifice
and understanding her pain,
Sanosuke changed
his mind about her.
Sanosuke made
peace with Megumi,
then he was involved
in an epic battle
with a strong man
of the Oni gang,
Shikijô.
It was a classic
confrontation
between the forces
of good and evil.
Sanosuke fought hard
to rescue Megumi
from the gang's clutches,
and even though
he's a great
martial artist,
no one thought
Sanosuke had a chance.
But when all was
said and done,
Sanosuke proved
his mettle against
his awesome opponent.
Even though Sanosuke
was victorious,
Megumi was taken to
the gang's stronghold.
With our brave
friend kidnapped,
Kenshin, myself, and the
rest of our peace force
have decided
to save Megumi
no matter what the cost.
♪
(clank)
What the hell is that?
(grunts)
Megumi's got to be inside.
We are here to free
our friend Megumi
and none of you
will stop us.
♪
Don't just stand there,
you idiots, attack!
(yelling)
♪
Well...
welcome back,
my precious Megumi.
I knew once you
came to your senses,
you'd return to us.
I need you to get
started making
your special brand
of opium right away.
(chuckles)
No answer, eh?
You've become quite
rebellious lately.
Well, if you're not
willing to cooperate
with my ideas,
there are...
consequences.
♪
There really is
something you can do
to compensate
for Yoita's death.
You can make Takeda pay
for forcing you
to do his dirty work.
♪
There's only one way
to stop this monster.
♪
You wouldn't
kill me, would you?
(chuckles)
That all depends on you.
There's only one way
to stop you and your evil.
(screams)
(gasps)
You really thought
that you could stop us?
Why you--
You're stupid!
I've treated you
nicely in the past,
but don't push your luck.
I am Henry Takeda,
and nobody gets to me.
I could kill you right now,
but that can be delayed.
I want to get
that opium formula
out of you first, Megumi.
I need to hear answers,
otherwise I'll have
to start torturing you.
(laughs)
(whistling)
Huh?
Sounds like someone's coming.
♪
They're quick.
Yeah, but they're
not very tough.
Hey, you guys,
clear the way!
♪
Clear it!
What a fighter!
Wait a minute.
But aren't there
four of them?
Ow!
All present
and accounted for.
Hope you two
have a nice nap.
-Yeah!
(grunts)
♪
All right, men,
fire on my command.
(shouting)
♪
All right,
that's enough.
Let's finish him off.
All right.
Ready, aim--
Yoshi, try jumping at them.
Hi-ya!
Like this!
You're through, kid.
Huh?
♪
(groans)
(gasping)
Ah!
Yoshi, get rid
of that gun.
(clang)
Hey, Sano,
what were you
thinking about
tossing me
through the air
like a spear?
Well, I know how much you
like action, so why not?
Huh, thanks.
Don't do that again, Sano.
I don't understand.
Why is Battousai the Slasher
putting himself
in so much danger,
risking his own life?
What does he have
to gain by this?
It just doesn't
make any sense.
Megumi has no money.
Why risk it all for her?
Can't you see
what motivates him?
If Battousai was
the kind of guy
who did things for profit,
he would be a military
captain by now.
He believes that
honor and justice
are more important than money.
As misguided as
his value system is,
I actually understand it.
But what's important now
is how we're going to stop him
from destroying
our whole gang.
(shudders)
♪
We have come here
to collect our friend
Megumi, Takeda.
(groans)
And if you know
what's best,
you'll bring her
down right now.
(groans)
Sure, but let's talk first.
I wanna congratulate you.
You just neutralized
my guard force.
Of course you are Battousai,
the world famous
slasher, aren't you?
But how does he know
that about Kenshin?
The Oni syndicate knows
about almost everything.
And so, I have an
exciting proposal
to offer you.
It would be an honor
to have you join
the Oni syndicate.
Your pay would be so much
that you could retire
in just one year.
Just think, after just
one year of working for me,
you'd never have
to work again.
Say yes?
Well, what do
you say, Battousai?
Are you going to
bring down Megumi now?
Or should I come up?
Huh?
I'll pay you
a thousand yen a day.
L-Let's make it two thousand.
Don't you understand,
this man is different.
He will not be bought.
Just shut up!
I have heard
enough from you.
(groans)
All right, you've
wiped out most of my men,
so I guess I have
to surrender.
I will bring
Megumi to you.
But before I can surrender
and give you Megumi,
I need to get
my affairs in order.
Please, give me an hour
so I can get ready
to leave the premises.
You really expect us to buy
your cock-and-bull story?
He's just stalling.
Now, I need to squeeze
that opium recipe
out of Megumi
and escape.
Then I'll be set.
♪
What the...
-Wow.
-Whoa.
(gasps)
♪
You've got an hour,
and Megumi better
be all right.
If she's not,
I promise you,
you'll be dead.
(shuddering gasp)
You shouldn't have
infuriated him
with your silly offer.
You're just stalling
the inevitable.
The only chance
we've got to stop him
is to challenge him
and then kill him.
The reason you're
part of the Oni gang
is times like this
when I really need
someone to deliver, Han'nya.
And I won't tolerate
idiotic mistakes
like the ones
Beshimi and Shikijô--
No, you listen to me.
There's only one person
that controls what I do
in this gang,
and that's Aoshi,
because I respect
him, understand?
So, don't try to
give me orders, got it?
Yes, I understand.
You're the kind
of gutless slime
that I tolerate
in the hope that someday
you'll grow a spine.
You should know that
a real man's honor
can never be bought
or compromised.
It would appear that
you're a little confused
as to who's the boss
of this syndicate.
I'm the guy with
the money who's kept
this organization
working like
a well-oiled machine, hah!
You're nothing but
a glorified accountant.
Boys!
Just what are you two doing?
Aoshi.
Glad you're here.
Tell Han'nya who's
the boss here?
You're through being
boss around here, Takeda.
What?
Your attempts
to keep our gang tough
have been pathetic.
You've allowed us
to become way too soft.
Just what do
you mean by that?
To you, the only thing
this syndicate is for
is to generate money.
You have no sense
of pride about
the Oni gang and
the fear and terror
that we have made
our trademarks.
You are nothing but
a money-hungry jellyfish
with no honor to speak of.
So, based on your
lack of vision,
you can understand why
an individual like myself
will be replacing
you as boss here.
Now that that's settled,
let's get to the more
serious business at hand:
dealing with
Battousai the Slasher.
I haven't seen such
a good fighter in years.
He's our target,
you got it?
But I need some protection.
He's coming back
in less than an hour.
What happens to you
from now on is of
little concern to us.
He'll kill me!
Too bad.
The only thing
he really wants
is to get Megumi back,
so we have the bait
to bring him to us.
I'll take her up
to the third floor.
Han'nya, take your position.
Yes, sir.
Hey, what am I
supposed to do, Aoshi?
Why don't you just
count some money,
and keep a low profile, okay?
(groans)
Aoshi, I will get you for this!
♪
Takeda and his gang
have had a lot of time
to set up traps for us,
so we'd better
be extra careful.
Ow!
I think you better
bring up the rear.
(grunts)
♪
Welcome, Kenshin Peace Force
and especially you, Battousai.
We have been
anxiously awaiting you.
I am Han'nya,
the undercover guard
here at Edo Castle.
And now, I suggest
you prepare to meet
your doom.
(evil laughter)
(dog barks)
♪
Your friends from
Kamiya Dojo have
followed you here,
and they are making
an attempt to rescue you.
You mean Kenshin is here?
There's no hope.
Don't even think
you have a chance
of escaping,
'cause it's over for you.
♪
After your friends
are disposed of,
the only thing
left for you
is a torturous death
at the hands of Takeda.
Here.
I think this is your
kodachi, Megumi.
You can choose
to live and endure pain,
or you can die with ease.
It's up to you.
♪
I'd like to avoid
any unnecessary fighting
and bloodshed,
so please step aside
and let us pass.
I have orders to defend this
passageway with my life.
(metal clang)
You hear that?
That guy's got
armored gloves
underneath those
leather ones he's wearing.
What's that posture
that he's in?
He's a Kenpo fighter.
♪
I don't wanna
waste any time here,
so excuse me for
not waiting for you.
I agree.
I'll try to make
your death quick
and painless as
possible, Battousai.
♪
(grunts)
He got him.
Backfist.
Kenshin!
(groans, grunts)
♪
Just what's going on here?
Kenshin, you nut,
why are you
getting hit by him?
Just what's the big deal?
What's happened
to your ability
to see punches
before they come anyway?
I'm moving enough to
dodge anyone else's punches,
I can see his punch
and backfist coming,
but as he finishes
his punches,
he's overextending his arm.
It's hard to dodge him.
You've gotta adjust.
(steams)
What's the trouble, Battousai?
From what I
heard about you,
I expected you to do better.
You're doing a great
imitation of a punching bag.
If you can't
beat my spell,
you don't stand a chance
against my boss, Aoshi.
(laughs)
What spell?
The minute you saw me,
you fell under
my powerful spell.
You didn't even realize
that it was happening,
but now I've got you!
♪
By now they
must be fighting.
Han'nya uses his arm
stretching spell so well,
if Battousai
doesn't see through it
and make moves
to compensate,
he has virtually
no chance of surviving.
So, it's a spell, huh?
The first step
to defeating him
must be breaking the spell,
then I'll have a chance
to control the outcome.
I wonder why he has
chosen that posture.
I don't get it.
It looks like a posture
of the seigen technique.
No, Yoshi.
It's shinken technique.
"Shin" is for believing,
and "ken" is for sword.
This is a truly
classic defense posture
that can usually
handle any change
in an opponent's attack.
Battousai,
the shinken posture.
That's strictly
a defensive move
from which it's almost
impossible to switch
to attack.
I can't believe
you've given up
this fight already.
So, the legendary Slasher
has gone into his shell.
You're not the master
they made you out to be.
You'll never get
the chance to save Megumi
because I plan on
finishing you now.
Your posture doesn't
stand a chance
against my spell!
(groans)
♪
(grunts)
About time!
It really worked!
(grunts)
How were you able to see
through Han'nya's spell
and break it, Kenshin?
I saw that the true
character of his spell
is the horizontal
striped tattoo
covering his arms.
The stripes?
I got it.
The horizontal
stripe on his arm
acts as an optical illusion
making things seem thicker
than they actually are.
That's why you were wrong
about his true distance
from you, Kenshin.
So, your shinken
defense posture
wasn't just to defend
against my attack.
It was just a ploy
to draw me in
so you could measure
the actual length of my arm.
Wow.
So, what you
were really doing
was using your sword
to act as a ruler!
I should've known
better than to take
you so lightly, Battousai.
(glass breaks)
I've been through
hell many times,
but you're the first one
to truly challenge me in
all the countless fights
that I've won.
(gasps)
Hmm.
Your reputation
as a famous slasher
precedes you
wherever you go,
but I've had a much
harder road proving
my fighting skills.
My pride and reputation
is on the line here.
And I will beat you!
Razor claws.
What kind of pride is
there in kidnapping women?
You're just a loser!
(groans)
(clink)
(grunting)
♪
Hah!
You think you're ready
to battle Aoshi, huh?
You haven't got a chance!
(grunts)
You've been wounded.
It's nothing.
We've gotta
save Megumi.
Let's go.
But wait!
Hmm.
I wonder just what kind
of man is this Aoshi?
He's controlled
the likes of Shikijô,
Beshimi, and Hyottoko.
He must be very powerful
to have controlled
such tough men.
I think we'll need
all the luck we can get.
Before we go in there,
shouldn't we make a plan?
I bet that they think
we've already been killed
by Han'nya.
Come on, guys.
Let's stop them.
(shivering)
Yeah, look at them all
shaking like a bunch of leaves.
(grunts)
Kenshin, Sano,
get upstairs
and find Megumi.
You two, handle these guys.
Yeah, get control down here
then come upstairs and help.
There's just the two of them
against all of us.
You shouldn't
underestimate
Kamiya Kasshin style.
It's time to show you why!
(grunting, fighting)
(doors open)
♪
I guess you're him,
mobster Aoshi.
♪
What concerns me
is that he doesn't
look imposing.
That means he's got
some hidden skills.
So, tell us where
are Takeda and Megumi?
If you really want me
to answer your question,
don't ask me
with your voice.
You should ask me instead
with your reversed-edge sword,
Battousai the Slasher.
And I swear, I'll
answer your question
with this.
You must believe
in very short answers,
'cause you won't have
a chance against Kenshin
with that little knife.
You've really
gotta be joking.
My only concern is
to fight Battousai.
And my advice to
you is you do well
to sit this one out.
Sit this one out?
I'm sorry, pal,
but I don't listen
to advice from
scum like you.
Now, let's get up
close and personal.
Sano, don't do it!
(shouting)
♪
He's strong,
but he's too impulsive.
♪
(grunts)
Whoa!
Sanosuke!
Wow, he's been knocked out.
Sano, knocked out
with just one punch?
I'm glad he finally
took my advice.
Now, it's time
to settle this matter.
So, shall we proceed?
A kodachi.
Yes, it's a little
smaller than a Samurai sword.
It's shorter so it
doesn't have the same power,
but it's lighter
and excellent for defense,
that's why it's known
as the sword that can
be used like a shield.
However, it's not exactly
an offensive weapon,
because it's almost
impossible to attack with.
He must be really good.
I can't imagine that he
concentrates on defense.
I'll let him attack
first and see.
Why are you just
standing there?
Are you just waiting?
Should I attack first?
Huh?
(shouting)
(swords clink)
♪
He's using the same
technique as Han'nya.
(punching)
♪
Come on, Kenshin.
So your fighting style
is to use your kodachi
as a wall of defense,
and while your
opponent is blocking you,
you attack using Kenpo,
just like Han'nya.
You catch on fast,
but here's something
you don't know.
I taught Han'nya
everything he knew.
What?
♪
As you know,
between a master
and his pupil,
there's a big difference
in the speed and power
of their fists.
He's really hurt.
Oh, Kenshin!
(stirs)
This might be real
trouble for all of us.
♪
It's unbelievable.
How does this guy possess
so much power anyway?
For what?
♪
(theme song)