♪
Since Sir Okubo's murder
by Shishio's henchmen,
a lot has happened.
Makoto Shishio met
a long-lost nemesis,
Aoshi Shinomori, the
head of the Oni gang
and asked him to
join his group.
But Aoshi refused and went
to Kyoto to kill Kenshin
While walking to Edo,
Kenshin encountered a
robbery in progress.
♪
I'd say you might
as well just give up
because there's no way
you'll escape my robbing you.
Stand and deliver.
Just be calm
and give me--
(boinging noise)
Sorry, but I have no money.
(audible sigh)
With the kind of rags
this guy is wearing,
I believe it.
So what happened, did
your wife leave you?
Huh, I've never
been married!
Well, I'm not surprised.
Ooh, nice sword.
I'll let you live but you
must hand over your sword.
But this is
all I've got!
A sword like that
must be worth a lot,
you know, they've become
quite rare since the decree
made them illegal, so
hand it over, poor boy!
Huh?
(shouting)
♪
I got ya!
Oh, was that a punch?
I can't believe
you weren't broken
completely in two by
my attack, what gives?
Well, you're not the
best at using leverage,
and you don't have
much body weight
so it just
wasn't effective.
(growling)
Well, I was
just warming up.
That was just a
suck-you-in punch, boy.
(shouting)
♪
Oh!
(shrieking)
(grunting)
Stop trying to dodge my
power, you gutless guy!
Uh, sorry, I was
trained that way.
(grunting)
(yelling)
Oh.
(grunting)
Whoo, I think
you dropped this,
is this your money?
Huh, oh.
Yes, it is!
Now you will die!
You fool, no one
can survive Hikumo.
(screaming)
♪
Ahh!
That's my cloak!
Uh oh, now I've
really done it.
Give me that back now.
I saw you take
this bag of money
from those men
you knocked out,
and it's only right that it
should be returned to them
because it's theirs.
You're wrong,
now give it here!
They stole it
from someone else
so I earned it, now you
got the whole story, do you?
Now here's your choice,
you're either gonna
give me the money
or give me your sword
so what ya gonna do?
All right.
That's more like it.
I hope the
blade's not rusted.
Oh, what are you doing
with a reverse-edged sword?
Nobody wants a reverse-edged
sword, it's not worth a yen,
but it's the only thing
in the world I cherish
so why don't you just
give it back to me?
Hmm.
Well, you wrecked
my favorite cloak
so I guess it's only fair
I get to keep your sword.
Ah, but I've had
that sword for years!
Please!
Well, I had
this for years
and, thanks to you,
it's worthless.
Here you go!
Okay, I've been holding
out on you, here,
you can have all my money,
just give me back my sword!
Really, ha!
Great!
Aw, there's not enough here
to even pay attention.
Well, it's become obvious to
me that you and these hoods
are not the rightful owners
of this bag of money.
So what?
So, I'm gonna
return this
to whoever it
really belongs to.
Hey, hey, hey, wait up!
Let's talk this over.
(grunting)
She'll pay for this.
(dog barking)
The Odawara Inn
and Money Exchange.
Well then, this
must be the place.
It's locked.
Pretty quiet
around here,
they don't even
seem to realize
they've been robbed.
They'll be pleased that
we returned this to them.
(grunting)
So am I supposed to be
impressed or something?
I can tell
by that move
you're a thief as
well, Mister Honesty.
Whatever you are,
get ready, I'm coming!
(yelling)
Whoa!
(grunting)
Ha!
From the way she
made that jump,
I'd say she studied
Kenpo and Tang Soo Do.
She must have had some
excellent senseis
to do that as
well as she did.
And the way
she's dressed,
her tight little body
is making my blood boil.
Don't give
yourself eye strain.
Oh.
I can't believe this,
these people are loaded.
Well, it's certainly easy
to see why they got robbed.
They leave their
safe wide open.
There, well, now that
that's taken care of,
I guess I can--huh?
I've hit the jackpot.
Oh!
I know being in here
must be very tempting
for a person like you, but
you just have to resist.
But how's a poor
girl like me
gonna get all the way
to Edo without money?
-Uh, Edo?
-Yeah, Edo,
what's the big deal?
♪
(water lapping)
That's interesting, I'm
headed for Edo myself.
So, I guess your home
is in Edo, right?
Right, I had to go to Kyoto
to check something out,
but, unfortunately,
I've run out of money
on the way back home.
Why would a girl like you
want to go to Kyoto alone?
I'm just curious.
Well, I'll tell you, I
was looking for someone
who was a very important
person in my life.
I was orphaned as a baby
and this person took
me under his wing.
He raised me as if I
was his own daughter.
This was a long time ago,
just after the Tokugawa Era.
We lived in
a large group.
They were all very kind.
So the reason you went
to Kyoto was to look
for your stepfather?
Yes, when I was 11, we
were traveling through Edo
and he decided
to leave me there.
Are you telling me
he deserted you?
No, he left me in
the care of an old man
because the police
were chasing him.
He was the best,
and I know someday
I'll find him.
Until we're reunited, I'll
keep searching for him,
but I gotta go back
home to earn more money.
♪
So I was in Kyoto
trying to find him.
But I went broke before
I could locate him.
I'm sure that if
you stick to it,
you'll find him someday,
Miss--what's your name?
Misao.
My name is Misao Makimachi.
But it's okay if
you call me Misao.
Ms. Misao, I know
you need money,
but I'm sure you know
just how wrong it is
to steal it from others.
You don't have
the slightest idea
what it's like to have
to eat grass for weeks
because you don't have
any money to eat real food.
When you've tried
a steady diet
of caterpillars,
cockroaches, frogs...
Why don't you use
the money I gave you
to write your old
man friend in Edo...
What a good idea!
(thudding)
(audible sigh)
You know those guys
you knocked out
are probably angry.
I wouldn't be
a bit surprised
if they're out right
now looking for you
and that bag of loot
you took from them.
They could be yakuza.
And no matter
who they are,
you better leave town
before they find you--
There's that bitch!
-Hey!
-Let's get her!
Yeah!
Now you've had it!
No one gets away with
what you tried to do to us!
Give us your money!
♪
And even then,
we're gonna kill ya!
(laughing)
Well, here goes nothing.
We're completely surrounded.
I'm sorry that I
put you in this jam,
but now I could
really use your help.
Get 'em, boys!
♪
All right, I'll help.
Listen, I'll give
all of you one chance
to leave us alone.
Huh?
(shouting)
♪
I'd say, "You two
haven't got a chance."
It's all over for you.
♪
(gasping)
You guys stole that loot
and this girl robbed you.
I'd say all of you
made a big mistake.
So here's what
you should do.
All of you should
give this up
and let's just
call things even.
(grumbling)
(cracking)
(yelling)
My--oh!
(water lapping)
You know, I'm not sure
you're much of a fighter,
but your wit
certainly served us
well on that bridge.
Well, years ago, I was in
many battles on bridges.
What I just did was pretty
much second nature to me.
You have to know
that kind of a bridge.
it's supported
and what's stressed when
it's got weight on it.
When all those
men got closer,
it was easy to cut it,
making it collapse.
Hmm.
The man who raised me
had a group of guys
around him that
were amazing.
They were great
martial artists.
So let's hear
all about 'em.
He and his men
guarded Edo Castle
during the disturbance
at the end of
the Tokugawa Era.
♪
Ah.
His name's Aoshi Shinomori.
I wonder just where
he and his Oni gang
are tonight under
the full moon.
♪
Shinomori, Aoshi?
Huh?
(wind howling)
(water lapping)
What do you know
about Aoshi?
So do you know him?
Tell me, where are they?
Is he doing well?
Just when is the last
time you saw Aoshi anyway?
(giggling)
You must be old friends.
♪
Kyoto, Battousai,
I'll have my revenge.
(birds chirping)
So you haven't exactly
been very talkative
since I brought up Aoshi.
I have to think from your
silence that deep down,
you're jealous of Aoshi
and the fighting skills
of his Oni gang, so don't be
a spoilsport about this.
I got it, someone in his
gang must have given you
an old-fashioned
butt whipping.
It was probably Han'nya,
he's great at Kenpo
and really kicking
guys' butts.
Hey!
Where you going, Mr. Redhead
Fred Rag-Picker Jones,
Mr. The Martial Artist
Formerly Known As
Mr. X Marks The
Scar On My Face!
In case you're
interested, Misao,
my real name is
Kenshin Himura.
If you could, please
call me by my real name.
So you mean if I call
you by your real name,
you might fill me in
on my long-lost friends?
Calling by my real name
should have nothing to do
with that other issue.
Oh, Kenshin.
Ya!
I guess this is
another issue, too!
(moaning)
All right, I want
you to cut the crap
and spill your guts!
Oh, stop running away!
I can't give
up on this.
I really feel that
he knows something.
This is the first time
in all of my searching
that I've met someone who
might actually know Aoshi.
(birds chirping)
(clanging)
Hmm?
Kenshin, we've got
to get under a tree,
it's gonna rain!
(thundering)
(raining)
It's a good thing
the Oni gang taught me
how to read weather.
Just think, we'll be
in Edo in one more day.
Boy, looks like rain.
Yeah.
This is a big storm,
I wonder if Kenshin's getting
soaked by this rainstorm.
I remember a time when
we were all together
and got stuck in a
thunderous rainstorm.
♪
Kori, hurry up, will ya?
Gosh, the rain's just
really coming down,
it's a real downpour.
It's like a flash flood.
My new kimono is
completely soaked.
It'll be all right.
♪
(audible sigh)
Oh, Kenshin.
So you feel like
talking, Kenshin?
Sure.
Well, we don't have
to talk about Aoshi
if you don't
want to, okay?
Aoshi.
But as a dad, he did a
fine job of raising me.
I feel like he was
the greatest dad
a girl could ever have.
You know Aoshi
was so smart,
he was the head
of the Oni gang
when he was just 15.
And under his leadership,
we all flourished.
He always had a strong
sense of responsibility.
And even though he rarely
showed his true feelings,
he was always very
caring towards me.
I lived with him
for nine years
and even I never
saw him smile
except for just one time.
I'll never forget it,
he captured someone
that tried to betray him.
He had the
man executed.
But I bet when
he sees me again
after all these years,
he'll have a big smile
on his face for me!
Hey, where the
hell are you going?
The rain stopped
so I'm off to Edo.
Then wait for me!
(birds chirping)
♪
Maybe I should tell
her about what happened
to Aoshi and his Oni gang.
Then again, the news
would probably crush her.
After all, we want to
see our dreams fulfilled.
Maybe it's better to
let her keep her dream
of seeing him again.
On the other hand,
she has such a
distorted view of Aoshi.
She actually
thinks he was nice.
Maybe to her he was.
Besides, Aoshi and his
gang are all dead now.
What's the point in
destroying her image
of a man who
cared for her?
She's not gonna stop
asking about it though.
I think the best
way to handle this
is to lose her.
Hey!
Wait up!
So you think you
can escape from me.
Well, not only did I
grow up in the Oni gang,
but the trained me in
the art of stalking
and now you're my prey,
so you can run,
but you can't hide.
So come out, crawl out
wherever you are, Kenshin.
Chicken!
(boinging)
(growling)
(grunting)
(panting)
♪
She wasn't kidding.
Miss Misao runs
as fast as a deer,
I can't lose her.
She must really
want some answers
about what
happened to Aoshi.
Hey!
Damn, I'm having
a hell of a time
keeping up
with this guy.
I gotta stay with him.
This Kenshin is
something else.
I wonder if he and Aoshi
ever fought each other,
and, if so, what happened?
I guess--whoa!
Oh!
All right, where
the hell'd you go?
Our little game of
cat and mouse is over.
I'll be the one who says
if and when we're through
with each other.
Now you're in trouble!
(grunting)
(gasping)
Oh.
♪
You have got
to be kidding.
There is no way he
could've jumped this canyon.
Is there?
Well, I've got
to do something.
I can't let a man with so
many answers just get away.
Well, you can't
get away from me!
(whooshing)
(exploding)
Huh?
He created air pressure
that stopped my hikimu
from even reaching him.
You need to
go back home.
Leave me alone and
get on with your life.
(gasping)
♪
I wish I could tell you
something about Aoshi
but the truth is,
I never met the man.
I had just heard
stories about him.
I'm sorry if I
got your hopes up.
But you shouldn't feel
bad about him leaving you.
He probably loved
you very much
and didn't want to
see you get hurt.
That's why he left
you with the old man,
he knew the life
of a gangster.
It's a sad life that
almost always ends
in an early
death or prison.
♪
I know what it's like
having a burning emptiness
in your heart that can only
be put out by a loved one.
But sometimes we
have no choice
but to live
without them.
♪
I wish you well.
I never give up.
(shouting)
♪
You really think you
can get off that easy?
Well, I've got news
for you, Kenshin.
The Oni gang
never quits.
(grunting)
No!
Don't try it, Misao!
How can you even think
I could live with myself
the rest of my life
if I didn't at
least try to do it?
Huh?
(shouting)
♪
(yelling)
(screaming)
♪
(shouting)
(exploding)
Now I understand.
Kenshin must've
known Aoshi.
He probably became a
part of the Oni gang
after they left
me in Kyoto.
He must know
where they are.
Now I can finally relax
knowing all my years
of emptiness will
soon come to an end.
♪
Oh my!
What happened,
was I knocked out?
Uh huh.
Misao, I want
you to promise
that's the last time you'll
ever do anything that crazy.
I promise.
I just couldn't
stand the thought
of not knowing the
truth about Aoshi.
And wherever
you're going,
I'm going to
go with you.
I just want you to
know ahead of time,
there are some pretty vicious
people that are after me.
You might be
risking your life
just traveling with me.
But if you're willing
to accept that risk,
I'd consider it an honor
to have your company.
Okay, Kenshin,
you've got a deal.
I'm not afraid!
And on the way to Edo,
you can tell me all about
what really happened
between you and Aoshi.
Ugh, don't you
ever give up?
No way!
♪