♪
Human beings
going to the moon?
It'll happen one day.
-Mark my words, it will.
-Oh, I ate too much.
I though you were
going to be sick.
Men will walk on the moon.
What do you mean,
men on the moon?
I mean it will be a fact,
I am quite serious.
You're quite delirious.
Look, there
are people overseas
who have been
studying the idea.
They will be constructing
a large cannon
and actually shooting
men at the moon.
♪
Of course, the mathematics
involved in the calculations
are extraordinarily complex.
Why don't you calculate
something useful,
like how to make
food out of air?
Huh?
Or maybe how to make
money grow on trees.
(laughs)
Huh?
(sigh)
♪
Was that really true
what you were telling them?
(gasp)
Kenshin, what are
you talking about?
Not even little kids
believe a fairy tale like that.
But I tell you
it is not a fairy tale,
nothing like that.
When science is much more
advanced than now,
we'll definitely
be going to the moon.
I really envy the first
people who go up there.
♪
Thanks for being so polite.
Most people just laugh
at me and walk away.
Hey, Daigoro, time to leave.
I'm coming right away, sensei.
Well, uh, goodbye.
Now that young man's strange.
I think going to the moon
is a romantic idea.
You are kidding, right?
Sano, you've got no
romance in your soul.
He forgot his books.
He's not too organized.
I'll just take
them over to him.
Whoa!
(footsteps)
What's wrong, sensei?
Oh, oh, sensei!
♪
Hey, you forgot
your--what the...?
Hey, what's this?
It's getting to the point
where decent people
can't even walk in the
streets of Tokyo anymore.
♪
Move in!
(punching)
♪
Kori, cover those two there.
(punching)
♪
Help, help, sensei!
Hey, Daigoro,
watch and learn.
Ahh!
♪
Hey, are you two all right?
Yes, thanks to you.
That was our pleasure.
I feel much safer with
her than I do with you.
Whoa!
Huh?
♪
(sword unsheathing)
Sensei.
It's Tetsuma!
You know, a long
time ago I decided
that attacking my sensei
is just like attacking me.
But I fight back.
Get out of here, now!
They always seem to run away
just when it starts
to get interesting.
Sensei, are you sure
you're all right?
Yes, I'm just fine,
because of these
good-hearted people here.
I'm very grateful,
thank you, all.
No thanks necessary,
it was good exercise.
Right?
You're welcome.
Sensei Kaishu,
I've told you before,
you have to be more
careful when you go out.
Yes, you're right.
If anything
happened to you now--
I understand.
I'll take you home now.
Daigoro, listen,
if you are with the sensei,
you are supposed to provide
him with protection.
Um, um, I really am sorry.
Tetsuma's right.
At this point,
I think you're more
trouble than you're worth.
But, sensei!
♪
If you're ever going to
grow up to lead this country,
you'd better learn
to take care of yourself
in addition to others.
I really don't need
a pupil like you.
Hey, that's a
rotten thing to say.
You can't just
drop him like that.
You'll do well
to stay out of this.
It's none of your business.
You don't really think
this boy has any future
if he just wastes
all of his time
dreaming instead of doing.
Well, with friends like that.
Sanosuke, I hate
to admit it,
but you're absolutely
right this time.
And that's why I'm
going to teach this boy
everything I possibly can.
He'll be a true swordsman
in the Kamiya Kasshin style.
I admire your determination,
but I think it's
a great waste of time.
♪
Daigoro, until you become
a decent swordsman,
don't bother
coming to my home.
But sensei.
Come on, Tetsuma.
Oh, by the way, young man,
what's your name?
Well, who are you?
Himura, Kenshin Himura.
And as for me,
the name's Katsu.
Kaishu Katsu.
♪
(crying)
That's just about enough!
He threw me out!
You've got to pull
yourself together
and start acting like a man.
If he had that
kind of self control
I bet he
wouldn't have been
kicked out in
the first place.
It's just so mean.
I don't care how great
a teacher he is,
you've got to have some
responsibility
for your students.
Speaking of which,
I find it incredibly
hard to believe
that Mr. Katsu can really be
as cold-hearted as all that.
Kaishu Katsu was a heavy
supporter of the Shogun,
able to avoid
bloodshed many times.
Hey, Kenshin, weren't his
plans what helped to save
Edo from the Satsuma
army's attack?
Yes.
Even his fiercest enemies
admired and respected him
for his diplomatic abilities.
When our envoy went
to the United States,
Katsu was right
there with him.
He's a master
of political balance.
Well, he lost his balance
when he threw Daigoro
into the street.
But we're gonna train him
and make him strong, right?
Well, I don't know.
How about a little
positive attitude?
You can only
accomplish something
if you think you can do it.
Great idea!
If I can learn to
take care of myself,
he'll have to
respect me again.
There, that's the spirit.
(distant dogs barking)
Ah, seito isu,
what is that?
Well, it's a
form of science.
It's a field
of great study
in most of
the Western countries.
We're behind the times,
and Sensu Katsu believes
this knowledge
can really be of great
help to our country.
-Hmm.
-What's the matter?
I just wish the sensei
could be as proud of me
as he is of Tetsuma.
♪
Tetsuma, isn't he
that stuck-up guy
with the weird
straight sword?
Yes, his sword is used for the
Western Kendo they call fencing.
When he went to England
to study at the university,
he learned to fence there too.
He's very good at it.
And with his education,
he's already promised
a high government office.
His future is all set.
♪
(sigh)
I don't think I'll
ever do that well.
But you know a lot more
about this seito isu
thing, don't you?
I suppose so, why?
Don't you see?
That means there's
something you're better at
than he is.
So, if you really study
this seito stuff,
does that mean you
can go to the moon?
Sure, why not.
Just look at this.
All right, listen carefully.
Now, you take
a man and a dog
and put them in this
giant cannon shell
and fire it at the moon.
Wow!
Yeah, yeah.
This is from a book by
a Frenchman named Jules Verne.
It's titled something like,
"A Trip To The Moon
and Back Again."
♪
Father, father!
What's all the noise?
It's too early for this.
Hmm.
In case you
didn't notice, father,
Daigoro didn't
come home last night.
Where did he go?
He will remain away until
he learns to use a sword.
It's not right for Daigoro
to learn sword fighting.
You're the one who said
his greatest strength
was his intellect.
And now you suddenly
decide it's all right
to abandon him in the streets,
defenseless and innocent?
Yes, well, whatever.
Shame on you.
I'm going to find Daigoro
and bring him home.
Itsuko.
I'm serious, father.
Ah, well so am I.
If you're not
going to obey me,
you don't have to
come back either.
Hmm.
♪
He doesn't even comprehend
the first thing about people.
♪
Good morning, Itsuko.
Yes, morning.
♪
Hey, wait a minute.
Where are you going?
I told father
I'm going to find Daigoro
and bring him home myself.
Tetsuma, I'm sorry.
What are you
doing here so early?
I'm a little bit
worried about yesterday.
I came to see
how the sensei is.
As usual, stubborn
and pig-headed.
I see.
I have to go find Daigoro.
Then, let me show
you just where he is.
I know the dojo where
he's doing his training
and I'd be happy to take you.
Thanks so much.
You're very thoughtful.
(carriage wheels rumbling)
(splashing)
-Now we have balance.
-(yawning)
Daigoro, starting today,
you are a student
of Kendo Kamiya Kasshin.
Starting today,
you're the junior
pupil around here.
We're gonna have fun now.
(coughing)
Thanks so much.
So why don't you start
by cleaning up the dojo?
(smack)
Ooh, ooh, oooh.
I don't understand why I
still have to do this now!
Don't give me
any complaints, Yoshi,
it's an important
part of your training.
Maybe he really
can learn something.
Stranger things have happened,
and with Kori training him,
well, he could
surprise everyone.
♪
Aaah!
(crashing)
(neighing)
Huh, whoa.
This way.
Wha--Lady Itsuko.
Huh?
I'm glad that
you look so well.
Itsuko has come
to take Daigoro
back to Sensei
Katsu's house.
What, you mean
that stubborn old man
came to his senses?
We really don't
have to worry about
what father
thinks right now.
Uh-oh.
Yes, now come on.
Aahh, hey, I said no.
Daigoro?
I think Sensei Katsu
has good reasons
for me to learn the sword.
I want to do it.
Everyone has
different strengths.
Swords don't suit you.
But studying does.
You're very good at it.
Hmm.
Listen, I'll talk
to my father.
I won't go back.
Look, Daigoro.
You look, Itsuko.
Daigoro is our student,
you just can't take him.
He's here with us
because he wants to be here
and that's that.
But he's our student,
our scholar.
And your blockhead father
threw him out of the dojo,
that was a bad
decision that he made.
Why don't you
just stay out of it?
Calm down, both of you!
You stay out of this,
Yoshi, or else!
If he truly wants
to stay, let him stay.
After all,
the decision is his.
But, Tetsuma.
As your father's
student for many years,
I think I understand.
Kaishu Katsu does nothing
without a good reason.
In this particular situation,
his thinking is obvious.
Daigoro has neither
the spirit nor the ability
your father requires.
What did you say?
It's better for him
if his skills
are never tested.
For him, to cross
blades in this dojo--
I'm sorry, but I don't think
Daigoro will gain anything
from taking weapons
training here.
Then again, maybe it's
a perfect place for him.
No pressure
to achieve anything,
a woman for his teacher.
(growling)
♪
I think that maybe you
need an introduction
to the power
of Kamiya Kasshin.
Prepare yourself.
I learned my style
from masters of the blade.
It's called fencing
and it was taught
to me in the West.
Tetsuma, don't do this.
Not to worry, Itsuko,
I'm just going to
show her what it's like
when a girl plays along
with the big boys.
No, Tetsuma.
Step aside, please.
♪
Now prepare yourself.
It looks like
he knows his blade.
I'll never understand
why you people
are still using sticks
in this day and age.
See what a stick can do!
Aaahh!
(gasping)
Ughhhh.
Please don't fight
'cause someone
might really get hurt.
I'm so sorry, Kenshin.
Uhh.
I have some important
business to take care of.
Look, Itsuko,
I have to leave now,
so please promise
me you'll be careful
on your way home.
(footsteps)
I'm quite
serious about this.
I'm going to stay and
study with Sensei Kori.
Please tell Sensei Katsu.
I understand.
If that's really
your decision,
then I won't say
anything more to my father.
But I want you to know,
I'll be staying here too.
Wait a minute,
you'll be doing what?
I'll be staying right here
until Daigoro
is sufficiently trained
to satisfy my father.
(gong ringing)
(crow cawing)
♪
What do you think
you're doing, Itsuko?
What do you mean?
I'm cooking dinner
for the dojo.
But you can't do that?
I've just got
to do something.
♪
And I happen to be
very good at cooking.
Is that all right?
Well, you see,
it's like this--
Hey, it's good!
What, it tastes good?
Ooh!
♪
You're right, Yoshi,
it's really good!
(gulping)
Better than Kori's!
What do you mean
better than mine?
Dirt is better
than your cooking.
You must be getting tired.
I had no idea what a task
master Sensei Kori can be.
(laughing)
Yes, she even finds work
for me if I don't hide.
By the way,
I'm really impressed
by your dedication of study.
Sometimes I think
that's my only strength.
♪
You know, Kenshin,
I can't help thinking
that a guy like Tetsuma
is absolutely perfect
for someone like Lady Itsuko.
♪
No, I don't think I agree.
(sigh)
Well, I know the truth.
I've seen people like
Tetsuma all my life.
They're the ones
who never seem to lose.
Doesn't seem fair,
but that's real life.
But Itsuko
disobeyed her father,
left her home,
and traveled here
because she was
worried about you.
She really cares for you.
(gasp)
♪
Everyone, dinner is ready.
Thank you, we'll
be right there.
Itsuko, that was great.
Where are you going,
you got an after
dinner appointment?
I need to tell Kaishu Katsu
where his daughter is.
Going to my father?
Kenshin, please
don't do that.
I don't think
he's even worried.
-More please!
-Me too!
Huh?
(crickets chirping)
(water gurgling)
Oh, it's you.
Sorry to drop by
without notice, sensei.
Not to worry.
I'm the only one here
in this big
empty house, anyway.
I just came by
to let you know
that your daughter
is all right
and she's staying at
the Kamiya dojo with Daigoro.
Thank you for taking
care of them both.
She's such a rebel.
I hope she's not
giving you any trouble.
Not at all.
She's a wonderful cook
and a warm spirit.
It's good to have her there.
Good news.
Always pleasant to hear.
(water gurgling)
♪
It's so very quiet.
Makes me think of things
I never got to do.
Ever think of those things?
Sure I do.
You know, every once in
a while, everyone does.
In the old days,
I could never imagine having
an evening visit like this.
I was quite famous, you know.
A lot of men
wanted to kill me.
And fortunately
for me, they missed.
♪
There was such
fire in our hearts,
everyone staking his
life for his beliefs.
Bring down the Shogun.
Save the Shogun.
Hope in the country.
Keep the foreigners out.
Ah, we lived
one day at a time.
Now I look to the future.
My time, my kind, are over.
It's up to
the younger generation
to fix our mistakes.
Or to make their own.
Mr. Katsu.
Sorry if I tend
to ramble, young man.
I'm just an
old man reminiscing.
You should just
forget about it.
Mr. Katsu, I don't
think you really believe
your work is quite done.
Well, you're wrong.
Hmm.
Please take care of my Itsuko,
and Daigoro as well.
Wont you, Mr. Battousai?
♪
Sorry, my mistake,
you're called Kenshin
Himura these days.
♪
That's right.
And don't worry,
I will take care of them.
Mmm.
♪
What is Kaishu
Katsu working on?
What's his plan?
And is he pushing
his daughter and student
out of danger, or into it?
(footsteps running)
♪
You might as well just
come on out and say hello.
♪
Didn't I see you yesterday?
Don't get involved.
You stay away
from Kaishu Katsu.
♪