♪
Mr. Shishio, we've received word
that Saito, Kenshin Himura,
and Sanosuke Sagara are
on their way here now.
Good, summon the Juppongatana.
Finally.
We should've dealt
with those troublemakers
a long time ago.
Pardon me, sir, I'd like
to suggest a strategy
which would ensure
our total victory.
Strategy.
Of course, why not?
Exactly what is this
strategy you'd like to suggest?
Tell us, Hoji.
What I have in mind
is not just getting rid
of those three men,
but an absolute complete
and total victory.
Sounds interesting so far.
-Go on.
-Thank you, sir.
In the upcoming battle,
those three men
will have to fight
our entire group.
Ten opponents in all!
So the odds are
greatly in our favor.
I would say that's
putting it mildly.
What are you getting at,
Hoji, what is your point?
My point is that no
matter how much the odds
are in our favor,
we must eliminate even the
slightest chance of defeat
by demoralizing our enemies
before the battle begins!
I suggest we keep only
the three strongest fighters
of the Juppongatana here
while the rest of the
group obliterates Aoiya.
The only ones left alive
will be the ones we
choose as messengers
to bring the news to
Himura and the others
that their friends
and supporters
have been destroyed.
Good idea.
This strategy would also serve
to get rid of the
troublesome Oni gang members
and those who are loyal to them.
For years, they supported
Himura in any way they could,
such as spying on a group and
giving him vital information.
It was a mistake not to have
taken care of them sooner.
That's right, but a
sneak attack's not right!
Only one thing matters now,
and that's for Mr. Shishio
to gain control of
the entire country
and nothing less will do.
When you're playing
for stakes this high,
there's no right or wrong.
We have to make the best
of this opportunity!
Results are all that matter,
and if a sneak attack on Aoiya
will increase our
chance of winning,
that's what we should do!
I see.
Just one question.
How can I trust anyone
who suggests a strategy
so dishonorable?
Huh?
I told Himura that I was
challenging him to a duel,
an honorable battle
between two worthy opponents,
and I will not break my word!
And it will be a
fight to the death!
Those are the
conditions we agreed upon,
and being a man of my word,
that's how it's going to be!
Understood?
The three men who
are on their way here
are three of the finest
fighters Japan has ever seen.
So even against ten to one odds,
they're bound to kill
a few of our men.
Now that the Rengoku
has been destroyed,
the only asset we
have is Juppongatana.
So we must do
everything in our power
to protect it.
I swore an oath that I
would do anything I could
to lead you to your
goal of total victory!
To help you become
the most powerful leader
since Ieyasu Tokugawa.
We can no longer worry
about what is right!
Victory is the only thing
that matters right now!
Failure is unthinkable!
The stakes are too high.
You know I'm right!
We have to do whatever's
necessary to gain control!
You understand?
By foul means or fair,
any act is justified
as long as we win!
You may hate me for saying it,
but that's the way
it has to be, sir.
You've convinced me that
you want me to win, Hoji,
I appreciate that.
Sojiro, summon the Juppongatana!
Yes, sir.
I want the entire group
assembled in ten minutes!
The three swordsmen
are on their way
and will be here shortly,
but before the duel begins,
I want to explain what
happened to the Rengoku.
We were wondering about
that and another thing.
We were supposed
to set fire to Edo,
but they were ready,
and we weren't able
to carry out the job.
Yes!
You know it was almost like
they knew what our plan was!
Why is that?
Unavoidable, I'm afraid.
Edo is going to be
burned the same way
the Tokugawans burned
Yeido over 250 years ago
with the guns of the Rengoku
causing most of the destruction.
Unfortunately the plan
failed due to the negligence
of one of my top advisors!
♪
I am right, aren't I, Hoji?
(whimpering)
I admit it!
It's my fault!
I beg your forgiveness!
Oh, great!
I thought we were gonna have
to waste a whole lot of time
figuring out who set us up!
But now we don't have to
worry about it anymore!
We can just kill Hoji!
But was it him alone,
or was he following
someone's orders?
Hoji.
(gasping)
Tell us the truth.
What--what do you mean?
Lying to me won't work.
Eyes of the heart
always know the truth.
If you were working with anyone,
tell us now or you're
going to suffer.
No!
(screaming and crying)
Oh, come now, Hoji,
tell us the truth.
♪
I am telling the truth!
I swear to you on
all that is holy
that it was my negligence
that led to this disaster!
But I am still
your loyal servant,
and I will prove it!
Prove it with blood!
(groaning)
Shishio, I beg your forgiveness.
My orders are as follows:
Sojiro, Usui, Anji--you three
will stay here and fight!
The rest of you
will attack Aoiya.
Kill them all,
bring me their heads!
All their heads?
This oughta be fun!
But why send all of us?
I could handle this myself!
Hmm.
(door creaking and shutting)
All right, Hoji, you
asked me for my forgiveness
so I forgive you.
You've convinced
me of your loyalty
and will therefore continue
to be my chief advisor.
Together we'll
conquer all of Japan!
Sir.
This is it, we're here.
This is the Rukutsurane
shrine, Shishio's hideout.
Let's show Shishio and his
gang they're not so tough.
(footsteps)
Huh?
Welcome, Yumi
Komagata is my name.
Mr. Shishio asked
me to greet you
and to take you to him.
Our defenses are impenetrable
to anyone who doesn't
know the way through,
so I will be your guide.
Probably sent a woman so
we'd let our guard down.
Does he really think
that we're that stupid?
Not quite, he only thinks
that you're that stupid,
and he's absolutely right.
Stick to fighting, Sano.
We'll do the
thinking, all right?
Follow me, please.
Whoa, this isn't just a maze,
it's a huge
underground labyrinth!
One wrong turn and you'd
never find your way out!
I've got to admit,
Shishio certainly does know
how to protect himself.
(water tinkling)
Allow me to explain the rules.
Each of you will fight
one member of the
Juppongatana in single combat.
While that duel is going on,
the other two may watch,
but are not allowed
to interfere.
Do you accept these conditions?
Yeah, we accept.
Whatever you say, lady.
Now, come on, can
we get on with it?
I'd just as soon beat
all of them at once,
but if Shishio
prefers it this way,
I'll go along with it.
Battousai, you agree?
I agree, but there's
one more condition
that I will have to insist on.
That these duels
are not to the death.
When one fighter is
clearly the winner,
the other is allowed to concede.
I'll meet any
opponent in combat,
but I won't stand
for any killing.
Is that understood?
Yes, of course!
I understand.
Shishio, I don't mean to meddle,
but isn't it somewhat dangerous
allowing Sanosuke Sagara
to fight against Anji?
Anji was his teacher!
He taught him the
extreme fist technique,
and you know how
strong the bond can be
between teacher and student.
Anji may feel sympathy
for his former pupil,
and he won't be
able to kill him.
Anji may be called
"The Depraved Monk,"
but he's a monk nonetheless
and has more compassion
than the rest of the
Juppongatana put together!
But his rage far
surpasses his compassion!
♪
I have no doubt
that Anji will destroy
whomever is unlucky
enough to face him.
Waiting for the fun to start?
Single combat's enjoyable,
but not nearly as
exciting as the death cries
of innocent women and children.
Exactly what I
was thinking, Usui.
(chuckling)
How about it, Anji,
let's join forces.
Together we'd be unstoppable.
We'll get rid of Shishio and
split his kingdom between us.
Well, are you with me?
You're wasting my time, Usui.
Ha!
Self-righteous prig.
♪
Whoever's fighting
first, go right in.
♪
(gasping)
Why, it's Anji.
What's up, Sano?
Do you know this guy?
Anji, the Depraved Monk.
The one who taught me
the extreme fist technique.
Huh?
Anji's the first one
to fight from our group.
You must decide now
which of you will face him.
♪
(doors creaking)
Anji, the Depraved Monk,
who lost his way and
joined the Juppongatana.
♪
The question is, can the
student teach the teacher?
♪
He's one of Shishio's
most powerful fighters,
but what's strange
is that he's the one
who saved Misao's life.
I sense something
extraordinary about him--
a combination of focused
power and intensity
that makes him a
dangerous opponent.
Sano will have to be at
his very best to beat him.
I hoped I'd see you again, Anji,
but I didn't expect
to see you here.
I must say, I'm a
little surprised by this.
And I'm surprised to
see you here as well.
It's hard for me to believe
that everything
that you talked about,
all that stuff you told me about
hating the Meiji government,
was just a pack of lies.
I'm very disappointed
that you lied to me.
How dare you say that to me?
You who spouted
all that nonsense
about saving the people of Japan
and then went to
work for a murderer!
Where's your salvation now?
It's now the responsibility
of those who belong
to the Juppongatana.
It's what?
You think salvation means
to rescue the downtrodden
from pain and misery.
To alleviate the
torment and suffering
so pervasive in our society.
I used to feel the same way,
until I realized that
the problem is our society.
♪
Our country's in the iron
grip of inhuman monsters
not worthy of being saved.
The heartless minions
of the Meiji government
who care only for
their own welfare,
rather than that of the people.
This is how the
real world works.
A world in which these
beasts in human form
have abandoned those
who depend on them
and have taken away the future
of those whose hearts are pure,
but now, finally, those animals
are going to get
what they deserve.
That's why I became one
of Shishio's followers,
why I became a member
of the Juppongatana,
and why I am now
known as Fudo Myoo,
the Fist of Fury.
My goal is still the same--
the salvation of our
country and its people.
But only by destroying
that which is
and starting again
with a clean slate
can our people be reborn
into a state of grace
deserving of salvation.
♪
Now do you truly
understand, Sano?
Yeah, sure I understand.
You're so concerned
about the people
that you wanna be the one
to tell them what to do,
but I'm afraid I don't agree.
As a matter of fact,
I think you're a total nutcase!
He used that technique when
we attacked the Rengoku.
The extreme fist move.
That's the technique he's
been trying to perfect.
You taught me well, Anji,
and now I've become an
expert at focusing the force
of Futae No Kiwami.
When I was travelling
between Shimotsua and Edo,
I practiced constantly
by breaking hundreds
of rocks along the way.
You were the one who taught
me the extreme fist technique.
Now that I've perfected it,
somehow I don't think
it would be right
to use it against you.
Perfected it.
I don't think so!
The only things you learned
were the basics, Sano.
I'm the only one
who has perfected it.
I thought I was his equal,
but he's a whole lot better
than I thought he was.
Looks like Sanosuke
might be in trouble.
Sano!
(groaning)
I thought I could make you
understand why I'm doing this,
but it doesn't really
matter whether you do or not.
I won't allow you to get
in my way, understand?
How can I possibly defeat him?
He can use the Futae No Kiwami
technique with both hands,
both feet, his
knees, his elbows--
with any part of his
body, even his head!
And all I can do
is use my right hand.
So, want me to take your place?
No way!
I'm not through yet.
You still don't get it, do you?
You can't win.
I thought you were smart
enough to understand that.
Understanding isn't
his strong point.
Mind your own business!
Sano, focus!
What'd you say?
Even with an attention
span as short as yours,
you can come up with a way
to win if you just think!
Thanks for the vote
of confidence, Kenshin.
Listen, a guy who
fights with one sword
has just as good
a chance of winning
as a guy who fights with two
as long as he knows
exactly how to use it!
I told you what the rules were.
No interference, remember?
You are forbidden
to help him fight.
I know, that's why
I put it into words.
You never said I
couldn't talk to him.
I know I can beat
you, Anji, yup.
If you think that,
you're a fool.
You don't have a chance, Sano.
Is that so?
We'll see!
(grunting)
Just as I thought.
He's trained so hard,
he's become muscle-bound.
His muscles have lost
some of their flexibility.
His fists are still
incredibly fast,
but the rest of his body can't
keep up with his hand speed.
He'll have to beat him
with a single blow.
It's the only way.
One hand is all I need!
(grunting)
See ya later!
Got him!
It can't be!
Amazing, Anji used
the reverse force
of a blow to his own body
to absorb the power
of Sano's punch.
As I told you before,
you've perfected nothing!
That was a close one.
I was lucky to avoid the
full force of his strike.
Sano!
Even though he
barely touched me,
the impact caused
a lot of damage.
His strength is incredible.
Sano.
I don't want to kill you.
Surrender, and
I'll let you live.
Let him live?
He can't mean that!
Of course he meant it, and
if Sano has any brains at all,
he'd know he has no choice
but to accept the offer,
but of course he
won't, the fool.
Anji, what do you
think you're doing?
Shishio gave
everyone instructions
to kill whoever they fought!
No, Shishio agreed
that it's up to me
to decide which of my
opponents live or die.
So that's it!
Now I understand!
Having the power to choose
who lives and who dies--
that's what it's all
about, isn't it, Anji?
That's what you're hooked on!
And Shishio's the one
who gave you that power,
so naturally you
worship him like a god!
How sad that you gave
up what you believed in
to worship a maniac.
You're wrong.
It's not like that at all.
I told Shishio at the very first
that I would join the
Juppongatana on one condition.
That I would decide which of
my opponents would live or die.
I joined him because he knows
the government
must be destroyed.
Shishio will create
a new government,
and if Shishio proves
unworthy, I'll destroy him, too.
(gasping)
So, the destruction doesn't
end until you're satisfied!
Is that it?
What if you're
never satisfied, Anji?
What then?
Do you just keep on
destroying everything
for the rest of your life,
tearing down what
the rest of society
has spent years trying to build?
You think that you know what
the real world is all about,
but you don't have a clue!
The real world is
made up of people!
People who care
about each other,
who work hard because
they believe in the future,
and believe that the future
is worth fighting for!
Believe me, Anji,
I don't like the Meiji
government any more than you do,
but I'll be damned if I'm
gonna let you or Shishio
or the Juppongatana
decide what's best
for the people of Japan!
I'm gonna win!
No problem!
If he really believes that,
I'd say he's a bit out
of touch with reality.
What do you think?
I remember the very first
time I ever fought Sano.
He used exactly the same words.
"I'm gonna win," he told me.
I hope he means it this time.
(yelling)
Seems to me that
Sano doesn't realize
that Anji can't be defeated
by a multi-strike attack.
One blow correctly
placed would finish him.
It's clear that Anji is
defending his left side,
so that Sano can't strike
with his right hand.
You worry too much.
Trust me, Saito,
sooner or later,
Sano's gonna find an opening.
Anji's going down.
Hey, how much longer
is this gonna take?
You should be done by now!
Come on, Anji, get it over with!
This is the first fight,
and we're already
behind schedule!
♪
Well, Sano.
Do you give up or do
I have to kill you?
I'd rather not, but I
will if you force me to.
Surrender and live
or fight and die.
What is your decision, Sano?
We've run out of time.
If we're gonna save him,
we've gotta do it now.
Are you really that
concerned about Sano?
What concerns me
is how his death
would affect your
ability to fight.
And I gotta quit smokin'.
Sano will win, so don't
worry about it, all right?
♪
Nice knowing you, Sano.
You should've surrendered
when you had the chance!
(grunting)
He did it!
♪
Namu Amida--
-Wait a second, Anji.
-Hmm!
I don't think you should
start chanting just yet.
You missed me, Anji!
I'm just too quick for ya!
♪
(grunting)
(breathing heavily)
Oh, no.
Shishio expected Anji to win.
All right, I admit you
were right, Sano won,
but if you ask me,
he just got lucky.
No.
Earlier when we first
started fighting,
I realized that he
was muscle-bound.
That, in comparison to
the rest of his body,
the muscles in his arms
and legs were overdeveloped,
which reduced his
quickness and flexibility.
And once I determined that,
I knew he was vulnerable
and that I could beat him.
(grunting)
It's not possible!
I can't believe it.
No one could have
survived that blow.
♪