♪
(singing in Japanese)
(insects chirping)
These fish are
just about done.
Let's eat, Kenshin!
Boy, they smell delicious!
Yum, let's dig in!
Hey, aren't you hungry?
Kenshin, what is it?
Hmm?
Ahh!
(yelling over each other)
Say, what's in that letter
you just got?
What is that, a letter?
It was sent from Kyoto.
So, Misao wrote another letter?
Another one?
She must really miss us,
'cause that's the second letter
she's sent us this month!
I guess she wants
us to write back
and be her fan club!
(ascending note)
Hmm...
But this letter's different
than the other one.
It's really grim.
She says a strange event
happened in Kyoto.
What does she mean
by strange?
This week,
a body was found
floating in the river here.
There was something strange
about how the body looked.
It was an important man
that worked for the shogunate.
How could a man of influence
end up this way?
There are many rumors,
but I only know what I saw
when they found the body.
His body had strange markings
carved into it.
There was an almost eerie symbol
carved deep in his back,
I didn't recognize it.
Maybe it's an occult symbol,
but no one's figured out
what its significance is.
I heard that this man
had received a letter
proclaiming that his death
was imminent and
absolutely unavoidable.
The question remains,
who did this and why?
Please, Aoshi,
name your price
and I will pay it.
I beg of you to help me!
I've heard of
your fighting prowess,
after all,
you're the former
head of the Oni gang.
And even though
I know you've retired
from being a slasher,
I know money can be
a powerful incentive.
Please defend me
with your deadly sword,
I beg of you!
Hey!
You just don't get it, do you?
All the money in the world
is not going to convince him.
He won't fight for anybody
unless he truly wants to.
Well, allow me to appeal
to your sense of honor.
Let me show you
the insolent threat
this coward dared to send me!
It says soon,
I'll be like
that man in the river,
floating my way to Hell.
And just how was that
note delivered to you?
That's not important.
What I need is for you
to protect me, Aoshi.
I just don't trust the police.
Obviously,
you've done something
to bring this on yourself.
No matter how you
try to convince me,
I will not take up
the sword for you.
You're on your own,
please leave.
♪
(insects chirping)
What do you think?
I can't read the writing,
it looks strange.
From the look of this,
it's some foreign language.
A foreign language?
Very interesting.
This is exactly the same kind
of writing as the note
they found on the dead man
in the river.
I can't be certain,
but in my opinion
this note is written in
either Dutch or Portuguese.
So, if it's in another language,
does that mean this assassin
is a foreigner?
I'm not sure.
Well, will you
help me find out?
I know you feel it
just like I do.
You and I both know
this is going to lead us
to some extraordinary event.
(trees rustling)
Aoshi, is Misao here?
I've got news for her.
What news?
She asked me to investigate
something for her, and I did.
It's about that
note she brought me.
So, just what was
it you found out?
The story began
200 years ago,
and it's come full circle.
His time for vengeance is now.
It began as a river of blood,
and soon the prophecy
will be fulfilled.
It has been written
that a child of God
will appear when
the day turns into darkness.
This symbol was used
by early Christians
at the start of
the Edo period,
and it's been banned ever since.
Misao, stay out of this.
(insects chirping)
(fire blazing)
Go on, phantom assassin,
let's see you go for it.
They may not get you,
but I promise you, I will.
Just show yourself
and you'll be finished.
Hmm?
Beat 20!
♪
Ugh...
(gulping)
♪
(panting)
(yelling in the distance)
Oh!
What the hell was that?
Attack!
(door breaking open)
Ugh...
(slam)
(slice)
(slicing)
Hmm.
Ugh.
Oh?
(gunshot)
(crash)
(gunshots)
(shells falling on floor)
(grunting)
(slice)
Ugh!
(thud)
(panting)
♪
No!
Ugh!
(thud)
♪
(panting)
(footsteps)
(whoosh)
Huh?
♪
Oh, ahh!
(whooshing)
Ugh.
Miss Kaoru!
(panting)
Shirojo,
what are you doing here?
♪
I've been running for days.
I must talk to Kenshin.
Oh, of course.
♪
Go to Kyoto?
Aoshi said you need to get there
as soon as possible.
♪
He sent me to accompany you.
Now please, pack quickly.
♪
Whoa!
We better get moving.
(footsteps)
♪
Let me make sure
I've got this straight.
Someone left this
threatening letter
for you yesterday,
and you translated it
and it says you're going to die?
Is that about right, Shiraishi?
Yes, that's all I know.
Wait a minute,
are you saying
you have no idea why
they want you dead?
No.
I don't know anything.
I have to know the truth here!
I cannot have you
holding out on me!
Tell me who wants you dead!
I swear,
if you tell me
this guys' name,
I'll take care of it
for ya!
But I can't do it
without your help.
Well?
Huh?
♪
Oh.
The answer is right in here.
This book was
written 200 years ago
by a Portuguese missionary
who sailed to Japan.
The characters
don't look familiar.
Can you translate what it says?
It explains what's happening
right now.
"When the river
of Christian blood stops,
it will be our time
for vengeance.
When the day dies
and turns into darkness,
a child of God will appear."
♪
(splash)
(insects chirping)
(sigh)
Huh?
(wheels rolling)
Master Okina,
there's a bunch
of people coming!
♪
(water splashing)
(chimes)
♪
It's good to see
both of you again.
We just got through
visiting Misao.
I understand that
she's still very weak.
It's unexplainable
what happened to her.
She was incapacitated,
and yet she had
no physical injuries.
Huh?
Then what happened to her?
She was shot with light.
It actually stopped
her heart for a moment.
I saw it happen,
she almost died.
There was this light.
As it shot out of his sword,
I was blinded by its brightness.
I've never seen
a light like that,
and it knocked Misao down.
Shino Epo.
You think it's Shino Epo?
Well, he had to be using
some kind of trick
to pull off that stunt.
Shino Epo hits an opponent
with sword energy
to stop their movement,
giving one time to knock
your opponent down.
But I swear,
this was no trick.
The power of his
force was very real.
I believe you.
Tonight, that
assassin killed Kissai.
There was no one else
in the whole place hurt
except for him,
all the guards
were knocked unconscious.
Speaking of unconscious,
did I ever tell you
of the time I had
a sake drinking contest
with these two fishermen
from Osaka?
Talk about being knocked out
from here into next Tuesday!
But that's another story.
Oh!
Wait a second,
I got it!
He's using a
high-speed technique
just like...
Hiten Mitsurugi style.
Understand?
That's why I wanted you
to help solve this problem.
You're saying his sword style
is like mine?
Yeah.
Just what are
you trying to do?
Are you trying
to blame Kenshin?
He has nothing
to do with this guy!
Sanosuke,
you need to borrow
the brain of a chicken
so you'll be smarter.
Then you might understand
what I'm saying.
Now, hold on!
You can't tell me
I'm not as smart
as a chicken!
There are feathers
with more brains
than you, Sano,
now be quiet.
What's important
about this discussion
is the fact
that this assassin
is using the
super godspeed move.
But that just can't be!
No one can do that move
but Kenshin!
You think he's
better than Kenshin?
(laughs)
You really believe someone's
better than Kenshin?
Then he would have to be a god,
'cause there's no human being
that's better!
I agree,
but from what I saw,
he is a god.
He's that good?
♪
I apologize for my
outburst earlier, Aoshi,
but I...
...I find it hard to believe
that there's a swordsman
that's faster than Kenshin.
♪
(birds chirping)
I knew you'd
come here for this.
(footsteps)
(wind rushing)
(gulping)
It's just like you
to bring me trouble,
and when you come to see
me with these problems,
have you ever thought
of bringing a gift,
a souvenir, anything?
What was that you said?
You know, souvenirs,
something from the city,
like some incense.
It's customary for a guest
to bring a bottle of sake.
I see,
you expect me
to act like a houseguest.
Too bad your manners
aren't as good
as your swordsmanship.
All right,
the next time
I visit, I'll
bring you some sake!
When I heard about
what's been occurring
in Kyoto recently,
I knew to expect
a visit from you.
Those mysterious symbols,
influential people
being murdered by someone
who's using Hiten
Mitsurugi sword technique.
None of these
events surprise me.
I know the time
spoke of long ago
has finally come.
Please share with me
exactly what you know,
Master.
(wind rushing)
(gulping)
His name is
Shogo Amakusa.
Shogo Amakusa?
Actually, he's
a Christian swordsman
who's supposedly
the second coming
of Shiro Amakusa.
♪
(marching)
What's he waiting for?
This waiting's intolerable.
I don't get it.
What does it all mean?
"When the day dies,
and turns into darkness...
(marching)
...then a child of God
will appear."
What kind of mumbo-jumbo
is he talking about?
That kind of talk only proves
that people in power are crazy.
(wind rushing)
(wings flapping)
I first heard about
this legendary story
40 years ago.
It was first told
to me by my master.
He was Seijuro Hiko, the 12th,
and he was my predecessor.
There was this young man
who studied under him
who was expected to become
Seijuro Hiko the 13th.
His name was Hyoei Nishida.
But Hyoei didn't pass
his last training test.
He just broke under pressure.
During that test,
the pupil has to beat
the Master's
nine-headed dragon thrust
using Amakakeru Ryu no Hirameki.
If he does not
succeed in besting
the master's Kuzu Ryu Sen,
there is only one fate
left for him.
That fate is death.
Whether this is
a fair test or not,
you understand that's how
Hiten Mitsurugi style is.
To fail is to die,
and Hyoei failed.
Ahh!
(yelling)
Hyoei had lost and fell
into the waterfall and died,
or so everyone believed.
A little over ten years later,
we heard a rumor that
Hyoei was alive in China.
He was alive.
Somehow,
he had survived the fall.
What?
We now know for a fact
that Hyoei is still alive
and he's over 70 years old.
We also know while
he was recovering
in China,
Hyoei Nishida
proclaimed he was a Christian.
♪
He made the perilous voyage
to Nanking,
and there,
he regained his strength,
physically and mentally.
So then, Nishida was
a Christian in hiding?
In China, he became renewed.
He was able to worship freely,
with no fear of
religious persecution.
But instead of following
the Christian precept
of loving his fellow man,
Hyoei returned to Japan
12 years later
with his heart
set on revenge.
He used Hiten Mitsurugi style
and had this guy with him,
called Child of God.
Hyoei Nishida wanted to
make this Child of God guy
the avenging savior of
all Japanese Christians
who had been mistreated.
♪
(footsteps)
Hyoei's Child of God
pupil was very gifted.
He mastered super
godspeed by age 14,
and beat Hyoei's Kuzu
Ryu Sen soon after.
If this Child of God
possessed technique
good enough to
beat Kuzu Ryu Sen
20 years ago,
he must be good.
Keep in mind, Kenshin,
Hyoei was never truly qualified
to teach the
Hiten Mitsurugi style.
But there's no telling
what kind of techniques
he may have picked up
during his stay in China.
And according to
the prophecy written
200 years ago,
now is the time.
♪
(wind rushing)
There's something
out of balance here.
What's happened to
the birds and animals,
why have they fallen silent?
Something's about to happen!
Shiro Amakusa
was reputed
to have caused
all kinds of miracles
during the War of Shimabara.
Hyoei gave this
Child of God guy
a legendary sword
that once belonged
to Shiro Amakusa.
As much as I know about this,
it's uncertain to me what
this Child of God will do.
I'm not even sure if he's human.
Maybe he really
is a Child of God.
By the way, his name
is Shogo Amakusa.
♪
"The time of vengeance has come.
The Child of God
is going to be here...
...when the day dies
and turns into darkness."
(wind softly rushing)
This is strange.
It's really weird weather.
(wind rushing)
♪
Huh, now I see.
This is it!
Now I understand the prophecy.
"When the day dies..."
♪
What is this?
(whimpering)
♪
(singing in Japanese)