♪
(singing in foreign language)
You know some kind of secret
about Shogo and Magdalia?
Yeah, come on,
Misao, tell us.
It's about the tragedy
of their childhood.
It really explains what
motivates their behavior.
♪
(clopping)
(indistinct chattering)
He's here.
Mommy, look.
When Shogo came to
Shimabara a year ago,
he arrived as a healer,
a traveling mystic.
He came to establish a
hospital and an orphanage,
but in addition,
he organized a secret
army of Christians.
♪
That's good.
This is a
special medicine
that Shogo mixed
up for you himself.
Oh, why my pain,
it's gone away!
Amazing!
I thought I'd
never be rid of it.
Oh, thank you, sir!
You'll be all right.
Take this medicine in
the morning and at night.
In a couple of days, you
should be strong enough
to go home to
your loved ones.
Thank you, you
are a holy man.
I'm forever grateful.
A miracle!
Shogo has cured
Matzu's illness.
She faced certain death.
It's true, she had
an incurable disease.
Shogo is a child of God.
Perhaps he has come
here to Shimabara
to deliver us out
of our poverty.
Can it be that our savior
has actually arrived?
If it's true, after
300 years of hiding,
we Christians can
finally stand tall.
A new word is coming,
I can feel it.
♪
Tomorrow is a day
of the Holy Ghost.
We must hold a mass to
honor the spirits of those
who were martyred in
this village 14 years ago.
Who was martyred here?
Shogo's mother and father
were willing to sacrifice
their lives in
defense of their faith.
I will go pray
in the mausoleum.
(indistinct shouting)
We will go with you!
♪
I hear your cries.
Let us pray
together, my people.
The reason Shogo was
able to cure the sick
and predict celestial events
was not due to miracles
or magical powers.
Rather, it was a result
of his extensive study
of western medicine and
the science of astronomy,
which he learned
from the Chinese.
Of course Shogo
had no intention
of admitting this
to his followers.
That would've weakened his
position as their savior.
But the truth was he
was unable to cure
the one person who
meant the most to him.
Who was that, Misao?
It was his younger
sister, Sayo.
She suffered from
the same disease
that cut her
mother's life short.
It was his
deepest secret,
it showed him to be
both human and fallible.
(birds squawking)
♪
Oh, no, Sayo!
Brother.
Sorry.
Sayo, can you move?
Mm-mm.
(audible sigh)
♪
Thank you, Shogo.
The dream came back again.
Everything was white.
And tomorrow is
the anniversary
of their passing,
the day our mother
and father left
their mortal bonds
and ascended to
a higher plane.
Sayo?
Shimabara was so white
and bright that day.
Everything sparkled
in the heat of the sun.
I see it so clearly,
the last day our
family was together.
It was wonderful.
Do you remember?
♪
Ah, keep up, Sayo!
You're behind!
Wait for me,
you go too fast!
(coughing)
Mother, are
you all right?
Uh, yes.
Don't worry, children.
Everything is just fine.
We'll catch up later,
you go ahead.
-Okay!
♪
Mother Mary,
please protect my family.
In the name of the
Father, the Son,
and the Holy Spirit, amen.
♪
Shogo, I'm going to
tell you something
I want you to remember
for the rest of your life.
Are you paying attention?
Yes, Father,
I'm listening.
For more than 250 years,
the people of Shimabara
have protected
their true religion
from the outside world
and have worshiped
behind closed doors.
They are all
Christians in hiding,
and every day as
they work the fields
and do their chores,
they risk their lives
because of their devotion
to their faith.
That faith is what gives them
the strength to carry on.
Remember this one
truth, my son...
In spirit, every
single man is equal
in the face
of the Lord.
"In spirit, every
single man is equal
in the face
of the Lord."
God says, "The worth
of a man is measured
not by his class or
the size of his estate,
but instead, by the nobility
and beauty of his heart."
I believe this is the
great lesson of life,
just as I believe that
no man has the right
to rule over another.
And because of
these beliefs,
I will soon be
arrested and executed.
No, Father!
It's true.
We've made arrangements for
you children to go to China.
Your Uncle Hyouei will
pick you up tonight.
Go with him for
your own safety.
Can't you and Mother
run away with us?
Pa?
♪
I'm afraid it's
too late for that.
Shogo, I'm counting on you.
Someday, you will be the
one who sets the people
of Shimabara free from
religious persecution.
You have to be
strong for me.
And for God.
I will, Father.
Soon you will be safe
in a foreign land,
but one day, you will
return to Shimabara.
And then, you'll
be the savior
of those who have
been so mistreated.
Hmm.
(panting)
Huh?
We've been looking all over
for you, Tokisada Muto.
We know all about you.
A Christian traitor trying
to destroy our way of life.
Shogo, run away!
No, Father!
Father!
Shogo,
someday soon, my son,
you'll be the savior for
the people of Shimabara.
Ah!
Father, no!
♪
(coughing)
It's not safe, Mother,
we should hide.
Shogo's right.
Too weak to move.
Mother, please!
I don't understand
these Christians at all,
I'm telling you they're
complete fanatics.
All they have to
do is renounce
this so-called
Messiah of theirs
and everything
would be fine,
we'd leave them alone.
Instead, they're
willing to be tortured
and killed for
their beliefs.
If you asked me,
they should be killed.
They have no business here
worshiping a foreign god.
We're doing them a favor.
We're helping them join
their savior up in Heaven.
(laughing)
Look, here's one
we missed earlier.
How rude.
She's still breathing.
I guess we'll
finish the job now.
You leave my mother alone
or you'll answer to me.
That's big talk,
grasshopper.
I can fight you!
That may be so,
but can you win?
Shogo!
Ah!
♪
(groaning)
How dare you commit
murder in the name of God?
Brother!
(yelling)
♪
We all have to hurry,
the boat's ready to leave.
Mother's too weak.
I'll never be
able to keep up,
you should stick
to the plan.
Leave me here and take
the children with you.
There's no time.
Mother, get up!
Go now, quickly
while you can.
No, Mother, we'd never be
able to forgive ourselves,
you have to try!
Shogo!
I made up my mind,
now don't argue with me.
But, Mother, we can't
just leave you here.
You must.
I'll just hold you back.
You can't stay
here out of pity.
The greatest good
demands sacrifice.
My life is over.
Yours is just beginning.
You have to be strong
because one day
you'll come back
and lead all these
people to freedom.
If you die
now, my son,
all their hopes
will die with you.
Look, down there!
You two, go cut them off.
We have to go!
Farewell, Sister.
Sayo, take this.
Hyouei, watch over them.
I will.
I'm sorry, my sister.
Mother, Mother!
No!
That's right,
Shogo, run and live.
Live to fight
another day and win.
♪
(waves crashing)
(gunshot)
No!
(gasping)
Mother!
(crying)
♪
(gasping)
Shogo, you have to
be strong for me.
And for God.
One day you
will come back
and lead all these
people to freedom.
You can't stay
here out of pity.
When you finally return
to Shimabara, my son,
you will be the
savior of all those
who have been
so mistreated.
I will be strong.
I'll grow up and
be strong like God
so I never have to bow
down to anybody ever again.
And when I
do come back,
I'll make these people
pay for the deaths
of my mother
and father,
that much I swear.
♪
(water dripping)
Sayo?
I feel it won't
be long now.
I'll finally get
to go to Heaven.
I'll be there.
I'll join Mother and Father.
I'm not scared, Shogo.
In fact, it's kind
of a blessing.
Please, Sayo.
Don't you give up on me.
I won't let you die.
I promised to protect
your life and I will.
♪
My gosh, Himura,
you're just amazing.
Watching you move, I would
never believe you can't see.
Yeah, how'd you do it?
I was following the sound
of Miss Misao's footsteps.
You're joking.
It's quite simple
and by listening
to the placement of
everyone's breathing,
I can pretty much orient
myself to my surroundings.
Astounding.
So we've become your eyes
and ears, am I right?
-Mmhmm.
-That makes sense.
Oh, I should've figured
you had the senses of a cat.
(waves crashing)
It's a boat.
You're sure?
He's right,
it's over there!
♪
It's Santo from
the Dutch Consulate.
I saw him
yesterday morning.
How strange.
What in the world
would he be doing here?
I have a feeling he's part
of a larger conspiracy,
and the man who's pulling
the strings is--it's Kaiou.
You're sure?
Wait a minute, now
that you mention it,
that makes sense.
According to the
information I've gathered,
my contacts have
identified Kaiou
as one of the
most dangerous
and powerful figures
ever to operate
during the Tokugawa Era.
What were you
able to find out?
Kaiou himself
is a minister
and his mother was
a Christian in hiding.
When the Tokugawa
government started
to suppress the
Christian movement,
she was able to
escape from Japan
and went to China.
After they arrived in
China, his mother died.
Kaiou was left
orphaned and homeless.
He had a hard life
and cursed Japan,
which had taken his
nationality away from him.
During the upheaval at the
end of the Tokugawa Era,
he slipped back into Japan
and settled in Kyushu.
He's been here
ever since,
consolidating power and
waiting for the opportunity
to take his revenge.
Interesting.
Both Shogo and Kaiou
suffered as Christians,
and now each one
seeks vengeance.
Hmm, what's going
on over there?
He's flashing a signal to
someone over there on land.
Hold on!
Who's that?
The army?
Yeah, that would be my
guess, that makes sense.
What the hell's
going on here?
(gasping)
(grunting)
Kenshin!
♪
(knocking)
Lady Magdalia?
Are you in there?
Genemon?
Please open the door.
Sorry to bother you,
but I have
important information.
It's very late.
What is it that's
so important?
I saw it, my lady.
There's no doubt it
was your medallion,
I'm absolutely certain.
I wanted you to know.
My medallion,
where was it?
It's at the house
of Master Kaiou.
Are you really
sure about this?
So how many times
am I gonna have
to repeat myself, pinhead?
Read my lips,
your angel medallion
was taken by the
blonde guy, get it?
If your information
is accurate,
the medallion might
be at Sir Kaiou's.
How perceptive of you.
That's why
I've been asking
if this is the right
way to Kaiou's place.
If you expected a
pleasant response,
you should've asked
in a pleasant way.
(grunting)
Fine, don't
come with me.
-You are such a...
-What the hell?
Now that's strange.
Why is there light
coming from down there?
This is your kingdom,
don't you know
what goes on here?
Not always, we just
arrived last year.
Kaiou has been
using this area
for at least
five years.
I'm still learning this area.
So Kaiou has
my medallion.
(water dripping)
(gasping)
(door creaking open)
(footsteps)
♪
(gasping)
Brother.
Behold a depiction
of Shogo Amakusa's last moments.
(gasping)
Tomorrow morning that
picture will become reality.
♪
(chuckling)
(laughing)
♪
(grunting)
You traitor.
You were going
to betray us.
From the beginning.
I was thinking about how to
kill you and your brother
from the time I
first met you.
It took some
maneuvering,
but now my plans have all
come together on schedule.
Tomorrow morning on the
day of the Holy Ghost,
your brother will ascend
into Heaven in such a way
that he'll
become a legend
to the people
of this country.
Then I will become the
Archbishop of this church
and spread his
gospel far and wide.
Hmm?
Behold the Book of
Prophecy by Shogo Amakusa.
Once the savior is gone,
his followers will read
the material in this book
and swear their
complete allegiance to me.
Then they will make
it their mission
to make these
prophecies come to pass.
My brother Shogo has
never written such a book.
Ha-ha, of course not.
I wrote it,
you stupid fool.
You'll never get
away with this.
Oh, the plan is
foolproof, I assure you.
People will be willing to
kill in your brother's name.
He'll be a
god to them.
Thousands of people will
mobilize to carry his word
throughout the land.
And everywhere they go,
their fanaticism will
lead to chaos and riots.
They'll turn this
country upside-down
and political power will
move into Dutch hands.
I will then step
forward and become king.
And Japan will disappear
from the face of the Earth.
My friends and I might
have something to say
about that plan, Kaiou.
Sanosuke!
Lady Magdalia!
It's you, Shozo.
I'm all right, my lady.
And I swear
this mad man
will never carry out
his plan to become king.
I second that
motion, in fact,
I have a plan of
my own for him.
I'm gonna send
this man right down
to the deepest
pit in Hell.
♪
Damn!
(laughing)
So much for your
empty threats.
I'm afraid I
must leave you.
You're an evil monster.
My brother is too virtuous
to fall into your trap.
The Lord won't let
you destroy him.
That's your belief.
But what if God
is on my side?
That can't be!
(exploding)
(shouting)
(gasping)
♪
(singing in foreign language)