♪
(singing in foreign language)
(boat horn blaring)
Six bells and all's well!
Well, Captain, no sign
of that pirate ship, sir.
I kinda hope that
we don't see it, sir.
Huh?
♪
Captain, they're flying no flag!
It's the pirates, sir!
All hands prepare for battle!
♪
(shouting)
(grunting)
♪
Yah!
(shouting)
(piercing thud)
♪
Another ship waylaid by pirates.
The pirates killed
all hands and robbed the ship.
Their ship is known
as the Sea Dragon.
That's one motley crew
I wouldn't want to meet.
Hm.
Aw, I'm as hungry as a bear.
Me too, Yoshi.
I haven't had anything
to eat since yesterday morning.
What I wouldn't give
for some broiled eel now.
Or some tasty tempura.
Or lobster tail.
Yeah, come to think of it,
we haven't had any beef
in over four months either.
Dinner's ready, boys!
Huh?
Yeah!
♪
Is--is that all there is?
I know you told us that
we don't have any money
and we have to cut back,
but you've gotta be joking.
That fish isn't even
big enough to be called bait.
Well, that's all we've got,
so enjoy your supper.
I know you all
know how to share.
I'm going to teach.
See you guys tomorrow.
(grunting)
The middle part's mine!
It's all mine,
you little parasite!
(commotion)
Why can't you two guys
just join hands
and love one another?
I'll share it with you,
but I won't share
with this greedy pig.
After I beat beanpole here,
you and I are eatin' fish.
(grunting)
♪
Hey, look, it's a leftover.
We can't waste that.
Waste not want not.
(commotion)
Huh?
(pained grunting)
(meow)
Oh!
Not even a grain of rice.
(groaning)
This is rough.
The person who's
responsible here is Kori.
-I see.
-Huh?
You're right,
I am the only one
around here that's responsible.
You three freeloaders
depend on me for everything.
I work every day giving lessons
to whoever will pay me.
I'm busting my butt trying
to scrape up enough money
to keep us afloat
and feed you spineless bums,
and when I leave for one second,
this is what you deadbeats
masquerading as men have to say?
You've got a lot of nerve.
Hey, where are you three going?
Yah!
My little speech must
have got you guys motivated.
(wincing)
I bet you're
leaving to find work.
Nature's callin' me.
Actually I'm just goin' out.
I have some clothes
that need washing.
What?
Why you!
(angry grunt)
(grunts)
(dazed muttering)
♪
Boy, Kori was
really steamed at us.
Well, she does have a point.
The three of us never
have brought in any money.
But what kind of jobs can we get
when we don't have
any job skills?
Yeah, I mean, the only
things we're really good at
is martial arts
and swordsmanship.
Did I just hear you say "we"?
Calling all men
that are good fighters.
The Sebonya needs you.
The Sebonya is adventure,
and if you're qualified,
you'll be paid lots of yen.
Did he say money?
Good food and every man
that sails with us
will be paid at least 200 yen.
Two hundred yen?
You can count me in!
Here's our situation, men.
Our merchant ships have been
attacked four times straight
by the pirates
of the Sea Dragon.
We are going to set
sail tomorrow morning,
and it's essential
that the Sebonya's cargo
arrives safely
in Yokohama no matter what.
It's very important that
we let these renegades know
we will not be intimidated.
Now while we're not
looking for bounty hunters,
anyone who kills a pirate
will receive a 500 yen bonus.
And--and just for
sailing with us,
each man will receive 200 yen.
(excited murmuring)
(shouting)
Yeah, money!
Hm.
♪
(boat horn blaring)
Ah, this is exciting.
I might get to fight again.
I mean, if they
keep up their end,
then we'll be attacked
and I'll get to send
some pirates to Belugaville.
You know, I'm not so sure
that this was such a good idea.
Hey, Kori wanted us
to bring home some money,
and we did leave her a note
explaining we'd be back
in ten days with
a nice surprise for her.
He's right, Kenshin.
And when we get back,
we'll bring her lobster
and some broiled eel.
Uh, you shouldn't be lying down.
That's a really good
way to get seasick.
(muffled sounds)
(vomiting)
I guess it's heave-ho time.
(muffled sounds)
(vomiting)
Hm.
Huh?
Ah, sorry for barging past you,
but when my stomach says purge,
I do what it says.
Huh?
♪
Kori?
What are you doing here?
Well, I'm earning money.
Uh...
I think I'm a little homesick.
Bleh, watch the shoes!
(boat horn blaring)
(soft slicing sounds)
So why are you on
the Sebonya with us anyway?
After I yelled at you guys,
I felt so bad that I decided
to get away for a while
and earn some
money in the process.
Wow, you mean you fibbed
about giving those lessons?
That really surprises
me that you'd fib to us.
I knew if I told you the
truth you'd be worried about me.
Hey, don't stop
peeling, Kenshin!
Well, of course we'd worry.
This could be dangerous.
There might be trouble.
They say the pirates
of the Sea Dragon
are a fierce crew.
Fierce isn't the word.
They're bloodthirsty killers.
Huh?
What they live for is
to see people suffer.
♪
(sounds of battle)
They surprise attack
you out of nowhere
and steal everything
that's not nailed down.
They'd as soon kill
your crew as look at them.
Isn't the leader of these
pirates a man called Shura?
Yes, Shura is the heartless
monster that leads them.
But we don't know much about him
because no one's ever
lived to describe him.
But we are sure of one thing--
he's as evil as
the devil himself.
I must admit we don't
have a clue where he's from
or why he seems to be
persecuting my Sebonya ships,
but he's left many of my crew's
families orphaned and grieving,
and he's certainly done his best
to make my life a living hell.
We have to stop him.
His heartless hunger for money
has almost cost me
everything I own.
(boat horn blaring)
I wonder just what
makes Shura tick.
Kenshin?
Huh?
What is it, Kori?
I was having trouble sleeping.
So why are you still awake?
So tell me what's on your mind.
Well, I don't want to alarm you,
but I had a premonition about
those pirates attacking us.
Really, Kenshin?
What do you think's
going to happen?
I feel like Shura and
his crew are toying with us
like a cat plays with a mouse.
They know where we are
and when to attack.
And if I had known you
were aboard before we left,
I would have done
whatever it took
to make sure you
never sailed with us.
Um...
So are you feeling
angry towards me?
No.
You really care
about me, don't you?
I promise I won't
make any trouble.
You don't have to worry
about protecting me, Kenshin.
And I won't try to kiss you.
♪
(laughs)
Huh?
(thunder rumbling)
♪
Hm?
Rain?
Well, at least it's a calm sea.
♪
Good news, with this
kind of weather,
at least we don't have
to worry about pirates.
Wrong.
It's perfect weather
for them to attack.
(thunder cracking)
My gosh, it's them!
All hands on deck,
we've got pirates!
♪
Dammit, they snuck up on us.
Now you'll earn your pay.
Huh?
♪
(evil laughter)
(growling)
♪
(thunder cracking)
That's just gotta be--
Shura!
♪
(thunder rumbling)
(thunder cracking)
♪
Ya!
(grunting)
♪
(thunder)
(shouting)
(trembling)
Ya!
♪
(grunting)
Ya, ya!
♪
(creaking)
(shouting)
♪
(grunting)
They're swarming all over
this ship faster than locusts!
Huh?
♪
Shura!
Shura?
That's Shura?
He don't look so tough.
Which one of you wants
to be my first victim?
Let's kill that bastard!
♪
(shouting)
(grunting)
♪
(thud)
(grunting)
♪
Ah!
Ha!
♪
(gasping)
Well, it's finally here,
the moment that I
really made this trip for.
Let's get ready to rumble!
(grunting)
♪
Ha, at last
an opponent worth my time,
if that punch of
mine didn't stop ya.
(grunting)
Hey!
Huh?
(evil laughter)
♪
There's gotta be
somebody on this ship
that'll give me a challenge.
(panting)
(grunting)
♪
I told you I want
you to go below now.
I'm not about to
quit and let you down.
It's too dangerous here.
Now go!
I'm doing fine.
I can handle myself.
(hollering)
Hey, Butt Boy!
Yah!
Yoshi, take Kori down below!
Kenshin, on your left!
(grunting)
Kenshin!
Huh?
(gasps)
(grunting)
(humming "Row, Row,
Row Your Boat")
Hm.
(grunting)
(evil laughter)
(thud)
Hurry up, you oafs!
We've got to hide that
before they get down here.
Move, move!
(grunting)
Huh?
Hey, take it easy
with that chest!
It's important!
You stupid idiot!
We've got to protect that
particular chest at all costs!
I could care less about
the rest of the cargo.
They can take the whole
ship as far as I'm concerned
as long as we're able
to save this chest.
Thanks for the hot tip.
Well, if it isn't
the owner of the Sebonya line,
Mr. Yohi himself.
Hi there.
No, no, no.
(trembling)
It sure is a pleasure
to meet you, bub.
(trembling)
Just relax, guys,
and things'll be fine.
Mr. Yohi's gonna make
a little donation to us.
(sighs)
Okay, boys, move it out.
I'm sure you know
that we've killed
your entire crew in the past,
but we're feeling
merciful today, you scum.
Whoa!
Foreign cigarettes.
Hm.
All right.
Let it go.
No!
♪
All right, just let the lady go
and we can finish this like men.
Kori, how are you doing?
I should have listened to you,
but I'm okay.
It's only a little scratch.
♪
Just stay close to me, Kori.
If they try to hurt you,
I'll kill them all.
♪
(grunting)
(thud)
♪
Ah!
(grunting)
♪
Hm.
(pained grunting)
Kill the girl first!
She is his weak point!
(grunting)
♪
(angry grunting)
(grunting)
Ah, ah!
Oh no!
♪
Hey, Sanosuke, save Yoshi!
(grunts)
(gasps)
(grunting)
Oh, Kenshin!
♪
It's okay.
You've been poisoned.
Wait!
Huh?
I've been watching
this one fight
and I feel that he might be
worthy enough to fight me.
♪
(thunder cracking)
Don't tell me that you're
disappointed that I'm a woman.
I haven't found a man
yet that can beat me.
(thunder cracking)
♪
I guess I'll make
the first move.
♪
(grunting)
Incredible.
I've never seen
a woman so strong.
I can't believe he's
been able to elude my attack.
♪
So tell me, what's your name?
Kenshin Himura.
Well, allow me to say
it's just too bad
you're on the other
side today, Kenshin.
(grunting)
Huh?
(thunder)
Ya!
(grunting)
♪
(gasps)
You won!
♪
Hm.
(groaning)
Oh!
Kenshin!
Just tell me that
you're all right.
I'm just dizzy.
(maniacal laughter)
Wait, you mean
this guy was poisoned
and he still beat me?
Huh?
(explosions)
Ah!
(hollering)
Hey, what's the navy doing here?
Just relax.
They won't sink this can
knowing Mr. Yohi's onboard.
(explosions)
The cargo all loaded up?
Aye!
Now hear this,
we're shoving off.
But it's only one lousy gunship.
Why don't we stay here and let
the navy know we're serious
and sink it?
(grunting)
Hey!
(squealing)
Geki.
I stole her from
that guy that beat you.
Besides, I need a girlfriend.
Help!
Let me go!
(grunts)
(whimpering)
(trembling)
Wait, hold it!
Please, take me instead.
It's not fair to
kidnap an innocent person.
Shura, a few minutes ago in
battle I could have killed you.
As an honorable warrior,
I ask you now to set her free.
Let her go!
She means you no harm.
First, let's rearrange her face.
(snickering)
-Stop it!
-Huh?
As barbaric as pirates are,
we have our own law.
We are proud of who we are.
We never kill women or children.
That is our law.
I'll show you.
To prove we mean it,
I'll set her free.
(gasps)
Of course, we pirates also
believe in another law,
an eye for an eye,
so I will accept your
offer to take her place
and you will
stay here with us.
Now I'll take
your sword for myself.
Doing battle with you
was quite a challenge.
Let the girl go free!
♪
Kori!
They've kidnapped Kenshin!
Bring him back, damn you!
(explosions)
♪
If we don't leave now,
we risk being sunk.
Full steam ahead.
The crew has seen
this man beat me.
I can't allow him to live.
♪
Execution!
Kill, kill, kill,
kill, kill, kill!
Please don't kill him!
Come back, Kenshin.
Yoshi, Sanosuke!
Take care of Kori!
Kori, I love you!
♪
And I love you.
Kenshin!
♪
(singing in foreign language)