♪
(singing in Japanese)
(bell ringing)
♪
(crashing)
It doesn't seem to be here.
Yeah, Lance, I guess the
doctor must have it on himself.
He was just here!
We must have just
missed grabbing him.
♪
Heh, don't worry my friends,
we'll find the good doctor
wherever he tries to hide.
He cannot escape.
♪
Every time we leave
the dojo to give a lesson,
I get depressed.
A long time ago,
that dojo had more than
50 students on the roster,
and now there's hardly
any students at all.
Sure, Yoshi's
right, at this rate,
kendo's going to
be a lost art form.
Due to the Meiji restoration,
it seems kendo has lost
a lot of its popularity.
Kenshin, don't say
things like that.
That sounds really negative.
I'll do anything
to keep Kendo alive,
even if I have to work
alone with nothing more
than a skinny arm.
Skinny arm?
I don't think you have
a skinny arm, in fact,
I think your arm's
stronger than mine.
Are you trying to
say I'm not feminine?
(grunting)
How dare they make
fun of the weaker sex!
Hey, Yoshi, did
I just hear Kaoru
say she was the weaker sex?
Just agree with her
or she'll hit us again.
Yoshi, please do me a favor,
take these to the dojo.
Bye!
Hold on, Kaoru!
Man, she should do it herself.
Darn it.
Sanosuke?
Anything happen
while we were gone?
Unbelievable.
Rats, I can't win one!
You're unstoppable, it
isn't fair, I tell ya.
(laughing)
Looks like Sano is playing
chess with a foreigner.
You're right.
Hello there you two, I...
Kenshin, say something,
I don't speak
another language!
Hello!
Hello there, young folks,
my name is Hans, and
I come from Germany.
It's nice to meat you.
Oh my, you speak English.
Sano, why didn't you tell us?
Not only does this
guy speak English,
but he's an expert at shogi,
you know, Japanese chess.
I'm pretty good,
but he's unbeatable!
I've lost five
straight games to him!
Checkmate.
That makes six in a row!
I don't know anybody from
Germany, do you, Kenshin?
No, I sure don't.
You must be
the master samurai,
Kenshin Himura,
I've heard a lot about you.
Don't they call you
Battousai the Slasher?
Huh?
That's really incredible,
they even know all
about you in Germany!
I think you're mistaken, Kaoru.
Did you tell him, Sano?
There, beat that one!
Oh, that's simple.
(shouting)
I lugged this thing
all the way to the dojo,
and there's only
one student here!
Huh, who's that guy?
Maybe this guy's come here to
make a challenge to our dojo!
I, Yoshi Myojin, will
accept this challenge.
Huh?
It can't be.
Y-Yutaro!
Yoshi, it's you.
Yutaro, you came
back to see us.
I was in the neighborhood,
so I thought I would drop in.
Aren't you happy to see me?
Yeah, but you're the last
guy I thought I'd see.
So, how's your arm,
is it any better now?
Um, well, I'll tell you
how much better it is,
it's good enough
to beat you, Yoshi.
You game?
All right, let's go for it!
(grunting)
♪
It didn't take long for
Yoshi and Yutaro to go at it.
It must be really nice
for them to see each other.
Why didn't you tell us
Yutaro was here, Sano?
What?
Did you say something?
Never mind.
(grunting)
Do you remember our match?
Oh, who could
forget that, Yoshi.
I am ready for you.
I have been
training in Germany
for this moment
to finally arrive.
Let's see what
you've learned.
All right, let's go!
(grunting)
♪
Oh?
Wunderbar, the boys are
practicing kendo together.
Let's watch.
It looks more like a fight
to me; knock it off you two!
Nah, Kaoru, leave them alone.
What?
They haven't seen each
other in a long while,
they need to get
back together again.
-Right?
-Right.
They're ecstatic when
those two are fighting.
Leave them alone and let
them make up for lost time.
♪
Hey, what's wrong Yoshi,
have you had enough yet?
Hey, that'll be the day!
Yaa!
Keep your guard up, Yutaro!
Yeah!
That's right, great!
I'm a little bit
worried about Dr. Hans.
He might just pop
a blood vessel or something.
Oh, he'll be just fine.
♪
Excuse me, Lieutenant Meldars.
I welcome you to Japan.
We are celebrating
your arrival here
and we want you to feel
right at home here.
Welcome, my friends!
Minister Hoodle.
Yes, Lieutenant?
I want all these guests
out of here right now.
There are some things I
need to talk to you about.
No, we can talk anytime,
let's have a drink.
Give me your wine
glass, Lieutenant,
let's drink to the future.
Hey, did you flash your sword--
You cut clear
through the bottle!
Now, let's get
serious, minister,
I need you to clear
this hall immediately!
Yes.
Attention, stop the music!
Everybody, you have
to leave right now!
I'm terribly sorry!
That's right,
everyone leave.
I'll make it up
to you somehow!
Keep moving!
You can clean that
stuff up later.
We want you all to
leave right away.
Go on, get out, now!
(chuckles)
All right, everybody's gone.
I thought that you Germans
would enjoy a party,
but I guess I was mistaken.
Now, what was so important
that it couldn't wait
until the festivities
were completed?
Know this, from
this time forward,
this consulate is
under our command!
Anything that goes
through this consulate
will go through us first,
is that understood, minister?
-What, how can that be?
-No questions!
From now on, you will
take your orders from me.
If anyone asks you
anything, you know nothing.
You will be richly rewarded
or severely punished,
the choice is yours.
But, how do you think you can
get away with that, anyway?
I'm certain you have
seen this symbol before,
it's the reason we can
do anything that we want.
It can't be, that's the
symbol of the Black Knights!
So, you are
the Black Knights?
We are not here
representing Germany.
We are in your country now to do
the bidding of our great leader.
We'll do anything
to attain our goal,
so it's best that you
keep your mouth shut.
Of course I will, you can
count on me, Lieutenant Meldars.
Just be sure to stay out
of our way, Minister Hoodle.
I have an assignment I'd
like you to do for us.
Yes, what is it you want?
We believe that this man
is somewhere in Japan.
He is a German doctor
traveling with a young
boy who is Japanese.
I want you to find out
exactly where they are located.
♪
Why is Dr. Hans up so late?
It's got something
to do with that map.
He was looking in it the whole
time we were on the ship.
Hans is a doctor
who successfully
operated on Yutaro's arm.
You think he's a
brilliant doctor,
you should try playing
him at chess sometime.
I really don't understand
why they checked into a hotel,
they could have
stayed here with us.
Maybe we should tell them that.
And now that Yutaro's arm
has healed completely,
we should throw
a party here at the dojo
to celebrate his
coming back here.
That's a great idea, and we'll
thank Dr. Hans at the same time.
Let's do it at Lenny's!
And that way, we can watch
the fireworks at night.
I'm not going.
I have no reason to
celebrate anything.
Honestly, Yoshi,
don't be a party pooper.
All right, I'll go to Lenny's
then and celebrate a little.
But only if it's beef pot!
Well, I'm glad
you got over that.
♪
Ever since I obtained this map,
I feel as though
someone is after me.
♪
This isn't safe
in my possession,
I'm going to have
to hide it somewhere.
I don't know what
the future holds,
and I can't jeopardize
Yutaro's safety.
♪
Hm?
What are you doing awake?
Sorry I startled you.
I couldn't sleep, sorry.
Oh my, Yutaro,
I'm so sorry,
I didn't mean to
yell at you so loudly.
I'm so jumpy lately,
I'm so sorry, Yutaro.
It's all right, sir.
Hey, don't you have
a lesson at the dojo tomorrow?
You should go get some sleep.
All right, I'll do that.
♪
Hah!
That's right, keep
your stance straight.
Put some effort
into your movement!
Hah!
Hm.
So...
(chuckles)
Match this.
It's not good enough.
Oh no!
Looks like I win again, Sano.
Rats!
There's your reward for losing!
Let's play just
one more game!
I won't lose this time!
Yeah, if you
insist, be my guest.
Try and beat that!
You only got
two, I win again!
No, not again!
Here, congratulations on your
complete recovery, Yutaro!
This wooden sword
is a gift to you
from the Kamiya Kasshin dojo.
Wow!
Thanks so much, Kaoru!
Yeah, that's wonderful.
This is a happy occasion,
we should all celebrate!
-Dig in, everybody!
-It's great.
Listen up, Yutaro, I'm still
the number one student, got it?
And you're just
a second student!
What are you
talking about, dork?
That's not the way you
address your superiors!
You're not my superior!
You boys knock
that off right now!
Stop it!
It's all right.
Yutaro's very happy here
since we arrived in Japan.
They fight just like brothers.
So, Kenshin, should we
get the hot beef pot?
Sounds like a good idea.
Hey, listen, if you two
are too busy fighting,
Sanosuke will eat up
everything on the table!
Hey!
You know, Sano, you're
nothing but a big pig!
Shut up.
Save some for us!
♪
Did you find it?
It's not here.
Not here, either.
I guess we'll have to ask the
doctor where it is in person.
Yutaro's arm was injured,
and now it's
completely healed up.
Don't you think Western
medicine is absolutely amazing?
Yes, you see, Dr. Hans is a
very famous doctor in Germany,
and compared
to German medicine,
Japanese medicine is ten
years behind the times.
No, I'd say 100
Now, now, let's not exaggerate.
(chuckles)
I would love to hear what Megumi
would have to say about that.
Well, I really have to
study hard over there.
I'm learning Western
medicine from Dr. Hans,
so I can be a doctor, and come
back here and save many lives--.
-Yutaro!
-Huh?
All you talk about is
Western this, Western that,
it's sickening!
Do you have any idea
how annoying you are?
What did you just say?
You know!
Calm yourself down, Yutaro.
Why should I?
There is no East or West
when it comes to saving people
who are suffering
from illnesses.
There are many positive things
that come out of
both of our cultures.
The important thing
is to remember
that all of us can
become good friends.
I'm sorry, Dr. Hans.
So, do you think Sano will ever
beat you at chess, Dr. Hans?
Sure I will!
I'll have you know,
Mr. Bigmouth,
that I'll beat him!
Tomorrow we'll have
a rematch and I'll win!
I'll play you as
often as you'd like.
Sano's not a very good loser.
(laughter)
See you tomorrow at the
dojo, all right, Yutaro?
Right!
Then we'll see who the
best ninja is, Yutaro!
I'll show you who's--
Oof!
What're you doing?
You talk too much!
(blows raspberry)
Yeah, Kaoru is right!
Well, thanks again,
we'll be pushing off, now.
Good night, Dr. Hans.
(cacophony of farewells)
We should head home, we could
watch the fireworks on the way.
What about dessert?
You still hungry?
Hm?
I think it's great Yutaro
wants to be a doctor.
It's a wonderful profession.
You help so many
people feel better!
It would be nice if you could
learn a little something
from him, Yoshi boy.
Hey, why do you always
take his side on everything?
If Yutaro is going to use
medicine to help people,
you can use a sword
to help people.
You can help,
just like Kenshin.
That's right, I'll help
people better than Yutaro!
That's the spirit!
What do you think, Kenshin?
Whoa, what happened to Kenshin?
Hey, Kenshin!
Those people at your Kamiya
Kasshin dojo are very nice,
aren't they?
Yeah, everyone, that is,
except for Yoshi.
Hm?
(laughing)
Well, if you ask me,
you and Yoshi look like
the best of friends, Yutaro.
Really, you think so?
♪
Who's there?
Dr. Hans, I presume?
We've been looking all over
for you, I'm glad we found you.
What in the world could
a German army officer
possibly want from me?
Please hand it over, Dr. Hans.
Hand what over?
What're you talking about?
Fork it over, Doctor,
we know you have it.
Is it worth dying for in
a foreign country, Doctor?
We do not have time
for this, Doctor.
You people are not
regular soldiers, are you?
You have a good grasp
of the situation,
I knew you were
a clever fellow, Doctor.
You are...
The dreaded Black Knights!
♪
Yutaro, you must run away now.
No, I can't!
I won't leave you behind!
Don't argue with me.
Do as I say, now!
Never!
Go!
♪
(screaming)
Dr. Hans!
Lieutenant, I found it!
Good, now complete
the job, Schneider!
Dr. Hans!
♪
Easy!
What's the hurry?
Good night.
(laughing)
Now back off,
I'm not about to let
you hurt this young man.
Kenshin!
You're not too bad, kid,
I didn't think anyone
in this backwood country
could use a sword.
This must be that famous
samurai we heard about!
Second Lieutenant Lance,
let me take care of him!
Very well.
What are you waiting for?
Go on, make your move.
Kenshin!
Yutaro!
Hurry it up, Schneider!
(screaming)
Schneider, that is
enough, we're leaving!
(growling)
Kenshin!
Hey, Yutaro, are you all right?
Dr. Hans!
They hurt Dr. Hans!
(groaning)
He's seriously hurt, why did
they have to do this to him?
Dr. Hans!
What's going on, Kenshin?
We have to get him to
Dr. Gensai right away.
♪
Those bastards...
Oh God, please
don't let him die.
Yutaro.
Yutaro...
Yes, Doctor?
I'm right here.
You just gotta
hang in there.
Forgive me, Yutaro,
I put you in danger, I came
here to look for something.
(groaning in pain)
That's the real
reason I came here.
I had no right to hide
the truth from you!
Well, what was it?
Does it have something
to do with that map
that was taken from you?
I hid the final clue at
the dojo, just in case.
It's hidden in the
moon watching platform.
Hm?
Don't let those men find it!
Protect the incredible medicine
from falling into evil hands!
You must promise!
(groaning in pain)
Don't worry, I promise you!
Doctor, the operating room
is now ready for his surgery.
Don't die!
Dr. Gensai and I
will not let him.
He will be just
fine, you'll see.
♪
Please, take good care of him.
Cheers!
Even if the Japanese government
decides to take action on this,
you won't have a thing
to worry about, my friends.
Once we have this medicine,
we will have the
world at our feet.
What are you doing here?
Get out of here at once!
Can't you see this
is a private meeting?
You incompetent old fool!
(laughing)
I wouldn't be so quick to
congratulate yourselves,
gentlemen.
Who's that?
Where is she?
(shouting)
Hold it.
(laughter)
Gentlemen, I can help you,
in fact, you need me
to decipher the map.
Really?
And just who might
you be, my dear?
My name is Misanagi,
head of the Sanada Ninjas.
Nice to meet you, Misanagi
of the Sanada Ninjas.
Had we know you were
such a lovely lady,
we would never have attacked you
in such an ungentlemanly manner.
Please come over to join us.
I hope we haven't upset you.
It would be an honor
for us to meet you
and discuss our future
business together.
My pleasure.
Hm.
I feel it, here it is.
This is the Doctor's journal!
What is that thing?
Looks like a regular stone.
Hey, Yutaro, what is
the miraculous medicine
that the doctor
was talking about?
Can you tell us?
Miraculous medicine, does
this have to do with drugs?
Well, I don't
know about that.
Right now, these are the
only two clues that we have.
♪
Yutaro?
I don't know what
this is all about,
but we'll help you
any way we can.
You can count on
all of us to help!
Thank you all.
♪
(singing in Japanese)