♪
(singing in foreign language)
These buckets must
weigh 80 pounds.
I'm not complaining,
but did you have
to buy everything
they had in the store?
It's cheaper if you
buy in large quantities.
And I have to look
for bargains when
I'm shopping for groceries.
You may not have noticed,
but you boys
eat like horses.
I'm feeding a small army.
Your cooking tastes
like it's for the army.
Oh, here he comes!
Maybe I can get
his autograph!
This is really exciting.
It's Senryoyama.
Who is he?
Kenshin, don't
you follow sports?
That's Senryoyama.
He's an up-and-coming
star in sumo wrestling.
In fact, it's only
a matter of time
before he becomes
the grand champion.
Excuse me, sir.
Could you please
hold my grandson
for just a minute
so he'll grow up
big and strong?
Certainly.
Gotcha!
Oh, I'm scared.
Hey, little boy,
I'm not going to drop you.
You'll have to be
a whole lot braver
if you wanna grow up
to be a wrestler like me.
(laughing)
Come back here!
You didn't pay your bill!
Hey!
Toramaru.
Hmph, first you run
from our training stable,
then you run from your debt.
But I was hungry.
You're an embarrassment.
You've disgraced our stable.
Get away!
My pinwheel!
(murmuring)
Thanks, mister.
Come on,
we have to go.
Even though he
skipped out on his bill,
he's a nice man.
But that doesn't
work in his favor.
He needs the discipline
to act like a sumo,
even against his
own classmates.
You've disgraced
the stable, Toramaru.
You should be punished!
I'm really very sorry.
Shut up!
Please, I couldn't help it!
Leave him alone,
you bullies!
Stop, Kori!
It doesn't matter
what he did.
You have no right
to gang up on him,
especially when
he apologized.
You keep out of our business.
You're pretty
cocky for a girl!
Help her!
(voice wavering)
♪
What is your problem?
Hey, sorry about that.
I have to say,
it seems to me
Kori's right, though.
You shouldn't all
gang up on this guy.
Oh yeah, and maybe
you should show us
a little more respect,
Mr. Smart Mouth.
Yah!
♪
You can't do that
to our friend.
♪
Oh my.
(voice wavering)
Come back here!
Kenshin's protecting you!
Hey, maybe it's
better if he leaves.
You're gonna pay for this.
Forget it, boys.
He's just a washed up samurai.
There's no respect
to be earned
in beating up a guy like that.
But he was interfering.
Toramaru is long gone.
There is no point
to this exercise.
Now, let's go home.
♪
I know Toramaru very well.
He used to come
into the restaurant
all the time
with Senryoyama
and the other trainees.
It's so strange.
I wonder why he ran
away from his stable.
It's obvious to me.
He's weak and he doesn't
have the guts to survive
the training.
I don't think that's it.
I heard that for
quite some time now
he's been bullied and
tormented by Senryoyama.
He was practically
chased out of the stable.
(gasps)
So, he stiffed the bill
because he didn't have
the money to eat.
That's terrible.
Senryoyama gets away
with this behavior
because he's strong
and intimidating.
No one's been brave
enough to take him on.
As a result,
he's gotten worse.
He's been getting
drunk each night
and acting like
some kind of wild man.
He's very destructive.
The only reason
he isn't in jail
is because the police see him
as some kind of sports hero.
♪
Hmm?
You don't think that
guy's gonna jump, do you?
(gasps)
That's Toramaru!
Don't worry about it, Kori.
I'm afraid this guy's
way too much of a coward
to kill himself.
You don't know that!
Don't do it!
Leave me alone.
The only thing left
for me to do is die.
You shouldn't even
say such things!
I'm a coward
and a failure.
I tell you,
I'm better off dead!
Let me go,
don't try to stop me.
Don't!
I'm not gonna
let you do it!
Ahh!
(splash)
Kori!
Don't worry, Kenshin.
They're gonna be all right.
The water in this river is
only about six inches deep.
Oh.
Oh no, this is
a new kimono.
I put it on for the
first time this morning.
Oh, I'm really sorry.
♪
Listen, Kori,
I know you're
the kind of person who
likes to help people...
but helping someone
commit suicide
is going a little bit
too far, don't you think?
(laughs)
I can never figure out
why goofball does
the things she does.
Don't call me
"goofball," jerk head!
Achoo!
I'm sorry to be
such a burden.
I figured if I went
back to my hometown
I'd be more trouble
for my family.
My disgrace would
humiliate them
in front of all their friends.
Hey, you don't have to go.
You can stay here until
the scandal blows over.
I'm already
feeding a big crowd,
one more at the
table won't matter.
That's very generous of you.
Don't get excited about this.
I'm warning you,
her cooking's awful.
Come on, you have to admit,
it's gotten better recently.
As a matter of fact,
I'd say it's almost edible.
It's an easy way
to commit suicide.
(laughing)
I don't see you starving!
This food is great.
Huh?
Yeah, I haven't had
anything this delicious
since I left home.
Well, I'm glad you like it.
It's obvious that
people who know good food
enjoy my cooking.
Have some more.
Thanks!
I appreciate it.
He's a champion eater,
that's for sure.
I guess that's
one competition
where he'll
never get beat.
Can I ask you something?
Did Senryoyama
harass you to the point
where you wanted
to quit the stable?
Well...
I don't know if that's
an accurate thing to say.
He was certainly strict,
but I'm the one who
lacked the ability.
For many years,
I was the strongest boy
in my hometown.
For as long as
I could remember,
I dreamed about
becoming a wrestler.
But when I got to Kyoto,
I realized I wasn't
good enough to excel
against the competition.
So, you mean,
instead of trying harder,
you're gonna just
give up your dream?
Well...
What would be the point?
He doesn't have
the desire to win,
so continuing to train
would just be a waste.
I think there's more
hope for him in sumo
than there is for you in kendo.
Why's that?
Because he's honest
about his shortcomings
and wants to improve himself.
And because he
appreciates my cooking,
which makes me feel
good about myself
and inspires me to do
something for him in return.
In fact, I'm so grateful,
I'm gonna train you, Toramaru.
You know sumo?
Not specifically.
But sumo and kendo
are both martial arts
and each one requires
the same discipline.
I'm a master of
the Kamiya style of kendo.
Don't worry, I can
handle the job.
Aw, come on.
Your training doesn't
qualify you to give
advanced sumo lessons
to someone, it's nuts!
Wanna bet on it?
Does that mean you're gonna
be wearing a loin cloth?
It's tradition, you know.
♪
(muttering)
Here, Toramaru,
have some more!
Thank you very much.
What about us?
Yeah, we're hungry, too.
You've had enough.
But--
Aw, all gone!
Time for bed!
After all,
you're in training.
(thumping)
♪
Not bad, but remember
to keep your balance.
It's tough.
You're getting there.
About 200 more
before you stop.
What?
I'm never gonna make it.
One thing about Kori,
she's really enthusiastic.
That's one way to put it.
Other people might
call her a slave driver.
(chuckles)
I bet he runs away
before tomorrow morning.
I'm sorry, Kori, I'm tired.
This is harder than
training with the other sumos
at the stable.
This is just
the beginning.
You can't quit now.
Show some determination.
Think about all the people
back in your hometown.
I'm sure they're
looking forward to the day
you become a champion
sumo wrestler.
I just can't do it.
Come on, Toramaru.
You're big and strong.
You can do anything you want.
And Suzie and I will
cheer you on, okay?
Toramaru, go, go.
You're the dojo's champ.
Nobody ever cheered
for me before.
I can't let
my fans down.
Kori, do me a favor?
This may sound weird,
but can you pinch me?
It's silly, but that's
how my mom used to get me
to do things back when
I was a little boy.
Well, I'm not your mother,
but here it goes!
Ow!
Sorry, was that
a little bit too hard?
Not really, in fact,
I think it's helping
to increase
my energy levels.
♪
(grunts)
Hooray, it worked!
Hooray!
Keep going, Toramaru!
Wow.
He really woke up.
(birds chirping)
(shouting)
(creaking)
Okay, once again.
Yah!
You're coming along.
Kori!
Toramaru!
We brought you lunch!
Rice balls!
Toramaru has
a double portion.
Thank you, girls.
All right,
we'll take a break
and eat them
before they get cold.
Here's some news I just
picked up this morning.
Did you know that
Toramaru is still around?
He's staying at
the Kamiya Dojo.
Yeah?
He must've decided
to give up sumo
and take up kendo.
He's so slow,
he'll get cut up
before he can draw his sword.
(laughing)
The rumor is
they're training him
for sumo out there.
What?
Worse than that,
the stable master
heard what's going on,
and he's willing to let
Toramaru come back
and continue
training with us
if he wants to.
It's a mystery.
I don't know why Oyakata
keeps defending
that blockhead.
(grunts)
(gasps)
Huh, what's the matter?
Are you all right?
Find Toramaru.
I wanna know
where he is.
What?
Didn't I make myself clear?
Absolutely.
-Of course, sir.
-Right away.
♪
Senryoyama's guys
have been sneaking
around outside.
Yeah, they think they're
being inconspicuous.
I noticed them earlier.
Something's going on,
but I don't know
what it's all about.
It's gotta have
something to do
with the other day, but what?
Kenshin, Tae is here.
She's got a question.
She wants to talk to you.
Is Toramaru here
at the dojo?
Not right now,
he's over at the shrine
training with Kori
and the girls, why?
♪
Delicious.
This fried rice is
exceptionally wonderful today.
That's because
Kenshin made it for us.
He's the best cook
in the dojo!
I don't know what
the problem is.
I try and try,
but I can't make
a good rice ball.
You can't help it, Kori,
you're a terrible cook.
Hey!
(laughing)
Toramaru.
What do you guys want?
I want Toramaru.
I hear our stable master
might allow him to come back.
Well, I'm not gonna
let that happen.
If he were
to come back,
it would corrupt the
discipline of the stable.
To prevent that,
I've decided
to end his career.
Wait a minute.
What do you mean
when you say
you're gonna
"end his career"?
You want me to be specific?
I'm going to beat him
so he'll never be able
to do sumo again!
You'll have to get
through me first, you jerk!
Toramaru,
take the two girls
and get them back
to the compound.
All right.
Stay where you are!
Ow!
You witch!
Back off!
If you think I'm just
a helpless girl, come on!
You better have
a good doctor!
(whacking)
(grunting)
Hey, he's skipping out.
What?
(whack)
♪
Don't let him get away.
-Yes sir!
♪
See how they like this.
(rumbling)
♪
Kori, I'm coming!
Amazing.
(gasps)
(shrieks)
Toramaru, they're
gonna be crushed!
♪
You saved us!
Kenshin!
Are you interfering
again, samurai?
We'll be glad
to beat you, too.
Hey, include me in.
I hate to see my
friends have all the fun.
Yeah, me too.
You blubber bellies
aren't so tough.
We'll show you
how tough we are.
We'll take on all of you!
(grunting)
♪
Hmph, these aren't sumos.
They're thugs with sticks.
(grunting)
If you're such good sumos,
why don't you attack
with your bare hands!
♪
Back him into a corner
and finish him off.
Kenshin!
It's all right,
don't do anything.
(whimpers)
Coward!
♪
(whacks)
How boring.
That's all
these guys had?
What?
Who are those brats?
Where did they come from?
Are you ready
to listen now?
Mm-hmm.
Answer one question for me.
Why are you so anxious
to get rid of someone
as gentle as Toramaru?
Why?!
Because he's
a yellow-bellied coward
and an embarrassment
to the Hamakaze Stable.
That's what you say, Senryoyama.
Tell me the real reason.
Huh?
You're calling me a liar!
That is a real reason.
For such an insult,
I should stomp you to pieces.
Why waste time with me?
Your real opponent is Toramaru.
Huh?
You must've lost your mind.
Toramaru has no chance
against Senryoyama.
You know that!
I'm not so sure about that.
He's a lot stronger
than he appears.
You should've seen him today.
Come on, show him
what you're made of.
You can do it!
Uh, but at the time
I was desperate.
I don't think
I could do that again.
(laughs)
You country bumpkin,
I'm ready to wrestle.
But I bet you don't
have the courage
to go toe-to-toe.
Go ahead, Toramaru!
You can do it.
You're the champion!
I want to,
but my legs won't move.
Oh boy!
Hey, whatcha doing?
Toramaru, snap out of it!
Get moving!
Ah!
(grunts)
Thanks, Kori.
You girls have inspired me
to take on that bully.
I'm ready!
-Yay!
All right, let's do it.
Hmm?
♪
This'll be a short fight,
you loser.
Get ready.
Go!
(shouting)
Oh yeah?
♪
Toramaru!
Whoa.
(grunts)
Hm, whoa.
That was unbelievable.
-Hooray, Toramaru wins!
-Champion, you won!
-You did it, you did it!
So, Senryoyama,
I guess this is
what you were afraid of.
Oyakata.
Wha-what's going on?
You know very well
what's going on, Senryoyama.
You've been aware of
Toramaru's hidden talent
for some time.
But you were afraid
that someday he would
replace you as the number
one sumo in the stable,
so you made his
life miserable,
forcing him to run away.
You're saying Toramaru is
more talented than Senryoyama?
I'm surprised
you didn't pick up
on his natural abilities.
When he was thrown by
Senryoyama the other day,
his flexibility helped
him to avoid landing
on the child's toy.
And when the column
was about to crush Kori,
he tossed it aside
like a piece of paper.
He's the most talented
sumo wrestler I've ever seen!
The others were just too
jealous to tell him the truth.
I knew I was right about him!
I just had a feeling.
I guess I'm a better
judge of talent
than you thought,
Mr. Smarty.
This guy's gonna be
a grand champion.
Yeah, I guess
his only problem
is a lack of self-confidence.
We can work on that.
We can?
I'd be glad to
keep training you,
if you'd like
to come back.
Huh?
Would I like
to come back?
Of course!
I'm so happy
for you, Toramaru.
Yeah, me too!
We should all be happy
for you, Toramaru.
But if certain people
can't overcome their pride,
they may have
to leave the stable.
If you have the true spirit
of a champion sumo wrestler,
Senryoyama, you should
swallow that pride
and train Toramaru.
Help him achieve his dreams,
and you can make up
for what you've done.
What do you think, Oyakata?
Would that work?
If Toramaru is willing
to forgive Senryoyama
for his behavior.
I'll tell you this, Toramaru,
it would be
to your advantage.
Sumo is like any
other martial art.
You have to go up
against a tough opponent
to improve your
skills and advance.
(groaning)
You are right!
I wanna train
to be the very best
that I can be.
So, I ask you,
please help train me.
I'm touched.
♪
(birds chirping)
We haven't seen Toramaru
for quite a while now.
I wonder how his
training is coming along.
Hello, everybody.
-Huh?
-Hmm?
♪
It's Toramaru!
Toramaru!
Wow, his ears
must've been burning.
We're glad to see
you, Toramaru.
Don't tell us you ran
away from the stable again.
No, everything's
going very well there.
I just wanted to thank you for
all that you've done for me,
so I brought you
two bags of rice
with all the money
I've been saving.
That's very nice of you.
Let me help you
with those.
Oh!
(gasps)
Are you all right, Kenshin?
Well, he may be
a champion sumo,
but he's still
a bit of a blockhead.
Gotta tell you,
Kenshin's not much better.
He may be number
one at sword play,
but when it comes to taking
on a couple of rice bags,
he's not too bright.
You're right!
(voice wavers)
(laughing)
♪
(singing in foreign language)