♪
(grunts)
So much of warfare
fought in modern times
depends on who has the
greater number of troops.
This is decidedly different.
I love the feel of
battling one on one.
Meldars' master plan
is to take over the world.
He fancies
himself to be
the chivalrous
knight battling me,
who he sees
as inferior.
I must stop him,
no matter what the cost.
(grunts)
♪
He got him!
Come on, Kenshin, don't
let him get away with that!
Lay some Kuzurysen
on that jerk!
It's impossible.
With him up on horseback,
it's just not that easy.
Even with Kenshin's
leaping ability,
he can't get above Meldars
to deliver a killer blow.
As the Mongols
taught the Chinese,
you have to kill
the horse first.
That's how to
bring a rider down.
Kenshin can stop an
attacker on horseback,
but we've never seen
anyone ride like this.
♪
(horse neighs)
The way they move,
it's as though Meldars
and the horse
are one being.
That's true.
Besides, Kenshin's used
to fighting samurais
with short swords, not a knight
with a long jousting pole.
Are you saying he
hasn't got a chance?
♪
Simple physics of
him being on that horse
adds too much energy
to his every move.
(grunts)
If I don't get in closer
and take out his horse,
I haven't got a chance.
(grunting)
(yells)
Looks like
even Battosai
can't give Meldars
a good challenge.
(groaning)
So, Battosai, is
that the best effort
the Japanese can muster?
You talk a good game,
but I don't think
you can deliver.
(groaning)
There's no edge
on his sword.
He can't win.
You don't know
much about Kenshin.
I do know a reverse edge
sword is useless in battle.
You can't kill
with that sword.
That's why he's
got that sword.
He stopped killing
people a long time ago.
He's not a slasher anymore,
but he'll find a way to win.
Huh?
He is trying to
protect people,
not bend other people
to his will like you are!
Ha, from his looks
he'll be lucky
if he can protect himself.
No one can stop me,
and once I get a
hold of the medicine
I'll be invincible.
The Black Knights
will soon rule the world.
A new world,
a new world order
where we will
bury your kind.
This new world order of
yours will only promote hate.
Any new world order
should foster peace,
acceptance
and understanding.
You must be stopped
or innocent people
will have their lives
snuffed out by your mob.
And you can't stop it!
I will stop you
with all that I have.
I'm ready!
♪
So, you're ready, huh?
(laughing sinisterly)
♪
I must kill you,
you oriental monkey!
♪
You and your people
have no sense
of the history of the
Order of the Black Knights
and how through the
ages we have perfected
our techniques for warfare.
Our order was born
in medeival times
and over the centuries
we have created strategies
that have been refined
far beyond anything
you rice eaters
could develop.
Our ideas were
battle-tested
under so many
different conditions
it boggles the mind
and our individual
skills are superior
to your inferior
knowledge of combat.
Your people
know nothing!
This is the end.
Your crude attempts must
be eliminated permanently.
The way you monkey
people use your swords
is an abomination to us.
You have fought well
against my Lentz,
I will try to make
your death painless.
Have you had your say?
Even with all that talk,
I'll make this
painless for you.
You are dead!
From the front?
Don't do it!
Kenshin!
Mitsurugi!
♪
He did it!
That was fantastic!
Great job!
Yoshi was right.
Looks like Kuzurysen got
him close enough to strike.
Looks like Kenshin's
blow has taken its toll.
How did he do that?
(groaning)
Why didn't I take
him more serious?
♪
(groaning)
(laughing evilly)
Well, that was
quite a test!
♪
(snickering)
He's not even hurt!
♪
You know what
you fight like?
A blind baboon!
♪
Now you die!
(yells)
♪
(laughing)
He's barely
surviving against
the superiority
of a Black Knight.
Is that the way
of the samurai?
You know nothing!
Look how pathetic he is.
(grunting)
♪
Hmm?
What's he doing?
Oh no!
Huh?
The medicine
will be destroyed.
What?
(horse neighs)
Lentz, move it!
Lentz, get over here.
I need some of these plants
collected for chemical analysis.
Move it!
We have to put
out the fire.
Misanagi, you can't,
you're hurt.
Besides, in a
matter of seconds,
that fire will hit the
oil reserves and explode.
Yutaro!
You want to show
off or something?
Stop that!
Yoshi!
What are
they thinking?
I'll get 'em!
But Sano, please wait!
You must wonder why
I keep toying with you.
I wanted to see you beg.
But that's enough.
Now it's time to
finish you off.
(yells)
I wasn't able to kill you the
last time I had the chance.
This time you will die
slowly and painfully.
I don't think so,
you overgrown ass!
(yells)
(shouting)
Yoshi!
(gasps)
♪
Why is he taking
that stance?
That's the stance used for
Amakakeru Ryu no Hirameki.
But how could his sword move
fast enough for it to work?
Kenshin's lost a
lot of strength.
With Meldars
so high on that horse,
I can't understand
Kenshin's thinking.
Just let him live.
♪
(urges horse)
(grunts)
♪
(snickers)
Oh no!
(shudders)
♪
Against me, I knew even
Japan's greatest would fail.
Cause you're all
just monkeys, huh?
Whoa!
What the hell?
(yelling)
Kenshin beat Meldars.
He chose not to beat
him with his sword,
but with his
brains instead.
Meldars was convinced that
he could only be beaten
with a samurai sword.
Kenshin created a vacuum
with his sword's movement
and he made sure that fire
would fill that vacuum
right where
Meldars stopped.
♪
Kenshin!
Please, Kenshin, be alive.
Now, you both will die!
(grunts)
Now the fun begins.
I look forward to
cutting off your arms
and lopping off your
feet might be appropriate
so you won't be able to run
away from the pain and agony.
I want to kill you
and all your people.
And you call
yourself a knight?
Huh?
You are the lowest
scum on Earth.
You must be
exterminated.
(growls)
You must die first!
(grunts)
(groans)
It looks like
you killed him.
I had to, there's no
honor in extermination
but a hatemonger
should be annihilated.
Wow!
What the heck
was that explosion?
The fire's finally reached
some of the oil reserves.
That's the end
of the medicine.
We better get everyone out
of here or we'll be killed.
♪
Hmm.
-Yoshi.
-Huh?
Hold my sword.
-Wha-- wait!
-Yutaro!
-Don't!
-Stop!
Yoshi.
Why'd he run
into the fire?
To get the
miracle medicine.
What?
Why'd he do
something like that?
He'll get killed.
Damn it,
I'm going after him.
You stay here and gather up
Kaoru and your other friends.
♪
All three of them.
I hope they live.
You have
got to believe.
Sano will rescue them.
♪
(grunting)
I think we better leave.
It's too dangerous.
I think I'll stay here.
Everything that I believed could
help us has been destroyed.
It's gone,
it's all in shambles.
I'm sorry.
I'm partly to
blame for taking
so much away
from you, Misanagi,
but once I really
knew you, I changed.
I want to help you.
Our ancestors were
the same kind of people,
fiercely dedicated
to their causes,
but the Black Knight
motives are twisted.
I see that now.
Please forgive me
for ever hurting you.
You don't have
to apologize.
When it comes
to this situation,
we've all made mistakes.
I thank you.
I'm grateful you chose to save
my life, but now it's over.
One setback
and you give up?
Life's more precious
than that, Misanagi,
don't just throw us away.
Wait, what do you mean "us"?
You've been saying that your
life's not worth living.
Well, you're wrong.
I have risked my
own life to save you.
I would not put my life
on the line for anyone
I did not feel
was important.
Doesn't that
mean something?
To give up on your life now,
is to do a disservice to me
and to your ancestors as well.
Don't give up on life.
Besides, you and I
still have so much to do.
That's right!
Kaita!
♪
(breathing heavily)
Huh?
♪
Lieutenant Meldars!
Lieutenant!
♪
(gasps)
It's gone.
My master plan
went up in smoke
and I'm the one
who lit the fire.
All I have left
is nothing but ashes.
(laughing maniacally)
♪
No, don't go!
Schneider!
Go.
Leave this
hell and live.
I love you!
Misanagi!
♪
Why?
(grunting softly)
Where-- where is it?
Yutaro!
There's no use in you
taking anymore chances here.
So much of your life
is still ahead of you.
You can't become a doctor
if you don't stay alive.
I believe in you
and your future.
Now, let's get going.
Boy, it sure is a neat feeling
when people believe in you.
Now, I know what it feels
like to be a birthday cake
baking in an oven,
but let's put that idea
on the backburner for now.
Now, what are
we going to do?
(horse neighs)
Hmm?
(horse whinnies)
I can't believe Yutaro left his
most prized possession with me.
Maybe I should
have been nicer to him.
Huh?
♪
Six-five Sanosuke
saves the day.
It's all right,
I came back, Yoshi!
Why are you making such a
big deal about it, Yutaro?
It sure took
you two long enough
to figure out how
to get back here.
So, I'd say we found out
that samurais like Kenshin
are not to be trifled with.
We saw the bushido style
for fighting works.
Pretty impressive, eh Lentz?
(groans)
♪
I thought that unifying
our Sanada ninja group
with the Black Knights
would help us,
but these
creatures from Europe
have no sense of honor.
They failed and broke the
promises they made to us.
Not only did they fail,
I failed as well.
I was vigilant about
the Black Knights actions,
but the great gift
our ancestors left us,
the holy medicine,
was destroyed.
I'm willing to
accept any punishment
the group sees
fit to give me.
That is enough, Misanagi.
You did everything
that you could
to further the goals
of our Sanada group.
What happened was
beyond your control.
I know it!
But I--
I believe that
Kaita is right.
We know our group's power
has been declining
since the end
of the Tokugawa era.
We also knew it was a risk to
align ourself with foreigners,
but now is the time we
really need to pull together.
With our strength united,
we will stand tall.
Chara speaks the truth!
Yes, Misanagi
should be our leader!
We must make
our group stronger
and Misanagi is
a brave leader!
Besides, she's better
looking than any of you.
(laughing)
That's an insult considering
the way you look, Soricho.
Well, you're not exactly a
wood carving yourself, Rachiro.
(group all laughing)
♪
(crying)
Schneider,
you saved my life.
You told me not to
give up on my dreams.
I only wish you were here,
so I could share
my love with you.
♪
(groaning)
Sano, he's conscious!
Really, he is?
I'd better get Megumi!
♪
Huh, so you're saying this
little plant saved my life?
I used an extract
from that root
to save you from wounds
that should have killed you.
So, that means...
This is it!
The holy medicine.
Mm-hmm.
That is it.
That root is from a
flowering plant we found.
It's the miracle medicine
we've dreamed and talked of.
It really is a
miracle medicine.
With the wounds you had,
you really had no chance.
Your breathing and
pulse were so low,
I thought within
minutes you'd be dead,
but that extract
stabilized you
and your recovery's
been unbelievable.
Hey, Dr. Hans,
there's a letter for you
from the German consulate.
♪
It says that Lentz
and Schneider,
the last two members
of the Black Knights,
have been found.
They turned themselves
in to the authorities,
but that's not all.
They plan on going
back to Germany
and dismantling the
rest of the Black Knights.
This really signals the
end of the Black Knights.
So, it's safe to
go back to Germany?
Mm-hmm.
♪
It's hard to imagine I may
never see this dojo again.
I learned so much here.
Not just about fighting, but
about how to live life as well.
♪
(yelling)
Try again and keep
your feet facing forward.
(yelling)
♪
He was standing there alone?
I guess Yutaro's really
gonna miss being here.
We should do
something nice for him.
After all, he's
really a great kid.
Let's give him a
special going away gift.
I think I know exactly
what he would like to have.
(ship's horn blows)
I just can't see
you quitting kendo!
You'd better not!
Take it easy, Yoshi.
Yutaro's chosen to continue
studying medicine instead.
He must follow his heart.
Right, a hunter
who chases two rabbits
winds up with
nothing for dinner.
We all wish you
lots of luck.
But we wanted you to have this
special gift from us, Yutaro.
The Kamiya Kasshin
spirit will assist you
in your studies
of medicine.
I'm letting you
off easy, buddy,
but if you don't live with
the spirit of Kamiya Kasshin,
I swear, I'll
come over there.
You understand me?
Understood.
I'll be the first
Kasshin doctor.
All right!
And we'll compete
to see which one
becomes the best
in his field.
Okay?
You bet,
and I'll win.
♪
Miss Kaoru?
What, Kenshin?
With Yutaro and
Yoshi as students,
your Kamiya Kasshin style
has a bright future.
(ship's horn blows)
♪
You are a lucky
young man, Yutaro.
You have many friends.
Huh?
I'm a very
lucky man as well,
because I have a
bright, disciplined,
young man as my protege.
You, Yutaro.
Thank you, sir, I appreciate
your praise, Dr. Hans.
Yes, someday, the
world will be proud of you.
♪
Yutaro, if you
want to be great,
then dedicate yourself
to always doing your best.
I-- I promise.
That's the spirit.
Being with those friends
has made you even stronger.
You're right, they
gave me love and respect
that I will
remember always.
♪
I thank my good friends
at the Kamiya dojo.
Sanosuke, Kaoru,
Yoshi, Misao,
my deepest
thanks go to you,
and most of all,
thanks Kenshin.
♪