(theme music)
♪
(loud clashing)
Found it.
A sensei saved my life
with this medicine.
Now, he's the one
who needs some.
I can't go down the mountain
and look for a doctor.
There isn't enough time.
I'll just have
to rely on his medicine
and hope that it works as well
for him as it did for me.
♪
It's gotta work.
Just as I planned.
I knew I couldn't find Kenshin
without having any
idea where he was,
so I got myself arrested
'cause I figured that
you police would know
where I should look.
I figure you're
looking for him too,
so we're on the same
side here, right?
♪
Listen, I can handle myself
if that's what
you're worried about.
Come on in and I'll give you
a little demonstration.
Any idea who he is?
No, I've never seen him before.
Me either.
Probably a case
of mistaken identity,
but we better keep him
locked up 'til we're sure.
You better let me out of here,
'cause if you don't,
I'll let myself out!
(footsteps)
What the...
Ohh.
Don't look so surprised.
I told you I could
take care of myself.
You could end up
just like that door.
-Is that so?
-Don't worry about it, Chief.
If you don't mind,
I'd like to handle this my way.
I'd like you to wait
for me upstairs, all right?
Good, we can have
a nice little chat
and you can answer
all my questions.
And the first question is,
what did you mean when you said
you were gonna
handle this your way?
Ah.
I see that your style
is somewhat similar
to the Watermark technique,
though yours isn't as effective,
and from what I've seen,
not nearly as strong.
You're all offense--
no defense.
Huh?
(laughing)
Mm mmm.
Hey, you take
your hands off of me,
why don't you, Saito?
You don't win fights
with defense.
You gotta attack.
So, keep your
advice to yourself.
I'll fight my way.
Wow, you're even denser
than I thought you were.
Hey, we're not through yet!
Sorry, kid, I'm busy.
Make an appointment.
Hey, you're running away
'cause you don't wanna fight.
You know you can't
win this time.
Fine, whatever.
(grunting)
Hey!
That's not fair,
you gotta fight!
Come on, you!
Turn around
and fight with me!
Huh?
Why the big security lock?
What do ya got in there?
Answers, I hope.
A guy that just might
be able to tell us
what Shishio's plans are.
He's one of
Shishio's mercenaries.
Calls himself Cho,
the sword hunter.
You guys sure are noisy.
I can't sleep with you guys
making all that commotion,
you know?
I don't think that's very
considerate, do you?
Let's just cut the crap.
I need you to answer
a couple of questions.
Ha!
My first question's
about the Kobe incident.
One night, 50 expert fighters,
members of the police force,
and the army were taken
out by a lone assassin.
Can you think of anyone among
Shishio's Juppongatana group
who could've pulled off
an attack like this?
I could,
and so could just about
any of Shishio's assassins.
It wasn't that tough,
they had lousy security.
And you're a liar.
Now, tell me the truth.
Hey, don't call me a liar.
I mean, why should I?
Stop it, you're
just wasting time.
Tell the truth
and I'll talk
to the authorities
and get you outta here.
There's no one
out there I wanna see
and no particular
place I wanna go.
What you mean is
you're afraid of Shishio.
It doesn't really matter
what you tell us.
He'll have you killed anyway
because you're not supposed
to let yourself fall
into the hands of the enemy.
It's safer in here
where he can't get to you.
Isn't that right?
Hey, you can think
whatever you want,
but I ain't talking.
And I'm not afraid of anyone--
Shishio or anybody else.
So, if you think I'm a coward,
you better think again,
you big bird brain.
I was up the entire night,
and when I get cranky,
I get real tired,
so don't start calling me names
unless you want
a fight, asparagus head.
(spits)
(electricity zapping)
Let's go, vegetable stock.
Listen to the birdie sing.
All right, let's do it.
Rutabaga leaf!
Fish bone breath!
Celery with endive!
Chicken lips!
If you win, I'll
answer your questions.
Come on, let's do it.
Right!
(together)
Don't just stand there,
give us some kind of
start signal, will ya?
As soon as it hits the floor.
(grunting)
Ahh!
Hi-yah!
Well, what do you know?
Looks like you lose,
fish breath.
-What?
-Ah!
I had to get rid of
those manacles for ya,
otherwise it wouldn't be
a fair fight, now would it?
Yeah, right.
We'll take off those nasty
leg shackles, as well, 'kay?
N--I...
Y-You don't need to do that.
You made your point.
Say it.
You win,
I lose.
There's no way I can beat you,
and you're right,
I'm a dead man if I leave,
so go ahead and ask
your questions.
Mmm hmm.
Now that we're all
on the same page,
you can start by answering
the question I asked earlier.
(simultaneously)
Neither one of us is the winner.
He is.
I need the name of someone who
could've killed all those men.
Fifty men in two or three hours.
Know of anyone
who could handle that?
Sure do.
Juppongatana has
two guys coulda done it.
More than one?
You gotta be kidding me, right?
You said 50 guys in
a couple of hours, right?
Listen, if it weren't
for the time limit,
I coulda done it myself.
Oh, I get it.
That means that if it
weren't for the time limit,
anybody in Juppongatana
could've pulled it off.
Huh?
That's not what I said!
It's true, though, since
everyone else in the group
is a lot better than you are.
(grunting)
I'm gonna make you sorry
you were born, gamecock.
I'm gonna really enjoy this,
asparagus head!
I'm still waiting for a name.
One of the guys I'm talking
about is called Sojiro.
He's the one that uses
the Heaven's Sword technique.
Thought so.
But he couldn't have
been the one who did it
'cause he was on
a recruiting trip
in East Japan when it happened.
And that means...
That's right,
wasn't him.
So, it had to be the other one.
♪
(groaning)
Finally, the whole Juppongatana
is going to meet.
Ten of the most loyal
swordsman in Japan,
all of them loyal to Shishio.
Some of them have
already arrived.
Anji and Hayara showed up
just a few hours ago.
The others will be here shortly.
Mr. Hoji!
The compound's been attacked!
No one saw the intruder.
He took out five of our
sentries, then disappeared.
It's as if he just
vanished into thin air.
This compound is more secure
than any place in Japan.
How could this have happened?
Mr. Shishio, I've sent
Anji to locate the intruder,
so we'll know his identity
and why he murdered our men.
But I already know who did it.
A member of the Juppongatana.
It was one of ours?
In fact, he's with us right now.
-What?
-I don't see anyone.
♪
Oh, no, look!
(metal clanging)
You're much better
now than before.
Usui, it was you!
May I present
the world's greatest
blind swordsman, Usui.
Usui was called
the blind sword,
and he was one of
the greatest swordsmen
in Japan at the end
of the Tokugawa era.
He and Shishio
fought each other once.
Usui was slashed across
the face during the fight
and lost his sight in both eyes.
So, Shishio helped him develop
the Blind Sword technique
called Shingun,
or "eyes of the heart,"
and now he's even deadlier
than when he could see.
He's a stone-cold killer
and he loves his work.
What are you so mad about?
The deal was
I can take out
whoever I want,
whenever I want.
We made a bargain, right?
And that was one
of the conditions,
otherwise I wouldn't
have come here.
-Would I?
-I doubt it.
When I made that deal with you,
I never imagined that you went
to attack and slaughter
a half a dozen members
of our security squad.
I've had the good fortune
to kill over 200 men,
but for practice,
only live targets
produce verifiable results.
Ever been to Kobe?
Ran across it on my way here.
Killed 10 men for every finger.
Fifty men in just two hours.
Usui, did you see a man there
whose face was marked with
a scar that looked like a cross?
Or a guy who looks
sort of like a tall,
lean wolf, named Misato?
Afraid not.
I would appreciate the end
of their existence...
very much.
Agreed.
Those two guys scare you,
for some reason, don't they?
(gasping)
And our leaders shouldn't
be scared of anyone.
Isn't that right, old friend?
Blind Sword and Heaven's Sword.
Sojiro and Usui,
they are the strongest.
I'm telling you, even
you couldn't handle Usui.
The guy's so fast
you can't even see
what he's doing.
Well, we'll just
have to see about that.
One more question.
We know Shishio is planning
to take control of the country.
Is it also true...
that his scheme...
includes the full
destruction of Edo?
What?
A plan to destroy Edo?
♪
I'll ask you again.
Just how does Shishio
intend to destroy Edo?
♪
Sorry, force of habit.
I'll tell you two
whatever I can.
You two know anything
about the Ikedaya incident?
♪
No, not any of the details.
Oh.
Ikedaya.
A long time ago
it was an inn in Edo.
(screaming)
A faction of the
Meiji Restoration Royalists
met there in order to plan
the assassination of important
government and public officials,
but the Shinsen
group found out,
and none of the
royalists got out alive.
The plan had called for 500
soldiers to shoot liquid fire
into the Edo Business District
and reduce it to ruins.
And for the covert assassination
of certain influential people
during the fire and confusion.
That's where Shishio
got the idea for his plan.
It's payback time.
Using a plan created
by the same Royalists
who tried to burn him to death
in order to get his revenge.
Figures, right?
That's just like him.
A knife in the ribs
isn't enough.
He has to twist it a little
before he's finished.
The plan's supposed
to be carried out soon,
right after all the guys
in Juppongatana
go to meet Shishio--
not just soon, very soon.
♪
I see.
Edo is an important
symbol of stability
to everyone in Japan,
and its destruction would
have grave consequences,
such as confusion
and a lack of confidence
in our government,
just what Shishio
needs to take control.
Politics, I'm sick of politics!
There's only one thing
that matters to me:
the people of Edo.
It's been 10 years since
the turmoil at the end
of the Tokugawa era,
and people have finally
learned to live in peace,
but now Shishio's ambition
and the government's
stubbornness
are going to ruin
everything...again!
No one's gonna destroy Edo.
I won't allow it!
Glad to hear it.
We've also gotta watch
the Shinsen group.
They'll use an emergency
as a means of taking control
of the whole country.
What?
I never thought that you
and I would agree on anything.
Hmm.
Oh, well, looks like we'll
have to finish our fight
another time.
Right now, what we gotta do
is find Kenshin.
Yes, it'd be a waste of time
for us to fight each other.
We've got to find
Kenshin immediately.
Well, don't just sit there,
bird brain, get moving.
We've got a lot of work to do.
Or weren't you paying attention?
Hey, don't order me around.
I'm not working for you.
All right, stay here.
Locked up with asparagus head?
No thanks!
Move your tail
feathers, bird brain.
-Don't call me bird brain!
-Okay, chicken lips.
♪
I'm home.
-Thank goodness.
-What's wrong?
What are you so upset about?
(panting)
Where have you been?
I was going crazy being
stuck out here for so long,
so I went into town
and got some really
tasty desserts
for us to nibble on.
Calm down,
don't worry,
I got the kind you
like, too, Ayumi.
So, that's why you were
gone for three days?
Yeah, I couldn't decide
which ones to get.
You don't know
what happened here.
That madman, Usui is
completely out of control.
And what did Usui do?
Hey, Blind Sword, man,
it's nice to see you again.
Here, have some.
(sniffing)
Yatsuhashi.
You offer sweets
and sweetness, Sojiro,
but your soul is
covered with frost.
You have your own agenda,
and you think that you're
a whole lot smarter
than the rest of us are.
Eyes of the heart,
see through the
deception of your smile
to the emptiness
of your inner core.
(laughing)
Right now, whatever
it is you're hiding
is none of my concern.
(groaning)
Oh, one more thing.
The meeting will begin
in just a few minutes.
Everyone has finally arrived,
and once we've
gotten organized,
nothing is going to stop us.
Hi, Kamatari.
Sojiro, how are you?
Ayumi, it's good
to see you again.
It's been a long time.
So, you're still
with Shishio, huh?
That's really surprising
considering the fact that
he only likes younger women.
You're wrong,
he likes women
who have the experience
to give a guy what he wants,
like good advice.
Sure.
You youngsters are
so entertaining.
Mr. Saizuchi,
why you look younger every year.
Heh, I tell myself that,
but I'm a liar like you.
At least you make an
attempt at civility, Sojiro.
Most young people have no
respect for their elders.
I could teach 'em a lesson
by turning them into toads,
but I'm not responsible
for their manners.
Right.
Where's Fuji?
Hasn't that guy always
been your right-hand man?
Oh, he's outside,
he's superstitious.
He said this place
gave him the willies.
Everyone is here,
let's begin.
♪
Sorry I was gone for so long.
I brought you a really
tasty treat, Boss.
Oh?
♪
It's terrific,
try some.
Another time.
Right now he's got more
important things to do.
It's really quite good.
♪
Thanks, Sojiro,
I'll eat it later.
Hmm.
Welcome to you all.
Thank you for being here today.
I also want to thank you
for adjusting your schedules
due to the delay,
which was necessary
because of the
negligence of Cho,
who used to be one of us.
Though he can't be with us
on this momentous occasion,
I am glad to see that every
other member of our group,
the Juppongatana, has shown
their loyalty and dedication
by honoring their pledge
to attend this meeting.
Sojiro...
Anji...
Henya...
Iwambo...
Hoji, Ayumi...Kamatari.
Right here.
Usui, my old friend,
the time has come
to destroy the government.
We'll begin the Edo Fire Plan
tomorrow night at 11:59
and the city will be destroyed!
Edo will burn to the ground!
(birds chirping)
Hey, wake up sleepy head.
Huh?
You told me all about the ones
that were waiting for you
back home and you
also told me how much
they were counting
on you, right?
It's time for you to
get a move on, Kenshin.
Huh, huh?
Sensei?
Sensei, ahh!
I got a thing about
men trying to hug me.
It's just not my cup
of tea, understand?
Sensei, the medicine worked,
you're not sick anymore.
Huh?
Well, you're wrong about that.
None of this stuff has
any medicinal value at all.
It couldn't even
cure a runny nose.
Huh?
But, wait, I don't understand.
You will, in time.
Know what this is?
Sure I do, it's
a reversed-edged sword.
Look more closely.
You see this peg
below the haft?
It's like a spring,
it helps absorb the force
of an opponent's blow,
so that my hand remains steady.
This is an excellent sword
that can intuit the purpose
of the person who wields it.
(gasping)
Mr. Shakku.
I've kept the secret
of the nail for many years.
In fact, I thought that
I would never tell anyone,
yet I sense that now
the time has come for me
to pass this knowledge
on to another,
to someone who I believe
will use it wisely.
Huh?
But, you must promise to
develop your technique alone,
within no boundaries,
with the freedom known
only to a wanderer.
So, you are forbidden
to swear allegiance to anyone.
Do you understand?
Yes.
♪
Thank you, Sensei.
Kenshin, wait.
This is the cape given
to each new generation
of the Hiten Mitsurugi style.
It's the proof that
you've finally succeeded.
It's yours.
You have earned it,
and you deserve it.
I'm honored, but
must humbly decline.
It's just not my style.
True, it's not.
Sensei, as much as
I respect and honor you,
I can't follow the path
you've chosen for your life.
I must choose another way
and create my own life's work.
I can't tell you
how grateful I am
for all the things
you've taught me.
I respect your decision,
you certainly earned the right.
Huh, I'll just keep it
for old times' sake.
♪
Sensei, one last request.
I need help.
While I am away fighting
the Juppongatana,
would you see to it that
the people in Aoiya
aren't left unprotected?
♪
-Certainly...
-Oh.
...not!
I can't believe
you have the nerve
to ask me for anything.
To choose your way in place
of the Hiten Mitsurugi style.
Ha!
You're no longer my pupil.
Forget I was your sensei.
Sensei, wait!
Now, I will have to begin
the search for another student
who can succeed me as the master
of the Hiten Mitsurugi style.
♪
May good fortune
always follow you.
Goodbye, Kenshin.
♪
There are bandits everywhere.
No place is safe these days.
Hi-yah!
Why are the police here?
What's wrong?
Nowadays, it seems there are
policeman everywhere you look.
♪
Fujita!
Have I got news for you,
just wait 'til you hear this.
I just found out about it,
I can hardly believe it.
Battousai the Slasher,
the legendary swordsman,
is coming here right now.
Some villager down in the valley
was taking a walk
and spotted him.
I sent a carriage
to pick him up.
Ooh.
Mother Magri,
I think it's him!
♪
He's different.
What has Kenshin seen?
What has he learned
that could have
changed him so much?
♪
(theme music)