♪
(grunting)
Aoshi, listen to me.
Your thought processes are all
wrong and you've lost focus.
You can't defeat me and
I refuse to kill you.
Instead, I have
chosen a technique
that will cause
temporary paralysis.
You can be redeemed.
Think about your
friends who are now gone
and the ones
you've endangered.
You must waken your
sleeping conscience.
Beshimi.
Hyottoko.
Shikijo.
Han'nya.
And of course, Misao.
♪
(footsteps running)
Why rush?
It's already too late.
What?
You believe you're in
control of the situation,
but the truth is, you're running
in place and losing ground.
I don't have time to
listen to your nonsense.
Our friends are in danger
and we're gonna rescue them.
You're not going
to rescue anyone.
It's an empty gesture.
The die has
already been cast,
and your friends
don't have a prayer.
Stop babbling, what
are you talking about?
You think the Juupongatana
is made up of fools?
Right now, our secret weapon
is arriving in Aoiya.
You're bluffing, lady.
She doesn't sound
like she's bluffing,
and it wouldn't surprise
me if these people
had a few tricks
up their sleeves.
I just hope we make
it there in time.
♪
(shouting)
I am Hennya, winged warrior
of the Juupongatana.
No matter what kind of sword
technique you've mastered,
you're helpless
against fighting me.
I attack from the air.
It's the one angle from
which you have no defense.
(growls)
You challenged me to
kill you if I could.
Not only will
I take your life,
but I'll take my time and
blow you apart piece by piece.
♪
Huh?
(grunts)
(yelling)
♪
I've got a way to
defeat this bird-brain.
It's my responsibility
to take care of this.
I promised Kenshin.
You know I can help out!
I've been training
really hard with Kaoru
and I've improved a lot.
How about giving
me a chance
to show you
what I've learned?
Let me come with
you, and Kenshin,
I can beat anybody
in a fair fight.
♪
Listen, I believe you,
but that's why
you have to stay.
I need someone
I can trust
to protect everyone
while I'm gone.
I can't let Kenshin down.
I swore that I'd
protect everybody
and that's what
I'm gonna do.
(grunts)
(groans)
Gotta hang on.
Ouch, ouch,
hot, hot, hot.
(blowing air)
Hey, watch it,
Dynamite Breath!
If you'd got any closer,
I would have
been barbecued.
You're not much of
a leader, are you?
What are you
talking about?
Bat Boy up there
doesn't care who he hits.
You're letting him sacrifice
your men for no reason.
I'll punish you
for that remark.
(shouts)
Come back,
you coward!
♪
Yoshi hasn't
got a chance.
While he tries to recover
from the explosions,
this guy swoops down
and slashes him.
I've got to find
a way to even the fight
before he cuts
us to pieces.
Stop that!
Hold it, missy.
If you are fool enough
to turn your back on me,
I assure you,
you'll regret it.
Since you can't help him,
I advise you
not to interfere.
You're all going
to die in the end anyway.
Oh, you'll
be going first!
(gasps)
If you want to fight,
why don't you both
attack at the same time?
I'm giving you a two to one
advantage, don't waste it.
What more could you ask?
♪
(grunts)
I have to fight back.
But how can I attack him?
He's out of my reach
and he's too fast to
grab when he flies past.
Think, Yoshi,
there must be a way
to get a tactical
advantage over him.
Wait a second.
Getting over him could be
the secret to taking him out.
I bet no one's ever
attacked him from above.
It would be such
an unexpected maneuver,
he'd probably have
no defense for it.
I just have to
figure out a way
to get up high enough
to jump on his back.
Come on now, there has
to be a way to do this.
If I were Kenshin,
I could probably use
my speed and strength
to propel myself up
one of these buildings
and attack him
from they roof.
But I'm not Kenshin, so
I'll have to improvise.
I wish I had wings
or something like wings.
(grunts)
What a shame.
Only one bomb left.
I guess it'll have to do.
(yells)
Yoshi, run!
Get inside the house!
Hurry, come on boy!
Run while you
have the chance.
This is it.
If I'm in the right position
when the bomb goes off,
I can use the
force of the blast
to get me where
I need to be.
(screams)
♪
Hmm!
So much for that
little shrimp.
Must've been
a direct hit.
There's nothing left
even to scrape up.
He should thank me.
No one's going to have to put
out any money for a funeral now.
Unbelievable.
The only funeral around
here is gonna be yours.
Huh?
No, it can't be!
Oh no, he rode some of the
debris to get on top of me.
(yells)
That's it for you!
Time to clip your wings!
The higher they are,
the harder they fall.
(moans)
Atta boy!
Ah, very impressive.
It was a perfect plan.
It's obvious he's
been studying tactics
and strategy from
a very good teacher.
Probably Kenshin,
and it worked.
In a few more
years training,
he'll be one of the
best fighters in Japan.
♪
I had no idea Yoshi
could be so creative
with his battlefield technique.
He really has been paying
attention to my training.
I'm so proud of him
and Kenshin will be too
when I tell
him what happened.
♪
Wow, alright!
Except for the landing,
I had everything figured out.
(muttering in astonishment)
♪
Look at that;
he's killed Hennya.
I thought his aerial
attack was invincible.
♪
That's one down
and two more to go.
-Yeah.
Let's go get 'em.
(coughing)
♪
(sputtering)
Yoshi!
♪
Now, maybe
you'll listen.
I warned you before.
To oppose us is fatal.
Yeah, right!
You don't scare us.
Yoshi's strong.
He won't die
from those wounds.
Now it's our
turn to fight.
♪
If you're no better
than your flying friend,
you better say your prayers.
Hmm, you're a lot
braver than your partner.
She's shaking
like a little girl.
Guess she's not
much of a fighter.
What?
Let me at her!
Calm down, she's
trying to upset you.
The fact is, Kamatari,
that Misao and I
are not that different
when it comes to bravery
on the battlefield.
It's just that
I have more experience.
I fight not as
a woman or a man,
but as a warrior.
I think you'll discover
that I'm not very
different from you.
I see.
However, you're
about to learn
my talent as a warrior
far exceeds your own.
You may be good
with a sword,
but you're no match
for my scythe.
You won't last long.
We have to proceed
very carefully.
Check out her weapon.
Whoa, that thing's humongous.
Looks lethal too.
The handle and
scythe together
must weigh at
least 65 pounds.
Not counting the
weight of the chain
and the iron ball
attached to it.
If she were to
swing and miss,
she'd have an awkward
time repositioning
for another attack.
I think we could
gain a tactical advantage.
So here's my plan.
I'll draw her attack
and jump out of the way.
When she swings and
misses, you take her down.
If we move fast,
one of us will get her.
Just don't forget, Kaoru.
This one's mine.
♪
Come on, what are
you two waiting for?
That's it!
I've really had
enough of you!
(shouting)
♪
Wait, hold on!
(yells)
(grunts)
♪
Misao, no!
(grunts)
(groaning)
Misao!
No, Misao!
(moaning)
Did you take me for
some kind of fool?
I could see what your strategy
was before you even began!
I've faced many opponents
who tried that tactic.
Not one of them was
ever able to beat me.
I'm always a step ahead.
That's why I always win.
And now, my dear,
the coup de gras.
It's time to
end this game.
Nice knowing you.
♪
(growling)
Look, this is it!
Kamatari's death blow!
No one can survive this.
(yelling)
Don't bother running.
Once the scythe has
achieved its full momentum,
it can't be stopped.
It'll cut through
everything in its path.
There must be a way
to overcome this weapon.
She can't be
invulnerable.
Hmm?
Misao, get up!
Come on, Misao.
Kaoru's in trouble.
You've got to
try and help.
♪
Oh.
(soft grunting)
♪
(giggling)
(yelps)
(laughs)
♪
(giggling)
All my old friends.
♪
Misao, wake up.
Open your eyes.
Who are you?
You know me, Misao.
Han'nya?
Why are you here?
I have a message.
Battosai kept
his promise.
Aoshi is coming
back to you.
(gasps)
(moaning)
Must have
been a dream.
Hmm, now I see.
Han'nya came to tell me
it's gonna be all right.
(gasps)
Kaoru!
(moans)
Oh no, my rib is broken,
but I've got to try to help.
Here, Misao!
-Catch!
-Great!
Thanks, Okina.
♪
But what good can I do?
I'm weak.
I can't get to her
through that weapon.
The only thing I can hit
is-- yes, that's it.
Kaoru!
I'm here to
back you up.
(shouts)
Forget it.
It's a wasted effort.
(grunting)
♪
I thought she was
just aiming at me!
She was aiming
at the weapon.
I'm defenseless.
(growls)
Well Kamatari,
perhaps we're not
as experienced
as you in battle,
but we know something
about strategy.
Faced with a
superior weapon,
we needed to level
the playing field,
and we did so.
You had me really
worried, Misao.
I thought you were
out of the fight.
Lucky for me,
you hung in there.
Well, we make
a great team.
The fact of the matter is,
I didn't have any choice.
Aoshi's
coming home
and I didn't
want Han'nya
to worry
about me anymore.
Huh?
(laughing)
It's all right,
forget it, Kaoru.
The important thing is
we have the upper hand,
so go in and
finish her off!
Hang on,
not so fast.
Huh?
Let me ask you, Kamatari.
Considering your situation,
are you prepared to withdraw?
Your weapon's
been destroyed
and so have your chances of
defeating us head to head.
If we fight now,
you might well die.
I'm giving you a
chance to retreat.
What do you say to that?
Ha!
What makes you think I can't
defeat you head to head?
Believe me, you are the
one at a disadvantage here.
That's not true.
You forget, I am a
very skilled swordsman.
I'm using my
weapon of choice,
and you'll be
forced to improvise
with an unfamiliar one.
So, even though
I have no blade,
I still have an
advantage over you.
If necessary, I can beat
you with just this handle.
I doubt it.
I'm good with swords,
but you'll find that out.
I wouldn't be
much of a warrior
if I trained with
one weapon alone.
Let's see if
you're any good.
♪
I hope Kaoru
can handle her.
She's certainly
not intimidated.
Why should I be?
No one's ever beaten me
in a battle before.
We'll change that!
I wouldn't
count on it.
People who misjudge
me often find
it's a very
fatal mistake.
No matter
how I look.
Whether I'm
plain or exotic,
inside of me beats the heart
of a cold-blooded killer.
It's my mission.
And believe me, I'm
very good at what I do.
I'd invite you to
question my opponents,
but they're all dead.
Now, if you
don't mind, ladies,
it's time to wrap
up this conversation.
Watch.
I'm going to prove
just how good I am.
♪
(grunts)
Let's see how
you handle this.
I don't think that stick's
gonna be enough of a defense.
(yelling)
You asked for it.
(shouts in pain)
You won't understand,
but I'm sorry it
had to come to this.
It's because I
had a mission too.
I promised I would
protect all these people,
and I always
keep my promises.
♪
I promised Kenshin we'd
go back to Kyoto together,
and I intend to
keep that one too.
This battle is
over, Kamatari.
It's time to
admit defeat,
gather your forces
together and leave.
♪
Hmm.
As I told you, completing
my mission is vital.
It means
everything to me.
I can't go back and face
Shishio-- not in defeat.
There's only one honorable
way out, so goodbye.
(grunts)
♪
You robbed me
of my honor.
♪
Did you kill her?
Nope.
She'll be all right
when she wakes up,
but she'll have a pretty good
headache for a few days.
I figure the pain
of being defeated
is going to be
punishment enough,
and I'm not
vindictive, am I?
♪
Good girl.
(muttering)
This can't be happening!
First, they defeat
Hennya and now Kamatari.
Maybe we should retreat.
Those three are the best
fighters I've ever seen.
No!
Stand your ground.
Have you all forgotten?
We still have Iwambo!
He'll crush these
fools like ants.
Of course, what
were we thinking?
We still have a chance.
(chuckling)
♪
He won't last
five minutes.
We're doomed.
Retreat!
Uh?
(chuckling)
Did you see that?
What a rubberneck!
Now, that's
some serious yoga.
I as hoping it
was a bad dream.
(muttering to himself)
(shouts)
-Alright, he ran away!
Yes, and I understand why.
He knew what
he was up against.
Can you blame him?
You're the very best.
Thank you everybody,
we have won.
♪
(loud rumble)
Hmm?
(loud footsteps)
What's that?
I'm afraid to guess.
It's big.
I suspect it's
more than that.
It sounds monstrous.
♪
Hmm?
Well, well.
Would you look at this?
Kamatari's attack
group has been defeated
by this pitiful band
of samurais in training.
♪
Looks like it's two
of us against eight.
I suppose that
would be a fair fight.
Right, my friend, Fuji?
(laughing evilly)
♪