♪
(singing in foreign language)
Nine-Headed Dragon Flash!
(yelling)
♪
(gasps)
(labored breathing)
♪
What the hell's going on?
There's fire everywhere,
it's burning
everything in its path!
It's a reflection
of Shishio's rage.
It's reacting to him
like the leaves reacted
to Kenshin.
Not quite.
I think that Shishio's
totally out of control.
Are you ready for
the final encounter?
♪
You're alive!
Behold the secret sword
technique of Kaguzuchi!
(labored breathing)
(flames roaring)
(heavy breathing)
(groaning)
♪
That's the stance
he uses for Amakakeru.
So what if it is?
Just look at him.
He's too badly injured
to be of any danger.
Even if he tries,
Himura's Amakakeru secret
is already known
to Mr. Shishio.
Even though Sojiro
lost to Himura,
he learned the secret
and told Mr. Shishio.
♪
Come on.
The key to the Amakakeru
is a certain movement
of Himura's left foot.
When Mr. Shishio sees that,
he'll know it's coming
and he'll be able to block it.
♪
I admit, it's been
an enjoyable battle.
I haven't fought anyone
this good for a long time.
But I have the whole
country to conquer
and don't have much time,
so I'm afraid I'm going to
have to end this fight quickly.
♪
You're right about one thing.
It's been a long fight,
the time has come to end it
one way or another.
I don't care if I win or lose
as long as I do my best.
But if you win, the lives
of millions of innocent people
will be ruined and that's
why I have to stop you.
You're welcome to try
but you'll never stop me
as long as I can
hold this sword.
♪
And I'll never stop trying
as long as I can hold
mine, Shishio Makoto.
♪
Come on.
Let's do it.
♪
Ya!
(birds chirping)
Everything's so badly damaged,
I don't know if we'll
ever get it cleaned up.
What?
You call this badly damaged?
This is nothing compared
to what it was like last time.
We'll have this mess cleaned up
and everything'll
be back to normal.
'Course, we have a little
remodeling to do here and there
but that'll make it
nicer than before.
(laughing)
I just don't want you pushing
yourself too hard, that's all.
You're not as young or strong
as you used to be, you know?
Oh yeah, says who?
They don't call me
"Tiger" for nothing.
Whoa!
Here's the water
you asked for, Kori.
Thanks, Omasu.
(grunting)
Okina!
Will you please
stop goofing around
and help me clean up?
We've got a lot
of work to do...
Tiger.
Could you help me?
You got yourself up there,
you can get yourself down.
Thanks a heap, oh!
Kori!
You're worried
about him, aren't you?
Huh?
You don't have to
worry about Kenshin.
As long as he uses the
secret fighting technique
that I taught him,
he can not ever
be defeated in battle.
Even if an opponent avoids
the jaws of the dragon,
the wind of its passage
will render him helpless
and he'll be
torn apart by its claws.
Of course,
that's assuming that...
(slurps)
...he's in perfect condition.
But if he's badly
wounded to begin with,
his technique won't do
him a damn bit of good.
Have I told you lately
how pretty you are?
Mm-hm.
(giggles)
I'm not that worried.
Kenshin's going to win
and come back safe and sound.
Right, and the same
goes for Aoshi.
It won't be long before
he comes back again.
Yup, then we'll be together
forever till the end of time.
I don't understand you.
How can you be in love
with such a weirdo?
(yelling)
Right now you're not
old enough to understand
what love is all about, Yoshi.
It's different for everyone.
Ask a hundred people
and you'd get a hundred
different answers.
That's one of the
great things about love
that makes it so wonderful.
(grunting)
Take that, you little brat!
I know you'll
come back, Kenshin.
I know...
that you'll keep your promise.
♪
Yeah!
Shishio!
Don't worry, Kenshin
doesn't have a chance.
(laughing diabolically)
♪
Mr. Shishio is using
his secret technique.
Himura will be destroyed.
(laughing)
♪
Huh?
I avoided the first blow
of his secret technique
but his sword strike
is so powerful
that it created a vortex,
a zone of rushing air so strong,
it's like trying to fight
the force of a hurricane.
If I can't move,
I'm defenseless.
I've got to find
a way to break out.
Huh?
(yelling)
Even if an opponent avoids
the jaws of the dragon,
the winds of its passage
will render him helpless
and he'll be torn
apart by its claws.
♪
(yelling)
(thunderous crash)
(heavy breathing)
My secret fighting technique
utilizes extreme
hand and sword speed.
and the Hiten Mitsurugi style
is a combination
of offense and defense.
If you combine the two,
then you will win.
Thank you.
(rumbling)
You did it.
(grunting)
♪
(yells)
Well done, Kenshin.
♪
Kenshin used his sheath fake
with his first step,
then used his own
centrifugal force
to obtain position
with the second step.
Then, using a double-step
crisscross technique,
he distracted his opponent
from the true direction
of his sword thrust.
The final blow used
the focused energy
of every muscle in his body.
If Shishio survives that,
he must be immortal.
(grunting, gasping)
♪
Mr. Shishio!
(yelling)
♪
Wait a second, what's
goin' on with Shishio?
I don't get it!
(yelling)
♪
Take it!
(groaning, yelling)
Ayumi, don't go!
(gasps)
♪
-Stop!
-What?
Leave him alone!
He's dying, can't you see that?
The doctor said he could
only fight for 15 minutes.
Once he exceeds that time limit,
his body won't recover.
His body heat will destroy him!
He's no longer a danger to you.
Not anymore.
The fighting is over.
Let me care for him...
till he's gone.
♪
(groaning)
It's not over.
(screaming)
♪
Shishio Makoto,
you're a fiend from hell.
Only a monster could kill
the woman he loves
in order to win a fight.
You're not human!
What is done is done.
You cannot judge me
by your standards, Kenshin.
Our love is stronger now
than it ever was before.
She's happy to have sacrificed
her life out of love for me.
I'm so...glad...
that I could help.
I always wanted...
to do...whatever I could
and now I've done
something to help you win
your greatest victory.
Oh, my love.
I was always so jealous
of Sojiro and the others.
They could help you
to reach your goal
to fulfill your dream
while all I could do
was tend your wounds
and give you momentary pleasure.
But now I've helped you win
your most important battle
and that makes me so happy.
♪
My love...
you're the only man
I ever loved.
♪
You...and I...
together...
always.
♪
(gasps)
Faithful Ayumi.
She's been looking
for happiness
all of her life
and finally found it at the very
moment of her untimely death.
(groaning)
Happiness, Hoji?
Is that what you call it?
She didn't have to die,
she was only trying to--
(grunting)
Her death is no longer
of any importance.
The last battle
is not yet over.
The winner has yet
to be decided.
The strong will live
and the weak will surely die!
Only one of us will
leave this place alive.
Kenshin.
(gasping, heavy breathing)
♪
Huh?
Why is red steam
rising off his body?
The internal temperature
of Mr. Shishio's body
has risen to the level
that the coagulated blood
from his wounds
is evaporating as steam.
(groaning)
♪
He's wounded so badly yet he
still has that much spirit.
Maybe Shishio does
deserve to win.
♪
Kenshin!
I've lost so much blood.
All my energy seems
to be draining out of me.
My body seems so far away.
I can hardly feel anything.
I've been close to death before,
but never this close.
Is this really the end?
Is this what it feels like?
Dying?
But can I allow myself to die
while Shishio still lives?
Yes.
Even if he survives his wounds,
it'll take him years
to recover his strength
and regain his power,
and by that time, others will
be strong enough to stop him.
It's up to them now.
I don't think I have
it in me to go on.
♪
I'm sorry I couldn't
return to Aoiya,
sorry that I'll never see
Kori and the others again.
But I've done everything
else I set out to do.
I protected my friends
and my country.
My duty is done.
(sobbing)
Kenshin!
You are not allowed to give up.
You have a task that
hasn't been completed yet.
Quickly, wake up!
We're going home
together, remember?
You promised.
♪
I solemnly swore to meet
someone who's waiting for me
and I won't break it because
of you or anyone else!
My will to live
is stronger than you.
It's stronger than anything.
The will is only as strong
as the person within
whom it abides.
You are strong, Battousai,
but you're not the strongest.
As you are about to find out,
the strongest is me!
♪
I knew you'd make
a fine meal, Kenshin.
The time has come to eat!
(grunting)
Mr. Shishio's going to win.
No!
He's gone past his limit.
(screaming)
It just can't...be.
He's consuming himself.
Burning from within.
His body is using his own
fat and phosphorus as fuel.
(flames roaring)
(gasping)
♪
(laughing)
(exclaiming)
No!
I refuse to believe it!
Shishio was winning the fight
and he should have won it!
♪
No, Hoji.
Remember, the laws of nature
also apply to him.
As Shishio used to say,
nature allows only
the fittest to survive.
In this case, Kenshin.
It wasn't the time or place
for a man like Shishio
to take control.
All his efforts,
all his plans,
the extinction of
the Juppongatana group,
they were for nothing.
Kenshin was merely
an instrument.
The outcome was decided
by the ebb and flow
of history and fate,
which would never have
allowed Shishio to succeed.
♪
You won, pal.
Did I?
♪
No, he's won nothing!
Nothing, do you hear?
I will kill you all!
Yes!
You're all going to die!
Kenshin!
♪
Damn!
If my right hand weren't broken,
I could break down this door
and put Hoji out of his misery.
We've gotta get
Kenshin out of here.
Get out of the way.
♪
Saito.
Saito, don't do it.
You'll open up your wound again.
♪
Hey, you okay?
Sano, take Kenshin and Aoshi
and get out of here.
I'll find Hoji
and take care of him.
Go on.
Hey...what's that?
Huh?
♪
What in the world's that?
What the hell's goin' on?
Die!
You're all gonna die!
Mr. Shishio's enemies
are all gonna die!
Yes!
I'll kill you all!
And then when
you're dead and gone,
Shishio will have won!
(explosions)
(explosion, rumbling)
♪
(singing in foreign language)