♪
(singing in foreign language)
(explosions)
(fire roaring)
Huh?
You okay?
♪
Saito!
Well, well.
Huh?
♪
You know the way out, right?
Yeah, so?
Which way?
I gave a map of this
place to Shinomori.
He can show you where
the secret passage is.
What, hold on!
Stay there, you
can't run away now!
You said you'd give me a
chance to fight you again!
Come back, you coward!
I've seen enough carnage
here to last me a lifetime,
Sano, haven't you?
♪
See ya around.
(explosions)
Saito!
♪
(laughing)
(fire roaring)
♪
(gasps)
You okay, Hoji?
Why did you save me, Anji?
Why, Anji?
I wanted to die like
Shishio and Ayumi did.
(crying)
I can't believe that
Mr. Shishio is really dead.
And poor Ayumi is gone too.
(crying)
Time to go.
Goodbye.
-Where are you going?
-I don't know.
I wanna learn the truth.
It's out there somewhere.
I'll find it eventually.
Or it will find me.
Sayonara.
♪
I'm going to give myself
up to the police,
pay for my crimes.
What about you, Hoji?
What are you going to do?
I'll go with you, I want them to
put me on trial for my crimes.
Once I'm in court I can tell
Mr. Shishio's side of the story.
I'll make certain everyone
hears his message.
The public will finally
hear what the government
has been trying to hide.
That our country is governed
by weaklings who cannot admit
that Japan will not survive
unless we are put into power!
The fundamental law of nature
is survival of the fittest.
I must make people see
that Japan is in danger!
♪
Damn, Shishio.
After all the pain he's
caused, I'm glad he's dead,
but Aoshi, I swear
on all that's holy,
if Kenshin dies, I'll
find Shishio in hell
and kill him again!
♪
(crickets chirping)
It's so quiet here tonight.
You'd never know there was
a huge battle here today.
Sir, we arrested the
people who attacked you.
Come with me now, and I'll
take you to the hospital.
Huh?
There's no need for
that, I'll be fine.
It barely hurts at all.
But, sir, it looks like
you've been badly injured.
You really should go to the
hospital, and be examined.
-No way.
-Why not?
Some friends of ours
are gonna show up soon.
None of us are going
anywhere until they get here,
even if it takes
all night, got it?
But--
We know they'll come.
Kenshin will do whatever
it takes to get here--ah!
Try to be still
or it won't heal.
I don't understand why
you all have so much faith
in an impetuous
guy like Himura.
He was your student, how can
you talk about him like that?
Because he was
such a bad student.
On the other hand, he
managed to learn enough
to survive just about anything.
The guy you're waiting for
is a survivor too, right?
Huh?
That's right.
Han'nya told me.
Aoshi won't let anything
stop him from coming back.
Huh?
-Huh?
-Oh.
-Oh my.
Wha--?
♪
Sano and Aoshi had
found their way back
by the light of the full moon.
Kenshin was too
badly wounded to walk,
so Sano had carried
him the whole way.
Even so, Kenshin had
lost consciousness,
and no one could revive him.
All we could do was tend
to his wounds and wait.
Kenshin.
I sent Megumi a letter,
and she rushed to Aoiya
as soon as she heard
that Kenshin was hurt.
A month passed, and
winter turned to spring,
and then it was summer.
Megumi and I nursed
Kenshin back to health,
but it took a long time,
which gave all of us time
to reflect on the past,
and what we wanted
for our future.
♪
Huh?
Uh, Kenshin?
Are you sure you're
well enough to get up?
Yeah, thanks for all your help.
My wounds are all healed now.
Besides it's too
noisy around here
for anyone to get any sleep.
(mixed remarks)
Where's Aoshi?
You're right.
Darn, there's no way I can use
chopsticks with my left hand.
Aoshi, where are you?
I wanna see you right now!
Hey, take it easy, will ya?
-I drank too much sake.
-Go lie down.
Kenshin, you woke up!
-You feeling better now?
-Welcome back!
Hey everybody, it looks
like Kenshin woke up!
Somebody get the guy a
drink, and make it sake!
-Tae, it's broken!
-Sorry, Sano, I'm Sae.
Tae's my older sister.
You never have figured out which
one of us is which, have you?
No one has figured that out.
You two look exactly alike.
Can I please have
another chopstick?
Sure, let me get you one.
This is Sherri Baby's,
the sister restaurant
of Lenny's in Kyoto.
Tae is working at Lenny's
for now, but this is her home.
She's letting us
stay here until Aoiya
is fixed up and back to normal.
Megumi's staying here too.
Megumi?
I wanna thank you
for tending my wounds.
You're welcome, Kenshin,
but you haven't healed
completely so be careful.
-Right--
-Aoshi!
I am not gonna wait forever!
Aoshi is praying
at the Zen temple.
Again?
I can't believe it,
he's been there every day
since he came back.
You must have patience, my dear.
He's got a lot on his mind.
He needs to be alone for
a while, that's all.
Take this food to Aoshi.
He needs more protein
to heal properly.
Well, now.
I think this is the place
I'll find Kenshin Himura.
-Who's that?
-Huh?
It's Cho, the Sword Hunter.
Oh, darn.
I didn't think you were going
to recognize me again so fast.
Oh well, so much
for fooling you.
It's you, the broom head!
I thought you were
still in jail!
(laughing)
-So you met this guy in jail?
-Sano did.
How'd you get out?
I made a deal with the
government of course.
What are you doing for them?
Oh, the usual, spying,
that sort of thing.
I know it's a lousy way to
make a living, believe me,
I don't feel great about it,
but I didn't have much choice.
It's the only way I could get
them to drop the charges,
you know how it is.
Soon as those government
guys stop watching me,
I'll quit, and have some fun.
You can't quit, a deal is deal!
You're gonna have to do it
whether you like it or not!
What do you know about
it, ya little weasel?
-Mind your own business.
-Who you calling a weasel?
-You little--
-All right.
So we know who
you're working for.
What's that got to do with us?
I have some information I
thought you'd like to know,
and that's why I'm here.
I had a hunch that you'd
want to know what happened
to the members of
the Juppongatana.
After all, you've been
fighting them for so long,
I thought you'd be interested
in what they're up to.
♪
Go on, we're listening.
Well, most of them got the
same kinda deal as I did.
You see, the government's
politicians may not be good
at getting anything
done themselves,
but they are good at recognizing
other people's talents,
and how to use them.
♪
Han'nya was assigned to work
for the army and navy,
because his ability
to fly made him invaluable
as a military spy.
Remember that little
blabbermouth called Saizuchi?
He speaks three or four
different languages,
so they assigned him
to the negotiating team
at the foreign office.
And Fuji, that huge guy
that Hiko Seijuro defeated,
has been sent to the northern
provinces as lieutenant
in the colonial brigade.
He's helping to develop some
wilderness area up there.
There was a lady that
we fought against.
That's right, she's called
Kamatari, the scythe lady.
What about her?
She's the lucky one, she gets
to travel all over the world
spying on foreign governments
posing as an exchange student.
-That is if she's well enough.
-Well enough?
I mean if she ever recovers
from what happened.
Really, I didn't realize that
her wounds were that bad.
You're right, she wasn't
that badly injured,
but when she found out
that Shishio had died
she got so depressed
she couldn't eat.
If I hadn't talked
her out of it,
I think she might
have starved to death.
So, he's really dead.
Then perhaps I
should die as well.
I don't think Shishio
would approve of that.
What do you mean?
Why not?
Since you were a late joiner
I guess you never heard
what the Juppongatana members
were supposed to do
in case we lost.
Huh?
When we first formed
the Juppongatana,
Shishio told us that there
weren't any guarantees
in a struggle like this,
that we had to have a plan
in case things
didn't go our way.
If Shishio failed
to take over Japan,
the Meiji government
would rewrite history.
They'd say that
everyone supported them,
that Shishio never existed.
It would be our job to tell the
public our side of the story.
Liar!
I'm from Kansai, we may joke
a lot, but we never tell a lie.
As a matter of fact, when
Shishio told us about this
he mentioned you specifically.
I gotta admit he knew
who was right for the job.
I can't think of
anybody from the group
who'd make a better
public speaker than you.
Really?
Maybe you're right.
I've always had a way of
making people listen to me,
and it would be an honor to
tell them about Mr. Shishio.
So now she has a goal in life.
I find it hard to
believe that Shishio
would have said such a thing.
Yeah, why would he plan
anything in case he lost
when he was always
so sure he would win?
You guys are as
gullible as she was.
I made the whole thing up.
(gasping)
Shishio was the man
of Kamatari's dreams.
She wasn't just in love
with him, she idolized him.
If she thought she was
following his instructions
it would give her
something to live for.
You're quite right.
How about Anji the Mad Monk?
Do you know what
happened to him?
Don't tell me he cut a
deal with the government,
I know him better than that.
I think he'd rather
go to prison.
You're right, he turned himself
in even though he expected
to get the death penalty for all
the terrible things he'd done.
But because he showed so much
remorse for what he'd done,
and because of the good
word you put in for him,
they sentenced him to 25 years
to be served in Hokkaido prison.
Sentenced to 25 years,
that's a long time.
What about that other guy?
-Huh?
-Hm?
That skinny one who was there
when I fought Shishio
that last time.
I think he was the most loyal
of all Shishio's followers.
Hm.
I'm afraid he's gone.
♪
He was Shishio's chief
advisor and confidant.
One of the most determined
men I've ever met.
He's dead?
What caused his death?
He gave himself up to
the police like Anji did,
expecting to be put on trial
which is why he wanted
to be arrested, but
there was no trial.
A trial would've given
him a public forum
to speak on Mr. Shishio's
behalf, to tell everyone
that Shishio's goal was
to strengthen our country.
So, when the government
realized that Hoji wouldn't cut
any kind of deal with them,
they locked him in jail where
he couldn't talk to anyone,
and threw away the key, right?
And what's ironic is that of all
the guys they made deals with,
he was the one that
could've done the most
productive work
for the government.
He had tremendous
administrative ability,
and knew how to
plan for the future,
but they knew he was
fanatically loyal to Shishio,
and that made him dangerous.
They threw him into
solitary confinement,
and probably would've kept him
there the rest of his life.
Finally, having completely
lost his faith in his government
and his country, and
without hope of ever seeing
freedom again,
he took his own life.
♪
Well, I guess there are
two sides to every story.
Even though he did bad things,
he was thoroughly
convinced that he was right.
That's what being
a fanatic is all about.
Yumi was like that too.
Do you mean that courtesan that
hung out with Mr. Shishio?
That's the one, Yumi Komagata,
a beautiful intelligent woman.
I once thought our
country was strong,
but Shishio has shown me
how weak we really are,
and that the world
is full of lies.
Like Kamatari, she was
in love with Shishio,
but in her case that
love was returned.
If Shishio trusted
anyone is was Yumi.
To most people, Shishio was
a power-hungry bad guy,
but to her he was
the savior of Japan.
Well, I'd better get going.
Thanks for the sashimi.
Oh yeah, I almost forgot.
Two of the guys never got
caught, they got away.
One of them is that kid you
fought, Kenshin, Sojiro Seta.
I doubt they'll ever
catch him, he's too clever.
Right now he's probably
on the top of a mountain
at some Wayfarer's inn
eating litchi nuts,
and enjoying a cup of tea.
The other one is Iwanbo,
that big tub of lard
you took care of in
the battle of Aoiya.
Without someone telling him
what to do he's fairly harmless.
(laughing)
-Cho.
-Yeah?
Shishio's right hand man,
the one who killed himself,
I'd really like
to know his name,
and you never told
me what it was.
Hoji, Hoji Sadojima.
Shishio Makoto
and Yumi Komagata,
and the Juppongatana group.
Although their names won't
appear in any history books
please tell the spirit of
Hoji Sadojima that those names
along with his will be
remembered in my heart.
Sure, I'll deliver the message
for ya, though I don't know
how happy his ghost is gonna
be to hear it coming from me.
Sayonara.
We won, right?
I mean, what they did
was wrong, wasn't it?
We did win, so we
must have been right.
If you're saying we
were right because we won,
then you're thinking the
same way Shishio Makoto did.
We fought and defeated
Shishio and the Juppongatana
because we believe that stopping
him was the right thing to do,
but everyone on their
side thought that fighting
for Shishio and his cause
was the right thing to do,
because they believed
in his philosophy,
and felt that Japan
needed him as a leader.
In that sense, we're the same.
We both fought for what
we thought was right.
Just because we beat them
doesn't mean their point of view
was any less valid than ours.
It only means they lost.
None of us can know who was
right and who was wrong,
not here, not now.
History will have
to be the judge of that.
However, there is
one thing I know
that Shishio was wrong about.
His so-called law of nature,
the survival of the fittest.
There can be no
such law among humans
if mankind is going to survive.
♪
Where am I?
I'm sure I killed
myself in that jail cell.
-Which means this is--
-Hell, of course.
Mr. Shishio!
You see, darling, I told
you Hoji would be joining us
sooner or later.
Yes, come on, Hoji,
we have work to do.
What, where are we going?
Going down.
We're forming a new group.
I'm taking over hell.
If anyone can do it,
you can, darling,
but first, let's find Usui.
I'm sure he's down
here somewhere.
Good idea.
Come on, Hoji, what're
you waiting for?
You're my chief
advisor, aren't you?
Now you'll have to come up
with a whole new campaign,
and entirely different strategy.
You promised me a victory,
and a victory I shall have!
Yes, right away!
We shouldn't have lost anyway.
The upper-world's filled
with pusillanimous weaklings
who couldn't make
sacrifices necessary
for their miserable
country to have a future,
but down here there
are only bad guys.
(laughing)
♪
Well, I guess I'll be going now.
Thanks for your hospitality.
Oh, where are you
going, young man?
I'm not sure, ma'am.
I'm looking for something,
but I don't know where it is,
or even what direction
I should take to find it.
It could be just about anywhere,
but I figure I'll find it
in about 10 years or so.
(groaning)
Why so long?
These two guys I used to
know, they went looking
for the same thing,
and that's about how long
it took them to find it.
I hope it won't take me that
long, but you never know.
Tell you what, as
soon as I find it,
I'll come right back here,
and tell you all about it.
It sounds like a lot
of work to me, mhm.
There seems to be quite a few
travelers walking up this road.
Where does it go?
I've been told it makes its
way to the northern provinces.
The northern provinces, hm?
-Sounds good to me.
-Oh, I wish I could go with ya.
I bet it won't be as hot up
there during the summer months.
Thanks again.
-So long.
-Hey wait, you owe me money!
♪
(singing in foreign language)