♪
(singing in Japanese)
(insects chirping)
♪
Wow, look at that!
Yeah, that ring
sure is beautiful!
Yes.
Kaoru, that's called
an engagement ring.
People use that to swear
eternal love to each other.
What exactly does that mean?
When a man wants to marry a
woman, he gives her a ring,
and if she accepts his
proposal, then they get married!
You should wear it on
your left ring finger,
and if you're proposed
to on Tanabata Day,
it's very special.
Oh, really?
That's right, Kaoru.
It is every woman's
fondest desire
to receive a ring like this
from the one that we love.
It's great!
♪
Hello, Kenshin!
You said that it was
important to meet you here.
♪
I'm sorry to keep you
waiting so long, Kaoru.
I want you to accept this,
on the night of Tanabata.
♪
Kenshin.
Kaoru, will you marry me?
I promise to love you forever.
Kenshin.
I wanna marry you.
Oh, yes!
♪
-Kenshin, be gentle.
-Oh, Kaoru.
Oh, my goodness,
she's fainted!
Kaoru!
Kaoru, are you all right?
She's saying something!
Be gentle, be gentle!
Kenshin, hold me close to you.
Oh, my!
She feels like
she's really on fire!
Yes, she must be really
thinking about him.
You think so?
Unfortunately,
their relationship
isn't going anywhere.
That's too bad.
Well, I guess there's
nothing we can do about it.
I've got it!
I'm going to do
something special
to make her dream come true.
Tomorrow is going
to be Tanabata!
I don't understand.
How is that
going to help Kaoru?
I'm going to
play matchmaker!
All she needs to
be happy is for me
to shove Kenshin in
the right direction.
I hope you're right.
Kenshin, stop it!
Oh, Kenshin!
♪
Kenshin, Kenshin!
Oh, Miss Tae!
I have to talk to you!
Sure.
An engagement ring.
Hi there, Kaoru!
Good morning!
Morning, Kenshin!
Where're you going so early?
I'm gonna go fishing, so
I guess I'll see you later!
All right?
Uh, hey, Kenshin!
Don't you think that
you're forgetting something?
Hmm?
Oh, I almost forgot it!
You see there?
Yeah, without this
bait, I can't catch fish.
Thanks, Kaoru!
What I mean is, do
you know what today is?
Sure, I do!
It's a great day for fishing,
and I feel very lucky today!
In fact, I think I'll catch
a whole school of fish!
♪
It's Tanabata Day.
I thought that maybe Kenshin
had an engagement ring for me.
I should know that's
too much to hope for.
I guess to Kenshin I'm not
as important as going fishing.
I hope you don't
catch any fish,
and that you fall in the water
and get eaten by a large shark!
(grunting)
You have to keep your guard up.
Now, attack me one more time
and stay focused this time!
This is a special, romantic day,
and here I am
practicing in the dojo
like nothing else matters.
Heads up!
(yelling)
Ow!
Kaoru, you dropped
your guard that time!
You're right.
I just wasn't paying
attention, Yoshi.
You'd better listen
to your own advice.
Stay focused,
otherwise you'll end up
with some fractured bones.
Now you're the one
that's exaggerating!
I'd better get a
cold rag for you
to stop the swelling!
Hey, Yoshi sure is being
a nice guy to me today!
♪
(yawning)
I haven't had a single
nibble all day long.
Maybe I'm not that lucky.
Huh?
Ahh!
(yelling)
That feels so nice, Yoshi.
A cold rag always
stops the swelling!
Hey, I know what'd
make you feel better!
A massage!
You're going to
give me a massage?
You've never done
anything like that before!
Well, you've always taken
good care of me, Kaoru,
so I just wanted to
return the favor to you.
That's all!
How nice!
Hello there, Kaoru.
-Hello, Sano!
-Hey, Kaoru,
I thought that you might
like some cake today.
I have some left over
from my meal at Lenny's.
I know you have a sweet
tooth, so I brought it for ya!
Great!
I love cake!
We can all share it!
Sound good to you, Yoshi?
Don't worry about me.
He brought it for you!
Really, you should have it!
It looks delicious!
Mmm.
It's fantastic!
That's great, I'm glad
you're enjoying it!
You could use some tea.
I'll go and make some!
That's weird.
Why are they
acting so nice to me?
Sano always teases me
and makes fun of me.
Maybe he really loves me!
Maybe he's really
flirting with me!
But why is Yoshi being so nice?
He can't be in
love with me, too!
Or can he?
That's awfully sweet,
but he's really
too young for me.
He's probably just
got a crush on me.
I can't take it!
It's just too much pressure!
What's wrong?
Why are you crying?
Nothing, it's just that no one's
ever been nice to me before.
Uh, by the way, Kaoru--
Sorry, Yoshi.
You see, I don't think
it could ever work out
between you and I.
I'm a lot older
than you are,
but at least we'll
always be good friends.
Good friends?
Well, great, 'cause I
broke this vase of yours!
I thought you'd be mad,
but since we're friends,
you forgive me, right?
Are you out of your mind?
That's my favorite vase!
How could you?
Accidents do happen,
you know, Kaoru.
And since you're
such good friends,
why don't you cut
him some slack?
And since I'm your friend,
you could do me
a big favor, Kaoru.
I need you to loan
me a little money.
I need money to pay
for the cake I bought ya.
(chuckling)
(groaning)
♪
No, you can't!
I thought that you'd
planned all of this
because today is special!
What is she talking about?
Do you know, Yoshi?
-No.
-Yahhh!
Good friends, my foot.
Those two are nothing more than
a couple of scheming scoundrels.
Thank goodness, at least,
I still have Kenshin.
Hey, hello, Kaoru!
I caught a really
big catfish today!
Really?
How nice for you.
Today is a very special
day for you, Kaoru!
I was able to bring
you back a nice fish
for today's celebration!
Celebration!
Oh, so is that the reason
why you went fishing
so early this morning?
Yeah, that's right, Kaoru.
Huh?
♪
He is going to propose
to me after all!
Thank you, Kenshin!
I'm happy for you, Kaoru!
Kenshin caught something
for dinner all right.
Boy, was I lucky!
We're gonna eat a
delicious catfish!
And here he is!
(grunting)
I guess she doesn't
like catfish.
What's the matter?
♪
I love catfish, don't you?
Mm!
No one told me that it
was Kaoru's birthday today.
Did you guys know that?
Kenshin, don't you
think you should get her
a better present than catfish?
Otherwise, my plan won't work!
Oops!
Did you come here to
collect the money I owe ya?
I haven't forgotten that,
but I'm here for more
important things right now.
Did you get a bone, Kenshin?
Something hard.
An engagement ring.
You'd think the
least he could do
on a romantic day like this
is bring me a red
snapper, but no!
No, not Kenshin.
He brings me a
smelly old catfish!
He doesn't know women.
Kenshin, you don't seem
to be paying attention
to everything that
I have been saying.
Today is a special
day for Kaoru,
and you need to get her
something that shows you care!
It's a lucky thing for you
that you found that
ring in the fish!
Now you have something
special to give her!
But I don't think
he should give her
something he found
in a fish, do you?
Shut up and stay out of this!
Now march in there and
put that wonderful ring
on her left ring
finger, Kenshin.
I'll do it!
♪
Huh?
Who's there?
Um, may I come in, Kaoru?
Kenshin?
(grunting and clanging)
Did you wanna talk to me?
I'm sorry I made
you wait so long.
What?
Kaoru, this is for you.
(shrieking)
♪
I just can't believe this!
Am I dreaming?
It's not a dream!
That's an engagement ring!
He wanted to surprise me!
That's why he pretended
to give me a catfish!
He wanted to wait for the
right moment to give it to me!
What a wonderful ring!
♪
I love Kenshin forever.
Kaoru, are you all right?
Hey, just what's
up with Dog Face?
Go ahead, put it on
her finger, Kenshin!
Go put it on her finger!
(groaning)
(gasping)
(yelling)
(moaning)
It's your own fault, Kenshin!
You can't do something romantic
like that in front of Yoshi!
Oh, ahh!
He gave me an engagement
ring on Tanabata Day!
-All right!
-Yeah!
That was weird.
My engagement ring is lovely!
Thank you!
(moaning)
♪
(humming wedding march)
I will soon become
Mrs. Kaoru Himura,
but when we get
married, we'll live here.
That means Kenshin will
be marrying into my family.
Does that make
him Kenshin Kamiya?
That sounds nice!
I don't know how
these things work.
When we have children,
will they follow
Hiten Mitsurugi style
or will they follow
Kamiya Kasshin style?
Kenshin doesn't wanna
teach Hiten Mitsurugi style,
so I guess they'll
follow my style!
I wonder if it'll
be a boy or a girl.
If it's a boy, he'll be
strong and gentle like Kenshin.
If it's a girl,
she'll be gorgeous!
Maybe she could be an actress.
Hey, Kaoru?
(yelling)
I'm sorry to disturb you, Kaoru,
but I was just getting ready
to clean up the house right now.
I wanna get it out of the way
'cause I have a
lot of chores to do.
♪
Huh?
There you are, Kenshin.
I don't want you
to do a thing today.
Just relax and
enjoy yourself.
But Kaoru--
I think it would
be a good idea
if I were to take
some cooking classes!
Maybe Wadi could teach me
how to cook like a gourmet!
You just stay there, my love.
I'm going to clean
up the house today!
Kaoru's gonna
learn to be a chef?
The sky must be falling.
(insects chirping)
Here it is.
This is where Kenshin
caught the really big catfish.
Huh?
Shiori, please forgive
me for killing myself.
What do you think you're doin'?
I'm gonna end it all!
Listen here, if you're
planning to kill yourself,
please do it somewhere else.
I don't want to have
to witness your death.
It could give me bad dreams.
You just don't understand!
I've acted so stupidly!
(sobbing)
Did somebody break
your heart or something?
I threw away
an engagement ring
I was going to
give my girlfriend!
A ring?
That's awful,
I think that maybe
you should tell me about it.
Well, my girlfriend,
her name is Shiori.
We were going to get married,
but just a few days ago...
♪
I've really missed you, Shiori!
I've really missed
you, too, Shinji!
I just couldn't believe
that she had somebody else.
It was like an knife
had stabbed my heart.
(water running)
This ring is meaningless!
But later, I found out
that the guy she was with
was a cousin she
hadn't seen in ten years!
Well, I think to say
that you overreacted
is an understatement.
This isn't a joke!
I worked two jobs for
five years to buy that ring,
and she was really looking
forward to me giving it to her!
Not only did I throw away
the ring, I mistrusted her.
What are you going to do?
I don't know.
I've looked all
over the river for it.
I wasn't able to find
the ring anywhere!
I feel so bad that I thought
if I would just end my life,
maybe she'd forgive me.
She'll find somebody else.
(grunting)
Stop that!
Tell me something,
that engagement ring
that you threw in the river,
does it have a blue stone in it?
Yes, it does!
Her birthstone
is a blue sapphire.
That's why I had
it made like that!
Hey, why are you
asking me that?
Oh, there's no reason, really.
Now listen!
I want you to wait here,
do you understand?
I might be able to help
you with your problem,
but if you kill yourself,
you'll break your girl's heart!
All right, I'll stay!
(birds and insects chirping)
Kenshin, we've
got a big problem!
So, you're saying that
the ring Kenshin found
in the catfish the other day
actually belongs to this guy?
Yes, that's right.
Then I'll have to
explain this to Kaoru
and get the ring back
from her right away!
Hold on, compadre, it's
not gonna be that easy.
Why not?
Kaoru will never
give back that ring!
I don't think Kenshin knew
what he was getting into before,
but Wadi can explain.
Tell them what the
ring really means.
Let's get this straight.
A boy gives a girl a ring,
and that means that
he wants to get married?
Yes, that's right!
So, what you're saying is
that when Kenshin
gave Kaoru that ring,
he was really asking
her to marry him!
That is correct.
But that's just not fair!
Kenshin doesn't know about all
of those western traditions!
The worst part about all this
is it happened on Tanabata!
I thought that I was
only giving her the ring
as a gift for her birthday!
The whole situation
is entirely my fault.
I just wanted
Kaoru to be happy!
Kaoru's birthday is actually
in the month of June.
I see, that's why Kaoru's
been so happy lately!
So I guess she thinks she and
Kenshin are getting hitched!
The major problem here is
how are we ever gonna get
that darn engagement ring
back to its rightful owner
without hurting
Kaoru's feelings?
Right, Kenshin?
He's fainted!
We gotta do something!
That's for sure.
You can count on me.
It's such a lovely ring!
Kaoru!
Do me a favor.
How about a lesson today?
Okay.
I'm surprised you wanted
a lesson on your day off.
Well, I'm dedicated, all right?
Well, that's great.
Actually, I won't
be able to spend
as much time with you anymore,
so let's begin our lesson.
♪
All right, are you ready, Yoshi?
Kaoru, hey, let's work
on our judo today!
Yah!
♪
She's too good with a sword,
but this way I
can overpower her.
Nice move.
There it is.
All right, Yoshi.
I'll show you something.
Kamiya Kasshin style judo!
(yelling)
(groaning)
That's pretty good, huh?
Yeah, it's a very
effective style!
We included judo into the
Kamiya Kasshin style years ago!
You should've known that!
How come you didn't
use a counter-move?
I don't know.
And since you
wanted a good workout,
I'm going to go especially
rough on you today.
Let's go!
-No, really, Kaoru!
-We've only just begun!
That's enough for today!
(fighting)
♪
Kenshin.
Huh?
Kaoru, how's the
water in your tub?
Mm, it's just perfect.
Thanks!
Good, just take your time!
Boy, I hope this plan works.
(humming)
When we get married, we'll be
able to take a bath together,
and we can wash each
other's backs all day long!
(unintelligible speech)
♪
Women generally take
off their jewelry
when they take a bath.
Let's hope Kaoru
took that ring off.
You check her things out, Yoshi.
-No way!
-Would you hurry up?
I can't touch a
woman's underwear,
even if it does
belong to Dog Face!
It doesn't matter, just
get in there and do it!
Go on!
I am the son of a
great samurai warrior.
I cannot dishonor
my family name!
It would be better
if you did it.
Are you telling me
it's okay for me
to engage in
this shameful act?
You're the one who came
up with the stupid idea!
Do it yourself!
You told me I
could count on you!
Don't samurais
keep their word?
(clanging)
Stay out of here!
Perverts.
(bells tinkling)
Hi there, Kaoru,
we're really sorry
about disturbing
your bath earlier,
but we were just
looking for something!
What were you looking for?
Oh, uh, nothing important.
Would you like
an ice cold drink?
What is this stuff?
It's a brand new
drink called "beer."
I just got it from Lenny's!
All the sophisticated
Americans drink it
after they have
taken a bath.
That so?
(slurping)
Does this stuff have alcohol
in it, by any chance?
Why, yes, it does
have alcohol in it!
But it is a special
day today, isn't it?
It sure is.
I don't feel so good.
Whoa!
-All right!
-Yeah, we'll get it this time.
Get it off of her!
All right, I will!
Cut it out!
That tickles!
Hold still, will ya?
Come on!
Would you hurry up already?
Hey, you guys.
As I recall, Kaoru has a
bad reaction to alcohol--
she turns into a raving lunatic.
I warned you to stop it!
♪
It tickles!
(grunting)
(yelling)
-I give up.
-We'll never get it off.
It's Kenshin's fault.
He's the one who found
the ring in the catfish.
What is he talking about?
What did he find
in the catfish?
Huh, Kenshin?
I'm sorry, Kaoru, I'm gonna
tell you the whole truth.
What?!
That's the whole story.
Sorry, Kaoru.
We need to get him back his
ring before he hurts himself.
Kaoru, just give him
back the ring already!
If the guy kills himself,
we'll be partially responsible.
None of us wants that, do we?
I'm really very sorry.
Sano, Yoshi!
Let's do it.
All right, all right,
stretch your finger out.
(groaning)
(indistinct talking)
All right, all right,
somebody get some pliers!
-There you go.
-How 'bout some oil?
No, I got it, how
'bout some lard?
None of this stuff is working.
Why won't that thing come off?
The only way we're
gonna get this off
is to saw it off.
Maybe Kaoru's fingers are thick
from all of her
physical training.
Perhaps that's the reason
that we can't get
the ring off of there.
I'm sorry!
(sobbing)
I don't want
your stupid ring!
I'm sorry!
You're thoughtless!
(yelling)
Hey, Kenshin's jaw
knocked it loose!
Yeah, now that
was a lucky punch!
I can't thank you enough.
Shiori and I are now engaged.
Thank you, Hikojiro.
It's beautiful.
Congratulations and
don't ever do that again!
For all our sakes.
Well, they're happy,
but Kaoru sure isn't.
When your heart's been broken,
there's nothing
to do but eat
and eat and eat
and eat some more!
Man, Kaoru's really gonna be
impossible to live with now.
I'm responsible
for this mess.
I brought you
a peace offering.
Here, give this to Kaoru,
and she'll feel better.
I hope so!
♪
Uh, excuse me, Kaoru?
Huh?
It's not a ring,
but I hope you'll
accept my sincere apology.
You're right, it's not a ring,
and I don't know if
I'll ever forgive you!
Don't be too hard on
him, it was all my fault.
Don't try and fix
it for them, Wadi,
they'll iron it
out for themselves.
They're nice.
Thanks so much.
Those flowers that you
brought are really very nice,
Wadi, I think
they did the trick.
Hey, I wonder where
Yoshi went off to!
♪
Here, I thought you
might like these!
Thank you!
That Kenshin!
I've gotta figure out
some way to get him
to propose to that poor girl.
She just loves him so much.
Oh, Kenshin,
they're so beautiful!
Really, I just love them.
♪
Well, that was a close call.
I'm so glad I don't
have a woman in my life
to complicate things.
(singing in Japanese)
♪
♪ It's gonna rain ♪
♪ It's gonna rain ♪♪
♪