(theme music)
♪
Sir, we welcome you home,
Great Shishio.
Thank you for the
welcome, gentlemen.
And thank you, Hoji.
All hail, Shishio!
Hail, Shishio!
Hail, Great Shishio!
♪
Just look at it.
It's really
great to be home.
Come on, Himura.
Oh, look, Misao
is back in town.
It's been ten years since
the Meiji Restoration
and I've been wandering
all over Japan.
I never thought I would
ever come back here.
(yelling)
The end of the
Tokugawa Regime,
it was a time
of tremendous
upheaval and chaos.
Not a day went by
without bloodshed.
-Himura!
-Huh?
Why are you standing there
like a bump on a log?
Can't you read
that big sign?
It's Grandpa's restaurant.
Sherry Baby's?
That's right and
a matter of fact,
it's a very
famous restaurant.
Hey!
Grandfather!
Hmm?
Hey, it's my Misao!
Grandpa!
(laughing)
We were so worried.
Grandpa, I'm so
sorry I arrived late.
Oh, yeah?
Ow!
That's what you
get for being late.
Open up, see, what
did I tell you?
Misao!
You're back!
Misao, wake up.
She's out
like a light.
Misao, don't you
recognize me?
Well, I'll
be on my way.
Wait, I haven't
thanked you properly.
You must be tired
from your journey.
Please, rest
before you go,
Battousai the Slasher.
You know hiding that
scar won't disguise you.
I still know
who you are.
I see.
Come inside, we'll
talk, follow me.
I'm gonna take a nice
hot bath to freshen up.
Ah, that's a
wonderful idea.
Tell me something.
During your long
journey together,
did Misao ever mention to
you that she was a member
of the Oni gang of spies?
And you must be...
I'm afraid so.
Your instincts are correct.
I am Nenji Kashiwazaki,
I once was an
important member
of the Oni gang's
spy network.
Code name: Okina.
I was part of a special
investigation team.
The Aoi-Ya was established
as the base for Edo,
but, unfortunately,
the Tokugawa Regime
fell first and many
of my colleagues
who were unemployed came
here looking for work.
And I hired them.
I see, that explains why
Aoshi sent Misao here
for you to take
care of her.
Then you are
familiar with Aoshi?
Yes, I am.
I suppose I should tell
you the entire story.
♪
Now I understand.
All of Aoshi's
Oni gang are dead
and Aoshi is missing.
Please, if you could,
keep this information
from Misao for
the time being.
Yes, I think
that's wise.
There's something
that I'd really like
to ask you, Battousai, you've
stayed away from this place
for over ten years, why
is that you return now,
if I might be so
bold as to ask?
Does your return
have anything to do
with your successor,
Makoto Shishio?
Hmm.
Trust me, Battousai,
I have experience
in these matters,
I know everything that
happens here and believe me,
I know all about Shishio.
I couldn't believe it
when I heard that
he was still alive,
but I know that
he's here in town
and probably
up to no good.
I also think that you
must have come here
because of him.
He has a lot of troops.
What do you say
we even out the odds
and you take me on
as your partner?
We'll massacre 'em.
Ah.
I love this city
the way it is now
and I'll be damned
if I'll let anyone
including Shishio destroy it.
If that means I
have to do my part,
I'll become an
old soldier again.
You're scaring me.
(singing)
Don't worry about the Aoi-Ya,
we're all trained
soldiers here.
Remember, we're all
former Oni gang spies.
We're fully capable
of protecting Misao
against any intruders,
if you get my drift.
-Listen...
-Nah, I'm afraid
I won't take no
for an answer.
I take full responsibility
for Misao's protection.
I really wish you wouldn't
get involved in this.
(laughing)
Too late!
All right, in that case,
I'll ask you one favor.
Sure, name it.
There are two people I would
like you to find right away.
Hmm?
Shakku Arai and
Seijuro Hiko.
Please locate these two
men for me right away.
♪
(water lapping)
Hey, Himura,
rise and shine!
Huh?
Rats, I wanted
to wake you up.
I've been up for a while,
what are you wearing?
It's what I wear
when I'm home.
There's no reason for me to
wear a spy suit around here,
you know, that
would be ridiculous.
Isn't it a good
morning, Okina?
-Sure is.
-Here, take this.
-Grandpa!
-Good morning,
how are you today?
Himura, I found
one of the two men
you were asking me
about yesterday.
He's dead.
Shakku Arai's passed away.
He was considered
the greatest craftsman
in the world for creating
samurai swords of all kinds.
A sword maker,
oh, I get it,
he wants to replace
the broken one.
But if this guy's dead,
there will never be
another reverse-edged sword.
But there is still hope.
Shakku has a son
and he was the great
sword builder's apprentice.
If anyone can build
your sword, he can.
Good, except it'll
be dangerous walking
with me in broad daylight.
Now if Shishio
is after you,
then he already
knows you're here.
There is no
hiding from him.
-Let's go.
-Okina?
Battousai, if you're
going to fight Shishio,
you must assume an air
of dignity at all times.
Huh?
You must assume the
style of a righteous man.
Bet you didn't know I was
so philosophical, did you?
I come up with some
pretty good stuff.
(laughing)
I know sometimes he
sounds a little nutty,
but when he belonged
to the Oni gang,
the group nominated him
to be the leader
of all operations.
But he declined
and recommended
Aoshi to the post.
He thought that
a younger leader
was a wiser
choice at the time.
He went on to
become a member
of the investigative team.
Shakku Arai was
known the world over
as the best
sword maker around,
but because he went from
making a cutting sword
to a killing sword,
he was considered a heretic
by the other sword makers.
The same sword maker
who made a killing sword
also made a
reverse-edged sword?
That just doesn't make
any sense to me, Grandpa.
Things don't always
make sense, angel.
Sometimes people do things
that appear contradictory.
Right, Himura?
Shakku's son took over
the family business.
His father taught him
to be a sword master
in his own right.
And because of
the Meiji Era,
there's been no
demand for fine swords.
He's had to make a living
making kitchen knives.
Let's hope he
can still make
a reversed-edge
sword for you.
Hello, we are customers,
we're looking for
Mr. Seiku Arai, is he in?
Hi!
Ahh!
-Huh?
-Seiku?
-Can't be.
-Hello!
So you want to
shake hands?
What's that,
who is this boy?
What's he want?
Give me your hands!
Oh, I get it, this boy's
the official greeter.
Iori, are you
being a good boy?
Ah, Mama!
Welcome, is there something
in our store
I can show you?
Yes, I would like to look
at some of your knives,
if it's all
right with you.
You want a knife?
May I try cutting something
with one of your knives?
-Sure.
-Yeah,
look at the knife!
(gasping)
-That's remarkable.
-Look at that.
It stuck together again
as if it were never cut.
How is that possible?
(speaking foreign language)
Amazing.
It means "restored cutting."
It's the first time
that I've ever seen
it performed before.
He cut this
without destroying
any of the essence.
None of the
fibers are damaged
so you're able to
stick it back together.
It's a highly
technical skill
that can only
be accomplished
with a fine blade and
a master swordsman.
That's incredible!
If his knives are that
good, can you imagine
what his reversed-edge
sword would be like?
We would like to
meet Mr. Seiku Arai,
the man who
crafted this knife.
Huh?
I would like to
commission him
to make a reversed-edge
sword for me right away.
Uh huh, but...
Hello.
-There you are.
-Daddy!
My name is Seiku Arai,
can I help you, sir?
I don't believe it,
you're Seiku Arai?
You don't look
like a master.
I know, everyone says that.
I happened to overhear
your conversation.
You were asking
if I could make
a special sword for you?
Actually, I no
longer make swords
so I'm afraid I'll have
to turn down your offer
to make you a new one.
-Huh?
-Hmm?
What?
I'm really sorry.
Listen here--
Why won't you make this
special sword for us?
My father was
considered to be
the best sword maker around.
He made thousands of swords
and they were
all used for war.
My father used
to say to me
that at the end of
the Tokugawa Era,
his swords would
make the new era.
He believed this
and his swords
became the weapon of choice.
Many men were killed
with my father's swords,
but I don't understand
what kind of new era
comes from bloodshed.
I really don't want
anything that I make
to be used for killing.
Ah, Daddy!
(gasping)
There, now I've got you.
Oh, I'm sorry, Seiku.
It's all right.
Besides, we're
in the Meiji Era.
Swords are not necessary
any longer, we're at peace.
I've decided that I don't
want to make swords anymore,
I only want to make
household items
that people can enjoy.
I don't want to make
things that hurt people.
Well, Seiku, I can see
that you and your father
are complete opposites when
it comes to these matters.
Oh, well, all I can say
is that I like peace,
I think everyone does.
I make tools that help,
not things that
destroy people's lives.
I can't believe what
I'm hearing here.
You're a wimp, there
are a lot of people
that are trying to
take away your peace.
We're trying
to help you
and you're too
stupid to know it!
Thanks for your
time, sorry we made
an unreasonable
request of you.
We'll be going now,
have a nice day!
What, we're leaving?
Bye-bye!
What are you gonna do
about getting a sword now?
I don't know but a
reversed-edge sword
is still a weapon
of destruction.
He made it clear he didn't
want any part of that,
and I wouldn't feel right
involving him in anything
that wasn't peaceful.
I'll just have to
find another way
to get a reversed-edge sword.
You know that swordsman?
He seemed to be in some kind
of trouble, didn't he, dear?
You don't have to
make him a new sword,
why not give him the last
sword your father made?
He really needs it.
Nah, it's not necessary.
Up you go.
This is the more
peaceful Meiji Era,
no one needs
swords anymore.
Battousai's been
spotted in town.
Tell Mr. Shishio immediately!
Right.
(giggling)
I can't believe that guy,
he was such a
self-righteous wimp,
you know, I would've
gotten that sword for you,
and I wouldn't have left
until he gave it to us.
No, that wouldn't be right.
I can't interfere with
his peaceful lifestyle
just for my own
personal reasons.
Now you're acting
just like a wimp!
Even if we forced him
to make us a sword,
it wouldn't be the
same as if he made it
with his heart and soul.
A sword made with no
spirit is worthless
and could prove
fatal to its owner.
The craftsman's
attitude is important
when creating a sword.
We don't need a sword
just for appearance sake,
the new reverse-edged sword
must exceed the old one.
You should've figured
that one out, Misao.
After all, I did
raise you, you know?
If you're so smart--
(smacking)
You're cracking my
ribs, you big dummy!
Who are you
calling dummy?
Why don't you try contacting
the other sword makers?
What do you think
I've been doing?
Handshake!
I know I did
the right thing.
If Seiku makes me
a reversed-edge sword,
Shishio's men will
come after him.
I don't want to
bring turmoil
to his peaceful family.
I don't want to bring
harm to these two either.
I know they're
professional spies,
but Shishio will
be tough to beat.
As soon as find
the other man,
I should leave here.
♪
(laughing)
Hoji, I trust that you
took care of everything
while I was away?
Yes, I got all of
the fire equipment
just as you requested.
I was just a
little curious
as to why Sojiro isn't
here with you right now.
I have put him in
charge of gathering
the Juppongatana, our
Ten Swords from East Japan.
The eastern men like
Anji are hard to contact.
And I personally took charge
of getting the men together
on the western
side of Japan.
Then we--
Yes.
As soon as all of the
ten swords arrive here,
we'll take over.
Yeah!
(cheering)
It is now the time
for an all-out revolt
against the
present government!
We must all be ready to
make the ultimate sacrifice.
Hail Great Shishio!
Hail Shishio!
♪
I should really
go and alert
the other associates
of our organization.
Hold on, I have
things I want to say.
It will take some time
before all of the Ten
Swords arrive here.
I am certain they will
be thirsty for blood.
As part of the celebration
before the takeover,
I will have
the Ten Swords
personally get rid
of Battousai Himura
once and for all.
But, Shishio,
the Ten Swords
are an integral part of
the special military unit.
They are extremely
vital to us.
What if they fight Battousai
and are defeated by him?
We can't afford
a loss like that.
I must say I was
surprised, too,
when he wanted the Ten
Swords to fight Battousai,
but they are
very powerful.
She's right.
You should listen
to her, Shishio.
After all, a
so-called slasher
could never defeat
the Juppongatana.
You're here early,
Cho the Sword Hunter.
That's because I live
so close in Osaka.
Besides I wanted a
chance to show off
my brand new sword.
I think that you'll
really appreciate it.
Look at this great sword.
It's called
a Masayuki Bizen,
I got it by
killing its owner.
This thing has
cut a lot of skin
and absorbed
a lot of blood
but it still shines
like a beautiful mirror.
It's truly magnificent,
don't you think?
(chuckling)
Whenever you
boys get together,
you get so excited talking
about your long swords.
Hoji, could you tell me
where Battousai is now?
Only a matter of time
before we find him.
But just the other
day he was seen
trying to buy a sword
from some merchant.
It turns out
it was Seiku,
son of Shakku Arai.
He's trying to replace
his reversed-edge sword
that Sojiro broke in
the last fight, and?
Seiku turned
down his request
to make him
a new sword.
But our informants tell us
that Shakku made
one before he died.
Battousai wasn't
able to obtain it.
Really, the last sword made
by the famous Shakku Arai
at the end of
the Tokugawa Era?
That's quite a
collector's item.
I have to have it.
We're nearing our goal,
don't cause a commotion, Cho.
Perish the thought.
(chuckling)
♪
I don't care what
Grandpa and Himura say.
I'm gonna get
that sword made.
It goes round and round.
(giggling)
Ha, your hair's like a tree.
A tree?
You should talk, your
head looks like a bean.
'Cause you're
a human bean.
Boy, where is
your father?
Huh, Daddy, Daddy!
Oh, hello there.
Is there something
I can help you with?
I heard that you have
Shakku's last sword.
What's that?
My dad's last sword?
That's right, your father
was kind of a hero to me
and I heard a rumor
that there was only one
of his swords left.
I understand
that you have it
and I was wondering if
you could show it to me.
I sold this guy
a sword before.
I'm afraid that you
are mistaken, sir.
If there are any of my
father's swords still around,
I certainly don't have them,
and to tell you the truth,
I think they're all gone.
Oh, yeah?
(gasping)
Well, I can't say
I'm not disappointed
that you don't
have the sword.
I guess you should never
pay too close
attention to rumors.
Sorry if I disturbed you,
it's just that I love
swords, I collect them.
And I would love to have
one of your father's swords.
-What are you doing?
-I suggest you relax.
♪
Whoa-ho!
Ahh!
Oh!
Iori!
(panting)
Oh!
On top.
(gasping)
(crying)
I call this next trick
"reverse mid-air
sword return"
and not too many
swordsman can do it.
It's a real shame that you
don't have that last sword.
Of all the swords,
Shakku's are my
very favorite.
Ah, well, we'll just
have to try another trick,
although I don't know
if I can be successful
two times in a row.
Here we go.
It's always more exciting
when something's at stake,
don't you think so?
Hey, leave him alone!
Oh, Seiku!
You two are in
for quite a treat.
I rarely give the
same performance
to the same audience.
We're going to have a
lot of fun this round
so keep watching.
Here we go.
Leave him alone, my
father-in-law's sword
is not even here.
-Azusa!
-Hmm?
We took his father's last
sword to the Hakusan shrine
and dedicated it as
a gift to the gods.
So you do know where
the sword is after all?
That was a mean trick
you tried to play on me.
I'm going to go and see
this sword for myself.
And just to make certain
that you're not
lying to me again,
I'm going to take a little
collateral with me this time.
I'll take your son with me.
(gasping)
(crying)
Please don't do this!
Stay where you are!
And don't do
anything dumb.
When I get the sword,
I'll release him,
so don't do
anything stupid,
you don't want to have
to start your family
all over again, do you?
(panting)
I have to convince him
to make that sword!
Why did you tell him
about that sword?
That sword was made
as an offering.
It's the only one that
isn't stained with blood.
If that sword
causes any bloodshed,
I don't think
I could handle
if my father will be
remembered as a monster
who created weapons
of destruction,
they'll forget that
he was a craftsman.
The memory of your
father is important,
but the life of our
son is more important,
and that's what I'm
worried about right now.
Didn't you see his eyes?
Those aren't the eyes
of one who loves swords.
Those are the eyes
of one who loves
to kill with a sword.
He's a cold-blooded killer.
If he finds father's
powerful sword,
he'll have an
unquenchable urge
to try it on the nearest
living thing to him.
Iori!
This is the reason
I didn't want to work
on swords any longer.
I'll just die if anything
happens to our child.
Weren't you
here earlier?
Tell me, what just happened?
We can't.
Tell me so I
can help you!
(panting)
Oh, it's you, Misao.
It's so nice to
see you again.
Shiga, have you seen my
grandfather anywhere?
It's really urgent.
(whooshing)
♪
Huh?
This bird belongs
to old lady Shiga.
I wonder what she wants.
Oh, yeah?
This is how we
send messages.
It's some kind
of emergency.
Hmm.
Shakku's little
child was kidnapped
by one of
Shishio's henchmen.
(gasping)
Wait, Himura,
your sword is broken.
They'll kill you!
Don't be a fool,
you can't fight
them with that sword!
Himura, don't do it!
Himura!
♪
(crying)
I can't wait
to get my hands
on that last
sword of Shakku.
It must really
be something.
Hmm?
♪
Ah, it's you!
You don't look like you'd
be a visitor to this shrine,
so who are you?
♪
Let the child go.
That's quite a scar.
There's only one man I
know that has that scar,
Battousai the Slasher.
So you came for the last
sword of Shakku, too, huh?
Well, I'm warning you,
I was here first
and I'll kill anyone
who comes between me
and my collection.
Get lost or I'll kill you!
♪
(theme music)