♪
I'll tell you what, Kenshin,
I'll let you borrow my
favorite blue ribbon,
but I'm only loaning
it to you, understand?
I don't want you
damaging it in any way.
You promise?
Oh, sure, I'll take
real good care of it!
All right, fine.
(grunting)
♪
(laughing)
Kori!
Worried about your girlfriend?
Don't leave!
That's it, boy, get mad!
Let me see you become
what you were years ago!
Hate me with all your guts!
Hate me enough to go back to
being Battousai the Slasher!
Kenshin!
(laughing)
Jinei!
♪
(bird squawking)
What do you hope to
accomplish by staring at me?
You think I'm going to
crumble into little pieces?
You coward!
Is this the only way you
think you can beat Kenshin?
♪
Don't be stupid.
If I wanted to defeat Battousai,
I could do it before I
finish this cigarette.
That's how weak he's become
since he stopped fighting.
But what kind of
challenge would that be?
I want him at his best!
Now he's mad.
Keeping you hostage
will inspire him
to become a slasher again.
No, you're wrong!
He's moved past that.
He'll never go back again!
Is that right?
Let me tell you, the boy's
a natural born killer!
At the end of the
Tokugawa regime,
Battousai was the most
talented swordsman in the land.
He was lethal.
Back then, I was also in Kyoto.
I was a Royalist working
for the Restoration.
A Royalist?
You?
(laughing)
♪
You are completely
out of control.
To preserve our honor, Jinei,
we're going to have
to eliminate you.
Your death will be merciful.
(yelling)
♪
(grunting)
There was only one
fighter who had the nerve
and the skill to challenge me.
Battousai the Slasher.
We fought often.
Neither of us was able
to beat the other man.
It was bloodlust.
That was in the past.
He's a much different man
than the one you remember.
He'll never go back to
being a killing machine!
He's beyond that!
(laughing)
(birds cawing)
You're kidding!
Kori's been kidnapped?
"Jinei has designated the place
for the final duel between us.
If I should die, you'll be the
only ones who can help Kori,
but be careful!
Jinei is as deadly
as his blades."
Huh?
He's gone off to
save Kori by himself.
I guess he wants
to settle the fight
with this creep
slasher to slasher.
That's fine except
for one thing!
Kenshin stopped being a
slasher a long time ago!
It won't be a fair fight.
He knows his skills aren't
as sharp as this monster's.
It's his damn pride.
♪
There's nothing to talk about!
I'm goin' after him!
Wait, you fool!
Ow, I'm gonna save
Kori and Kenshin!
I don't care what he's
done in the past, you hear?
I don't care about
the Tokugawa regime!
Don't try to stop me!
I'm not trying to stop you.
You won't be much
help without a weapon.
Right.
-Don't fall behind!
-We'll see who gets there first!
♪
(clock ticking)
His time is just about up.
♪
(gasping)
So, the last act is
finally gonna be played out.
Kenshin!
(gasping)
♪
Your eyes tell me
you're ready to fight.
Yes, I'm ready.
I'm ready to have my revenge.
I'll kill you for
kidnapping Kori,
and for humiliating me!
That's not the Kenshin I know.
It's like he's possessed!
(laughing)
I knew the warrior in
you would finally come out!
All you need to complete
the transformation
is a proper weapon!
Come on, show me
the man who killed
for the simple joy of murder!
Shut up!
(laughing)
(clanking)
♪
(laughing)
This is your last battle, Jinei!
He's enraged!
Is this was Battousai
the Slasher was like?
You think you can agitate me!
Forget it, I've waited
years for this face off!
♪
One-handed thrust!
Next comes a straight move
followed by the side slash.
From there the crossroad
leading to the
cut straight down,
then the thrust of destruction!
♪
(laughing)
Kenshin!
♪
-Kori!
-Kenshin!
No answer.
Where could they be?
We'd better find them fast
or there'll be nothing left
but bodies to bring home.
This won't do.
This is not the Battousai
I've been waiting
for all these years.
You see, the truth is
you don't really
want to destroy me yet.
As long as you feel you can
defeat me without killing me,
I can slice you up with
very little effort at all.
It's quite a disappointment.
Kenshin, Kenshin!
Leave him alone, you monster!
You're insane, you hear me?
You're a demon!
Leave him alone!
(laughing)
Apparently you need
some more motivation!
♪
Ken...
shin!
Talk to me, Kori!
Jinei, you did something to her!
What did you do?
I put a real strong
crouch spell on her.
She should be finding
it very hard to breathe.
She'll suffocate in
about five minutes or less.
What?
(laughing)
There are only two ways to
release her from the spell--
one would be for her
to break it on her own,
but that would take
a person of iron will.
Someone whose powers are
much greater than mine.
I wouldn't count on
her being that person.
The only other way to break it
is if I were no longer
able to maintain control.
♪
In other words, you're
going to have to kill me,
or she'll die.
♪
Don't you get it?
You have no choice left!
Unless, of course,
you're willing to
let her choke to death.
♪
Damn you.
Don't you understand?
You have no choice here!
Unless you're willing to
let the girl choke to death.
That's such an ugly
way for her to die!
(laughing)
Stop this.
Don't bother to
beg for her life!
The time for talk is past!
Whatever you have to tell me
you can say with your sword.
(yelling)
(panting)
(laughing)
I never even saw you move!
Only one man could pull off
the soaring sword maneuver,
a master killer
resurrected from the dead!
That's you,
Battousai the Slasher!
Now that you've returned,
I presume you're
ready to face me.
The time for talk is past.
Whatever you have to tell me
you can say with your sword.
I'm gonna kill you.
Ken--Ken--Kenshin!
You're threatening me?
Good!
Very good!
♪
I've been waiting
to hear you say that!
Now I know you're finally back!
This will determine
who's the best,
me or you!
Stop, Kenshin!
Don't do it!
(laughing)
The final battle
is about to begin!
Say your prayers, Battousai!
♪
-Cold feet?
-No!
I just decided it's
best to take precautions.
When it comes down to it,
you're no ordinary opponent.
♪
I figure, to protect myself,
I better create an advantage.
Otherwise, I might
as well commit suicide.
The crouch spell is designed
to make a person
weak and helpless.
I will use a reverse version
of that spell on myself!
When I'm through, it will
release all my dormant strength
and put me on an
equal footing with you!
♪
I am unbeatable!
I am invincible!
♪
I am your worst nightmare!
There's a variation
of the crouch spell
called the demon possession.
I haven't used it in 15 years,
but I was able
to invoke it today.
Allow me to
demonstrate its power!
♪
Yahhh!
(clanking)
Very impressive, but useless.
I said I was gonna kill you,
and that's how it'll be.
There's no spell strong
enough to overcome my will.
♪
Look at him!
He's in the killing position!
Removing the sword allows
him to speed up the motion
and slice his opponent to
pieces in a split second!
It would be bad enough in the
hands of a regular assassin,
but his speed is supernatural!
Now, step forward
and face me man-to-man!
I'll show you how I got my name!
♪
I know where he got his name.
From the batto technique
of drawing his sword.
It leads to death
from a single blow!
But he has nothing
left afterwards,
so if I can dodge
his initial attack,
I might be able to survive.
♪
I can do it--I must!
His blade is curved,
so there will be a slight
delay in withdrawing it.
That's his weakness!
♪
It's all over for
you, Battousai!
♪
You missed with your
first lunge, now I'm--
(grunting)
You tricked me with
the double batto maneuver.
(gasping)
I used the flying sword strategy
followed by the
Double Dragon Flash!
I knew that my reverse blade
didn't suit the
standard batto technique.
So I mastered all the variations
that were ever developed,
and that's how I
got the name Battousai.
I cut the tendon in
your right shoulder.
You'll never be able
to use your sword again.
Not that it matters, because
now I'm gonna kill you!
♪
Kenshin!
(wind blowing)
What's the matter?
Are you having second thoughts?
This is where your weak
will defeats you, Battousai.
In order to save the
girl, you have to kill me.
Stop, Kenshin!
I understand, but for
the chance to rescue Kori,
I'll risk becoming a
slasher one more time!
This is my victory!
Even as I die, I will
emerge triumphant!
You're in a corner,
Battousai, you're trapped!
So be it.
My sword was a deadly weapon...
♪
and my swordsmanship was
just a technique for killing.
No matter how I
tried to avoid it,
this was the truth of my life.
♪
But now I've learned to
turn away from the past
because, for me, nothing
matters anymore except Kori
and her sweet spirit.
♪
Kenshin!
Kenshin.
I love you, Kori!
Oh, Kenshin!
♪
Don't let that man force
you into killing again!
Don't go back to
committing murder!
(grunting)
Kori!
♪
Kori, talk to me!
Tell me you're okay!
What did you say?
Are you able to breathe freely?
♪
The spell must be broken.
I'm okay!
You're sure?
I'm speaking.
That must mean something!
I guess I overcame
the spell somehow.
I must say, I'm impressed.
I would never have believed
my spell could be
broken by a woman.
Put away your weapon, Jinei.
You can't use your
right arm anymore.
There's no point to
continuing this vendetta.
You might as well turn
yourself in to the authorities.
It's all over for you now.
I'm the one who
decides when it's over!
I'll never surrender!
Not while I can--
(grunting)
It's the only way.
♪
Don't look at me with pity
in your eyes, Battousai.
I don't want it.
It was better when you said
you were going to kill me.
You may not believe it, but
you'll always be a slasher.
Take it from someone
who knows what
bloodlust is all about.
Slashers are slashers
until the day they die.
They can never be anything else.
You're a fool if you think
you can deny your true nature.
I'll be there to greet
you at the gates of Hell.
(laughing)
♪
Maybe he's right.
Maybe I'll be a slasher
till the day I die.
You all right?
I guess we should
contact the police.
Look, footprints!
I think they could be Kenshin's!
What--are you sure?
Of course I'm sure!
They lead this way!
They're heading
right for the meadow!
You idiot, those are cow prints!
No, they're not!
I know a cow's print!
Get out of the way!
-Ow!
-Let go of me!
Little brat!
Hey, blockhead, we found them!
Don't worry about a thing, guys.
I'm here to help save you!
He'll have to
save himself first.
(laughing)
Oh.
Rats, after all that,
we didn't get there
in time to help!
What a waste.
Probably would've done
better if we'd eaten first.
It's hard to be a hero
on an empty stomach.
From now on, no rescues
till after lunch.
That was quite an experience.
Are you sure you're
all right, Kori?
I'm fine.
Um, Kenshin?
Thanks a lot for
coming to save me.
I'm not very good at
expressing gratitude.
Listen, the truth of the matter
is I'm the one who
should be thanking you!
Huh?
Kenshin, what do you mean?
If you hadn't stopped
me when you did,
I would've killed Jinei,
and my past would've
caught up with me.
I probably would've gone
back to being a slasher.
You saved me from that.
I'm just glad you had
the strength to stop.
Yeah, me too!
Oh, I almost forgot!
I'm still carrying
your blue ribbon!
I wanted to be sure
to return it to you.
Here you go!
(groaning)
What's the matter,
don't you want it back?
What happened to it?
Gee, I guess it
got a little bloody.
That ribbon was the
nicest one I ever had!
I should've known you'd
find some way to wreck it,
-you clumsy ox!
-I'm sorry!
It wasn't my fault!
Hey, you stepped on my foot!
What wasn't his fault?
You're a kid.
You wouldn't understand!
Who are you callin' a kid?
♪
You're wrong, Jinei.
I may have been a slasher once,
but I'll never go
back to that dark path,
no matter what happens.
♪
I have a new road to travel now,
and with the help of my friends,
I'll make that
journey in sunlight,
not in shadow.
♪