♪
(singing in foreign language)
(waves crashing)
Himura!
Hey, Himura, wait up!
I don't know what you're
trying to prove, Himura.
You don't have to fight
Shishio, you know.
I really wish you'd
just think this over!
Just forget the
whole thing and go home!
Yo, Red, I'm talking to you!
Come on, there must be
someone who would cry
if you were killed.
Unbelievable.
I worry about you
and you don't care
about your own future.
Maybe you'd like it better
if I didn't give a damn
what happened to you at all.
Maybe you don't have any friends
who care about you either.
Well?
Huh?
I have friends.
Back in Kyoto.
I knew it, they're probably
worried sick about you, Himura.
Really?
You really think they are?
Of course they are,
what are you thinking about?
They're your friends,
aren't they, you bonehead!
(grunting)
You are so thick sometimes!
Don't fight this guy, Himura.
You'll come to my house
when we get to Edo
and we'll have a huge
feast when we get there.
And you'll rest.
Won't that be great?
So don't lie there, let's go!
Come on, I bet you
can't catch me, Himura!
Maybe she's right.
Maybe they are worried about me.
I wonder what they're doing now.
Himura!
(waves crashing)
♪
(bird squawking)
This isn't right.
I think I took a wrong
turn back there somewhere.
Which one of these paths
will take me to Edo?
Where the heck am I?
I wonder if this is
the right way there.
Damn!
I wonder if Kenshin's
in Edo by now.
I wonder if Kori and Yoshi
have even left for Edo yet.
And what about Megumi?
Nah, she can't go,
she has patients.
I'm sure that
bastard's in Edo by now.
I don't want to think about him.
(groans loudly)
♪
Huh?
Something about this forest
looks very familiar to me.
What is it?
♪
(groans)
All this walking around
has made me very hungry.
My last one.
After this biscuit's gone,
I'll have to catch some frogs
or something.
Here it goes.
(groaning)
(thunderous crash)
(growling)
Hey, who dares
to disturb my dinner?
Don't you know that
dining is sacred?
Show yourself!
(chanting)
♪
Huh?
(thunderous crash)
(gasps)
This guy must be a monk
in some kind of hidden cult.
What's that he's doing?
Some kind of chanting?
(yells)
(thunderous crashing)
That was amazing!
Just great!
Is that some kind
of monk power
that you're using
on those rocks?
I've never seen anything
like that before, my friend.
Could I see that again?
Are you lost...friend?
Yeah, I don't have
a clue where I am.
Boy, am I starving.
Got any food,
I'm weak from hunger.
Did anyone ever tell you
you have bad manners?
(bird squawking)
I'm sorry my training
interrupted your meal.
I trust you're
enjoying your frog.
Mmm, oh yeah, it's delicious.
Best frog I ever tasted.
Thanks to you, I have
a hot meal and a drink
and I was able to observe
you practicing houriki
earlier today.
You're wrong, I wasn't
practicing houriki.
Hmm?
Houriki is nothing
but a bunch of lies
made up to make people
have stronger faith.
I've never seen it
and I used to be a monk.
It doesn't exist.
And if it does,
it's no use to me.
A lot of lies are told to people
to get them to have faith.
I didn't think monks
drank any kind of alcohol
or ate any kind of meat.
I'm what they call
a depraved monk.
Destructive monk?
No, a depraved monk.
A depraved monk is one who
has violated all the laws
and every one of the
commandments of Buddha.
Oh.
(fire crackling)
Well, it makes sense now.
You don't look
like your everyday,
run-of-the-mill kind of monk.
You have sort of
an evil look to you.
You don't look like
a religious man yourself.
Ha, anyway, I wanna
hear more about you.
If you gave up your faith
like you said you did,
why are you out here
training in the woods?
I may have left my faith,
but I still have
a strong desire
to save this world
of ours, my friend.
Only people can save
their own world.
I train to gain
the power to do so.
To help save our world,
I will need the strength that
will even surpass the gods.
That is my extraordinary quest
that I have set out
to attain, my friend.
That's great.
You didn't become
a depraved monk
out of selfish greed, did you?
(fire crackling)
Tell me something.
Have you ever heard of
the anti-Buddhist movement
of ten years ago?
Huh?
No use discussing it
if you haven't.
I really don't know what
burdens you bear, my friend,
but tell me,
if that wasn't houriki
that you were doing,
that means that a faithless bum
like me could do it, right?
Can you teach me
that technique?
I promise that I
won't use it for evil.
How come you desire
to have such strength?
How come?
What is this, one of
those Zen conversations?
Well, there are
many reasons, really.
Hmm, but actually,
it's very important
for me to make myself
much stronger.
When I left Tokyo recently,
I had a terrible fight
with this one guy.
He told me that I don't
know the basics of defense.
He told me that I
didn't know how to fight
and proceeded to give me
a total thrashing.
(groaning)
I wanna know your secret weapon!
I wanna become strong on my own!
Won't you please
teach it to me?
Please, I'll do anything.
Don't do it.
Yeah, why not?
There are many
who are just like you,
who desire
extraordinary strength.
However, Sanosuke, there
isn't a single soul around here
who can survive my
rigid training method.
You'll never know
until you try me, Anji.
It's dangerous.
You could lose your life.
I'm not sure I'd take
the chance if I were you.
Maybe you should just
admit your limitations.
Well, hey, I'm willing
to give it a whirl
if you are.
See for yourself
if I'm a weakling.
(yelling)
(chuckles)
Please, I need to be strong.
I have a very good reason
for wanting to be strong
and I know that next to you
wanting to save the world
my reasons may seem very selfish
to someone like yourself,
but as far as I'm concerned,
it's worth risking my life for.
(fire crackling)
I want to ask you one question.
I want you to tell me
how you feel about something.
All right, go ahead,
how do I feel about what?
The Meiji government.
What kind of question is that?
What in the world could
that have to do with anything?
Ask me something
that's pertinent
to why I want to the strength
and I'll answer that question.
I hate them, if you must know.
They killed my captain
and tricked us all
into becoming traitors.
But what does that have
to do with anything?
Never mind.
Listen to me.
You are about to apply
force to this rock
in order to break it.
However, anything,
including this rock,
has a resistance all of its own
that will prevent
any external forces
from going through it.
Any attempt to break it
will be a waste of force.
At least that is the way it
has always been, until now.
And now?
And now there is a way
to prevent this waste.
First of all, apply
the force to the rock
with your fist vertically.
Then at the instant
the force of the initial blow
contacts the resistance
of the rock,
bend your fist to apply
the second force.
When you do this,
your second force
will not be met
with any resistance.
It'll go through
the rock completely
and pulverize it into pieces.
♪
It took me ten full years
of training to acquire
this secret weapon
I now call "Futae No Kiwami."
It means "the dual extreme."
The dual extreme...
It has been a very helpful
secret weapon to me.
As you know, you can do
what you saw me do:
destroy things from a distance.
It seems so simple, really, when
you stop and think about it.
I don't know if this
is such a good idea
to tell me all
about this stuff.
-Here, try it out.
-Huh?
♪
(grunting)
Hey, it didn't break
into a lot of pieces.
You're just hitting
the rock twice.
Huh?
The force should be
applied very swiftly,
practically instantaneously
in just a split second.
At that second, you need
to apply the second force.
(thunderous crash)
(gasps)
After I had created the secret
of the dual extreme in my mind,
it took me an entire month
before I could crush
a single rock into pieces.
You'll need an entire month
to work on this yourself.
You once told me
you'd risk your life
to try this.
If you don't master this,
you'll have to die.
♪
The dual extreme
is a secret weapon
that I alone created
in order to save the world.
It is not meant to be
taught to others
or to be spread around.
You either complete
this successfully
or you'll have to die.
Those are my conditions.
I've never met any monk
who asked for my life
in exchange for knowledge,
but all right, you have a deal.
If I can't learn this,
you can kill me.
I'll risk my life to
obtain this knowledge.
At any rate, I don't
have time to waste.
I don't need a month
to learn your technique.
I'll learn it in one week.
♪
(grunting)
(cracking)
Darn it, I'm doing
something wrong.
Try to hit the rock swiftly
and twice in succession.
Sounds easy enough,
but I just can't do it.
Listen to me,
the dual extreme
is very difficult,
if not impossible.
Do you think you can understand
what I was trying
to tell you now?
Why don't you admit it's
impossible to do in a week?
I will do it!
Ah, you are a
hammer head, my friend.
This is only day three,
I still have four more days.
I told you that I could
do it in a week and I will!
Just wait four more days
before telling me
it's impossible.
♪
Advising you is like
preaching to the deaf.
Hey, who are you calling deaf?
Those who won't hear.
Oh, just shut up.
Fine.
You have just four days left.
♪
In four days, you had better
have mastered the dual extreme.
(grunts)
Or as we agreed upon,
you will die.
I'll master it, friend.
(yelling)
If it's easy from the start...
(grunting)
...and not worth risking...
my life for...
it's not worth it!
What I really want is...
Impossible.
He's wasting his energy.
Futae No Kiwami
is the end result
of my ten years of training.
It's not something
that can be attained
with just spirit.
(yelling)
(panting)
I'm not even close
to getting the answer.
(growling)
No!
(grunting)
-Yoshi!
-Huh?
I'm glad to see that you're
finally over your seasickness.
Yeah, I decided to come up here
and get a little practice.
I have to maintain my status
as the star of
the Kamiya Kasshin school.
Oh really?
In that case, I think
I should be your opponent.
All right, come on!
So, Kori, you think you can
beat the master, do ya?
Come on, and I won't hold back.
(yelling)
(grunting)
You still have a long way to go.
Yeah, I'm just getting started!
(exclaiming, applause)
♪
-Huh?
-These people are actually
applauding us.
They think we're
the ship's entertainment.
Let's finish the show.
(giggling)
(applause, cheering)
(yelling)
I'll never get
this technique down.
♪
Is it like this
or is it like that?
Or is it a timing thing?
(yelling)
Huh?
♪
(yelling)
I've gotta get this down
by tomorrow or else...
♪
(yelling)
This time I...
I have all night
to figure it out!
(yelling)
♪
(panting)
Can't stop, have to keep trying.
There's still time.
(groaning)
Guess I used up all
the good rocks around here.
I should look for some others.
Better get going
while there's still time.
(grunting)
Time's running out,
but I don't feel like
I have any more energy.
(candle wick hissing)
(grunting)
I'm so tired.
I can't go on.
Can't think straight
but if I give up, I'm dead.
(wind blowing)
Huh?
Sanosuke...
Captain Sagara?
Is that you?
I must be hallucinating.
I'm over-fatigued.
(hysterically whimpering)
You don't have any feet,
you're a ghost!
Don't be afraid of me, Sanosuke.
I would never hurt you.
You have done your best,
given it your all.
If you admit to the monk
that you cannot do it,
he will spare your life.
But if you continue like this,
I'm afraid you'll kill yourself.
I can't do that, Captain.
I want you to stop
trying right now.
Forget everything and rest.
That is an order.
♪
I can't obey that order.
I remember the day
our Sekiho troop
was labeled traitors.
They took you,
you were executed,
and they put
your head on display
for all the people to see.
All I had was hatred
for those Meijis
and I blamed and
hated myself as well.
Because I had lost you,
the one person
in the whole world
that I respected the most
and there was nothing
I could do about it.
♪
I was like a man without
any soul, wandering aimlessly,
hating everything and everybody,
not even knowing
what to do with myself.
Ten years passed
and a good friend
brought me back to life.
Now he's caught up in the
biggest fight of his career
and may get killed.
I don't want to have to
endure that kind of pain
in my life again!
I just couldn't take it!
I finally found a family,
a place where I belong,
a place where I can laugh again.
And that is why I have to
learn this secret weapon.
To help my friend.
You should understand that.
I have to attain the strength
to overpower evil
with these fists!
♪
Captain, even if
you are a dream,
or a phantom,
or in my imagination,
I'm glad I got the
chance to see you again.
Goodbye, friend.
Goodbye.
And may Buddha bless you.
♪
Hm?
Poor fellow wouldn't give up.
I guess he killed
himself trying.
I'll give him a proper burial.
Don't bury me just yet.
(chuckles)
(yawns)
I was just catching
a little shut-eye.
Looking at the rock
in your hand,
it appears that you
did not have enough time
to master the dual extreme.
Hmm.
(grunts)
(thunderous crashing)
(gasps)
It was just this morning
that I got it.
Once I figured it out,
it's really easy.
I guess that I was right,
I was able to understand
your secret in just a week.
You've got quite a talent there.
Hey, I almost died
trying to figure this out!
Don't reduce it all to talent.
It took a lot more
than just some talent.
You're right.
I didn't mean to
simplify your achievement.
Hmm.
Real good job.
I must say,
you've impressed even me.
You are the only one
who knows my secret.
Well, I've spent
too much time here already.
I'm on sort of a mission really.
I have to be
leaving for Edo now.
-Edo?
-Yeah.
I think I can find my way
once I get to Nakasendo.
Oh, that's easy.
This is Shimosuwa.
Just go through the forest
and then you'll arrive
at Nakasendo.
(gasps)
Shimosuwa?
Yes, is something
the matter with that?
(laughing)
No wonder this forest
looked familiar.
Shimosuwa is where the
Sekiho troop got wiped out!
♪
Pardon me for laughing
like a lunatic,
but I haven't had
very much sleep lately.
It's just that something
struck me funny
and I think, for
the first time in my life,
I believe in divine providence.
How's that?
Never mind, forget
I said anything.
I just wanted to thank you
for everything, Anji.
I really enjoyed
my time with you.
I hope to see you again soon.
Goodbye!
You can count on it,
Sanosuke Sagara.
You have a safe trip.
I can't believe it,
but in one night
he went from being
a braggart kid
to a mature man.
I hope he uses
the secret wisely.
Ah, there you are.
I've been looking
all over for you.
Ah, it's you, Mr. Soujiro.
The battle is going
to begin very soon.
All ten of the
Juppongatana swordsmen
are to report to
Edo immediately.
This is a direct order
from Mr. Shishio himself.
Hmm.
♪
We'll be arriving soon, Kori!
We'll get to Osaka tomorrow
and then Edo won't be more than
a couple of days after that!
Great!
I can't wait to see
Kenshin again.
♪
Hurry, Himura!
Hey, come on!
I'm coming, what's the big rush?
There's just one more mountain.
We're practically in Edo!
I just can't wait
to see everyone.
I guess I can't blame her.
She's anxious to get home.
Once we get home,
I'll show him.
I'll use truth serum to get
him to talk about Aoshi.
(laughing diabolically)
♪
I can't believe
I'm coming back here.
It's been ten long years
since I was here.
I never thought
I would return to Edo.
Hurry up, come on!
I think I know what awaits
me over those mountains
and I'm afraid a lot of blood
is going to spill this time.
♪
(singing in foreign language)