♪
Look out!
Huh?
(gasps)
Hey!
That was close.
♪
(gasps)
Look up there.
(bats squeaking)
Careful!
Get away from here!
(grunting)
(yelling)
♪
(yells)
-What?
-Huh?
(breathing shakily)
♪
(laughing)
We are the
Sanada Three.
You can't win.
None of you will ever make it
out of this place alive.
Time to die.
Who does this guy
think he's dealing with?
Well, it's obvious he's
never dealt with us before.
That's right.
This guy found the
wrong group to pick on.
Let's do it.
(grunting)
♪
What's wrong with Sano?
He can't get
close to that guy.
That sasumata's very sharp.
The fact that his hand's
injured doesn't help.
He has to wear him down.
Be very careful, Sano.
(yelling)
♪
(bats squeaking)
Look at that!
Where do all those
bats come from anyway?
All these bats
are from Baku.
He can actually
communicate with the bats.
He's trained
them himself.
He talks to bats?
Sounds like a nut!
(bats squeaking)
That's it!
What are you saying, Yutaro?
Bats hear certain pitches
that human beings can't hear.
He must be
using those sounds
to communicate
with the creatures.
Bats are pretty smart
and they can be trained
to do simple tasks.
He's right.
They must be using
the bats the same way
we would use
carrier pigeons.
The Oni gang uses pigeons to
send messages back and forth.
That's exactly right.
There's also another reason
he trained those creatures.
♪
Huh?
(yells)
(laughing)
What was that?
Some sort of illusion?
(groans)
♪
(yells)
Kenshin!
♪
How is he doing that?
What's causing it?
Leave him alone!
Ren!
Ren, leave him alone.
His death will
accomplish nothing.
Stay away from him.
You can't defeat him
in your weakened condition.
Listen, Kaita, I'm only
following my orders.
I'm not exactly sure what
it is you think you're doing,
but I think that
you'd better remember
whose side you're on
and remember it quickly.
Ren, I am
a Sanada ninja.
I know whose
side I'm on.
Protecting the
medicine is our duty.
I'm torn.
It used to be a source
of pride to be a ninja.
Where's the pride in
protecting the medicine
if we end up selling out
to those Black Knights?
He's right!
Don't you know what'll
happen to everybody
if those Black Knights
get their grubby paws
on all the holy medicine?
They'll take over and
control the entire world
and they won't give a damn
about you or anybody else.
You're all going to die.
Hey, are you crazy?
I am a soldier, and
like any good soldier,
I do what my
commander tells me.
I have no time to
listen to you lecture me
on what is good
and what is evil.
The world doesn't care
about good and evil.
It only cares about winners.
The evil ones are good
if they are winners.
That's not true!
We're here because
good people fight
for what they believe in.
If evil dominated the world,
the human race would have
vanished a long time ago.
If you do this, you'll
help to destroy the world,
cause the Black Knights
want it all for themselves.
Very nice.
What a speech, little man.
Since you're so
interested in what's evil,
I'll make you a
little proposition.
Listen up.
If you losers can
defeat the Sanada Three,
then you will be good.
However, if we defeat you
cretins, then you'll be evil,
and once we
kill all of you,
this will all seem
more reasonable.
I've had it!
(yells in pain)
Oh, no, Kaita!
♪
Yutaro!
Don't do this!
It's not worth
getting killed for.
(yells)
Leave me alone!
But I just saved you.
Stay out my way!
You can't do it alone.
Stop fighting
with each other
or you're going to
get us all killed.
We have got
to help Kaita.
(yells in pain)
(laughing)
(straining)
♪
(laughing evilly)
This guy's too strong.
I can't hold him
off much longer.
(laughing)
(straining)
Hey, you big ape!
Huh?
Leave him alone!
(yells)
(screams)
(grunts)
Huh?
(yells)
(groans)
(snickers)
Way to go, Sanasuke!
Yeah, I couldn't use my hand,
so I used my elbow.
That jerk almost
shish-kabobed me.
(grunts)
Sanasuke!
Kaita, we've got to
get you out of here.
Kenshin!
Looks like Battosai,
the Slasher,
is on his knees
to Ren, the Snake.
I'm not just fighting
against you, Ren, the Snake.
My real opponent is
somewhere else, isn't he?
What are you talking about,
Battosai?
You are delirious!
Now, get ready to die.
Must have something
to do with those bats.
Kenshin!
It's Baku
controlling the bats.
Huh?
(bats squeaking)
(gasps)
♪
You're dead.
(groaning)
♪
They're all dying.
Why is that?
(yells)
♪
(screaming)
Kenshin!
The bats were emitting
a subsonic sound
effecting my vision.
That's what caused my
equilibrium to be altered.
I have never heard of
bats being used like that.
How did you ever figure out
what it was they were doing?
If Kaita hadn't
given me a clue,
I never would have been
able to figure it out.
Thanks for you help, Kaita.
Well, that's good, but we've
got a lot more injuries now.
I'm having trouble keeping
up with all of this.
You're doing great.
Good thing you're
here, Yutaro,
cause wherever we go,
we need a doctor.
(all laughing)
Now that that's over,
we should move on.
Are you all right, Sano?
Yeah, I'm all right.
Yutaro should take a look
at your injuries, Sano.
I'll be just fine,
Kaoru, no need to worry.
But how are we going to go
after the Black Knights now?
We have absolutely
no idea where they are.
I'm pretty sure
the Sanada Three
won't tell us
anything at all.
What about the bats?
(bat squeaking)
They said they used
the bats to communicate.
Do you think they'll find
their way to the Black Knights?
Yeah!
Let's just follow them.
♪
(gasps)
You have to see this!
♪
It's-- it's amazing.
What a lovely garden!
♪
It reminds me of
the Garden of Eden,
or how I imagined it
looked when I was a kid.
It's really beautiful.
It's absolutely perfect.
This is incredible.
It's unbelievable
that all of this
grew underground
without any sunlight.
I did it!
I finally found the
holy miracle medicine.
(laughing)
♪
With this kind of power,
we can rule the world!
(laughing maniacally)
(bats squeaking)
♪
We'll take all of these
flowers back to the homeland
and give them to our
scientists to analyze.
(laughing sinisterly)
And soon we'll have
a brand new medicine.
A medicine that can cure
all kinds of illnesses
and only the people
we want to will get it.
Right, with that miracle
medicine in our hands
the entire world will be at
the feet of the Black Knights.
This medicine is all we
need to take over the world.
Uh-huh.
A new world order will be
created with us in charge.
The Black Knights will
be feared the world over.
I just cannot wait to deliver
this great news to our master.
♪
(sniffs)
Hey, there, Meldars.
You haven't forgotten
our deal, have you?
Hmm?
In exchange for leading you
to this miracle medicine...
We, of the Sanada ninja
group, will rule Japan.
That was our
agreement with you.
♪
Misanagi,
without your help
we couldn't have
found this medicine.
We thank you,
but you seem
to have outlived
your usefulness to us.
-Hmm?
♪
What do you
mean by that?
♪
(grunts)
Meldars,
stop this!
You're going back
on the promise
that you made to Misanagi.
Well, Schneider,
I told her what I had to
in order to get her to
help us find the medicine.
I would do or say anything
I had to for the Black Knights.
We are the rulers,
not anyone else.
(gasps)
You don't have to feel sorry for
these rice eaters, Schneider.
Meldars, you were even
planning on betraying Misanagi
from the very
beginning, weren't you?
The woman was merely
a stepping stone
to allow us to
accomplish our goal.
The one who is deceived is
the stupid one, Schneider.
Remember that,
Second Lieutenant.
Yes, sir.
♪
(breathing heavily)
I suppose we should
be thanking you.
Without you, we never
would have found this place.
It's a shame I
have to carve you up.
If things were different, maybe
we could have gotten together.
(grunts)
(groans)
♪
(yells)
(grunting)
♪
You don't know who
you're dealing with.
My ninjas will kill you.
You've got me all scared.
(groans)
Oh, you're hurt.
It's a shame every time you
move, your wound opens more.
Just stand still and
let me cut you in half.
(laughing evilly)
Time to say
goodbye, my dear.
♪
(laughing evilly)
Time for you to split!
♪
(groans)
Schnei-- why, Schneider!
♪
Just what do you
think you're doing?
Meldars, I used to think
of you as a great man
that I would have
followed anywhere.
I respected you and
admired you as a friend,
but you have
betrayed that trust.
You're a liar.
So, you are deliberately
disobeying an order?
That is serious.
No, Meldars, what is serious
is lying and cheating
and disgracing
everything I believe in.
You forget one
important thing, Schneider.
We are not some ordinary
soldiers or swordsmen.
We are members
of an elite group
that will someday
rule the world.
We are sworn members
of the Black Knights.
You, yourself,
have sworn allegiance.
You must obey a superior
officer's orders
or you will
suffer consequences.
We have all sworn
loyalty to the master.
So, Meldars, the end justifies
the means, is that it?
♪
You will stand fast, or
you are finished with us.
Mm-mm.
♪
Schneider, have you lost
your mind all together?
You can't do this!
Meldars has given
you a direct order.
Don't throw it all
away for this woman.
What are you doing?
♪
(groans)
Don't do this.
Those men will
kill you too.
Why are you--?
I am a knight,
not a butcher.
Meldars will
come after me.
When we are fighting, get
out of here any way you can.
Otherwise, he'll
kill both of us.
Don't wait, just go
and get out of here.
-And you?
-Just leave!
♪
(yells)
(grunts)
♪
Just remember, your sword style,
your fighting technique.
I taught you everything!
Do you seriously believe for one
minute that you can defeat me?
Well, you are wrong.
Ja, you taught me,
but you taught me to use
a sword only as a weapon
to do all of your evil deeds
for the Black Knight group,
but I have seen another way.
The sword has other uses.
Fighting that
samurai the other day
made me think about
a lot of things, Meldars.
He fought with pure spirit.
He was on the side of right
and with that knowledge,
he gained true strength.
I could see it in his eyes,
and I knew in my heart
that killing the
old man was wrong.
(yelling)
♪
He could've killed me,
yet he spared me, perhaps,
so I, too, could do some good.
A sword is not just
a tool for destruction.
It can be used as
a tool to help people.
I would prefer
to help people
than to kill them
as you would do.
Have you hit your
head recently, Schneider?
Cause you're talking
a lot of gibberish.
I never felt
better in my life.
Meldars, I know you will
find it hard to understand,
but after I met that samurai
everything changed for me.
My priorities
are different.
I won't let
you hurt her.
(grunts)
♪
I see.
You are an idiot.
(urges horse)
♪
(yells)
(gasps)
♪
And now, Lieutenant,
time for you to be executed
for failing to
carry out an order.
(breathing shakily)
(bats squeaking)
Hmm?
Just a bat.
♪
There they are!
Kaita was right,
we found them!
Look at that garden.
I've never seen
anything like it.
Kenshin,
look at that!
Hmm.
What's going on?
They look like they're
fighting against each other.
They're falling apart.
I guess we'll have to take
care of the intruders first.
Then, I'll take
care of you, Schneider.
♪
Misanagi,
you all right?
Kaita, you're
still alive.
Of course, and you?
Yeah, I'm fine;
I'm glad you're all right.
You were right about
the Black Knights.
They betrayed me.
All except for Schneider,
he saved my life.
They were going to kill me.
Huh?
Who is Schneider?
He's one of the
Black Knights.
I fought him earlier.
♪
The Black Knights
killed Dr. Hans
and I'm going
to kill them.
Yeah, Yutaro, let's just
bust a couple of heads
in honor of Dr. Hans.
-Whoa!
What do you two
think you're doing?
You can't handle those guys!
They're cold-hearted killers.
Lieutenant Meldars, we know
what you're planning to do.
Your scheme is written
down in Dr. Hans' journal.
This very special
medicine is not for you.
You'll have to go
through me to get it.
♪
(chuckling)
(urges horse)
♪