♪
(singing in Japanese)
Ahh!
Stop, you thief!
Give me all
your money
and no one will
get hurt, see?
Don't mess with me!
I'm excellent
with a blade.
Don't try
anything stupid,
or I'll be
forced to
give you a
demonstration!
You don't scare
me with that knife!
Oh, yeah?
Now put that
stupid knife down
or you're the one
who's gonna get hurt!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Yoshi, please!
Don't worry, I'll
take care of him!
I'm not afraid
of this big bully!
I'm the star pupil of
the Kamiya Kasshin dojo.
I'll handle this.
Huh?
Careful, Yoshi boy.
Please don't
call me that.
That's it,
you little brat,
I'm gonna slice
you like salami!
Yeah!!
Oh!
Oh, yeah, well--
Huh?
(cheering)
(gasps)
Thank you so
much, Yoshi.
Ah, you're welcome,
it was really nothing.
That brat must
be with Battousai.
That was wonderful.
You're a regular boy
warrior, aren't you?
Ah, I'm not
a boy warrior.
Call me a swordsman.
We'll see about that.
Yoshi!
Hey, Yoshi!
Huh?
I found your bamboo
sword out there.
Put it away.
You better
take care of it
or you'll lose it.
And sit up when
I'm talking to you.
You're being very rude!
Ha, bamboo swords
are for kids!
Huh?
Hey, did you hear
about the robbery today
at Lenny's Restaurant?
Yeah, we heard.
They said some
crazy guy with
a knife tried
to rob them,
and you stopped him.
Is that right?
Hmm, yeah, this
guy was huge!
He was about
seven foot tall,
he was coming at
me with a dagger,
but I stopped him
with a parry thrust
and knocked him out!
He had a dagger?
We heard that he
had taken a knife
from the kitchen.
I understand
the guy was
not much taller
than Kaoru.
Ha-ha-ha,
whatever height he was,
I took care of him!
From now on,
you can just leave
everything at the Kamiya
Kasshin School dojo to me!
I'll take care of
anyone who tries
to bother us!
Well, that's big
of you, Yoshi.
I'm brave!
It's about time
that I taught
everything there
is to know about
the Kamiya Kasshin style.
Oh, and be sure you
put that bamboo sword
away before it
gets all moldy.
And you're getting too
big for your britches!
You're still
a baby, you hear me?
A baby and
nothing else!
What'd you say, pig face?
Hey, you better
call me "master."
Hey, knock it off!
I don't have
to take that.
She doesn't know what
she's talking about!
I don't want
to work out
with a bamboo sword.
I want to use
a real sword!
No, I don't think so.
You're a little boy,
you're not man enough
to handle a real
sword, anyway.
Wait till
you get older.
I am so big
enough to handle it!
Take it easy!
I'm the first one to admit
you've gotten stronger,
but remember, arrogance
is a very dangerous thing
for a swordsman.
Um, so what makes
you think I'm arrogant?
I just want to
use a real sword
for a change.
I'll decide when you're
ready for a real sword!
Nobody asked you!
Mind your own life, sis!
Can't we all get along?
Are you certain that
the Kisaki Brothers
can take care
of my problem?
They are the finest
assassins around.
They have never
been defeated,
and they are
feared by everyone.
And as long as you
have a lot of money,
they can be bought.
(choking)
What is it?
Ahh!
Death to all
who speak of us
with disrespect.
Death to all
who speak of us
with disrespect.
Ahh!
♪
I'm the one
who asked
for your services!
I want to hire you!
Please don't kill me!
You sent for us?
I'm willing to
pay you anything.
You see,
there's someone
I have to
get rid of.
Here, take this as
your first installment.
Let me know if
you want more.
This is a very
important matter to me.
So, just who
is this person
you want us to
get rid of for you?
Kenshin's his name.
He's also known
as Battousai.
Battousai the Slasher?
Exactly.
Once I was the
premier swordsman,
but Kenshin,
Battousai the Slasher,
busted my fingers,
ending my career!
He ruined my
life that day.
Fortunately, I got
into real estate
and made a fortune.
But I've always
held him responsible
for taking away
the one thing
that I truly loved:
my ability as
a master swordsman.
We don't care
about your grudges,
as long as we
get our money,
that's all
that's important.
We earn our living
as trained assassins,
not by listening
to other people's
trivial sob stories.
We need to know
all there is to
know about your victim
to trap him into our web.
Very well.
I have a plan then.
I think I know
of something
that will force
him to come to us.
Fine.
If you can
trap this man,
so much the
better for us.
We'll wait
outside of town.
If you want
to contact us,
write the word
"oni," on the tablet
at the old shrine.
Judgment day
is here, Battousai.
I'll finally
take care of you,
once and for all!
He-he-he!
Welcome to my
Kasshin dojo,
prepare for
your defeat!
♪
It's with the back
of the sword, don't worry.
I don't care
about that.
Don't forget
your chores.
You haven't
finished cleaning up!
And make sure you
clean the bath for me.
I want to take
a nice hot bath
after practice.
Huh?
What was that, Kaoru?
Are you saying now
you want me to clean
the bathtub for you?
That's right.
If you're going
to stay here,
you're going to
have to pitch in
and help like
everybody else.
I don't clean bathtubs,
'cause I'm a swordsman!
Hey, don't
sweat it, Yoshi.
I'll clean the
bathtub when I get
back from shopping.
When you finish
your training,
you can do the
rest of your chores.
She's always
ordering me around!
Who does she
think she is anyway?
Ugh, this is ridiculous!
Is this how
you repay a hero?
Make him wash
the floors?
A parade in my
honor would be nice,
or maybe a nice medal
with my name on it.
Ow!
Ow, that hurt!
Heroes like you
shouldn't be made
to do all the housework.
How pathetic!
Gohei Hiruma!
Ha-ha-ha!
You remember!
Of course I remember you!
How could I forget an
ugly face like yours?
Why, you little brat!
Even though your
friend Kenshin
crushed my fingers,
I can still take care
of the likes of you!
Would you
like to try me?
I would love to!
♪
I keep telling you,
it's not how strong you are.
An important part of
the Kamiya Kasshin style
is to take advantage
of the strength
of your opponent.
Who cares, Kaoru?
Ugh!
There!
What do you
think of that?
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
You're not bad.
Ready?
You're an amateur!
What do you mean?
If this umbrella
had been a real sword,
I could have
killed you about
20 times by now!
Oh, yeah?
The Kamiya Kasshin
School is called
the "Sword of Life."
Ha, that makes me laugh!
Your technique is
lame and so are you!
Hey, you watch
what you say!
You plan on going
against a real sword
with that
bamboo stick?
Any sword could cut that
ridiculous thing in two,
you pathetic
little insect!
Of course,
it's possible
that you could
stand some sort
of a chance if you
used a real sword.
But since your
Kamiya Kasshin style
prohibits killing
with a sword,
I guess that's out
of the question!
Therefore,
you'll always be
a loser because
you'll never be able
to finish any fight!
Hold on!
That's a big lie!
Kenshin has a
reverse-edged sword.
I'll take you
on with that!
Oh?
You'll use what
sword to fight with?
Kenshin's
reverse-edged sword!
Ah!
Then come to
the edge of town
and I'll meet you
there at the old,
dilapidated shrine
and bring that
reverse-edged
sword with you.
I'll be waiting,
little boy!
I'll be there!
I didn't think it
would be so easy!
That little brat
doesn't know who
he's playing with.
Ha-ha-ha,
he-he-he!
All these groceries
are very heavy.
I have to put
this away,
clean the rice
for dinner tonight,
and get the bath
ready before Kaoru
gets back
from practice.
Kenshin?
Huh?
Yeah, what is it,
what's going on?
It's just...well...
Come on, now, you
can tell me anything.
Uh, never mind!
♪
It's so heavy.
So, this is what a
real sword feels like.
Huh?
Now what's he up to?
Gohei, I'm here,
show yourself!
Huh?
Who are you?
Ahh!
What's going on?
Ow!
Well, that went
very smoothly.
That little fool
brought me Kenshin's sword.
Now Battousai will be
defenseless against us!
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
I'm so tired.
I hope my bath is ready
when I get to the dojo.
What?
Hey, who threw that?
♪
"If you want
Yoshi back alive,
meet me at the
Kikiyu dry riverbed
at sundown."
It's Gohei Hiruma!
It's all my fault, really.
I saw Yoshi take the
reverse-edged sword out
and I let him go.
Oh, that's terrible.
He left the dojo
with your sword?
I thought that if
he knew how dangerous
a sword was,
he might not be
so gung-ho about
wanting to use
a real one.
I had no idea
that Gohei was
behind all of this.
That little fool!
He let himself
be duped by Gohei.
Ah, Kenshin!
What can you do?
You don't have
your sword.
Gohei has set
a trap for you.
You never know
what horrible,
evil thing he
has up his sleeve.
You're right.
Without my sword,
I can't win,
but I have to go
and rescue Yoshi.
♪
(laughing)
Kenshin is doomed without
his reverse-edged sword.
Those hitmen
that I hired
will take
care of him!
And I have you
to thank for that,
little boy.
It'll be sunset soon,
and the Kikiyu dry riverbed
will be Kenshin's grave!
Once Kenshin's dead,
I'll be back to deal
with you!
(cackles)
This is all my fault!
I let him trick me,
and now Kenshin's
walking into a trap.
♪
If only I hadn't taken
the reverse-edged sword,
Kenshin wouldn't
be a sitting duck!
Why was I such
a stupid fool?
♪
(crying)
Hey, come on, Kenshin,
I was just playing around,
I was just teasing you!
'Cause you have
a real sword.
To them, you're
just a little kid,
but I know that inside,
you're very grown-up
and mature.
You should be
proud of yourself,
and proud of the
way you behaved.
Darn it, I'm not
strong enough.
I want to be able
to do it by myself,
without your help.
From now on, you'll
learn swordsmanship
at this dojo.
You will be great.
Kenshin!
Stay strong, Yoshi.
♪
Oh no, it's almost sunset!
Kenshin!
♪
He should be
here by now!
Hmm?
So, he came unarmed.
Where's Yoshi?
If you want
to really know,
you'll have to
kill us first,
that's the only way
you're gonna find out.
Who are you two, anyway?
Some hired thugs from Gohei?
Tekkan Kisaki,
at your service.
Gengo Kisaki's my name.
I sure don't like
the looks of this.
Kaoru, I want you
to stay back here
and watch.
I don't want
anything awful
to happen to you.
I'm the one they
want to murder.
So, is that why
they tricked Yoshi
into bringing
your sword to them?
That's right.
(chuckles)
Very good, you
managed to figure
all of that out.
Now I guess you
can die in peace.
I said, what are
you doing with
that sword?
I...
Don't you know
that having a sword
is against the law?
Listen, I, uh,
you have to get
out of my way,
this is an emergency!
Give me that
sword this instant!
Do you want
to go to jail?
Gimme it!
Stop right now,
hold it there!
You come
back here!
Ahh!
Keep an eye on him!
We'll get you!
Kenshin, hang on!
♪
He's pretty good.
He was missing
me on purpose.
I wonder what
game he's playing.
♪
You will now taste
the wrath of the
Tsuchigumo spider style.
♪
What the?
Ugh!
What sort of
power is this?
Kenshin!
♪
Kaoru, get
out of here!
Stay out of this!
Huh?
Kenshin!
Hmm, I really don't
think I need any help
defeating an unarmed man.
How are you going
to defend yourself
with just your left hand?
♪
Good, good,
now finish him!
(cackles)
Huh?
Kenshin!
That darn
annoying brat,
he got out somehow!
You little twit,
I'm not going to let
you get in the
way of my plans!
Last time I let you
think you could beat me
so that I could
lure you into my trap.
You won't be
so lucky now!
Come and get me!
You don't know
who you're fighting!
A real sword isn't
like bamboo, is it?
You can't control it.
Prepare to die!
Yoshi!
Use the strength
of your opponent
against him.
Don't try to use
your strength against
someone who is stronger.
Hi-ya!!
Ahh!
Kenshin!
Yoshi!
Ahh!
Yeah!
♪
Ahh!
Kenshin!
♪
Ugh!
Your evil trick of
using invisible wire
to bind your
opponent is nothing
once you
know the trick.
Guess you need
tricks to make up
for your ineptitude.
♪
Hiten Mitsurugi style!
Hi-ya!
(screaming)
How'd you do that?
Huh?
Kenshin...
I'm really sorry that
I took your sword from you,
and that I put your
life in extreme danger.
I...I don't
know what to say.
It's okay.
You guys were right
about everything.
I was nothing
but a conceited,
arrogant idiot.
Yoshi...
Huh?
You're on the road
to being a man.
For it takes a man
to admit he's made
a mistake like that.
Oh.
♪
Huh?
Well, Mr. Big Man,
I think it's time
we headed back
to the dojo.
Unless you want to brag
about something else?
As a matter of fact,
I just developed
a new technique for the
Kamiya Kasshin School.
It's by the new master,
Yoshi, and it's called,
"The nutcracker kick."
Oh!
You'll never change.
(laughter)
♪