♪
(water flowing)
My brother went
to the Holy Hill.
(coughing)
The village people
went with him.
If the army attacks them,
they'll all be killed.
That sounds like tuberculosis.
I won't buy that!
You should have Dr. Elsten
take a look at her.
Yeah, the Dutch man
used to be a doctor!
He'll know what's
wrong with her!
Hey, that's right.
♪
The captain wants
everyone armed and ready!
All right, let's move it!
♪
Twelfth Infantry
is in position, sir!
♪
Move 'em out--it's
going to be hot by noon.
♪
They're marching this way!
We've been betrayed.
Keiyo only pretended
to be our friend.
It's unbelievable.
I knew he was up to something,
but I didn't think he was
going to move this quickly.
♪
I've allowed myself to be so
distracted by Sayo's illness
that I've let my guard down.
I should have seen it coming.
Captain, sir!
The troops stand
ready for attack
awaiting your orders, sir!
Very good.
Get the field artillery
in place right away.
Sir!
This man, Shogo, thinks
he's the second coming
of Shiro Amakusa.
He's a danger to our country.
We can't allow him to continue
organizing his Christians.
He must be stopped.
♪
What should we do, Shogo?
Dear people of Shimabara,
Keiyo has persuaded
the army to attack us.
We stand no chance
against its might.
♪
Everybody listen.
We've been praying on this
holy land for a long time.
For hundreds of years,
Christians before us
have also prayed here
and suffered because
of their faith,
but their belief in God was
stronger than any mere pain.
We need that same strength now.
Although our prayer to
build God's Kingdom on Earth
has gone unanswered,
do not falter in your faith.
God has another plan for us.
We're leaving this Earth today.
We must prepare to enter
the heavenly kingdom.
We will die as martyrs,
but our faith will never die.
♪
I'm ready to go.
It's always sunny in Heaven
because it's up
above the clouds!
Does it have beautiful
butterflies and flowers?
It's a place where there's
no pain or suffering!
A place where no one interferes
with your belief in God!
And only good-hearted
people can get there!
(murmuring)
♪
Come on, everyone!
Let's go to Heaven!
(indistinct speaking)
♪
Grab your weapon!
Get ready to fight!
Open the passage to Heaven
by defeating as many of
God's enemies as you can!
Come with me to a land where
there is life everlasting!
(panting)
♪
I know it's a
long shot, Kenshin,
but I'm going to the
Army Command Center
to try to talk them
out of attacking.
Okay, good luck.
♪
Gotta hurry!
Better be quick.
♪
There's not a moment to lose.
I need to find the fastest way!
♪
Ah, what am I gonna do now?
(grunting)
♪
There's got to be some place
where I can cross this river!
♪
Sayo, you're awake!
Where are we going, Sanosuke?
I'm taking you to
a doctor right now!
It's time you got
some proper care!
Even though
Mr. Elsten is a consul,
he once practiced medicine,
so he'll be able to
prescribe a cure for you.
And as a consul, he has
enough political power
to stop the army if we
can convince him to do so!
I should be going
to the Holy Hill
to help Shogo!
You're not going anywhere.
Kenshin's on his way
over there right now.
Don't worry.
No matter what, we
won't let the villagers
or your brother die!
Kenshin will be able to take
care of the entire situation!
♪
All right, it's perfect!
Don't look, just hang on!
I'm ready.
(yelling)
♪
(grunting)
The ride might be rough, but
we'll save some time this way.
Hang in there--be strong!
♪
You're probably
too late, Doctor.
I think they've already
started the attack.
I can hardly believe it.
A riot by followers of God,
suppression by authority.
This is the same nightmare
that happened 250 years ago,
and now we're
faced with it again.
I can't help but wonder
if I could've done
something to prevent this.
I should've taken
Mr. Himura more seriously
when he predicted it.
(galloping)
♪
Listen here, men,
by my count, our opponent
number is less than a hundred!
We should be able to
wipe them out in an hour!
Just make sure no
one remains alive!
Yes, sir!
But what do we do about
the women and children?
Kill 'em, too!
They've been brainwashed by
a horrible religious belief!
Getting rid of them is
the way to stamp it out!
But Captain, I
heard the enemy force
is protected by a special sword!
It's supposed to have
some God-like power!
No way!
That's a big lie
spread by their leader!
We must crush him!
It is our duty to
eliminate this enemy
before they conquer
us by their lies
and their deceit!
Let's go, men!
♪
Huh?
(gasping)
♪
(grunting)
He's too good!
Stay away!
He's gone!
He really is the second
coming of Shiro Amakusa!
Shoot him!
Shoot him now!
(laughing)
(yelling)
Stop that!
♪
Look, there they are!
Well, I'm not going to Heaven
without a good fight first!
-Come on!
-Yeah!
(yelling)
-Get ready!
-Take 'em down!
(yelling)
We're too late!
What do we do now?
Everybody stop!
(yelling)
(rumbling)
(indistinct chatter)
(panting)
Both sides back off!
This killing is meaningless!
I won't let you continue!
Stop interfering
in our affairs!
This does not concern you!
Leave us alone--just go away!
Your showing up
is slowing us down!
We're trying to get on
with our sacred duty!
So beat it!
Kenshin!
Their sacred duty is
clearly out of this world.
All of them think
they're going to Heaven!
Shogo told everybody
if they die as martyrs,
they'll end up in God's Kingdom.
♪
Shogo Amakusa, this
is a big mistake!
I won't let you make it!
♪
Sanosuke.
We're almost at the main road.
From there it's close.
Tell me, why are you and
your friends helping us?
I don't think there's anything
you can gain by doing it,
so I was just wondering
why it was so important
that you should risk
everything for us.
I don't know myself.
I've never been able to
make choices about who I help
based on whether I gain or lose.
I guess I'm just
a sucker that way.
But I just can't
let those villagers
and their children
be slaughtered!
Besides, I made a promise.
What is the promise?
I promised Shogo
that I'd protect you.
Sanosuke.
Don't cry now.
Tears don't become you.
Please forgive me.
I'm sorry I didn't
meet you sooner
before I got so
sick, that's all.
I would've liked that
more than you'll ever know.
♪
(explosions)
(yelling)
I'm scared!
Don't be scared!
I'm not scared!
We're all going to Heaven!
♪
This is exactly like
the Battle of Toba-Fushimi.
Yes,
except that now,
with our new weapons,
Shogo's sword won't
be so powerful.
Time has a way of
changing things.
Stop it!
Let go of me!
Get your hands
off me, you idiot!
And who's that, Captain?
(growling)
♪
(waves crashing)
It shouldn't be much longer.
We're almost there.
♪
Well, all right.
Wait here for just a minute.
Wait!
Hold on!
Stop!
Hmm?
Thanks for stopping!
Oh my gosh,
Dr. Elsten, it's you!
Yes, and you're
Mr. Sagara, right?
A close friend of Mr. Himura's?
I have a very sick woman who
desperately needs your help.
Where is she?
Follow me.
Where is Mr. Himura?
He's gone to Holy Hill
where there's a very
serious situation.
It seems that the army
is planning an attack
on Shogo Amakusa and
his Christian followers.
Yes, that's what I heard,
which is why I'm on
my way there, too.
Kenshin hopes to talk
Shogo into surrendering
providing the army
can stop its attack.
Someone has to convince the army
to call off their
assault, Dr. Elsten,
and I feel that can only be you.
I plan to do that.
The past must not repeat itself.
I'm sorry to hear you
feel that way, Dr. Elsten.
Your interference right now
will cause my plan with Keiyo
to go up in smoke.
You leave me no choice.
(gasping)
(gun firing)
She saved me.
Santo, what are you doing?
You!
(yelling)
I'll get you!
(grunting)
Hang on, young lady.
Give me a pulse!
I'm at a total loss to
explain why Santo did this.
The wound's pretty deep.
She's very weak.
We need to get her to
a hospital right away.
But you're a doctor!
Why can't you do something now?
I don't have instruments or a
proper way to clean the wound.
I haven't done this in years!
But I thought--
Forget about me.
Help Shogo before it's too late.
Hurry, please!
Help my brother right now.
Go with God.
Don't let all the
people on Holy Hill die.
Please!
♪
You're a brave young lady.
The most unselfish
I've ever seen.
I'm very honored
to have met you.
♪
I owe my life to you, and so
will many others, dear one.
Please know God will hold you.
♪
It's finally finding
its way home to you.
I know how you treasure it.
You said you'd find it.
You kept your word!
I could never believe you, Sano.
I'm sorry, but
I've trusted no one.
I've been such a fool!
I closed my heart to strangers
thinking they were the enemy.
I thought everyone
wanted to torment me
because of my belief in God,
but your kindness
touched me so much
that it's allowed
me to see the truth.
I was so wrong,
for now I know that there
are a lot of nice people
with warm hearts
here on this Earth.
I was caught up
in my own hatred.
I refused to open
my mind to the joy
of loving people
without judgment.
I wish I could have
learned that sooner,
and I wish I had more time
to teach the children
what I have learned.
They need to know
that joy is here,
within God's kingdom,
when happiness
is in their hearts.
Don't make it sound
like your life is over.
You can still teach
as much as you want.
You have a reason to live!
Don't give up now, you can
still accomplish your goals!
Thank you, Sanosuke.
Your back was warm.
I appreciate all you've done.
How I wish I could live.
♪
Rest now.
Save your strength.
Just one more thing.
I need a favor.
Would you give
this to my brother?
Please, it's my last request.
♪
A will?
Why would you have made one?
Have you been planning
your own suicide?
Are you that depressed?
I've just always known
that my life would be short.
I wish it weren't true.
I'm sorry, but
I'm going away now.
What are you saying?
You're not going anywhere,
you still have to live!
And you haven't even told
me your real name yet!
Sayo.
My mother gave me that name.
I'm Sayo.
Sanosuke, I'm so
happy I've known you.
Goodbye.
(exhaling)
No, Sayo!
♪
Sayo!
Sayo.
I wonder if--
(yelling)
(grunting)
♪
(whimpering)
(yelling)
♪
Brother.
Huh?
♪
No.
Sayo.
♪
(explosion)
(crying)
♪
Genta, where are you going?
I'm going to Heaven,
Sakura, before anyone else.
Wait, Genta!
Don't go, come back!
I'm going to Heaven!
(explosion)
♪
Genta!
Oh, Mr. Amakusa.
Is this Heaven?
I don't feel so good.
Shogo Amakusa!
How can you allow all these
innocent children to be killed?
I will fight you myself
if you do no call a
stop to this slaughter.
And even though I
do not have my sight,
I will defeat you with
Amakakeru Ryu No Hirameki!
Kenshin Himura.
♪