♪
(Japanese theme music)
Hey you guys, over here!
Weasel woman sure
has a lot of energy
up here in the
mountains, Kenshin.
Misao, it's nice to have
you traveling with us,
but I'm concerned that
Okina will worry about you,
you sure
it's all right?
Don't you worry
about that, Kenshin,
I wrote him a letter telling
him about all my plans.
But tell me,
what happened
to you guys anyway?
You always have
problems when you travel.
We were forced to get
off the ship at Shimizu,
but there was a malfunction.
Since that time,
we've been walking.
Talk about rotten luck,
when are we gonna
eat something?
Would you guys like
to go to Hakone?
It's only a few miles
if we go this way.
I would really like that.
Hakone has great hot springs.
We might as well go as
long as we're right here.
I agree, a good bath
to soothe our tired bodies
and some warm food sound
really nice now, Sano.
Then it's settled.
We'll all spend
the night in Hakone.
Yeah!
Hakone's a great place.
I'm gonna soak
until I'm a giant prune!
-Oh, that was great food.
-I'm stuffed.
Ah, that was great.
Yeah, I'm so full.
Hey, this is really
living, isn't it gang?
Yeah, this room is great
and the food is fantastic.
We should treat
ourselves once in a while.
Welcome honored guests.
Hope you're enjoying
your stay with us.
These are our very
finest accommodations.
I'd like to get at least
some of the money you owe me.
No problem.
Kaoru, you got some silver
to take care of
the bills, don't you?
Yeah, I gave it to
Kenshin for safe keeping.
You have the silver?
Of course, I put it
in a safe place.
It was right here in my--
Huh?
It was in here.
Hey, what's this?
This isn't funny, Kenshin.
Find the money already,
the manager's waiting.
It must have slipped out
this big hole
I have in my sleeve.
So, what should I do now?
I haven't got it.
Kenshin, this is
a serious matter!
(punching)
Nope.
So, you're sayin' that
you don't have any money
to pay for for the lodgings
and all the food you just ate.
Please, sir, I'm very sorry.
Please, sir, we're sorry.
Mr. Sorjeson,
we have a problem.
Osado, can't you see
I'm dealing with guests?
A large group
just showed up
and we don't
have enough staff here
to take care of all
these guests, sir.
I hate to have
to turn them away,
but we don't have the
staff to accommodate them.
Ooh.
Hey, I've got it.
Why don't you let
me work off our bill
by helping you out.
What?
That's a great idea,
we can all help.
There isn't
anything we can't do.
Yeah, we're not afraid
of a little...work.
I don't know.
Wait a second,
have you heard of the famous
Kyoto restaurant, Sherry Babies?
That's my family's restaurant.
We can help you out,
you don't have to worry.
We're ready.
-Right gang?
-We got it!
♪
No, this one
isn't good either.
My drawings are terrible,
something's missing.
Excuse us.
We came here
to bring you your dinner.
I'm not very hungry, thanks.
She's perfect.
Kaoru, let's bring him
back something later.
All right, sorry about that.
Wait, don't go, wait!
Come back, don't leave.
She'll inspire me
to greatness.
Boy, it's really amazing
the way everything worked out,
isn't it, Kenshin?
I'm just happy
that he agreed
to let us pay
off our debt.
Maybe if we
keep working here,
then they'll
even pay us.
I'm sorry you
guys have to work
because of my
carelessness.
Don't sweat it,
it's kind of fun.
Yeah, I'm having a good time.
I have finally found her,
the spark to my flame.
She shines brighter
than the brightest star.
She is the sun to my moon.
She is the ultimate beauty.
Now that I have found her,
I cannot let her go.
Hah!
♪
(water gurgling)
Oh, this hot spring
feels just like heaven
after a long
hard day of work.
Doesn't this
feel good, Kaoru?
I could stay here all night.
Sorry you became involved
in this cause of Kenshin's.
Oh, that's all right,
it's really nothing.
So tell me, Kaoru,
just between us,
are you and Kenshin
really close?
You know like
girlfriend and boyfriend?
(gasp)
Ah, Misao, it's not
what you're thinking.
Kenshin hardly notices
that I even exist sometimes.
Sometimes I'd like to punch
him in the head, you know.
Somehow, that
doesn't surprise me.
Kenshin doesn't
really strike me
as all that much
of a ladies man.
He just doesn't seem to
have any interest in women.
Maybe it's something else.
Maybe he has
a woman in his past.
A beautiful woman that he
just can't seem to forget.
Oh, I'll bet that's it.
A dark, mysterious woman
that he met years ago
that he just can't get out
of his head or his heart
or anything and he just--
-Misao, do you mind?
-Huh?
My relationship with Kenshin
is nobody's business.
We're doing fine.
Could we please talk
about something else?
Sure we can, Kaoru.
I really didn't mean
to get so personal.
I apologize.
You see the only one
I truly love is Aoshi.
Aw, that is nice.
Who's up there?
Huh?
♪
I'll take care of this!
Yee-ahh!
Nailed him!
Oh, ah.
It's a peeping tom.
He's, he's a pervert!
-It's Kaoru!
-Let's go!
♪
Kaoru, are you all right?
Why you, get out
of here you lunkheads!
What's the matter with you,
you bunch of perverts!
Get out!
Can't you see we're
trying to bathe here!
What do you think
you're doing!
This is a ladies
only bathing area!
Can't you see we're just
poor defenseless women!
But I'm not a pervert.
Then what were you
doing in that tree
watching us bathe?
I promise you,
I wasn't doing anything bad.
You may not
think it was bad,
but we don't
like peeping toms.
I'm only a student.
I'm trying to be
a great artist in Tokyo.
My name is Ryuzaburo,
I mean you no harm.
How can you be
studying art here?
For the past few years,
I've struggled to
find the answers.
My fundamental question being
what exactly is this art?
I struggled to find an answer
until I finally decided to
go on a journey to find out.
♪
But meaningless days went by.
Week after week,
I still couldn't find
the answer to my question.
I had hit a dead end.
I felt like I was losing
my mind and going mad.
You see, without
finding the answer,
I lost my confidence.
I never thought I would
be able to draw again.
I was ruined,
I lost the spark
of creativity.
But when I saw
the ultimate beauty,
my inspiration came back.
What's he saying?
"The ultimate beauty"?
Did you see her
from that tree?
He is nuts.
So, are you trying to tell
us that the ultimate beauty
is one of these two girls?
She was taking a bath,
I didn't want to disturb her.
But I did want to draw
her beautiful body.
So you can
see for yourself
what kind of an
inspiration she is to me.
You were drawing
smutty pictures?
♪
Well, I'm very
flattered, of course,
but there's only one person
in this whole wide world
that I want to appreciate
my ultimate beauty,
and that one person
is Mr. Aoshi.
Hey, Sano, this is, uh,
wow, that's Kaoru.
That's right, it's Kaoru.
♪
Can't be, what?
Please, Kaoru,
let me draw you.
I can't go on without
your divine inspiration.
Be my model, I beg you,
for the sake of art.
Well, I don't know.
I've never been
a model before.
I don't know if I can.
I don't know if
I want pictures of me
hanging in galleries.
I can't, can I?
(laughing)
She's liking this.
It looks that way.
I think she'll do it.
I just cannot believe it.
He picked Kaoru over me.
Unfair!
(groaning)
Everybody is
waiting for you,
you'll have
to hurry up.
Sorry.
While we're over here
working our
fingers to the bone,
Kaoru's playing
model, goofing off!
I wouldn't exactly
describe what she's doing
as goofing off.
Yeah, Kenshin is right,
it's got to be
incredibly hard
just sitting
there all day long.
♪
Nobody ever told me
I was the most beautiful
woman in the world before.
I must admit,
it was a bit of a shock,
but it feels good to have
a man appreciate me for once.
Kenshin's never said
anything nice like that.
But what does he know,
he has lousy taste.
He doesn't know what he's
talking about, the jerk!
Kaoru, your face has changed.
Hmm?
Oh, I'm sorry.
♪
I was thinking of something.
I need you
to take that food
to the group in
the kiku room right away.
As you wish, Madam Osado.
Wow, that's incredible!
It's a perfect
likeness, Kaoru.
Yeah, he's doing
a great job!
This is just a sketch.
He'll be starting
the real drawing soon.
This guy's probably
a good artist
if he can even make
Kaoru look this good.
Shut up, Yoshi!
Yoshi is right, you are
a pretty good artist.
You've got me
convinced, Skinny.
This drawing,
it's not Kaoru.
This is just an outer shell.
It has no depth,
it's not the real Kaoru.
♪
Now stop that!
You destroyed it.
Your drawing was beautiful.
Ahh!
Why in the world
did you do that?
Because it wasn't her.
Oh, it may look like
Kaoru on the outside,
on the surface,
but my drawing does
not show her heart.
Her heart?
The reason that I
cannot show her heart
is...is...
because I...because I...
because I have fallen deeply
and madly in love with her.
(gasps)
♪
(water bubbling)
(bird song)
You have fallen
in love with her?
Well, now what will you do?
I don't know.
All I know is
that I love her.
When I was drawing her,
all I could think about
was being with her,
getting to know her better.
I think about her
day and night.
And the ironic
part of this is,
my passion has
clouded my vision
and now I can't
see her heart!
Wow, so you need
to see Kaoru's heart.
If you see Kaoru heart,
you might be sorry
you decided to look
inside of her to begin with.
Ow!
Whoa!
Please Kaoru, I beg of you,
I beg of you,
go out with me.
Then maybe some day I will
be able to see your heart.
I mean, really see it.
And that is the only way that
my art will ever be created.
But I'm afraid I just
can't go out with you.
That's right,
your heart already
belongs to Kenshin Himura.
I think that Misao
is exaggerating
just a little bit.
Kaoru, are you in there?
Oh, yes, Kenshin.
♪
Say, Kaoru,
do you happen to know
where the kiku
room is located?
Kaoru, do you know?
Go find it yourself!
Whoa!
(crashing)
Insensitive cad!
You can see for yourself.
Those two aren't getting
along all that great,
but she has very strong
feelings for Kenshin.
I'd like to give you
some friendly advice, pal.
Give it up,
you can never win.
Never, I can't.
I finally found
the love of loves
and I can never have her.
(crying)
I can't go on!
-Hey that's enough.
-If I can't have Kaoru,
then I don't want to live!
(crying)
Cut it out,
you don't have to lose
your life over this thing,
just relax, Da Vinci!
Ahh!
(crashing)
Shame on you, Ryuzaburo.
A grown man should
not be so willing
to throw his own life away.
Sano, I am serious!
Do you hear me?
If I can't have Kaoru,
then my wish is to die now!
Please, Sano, help me!
Well, what are you
waiting for, Sano,
you'd better help
the poor guy out.
He's counting on
your help, big fella.
Would you do me
a big favor, Misao?
Stay out of this,
I don't want to get involved!
Relax, I've got a great idea
on how to get rid of him.
Just listen.
Uh-huh.
I'll help you, Da Vinci.
You really seem to be very
passionate and serious
about this whole matter.
You'll help me, Sano?
Under one condition.
I knew there was a catch.
If you manage to defeat
Kenshin just once
before the end of sunset,
I will personally see to it
that you and your love Kaoru
are married and live
happily ever after.
So, how does that sound?
But I've never
fought with a sword.
I've never studied
martial arts before.
Then I'm afraid that
the whole deal is off.
Hold on, not so fast.
All right, I'll do it.
All right, I want you
to keep your promise to me.
You do whatever you want,
give it all that you've got,
and if it doesn't work out,
give up and walk
away like a man.
Well, do we have
a deal or not?
We have a deal Sanosuke.
I will keep my promise.
You can depend on me.
I am going to win this match.
I will win Kaoru's heart
and I will create great art!
♪
I forgot to mention
one little thing.
This guy that you're
gonna be fighting, Kenshin,
maybe you heard of him.
He was once called
Battousai the Slasher
and he's considered the finest
swordsman in all of Japan.
So, if you ever
want to paint again,
you might want to be careful.
I think our plan to scare
him off is succeeding.
He dropped the sword.
(laughing)
Did you see his face
when you told him
about Battousai
the Slasher, huh?
Let's hope that
discourages him enough
to call off this folly.
Yeah, but it wasn't right
that you went and
gave him my sword, Sano.
Relax, Yoshi,
he isn't gonna use it.
I bet he'll bring
it right back here.
Sano is right.
Hey!
♪
He's got your sword, he's crazy.
He's going to
go after Kenshin!
Uh, I must have cut
enough wood today
to build two log houses.
When I'm done here,
I'll have to start dinner.
♪
So, this guy used to be
the great
Battousai the Slasher.
Well, there's no way I could
beat him in a fair fight.
My only hope
is to attack him
when he least expects it.
♪
Ahh!
Huh?
♪
That's strange,
I thought I heard
something back there.
Oh well, must have
been my imagination.
Did you see that?
This guy's really serious.
It looks like our
starving artist friend
isn't giving up so easy.
Get my sword back.
Let me see here,
the okaeri room
has to be around
here somewhere.
Kenshin, over
this way, over here.
Sorry Osado.
Ugh.
Kenshin, please hurry.
All right, Osado.
♪
(brooms sweeping)
Huh, Ryuzaburo,
what's going on?
Uh, I thought I'd go
for a nice walk outside.
(laughing)
Thought I'd get
a little exercise.
Have you seen Kenshin
around here anywhere?
Argh!
(crashing)
(groaning)
I can't help but feel
that something
really weird is going on.
Maybe I'm just very tired,
that's probably it,
we've been working
non-stop since we got here,
that's why I'm
feeling so paranoid.
(groaning)
He's here.
(insects chirring)
Huh?
Hey, Battousai,
you can't escape me now!
(shouting)
That guy's really crazy.
What?
Why on earth would you
tell him such a thing?
Sorry, I thought
he'd back down.
We thought it would be
best to let him down easy.
Don't worry,
that little artist
couldn't defeat Kenshin
in a million years.
The worst part for me is
that they gave him my sword.
I'm not worried
about your sword,
I'm worried about Ryuzaburo.
We have to stop
this nonsense
or Ryuzaburo will
get badly injured.
I'm certain he's
given up by now,
but just in case,
we should find
him right away.
It's probably easier to find
Himura than the artist.
I bet you Kenshin probably
went to the mountains
to pick up some
vegetables for supper.
Ah!
♪
Wait for us Kaoru!
We want to go too!
You've got to help me
get my sword back!
♪
Kenshin!
Hmm?
Hey, Kenshin, are you here?
Where are you?
I'm over here.
Hi, Kaoru, I was just picking
some wild greens for dinner.
Oh, that's nice.
I guess we got
here in time,
nothing happened.
Hey, those
vegetables look great.
What's going on?
What are all of
you doing here?
(shouting)
He's lost it!
He's still after Kenshin.
That's my sword!
He's going to get hurt.
Hey, now.
Aahh!
(splat)
Hey, Sano,
what's going on here?
I'll tell you
the truth, Kenshin.
It's like this...
-Huh?
-Hey, help me!
(buzzing)
Let's go!
Kenshin!
Kaoru, stay back,
those are killer wasps.
Oh, no!
♪
Hey, Sano, grab that guy!
Okay.
♪
Ahhh!
(crashing)
(water bubbling)
I am so happy that you
weren't hurt badly, Kenshin.
But do me a favor,
don't do that again.
I'll try to avoid
all wasps from now on.
Oh.
♪
They really do care
about each other, see?
I tried to tell you
how close they are.
You were right.
I just didn't see it.
Huh?
Kaoru's true heart is that
she is in love with Kenshin.
That's what gives her
beauty from within.
Her heart is filled with
love for Kenshin Himura.
Finally, I can
draw the real Kaoru.
Now that I've
seen her true heart,
I can create again!
♪
Thanks to you, Kaoru,
I have art back
in my life again.
You are truly beautiful,
and you've been
an inspiration to me.
I shall never forget you.
You are a very talented
artist, Ryuzaburo,
and we expect to hear
a lot of things about you.
Good luck to you.
Thanks.
Goodbye, everyone,
I am going
to miss you all.
Take this, it is
my best work yet.
Ooh.
It's a drawing of you.
I really hope
that you like it.
So long.
Take care
of yourself, Da Vinci.
So long.
Try to find someone
more beautiful than Kaoru!
Yoshi, you talk too much.
I hope he does well
in the art world.
We should be heading back to
Tokyo pretty soon ourselves.
Come on, we've
got work to do.
-Take care of yourself.
-Bye!
♪
Tokaido is just
ahead on this road,
so we can go
straight to Tokyo.
I guess we'll say our
goodbyes when we get there.
Misao, you sound like you're
feeling a little bit homesick.
I bet you're probably
missing Okina.
Kaoru, you never let
us see the painting.
How about letting
us have a look?
Well, you'll just
have to wait, Sano.
I'm looking
forward to opening it
when I get back to Tokyo.
Oh, don't hold back,
show it to us now.
I second that motion, Kaoru.
Oh, all right, if you
want to see it that badly.
But just a tiny look.
♪
Huh!
Well, he titled it
"The Love Of The Goddess."
What do you think?
So, does it make
me look beautiful?
It's very nice.
You guys think it's
very nice don't you,
Sano, Yoshi?
♪
(laughing)
What in the world
are you talking about?
Why are you all leaving
in such a hurry?
Huh?
♪
Just look at
this monstrosity!
This doesn't look
anything like me!
Oh!
♪
Hey, Kaoru,
looks just like you!
Ha ha!
That's not very nice.
Did he paint that,
or did a bunch of the paint
spill accidentally
onto the canvas?
He certainly captured
Kaoru's essence, all right!
Hey, guys what
are you laughing at?
This is really good.
You just have to look
at it a couple of times.
This is real art.
Hey, guys, wait up,
guys, come on!
♪
(Japanese theme music)