♪
(singing in foreign language)
(laughing)
♪
They can't last much longer.
A few more minutes
and it'll all be over.
Isn't that right, Fuji?
They'll all be dead.
(laughing)
♪
Unbelievable; that's not
a man, that's a monster!
♪
There is nothing we can do.
(laughing)
I'm afraid that
you're quite right.
There's not a thing you
can do except face the fact
that you're all going
to die in a few seconds.
It's just not fair, we fought
so hard and defeated all
their best fighters,
and now, at the end,
after giving it
everything we had,
we have to face that thing,
but we'll still beat you,
monster or no monster.
What now, Kori?
Good question.
One thing's for sure, though,
we're not going to
give up without a fight.
I'll do everything I can
to keep the promise that
I made to Kenshin.
I told him we'd all
go back to Tokyo
together when this was over.
But now, I suppose we might
never see Kenshin again.
♪
You're wrong!
Huh?
It's...not...
over yet.
(groaning)
Kenshin's gonna come
back soon, got it?
He'll come back as soon
as he defeats Shishio.
We've gotta keep fighting
until he gets here.
-Yoshi.
Do as you like,
but I'm gonna fight.
I don't care if it's a monster
or the end of the world.
I'm gonna keep my promise
to Kenshin no matter what.
Goodness me, I see there's one
of you that still doesn't fully
understand the situation, so
out of the kindness of my heart,
I'm going to explain it
to you as simply as I can,
which is to say you're doomed.
In other words, you won't
leave this battlefield alive!
Based on our current situation,
there are three reasons
for this, all quite logical.
The first reason is
that you will never,
ever see Kenshin again.
He's not coming to rescue you
here in Aoiya,
you stupid fools.
Remember, those
who ignore history
are condemned to repeat it,
and Shishio has
never been defeated.
Himura will die and
the dead don't come here.
They go to the next world.
(grunting)
Now, logically speaking,
based on our current situation,
let us examine
the second reason.
You all deserve a tremendous
amount of credit for having
defeated the members
of the Juppongatana
you have faced up to this point
with a group of mere women,
teenagers, and children.
However, as a result
of this fighting,
you're on your last legs,
and you have no more strength
left to fight anyone,
much less a giant.
And now our conversation
leads us to the third reason
why none of you have a chance
of leaving here alive.
In case you're wondering,
his name is Fuji,
and though I could tell
you more about him, I believe
a simple demonstration
will suffice, right?
♪
(grunting)
By analyzing
the current situation
based on these three reasons,
it can only lead
to one conclusion,
which unfortunately for you
is that you're going to die
in the next few seconds.
Ain't it a pity?
(laughing)
We're not giving up!
Yoshi.
It's not over 'til it's over.
You'll see, Kenshin'll
get here soon.
I bet he's on his way right now.
Your belief in
the invulnerability
of your friend is touching.
Unfortunately, believing in
something doesn't make it real.
I've lived many more decades
than you have, young man,
and in all that time,
I've learned there's only
one thing that's certain.
The only one you can
believe in is yourself.
Now it's your turn to die!
♪
Yoshi, you better
get outta there!
♪
Kenshin.
Yoshi!
(laughing maniacally)
Kenshin!
♪
(wind whooshing)
(groaning)
(crying)
I can't believe it, look!
♪
(gasping)
(grunting)
♪
All right, way to go, kid.
That took guts.
You could have given up,
but you knew in your heart
that Kenshin wouldn't
let you down.
That's why I'm here today.
It's a master.
Yeah, Hiko Seijuro.
The master of the
Hiten Mitsurugi School.
Hiko Seijuro.
He taught Kenshin how to fight.
Just what's he doing here?
♪
When Kenshin said he had
a plan to protect Aoiya,
it was him.
Kenshin couldn't make
it, so he sent Hiko.
♪
(grunting)
Incredible, he absorbed the
full power of the giant's blow
and he's still standing.
♪
What is it, kid?
You shouldn't stare like that.
It isn't very polite.
Ugh, listen!
If you knew we needed help,
then why didn't
you get here sooner?
Another few seconds
and we would've died,
understand?
Save your complaints
for when Kenshin gets here.
If he'd given me detailed
instructions on how to get here,
I'd been here long ago.
I spent a week looking for you,
so show a little
gratitude, will ya?
Now, stay out of the way
and you won't get hurt.
Thanks, Hiko.
Thanks for saving Yoshi's life.
You're welcome.
Now, you'll have to excuse me,
I've got work to do.
To know one's opponent,
one must look into his eyes,
and in yours,
I see a strong spirit.
I could feel the
power of your strike.
It was well-timed
and well-placed,
but lacked the necessary
follow-through after
the downward thrust.
With a little training,
I believe I can turn you
into an excellent swordsman.
I assume that you are
Kenshin Himura's sensei,
Hiko Seijuro, correct?
Deflecting that strike
was quite impressive,
but not even the
strongest ant can survive
when he fights with an elephant.
And no man can possibly
survive for long against
the mighty Fuji!
Spare me the monologue,
Gramps, you're boring me.
(growling)
Just keep your mouth
shut, rat face.
I was talking to Fuji, not you.
♪
Talking?
How can you talk to a monster?
How can you be
sure he understands
what you're saying?
I can tell a great deal
about an opponent
from one sword strike.
And from observing and
absorbing that one blow,
I learned everything I need
to know about our giant friend.
You're unique;
a spirited person
of great complexity
and strong emotions.
Much more than that old
bastard gives you credit for.
And you're no monster--
you're a true warrior,
one of the few who are left.
You've just been brainwashed.
Huh?
I can imagine what it was like
when you were growing up,
being different
than everyone else,
having no one in your life
who understood you.
You must've suffered
a great deal.
No doubt he took
advantage of that,
but now you have to
stop listening to him.
He doesn't want
what's best for you,
only what's best for him.
He's an asinine old goat.
Asinine old goat?
Why, how dare you?
You're a true warrior,
Fuji, it's time for you
to regain your dignity.
(growling)
Don't listen to him,
Fuji, I forbid it.
You are to listen to me and
only me, is that understood?
Remember, without me, you
wouldn't be here today.
Have I made myself clear?
Have you forgotten
the misery your life was
before I found you?
Let me remind you.
♪
There he is!
You can't get away,
we're gonna keep you here
'til the soldiers come.
-He's so big!
-Stay back!
I can't tell if
it's human or not.
A human, that thing?
No way!
Kill it before it kills us!
It's so strong it could destroy
the whole village all by itself.
It's your duty to destroy it.
Right, fire!
(groaning)
♪
Don't forget, it was me
who found you lying in a pool
of your own blood, and
who saved you from death.
All I want in return for
my kindness is your loyalty,
now is that too much to ask?
-Quiet!
-Huh?
I'm warning you,
don't say another word.
This is between me and Fuji.
Wow.
He's quite a guy.
Fuji, take off your armor.
It's doing you
more harm than good.
It offers you no protection
and the weight will
weaken your heart.
If you continue
to wear it, you'll die.
He could talk a leopard
into giving up its spots.
He's some piece of work.
Oh.
-Wow.
-What a guy.
He's the greatest.
-Absolutely.
-Ohhh.
Don't take off your armor,
you foolish troglodyte.
He's just trying to trick
you with all that fancy talk.
Just how long are you
gonna have to go on
doing this old
goat's dirty work?
You've been paying him
back your whole life.
You don't owe him a thing.
It's time for you to start
choosing your own battles,
to decide who
you're gonna fight,
and why you're fighting them.
For starters, I know this one
guy who says that no matter how
big and strong you are,
you won't be able to beat him.
And guess what?
It's me.
(growling)
(yelling)
♪
(gasping)
I-I think he's crying.
Yes, he is.
They're tears of joy.
What, tears of joy?
Yes, I believe that throughout
his life, Fuji has never met
anyone who has perceived him
as anything but a monster,
an inhuman beast.
Considered a thing who
was either feared or used
and manipulated by the
unscrupulous to create fear.
But Hiko has treated
Fuji like a man.
To Fuji, it's as if he'd been
given a wonderful gift,
and that's what has moved him
to tears: Hiko's generosity.
But why in the world would Hiko
tell him to take his armor off
when that makes him
quicker and stronger?
He's dangerous enough.
'Cause that's just
how it has to be.
Oh, that's no answer.
Because he's Hiko Seijuro,
and he doesn't take
advantage of anyone.
And 'cause he's
the coolest fighter
that ever walked
the face of the Earth.
♪
(speaking unintelligibly)
Oh, no!
Now!
A fight, fair and square.
♪
(yelling)
Why'd they stop?
♪
-Sword range.
-What?
Fuji won't come within range
of Hiko's sword until he's fully
focused and ready
for an all-out attack.
Meanwhile, Hiko is
watching every movement,
every vibration of Fuji's body,
for changes in muscle tension.
That's how Hiko will know
when the attack
is going to come.
When the attack comes,
who wins or loses
will be evident
within a few seconds.
In this case, I believe that
master Hiko's counterattack
will probably be
the deciding factor.
I sure hope so.
Fuji's so powerful
and has already caused
so much destruction
that I'm afraid
the entire village'll
be destroyed
if this fight isn't over
within the next few seconds,
and if Hiko doesn't
win, then what?
-Quiet, will ya?
-Huh?
Hiko Seijuro is a master sensei
of the Hiten Mitsurugi style.
The last thing he needs to be
is distracted by
comments from you.
Don't worry, he'll win.
He's got to.
♪
What's the matter, Fuji,
what are you waiting for?
You scared of me?
Come on, let's do it.
♪
Let's go.
Oh, no, look at that!
Both hands.
Ha ha, that will
double the force.
There won't be
anything left of Hiko.
(yelling)
(groaning)
(screaming)
Hiko's gone.
The force of that
blow was devastating.
There's nothing left,
there's not a speck of bone
or even a drop of flesh, or...
Heh?
No!
Hey, that was
quite a blow, Fuji.
Huh?
Wow!
(gasping)
♪
Unfortunately, you missed me.
Ha ha ha, yeah!
♪
Hiten Mitsurugi style
Nine-Deaded Dragon Light!
♪
(groaning)
(loud crashing)
(explosion)
Wow, I didn't think he'd kill
him, but it looks like he did.
That's the difference
between him and Kenshin.
You're wrong, he's alive!
Look, at his sword!
It has a reversed edge
like Kenshin's.
There's no need to worry about
Fuji, he's only unconscious.
With a physique like his,
I have no doubt that
he'll recover within
two or three hours.
Ohh, master Hiko,
you're so cool.
You're our hero.
(chuckling)
The final sword exchange
was absolutely brilliant.
I've never seen
anything quite like it.
Fuji finally met someone
who treated him honorably,
like a true warrior.
He may have lost the fight,
but his spirit won
a great victory.
It looks like the old goat
could use a bit of help.
Just as long as he
shuts his big mouth.
Why is it that evil
old goats like this guy
always live so long?
Because he knows exactly
where he's going when he dies.
I've fulfilled my
promise to Kenshin.
Now, we can only hope that
he can survive his encounter
with Shishio, but I have
little doubt about that.
I happen to know he
had a great teacher.
Uh huh.
♪
Well, finally,
the battle is over.
Over?
♪
Hey, we...won.
We actually won.
Yeah, Aoiya is safe
and everybody's okay!
Yay, we did it!
Yeah, let's take care of Shishio
and then we'll head back home.
Hey, then we'll see Kenshin.
I hope so.
Please, Kenshin, hurry home.
♪
Is something wrong?
No, it's just that...
I thought I heard Kori's voice.
Cut it out, will ya?
Really, I'm fine.
Guess your fight with
Aoshi was really tough.
You might have some
kind of head injury.
Very funny.
Look, even if my imagination
is playing tricks on me,
I suddenly got
a real strong feeling
that everyone in Aoiya is okay.
I sure hope so, but I think
you're being pretty optimistic
to put your faith in
that teacher of yours.
He probably couldn't
even find the place.
Hiko Seijuro's never
broken a promise.
He'll protect our guys
in Aoiya, I know he will.
Ha, maybe, but I still
think we better get back
there as soon as we can.
(sighing)
Is there something wrong, Hoji?
Yes, I've just received word
from our informant in Kyoto.
Our attack against
Aoiya has failed!
All of our guys have lost.
Even that monster of
Saizuchi's been taken out.
We've lost!
So, almost everyone of the
Juppongatana group is either
injured or dead.
But how?
We were armed with the
most ruthless fighters.
We even had a giant.
How could we lose?
The answer's simple,
their guys were better
than ours.
It's called survival
of the fittest.
We live by the law
of the jungle.
The weak shall perish,
the strong shall survive.
Like me.
The only thing that matters
to someone like me is survival.
Don't worry, Mr. Shishio,
I'll defeat Kenshin,
and we'll carry out our plan
just the way we said we would.
I've gotta go now, I've got
an appointment to keep.
♪
Incredible, he never
ceases to amaze me.
I think he's got ice in
his veins instead of blood.
Indeed, Seijuro's strength
is due to his inability
to feel emotions the way
the rest of us do.
The weak shall perish,
and the strong shall survive.
That's the only thing
he believes in.
But he's a Samurai!
He must believe
in more than that.
You mean, Bushido,
a code of honor?
(laughing)
Let me go,
put me down, you animal.
Oh, come on,
lady, cut it out.
Why can't you understand
that I'm trying to help you?
You listen to me,
I've been carried around
like a stuffed animal
for far too long.
Huh?
What are you really
trying to say?
Stop it!
But I haven't done anything.
(grumbling)
Yumi, where do we go
to fight the next duel?
♪
Through that door.
I think you know
the name of the one
you're going to fight.
It must be Sojiro Seta.
Just who is this Sojiro?
Do you know if he's any good?
The Juppongatana's
best swordsman.
He's the one who broke
my reversed edge sword
into two pieces,
although we never did
get to finish our fight.
Huh?
So, this is the guy
you told me about,
the one who's so dangerous.
Yeah, he's the one.
When we ended that last fight,
we agreed to call it a draw,
but if we'd continued, it's
pretty clear who would've won
considering the fact that
I would've had to fight
with half a sword.
So, you ready for him?
I have a new reversed
edge sword now.
I've also combined several
different styles with the style
that Hiko taught me,
creating an entirely new form,
which Sojiro's never seen.
The other thing that makes
this fight different
is that this time
I can't afford to lose.
Are you ready?
'Cause there's no turning
back once you're inside.
What makes Sojiro unique is
his total lack of emotion,
which makes it nearly impossible
to know what he's
going to do next.
Sojiro also has another tactic
that makes him
almost invincible,
a secret move, which Kenshin
Himura doesn't know about.
That secret is what led to
the successful assassination
of Okubo.
Sojiro cannot be defeated,
he's the strongest swordsman
I've ever created.
Kenshin cannot win.
The moment has finally arrived
for the legend of
Battousai the Slasher
to come to an end.
Kenshin, how nice it
is to see you again.
♪
(singing in foreign language)