[MEI]
Trespassing again?
[MATSURI]
Aw, that's not nice.
So I don't even get a hello?
And after I waited for you
in the cold this whole time.
Come on, you know you
wanna warm me up.
Just like you did for
Yuzu at the bus stop.
[gasps]
[MATSURI] You know, at
first I was thinking about
paying you back for that
cute little stunt you pulled
by doing something
naughty to you, too.
But then I realized that
you're a dirty slut
who goes around
kissing everybody,
so then, it's not really a
punishment but more of a reward.
Stop messing around already.
[MATSURI]
Here.
I decided to bring you
a little present, Mei.
Check it out.
It's a pretty good
shot, isn't it?
Just tell me what you're after.
[MATSURI]
But I already did.
I want you to keep your
nasty mitts off my Yuzu.
[MATSURI]
Obviously, you weren't listening
the first time I warned you.
Well, I guess I shouldn't
expect a whore like you
to be able to control
her urges, should I?
You may try to act
all prim and proper,
but I can tell you're
just a huge tramp.
[MATSURI laughs]
Luckily, there's no need to
worry about that, though.
I came up with a solution.
I know somebody who'd
be perfect for you.
This way, you'll have an outlet
for all that pent-up energy.
[MATSURI] You're gonna get to
play with one of my clients.
I'd do it myself, but this
guy thinks I'm older
from the fake photos
I've sent to him.
Don't be sad, Mei.
There are plenty of other
lonely people out there
who'd love to touch you.
I hope you like the
present I got you.
Oh, and by the way,
if you decide to be ungrateful
and turn it down, well,
this picture might go to someone
you don't want seeing it.
Come on, you're a
pretty smart girl.
I'm sure you'll make
the right choice.
[MEI] She won't go back
to the way she was.
[MATSURI]
Yeah, that's okay.
She'll always be
my older sister.
Nothing else really matters.
[YUZU]
Aw, man, I screwed it up again!
[groans]
What's wrong with me?
I'm home, Yuz--
What happened?
I'm a failure.
That's a lot of tries.
Yeah, it turns out the cake
is the hardest part for me.
I don't mind grabbing
one from the store.
[YUZU]
No way!
I promised myself I would make
it from scratch this year!
I dunno.
Maybe the oven
temperature's not right.
I waited for it to preheat,
so that can't be it.
And I measured everything
just like it says.
Guess I didn't mix it enough.
[UME] I can tell this is gonna
be a Christmas to remember.
Tah-dah!
Aw, it's adorable! You
did a great job, sweetie!
Maybe I should stop buying
these and just have you...
[YUZU]
This Christmas is big.
It's the first one
with Mei here.
I hope the cake makes
her super happy.
[YUZU giggles]
[YUZU] Yeah, I went around
to different stores
looking for one Mei would like.
Look at that sweet face!
Welcome back, Mei!
Hey there, how was
student council?
Did you girls get
a lot of work done?
[YUZU] We're setting things
up for the Christmas party!
Anything special
you wanna eat?
Just let me know and I can pick
it up when I go shopping lat--
Sorry.
I hate to ruin your plans,
but there's still a great
deal of work left to do
for the student council.
I was looking forward
to tomorrow night,
but I'll have to cancel.
[YUZU]
What?
[UME]
Oh, no!
You have to stay at school
on Christmas? Really?
Are you sure you
just can't ditch it?
[UME]
Yuzu, don't guilt her.
[YUZU]
I'm not.
Please excuse me.
[sighs]
I was so excited about
Christmas, too.
Hey, I'm done. You can
have the bathroom now.
[MEI]
Good to know. Thank you.
Listen. Mei.
Are you sure you can't take
the day off tomorrow?
Just push it to the next day.
Oh, I guess that's
winter break, isn't it?
[MEI] Unfortunately, it's
something that can't wait.
Okay.
[YUZU]
I sound like a bratty kid.
[phone dings]
It's from Matsuri.
She wants to go out tomorrow.
A date, huh? On
Christmas day no less?
Jeez, doesn't she
have anybody else
she wants to hang out with?
[MEI]
Yuzu.
Uh-huh? What is it?
Go out with her.
She wants to see you.
That girl needs you, so you
shouldn't let her down.
[YUZU]
Matsuri needs me?
What did she mean by that?
[HARUMI]
Yuzu-chi!
[YUZU yells]
Ouch, Harumin.
What was that for?
[HARUMI]
You don't remember?
We were supposed
to walk together!
But you sit on a throne of lies!
Uh, what does that mean?
Anyway, I'm sorry.
I didn't hear you ask me to!
[HARUMI sighs]
You're all decked
out for Christmas,
but you don't seem to be
full of the holiday spirit.
Oh.
So what's the matter?
Well, it's just... Mei can't
come to the Christmas party.
Whoa. Not taking off?
I gotta admit, the
girl's got gumption.
Yeah, apparently there was
no getting out of it.
That's sounds awful.
Anyway, bye!
What? Harumin, wait!
You're going without me?
[HARUMI] I know you.
You're staying here.
[gasps]
[HARUMI]
Student council's not my scene.
See ya!
[YUZU]
That's it!
Might as well give it a shot!
[MATSURI]
Yuzu!
I never got a yes or no from
you yesterday, so here I am!
Matsuri?
Uh, come with me!
[YUZU] I told you not to
show up here out of the blue!
What if someone saw you?
[MATSURI] Aw. You're such
a widdle worry wart!
Hey, why didn't you
respond to my message?
I dunno.
I wasn't sure what my schedule
was gonna be for
today, that's all.
Yeah? I guess that excuse
maybe kinda makes sense.
But you know your schedule
by now, don't you?
So let's go on a date together.
[YUZU]
Mh-hm.
Sure, I'm free.
[MATSURI] Yay! I know just
the place I want to take you!
[YUZU] This is what
you wanted, right, Mei?
[giggles]
I haven't seen you
this happy in forever.
Who knew you liked
strawberry cake that much?
[MATSURI laughs]
Well, yeah, sure. the cake
here is pretty incredible.
But that's not the only reason
I'm in such a good mood.
[YUZU]
Huh? What do you mean?
[MATSURI] 'Cause I finally
get you all to myself.
That's so sweet.
It's kinda funny,
I've been practicing my
baking skills a lot recently.
So you'd think I would be
totally sick of cake after that.
[YUZU] But I'm scarfing
this thing down like crazy!
Wow. Did you make
a Christmas cake?
I'm surprised you didn't just
buy it from the store this year.
[YUZU]
Right?
It's super tricky getting
that fluffy consistency!
We never had homemade cake
when I used to go there.
[YUZU]
Uh?
[MATSURI]
Eh, nothing.
That reminds me.
We did Christmas
together all the time
back when we were
kids, didn't we?
[YUZU] Your parents
were always working,
so you would play by yourself.
[YUZU]
One day, I decided to say hi.
[BOTH gasp]
[BOTH giggle]
[giggling]
[YUZU]
That was the first day you and I
started acting like sisters.
Oh, yeah, speaking
of your parents,
are they still busy
with work these days?
[MATSURI]
Uh-huh.
Honestly, my mom and
dad are more married
to their dumb careers than
they are to each other.
Gee, that's a bummer.
Hey, how 'bout this?
Why don't you come celebrate
Christmas with our family?
it'll be just like the old days!
Let's make sure we're
on the same page.
Are you asking me to come
as your little sister?
[YUZU]
Mh-hm.
I think Mom's gonna be so
glad to see you again.
Oh, and Mei would probably
love for you to come over.
That way, she'll have
even more family.
[chuckles]
[MATSURI]
Sure, as long as Mei's happy.
Mei this, Mei that.
Don't you ever talk
about anything else?
You're so lame!
Uh, why do you sound so upset?
Since you're so
completely obsessed
with everything that girl does,
you should know she's meeting
some rando outside the station.
[YUZU]
Huh?
She's definitely enjoying
her Christmas right now.
What the heck are you
going on about, Matsuri?
I don't think that
joke is very funny.
But it's not a joke.
You remember my
work phone, right?
I've graciously let Mei
borrow it for the day.
Wanna call it?
If you call right now, you
might even get through to her.
[MATSURI]
Wake up, Yuzu.
She's not the perfect
goody-two-shoes
you think she is.
Can't you see she's
nothing but a skank?
It's not only that,
but she lied to you
about where she
was gonna be today.
Come on, you deserve
better than that,
so why don't you give up on her?
Who needs a liar when
you've got me, anyway?
Just forget about her already.
[YUZU]
So, when Mei... when she said...
That girl needs you, so you
shouldn't let her down.
[MATSURI]
Hm?
[YUZU]
Let's go. We need to apologize.
Huh? To who?
To the only person who has been
thinking of your feelings!
I wasn't even going
to do this today,
but Mei insisted that I should
pay more attention to you.
She cares about you, Matsuri.
[gasps]
We should hurry.
Seriously?
Are you telling me I played
right into her hands
in spite of all that planning?
I'm not the loser
here, she is!
She's just a boring,
stupid robot!
How can she win out over me? Uh?
[YUZU] You've got a lot to
learn about relationships.
It's not some kind of game.
Stop boiling it down
to winning and losing!
[YUZU] Please pick up.
Please pick up.
[gasps]
Mei, thank goodness!
Are you all right?
[busy tone]
[MEI]
Yuzu?
[gasps]
I think I hung up on you.
Sorry, I wasn't
trying to be rude.
I just don't know how
to use this phone.
[YUZU]
Oh, Mei!
I was so worried!
[YUZU]
Mei.
[MEI] So? Did the two of
you have a fun Christmas?
Shut up. Don't need
to rub it in.
You know it's
game over for me.
I'm sure Yuzu hates my guts
now that she knows what I did.
Looks like you've
stolen my spot
as her little sister
once and for all.
I should've known.
I was stupid to think there
was someone out there
who'd love me and nobody else.
You know something?
We're kind of alike.
I was always so desperate to
be loved, just like you are.
But I kept my heart
locked up tight,
and pushed everyone away
when they tried to get close.
Before I knew it,
I was left feeling empty.
Empty, huh?
[MEI] Yes, but there are certain
pushy people in this world
who will love you no matter
how much you protest.
And if we're lucky enough
to meet one of them,
then even we can end up happy.
Well, you might've
defeated me this time.
I mean, taught me a lesson...
But what you did
was really dumb.
What if that old pervert
at the train station
didn't wanna take
no for an answer?
[sighs]
I considered that,
and I was prepared for
that outcome as well.
What?
But you would've had to
do it with some gross dude
you don't even know!
As I told you,
we're quite similar.
I think I was testing Yuzu's
reaction... the way you would.
[MATSURI]
Take it from me, Mei.
You could stand to be
a lot more direct.
[YUZU] I still think
you should stay over.
[MATSURI]
Nah, it's too short-notice.
My parents would flip out.
All right.
Oh, yeah.
I almost forgot, I wanted to
give you a Christmas present
for all the trouble
I caused you today.
Why don't you come
a little closer?
What is it?
[MATSURI]
I know Mei plays it cool
and pretends like
she doesn't care...
...but underneath it all,
she really likes you.
Whoa! I mean as a sister!
Don't be weird.
Oh my God, I wish you could
see your face right now!
[YUZU]
Matsuri!
[MATSURI] Anyway, thanks
for playing with me today.
You're both good big sisters.
[MATSURI] Have a nice
night together, ladies!
Ooh! Next time, let's
have a threesome, yeah?
Bye!
A what?
[YUZU]
Matsuri!
[YUZU sighs]
Gee, I don't think I've
ever been this exhausted
on Christmas before.
I'm pretty sure Mom's
already gone to bed.
She said she had to work early.
Wait, there's one more thing.
[YUZU]
Hm?
[YUZU] It's not healthy
to eat this late.
Just wait till tomorrow.
But you specifically
made this cake for today.
And besides, if I save
it for tomorrow,
then it won't be as fresh.
[YUZU] You're the most stubborn
girl I've ever met, Mei.
Honestly, you're a lot
like your grandpa.
I'm flattered.
Well? How is it?
[MEI]
Hmm...
Disgusting.
[whines]
Did you think I would say that?
[YUZU gasps]
Aw, c'mon, would it kill you
to be up-front with me?
This is who I am.
By the way...
What happened today
was totally my fault.
I'm stupid, and I'm a
terrible older sister.
I hurt you and Matsuri.
I'm sorry.
[MEI] I can't believe
what a crybaby you are.
Mei!
Just promise me one thing.
Please don't ever put yourself
in danger like that again, okay?
Because if you get hurt...
...then it's gonna
hurt me and our mom
a hundred thousand times more!
Remember that!
You have to come to me
when you have a problem, Mei.
[MEI]
All right.
If that's what you want,
then I'll try to be
a bit more direct.
Whoa. Hold on, Mei.
Not so fast. What are you doing?
[MEI]
Here.
I don't understand
what's happening.
My heart is about to
beat out of my chest.
Can you feel it?
[YUZU] Wow. Why is she saying
this all of a sudden?
[MEI]
Yuzu.
There are some things inside
me that would thrill you
and some that would
terrify you.
I need you to understand that
much from the very start.
If you really want to see...
...just say the word.
[MEI]
I figured it was only fair
for me to give you
what you wanted.
Look, if you like someone,
you have to consider
their feelings, Yuzu.
[YUZU] Why did it have
to be Mei of all people?
Tell me how you feel about
me. I want the truth, Yuzu.
Um, how do I say it?