[YUZU]
Mei!
Is she already taken?
This is horrible.
Now what am I gonna do?
Wait.
Looks like maybe there's still
a way for me to help my sister.
It's the girl I met earlier!
[NINA]
Okay.
If this is Sara's destiny,
then I'm gonna help
make it happen.
This new shop really has
a warm atmosphere.
I'm sure it'll be
even more popular
as the weather starts
getting colder...
Yuzu. Cut it out, would you?
Our school trip is no time
for you to be a
stick in the mud!
It sucks that you got in
trouble for missing the train,
but it's not the
end of the world!
[YUZU] I don't get it.
What was the right answer?
[YUZU] I thought Mei liked
me better as a sister,
but now she doesn't
want that either?
This whole thing is so weird.
If you think I'm
gonna sit around
and let you ruin my good time
by acting like a bump on a log,
then you've got another
thing comin', Yuzucchi!
C'mere, you little grouch!
Take that! And that!
I'm not stopping
till I've tickled
all the bad feelings out!
[HARUMI, YUZU laughing]
[HARUMI]
Hm?
Aw, shoot, the weather's
gonna get bad.
We're supposed to check out
the Yasaka Shrine tomorrow.
I'm a history buff.
I can't miss a chance
to see the statues
of Shintarou Nakaoka
and Ryouma Sakamoto.
[HARUMI]
Wait, "promoting relationships"?
We're teenagers.
Why would they advertise
this place like that?
Do they want us to
make out? Besides...
[YUZU] I'll pray at every
shrine in town if I have to.
I just wanna patch things
up between me and Mei.
[HARUMI] And what's with
this sexy artwork?
[sneezes]
[HIMEKO] Ugh. I'd better
not be catching a cold!
We're going to the relationship
shrine tomorrow.
I have to be at my best ever!
[NINA] 'Scuse me.
Do you have a second?
Hurry up, sis!
We don't have much time!
Jeez, Nina. What's the rush?
Ugh, where are you taking me?
Less talking and more walking!
[SARA]
Stop pushing!
[NINA]
Tah-dah!
[NINA] I asked around a little
bit, and Mei will be here!
[SARA]
Huh?
[NINA] Which means you get to
visit a relationship shrine
with the girl of your destiny!
How cool is that, right?
[SARA] Well, yeah, I guess
it is pretty romantic.
But how can you be sure that
Mei's actually gonna show up?
[NINA] Trust me. She's
the one you want, yeah?
Then my take is,
if you have an opportunity,
you should go for it.
Just try!
Don't talk about people like
they're nothing but things!
Anyway, we're here, so I
might as well try, I guess!
Don't worry, sis. I'll make
sure that you get an opening.
You can do this!
Please give me a long-lasting
and wonderful future
with Mei-Mei!
Please make me a good big sister
who understands her
little sister's feelings!
[BOTH sigh]
[HARUMI grumbles]
There you are.
What took you so freakin' long?!
Don't come at me
with that attitude.
I have a lot of relationships
that need prayers, okay?
Same goes for me.
[SARA]
Hey, Yuzu!
[SARA laughing]
[YUZU]
Sara!
What's up? I didn't know
you were here, too!
[SARA]
Surprise!
Who's that girl?
I don't know.
[SARA]
So, wanna know a secret?
I saw my angel of destiny
again, isn't that great?
[YUZU gasps]
Whoa, really?
Yup, and this time, I found
out what her name is!
You mean you just
straight up asked her?
Look at you, being all forward!
[YUZU] Sara keeps getting
closer to what she wants,
but I'm over here even
further away from Mei
then when all this started.
[SARA]
...fate's on my side.
So I'm gonna confess to her.
What? You can't be serious!
I'm just saying, isn't it a
little soon to be doing that?
Probably so.
But still, I figure if I don't
tell her how I feel now,
well then, who knows?
So I'm all in!
I need to go catch
up with Nina.
See you later, okay?
And good luck to you, too!
We'll talk soon.
Let me know what happens!
[YUZU]
Sara seems so happy.
She's totally true to herself.
I wish I could be more like her.
[PEDESTRIAN A]
Oh, no!
[PEDESTRIAN B]
I forgot my umbrella!
[PEDESTRIAN C]
Crap, it's raining!
[YUZU] I'm not just
guessing at Mei's feelings;
I'm lying to myself about mine.
We're stepsisters,
so what I'm saying is,
you mean a lot to me 'cause
you're part of my family now.
Does that make sense?
[YUZU] It doesn't help
that I keep spouting off
these empty words that
don't mean anything.
I want to know your
true feelings about me,
and please tell me honestly.
[YUZU]
I have to do it!
Yuzucchi, here.
Uh. Wait, what are these for?
[HARUMI]
They're matching charms.
If two people share a set,
their relationship will
become really strong.
I bought too many, so...
I suppose you can have this one.
[HARUMI]
Is that the reason you insisted
on picking one she'd like?
What? Don't be absurd! Did not!
I found myself with
an extra charm,
and it happened to match
Aihara's fashion style!
[HARUMI] Yeah, yeah,
you're heartless, we know.
[HIMEKO]
...her a gift on purpose!
These are awesome. Thank you.
I'm feeling a lot braver now.
[NINA]
A-ha!
Good! I finally found you!
You do know everybody else
is on the opposite side, right?
Don't you wanna pray?
For good luck?
I don't pray for luck or
fortunes. It's too frivolous.
Suit yourself.
I just came to tell you
my sister likes you.
I dunno if you're dating anybody
or what, but if you're not,
do you think maybe
you'd like to go out
with my sister sometime?
Hm?
It's nice of you to let me know,
but I'm not sure I'm interested.
Aww.
That's too bad. I guess
I understand, though.
I know what you do want.
Anyway!
Well, I gotta go!
[SARA]
Nina!
Nina! Where'd you go?
[SARA]
It's Mei.
My little sister called and told
me she was over here somewhere.
So, uh, did you see her?
I did. A few minutes
ago, actually.
I think she's already gone
somewhere else by now.
What?
This is your chance, Sara.
You gotta take it!
Hey, listen. Uh,
here's the thing.
You should know that...
I have a huge crush on you, Mei!
When we met at Tokyo Station,
I couldn't help but fall in
love with you at first sight!
I understand that you
and I may not
know each other very well,
and I'm not even sure if
you're actually into girls,
but I really mean it, okay?
Every word!
Sara, just one question.
Tell me whether or
not you need me.
Of course I need you.
Being there for each other
is what love's all about.
[YUZU] I'm sorry to
interrupt your plans.
[MEI]
I'd prefer you to keep it brief.
[YUZU]
Uh, sure.
Last night was weird, so I was
hoping we could clear the air.
When I said that I loved
you as a stepsister,
I was being honest about that
part, but that's not all of it!
I had more to tell you,
so I'll just say it now.
Let's see. Uh, here's
the thing, Mei.
I... I...
I lo...
[YUZU]
Say it! Come on!
Sorry, that's no good.
Maybe I should start over.
[MEI]
Yuzu.
I have something I need to
make you aware of as well.
Earlier today, I found out
someone has feelings for me.
So now, I've decided I'm
going to date that person.
[YUZU]
No way!
This can not be real!
Mei found somebody she's into?
During our school
trip of all things?
[YUZU laughs]
[YUZU]
How's this even possible?
I mean, did she just up and
start dating some rando? Ha-ha!
I wonder who it is!
If Mei said yes to this person,
they've gotta be a
perfect ten, right?
[whines]
[YUZU]
Oh, man.
[YUZU] Wait, I don't have
any right to be upset.
I haven't even told
her my feelings yet.
Jeez, what am I doing
with my life?
[YUZU]
I never gave her this either.
If she's seriously
dating someone else,
then it doesn't matter
that I like her.
[NINA]
It's Yuzu! Heya!
Uh. Oh, hey there,
Sara's sister.
[NINA]
It's Nina.
You're so silly.
Anyway, what's wrong?
You seem upset.
You could say that, yeah.
Aww.
Oh, right!
Did you hear Sara's big news?
She confessed to that girl,
and it went super well!
[YUZU]
Did it really?
That's so good to hear!
[NINA chuckles]
I knew you would be
happy for her, Yuzu!
Speaking of which, I'm gonna
have to ask you a favor.
My sister's in love, so she
needs your support, okay?
Well, duh, is that
even a question?
Sara's my friend,
so why wouldn't I have
her back on this?
Really? Ha-ha!
You're so amazing!
[YUZU]
Nina, can't breathe.
[NINA]
I have your word, right?
You're not gonna change
your mind later on?
[YUZU]
Pinky swear.
Oh, by the way, I noticed
you're still in uniform.
Don't you wanna take a bath?
Ah! Oops, gotta go!
[NINA]
Yeah, you better hurry! Bye!
[YUZU]
Have a good night!
[chuckles]
[YUZU]
So, Sara's confession went well.
Good for her.
I can't help but wonder...
If Mei and I weren't
stepsisters,
and I actually worked
up the courage
to tell her how
I feel about her,
maybe that would
change everything,
and she'd wanna
go out with me.
It's so hard for me
to believe Mei
would want to date
anybody, though.
I mean--
Our group's bath hours have
ended. Try again tomorrow.
Huh? Then what are you
doing in the bath still?
Student council has patrol duty.
We have to be the
last ones to leave.
Your presence here
violates our school policy,
as well as the rules
of this hotel.
Which means you're
causing an issue
for the entire student body.
Therefore--
[YUZU]
Yeah, yeah, I'm the worst.
Tell me something I don't know!
I'll just be a few
minutes, all right?
[sighs]
I don't get it. Why does
my life suck so much?
[SARA sighs]
[YUZU]
Uh? Huh?
Sara?
Yuzu? I didn't notice you!
Are you okay? You look
a little lightheaded.
[SARA]
I feel great.
Oh, I know what's up.
You just look all spaced out
'cause you're in love, huh?
You're such a jerk, stop
picking on me, Yuzu!
Owie.
I was planning to tell you
before I went to bed tonight,
but I guess my dumb sister
already beat me to it.
[YUZU]
You're so lucky.
My little love story was over
before it ever had
a chance to begin.
Huh? What do you mean?
[YUZU sighs]
She said she's already
dating someone else.
It's fine. I just have
to give up and move on.
Deep down, I kinda knew
it wouldn't work out.
[SARA]
Yuzu!
[YUZU]
What's the matter?
[SARA] You should express
your feelings to her!
I can't do that. She's taken!
[SARA] I know! But even so,
you still love her, right?
[YUZU]
Yeah, I really do.
[SARA]
Then do something about it!
Your heart knows what's
best for you, Yuzu.
You just have to learn
how to listen to it.
If I was brave enough to
tell my crush I liked her,
you can do it too!
Aw, listen to you, you're
just a little player, huh?
Don't call me little! Yuzu!
[YUZU]
Yeah, not so tough now, are ya?
[SARA]
...my hairdo!
Come on! Let go of me!
[SARA screams]
[SARA]
Oh, great.
[YUZU]
You're the best, Sara.
I'm not gonna give up now,
no matter what happens.
[chuckles]
[SARA]
Huh?
Uh-oh. This is Yuzu's ID card.
Guess it fell out of her stuff.
Wait, Aihara?
'Kay, I'm just gonna say it.
See, I kinda have a
crush on this girl.
Problem is, she's
also my stepsister.
[gasps]
[door opens]
I'll be back soon.
I just need to turn in
the daily journal.
You here, Mei?
Shame on you.
Sneaking in uninvited.
You said you'd go
straight to bed,
but I assumed you
meant your own bed.
Don't you think we should
talk about this some more?
It's after lights out.
Whatever you want
will have to wait.
Please Mei, just listen.
It'll only take a minute.
[MEI]
Go to your room.
Can I just say one thing?
[sighs]
Forget it.
That's the rule, no exceptions.
Uh-oh! Momokino!
[YUZU]
Hey!
[HIMEKO]
Uh?
She must be exhausted.
See ya tomorrow, Mei-Mei.
[MEI] Listen, after she
falls asleep, get out.
[YUZU] Wow. I can't believe
she covered for me.
She smells so good.
[YUZU]
I can hear her heartbeat.
[gasps]
[YUZU]
This makes me feel so calm.
Oh, no.
Now's not the time to
be thinking like this...
...but I gotta tell her!
Look. Mei--
[MEI gasps]
I said leave.
[groans]
[YUZU] Why couldn't I have
just told her the truth
when I had the chance?
[SARA] I know! But even so,
you still love her, right?
[YUZU]
Yeah!
No one loves Mei like I do,
and she needs to know that!
[YUZU]
The station?
[HIMEKO]
Yes.
Apparently, she's meeting
someone there
so they can spend
the entire free day
strolling around town together.
Thanks, Momokino,
you're a big help!
I'm sorry, Harumin.
I'll have do a rain check.
Don't worry about me, girl.
I've got a whole list
of places to visit.
Then I'm off to Kyoto Station!
What?! Yuzu Aihara!
The president has business
with someone else!
[YUZU] Okay, if I were
Mei, where would I go?
[YUZU]
Here?
Not here either!
Here, maybe?
No luck!
This place is massive!
Well, great.
[NINA]
Yuzu.
[YUZU]
Huh?
Didn't think I'd see
you at the station.
[YUZU]
Nina.
I came here to talk
to my little sister,
but I can't seem to
find her anywhere.
[NINA]
Oh, Mei's with my sister.
[YUZU]
Huh?
Those two, really?
Hey, wait, why do
you know her name?
[NINA]
Why?
[YUZU gasps]
'Cause Mei is my sister's
girlfriend, that's why.
Sorry about that.
I guess I spaced out.
[SARA]
Oh, no, it's okay. I'm fine.
Hey, what's wrong?
[SARA]
Um, Mei.
Would it...
...be okay if I kissed you?
[NINA]
I love my sister, Yuzu.
I guess we both like
the same person, huh?
[HIMEKO]
They get so carried away,
they can't see what's
right in front of them.
[MEI] I have nothing further
to discuss with you.
I don't ever wanna feel
that way again, Mei!
So here's the truth.