What's gotten into you, Mei?
You're acting weird.
Come here.
Uh, don't you think we've
taken it far enough?
Oh, nonsense.
You know I'm in love with you.
Uh, that's unexpected.
Owie!
Oh, oops.
I wish you'd at least
try to stay focused.
It's almost test day,
and I don't have to
help you get ready.
[YUZU]
That's my little sis for you.
Always so affectionate.
[MEI] If you don't want
Grandfather to look down on you,
then you need to score
in the top 100.
[YUZU]
It's not my fault I can't focus.
It's all because
of that last kiss.
And then when she
held my hand...
[YUZU] I thought she
was trying to show me
she felt the same
way, but maybe...
With grades like this,
you might get held back.
[YUZU]
Why is she making that sad face?
Hey, Mei?
I'm just wondering,
should I get my hopes up?
Explain it so a dummy
like me understands.
When you kissed me,
what did it mean?
If you tell me,
then I promise I'll study.
'Cause the way things are now,
I have no idea how I'm
supposed to behave around you.
It meant nothing.
Stepsisters aren't meant to
be physical with each other.
You know that.
We're going to have to
start acting normal now.
So, let's consider
that our final kiss.
[YUZU] I guess, if that's
what you really want.
[HARUMI] Yuzucchi. You can't
just go rushing in like that.
I had to make a move
or nothing would happen!
You're way out of it.
I didn't realize you were this
stressed out over the exams.
I wasn't even the one
who started it.
Why am I the one fighting?
[HARUMI] Uh, because that's
how shooter games work?
[YUZU whines]
[YUZU] Man, I've gotten totally
wrapped up in this mess.
Now I keep losing sleep
and I can never
concentrate on anything!
[HARUMI]
Chill, it's just a game.
[YUZU] Maybe it's time
to throw in the towel.
I don't really get it, but you
should try to relax a little.
See, look. She's
keeping her cool.
[YUZU]
Huh?
[HARUMI] If you adapt to
your target's movements
like she's doing,
it's a lot easier.
[ZOMBIES grunting]
Hey. I think I know her.
Matsuri?
There you are, Yuzu!
I finally found ya!
[MATSURI hums]
[MATSURI]
Nice to meet you.
I'm Matsuri Mizusawa.
[HARUMI]
I'm Harumi Taniguchi.
This looks so yummy.
Matsuri and I grew up in
the same neighborhood.
She and I go way back.
Aw, so you were
childhood buddies.
[YUZU] Nah, I'd say
she was more like
my little sister, actually.
[HARUMI]
Hm?
She's grown a lot since
I last saw her, though!
Hey, I'm a second year in
middle school, you know!
I'm not a little kid anymore!
Fine, I'm sorry. Anyway,
you just here to goof off?
[MATSURI]
Uh-uh.
I came because I was hoping
to see you again, Yuzu.
[YUZU]
Huh?
This is your part
of town, right?
I thought I'd run into you
at one of these places.
So I made a fun little
game out of it.
[YUZU]
Couldn't you have just called me
and asked where I was?
[MATSURI] That would've been
like using a cheat code.
It'd be too boring that way.
I'm so glad I managed
to track you down.
Besides, this creepy
old dude just paid me
for my part-time job,
but I would feel kinda lame
if I spent all that
money by myself.
Wow, so you work part-time?
I'm surprised you can do
that in middle school.
[MATSURI] Yeah, some weirdos'll
pay top dollar for dirty photos.
Everybody knows that.
What? Matsuri, how could you
do something so sketchy?
Oh, relax already.
A girl's gotta get paid.
It's not a big deal.
But it's dangerous!
Nah, it's safer
than you might think.
I mean, it's not like
I'd be stupid enough
to send them pictures of myself.
I just find porno pics online
and pretend it's me.
Then I send a few texts,
and those pervs don't
know the difference.
Well, that's the kind
of world we live in.
It's full of pathetic
losers like them.
So, where do you wanna go next?
What's up with you? Quit it!
[YUZU]
Look, kiddo.
I don't care how good
the money might be,
what you're doing
is super messed up!
[MATSURI chuckles]
You've always been
sweet, you know?
One of your many good qualities.
[YUZU]
Huh?
You haven't changed much, huh?
Let's see what's new with you.
[YUZU] Wait, we're not
done talking about this!
Hey! Give it back!
I'm impressed, Yuzu.
Looks like you have
a lot of friends! Hm?
[MATSURI]
Hmm...
Your new school,
it's girls-only, right?
[YUZU]
Yeah.
Where'd that question come from?
[MATSURI]
I was just wondering.
At a girl's school, do the
girls all kiss each other?
[YUZU coughing]
[HARUMI]
Yuzucchi!
Hey, are you gonna
be okay there?
[YUZU]
If you go to a co-ed school,
I guess two girls kissing might
seem a bit out of the ordinary.
Maybe Mei feels awkward too.
It's getting late.
We should go.
Besides, we don't
want to get caught
stopping in our uniforms again.
Crap! I still need to go
buy ingredients for dinner!
Sorry, but we gotta
head home now.
It's been good
catching up with you!
Hey, wait up!
[YUZU]
Hm?
[MATSURI] There's something
else I wanna ask you
before you leave.
Oh, but feel free to go on
home by yourself, Taniguchi.
Uh, okay.
I've got a few
things to say to you
about the poor choices
you've been making lately!
[HARUMI sighs]
[HARUMI]
Screw it, I'll stay, too.
[bell ringing]
[HIMEKO] Perfect. We finished
right on schedule.
[MARUTA]
But look at the time.
We should post them tomorrow.
Yes.
Am I reading this correctly?
There's no way she
scored that high!
[MARUTA] And the tests were
especially difficult this time.
[HIMEKO] Perhaps Yuzu Aihara's
not utterly incapable.
[MEI chuckles]
[BOTH]
Hm?
I'm home from school
now, Kumagoro.
[sighs]
[music playing]
[MATSURI]
Woohoo!
[YUZU]
Aww, yeah!
[MATSURI]
You rock, Yuzu!
Thanks for coming!
Goodnight! Whoo!
And go buy my album!
--[MATSURI] Encore!
--You know what?
I think it's time
to wrap this up.
Aww, don't be such a buzzkill!
After this, we're going to
see her off to the station.
Understand, Yuzucchi?
Uh... Mm-hm.
[HARUMI] Okay. I'll take
care of the bill for us.
[phone dings]
[gasps]
Shoot. It's my sister!
Huh?
[HARUMI]
I'm so sorry!
It turns out I need to run
back to my house real quick!
[YUZU]
Okay.
Seriously though!
I want you to do exactly
what I just told you!
Don't disobey your Mama Harumin!
[YUZU]
All right, already!
Jeez, that was really random.
I wonder what Harumin
was freaking out over?
[MATSURI]
Who cares?
Anyway, Matsuri, we should
probably get go--
[MATSURI] Yeah, we'd
like more time, please.
[YUZU]
What the--?
Don't worry.
I've got lots of money.
Yeah, dirty money!
Besides...
[YUZU]
Matsuri?
I still have a few more
questions for you.
For instance.
Do you have a crush on anyone?
No way! I mean, uh,
of course I do.
Everybody does! So yeah!
But enough about me.
Do you have one?
Sure do!
Really?
Matsuri?
I'm looking at her.
[gasps]
[YUZU]
Why'd you take that?
[MATSURI] This is the
girl you like, isn't it?
The one with the long dark hair?
[gasps]
[MATSURI]
Aww, I'm so jealous!
Look, Mei and I are just--
Oh. So her name is Mei.
That's good to know.
But... the caption says
"little sister."
I thought you were
an only child, Yuzu.
Oh, I see.
Your mom got remarried,
so you're stepsisters.
Look at your face, though.
Do your parents know you're
horny for your own sibling?
What would they say?
Are you trying to keep it a
secret from your friends too?
Do you guys find places
to make out at school?
Have you gone all
the way with her yet?
Come on, do you honestly see
a future with your stepsister?
Stepsisters aren't meant to
be physical with each other.
You know that.
We're going to have to
start acting normal now.
So, let's consider
that our final kiss.
[YUZU] She's right. I haven't
even thought about the future.
[phone buzzing]
[YUZU]
A public phone?
Hello?
[MEI]
Yuzu?
[gasps] Oh, Mei!
[MEI]
Yes.
I came to the store to buy
us something for dinner,
but I'm not sure
what I should get.
I'm calling to see if you
already had something in mind
so I can pick it up.
[YUZU]
Right.
I'm sorry, it was my turn
tonight, wasn't it?
[YUZU] Just her voice makes
me happy enough to cry.
[YUZU]
Get whatever you want, Mei.
I'll make it as soon
as I get home.
You want me to choose dinner?
If you insist.
Who cares what for,
I'm just glad she called me.
That was the first time ever!
[YUZU] Who knows what the
future holds for me and Mei?
Right now, all I want to
do is enjoy this feeling.
[YUZU]
I'd better head home and cook.
Let's go, Matsuri.
[MATSURI]
Fine.
I told you I'd pay for karaoke.
It's fine; it wasn't expensive.
Just promise me you'll
stop messing with perverts.
[YUZU]
I wouldn't want you to get into
a bad situation, you know?
Matsuri! What are you doing?
[MATSURI]
I can't take it.
[YUZU]
Take what?
[MATSURI]
Listen, Yuzu.
Forget her.
You're my big sister.
Whoa. What the heck
was that all about?
Well, I missed my
chance to do it earlier.
Are you crazy?
What if someone saw us?
[MATSURI]
So?
It doesn't matter to me
what other people think.
[YUZU]
So cute.
[MEI]
Yuzu.
Uh-huh?
[MEI]
That last test.
You came in at number 97.
[YUZU]
Huh?
[YUZU] Wait, did she just
initiate a conversation?
Awesome.
Now I don't have to worry
about Gramps hating me.
You're like amazing.
Thanks for your help.
[MEI]
Dinner was great.
Thanks for cooking.
Sure thing!
That's Mom's super-special
curry soup recipe.
I can teach you how to
make it too if you want!
[YUZU] Is this Mei's new
way of tormenting me?
Uh, so anyway--
[MEI] Tell me, why did
you come home late?
Right, sorry about that.
I ran into somebody I haven't
seen in a long time.
We used to be pretty close.
She was like a
sister to me then.
And like, she tries
to act all grown-up,
but anybody can see
she's still just a kid.
It makes you wanna
look out for her.
Hm?
What are you doing?
[YUZU] I thought we were
done with this stuff.
[YUZU]
Stop it!
Be careful, I almost
dropped the plate!
But we're sisters,
so this is normal, right?
[YUZU] I was pretty sure
we had decided it wasn't.
[HARUMI]
Yuzucchi!
I'm sorry I abandoned you!
What happened? You're
not injured, are you?
[YUZU]
Well, I am now!
Jeez. Why have you been
acting so weird, Harumin?
What? How am I the weird one?
That girl was gonna
eat you alive!
Matsuri?
Yeah, I guess she did kiss me,
but she didn't take it
any farther than that.
[HARUMI] My sweet innocent
Yuzucchi has been... tainted.
[YUZU]
Uh.
Matsuri's always been
the clingy type though,
even back when we
were little kids.
That stuff's not
really a big deal
when you're practically sisters.
[HARUMI]
Yeah?
Then how would you feel
if the student council prez
was putting the moves
on you every day?
That's crazy!
What makes you think she'd
do something like that?
Look, you're my friend.
I won't tell you to stop
talking to that girl.
I just think you'll
regret it if you don't.
Regret it?
[HARUMI] You're way too
nice for your own good.
Hm?
[MATSURI]
Oh! There you are!
Well, it's about time!
I've been looking
for you, Yuzu. Hi!
Matsuri, you're not
allowed to come here!
You're supposed to be
at your own school!
But I wanted to see you again,
so I decided to come visit.
What's wrong with that?
So, what do you say you
and me go on a date
once you're done with class?
Just the two of us.
What?
All right, fine. We'll
do whatever you want.
Just get out of here before
you get in trouble.
[MATSURI]
Yay!
[MEI]
You there!
[MEI] Who gave you
clearance to be on campus?
I can explain, Mei.
Aha.
It's nice to finally meet Yuzu's
new sister face to face.
I've just heard so much about
you. Let's be friends.
[YUZU] Uh, don't worry, Mei.
She was just leaving.
[MATSURI]
But we haven't decided
where we're going
on our date yet!
[YUZU]
We'll talk about that later!
Now please,
quit bothering everybody
and go to your school!
[MEI]
Yuzu.
Yes?
[MEI] It's against school
policy to make stops
on your way home.
I've told you that
multiple times now.
Yeah, I know! I won't!
I'm gonna go home and change
clothes first, I swear!
Trespassing on private
property is illegal.
If you have business
here, then get a pass.
[YUZU]
'Kay, Matsuri, time to go!
[MATSURI]
Yes.
Hello there? I'm a resident
of this neighborhood.
About that standing sign at
the entrance to the school?
Yes, that one.
I just saw someone
knock it over.
I know, it's a shame!
Anyway, I thought I should
probably report it to you.
Oh, no, no. No trouble at all!
[MATSURI]
A student council president
with a stick up her ass?
She's way too
boring for my taste.
[music playing]
[MATSURI] I'm not gonna
let someone like that
rub off on my big sister.
I have to protect her.
Seriously, I've loved
you for years now,
as long as I can remember.
[YUZU]
Matsuri, wait!
[MATSURI] Yuzu's my sister,
so leave her alone.
I don't want your
dirty hands on her.
Are you finished yet?
I've heard enough.
This is gonna be fun,
in like a weird way.