[HARUMI]
Whoa, what happened?
I'm right here for you
if you need to vent.
Uh.
It freaks me out when you get
all quiet on me like this, girl.
I'm your friend, so whatever
you need, I've got you!
Thanks, Harumin.
It's nice to know that
you have my back.
Either way, I gotta solve
this one on my own.
All right, now I'm
super confused,
but that doesn't matter.
Not as long as you feel better!
[YUZU]
So this is what love feels like.
[YUZU] Who cares about
status and reputation?
[YUZU] None of those
things matter to me.
[YUZU] It's more important
to be true to my feelings.
I'm done running away!
All right, we need to talk!
[CHAIRMAN grunting]
Grandfather!
[NURSE A]
Shh.
He's sleeping.
Let's not wake him.
[NURSE A]
Oh, I meant to tell you.
A darling blonde girl
about your age
brought him in here
earlier today.
She was a big help,
whoever she was.
Stayed right by his side until
everything settled on down.
Then she refused to go anywhere
until we promised to
contact his granddaughter.
He's very lucky that
girl was around.
Such a sweetheart.
Aw, man, it's late.
I'm back, Gramps.
Uh. I didn't know you
were here. I'll go.
[MEI]
Wait.
[YUZU] It's so hard to
look her in the eye.
But just standing here is weird.
What if our eyes meet
and I get so nervous
I say something stupid?
No, I have to.
I promised myself
I wouldn't run.
Hey, about earlier--
[MEI]
Mei.
Just call me "Mei."
It is my name.
You told the nurse to
call his granddaughter,
but you didn't give her a
specific name to contact.
I can only assume you haven't
been using my name
because you can't
remember what it is.
No, I...
[YUZU] I was just too shy
to say it... after that.
[MEI] We may be sisters, but it
doesn't feel like you're older
since we're in the same
grade, and you're... you.
Even so, I think
it's appropriate
to be on a first name basis.
Especially... since
we're a family.
[YUZU]
What'd she just say?
Come on. It's clear you
wanted me to touch you.
Listen, you.
[YUZU]
Now that I think about it,
she's never said my name either.
But maybe now...
Anyway, would you
please tell Mother
that there's no need to worry?
[YUZU]
She's trying to move forward!
Sounds good!
Well, I better head home.
Let's do this whole talking
thing again tomorrow!
Have a good night, Mei!
[YUZU chuckles]
[YUZU]
Hey, Mom, what's up?
Yep, I'm on my way home now.
Uh-huh, that's the
way it sounded.
She even said we were a family.
Oh, and also she said
for you not to worry.
Yeah! It's starting to feel
like we're officially sisters!
[UME]
You there? Yuzu?
[YUZU]
Sisters.
Hey! Over here!
[chuckles]
How's it goin', Mei?
[YUZU]
I've said her name twice now!
[MEI]
I'm going in.
Oh! Okay then, uh.
So... look, I know it might
not be the best time
to bring this up, but still.
There's something
I need to say.
[CHAIRMAN]
Ah, about your expulsion.
Before we get to that,
I'd like to express my thanks.
I apologize for troubling
you yesterday.
[YUZU] Don't sweat it!
That wasn't a big deal at all.
Anyone would've
done the same thing.
And besides, you're my gramps.
Family sticks together.
Everybody knows that.
[CHAIRMAN] There's still
a great deal to discuss,
but I'm revoking your expulsion.
You may attend school.
[YUZU gasps]
[CHAIRMAN] Mei spoke with
me about it the other day.
I was being too prideful
in so many ways.
As chairman and grandfather.
This hospitalization
has given me a chance
to reflect on my shortcomings.
[YUZU]
Wow, that's awesome.
She talked to him for me!
As for you, Mei, I want you
to make your own decisions.
You have to choose how
to live your life.
[MEI gasps]
But, Grandfather!
Am I clear?
Yes.
[YUZU]
Thanks for your help, Mei.
[MEI]
It was nothing.
[YUZU] So, um, you
should come back home!
What did Gramps tell you?
Do what makes you happy!
[YUZU]
I bet Mom would be so glad!
Come on. Please?
[MEI] With or without Father,
Mother's house is still my home.
I'd go back no matter
what you said.
[chuckles]
[YUZU]
And just like that,
I returned to my normal
everyday life at the academy.
Hey, girl! Oh!
I missed you!
Get off me, Harumin!
I can't breathe!
I was scared you were
expelled forever!
[YUZU gasps]
Jeez, keep it down.
I don't want the whole
world to know that!
I apologize if I
upset you, Mother.
[UME]
Mei!
Welcome home, dear.
[YUZU] I don't care if
she didn't come back
because of anything I said.
I'm just really
happy she's here.
What are you doing?
[YUZU]
Hm?
Your bear just needed
a little surgery.
Please don't touch
my belongings.
He looks rough.
Did you sew this up?
Maybe.
[YUZU]
I thought you'd be more, like...
What?
Oh, uh. Y'see...
So what's his name?
[MEI]
Name?
[YUZU]
Yeah, what do you call him?
"Hello there, Mei!
It's me, your good
pal Ansoniko!
Ansoniko loves you...
so very much!"
Here!
Okay, Ansoniko.
[HARUMI]
And my grandma was like--
[MEI]
You two.
[BOTH]
Hm?
[YUZU]
Oh! Mei!
[MEI] Why are you wandering
around in the hallway?
You should be in the classroom.
Really? Come on!
On our way!
Rude!
[YUZU] I still don't understand
why she's never called me
by my first name.
That's weird. Do big sisters
not get called by their name?
Huh? What'd you just say?
Uh, it's not important.
Harumin, I wanna get
closer to my sister.
Any ideas on what I should do?
You're trying to bond
with the ice queen?
Man, I wish I knew. Good luck.
Oh, is that why you've
been reading this thing?
[YUZU]
Don't judge me!
I know it's gonna take time,
but we should do our best to
get along, at the very least.
It's tough 'cause we have
totally different lives, y'know?
And we're polar opposites.
She just doesn't
get me like at all.
[YUZU]
Now that I think about it,
I don't really know all
that much about Mei.
What are you doing, perv?
So crazy! I never knew a
person could bend that way.
Hey! This is not what
I meant by getting closer!
[HARUMI]
Jeez, stop screaming!
It's not like I was actually
gonna do anything! Chill!
[YUZU]
Sorry I'm late!
[MEI] You're supposed
to come straight home.
Where were you?
[YUZU] Yeah. I was just
doing some research.
[UME] I wish you would've
come home sooner, Yuzu.
We really could've used your
help setting it up, you know.
Huh? What's "it"?
See? A double bed!
You always wanted a
nice big bed, right?
Plus, now you get
to have more space!
And since Mei's back, it's
like a welcome home present!
Isn't it great? Aw,
look you're speechless!
Sure is!
I'm gonna go grab a shower!
What? But dinner's almost
ready, dear. Wait till later.
[YUZU gasps]
[UME]
Yuzu, don't make a mess!
[YUZU]
Oh, no.
This is bad.
This is really bad!
[YUZU] Of course, bedtime was
here before I knew it.
I don't get how,
but Mei is surprisingly
calm about all of this.
[YUZU]
She's already asleep.
Meanwhile, my heart feels like
it's gonna beat out of my chest.
I hope she can't hear it.
[YUZU]
I can feel her body heat.
So close.
Her skin.
Her hair.
[YUZU]
I want to touch her.
What?
[YUZU gasps]
Uh. I was just, uh...
Well...
[YUZU]
What the heck is wrong me?
Mei?
I can't sleep. Especially
not under the same covers.
It's far too warm for that.
Much warmer than usual.
Oh. Yeah, I suppose it is
a little warm tonight.
Are you gonna go sleep
by yourself then?
[MEI]
Yes.
I can't get a good night's sleep
with the way you've been
tossing and turning all night.
Mei, tell me...
Why don't you call me
by my first name?
Is it because I'm older?
Does that make it weird?
If that's all--
[MEI]
Don't be absurd.
We use our names
around other people
because it's expected of us.
Our parents getting married
doesn't make us close.
We're sisters, but I have
no interest in you.
[YUZU] If that's true,
then why did you kiss me?
[YUZU] You can't go around
kissing people without a reason.
That's just not
normal, you know!
Well, you kept
running your mouth.
[gasps]
[MEI] And obviously, this was
the easiest way to shut you up.
You see?
I see... that you're terrible.
It would seem so.
Sweet dreams.
Stupid jerk.
[HARUMI] We make one
stop on the way home
and they force us to
clean the bathroom?
Now that you're living
with the prez,
we can't get away with anything.
I know, right? I'm really
sorry about this.
Don't even worry about it.
I'm just kiddin' around.
[YUZU groans]
[MEI] We're sisters,
but I have no interest in you.
And obviously, this was the
easiest way to shut you up.
It would seem so.
She's so mean! All
while looking sad, too!
It's not fair, Mei!
Don't you know this hurts me?
Be careful, Yuzucchi!
You're just making it dirtier!
[HARUMI]
Aw, it's okay.
[YUZU] This'd be way
easier if I hated her.
[HIMEKO]
Unbelievable!
How many of these slackers
didn't take their
textbooks home?
[MARUTA]
Vice President, look!
Disgusting.
The student body keeps
getting more and more sloppy!
I bet I know the reason.
It's all because of this
stupid rebellious bimbo!
[MEI]
That's enough for today.
What?
I can handle the rest of this.
You two should go on home.
President!
If that's really what
you'd prefer us to do.
[HIMEKO]
I hate that delinquent.
[MARUTA]
You mean Yuzu Aihara?
[HIMEKO] We have to address
her nasty behavior.
She shouldn't be allowed
to do whatever she wants.
I'm so beat!
You sure taught that
floor a lesson, though.
[HARUMI sighs]
Wanna go get ice cream?
We should totally stop
on the way home.
You are seriously hopeless.
[HARUMI] Well, I worked up a
sweat cleaning the bathroom.
If I don't go cool off,
I'll drop dead.
Even President Hardass
can overlook something
that small, can't she?
[YUZU]
Sorry, Harumin.
Uh, I forgot that I have plans,
but we can text later!
[YUZU] I can't believe
this is happening!
Mei's asking to see me!
Hey, slow down!
No running in the halls!
That was her.
Uh, hey!
It's polite to knock first.
Uh, sorry. And I'm sorry
about yesterday too!
I shouldn't have let my
temper get the best of me.
[MEI] I didn't call you here
to make you apologize.
So...?
[MEI] This book, it was found
amongst your belongings.
[YUZU]
The manga I bought yesterday!
I thought it was in my bag.
I don't know why you'd
want to read this smut,
but I can only imagine what
our mother would think.
It seems troubling,
seeing as we are sisters.
Luckily, I'm the only
one who's seen it.
That said, I don't want to be
the subject of any rumors.
Please dispose of it before--
[MEI]
What do you think you're doing?
Stop! We're at school!
This is all your fault, Mei!
You had to go and kiss me!
I-I'm confused!
I don't get this!
[YUZU]
Since that kiss,
Mei is the only thing
I can ever think about.
[YUZU]
There's no going back now.
I'm sorry I'm such a bad sister.
Look, I've been the
president's closest friend
ever since we
were both children.
[YUZU]
I'm just adding to Mei's pain.
[HIMEKO]
From day one,
I've watched over her
and protected her.
You're acting strange.
What's the matter?
[HIMEKO]
I want you to look at me.