[MANAMI] Oh, yeah, he was being
a pain, so I dumped him.
[KANA]
What? Already?
Weren't you guys still hooking
up just like a couple days ago?
[MANAMI] Eh, summer's the
season of love, right?
I'll get a rebound soon enough.
[YUZU sighs]
[YUZU]
God, I hate being single.
[MANAMI]
Wait, didn't you just break up
with your boyfriend, Yuzucchi?
I'd say come to the
mixer if you weren't
transferring in the fall,
but who'd want a
long distance thing?
[KANA]
Not me.
Ew. They're the worst.
Don't even worry
about me, ladies.
They'll be a new hot guy.
There always is, am I right?
[YUZU humming]
[YUZU] It's nice being able to
change in a room this big!
[laughs]
[humming]
[groans]
[YUZU humming]
[humming continues]
Hot!
I haven't learned any
of this stuff yet.
Whatever, high school
girls only need to know
fashion and friends!
Aw, thanks, Mom!
I'm heading out now!
[YUZU]
The summer of my freshman year,
my mom kinda up and found
herself a new husband.
Because of that, we had
to move to a new town,
meaning I had to
start life all over
at a totally different
high school.
[YUZU]
If I want to be at the top
of the social food chain here,
I've gotta crank my
cuteness up to 11!
[SCHOOLGIRL A]
Oh, hi, there you are.
[SCHOOLGIRL C]
Hey, wait for me!
[SCHOOLGIRL D]
What's up?
[YUZU]
Of course, it doesn't matter
how much I pump myself
up about it, anyway...
[YUZU] ...because my new
school is an all girls' school.
It's just gonna be
downhill from here.
I've kept up the
charade until now.
Yeah, after the mixer, we
totally went to second base!
What?
Wow!
[YUZU]
But the truth is...
...I've never been
in love before.
When I do get my first kiss...
I hope it's super hot,
like in a romance manga!
Not that I could ever admit it.
I'm beyond clueless about love.
[MARUTA]
Um. Please excuse me.
Okay.
I'm sorry to bother you,
but would you mind showing
me your student ID?
Huh? What for?
[MARUTA]
Your hair color is in violation
of our school's dress code.
[gasps]
Not only that, but cell phone
use is prohibited here,
so I'll have to confiscate
yours now, please.
[YUZU] No way! I literally
just transferred here.
You can't punish me
if I didn't know.
Let me slide?
[HIMEKO]
Sorry, we can't make exceptions.
That sets a bad example
for the other girls.
But isn't this perm
against the rules?
It's my natural hair, thank you!
Will you stop touching it?
[MARUTA]
Actually, there's more.
Your top button. Makeup as well.
Plus, that red ribbon.
Blouse, jewelry, false
nails, bag, skirt length.
In fact, your entire
appearance is a violation.
Huh?!
[YUZU]
What kind of crap high school
doesn't let their
girls look cute?
You're screwing up
the whole point!
[HARUMI]
Hmm...
[HIMEKO]
Back off!
This is so stupid!
It's not like how you dress
makes any difference
in your grades anyway!
[MEI]
It does, though.
[HIMEKO]
President!
[MEI] Our rules are
extremely important.
They prepare us not just for
school, but for the real world.
Every student at this
academy will be held
to the exact same standard.
If you have a problem with that,
perhaps you don't
belong at this school.
I'm just saying it's silly.
If you're gonna be sticklers
about your dress code,
you should at least let
people know what it is.
Well, Student Council President,
what do you have say about that?
Exactly. I figured as much.
[YUZU gasps]
[YUZU]
Hey! What are you doing?
[MEI] I expect this won't
happen again tomorrow.
[YUZU]
Whoa.
What the hell was that? No fair!
[groans]
[AMAMIYA]
Hey! Aihara!
No makeup? This blows.
What a creep.
She smelled really nice, though.
It's probably her shampoo.
[AMAMIYA]
Aihara!
Um, you calling me?
[AMAMIYA]
I am. Are you feeling okay?
[YUZU]
That's what I'm talkin' about!
[AMAMIYA]
Hm?
Oh, uh, nothing!
I'm just not quite used to my
new last name yet, that's all.
I'm Mr. Amamiya.
Now follow me.
It's time for homeroom.
Yes, sir!
[YUZU giggles]
Whoopsie!
[YUZU] This place has been
like boot camp so far.
That said, if all the
teachers are that cute,
I might just be okay!
[YUZU] First things first, I'm
gonna make some new friends!
[YUZU grunts]
There's no club today.
[SCHOOLGIRL F]
Oh?
[YUZU]
Hey there!
What are we doin', girls?
[SCHOOLGIRL E] Um, well, we were
thinking about maybe going to--
Oh, yeah! Karaoke sounds fun!
I don't have any
friends here yet,
so I'd totally be free
to tag along with you!
What time?
Don't make eye contact.
I'm scared to talk
to her, y'know?
[YUZU]
What's their problem?
[YUZU gasps]
[HARUMI]
'Scuse us a sec.
Listen, Aihara,
that's not how people
make friends here.
[YUZU]
Right. I'm sorry.
You are...?
[HARUMI]
I'm Harumi Taniguchi.
But just call me Harumin!
Uh. Harumin.
Anyway, what'd I do wrong?
[HARUMI] This school's part
of an escalator system,
so most of these
sheltered little flowers
have been classmates
since elementary.
I started here in
high school, though,
so I'm pretty much in
the same boat as you.
Kindred spirits!
Wow, I guess you are like me.
Point is, the girls at this
academy have been trained
to watch their Ps
and Qs since day one.
The chairman runs a
pretty tight ship.
In other words, it's
the only way they know.
[YUZU]
That makes sense.
[HARUMI] Of course,
there is one special case.
[YUZU]
Special case?
[HARUMI] The beautiful
brainiac who made president
during her first year
of high school.
I heard she's engaged to one
of the top teachers here, too.
She's engaged?
Isn't she a little young
for that, though?
No, not if you're the
chairman's granddaughter
who's supposed to inherit
the school one day.
Whoa.
[YUZU]
I bet she's never had a chance
to date or fall in love, either.
[HARUMI]
Anyway, you're up to speed.
I'm gonna go ahead and
assume we're friends.
So what's your contact info?
A cell phone! They
confiscated mine. No fair.
They can't take it away
if they don't know it's there!
Let's see, if the
student council
hasn't given it
back to you yet...
...I'd say it probably
ended up in Mineko's room.
[YUZU]
Who?
[MINEKO] A lady must
always conduct herself
with the utmost
sophistication and poise,
not only at school,
but in the home as well.
Do I make myself
clear, Miss Aihada?
[YUZU]
Yes.
What on earth would possess you
to parade around our
prestigious academy
dressed in that shameful manner?
When I was your age,
I would've been embarrassed
at the very idea of
being seen in public
with my uniform in such
a state of disarray!
Honestly, how could
any respectable person
expect to be taken seriously
with that ridiculous hair color?
And let's not forget
about that phone, too!
Hm?
You're ignoring me,
aren't you, dear?
[YUZU]
Sorry.
Respect for rules and order
is one of the cornerstones
upon which this proud
establishment was built,
and if you think our
distinguished faculty...
[YUZU]
That was brutal.
Hope I never get old and lame.
[sighs]
At least I got my phone back!
[YUZU]
Hm?
Huh?
Oh, look! It's Mr. Hot Teacher!
I'm gonna get his contact info.
[YUZU chuckles]
[YUZU]
Mr. Amamiya!
[gasps]
[YUZU]
Tell me I'm not seeing this!
[gasps]
[YUZU]
I don't believe it!
The president and
Mr. Amamiya?
[YUZU]
Plus...
She totally knows I saw them!
[HARUMI]
Uh?
What's up, Yuzucchi?
Did you get your--?
Mineko must've torn
her a new one.
What a day.
That was so crazy.
[YUZU]
I'm home.
Well, that's kinda weird.
[UME]
Yuzu!
What took you so long, sweetie?
I've been waiting forever.
[YUZU]
Sorry. Something came up.
[UME] You promised you would
help me clean up after the move.
Yeah, I know. I will.
So, do I finally get to
meet my new dad tonight?
Oh, about that.
He sort of had to leave for
the other side of the world.
[YUZU]
Huh?
He won't be back
home for a while.
That's too bad.
I was looking forward to
seeing what kind of creeper
you're bringing into the house.
I mean, you do have a
history of dating weirdoes.
[UME]
Hm?
[YUZU]
This is a lot.
[UME]
Is it?
Well, growing girls need
plenty of nourishment, right?
[YUZU]
Hey, Mom?
[UME]
Hm?
[YUZU] Be honest with
me. Are you happy?
Oh, yes. Very much so.
[YUZU] Okay. If you're
happy, then I'm happy.
Of course I'm happy.
[UME]
Why wouldn't I be, sweetie?
After all, I've got my two
beautiful girls here with me.
[YUZU]
What? Two?
[UME] Oh? Did I forget
to mention that?
Surprise! You get to
have a new sister!
[MEI]
I'm home.
[YUZU gasps]
[YUZU yelps]
Why are you in my house?
Because I live here.
My name's Mei Aihara.
I'm Shou's daughter.
It's so nice to
meet you, Mother.
Oh, hell no! That's
my mom, not yours!
Aw, there's no need to be
so formal with me, honey!
We're a family now, remember?
[gasping]
[UME]
Be nice to your sister, Yuzu.
Have you been doing council
work all afternoon?
[MEI]
Yes, I'm always busy.
[UME]
What a hard worker!
You must be starving!
Well, we went all out to cook
you something delicious, Mei!
You're too kind.
[UME] Yuzu's birthday is first,
so she's the big sister.
That means you're the baby, Mei!
[MEI]
Okay.
You must be glad to have such a
cute little sister, right, Yuzu?
[YUZU]
Uhh...
[YUZU] Yeah, her death
glare's real cute.
[UME]
Aww.
And so shy. Isn't that adorable?
[YUZU]
Trust me, she is not adorable!
[chuckles]
[YUZU]
Ugh, I cannot deal with this!
[UME]
Yuzu, stop eating so fast.
Hey! I'm a growing girl!
[UME]
Well, that was awkward.
Sorry, Mei. Poor thing.
[MEI]
It's fine.
Anyway, remind me:
You were living with
your grandfather
before now, weren't you?
[MEI] No. I've been staying
in my father's house.
[UME] Really? But your
dad's always traveling.
You must have been by
yourself for a while.
[YUZU]
Hm?
[MEI] I haven't really seen my
father in almost five years.
[UME gasps]
[UME] Has it been hard
living alone at your age?
[MEI]
Not so much. My grandfather's...
[YUZU] So she's been living
by herself this whole time?
I bet she was lonely.
[UME]
Ah.
Yes, of course,
your grandfather is also the
chairman of your high school.
He's the one who owns that big
famous mansion over by Rikugien.
[MEI] I don't visit
his estate very often,
so I know very
little about it...
[YUZU] Wait, if she's
seriously my sister,
that makes me the chairman's
granddaughter, too!
Sweet, I always wanted
to be filthy rich!
[YUZU grunts]
[MEI]
Idiot.
[sighs]
I'm so tired.
[YUZU] How could Mom just
spring this whole thing on me?
And how could that girl act
so normal at the dinner table...
...after what I saw?
[YUZU] Sure was an interesting
face she was making.
Does kissing really
feel that special?
[gasps]
[YUZU] Wait! Why am I playing
it over and over in my head?
[YUZU]
Jeez, what's the matter with me?
Hey, the bathroom's free now.
[YUZU]
Aw!
That's a cute bear.
So, do you like--? Oh.
Okay, look, I know you and
I didn't exactly get off
on the right foot earlier.
But now we're stepsisters,
so we're gonna have
to get along somehow.
Or at least try, right?
We'll fake it if we have to.
[YUZU]
She's ignoring me?
All right then,
Little Miss Perfect,
if that's how you wanna play...
[YUZU]
So...
You made out with the
teacher today, huh?
You'd think there'd be a rule
against student
teacher hookups, too.
I totally get it.
You make out with
him in the open
because knowing you might get
caught makes it even hotter.
Now, if you ask me, I'd bet
that kiss was your first.
So, what was it like, anyway?
I always pictured it
to be really magical,
like confessing your feelings
without saying a wor--
[MEI]
It felt like that.
Magical enough for you?
What the--?
[YUZU] I've dreamed about
my first kiss for so long...
[YUZU]
What is wrong with her?
[YUZU] And it was just stolen
from me... by my own sister!
[YUZU]
She had to go and kiss me.
[MEI] A child who's never
been kissed before
shouldn't act like she has.
[YUZU
Because of me, she's...
[MEI] I just wanna know
if you're gonna rescue me
from my mean
grandfather's house.