Uh, I dunno, Mei. This is
kind of out of nowhere.
I need to show you my
gratitude for all you've done.
Those complicated feelings I had
about my father and grandfather.
You forced your way in and
helped me work through them.
So now, let's do
what you want to do.
I think I know what that is.
You mean...?
This'll make you happy, right?
[gasps]
Are you sure?
Yes.
[YUZU]
Sorry. I can't do this.
[gasps]
Have a good night.
[sighs]
[doorbell rings]
[YUZU]
Hello?
Meow!
Oh, Matsuri.
[MATSURI]
Good morning!
I came to say Happy New Year.
See? I brought candy.
[YUZU] But Thousand-Year Candy's
for a totally different holiday.
Plus, it's the end of January.
So, uh, where's Mei?
I don't honestly know.
But she's probably
planning the school trip
with the student council.
[MATSURI]
Aww, man, I was hoping
I could talk President Brainiac
into helping me study today.
Next time.
Sorry, I guess you should've
asked her if she was free
before you came over.
So, how did your
Christmas go, Yuzu?
Did you and Mei bang?
I wanna hear about
all the dirty details!
What? Why do you think
we would we do that?
[MATSURI] Are you guys
fighting or something?
[sighs]
[MATSURI] Ya know, you can
be pretty immature at times.
[YUZU]
Huh?
[MATSURI]
We live in the real world,
so love doesn't always
work out the way it does
in fairy tales and silly manga.
[gasps]
Ooh. Well, well,
what have we here?
I think I just found
your secret stash!
Come to Mama!
[YUZU groans]
Here's the thing.
If you like someone, then you
have to consider their feelings.
Their feelings? Yeah.
That's a good point.
[MATSURI]
Hm?
[YUZU]
Nothing. Forget it.
There.
Have a good night, Mei.
Sweet dreams.
[SARA] Perfect! Looks like
everybody got here on time!
The station's really
packed today, too!
It's a wonder we
made it this far.
Thanks to you, we were almost
late getting over here.
I already told you, Sara.
Tokyo's just as good
as Kyoto to me
as long as I get to hang out
with my favorite big sister.
Not to me, it's not!
I've been looking forward
to going on a school trip
for like, forever,
and you know that!
[SARA sighs]
[SARA]
Anyway...
What a nice person.
I'm so glad we met!
Wow, that must've
meant a lot to you!
I never imagined I would run
into someone so kind and helpful
in a big city like Tokyo!
Today might be the luckiest
day of my entire life so far!
I mean, getting lost like that
had to have been destiny!
Jeez, there you go rambling
on about destiny again.
[SARA]
Hey, Nina?
You bought that
Yuzubocchi, right?
Uhh... Nope. Guess I forgot.
[SARA gasps]
Didn't you tell me that was
a Tokyo-exclusive item
that you could only get today?
Yeah, but it's no biggie.
We don't have time to
go back and get it.
Come on, Nina!
It was your lucky color
and everything!
I'm okay.
Who cares what color it was?
You're all the good luck I need.
[SARA]
But you want one!
I'll go get it.
Stay right there!
[NINA]
Hey!
Don't worry. I'm not gonna
miss the train, 'kay?
[NINA sighs]
[NINA] That's my sister
for you. Oh, well.
[YUZU]
Crap.
Crap, crap, crap, crap,
crap, double crap!
"Crap" doesn't even
begin to describe it!
If I'm late for the school trip,
I'll be in huge trouble!
I'm on the way, Harumin!
[HARUMI] Where the heck
are you, Yuzucchi?
[YUZU]
Just now leaving my house!
Seriously?
[YUZU]
What about Mei?
I'm guessing she's already
there, right? Have you seen her?
[HARUMI]
Duh, like she'd be late.
Please, as we travel today,
remember that you ladies...
You better step on it,
they're about to call the roll!
[YUZU]
If I don't get there in time,
could you let Mei and
the teachers know
I'll catch up later?
[HARUMI] Sure, I'll tell them,
but they're not gonna like it.
Why'd I hafta oversleep today?
[YUZU] Jeez, Mei could've at
least said something to me
before she left!
[YUZU] Things have been weird
between us since Christmas.
[YUZU] Maybe she really
is done with me.
[sighs]
[YUZU]
Missed it. Of course.
[BOY A] Mommy, can we please
get one of these cakes?
[YUZU]
Great, now I'm all sweaty.
[YUZUBOCCHI] The secret
ingredient is yuzu-fruit...
[YUZU]
Yuzubocchi!
Bye-bye!
That's crazy! This store
uses mascot characters?
[SARA chuckles]
[SARA]
They do today. See?
We're at a limited-time
Tokyo-exclusive pop-up event!
Cool!
Check out this
awesome phone strap.
You can only pick
them up in here!
Aw, it's adorable!
Yeah, I know, right?
I'm out on a school trip!
We're supposed to meet up
at the gate at ten o'clock!
[YUZU]
Huh?
I'm gonna head over
in a few minutes.
You do know it's 10:15 now.
[SARA]
Whew!
I can't believe we're heading
in the same direction!
Talk about a moment of destiny!
This way I won't get
lost on the way there!
You are such a generous
person, Miss Yuzu!
Thank goodness Yuzubocchi
brought us together!
Thanks, but you don't have
to call me "Miss Yuzu."
We're the same age, aren't we?
'Kay, then you can call me Sara.
It's nice to make a new friend.
I know things haven't quite
gone according to plan so far,
but today's turning
out to be great.
[YUZU]
Hm.
Did something else
bad happen to you?
My sis and I got
lost back in Tokyo.
It was scary!
But then we met the
most wonderful person!
Wait, you never told
me your sister
was supposed to
be with you, too!
[SARA]
Oh.
That's the part that got you?
Yeah, we're twins, but she's
technically the youngest one.
She's totally gorgeous
and is like,
way better in school than me.
She can be pretty
selfish sometimes,
but I guess she's a
decent enough sister.
Doesn't sound like you
guys are very close.
It's not like I have a
problem with her or anything.
But she goes to my school,
and we're in the same class,
which means that people are
always comparing me to her,
and I hate that.
Yeah, I getcha.
[YUZU]
Sounds like my little sister.
But that wasn't the
point of my story!
I wanted to tell you about the
amazing girl I met earlier--
Wait, so a girl was
your wonderful person?
Uh. Gosh, Yuzu.
Maybe if you would quit
interrupting me, you'd find out.
[YUZU chuckles]
I'm sorry.
I do wanna hear about this girl.
It's just that, from the
way you explained it,
I could've sworn you
were talking about a guy.
I don't see why it
surprises you that much.
It's not all that complicated.
Whenever I find somebody
I have feelings for,
it doesn't matter
what their gender is.
This time, the person I like
just happens to be a girl.
Oh.
Well, "happens" is the
wrong word. It was fate!
[YUZU] She says it like it's
the simplest thing in the world.
I wish I had remembered to
ask for her name, though.
Because now I have no way
of ever finding her again.
[SARA] But hey, if it's meant
to be, it'll work out.
[YUZU] Why was it my fate
to fall in love with Mei?
[phone buzzing]
What's up, Yuzu?
Are you almost here?
[YUZU]
I just got off at Kyoto Station.
Send me the address and I'll
be there as soon as I can.
[HARUMI] Sounds good.
I'll keep an eye out for you.
Um.
[HARUMI]
Hm?
Did Mei mention me at all?
Does she seem worried?
[HARUMI]
Hm?
[HARUMI] Sorry. She's totally
silent, as per usual.
Why?
[YUZU]
No reason. I'll see ya soon.
I found out where I'm going.
Good! We should compare.
That's perfect, it'll be
like our own private trip!
[BOTH chuckle]
They're still so far
ahead of us!
Yeah.
[SARA]
Hm?
It's okay.
There's no point in getting
all stressed out.
Yeah, but--
Come on, I'm sure we'll
catch up to them soon.
If there's something
else on your mind,
feel free to tell me about it.
[YUZU]
Hm?
This time, the person I like
just happens to be a girl!
Well, actually, it might
be the kind of thing
you can help me out with.
What's up?
'Kay, I'm just gonna say it.
See, I kinda have
a crush on this girl.
Problem is, she's
also my stepsister.
It took me a long time, but
I finally got close to her.
And then on Christmas,
our relationship hit a snag.
It got awkward,
and we've hardly spoken
to each other since.
[MEI] So now, I think I know
what it is you want from me.
I was so happy she opened up.
In the moment, I must've
let my mind go blank.
[YUZU]
The things I want to do...
Things I've always wanted
to do with Mei...
[YUZU]
I just...
[YUZU] I love Mei,
so I should be with her.
[YUZU]
I got scared!
It'll be all right,
Yuzu. Cheer up.
Sounds to me like you were
just having an off day
when all that went down.
Even though we just
met this morning,
I can already tell you're
a really loving person.
And if it's clear to me,
then I promise you that
girl can see it too.
Sara.
We crossed paths for a reason.
There's no doubt in my mind.
Whatever happens,
I'll be rooting for you.
You're so sweet. Thank you.
How 'bout that?
We're in the same hotel.
[SARA] You know I'm all
about fate and everything,
but this many coincidences in
a row is downright creepy.
[NINA]
Sara!
Hey!
Ah!
Yay! Thank goodness
you got here safely!
I told you not to worry
when I called you!
We're in high school, remember?
Huh? Uh.
You're twins?
Stand up, Nina! Say hi to Yuzu!
We're BFFs now.
It's nice to meet you.
Hey, Yuzu!
[YUZU]
So tall!
[YUZU] I should probably try
to find my classmates now.
[SARA] You're gonna be
here a few days, right?
We should hang out again!
[YUZU]
Yeah! I'll see you around!
[SARA chuckles]
[NINA]
Hm?
[gasps]
[NINA]
Hey, Sara, is that her?
Huh? Is who her?
[SARA gasps]
It's the girl I met earlier!
Uh, hey! Wait up!
Excuse me!
You two again?
From the train station.
[SARA]
Yes!
My name is Sara Tachibana!
And this is my
little sister, Nina!
Please don't think
I'm a weirdo, but...
Would you tell me
what your name is?
[SARA] Our school is staying
at this hotel too, Mei.
I'm sure we'll get
more chances to talk!
How nice.
[HIMEKO]
I've had it with you!
It's called a group
activity for a reason.
You have to stay with the group!
[YUZU]
Mei.
Sounds to me like you were
just having an off day
when all that went down.
Are you listening to me?
Sorry, but I gotta go.
I need to take
care of something,
and I can't put it
off any longer.
Hold on a minute!
Don't you run from me!
[YUZU]
Mei, wait!
Do you think I could maybe
have a word with you alone?
[HIMEKO]
Yuzu Aihara!
Come.
Catch you later, okay?
[SARA sighs]
[SARA] Coulda done
without that lecture.
I don't understand why
I had to get yelled at
when you were the one who
went off on your own.
Well, nobody forced you
to go into the meeting
room, Nina, gah.
Why do you follow me
everywhere I go?
Uh-oh. Did I lose it?
What is it now?
I can't find the Tokyo-exclusive
Yuzubocchi strap
you bought for me!
Where did it go?
[SARA sighs]
Jeez, Nina, that thing
was the whole reason
we got in trouble
in the first place.
[crying]
--I'm so sorry, Sara!
--[SARA] Oh, come on, don't cry!
I'm gonna go find it right now!
What?
Wait, don't! It's
almost dinner time!
[YUZU]
It's cold here, huh?
[MEI]
Yes.
Hey, Mei, why didn't you
wake me up this morning?
We always walk to
school together,
so I thought you would.
I don't see how it's my fault
you didn't leave the
house on time today.
It's not my job to wake you up.
That's not what I
was trying to say.
So, is that why you
wanted to talk?
No, actually, it's
about Christmas.
You know, when we were
on the couch together?
I was really happy when you
expressed your feelings to me.
But, um... you and I are
still sisters, Mei,
so I felt like we
were starting to get
a little too physical
with each other.
Then, I have a question.
[gasps]
I want to know your true
feelings about me, Yuzu,
and please tell me honestly.
[NINA whines]
[NINA]
I hope I can find it.
Huh?
There it is!
I was about to give up!
[YUZU]
I don't know.
That's a tough question.
You kind of caught me off guard,
so it's hard to answer that.
Um, how do I say it?
If I'm being honest...
I, uh, love you.
[gasps]
Because we're stepsisters.
So I'm saying you
mean a lot to me
since you're part
of my family now.
Does that make sense?
Apologies.
[gasps]
What happened before,
please forget the entire thing.
If you have a shot, you
should go for it. Just try.
[SARA]
I saw my angel of destiny again!
[YUZU] I keep spouting
off these empty words
that don't mean anything.
Just tell me whether
or not you need me.
[YUZU] Right! No one loves
Mei more than I do!