You sure do have a lot...
A lot of what?
Books.
Oh.
We may not look it
on the outside, but...
People in our profession tend
to read books all the time.
It's my experience that
uneducated people...
tend to make very poor soldiers.
What kind of books
do you like to read?
Your file says that
before coming here,
your favorite thing to do--
No... never mind.
I'll read every book I
can get my hands on...
If that's what it takes
to make me a good soldier.
I put the bait on for you.
Now just cast the line
underhand like I showed you.
Now, we just sit and
wait for the fish.
Well if that's the case,
then you can definitely
count on me to act as
your legs from now on, sir.
But why did you keep these?
I want you to remember...
Always think clearly
before pulling the trigger.
I want you to be gentle, Claes,
whenever you put
those glasses on.
Now don't think of
this as an order...
It's a heart to heart promise.
Well, good morning, Triela.
Yeah, good morning...
How are you Claes?
I wish I had a mesosiderite.
I thought of it while I was
looking at the sky yesterday...
Probably because I've
been reading this book
about minerals recently.
You've got a real romantic
streak, you know that...
Let's go to the dining hall.
So are you going to the
training grounds again today?
Yeah... I'll be there
at least until dark.
You don't seem very happy.
I just have a lot
weighing on my mind...
But it's my problem.
Anyway, what are
you doing today?
The same things as every day.
Hey, Rico...
Yeah, what?
I'm sorry I yelled at
you the other day...
I know you didn't
mean to break it...
And the kaleidoscope is
fixed now, better than new.
So, Henrietta...
You're not mad at me anymore?
No.
That means a lot... Thank you.
You can stay by
my side again okay?
You should have
Jean buy you one.
What?
A mesosiderite.
Oh... Uh, no. That's okay.
Well, why wouldn't you?
It's not the kind
of thing you can
run out to the store and buy.
So what is it you're
trying to buy, Claes?
Oh, it's not that important.
You're... just eating
yogurt for breakfast?
Yes.
Are you not hungry or something?
This is all of the food
I am allowed to eat today...
I'm going to take my time,
so don't worry about me.
Huh...? The food...
It's already been taken away.
It's not long until lunch.
You'll be fine.
Look, Beatrice...
I have some cookies in my
room if you'd like a snack.
But... you'll have to
do some work for me.
Hey, what is all this?
Like vegetables.
So, they're weeds
that... you eat?
They're herbs.
Parsley, sage, rosemary...
Haven't you ever heard of
the song "Scarborough Fair"?
I don't think so.
Hello, Dr. Bergonzi.
How you doing Claes...?
Thanks for helping
us again today.
We're ah, going to do some
color dopplers of your heart.
Okay.
You seem like you're
exhausted, Doctor.
I suppose I've looked better.
There's an academic convention
next month; I'm preparing for.
It's the European
Cardiovascular Conference.
Thanks to you I can write
a pretty damn good paper.
I really appreciate your help.
You don't have to thank me.
It is my job, doctor.
Doctor Bergonzi...
Do you happen to know the
song... "Scarborough Fair"?
It's a classic.
Strange and thought-provoking
at the same time.
"Tell her to find me
an acre of land...
'tween the salt water
and the sea strand..."
"Will you plough it
with a lamb's-horn..."
"And sow it all over
with one peppercorn..."
"And then you shall be...
a true-love of mine."
What do you suppose that means?
How's the testing coming
along? Any trouble?
No, thanks.
What about your day to
day life? How's that?
If you need anything,
you just let me know.
I will... But I'm
fine, really...
I can tend to my
vegetable garden when I want...
I can wander around
the campus at my leisure...
and I can play the piano.
Each day of my life
is full and complete.
Claes, about that piano...
It's always been here.
Long before the agency
was even formed.
That's very interesting.
A thousand years ago
the only thing out here
was a monestary
surrounded by fields...
It wasn't until
after their time
that an aristocrat bought
the land and built a villa.
The government started
using it at the start
of the 20th century. Now it's
our agency's main facility.
How neat...
I'm growing herbs on land
cultivated by monks...
around one thousand years ago...
Pretty much.
Claes, what's wrong?
We're finished here.
A question.
Have you ever been
tremendously sad...
but the tears won't come out?
Sure... It happens.
That's how I feel right now.
My heart is overflowing
with tears...
but they just won't
come out of my eyes.
At night when I'm asleep...
they quietly spill out onto
the pillow without my noticing.
I feel like I've
been here before...
Hey... C'm'ere.
Cyborgs need to be
with their Handlers
at all times in order to
use the shooting range.
I know... I just came to
look around for a bit...
Wait... Aren't you
Captain Raballo's girl?
Um...
Yeah, you used to come
here all the time...
always with that same
GIS baseball cap on.
And you fired a VP.
You looked a lot
different back then.
I guess I didn't recognize you.
That was really nice, Henrietta.
Now, how many shots
do you have left?
I have three.
Good at keeping track.
Hi, Claes!
Hello...
What are you doing here, Claes?
I was just passing by.
So I thought I'd stop
in and look around.
Henrietta.
Yes, sir?
I need you to remove the
magazine and empty the chamber.
Let's call it a day, alright?
Of course, Jose... I'll do it.
I didn't mean to
interrupt your training.
You didn't.
Don't worry about it.
Just make sure you stay on this
side of the white line, okay?
Yes, sir.
I'm not sure why, but this
is such a familiar aroma...
Hey there, Claes!
What are you doing way
out here by yourself?
I'm not sure.
It's getting late.
You going to the dorms?
Yes.
Hop on. I can give you a ride.
It's a longer walk back
than you might think.
Angelica can sit in front,
and you can sit in the back...
Why don't you hop off
and climb around.
Okay, sure thing, Priscilla.
I get to ride with the two
prettiest girls around here!
Will you plough it,
with a lamb's-horn...
And sow it all over
with one peppercorn...
And then you shall be
a true love of mine.
Ask him to reap it with
a sickle of leather...
and gather it up with
a rope made of heather...
For then he'll be
a true love of mine.
If you say that you can't,
then I shall reply...
Parsley, sage,
rosemary, and thyme...
Oh, let me know that
at least you will try...
I'm finally home.
Welcome back.
So what did you spend
your day doing?
It was the same as every day...
I cultivated some herbs in my
garden, and played the piano...
Sounds like fun.
Claes, tell me that's
not gunpowder I smell
coming off you.
Are you sure that you're not
smelling your hands instead?
Yeah, you're right!
I'm beat. Good night, Claes.
Good night.
So what do you do when these
actually grow into big plants?
I really haven't
thought much about it...
Maybe I'll use them
for an herbal bath
or something like that.
What's that?
Honestly, I don't know...
I think it could be
some kind of mineral.
Fascinating.
Beatrice...
Have you ever heard of
a rock called mesosiderite?
Na-uh...
They're basically asteroids
that fell to Earth long ago...
And they still hang around
the corners of the planet
just waiting to be noticed.
Don't you think
that's enchanting?
Is this fun for you?
Doing the same thing every day?
Yeah... Is that so weird?
I don't know...
I've never really known what
'fun' is supposed to be like...
It doesn't matter if I'm in
the dorms or if I'm out at work,
I don't think that I've ever
felt moved to a smile.
Maybe you can tell me why it is
you know how to enjoy yourself.
I don't know...
I suppose that someone must have
taught me how a long time ago.