So... Have you picked out
your souvenir for Henrietta?
Not yet... I don't
know what to get.
She loves anything I give her
so that makes it tough...
You've got it easy. All you have
to buy are stuffed animals.
You don't get it, pal...
Triela researches
her gifts for me.
I can't just pick out
whatever I want...
She hates it when I find
something off the list.
So, of course, I got her
what she wanted again.
A Steiff Bear.
She wanted a German
bear from France?
Uh, Pardon me, sirs.
I take it both of
you are from Italy.
Yeah... Just a weekend
business trip...
The train back home
leaves in an hour.
Well, if it's a French
souvenir you seek,
I am most certainly your man.
That's great,
I could use some help.
I do hope that the gift is
for this girl Henrietta...
Because I believe I have
just the thing for her.
It has the most
wonderful story behind it.
I heard you're going
to the Balkans.
Is that true, Jose?
I'll be back before
you know it...
It'll only be six months.
But no! They say the radiation
is too dangerous...
Don't worry.
Your other brother will be
here to keep you company.
Jean never comes to my recitals,
but you're always there.
That's right, Jean.
The meeting with
the French Minister
of the Interior ended well.
Couldn't have gone better.
We're on the TGV
now heading back.
There's going to be a massive
demonstration in Rome tomorrow.
I need you two
back here in time.
Understood.
Okay! I'll see you later!
Jose, confirm the activists do
not appear to be making a move.
No... They're not doing
anything, brother.
This is my brother.
That's how I know him,
even though we're
not really siblings.
We're always together
during our missions,
so we're known as 'fratello.'
It means 'siblings'...
"Brother and sister."
We're close, but not
close enough to touch.
That's how great the distance
is between Jose and me.
I'd like more than anything to
be closer to him than this.
Rico--
Stay on the sidewalk.
Henrietta.
Is there something wrong?
No... everything's fine, Jose.
Got it...
Sir, we have a violent clash in
progress between the protestors
and the riot squad
at the Coliseum.
This is it, people...
They'll use this moment of
vulnerability as their chance
to make a strike
during the chaos...
Are all of the fratellos
on their marks?
Yeah, just about.
The Jean-Rico and
Jose-Henrietta teams
are heading north from
Circo Massimo Station...
Hilshire-Triela
team is on lookout
at the Memorial Observatory.
The other members are
on plain-clothes patrol,
looking out for
anyone suspicious.
Contact all of the Handlers...
Tell them that finding the
F.R.F. terrorists is priority.
Jose...
We're going back to the
chief's van for a few minutes...
Stay here and try to keep
an eye on the perimeter.
Got it.
So is it them...?
The Five Republics Faction?
No, these are all just
ordinary citizens...
Rome's got its
pro-indepencence supporters--
Jose, you're not
injured are you?
Blood.
It's only a scratch...
Now put your eye
back on the perimeter.
Look!
Let's go!
Priscilla!
Jose, I heard the explosion.
Everyone okay? What happened?
Padania terrorists...
I need your bike.
It's yours. Take it.
Get on, Henrietta.
Right.
Great.
My poor Vespa...
I sure hope I get it back.
I did it... Killed ten
of those bastards...
And all thanks to this.
These bombs are incredible.
Now we can get close
without those police dogs
sniffing them out...
When we get the chance,
we'll blow two or three
more of these suckers.
What in the--
I think we got a tail.
That yellow scooter.
It's been riding our
ass for way too long.
Not now... There's way
too much traffic here...
We cause a scene and the cops
will be on us in no time.
The passenger has a
Beretta Submachine gun.
Don't fire yet.
Jose, do you read me?
You're heading into the
administrative district.
That's where we'll corner
the target once you get there.
Rico and I are on the way.
Rico. We're going to
get up ahead of them...
Then, you take 'em.
I won't miss a shot...
Do I kill them?
You don't...
We need someone
to interrogate...
Just make them hurt a lot.
Right.
Shit!
Yeah, I think this will work.
Lead their car down this narrow
alleyway and then pick them off.
It's perfect.
We can set the trap right here.
Right... Good idea. Get it done.
You all right back there?
Hold on, okay?
Okay... Don't worry about me...
Dammit!
Did I do good?
You did. That'll work just fine.
And stay there...
This is the most rest
you'll get for a while.
Several years ago, the Italian
Prime Minister founded
the Social Welfare Agency,
a public interest organization
designed to perform
charity work.
The truth is, it's an
intelligence agency
established to covertly remove
those who oppose the government.
Triela... You're
not hit are you?
At the agency, Special Ops
Section 2 finds subjects
from around the country,
each on the verge of death.
We bring them back,
give them mechanical bodies,
and send them out
on dangerous missions.
Using what's
calling conditioning,
memories of their previous lives
are wiped from the minds
of these young girls.
They're re-engineered
to obey the orders
of their partners
and the agency.
And while they've been given
powerful enough
bodies to survive,
they've had to trade in their
connection to their pasts...
Along with every
ounce of free will.
These cyborgs can wipe
out a life without fear,
without regret,
without remorse,
and without a
moment's hesitation...
"Today, I killed
an enemy for Jose."
"I'm sad that I
couldn't have been
more helpful with
the situation...
But it did make me happy
when he held me on the scooter.
I felt so safe."
The end.
Hey, Jose...
It's me, Henrietta.
It smells like
cigarettes in here.
I didn't know that Jose smokes.
I wonder if that's the souvenir
he brought me back from France.
A golden kaleidoscope...
It's written in French.
"For my beloved.
Louise Antoinette Rolle"?
Sorry. I wasn't looking.
Henrietta...?.
So it's a kaleidoscope
wrapped like a present,
but it's addressed
to some woman...
I don't know...
Wait... No need to get upset...
Now what was that name again?
The one inscribed on the bottom.
Um, it, was Louise
Antionette Rolle.
I should just accept the fact
that it really is
his girlfriend.
I don't think so...
Not unless his girlfriend
died in the 19th century.
Huh?
Of course it could be
someone with the same name.
But the name is that
of a married woman
once doted upon by
a great French writer.
One of this writer's
most well-known
and loved stories is based
upon himself and Mrs. Rolle...
And he just so happened
to name the heroine
in that novel Henrietta.
Oh.
That means--
That means that
the kaleioscope was
a gift for you from
the beginning...
And actually a rather clever
one at that, I might add...
'Night.
Uh... Well... I...
I'm sorry... uh... I was...
Uranus rotates horizontally,
almost along the same
path as its orbit,
which gives us an
interesting perspective.
It looks a lot like a target...
Rings circling the outside while
the planet hovers in the middle.
I shouldn't forget the moons.
It's got 27.
Some are referred to
as shepherd moons.
I bet you can't guess why
they're called that...
Hey uh... Claes?
What?
I'm trying to sleep, you know.
Did that lovey/dovey
French novel
you mentioned earlier
have a happy ending?
No.
Then wouldn't it be bad luck
to get a present like that?
She'll be okay...
It's probably a fake, anyway...
After all, the kaleidoscope
was invented
right around that same time,
maybe even later.
That's good, I guess.
Besides...
when love fails in
a story like that,
it's because it was never
true love to begin with.
Have I answered all of your
questions for tonight Triela?
Yes, Miss Cleas.