That's the survey bridge...
Jose! Look!
It's odd that there's
no security over here.
Where did you station Pinocchio?
Up above, so he can
keep an eye on the land.
How much longer?
We need about 15 more minutes
to set all of the charges.
There's the security!
Franco... Let's take the
boat and get outta here!
We're not done.
They'll be on top
of us any minute!
Besides... With what
we've planted...
it might be enough
to destroy it!
Jose, come in...
I've found the enemy.
I'll be right there, Henrietta!
Just slow them down!
Right.
Stay on the ground!
We're getting out of here!
No!
Henrietta!
I'm here, Jose.
C'mon, we gotta move!
Will you be alright?
How's your gunshot wound?
It's better...
Now that the painkillers
have started kicking in.
I'm sorry... I'm sorry, Franco.
Nah...
It's all because I
hesitated to take a shot.
When did you hesitate?
The first time I ever
killed someone...
There was this girl
who was in the wrong
place at the wrong time.
I killed her.
It might sound weird, but
pointing a gun at a little girl
is something that
really scares me.
If I'm ever going to get
stronger, I can't be like this.
The bullet's still in there.
I'll be fine until morning.
Just leave it.
I made a call and got
a doctor from Rome coming.
I guess the thing
didn't collapse...
Guess not...
What do you think's going
to happen to Cristiano?
If the elders still
haven't decided
what kind of a move
their going to make...
He might actually have a chance.
I hate to say this...
we're gonna have
to tell Pinocchio.
You're right... We have to.
How you doing this morning?
Oh, I'm doing alright, Domenico.
Up early. So you're
finally heading out then?
Yeah.
You better be
back before autumn.
That's the harvest season.
I'll need you.
You can count on me.
Well, Pinocchio's gone.
Yeah...
Are you sad about that?
You know, I kinda am.
Recently you two had started
to talk like normal people...
I feel bad for you.
Triela.
We need to be going.
Yes, sir.
Word is this Pinocchio guy
is Cristiano's confidant.
I bet we'll find him again.
I sure hope we do.
You can fight all you want
when the time comes...
but you know... dying will
never solve anything.
Yes, sir... Hilshire.
Sorry to interrupt.
What is it?
Pinocchio is here and
would like to see you.
He's here right now?
Pinocchio, why did
you come here?
Uncle!
I don't remember calling
for you. You need to leave.
I won't leave.
I came here to help you!
What made you think...
that I even need your help?
Flanca said you're in trouble...
Is it true the police
are coming after you?!
You only damaged
the survey bridge.
It's too early to
tell what will happen.
Isn't there someplace you
can hide out for a while?!
I've lost too many men
these past months...
More than I ever have before.
If someone takes responsibility
for our failures, it will be me.
You can't be serious!
If the cops show up, you're
just gonna let them arrest you?!
That's crazy!
I've been thinking about
what to do with you...
What do I do with you
when the time comes?
I don't want to
leave you, Uncle!
I'm gonna stand
by you and fight.
No, you will not...
You have to leave
this place right now.
I'm not leaving!
Why is it that you
choose not to listen?
Because I love you, Uncle!
You saved my life.
I'll always be
indebted to you for that.
You helped me get out
of that basement room
and gave me a name!
It was just a whim!
It meant nothing to me.
I saved you on a whim...
Why else do you think
I gave you that name?
No real parent gives
their kid a name like yours.
If you choose to
stay in this place...
Then I'll kill every
person who comes inside.
Cristiano's mansion is on this
mountainside, right here.
There are two access roads.
This one and this one.
Not too far down the east
road is a gas station...
That's their lookout...
Hilshire and I will neutralize
it and continue to the mansion.
Marco, I want you to take the
west route and block the road.
Hilshire's fratello
and my fratello
will make the first
breach on the mansion.
Our objective is to
capture Cristiano
and neutralize anyone else.
I can't believe you're here...
It's been a long time
since we've had a job
together, Angelica.
Let's do our best.
I just wanna make sure that I'm
as useful to Marco as I can be.
Angelica you ready?
Yes, I'm ready when you are.
Then go set up the Steyr
on the roof of the car.
I'll get on it now.
Hey, Angelica!
Yes...? Do you need something?
No, I was just curious...
How you feelin?
Great!
Good...
Priscilla?
Yeah?
Hurry up with those barricades.
I'm almost done.
It seems as if Pinocchio
refuses to leave us.
I never sent the
kid to school...
The only thing I knew to do
was raise him as a killer.
Still... he said he loves me.
What a very nice thing to say.
I don't understand it...
How could he...
How could he not hate me
for what I've done to
him these 10 years?
He has his own unique reason.
As does anyone when
they love another.
And, if you'll excuse
me for saying, sir...
I have sensed your own
unique brand of love
for him over time, as well.
I'm sure I was not the only one.
You wanted more than
anything in the world
to treat him as your own son,
but no matter how
hard you tried,
you simply never knew how to
go about doing it. That's all.
What he said is true.
I believe he won't leave this
place unless I flee first.
Alessio.
Yes, sir?
Ready the car for my departure.
To be safe, I'm going
to escape overseas.
Triela...
Yes, it's finished.
He's down. Let's go.
Pinocchio!
You're that girl... from
Montalcino, aren't you...?
You're not walking
away this time.
Give me your best shot!