Pinocchio...
Do you remember
the target's face?
Yes, sir.
I'll wait at the rendezvous
for 20 minutes...
If you take longer than that,
then you're on your own.
Are we clear?
Yes, sir. Clear.
He's just a kid...
You really think
this is a good idea?
John Doe wanted him to
take this guy out.
Actually... The whole
thing was his idea.
Huh...
No... no...
Good morning, Pinocchio!
Good morning, Aurora.
Are you on your way to work...?
And where do you work?
In Genoa.
Genoa...? That's really far...
When are you gonna be back?
No idea. I never know.
I hope you have a good time!
Oh, then it's really simple.
You just gotta repay your debt.
But how... a kid
couldn't do that...
Even a stinkin' dog could do it.
Look at you, already
coming up with excuses
and you haven't
even started yet.
It's that kinda crap that
makes you even less
than a stinkin' dog.
Good evening, Pinocchio.
How did everything go?
What are you doing
up there anyway?
Doing?
That's not an observatory.
I don't know if you've
ever thought about this,
but Mercedes is
a woman's name.
It was a hundred years ago when
the first of these
babies rolled out.
And to honor her
grace and beauty
they gave her a woman's name.
Then I better get off of her.
You should treat women
with a little more respect.
Get your old man to teach
you the ropes sometime.
It's not my job.
I've never been
good around girls.
Bruno told me what happened...
Seems everything went
off without a hitch.
Yes, it did, Sir.
I trust things are going
well for you in Montalcino.
I just think I'd be
more helpful to you
if I lived here, in Milan.
It's best you learn more about
the ways of the world first...
Otherwise, you'll be of
little use down the road.
Don't fret. You'll see
some action soon enough.
It's going to be a big job,
with some others involved...
You will meet up with
them at Montalcino...
Then you devise the plan.
Right... Yes, sir.
My countrymen...!
You must not lend your ears
to the separatist voice...!
Their abhorrent methods are
based in the warped logic
of those who believe that
violence will win the day!
They care nothing about the
plight of the average citizen.
Their only desire is to protect
their families
and their fortunes!
They have forgotten about
their duties as Christians--
the calling to help
and care for others...
Italy must abandon
this regionalism
and unify itself in
the truest sense!
I call out to Italy--
To all our...
I'm sorry for the wait.
We must stop this movement
towards regionalism
and nationalism
on the world stage!
Now, let us begin.
Our first piece of business,
and the major topic on the
table today, is which policy
we believe our Milan
Group should adopt.
It's obvious we
can't use the public
to hold demonstrations anymore.
The one in Rome two months ago
was a complete disaster...
I believe we need an entirely
fresh approach here.
I assume you mean attacking
the Bridge on the
Strait of Messina.
I have people drawing up
plans for its destruction...
If we can force
such a large-scale
public works project to halt...
We should be able
to keep the south
from sucking dry all of the
tax money from the north.
So who'll be doing it? Your
bombers Franco and Flanca?
That's right. And I've got
Pinocchio assisting them.
Of course, stopping
the construction
of the Messina Bridge has been
our ardent wish for many years.
And while I approve
of its sabotage,
I feel it best to explore
other methods as well.
After all, things take planning.
We can't just blow
up whatever we want
whenever we feel like it.
Pinocchio is that kid you
took in years ago, isn't he?
He's been under my guidance
for a very long time.
That judge two days ago is the
most recent example of his work.
It would seem showing pity was
the best choice in that matter.
The search continues for Judge
Berdini, who, two days ago,
disappeared from
a party in Genoa.
Of course this is the same
Judge Berdini who is
presiding over the tax-evasion
trial of Mr. Pirazzi, a wealthy
and famous Five Republics
Faction supporter from Milan.
This is leading local
authorities to believe that
it's possible he was abducted
by the Northern
Independence Faction.
Flanca... We've just been
contacted by Cristiano.
He says he has a job for us.
He wants more bombs?
You've gotta be kidding.
No, it's different this time.
So ol' Milan's in a state
of political confusion.
And our big sponsor seems to
be having legal troubles.
I heard something about
the government having
a secret agency
out in full force.
Word is they use
children as assassins.
Are you serious?
That's hard to believe.
I got a reliable source.
Apparently, it was
the same agency that
intercepted Cristiano's
men last winter...
during that accountant
incident in Florence.
So, what does Cristiano want?
We're supposed to
go to Montalcino
and there we'll
rendezvous with Pinocchio.
Pinocchio?
That's his son, right?
No. But he's
treated like a son.
Cristiano took him in when he
was a boy and trained him...
Now he's an assassin.
Pino!
Hey.
I'm so glad you came home!
It's been lonely around
here without you...
My mom thought you might
be coming home soon,
so she went to the market
and loaded up on prosciutto
and salami and
cheese and stuff--
I thought I told you before
you don't have to do that...
I'm just another guy who
lives in your neighborhood.
You're not just another guy...
You're so cool and easygoing...
So, Pino, what is it
you do for your job?
I'm just somebody's errand boy.
You are?
I figured you'd do something
cooler than that...
Like paint or record music...
Well, see you around.
I'll bring you by
some food later.
It's such a
wonderful spring day.
Yeah.
There's no better season
for driving, right?
No better season.
Calm down...
You're getting too excited.
Franco and Flanca I take it?
So, have we met before?
No... This would be
the first time...
Where should I park the car?
I'll show you the way.
Mind if I head inside?
Be my guest.
Is this a Mercedes?
No, it's an Alfa
Romeo Giulietta.
You really Italian?
So this is a woman, too...
Are you two brother and sister?
He's my partner, my bodyguard,
and my explosives mentor.
But we're not related.
No blood there.
Pinocchio. You don't hear
that name everyday.
It was the old man
who gave it to me...
Oh...
Does that make
Cristiano "Geppetto"?
Because that means that you're
the long nosed troublemaker.
I'm his devoted son.
All right then.
Mind if I take a shower
before we get started?
Sure. Go ahead.
Cristiano said we're
to work with you
on the sabotage of the bridge.
That's what I hear.
Can we trust you?
Can you afford not to?
I only trust what I've seen
with my own two eyes...
And so far from you
I've seen nothing.
They say your
specialty is knives...
I just feel better
with a knife.
Guns can be a little scary...
You think so?
Then what would you
do in this situation?
Is that a serious question?
I could kill you before
your next breath.
And if I was doing this
10 meters away from you?
I'd get nine meters closer.
Well that's a little
easier said than done.
That's true.
You have an old injury
in your left leg.
I'd take advantage
of that first.
You wanna give it a shot?
No... No need.
So where'd he go?
Out shopping.
Well I hope you boys played
nicely while I was gone.
What do you mean?
You've been dodgy since
he let us in the door.
We're freelance terrorists.
I don't think there's
anything odd about being
suspicious of each other.
True.
Pinocchio has this
reputation of being eccentric.
And it's well-earned.
I don't think you and I are in
any position to point fingers.
You're different, Flanca.
So I'm the odd one out here?
Well why don't you tell me
what you think about him?
I don't know. But he is
an interesting one...
Maybe I'm... just motherly.
Buona sera, Pino!
Been shopping?
Yeah.
That's a lot of food
for one person.
And I didn't know
you drank wine.
I have guests.
Oh, that's nice...
Then I can just ask my mom to
make some food for them, too--
I'll pass. Sorry.
Okay...
Aurora?
Uh, yeah?
You need to stop
hanging around me.
What?
You're a nuisance,
you know that?
And you'll only
end up in trouble
or worse if you
keep this crap up.
Why, Pino?
Because I'm the long
nosed troublemaker-
that's all I know how to be.
So that's the Strait
of Messina Bridge?
You don't know anything do you?
That is a CG mockup of what it
will look like when it's done.
If they ever do complete it,
it'll be the largest
suspension bridge in the world.
So far, only its support columns
have actually been built.
Our best bet, if we're
going to blow up anything,
is to use one of them.
Hmmm...
The north is incurring almost
all of the construction costs...
Of course all of the
profits will end up
going to those damn
crooks in the south.
More than anything
else right now,
the F.R.F. wants
this bridge down.
It's gonna be one big job.
Are we planting the bombs
ourselves or are we hiring out?
We do it.
Amateurs wouldn't
be able to take down
a structure like this
on their best day.
And when you get a bunch
of amateurs involved,
bad things happen and
innocent people get hurt.
You got a problem with killing?
I only approve of killing
when it's necessary...
Anything less and I'd be nothing
more than an ordinary outlaw.
Flanca's weird.
Most of the terrorists
I've known in my day
have been angry
about something.
But not her. Or if it is anger,
there's something gentle to it.
You think so?
It's too bad she's nice enough
to choose who she kills.
If you ask me, that sounds
like one hell of a handicap.
She's different.
Not your ordinary terrorist.
Honestly?
She doesn't care about stopping
the bridge's construction.
Okay, then what about you?
I don't follow any
ideas or principles.
I hear you and
Cristiano are close.
Well, he did raise me.
That the only reason you
have to swear loyalty?
No... He's all that I have.
What's Flanca to you?
I'm a man who's lost his
goals along the way...
and she gives me new ones.
I'm amazed that Angelica
has recovered this well.
I don't know if she's
work-ready just yet...
I mean, she's fresh
out of the medical ward.
Nevertheless, we're ordered
to Milan tomorrow.
So...
I hear Special Ops Section 1
is sending you to Montalcino...
That's right.
Apparently, some Public Safety
offical's gone missing there.
Yeah, I heard...
I also heard that Public
Safety is desperate to find
some F.R.F. assassin
called Pinocchio now...
I believe my trip to Milan even
has something to do with it.
Watch yourself.
Milan's a central location
for those F.R.F. bastards.
We'll be fine...
You watch yourself...
Section 1 blames us when
anything bad happens...
They might try to
screw over Section 2
and laugh from the shadows.
I'll be careful.