Cristiano, it's me...
The job's done.
They've been taken care of...
The count is three men...
and one woman.
Wrong. The count is
four men and one woman.
And that would be, four.
Count the bodies again.
I'll be there shortly.
I've had the Polacco
family eradicated.
Indeed. Your work is always
so quick and precise.
I have high hopes
for your future.
Well, thank you for
your confidence, sir.
John Doe... We're leaving.
You know, if you would
give up the drink,
I'd be willing to
double your wages.
Except that drinking... is
the one thing I insist upon.
You sly devil...
When did you put
this in here, Polacco?
He's alive, I take it?
Yeah, he is.
Is he another one
of Polacco's kids?
Not if he's like this.
Then what do we do?
You wanna just leave him?
No, he comes with us...
Bring the car around back.
Kid... Come on out.
I see.
Of course... Understood.
Alessio... Any word on
how Pinocchio is doing?
As per your instructions...
he is still on standby at
Flanca's vineyard in Tuscany.
That's good.
Is there something
bothering you sir?
It's nothing...
Don't worry about it.
Hey, Pinocchio...!
You out there?!
Yeah, what do
you need, Domenico?
We should be heading back
soon. It's about lunchtime.
I'm ready now!
You've really transformed
into a ripe ol' farmer
these past few months!
You think so?
I've never seen
such a green thumb
on such a green kid before.
That's funny...
I had actually never even
thought about it until now.
While you're still
a young man...
You should try all
sorts of things.
Pino...
Did you go into the fields
again this morning?
Yeah, I sure did.
Good...! So tell me have
you seen Franco around?
Wouldn't he be in Flanca's room?
You think the two of them
are lovers too, don't you...?
I've thought they
seemed unusually close.
Who knows.
He may be gloomy...
but, he's cute.
Do you have a girlfriend?
I've never been
very good with girls.
So now we have
it calculated out.
Explosives delivery... was
being arranged by Cristiano.
But I think it's too late.
I heard the military's
illegal sales have stopped.
You think we'll be alright?
I don't know... The weapons
procurement route
the Milan group used
was busted the other day.
I guess we'll be stranded
here a little longer.
That'll just force Pinocchio to
have to mellow out even more.
I think it's probably
for the best.
Huh?
Don't you think so?
Yeah, I do... Who knows...
Maybe we'll be able to
just live our lives here...
Forget all of the
fighting and the hatred
swirling about in the world.
Mentally, Pinocchio's
still a child.
His emotions have been
frozen for so long,
but I've been seeing him
thaw out at this place.
I think he'll be able to change.
But... It may be
too late for me.
Franco... you think I'm
being obstinate, don't you?
But doesn't that
take courage too?
There's nothing wrong
with being obstinate...
And I'll follow you in
whatever you choose to do.
Thanks a lot.
Hey kid, you up
for a little walk?
I never thought we'd be able to
hide out so close
to Rome like this.
We haven't seen a single
cop the whole time.
The authorities in these parts
only have eyes for the
Five Republics Faction.
We should be able to lay
low here for quite a while.
Are you tired of
living out here?
Not at all.
I'm surprised how fond
I've grown of the country
in such a short time.
It's better than I
expected it to be.
Course, Domenico and
Paola are so nice to me...
But... it dulls my skills.
"Touching your emotions
will make you weak"...
That's what my
teacher said to me.
Teacher?
He was a bodyguard who
worked with my uncle.
He had this
beautiful black dog...
It always slept on the
top of his car with him.
They called him "John the
Nameless" or "John Doe."
He claimed to be former CIA, but
nobody knew his true identity.
If you really wanna
be a killer...
You're gonna have to ditch
those useless emotions of yours.
Those who never
stop thinking are weak.
You have to consider other
people's lives as garbage.
So, what happened to him?
It came to him out of
the clear blue one day.
The most skilled
assassin I've known
was taken down by nothing
more than a stray bullet.
You and Flanca are
such nice people...
I think it'd be a waste
if you wound up dead.
Then again...
It's not good to have a
defeatist attitude like that...
Sometimes... I think
that's why John died.
I don't know.
I'm surprised... never
seen you confused before.
So, are you and Flanca together?
We're not.
She drives away the
emptiness inside me
and encourages me to live.
She is my reason for living.
Just like Cristiano is to you.
Oh... I see.
I've been missing
my uncle a lot.
It's the same song again.
Apparently, it's a piece
Cristiano used to play a lot
for Pinocchio when
he was just a kid.
Did he learn to play
the piano from him?
No. He learned it by ear.
Which is why it's the
only thing he ever plays.
That's really sad...
He's Pinocchio's
surrogate father...
But he hasn't done
a damn thing for him.
Excuse me.
Oh hi, Paola. What is it?
You have a call from Marinov.
Hello? Uncle Marinov?
Hello, Caterina.
I was starting to get worried.
You've been out of contact
for two months now.
The police came after me
following my meeting
with you in Rome.
I had no choice but
to go into hiding.
Makes sense.
I heard you ran into
some trouble, as well...
I'm glad to know
you're all right...
There's more for us to discuss,
but we have some urgent
business right now.
It's about the in-fighting
among the Milan faction
I mentioned before...
It sounds as if Cristiano is
finally being shown the door.
The damage done is enormous!
I've lost count of the number of
M.P.s we've found slaughtered...
And our weapons
supply has been cut.
And don't you
conveniently forget
the disaster that
kidnapping plot turned into!
How could I...?!
This year's failures
will set a bad example
unless someone takes
some responsibility!
The Milan faction has
been doing nothing
but losing battles with
government agencies lately...
It's epidemic...
In all likelihood, he'll be
sold out to the authorities
soon enough, as a way of,
say, forced resignation.
Apparently, that's the endgame
the leaders decided on.
My point is that if you
want to continue your work
with the Five Republics
Faction, the wise money
would be on you severing
all your ties with Cristiano.
Do you understand?
Yes... I understand.
Where's Pinocchio?
He's already in bed.
Well what happened to him?
Got drunk... Had a few
glasses and keeled over...
Apparently it was the first time
the kid had ever had alcohol.
Is something the matter?
I see. So Cristiano
is being held responsible.
What now?
My uncle said the
best thing for us
would be to stay
put for a while.
Fine, we'll stay put then...
But how do we explain
all of this to Pinocchio?
I don't know.
Maybe there's a way he
can avoid being ousted.
But how?
With Cristiano out of the
picture, the Milan faction
may be forced to compromise
with the government.
Which would be
really bad for us.
So... we'll just have
to blow this thing up.
What is that?
It's a survey bridge they built
as a test before they began
the major construction
of the Messina Bridge.
It wouldn't take a whole lot...
I bet we could carry enough
explosives to bring it down...
If we succeed, they'd halt the
construction of the major bridge
and Cristiano could avoid
being held responsible.
I think you're right...
I'm game. Let's
draw up the plans.
We have to move
quickly on this.
Tomorrow afternoon,
we're out of here.
Franco?
Thanks.
So this leader came to
Florence six months ago?
Back during the Pirazzi
tax evasion incident.
The Milan Group made contact...
They called the Ministry
of Interior this morning...
Said they'd reveal his
location with conditions.
That's not a bad offer...
Do we have a name yet?
Yes, it's Cristiano...
Savonarola...
He's an upstart leader
from the middle-class...
Which, as you know, is quite
the rarity for the F.R.F.
As a result of this...
there's a lot of backlash
within the Milan group.
Savonarola, really?
Coincidence or not, it's ironic.
He may have given
himself that name.
We don't know.
What we do know is that
he's quite fond of art.
And that apparently he's
plotting a terrorist attack
on the Messina Bridge.
May we dispatch the fratellos?
Permission granted.
But I want Cristiano captured
in Milan at the same time.
Savonarola?
A Florentine priest...
500 years ago,
he held real power
over the people who
heard him speak.
While the word of God was the
basis for his harsh teachings...
He was still brought to trial...
and they executed him.
Oh...
What a weird looking hood.
This is Claes.
Claes. Is Triela there with you?
Yes, she's right here.
This is Triela speaking.
Triela. We have urgent work.
Yes, sir... So we're
going to Milan...
Yes... I'll tell her
right now, sir.
I'm going to Milan tomorrow.
And Rico, you're coming with.
Nice.
Henrietta and Beatrice
are going to Messina.
You think you can hold
down the fort, Claes?
Of course, I can.
Really? Milan?
Yeah...
We've been assigned to take down
a very high level F.R.F. member.
So how have you
been feeling lately?
I'm fine... I'm better
than ever... No problems.
You want to destroy the
test bridge? I'm intrigued.
If things go according to plan,
it'll be finished tonight.
I hear you. I think it
could lead to great things.
Do you want to talk
with Pinocchio?
Yes.
Hi, uncle.
Pinocchio. Are they
treating you well out there?
Now listen to me...
Flanca and Franco
are in your hands...
Do not let them get killed.
Not a chance.
You can count on me.
One other thing...
Yeah?
Ah, nothing. Forget it...
Just watch your back.
I will.
My uncle didn't sound
right on the phone...
You think something
happened to him?
No...
He was probably just
a little confused
because of the change
in our plans.
We need to stay focused
on doing the job...
Let it go.
Right.
Well, approaching from the
land side isn't an option.
Security is too
tight to sneak past.
Then the only choice we have
is to use a boat
to get close enough.
The survey bridge might have
its sea side unguarded.
I didn't see any security
ships on the satellite images.
Let's just hope
that's still the case.
Bernardo come in...
Do you see anything?
Everything looks pretty
normal from up here.
I've got nothing... Bea?
No... don't see anything.
What do you smell?
Nothing.
So, Jose...
You think the Padania's
really showing up tonight?
I mean there's no way
they could even get close
with all the security.
Why don't you return to the
construction site gate...
I think we're gonna walk
over to the survey bridge,
check it out...
Henrietta, stick close to me.
Yes, sir!
You didn't hurt
yourself, did you?
I'm fine.
I hear the runt's first
job went rather well.
Why did you feel it correct
to teach him how to kill?
Hey... listen it was
his idea, not mine...
He just wanted to be as
helpful to you as he could.
The kid's got a natural
ability to do this job...
Who knows? With a little work,
someday he could be
even better than me.
What brought this about
in the first place, though?
I've finally grown old enough...
I understand the joy that can be
found in teaching the youth...
It's kinda like... well...
like I'm leaving behind
a double of myself
so he can continue
the good work.
What? Is that wrong?
Everybody wants a legacy.
Well, it doesn't
matter anyway...
After all, he's just an
orphan I took in on a whim.
A whim?
No, I don't think so...
As long as I've known you,
you've always wanted a son.
Hell, that's why you
named him what you did.
I'm just a well-to-do thug.
No amount of money and power
can teach anyone
how to raise a child.
I certainly don't know how.
There are lots of different ways
that a father can
show affection.
Giving him orders and
teaching him to kill...
That's just one way
of going about it...
There are plenty of others.
What ever happened to,
"touching your emotions
will make you weak"?
Probably just goes to show
you how old I've gotten...
I may be dull in my old age...
But at least I'm having fun.