The ocean sure is big.
It's enormous.
Jean told me something.
He said that every time
he looked at the ocean
it makes him feel sad.
What about you, Henrietta?
What do you feel?
I guess... I guess it
makes me miss Jose.
Yeah, you're right.
'Cause it makes me miss Jean.
Look!
I heard the other
day they're gonna
demolish the survey bridge.
Too bad... after all
we did to protect it.
They're also restarting
construction on the real bridge.
It should happen
sometime over the next month.
How's Triela been lately?
In the dorm.
How's she been doing?
Her injuries from
Milan were pretty bad.
Maybe that's why she
hasn't been very cheerful
since she's been back.
Triela...
Is something the matter?
What...? No...
Nothing's wrong at all.
You're not feeling
sick, are you?
Trust me. I'm fine.
So, are you still feeling off?
I think most of the drugs'
side effects have worn off...
I think.
But I still don't feel any
better, even after I've won.
And that's what I wanted
more than anything.
May you not chase the
events of times past...
nor vex over the future
and what it may hold.
Don't worry about
what's happened...
and don't be concerned
with what's going to happen.
You've got a nice,
simple philosophy, Claes.
Actually... I think
it's our philosophy.
You know Triela...
You probably should
have gone with them.
Maybe...
It was Taormina.
That's in Sicily, right?
Yeah...
Jean, mentioned that they have
a villa outside of town there.
Oh.
I guess it doesn't
really matter,
just as long as Henrietta
and Rico have a good time.
I wish... I wish you and I could
always be together, Jose.
Oh yeah? Why's that?
Father is always too
busy with his work,
and you know Jean will
be late to everything.
I thought the whole
point of a vacation
is to get to spend
time with your family.
Yeah, I'm sorry...
Whenever I start to feel lonely,
I know that you're the
only one I can count on
to be there for me.
Jose?
Hilshire called...
The ferry's here.
It's docked on the
other side of the island.
Okay.
It's too bad we've only got
a few hours of relaxation left.
It is kind of short to
call it a real vacation...
But that's how it always is.
Do you remember
when we were kids--
that time we spent an
entire month up here...?
Everyone was always so busy.
I got an idea.
Yeah?
The old amphitheater--
let's go there...
just for old times' sake.
This place sure does
bring back memories.
We used to run around
here like crazy.
But, Jose.
I come to this city,
I see one thing...
Every member of
our family, dead...
That's the only thing I can
ever think of when I'm here.
I know.
And it doesn't bother you?
It's gotta stir up
memories of Enrica.
You don't get it, brother.
I come here to make
sure that no matter what
I never forget about her.
And it helps... Helps me know
how to treat Henrietta well.
It's changed.
What has?
Your attitude...
toward Henrietta, I mean.
You've put some of your
baggage behind you...
You're just more
natural with her now.
If I recall, you were the one
against doting over her. No?
Look, you didn't have
it in you last year.
You do now. Let's not
make a thing out of it.
I'm always open to any
prudent method of interaction.
'Course you are.
I hope the girls are
enjoying their down time.
Cyborg conditioning is mentally
stressful to an alarming degree.
I want to see if
this kind of time off
could help stem the problem.
I heard about the
second-stage girl.
How's she coming along so far?
You mean with the
new conditioning system?
They're lowering the dosages
and easing up on the
restraints, right?
I think it a good idea.
Reduce the load and
you get more mileage.
The chief has
high hopes for her.
Jose!
Hi, Henrietta.
These past few days
without you felt like forever.
I guess I missed you more
than I thought I would.
Hilshire... Thanks for
watching out for them.
They needed a good guide.
Well, It's all just part of
the Handler's job description.
What now...? Are you gonna
come stay at our place?
Nah, I'm taking a plane back...
I left Triela alone
at headquarters.
Sure. I know exactly
how you feel.
Have a good trip back.
Hello Jean... How are you?
I'm glad you're here...
This is a rare vacation...
so have a good time.
'Kay.
That's amazing!
I know.
I wonder if I'll have
to give up my gun again,
like I did last year?
Henrietta.
Jose...
We're going out for
dinner in the city tonight.
What do you say?
Great.
Uh... Um...
Here you go... Take my gun.
Oh, right... I forgot.
You told me before we left...
that I should try to be normal.
Like a normal girl,
on a normal vacation.
No... I want you to keep it.
Oh... Sure!
Now then...
Check inside that closet.
'Kay.
It's so cute!
Go ahead. Try it on.
Thank you so much, Jose!
What's that, Henrietta?
A new dress?
Isn't it nice?
That, outfit...
Um... It was Jose.
He was letting me borrow it.
Are you alright, Jean?
Yeah... I'm good, thanks.
Jose is getting the car.
Okay!
Rico couldn't wait
to come here either!
She was packed three
days before we left.
Any ideas about what we
should we do tomorrow?
Sightseeing and
shopping are about it...
There's really not
much else to do here.
Let's see the ocean!
I mean... please.
Okay... We will.
Cool.
Jean...! You're not
leaving already?!
Mountain training is beginning.
I need to return to Rome
before they head out.
But you can't...
We're all finally together
like we're supposed to be.
Besides you promised
the three of us
would go sailing this year!
You can't just leave and
break your promise to me!
Don't act so childish.
You can just go
with Jose tomorrow.
Those were Enrica's clothes...
You took this one
too far, Jose. Too far.
Did he really?
Enrica...
You're both my brothers...
but Jose is the only one
who tries to remember me.
I'm seeing things...
I have to be.
But you, my dear Jean...
Well, you're just
terrible to me.
I haven't forgotten you!
Your heart is filled
with the desire
to avenge what
happened to Sofia.
But Jose is terrible
in his own way, too.
Of course those clothes
do belong to me...
But he's letting
another girl wear them.
Now that I'm dead,
Jose has found a perfect
replacement for me.
That's right!
He's apologizing Enrica!
He thinks if he can
do everything for her,
then you might be
able to forgive him.
That's not for me...
He's doing that for himself.
What's wrong with that?!
The only thing the dead have is
the ability to curse the living.
Because you see
the living as weak!
He tried everything...
This was the only way Jose
could have lived with himself!
I was the one who suggested it!
Put the blame on my shoulders!
Jean?
Is someone out there with you?
It's just me.
What's wrong, Rico?
I had a bad feeling...
so I thought I'd look for you.
and when I heard your voice
it sounded like you were
angry with somebody.
I'm fine.
The stars are gorgeous tonight.
Yeah, they look a lot
different than they do
back at headquarters don't they?
It would have been nice to have
brought the telescope with us.
Then you could have
told me some more of your
star stories that
I enjoy so much.
I don't need the telescope
to tell you stories.
What's wrong?
It's Rico, she told
me something...
On the ferry... she said that
the ocean makes Jean feel sad.
It makes me lonely...
and uneasy.
There's no need to be...
I'm right here.
Yeah... I don't have
any problems...
...when I'm with you.
Jose?
Last night... I saw
an illusion of Enrica.
An illusion?
I don't know, maybe.
It could have been a ghost.
Really?
She scolded me... got me
feeling bad about things.
Jose, come in the water!
It's been a while since
we've gone swimming.
Let's hop in.
Sure.
Do you remember... the last
time we were all here...
we promised to
take Enrica sailing?
Of course, I remember.
You couldn't stay.
Had to go back to
Rome for training.
What would you say to
taking the boat out later?
Just you and me and the girls.
Sounds great...
Yeah. Let's do that.