( Cameo laughs )
I’m sure it’s quite
the traumatic experience
being eaten alive
by your own sister.
Then again, when a man
uncovers his deepest desires,
all of his weaknesses
are laid bare.
You gave nary a thought
to the depraved nature
of bringing someone
back to the world of the living.
Everyone desperately
wants to believe
that their loved ones
are still alive somewhere.
More than anything else,
your hope is that,
by some miracle,
they’ll suddenly pop in tomorrow
and say, "good morning."
Oh, before I forget,
I believe you said something
about a third wish,
but, if i’m not mistaken,
you’ve already made said wish.
( Polnareff gasps ) You mean...
Cameo: You wished for avdol
to come back to life!
Hail 2 u!
( Wind blowing )
( Polnareff gasps )
♪
No. He’s...
( Avdol roars )
( Polnareff screams )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
( Polnareff screams )
- Avdol, it’s me!
- ( Avdol screams )
( Polnareff gasping )
Av-avdol, why?
Avdol: My fingers,
they’ve crumbled to pieces.
( Groans )
On your feet, polnareff!
I blame you for all of this.
Because of
your idiotic bumbling, i--
polnareff, because of you,
I ended up like this!
♪
Polnareff: Avdol, you’re right.
The person to blame for this...
Is me!
Avdol: Mark my words.
You’ll pay for this, polnareff,
and you’ll do it
with your flesh!
Sherry: I’ll get better
if I eat, right?
Well, am I right?
Huh, big brother?!
- ( Yells )
- ( Polnareff screams )
( Whimpering )
Sherry:
What’s the matter, brother?
Polnareff: S-stay away!
Stay away from me!
Both of you!
Please go back to your graves!
Sherry: But why? You’re the one
who brought us back, aren’t you?
Avdol: The time has come
for you to enter your grave!
( Polnareff gasping )
I-i’m so panicked
that I forgot to summon chariot.
How could I have been
so caught up in my wish
that I neglected
to use my stand?
( Gasps ) Leave me alone!
Get away from me!
Please, just stay away!
What the--
cameo: "Please"? Oh, no, no, no!
You don’t have
any wishes left, remember?!
- ( Both growl )
- ( Polnareff screaming )
Cameo: I’ve already granted
your three wishes.
( Laughs )
And i’m sorry to say
you don’t get any more!
Polnareff: Stop it! Get off!
Cameo: Hail 2 u!
( Laughs )
Go ahead. Writhe and scream to
your pathetic heart’s content.
Since you’re
in the middle of nowhere,
your friends by the shore
won’t hear you.
No one can save you now!
( Laughs )
( Creatures chewing )
Polnareff: It’s no use.
This is the end.
I’m going to die. I’m finished.
Sherry, avdol...
I suppose you’re
giving me what I deserved.
It’s only fitting.
It’s like you said.
You died
because of my actions...
♪
( Sobs )
And so i’ve accepted my fate.
( Gasps )
Huh?
♪
What? My vision must be going.
I’m seeing double.
It looks like
there are two avdols.
Huh?
( Chuckles )
Of course
there’s not another one.
If i’m starting to see things,
guess it means the end is near.
The blood loss
is taking its toll.
I’m hallucinating.
All right, this is it.
I’ll have to tap out early.
Goodbye, Mr. Joestar,
kakyoin, jotaro.
I pray for your victory.
As for you, avdol,
i’ll atone in the next world.
- Hmm?
- ( Double groaning )
( Avdol chuckles )
Cameo: What? Impossible!
Polnareff: Huh? I was right!
I just knew I saw another avdol!
My eyes weren’t playing tricks!
Besides the dirt
and dust version cameo made,
there’s another avdol!
Avdol: Magician’s red!
( Magician’s red squawks )
( Double screams )
Cameo: But how?!
He’s supposed to be dead!
It’s impossible! He was stabbed
by the hanged man, centerfold!
Polnareff:
How the hell is he alive?!
Avdol: Tsk, tsk.
Polnareff: Are you
really Mohammed avdol?!
Avdol: Yes, you had
better believe I am!
♪
Polnareff: Is it really you?
Avdol: Tsk, tsk.
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
Polnareff: I-is it
the real you, I mean?
Avdol: Polnareff, you haven’t
changed in the slightest.
You still lose all common sense
when it comes to your sister
and never stop to think
of the consequences.
Cameo: I simply refuse
to accept this!
Mohammad avdol is dead!
I was told hol horse
put a bullet between your eyes
after hanged man
sunk his blade into your back
- and you died on the spot!
- ( Avdol chuckles )
You’re correct
about me being shot,
right in the forehead.
That said, because I was
stabbed in the back,
for a moment,
my face was looking up,
and the bullet only grazed me.
I suppose this is what one would
call a blessing in disguise.
Hol horse didn’t realize it,
but his bullet never
made contact with my brain,
so he didn’t inflict
a mortal wound.
He was only able to scratch
my skin and bruise my skull.
( Cameo growls )
Avdol: Although I did
completely lose consciousness.
( Cameo growls )
Avdol: So you call yourself
cameo of the judgment card.
Hell is near, so prepare...
For hell 2 u!
♪
Polnareff: I know it was only
the third wish, but still...
It’s really him.
It came true!
Avdol: Mohammed avdol
is indeed alive and well.
I would call this bad news.
That being the case,
shouldn’t you scurry away
to inform dio and your
fellow stand user compatriots
about my return?
( Cameo growls )
Avdol: Well,
shouldn’t you, cameo?
( Cameo groans )
Polnareff: That’s right!
I have to tell them!
I have to let
Mr. Joestar, kakyoin,
and jotaro know!
Avdol’s back!
Cameo: This is very
surprising news, to be sure,
but the way I see it,
I can spin it this way.
Not only did judgment’s cameo
slay the idiot polnareff,
but also succeeded
in eliminating avdol,
who was actually alive!
Oh, I can’t wait
to tell them the splendid news!
Avdol: Magician’s red!
Cameo: Whoa, there.
( Laughs )
( Avdol groans )
Polnareff: Avdol!
( Groans )
Avdol: This stand...
It’s far more powerful
than I expected.
Polnareff: Be careful.
It’s not just his power.
This guy’s got
incredible speed, too.
Cameo: Come now, avdol. Is that
the extent of your abilities?
If so, then sharing my good news
will be even easier
than expected.
May fortune...
- ( Sherry gasps )
- ( Polnareff gasps )
Cameo: Be with you both!
Avdol: What now?!
Cameo: Hail 2 u!
Sherry: Big brother...
Polnareff:
No, stop this charade.
You’re not the real Sherry.
My Sherry is gone, dead!
- ( Sobs )
- ( Chorus vocalizing )
You’re nothing but...
A hunk of dirt!
( Sherry gasps )
But, brother...
Avdol: Polnareff.
Apologies.
I would like to take back
what I said
about you not changing.
Polnareff: No, you were
right about me all along.
I’m the one
who should apologize.
( Cameo laughs )
( Avdol and polnareff yell )
This battle
has already been decided.
( Both groaning )
Cameo: Tell you what, avdol.
Before you head off
for that magic lamp in the sky,
i’d like to hear
your three wishes.
I’ll Grant them before I
put you to rest for good.
Go ahead.
You may as well give it a shot.
As I said,
you get three wishes.
Polnareff: Quel salaud.
He’s making fools of us!
Just ignore him, avdol.
You don’t have to make
any wishes!
( Avdol grunts )
Polnareff: Avdol,
are you listening to me?
( Avdol scoffs ) No good.
I want four wishes!
Polnareff: Huh?!
Cameo: What?
Avdol: My wishes.
Can’t you hear?
I’m asking you
to Grant my wishes,
only I want four
instead of three.
( Cameo growls )
Avdol: Tsk, tsk.
Cameo: Avdol,
you can’t be serious.
Avdol: Are you denying my wish?!
Cameo, you’re the one
who offered to Grant them!
I’m going to make sure
you keep your promise!
Cameo: You still insist upon
this futile contest of power?
( Laughs )
Your kicks are nothing!
( Gasps ) What?!
( Wails )
Polnareff:
That’s the way! Super!
( Avdol scoffs )
Tsk, tsk.
You should probably know
that my first wish
was to make you
cry out in agony,
and it came true.
Cameo: This is madness.
How can you be
so much stronger than before?
Avdol: The wound left behind
after I was stabbed
by the hanged man
hasn’t completely healed yet.
Because I was so focused
on guarding my wound
from an assault,
I had to hold myself back
a little.
Cameo: What?
Avdol: It was
only three days ago
that I was finally able
to stand again.
But since I took a plane here
from India,
the trip was very easy.
Polnareff: That’s avdol,
still the best.
Avdol: And now
for my second wish!
( Cameo gagging )
( Screams )
Avdol: I wish for you
to scream out in utter terror.
And while you’re at it,
Grant my third wish!
Cry in regret!
( Cameo wails )
- ( Avdol growls )
- Polnareff: That bastard!
He’s running away!
Wait, damn it! Get back here!
Avdol: Shh. Polnareff, quiet.
♪
With that kind
of power and speed,
given the rule of stands,
the user must be hiding
somewhere nearby,
supplying his stand with energy.
( Polnareff grunts )
Is he here?
Avdol: Yes, he should be
hiding out very close to us.
( Polnareff gasps )
Hey, could that be--
avdol: Shh.
( Man wheezes )
( Coughs )
Avdol: Shh.
( Man gasps )
Polnareff: Has this user really
resorted to hiding underground?
Damn coward.
How dare you use my sister
like some pawn in a game?
For what you’ve done,
I think i’ll show you hell.
Hell 2 u.
Connard.
( Chuckles )
I can think of a few things
to drop down this tube,
like dirt and sand...
A spider...
- Ants, too...
- ( Avdol gasps )
Polnareff: And a match.
♪
( Man gasping )
( Sputters )
Polnareff: Bastard.
I hope you’re ready,
because your suffering
has barely begun.
Avdol: Hey, polnareff.
I do believe it’s time
for me to drain the snake.
Polnareff: Huh?
Avdol: How about it, my friend?
Shall we engage in the timeless
ritual of male bonding?
Hmm. Tsk, tsk.
Polnareff: Huh?
Oh.
( Yelps )
( Man sighs )
Somehow I made it
out of that mess alive.
( Zipper unzips )
Huh?
( Gurgling )
Avdol: Come on, polnareff.
- Let me hear you laugh!
- Polnareff: Uh...
Avdol: I want to hear
the heartiest laugh
that you can muster!
( Laughs )
Polnareff: Avdol,
I might be wrong about this,
but it seems like you’re
the one who’s changed.
Before the incident,
you would have never thought
of doing something
quite so perverse.
( Chuckles ) This--
this isn’t a result of you
being shot in the head, is it?
( Avdol laughing )
( Polnareff laughing )
Avdol: That’s it!
Aim that thing!
Polnareff: Right!
( Both laughing )
( Man gagging )
Huh? What the--
( whimpering )
Please I beg you, forgive me!
- Huh?
- Avdol: Last, but not least,
my fourth wish
is to not Grant you
a single one
of your pitiful wishes.
My magician’s red forgives
no one, especially not you.
( Man gasps )
( Groans )
Polnareff: Ba-dum-tss!
Polnareff: Hey!
You guys’ll never believe it!
Guess who I ran into
while out and about?!
Joseph: Polnareff,
we were worried about you.
Kakyoin: Where did
those injuries come from?
Jotaro: Some kind of enemy?
Polnareff: My wounds are nothing
compared to my news!
Now listen up, and don’t
be too shocked, jotaro!
And you’re gonna have to promise
you won’t throw your back out
in surprise, kakyoin.
Who do you think I met
out there, Mr. Joestar?
- Joseph: Huh?
- ( Polnareff giggles )
Now prepare to be blown away!
Tum-ta-da-da!
Here he is!
That sly bastard avdol was
still alive! Isn’t that great?!
( Hums fanfare )
Joseph: Well, we should
probably get going.
Avdol: Here. Allow me
to help you carry your luggage.
Jotaro: Avdol,
how you been doing?
Kakyoin: It’s been a while.
How goes it?
Joseph: So, avdol,
is the wound on your back
- healing up all right?
- Avdol: It’s fine,
though my joints do get
a little stiff sometimes.
Polnareff: Hey!
Jotaro: Has it
really been two weeks
- since we last saw each other?
- Polnareff: Hey!
Jotaro: We’re lucky
to all be alive.
Avdol: Jotaro, you’re still
wearing your uniform?
Don’t you ever get hot?
( Laughs )
Polnareff: Hey,
just hold on a second, guys!
( Groans )
Didn’t you hear me?!
I told you to hold on a second,
you assholes!
What’s the deal with
those laissez-faire attitudes?!
A man we thought was dead
just waltzed onto the beach!
How the hell
can you just brush it off
and act like
nothing has changed?!
Joseph: Oh, yeah.
I’m sorry about that, polnareff.
When I told you
i’d taken it upon myself
to Bury avdol in India,
I may have lied.
Polnareff: Wh-wh-what the hell?!
Avdol: Mr. Joestar and jotaro
were the ones
who tended to the wounds
on my head back in India
after I was shot by hol horse.
( Polnareff sputters )
You assholes have known avdol
was alive the entire time,
and never once did it cross
any of your deceitful minds
to let me know?!
I’m most surprised
at you, kakyoin!
Kakyoin: I only found out
the day after it all happened.
But it was imperative
to not let the enemy know,
and since you have
such a big mouth, I suggested--
pardon. What I meant to say
was since it’s not easy
for you to lie on command,
I suggested
we keep it a secret from you.
( Polnareff gasps )
Jotaro: If you’d
let the secret slip,
avdol wouldn’t have been
able to recuperate in peace.
Kakyoin: We were
planning to let you know
the very moment
we knew that he was safe,
but we didn’t think
you’d run into him first.
Polnareff: Oh, yeah.
Avdol, we found your dad
living in a hut on this island!
Come on.
Let’s let him know you’re here!
Avdol: Oh, that was
just me in disguise.
Polnareff: Say what?!
Then you were in on it
from the very start?
Everything that happened
was a ruse you created?
Avdol: Don’t talk to me!
No one ever comes to visit
when they have
good news to report!
Just shut up!
Joseph: Don’t go there.
Avdol’s death wasn’t your fault.
Polnareff: You didn’t
have to go that far!
How dare you leave me
out of the loop?!
I think that’s the cruelest
thing you’ve ever done to me!
Joseph: Now, now, chin up.
There’s no reason
for you to cry.
Kakyoin: I’m sorry, polnareff.
I truly didn’t think
you’d be this hurt.
- ( Jotaro growls )
- Avdol: I apologize as well,
but I had a very good reason
for coming to this island
in disguise.
Polnareff: Yeah? What is it?
Joseph: It was partially
so the enemy wouldn’t find out,
but I also had avdol
do some shopping for me
while he was laying low.
Polnareff:
What kind of shopping?
Avdol: Since it was
a very conspicuous acquisition,
I disguised myself
as a wealthy arab gentlemen.
Joseph: All right, everyone,
let’s climb aboard and head out!
Come on, polnareff.
For the love
of everything that’s sacred,
- cheer up already.
- Polnareff: Huh?
Joseph: It’s almost here. Look.
Polnareff: I don’t understand.
What’s almost here?
I don’t see anything! ( Gasps )
♪
What?!
Whoa! A submarine?!
Joseph: That’s right.
From here on out,
we’re riding to Egypt in this.
Polnareff:
Y-you’ve gotta be kidding!
How did you afford this?!
♪
♪ All the old paintings
on the tomb ♪
♪ they do the sand dance,
don’t you know ♪
♪ if they move too quick
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re falling down
like a domino ♪
♪ all the bazaar men
by the nile ♪
♪ they got the money on a bet
♪ gold crocodiles
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they snap their teeth
on your cigarette ♪
♪ foreign types
with the hookah pipes say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian
♪ The blond waitresses
take their trays ♪
♪ they spin around,
and they cross the floor ♪
♪ they’ve got the moves
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ you drop your drink
♪ then they bring you more
♪ all the school kids
so sick of books ♪
♪ they like the punk
and the metal band ♪
♪ when the buzzer rings
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re walking
like an Egyptian ♪
♪ all the kids
in the marketplace say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian