Joseph: Tokyo,
Hong Kong, Singapore...
So the Indian leg of
our journey is finally upon us.
♪
But, well,
i’m a little bit worried.
I mean, is there anywhere
to get a cheeseburger there?
I’ve always heard India
was a land of curry,
disease, too many people.
Polnareff: I know.
I’m worried my stomach
won’t be able to handle
the culture gap.
( Avdol chuckles )
That assessment
is rather distorted.
You needn’t worry.
It’s a country
of extraordinary people.
That, I assure you, my friends.
Well, we’ve reached Calcutta.
Let’s get going.
( Car horns honking )
( Overlapping chatter )
Man: Let me carry that for you!
Man #2: Want a tattoo?
You’re very pretty.
Man #3: Need some antivenom?
It won’t hurt your stomach.
Man #4: Stay at our hotel!
Narrator: Calcutta, India,
in the 20th century,
its population is 11 million.
Calcutta buzzes
with a bustling energy
that will pull you in
and never let you go.
Joseph: I don’t need any.
Polnareff: I stepped
in some cow shit! Damn!
Joseph:
Seriously, thank you.
Kakyoin: Aw, crap. Somebody’s
already stolen my wallet.
Boy: Tip! Tip! Tip!
Boy #2: If you
don’t give me tips,
you won’t go to heaven, sir.
Polnareff: Hey, kid, don’t put
your nose all over my stuff!
- ( Growls )
- Joseph: Avdol!
So this is India?
Avdol: See?
Great country, isn’t it?
( Laughs )
They’re what makes India great,
don’t you think?
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
( Overlapping chatter )
( Avdol chuckles )
Here. Try this.
This is chai. I think
you’ll find it to your liking.
Narrator: Chai, one of india’s
most popular drinks,
a sweet concoction
made by boiling black tea,
sugar, and ginger with milk.
( Joseph sighs )
At last, a little peace.
Avdol: Be patient with India.
Once you get used to it,
you’ll see how wonderful
this country is.
Jotaro: You know, I kinda like
this place. It’s pretty cool.
Joseph: What, jotaro?
You cannot be serious.
( Polnareff sighs )
It’s a hell of a lot
of culture shock, though.
Guess i’ll like it
once I get used to it, huh?
Well, I guess people adapt to
their surroundings eventually.
Where’s the John?
Server: It’s right
over there, sir.
- Joseph: Polnareff.
- Polnareff: Yeah?
Joseph: Aren’t you
going to order first?
Polnareff: Pick for me.
It better be something amazing,
something gorgeous
and sophisticated
that suits a frenchman
such as moi.
Kakyoin: Which means
it doesn’t matter,
he’ll eat anything.
Let’s see.
What’s something he’ll like?
Excuse me.
Man: Pardon me, sir.
- Could you please wait?
- Polnareff: Eh?
Huh?
Man: Please use this
while you’re in here.
Polnareff: Hmm?
What am I supposed to do
with this? Hey!
( Growls )
Hmm? Hmm.
Hmm.
Ooh la la.
I must say,
the toilet looks weird,
but at least it’s a lot cleaner
than I had expected.
( Scoffs ) A gentleman like
myself has certain standards
and won’t stand for it
when a bathroom is dirty.
( Gasps )
( Screaming )
Man: Sir, is something wrong?
Polnareff: D-d-d-d-don’t
"is something wrong?" Me!
Th-th-th-th-the toilet...
The toilet...
There’s a pig
sticking its head out of it!
Man: Why, yes.
No need to be frightened.
He’s actually quite friendly.
The builders constructed
the pigpen down below
higher than they
were supposed to,
so when the pigs get hungry,
they come up for more.
That’s all.
Polnareff: But that’s not even
what i’m asking you about!
No. Wait. What?
So you’re telling me...
That this pig’s food is...
( Pig oinking )
Polnareff:
That’s what it’s there for?!
Man: As I told you, sir,
here. Use this stick,
like this.
( Pig squeals )
See? Now you can
do your business
while the pig’s knocked down.
- Though some like the pig.
- ( Polnareff gasps )
Man: Our manager gets the pig
to lick his buttocks
and always sings
the pig’s praises.
He gets it so clean. ( Giggles )
( Polnareff shuddering )
Man: Feel free
to take your time.
Polnareff: Hey, monsieur,
don’t leave me alone!
( Pig growls )
Polnareff: I don’t think
I could ever get used to this,
no matter how much I tried.
( Pig squeals )
I’ll wait
until we get to the hotel.
Server:
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Joseph: Oh.
Polnareff: Crap, the food.
Hmm?
( Gasps )
♪
( Gasps ) Where is he?
No way. Too weird.
I know I saw someone out there.
Huh. I must have imagined it.
I guess I can’t help it.
I mean, there was a pig
in the John, for god’s sake.
Oh, well. Nothing there.
What’s a little monster
in the mirror, anyway?
So this is what they mean
by culture shock here.
( Chuckles )
( Gasps )
♪
Wh-what the?!
Huh?
( Gasps )
What the hell is going on here?!
I can only see this damn thing
in the mirror!
This must be the mirror stand
jotaro talked about.
Merde, this is not good.
Mon dieu!
This is so not good!
Ah! Silver chariot!
Huh? Where did that bastard go?
Damn it.
Jotaro: Huh?
Polnareff: A stand!
Server #2: Hmm?
Polnareff: But where’s the user?
Who is it?!
The man with two right hands.
( Growls )
( Overlapping chatter )
Too many people.
Damn it.
Joseph: What’s the matter,
polnareff?
Avdol: What is this about?
Polnareff: If that was it,
if that stand belongs
to who I think it does, then...
That means
i’ve finally found him.
Jotaro, the stand user
who uses the mirrors, he’s here.
The bastard who killed
my sister, my angelic sister.
♪
The scum
who heartlessly trampled
my sister’s life,
soul, and pride,
who destroyed
the world’s most pure heart,
finally, finally we meet.
Joseph: Are you
absolutely sure it’s him?
Polnareff: It’s settled.
Mr. Joestar, i’ll be traveling
on my own from here on out.
- Joseph: Wha?!
- ( All gasp )
Polnareff: With my sister’s
murderer finally within reach,
i’ll be damned if i’m going to
wait for him to come after me.
I’m screwed
if he gets the drop on me,
and that’s just not my style.
I’ll find him first
and kill him.
Kakyoin: But we don’t even
know what he looks like
or what his stand is.
Polnareff:
He’s got two right hands.
That’s enough for me.
And don’t forget, he knows
that i’m coming after him.
That should put him
on the defensive
and give me the advantage.
See ya.
Avdol: Tough talk for a man
who’s digging his own grave.
Polnareff: And that means?
Avdol: Just as it sounds,
my friend.
Polnareff: Are you implying
that i’m gonna lose?
Avdol: Yes. Can’t you see?
The enemy attacked
in order to isolate you.
He’s exploiting
your biggest weakness!
I won’t let you go alone,
polnareff.
Polnareff: Listen up.
I’m only gonna say it once.
This whole time, I never once
gave a damn about dio.
Avdol: Hmm?
Polnareff:
I told you in Hong Kong
that I would go along with you
so that I could get my revenge.
Mr. Joestar and jotaro
already know this.
( Joseph grumbles )
Polnareff: I’ve been alone
from the beginning.
I’ve always been
fighting alone!
Avdol: You selfish fool!
Did you forget that you
were brainwashed by dio?
Are you so foolish you forgot
that he’s the root
of all of this?
Polnareff: You have
no idea how it feels
to have your sister murdered,
so shut the hell up!
I heard,
the last time you met dio,
you pissed yourself
and ran away.
A coward like you
would never understand
why I need to do this!
Avdol: What did you say?
( Polnareff grunts )
Don’t touch me!
You just got lucky the day
you beat me in Hong Kong.
Enough with this lecturing.
Avdol: How dare you?
Polnareff:
Oh, did that offend you?
But don’t forget! I’m a lot
angrier than you are right now
and with
a hell of a lot better reason.
( Avdol growls )
Polnareff: You can
just keep being yourself
with your holier-than-thou
attitude, avdol!
Avdol: Why, you--( Grunts )
Mr. Joestar!
Joseph: That’s enough.
Just let him go.
Now that his mind is made up,
I doubt that anybody
could stop him.
( Avdol groans )
Yeah?
I’ve lost all respect
for him, that’s all.
My impression of him
was completely wrong.
( Polnareff spits )
Avdol: You are correct
in that I did run
in fear from him.
You see, i’m certain
that foresight will let us win.
Rushing in without thinking
will get us killed.
Polnareff: Oh?
Then i’ll say this
with certainty, too.
Your precious little divination
will be wrong.
( Crowd murmuring )
( Avdol growls )
♪
( Distant rumbling )
( Elephant trumpets )
♪
Man: Time to get off.
I’m here to see
a friend of mine.
( Elephant groans )
Now get gone, girl.
You’re on your own.
( Woman gasps )
Please make me your wife.
I’ll do anything you want.
Man: Hmm?
Woman: My life
will belong to you.
Just say whatever
you wish of me, my love.
Please, let me stay with you.
Let me be by your side forever.
Man: Oh, come on now.
Don’t be stupid.
You’re still only 16.
Woman: I’m old enough to marry.
I love you.
( Man sighs )
( Elephant trumpets )
( Spurs jingle )
( Woman gasps )
Man: Listen. I’m just
a no-good drifter, baby.
I live each day
like it’s my last,
and one day,
the end will come for me.
Shh.
This is no life for a lady,
and you have royal blood.
We can’t have
a fairy-tale marriage,
no matter how much
we might love each other.
Woman: Really?
You’ve never said that before.
You love me?
Man: Yeah. You’re the only woman
i’ve ever loved.
( Woman sighs )
Man: That’s just it.
It’s ’cause I love you
that we can’t marry.
I want you to be happy
and have something better.
You understand, don’t you?
( Woman gasps )
Man: I know, sweetheart.
This breaks my heart
just as much as it breaks yours.
( Woman sobs )
( Man kisses )
But i’ll come back to see you
and hold you like this
whenever I can.
That’s enough to make me happy.
Woman: Okay.
( Man chuckles )
Goodbye. Love ya, darling.
( Elephant roars )
- ( Man #2 laughs )
- Man #1: Hmm?
( Man #2 laughing )
Man #1: You know,
it’s bad manners to eavesdrop.
You think I spend too much time
on romance, don’t ya?
Well, when you’ve
got girls like her
all over the world
at your Beck and call,
well, you’ve always
got an ally, a partner.
They’d do anything for me,
even throw away their own lives.
You are aware of how I work,
aren’t you,
Mr. Centerfold?
( Centerfold laughs )
Man: By the way, about this
silver chariot’s polnareff,
seems that he left the group and
is looking for you on his own.
What do you wanna do?
He totally fell for your plan,
hook, line, and sinker.
Heh. Shall we go
and kill him first?
Huh?
( Snake hissing )
Hmm.
♪
Let’s go.
You know, between
your hanged man and my emperor,
I have no doubt that we
can kill ’em all, no sweat,
this’ll be a hell of a ride.
( Centerfold chuckles )
♪
Joseph: So he really
didn’t come back after all.
( Kakyoin sighs )
♪
( No audible dialogue )
( Music playing only )
( Polnareff growls )
What? You’ve seen him?
Are you absolutely sure you saw
a man with two right hands?
Where?!
- ( Man murmurs )
- Polnareff: Huh?
( Growls )
♪
( Spurs jingling )
Man: Eh? I just saw him.
I don’t understand it.
He was just right there.
Polnareff: What?
Man: There. He was with
that man in the street.
( Polnareff scoffs )
Stand user: The gun
is mightier than the sword.
- Polnareff: Eh?
- Stand user: Mm, not bad,
if I do say so myself.
Polnareff: Wait. What?
Who the hell are you, buddy?
Hol horse: Hmm. Hol horse,
that’s what they call me.
I’m a stand user
just like you are,
and my card is the emperor.
Lord dio paid me
to get rid of you guys,
so say your prayers,
and get ready for a beating.
Polnareff: Look here, cowboy,
I don’t give a rat’s ass
who you say you are.
Hol horse: Hmm?
Polnareff: Where is the man
with two right hands?
Hol horse: That was pretty rude.
You asked who I am,
so I answered you.
Well, whatever.
I came here with that guy.
( Polnareff gasps )
Hol horse: He’s nearby.
Polnareff: What? Where is he?!
Hol horse: There’s really
no point at all
in you asking that.
I, hol horse,
will have the pleasure
of snuffing you out.
Polnareff: Arrogant morons
like you always talk trash,
and it always ends up
the other way around.
( Hol horse laughs )
Polnareff: Oh, was that funny?
Hol horse: Lord dio
had you pegged.
"Polnareff has the fatal habit
"of underestimating
his opponents.
Beating him into a corpse
won’t be any trouble for you."
He was exactly right,
so I couldn’t help but laugh.
( Chuckles )
( Polnareff scoffs )
If I can’t face him
until I defeat you,
then that’s
just what i’ll do, chump.
Bring it on.
Hol horse: Ever heard
of military chess?
The tank is stronger
than the soldier,
and the tanks are weak
against the mines.
See, it’s pretty much
the basics of battle.
My emperor is stronger than you,
so I thought i’d be a gentleman.
I’ll let you know
my stand’s abilities
before we fight
so we’re square.
The gun is mightier
than the sword.
Heh. Such a brilliant quote.
Polnareff: What are you
trying to say, exactly?
Hol horse: That I have
a stand that shoots,
and a sword
simply can’t beat that.
Polnareff: So, what?
A peashooter?
( Laughing )
( Hol horse laughing )
Both: Prepare to die!
( Hol horse spits )
You underestimated me!
And now, polnareff, you’re dead!
Polnareff:
If I take off my armor...
I can knock down a bullet!
Wait. What the?!
That’s impossible!
It bypassed my sword! Oh, crap!
Hol horse:
The bullet is also my stand,
and underestimating me
just cost you your life.
Avdol: Polnareff!
( All gasp )
Polnareff: What? Avdol!
Avdol: I’ve been
worried about you,
and now look where you are!
Your ego will end you,
polnareff.
Polnareff:
You’re worried about me?
Damn you! You came here
to lecture me again?
Avdol: The enemy already knows
everything about you!
You said you’re a loner,
but from now on,
you won’t be able to win alone!
Hol horse: Hmph.
What bad timing
for an outsider to interfere.
Avdol: Polnareff, move!
The bullet’s coming back!
Go, magician’s red!
( Magician’s red shrieks )
Avdol: I’ll melt it down!
( Hol horse chuckles )
Joseph: Damn that avdol.
He went
after polnareff himself.
Kakyoin: Where are you,
Mr. Avdol, polnareff?
I have a terrible feeling.
Man: Hey, there’s a weird fight
going on over there!
( Avdol grunts )
The puddle...
- ( Flowing )
- Polnareff: What the?!
( Kakyoin gasps )
( Polnareff gasping )
Kakyoin: Mr. Avdol!
( Onlookers murmuring )
Hol horse: Man,
today must be my day.
My gun and centerfold’s mirror
don’t do very well against
avdol’s flames, you see.
We were sure he’d be
our most formidable enemy.
Talk about luck.
With him gone,
the game is in the bag!
Kakyoin: Mr. Avdol!
( Gasps )
H-he’s just hurt. That’s all.
It’s just a minor wound. See?
He’s going to start speaking.
He’ll open his eyes in a moment.
Right, Mr. Avdol? Right?
You’re going to wake up, right?
Mr. Avdol, you gotta wake up!
No, please! Mr. Avdol!
♪
( Gasps )
Kakyoin:
That seemed awfully easy.
It was too quick.
( Polnareff spits, grunts )
That’s what he gets
for lecturing people.
Look at him now.
Kakyoin: W-what did you say,
polnareff?
Mr. Avdol was worried about you.
Polnareff: Who asked him
for help? Because I never did.
He likes to meddle
in other people’s business,
but he’s slow as hell,
so they got him.
Guys like him just
get in the way and screw up.
That’s why I said
I was going it alone.
( Kakyoin gasps )
You bastard.
He saved your life.
How dare you?
Huh?
( Polnareff weeping )
I am sick of it...
Having people
up and die on me.
Kakyoin: Polnareff.
Polnareff: I’m so sick of it.
You hear me?!
♪
♪ All the old paintings
on the tomb ♪
♪ they do the sand dance,
don’t you know ♪
♪ if they move too quick
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re falling down
like a domino ♪
♪ all the bazaar men
by the nile ♪
♪ they got the money on a bet
♪ gold crocodiles
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they snap their teeth
on your cigarette ♪
♪ foreign types
with the hookah pipes say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian
♪ The blond waitresses
take their trays ♪
♪ they spin around,
and they cross the floor ♪
♪ they’ve got the moves
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ you drop your drink
♪ then they bring you more
♪ all the school kids
so sick of books ♪
♪ they like the punk
and the metal band ♪
♪ when the buzzer rings
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re walking
like an Egyptian ♪
♪ all the kids
in the marketplace say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian