Narrator: Now with
a new set of wheels,
jojo and crew
head north from varanasi
to the nation of Pakistan.
Kakyoin: We’re about to hit
the indo-Pakistani border.
I guess it’s time
to say goodbye to India.
Joseph: You know,
I had mixed feelings
about the country at first,
but now I actually kind of miss
the hustle and bustle
of Calcutta
and frenetic chaos
of the Ganges.
( Jotaro scoffs )
Polnareff: I’ll be coming
back again one of these days.
I owe it to avdol
to give him a proper burial.
( Jotaro sighs )
( Joseph sighs )
( Kakyoin sighs )
Mr. Avdol.
Polnareff: The road’s
getting narrower.
Kakyoin: Hmm?
( Car engine revs )
( Polnareff coughs )
Quit driving so slow, idiot!
Out of the way!
I’m gonna pass the guy.
Kakyoin: Polnareff, calm down.
( Polnareff laughs )
This four-wheel drive is great.
Joseph: You know,
that crazy maneuver of yours
might have just damaged
that poor car.
Polnareff: Yeah. Your point?
Joseph: I’m saying we
don’t need any more trouble now.
I’m wanted because of
what happened in varanasi.
I’d like to get
across the border in one piece.
( Polnareff gasps )
( All grunt )
Kakyoin: What’s up?
Why’d you stop?
Joseph: I told you.
A crash could be disastrous.
Polnareff: I know that.
Just look who’s standing there.
( Anne humming a tune )
( Jotaro scoffs )
Good freakin’ grief.
Anne: Hey.
Long time no see, guys.
Got room for one more?
( All gasp, stammer )
( Car engine revving )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Anne: I mean, come on.
I’m a girl.
Soon i’ll be doing girl things
like wearing a bra
and doing my nails
to get the attention of boys.
I’d look pathetic
wandering around the world
when i’m that age.
This is the only chance I have
to be free and see the world.
Polnareff: Mm.
Anne: Know what I mean?
Look, I feel bad
for lying about going to see
my dad in Singapore, but let’s
just forget about that.
( Car horn honking )
Jotaro: Hey,
it’s that car we passed.
Looks like he’s in a hurry.
Joseph: Let ’em pass,
okay, polnareff?
Polnareff: Yeah.
( Car engine revs )
Polnareff: What the hell?
( All coughing )
Polnareff:
What’s he trying to do?
I let you pass.
Now hurry up, and go already!
Kakyoin: He’s probably angry
about your maneuver,
and these are
the consequences.
Jotaro: So did you get a look
at the driver’s face?
Polnareff: No. The windows
were covered in thick dust.
Couldn’t see a thing.
Jotaro: Neither could I.
Couldn’t be.
Joseph: Be very careful,
polnareff.
Polnareff: Hmm?
Heh. Now he’s wants me to pass.
Looks like the fool’s realized
how shitty
that piece of junk is.
You should have stayed behind me
the first place, dumb-ass.
Comin’ through!
( Gasps )
- What?!
- ( Truck horn honks )
( Polnareff screams )
Where’d that come from?!
Kakyoin: No use. Hold on.
Jotaro: Star platinum!
Polnareff: That was close.
( Sighs ) If it weren’t
for star platinum’s power,
we would have been crushed
beneath that like a tin can.
Joseph: He’s gone.
Where did that blasted car go?
Jotaro: Looks like
it just kept going.
I think the driver could have
been one of the stand users.
Then again, it could have
just been some sick bastard.
Of course
he’s one of dio’s lackeys.
We were almost roadkill,
for god’s sake.
Kakyoin: Then why didn’t he
simply attack us with his stand
when he had the chance?
- ( Car engine starts )
- Joseph: Anyway,
we’ve gotta keep heading
to Pakistan. Be on guard.
If someone comes after us again,
we’ll make ’em eat our dust.
Polnareff: Damn straight.
Kakyoin: What should we do
about that truck?
Star platinum left it a wreck.
It won’t be going anywhere.
Jotaro: That’s easy.
We pretend we never saw it.
Let’s get going.
♪
Anne: He’s so cool.
( Car engine revving )
Joseph: A roadside tea stand.
A break would do us some good.
If we take our time,
we may avoid running into
that crazy driver.
♪
( Rollers squeaking )
Joseph: What is that stuff?
Shopkeeper:
Fresh sugar-cane juice.
Care for a glass?
Joseph sure. Why not?
Mm.
What?!
( Gasps )
( Others gasp )
Polnareff: I-it’s him.
That car’s here!
Joseph: Hey, tell me something.
Who’s the owner of that car
parked over there?
Come on. Spill it!
Shopkeeper:
Uh, i’m not sure, sir.
To be honest, sir,
I didn’t notice it there.
Kakyoin: Our driver
isn’t just going
to come out and announce it.
Polnareff: He’s messing with us.
Joseph: Yeah.
Then, I guess this leaves us
with only one option,
right, jotaro?
Jotaro: Yeah.
Poor innocent bastards.
Customers: Huh?
Jotaro: We’ll just
beat them all down.
( Kakyoin gasps )
( Customer grunting )
Kakyoin: Hey, jotaro,
this is crazy.
Mr. Joestar, not you, too!
Polnareff: Pretty suspicious mug
you got there. Was it you?
Customer #2: Wha?! Not me!
( Car door closes )
- All: Huh?
- ( Car engine revving )
Polnareff: That slippery bastard
just played the lot of us,
didn’t he?
Joseph: Damn it.
Did anyone see his face?
Kakyoin: No.
What is he trying to do?
He could be
just some madman with a car,
or he could be
trying to kill us.
( Polnareff growls )
We need
to take care of this crap.
I won’t rest until I catch him
and get to the bottom of this.
Not to mention
we owe him payback
for the truck that
almost hit us earlier.
( Men gasping )
♪
( Tires skidding )
( Car engine revs )
Polnareff: Damn it.
For a piece of shit,
that car can
really get up and go.
♪
Kakyoin: That’s strange.
According to the map,
we should be running parallel
with train tracks or something.
Polnareff: Who the hell cares?
We’ll catch up soon anyway.
- ( Car engine revs )
- Polnareff: That bastard!
I’m gonna nail him
once we round this curve.
( Gasps )
A dead end! That’s impossible!
Joseph: Where the hell’d he go?
He’s gone.
Polnareff: Did he
just drive off the cliff?
Kakyoin: There’s no way he could
cross the suspension bridge.
- ( Crash )
- ( Car engine revs )
Men: What?!
( Anne gasps )
Joseph: I-it’s him.
He keeps pushing us.
Kakyoin: How the hell
did he get behind us?
- ( Polnareff grunts )
- ( Tires squealing )
Damn. How much horsepower is
that piece of junk running with?
Damn it.
It’s like fighting a tank!
( Engines revving )
( Yells )
It’s no use. Everyone, get out!
It’s our only chance.
Kakyoin: Polnareff,
what are you doing?!
You can’t get out of the car
until the rest of us
are clear first.
You have to hold down the brake.
Polnareff: Huh?
S-s-sorry.
( All yelling )
( Driver chuckles )
Kakyoin: Hierophant green!
Joseph: Stop!
Hierophant
isn’t nearly strong enough
to support this kind of weight!
You’ll be torn to shreds!
Kakyoin: Mr. Joestar,
with all due respect,
I am aware of my own abilities.
I am not a fool.
Joseph: Ah, I get it.
You used the car’s winch
instead of just brute strength.
Jotaro: Heh. Not bad, kakyoin.
I got a question for you.
You like sumo?
Especially deadlocks
at the edge of the ring?
Star platinum: Ora!
Jotaro: It’s exciting,
isn’t it?!
Star platinum: Ora!
♪
( Both groan )
Kakyoin: Yeah.
I’m a fan of sumo.
But in sumo,
it’s against the rules
to punch your opponent.
Jotaro: Hmm.
Suggests he used a stand attack.
I think it’s safe to say
he’s just some weirdo
with an ax to grind.
Polnareff: Yeah, either way,
he’s a goner after that fall.
Heh. I guess
what goes around comes around.
Anne: Yeah, but I still wonder,
how did it get behind us?
It was like watching a magician
or something.
It’s so strange.
( Radio static )
Man: Actually, little girl,
it’s not strange at all.
( All gasp )
Polnareff: The radio!
He’s coming through the am-fm.
Man: I was able to do that,
because it’s my stand, joestar.
Joseph: What?!
He knows my name,
so that confirms it.
He’s an enemy stand user.
Kakyoin: Where is he?
Could he really be
sending a signal
- from the car down there?
- Polnareff: No way!
Do you see
the wreck down there?!
Jotaro: No. That old jalopy
could very well be a stand.
You remember the boat stand?
This may be a repeat.
Stand user:
Behold the wheel of fortune.
My stand will lead you
to your maker.
Joseph: The wheel of fortune?
( Rumbling )
Kakyoin: What the--
an earthquake?
Polnareff:
I’ve got a bad feeling.
Joseph: Everybody,
get in the car!
Jotaro: No! Stay back!
Don’t go anywhere near it!
Polnareff: Couldn’t be.
Below us!
( All yelling )
( All groan )
♪
Polnareff: Impossible!
It burrowed up
through the ground!
All right,
I think it’s pretty obvious
that car is actually a stand.
Kakyoin: Looks like the stand’s
user is inside the car.
Polnareff: What the hell?!
Kakyoin: Now what is it doing?
Joseph: It’s like it’s alive!
( Engine revving )
Polnareff: It’s heading
straight for us!
( Jotaro chuckles )
If it’s a duel you want,
i’m happy to oblige.
Joseph: Don’t do it, jotaro!
Don’t fight it yet,
not until we know
what that stand’s power is!
( Jotaro grunts )
- ( Gags )
- Men: Jotaro!
Jotaro: Impossible.
I couldn’t see it.
What the hell
did he shoot at me,
and how the hell did he--
( stand user laughs )
Don’t even know
what hit you, eh?
( Laughs )
You’ll soon find out,
the moment you croak, that is!
Kakyoin: Jotaro!
( All groan )
Joseph: Jotaro!
Polnareff! Kakyoin!
( Anne screams )
( Polnareff gags )
Damn! What the hell is this?
The wounds aren’t deep,
but they sting like hell!
Kakyoin: I can’t see it at all.
I thought the car
threw something at us,
but there’s nothing
inside our wounds.
What the hell is going on here?!
Joseph: Jotaro,
are you all right?
Jotaro: Don’t worry about me,
old man.
I don’t know what the hell
he’s hurling at us,
but he’s got damn good aim.
Stand user:
I’ll pulverize your legs
so you can’t move
and then run you over!
Joseph: Everyone,
run between the boulders!
Stand user:
Stop running away, you cowards!
- Kakyoin: What?
- Stand user: What are you?
Roaches?
Joseph: Oh, no!
He’s digging his way through!
Kakyoin: And we’re
no match for him in here.
Polnareff: What a freak.
He’s acting like
some stupid musclehead
who got cut off in traffic and
flew into a fit of road rage.
Jotaro: Just keep running.
( Anne gasps )
Wait! Come back!
I can’t keep up!
( Screams )
Yeah, okay,
so I ran away from home!
I’m a good-for-nothing drifter
that nobody loves!
I’m gonna die!
Jotaro: Good grief.
If you have time
to say all that crap,
you can run away,
you damn little brat.
Anne: I love you
so much, jotaro!
( Sobbing )
( Stand user laughs )
Go ahead and climb.
There’s no path left
for you to take,
no way to escape,
no way to survive,
and, last but certainly
not least, no future!
Because this wheel of fortune
is going to grind you
into mincemeat
and splatter you
all over these boulders!
I’ll paint this mountain red
with your guts!
Jotaro: Hmm.
Joseph: Oh, no!
Kakyoin: It’s climbing
up the cliff.
Polnareff: Is there
anything this car can’t do?
Jotaro: Ah, good grief.
Looks like the time
to fight him’s now.
The rest of you, stay back.
He’s mine.
Once he climbs up here,
the car’s underside’ll be bare.
Then we’ll see
just how strong this thing is.
Kakyoin: I get it.
Once its underside’s exposed,
we may be able to attack it.
( Rocks crunching )
( Jotaro yells )
( Stand user laughs )
You’re pretty fast there,
jotaro, but not too bright.
( Jotaro yells )
Stand user: Your bodies reek,
and you haven’t even noticed.
Try paying attention!
( Jotaro gasps )
Kakyoin: Come to think of it,
I guess I did smell gasoline.
( Polnareff sniffs )
Oh, no. It’s coming from us.
Our bodies smell
like a gas station.
Kakyoin: That’s what
it was shooting, gasoline.
It was shooting
small amounts of it
at high speed like bullets.
Incredible.
Polnareff: This is nuts!
So he wasn’t trying to wound us.
He was dousing our bodies
with gasoline.
We’re covered in the stuff!
( Jotaro groans )
Stand user: Looks like
you finally caught on,
but it’s too late now.
Now all you need
is a little jolt.
Jotaro: What?!
- ( Men gasp )
- ( Anne screams )
Jotaro!
( Jotaro screaming )
Joseph: Jotaro!
Kakyoin: Mr. Joestar, stay back!
We’re soaking
with gasoline, too.
It’s too dangerous.
( Stand user laughs )
Joseph: Jotaro!
Stand user: I win.
Your Valiant hero
finally bit the dust.
( Laughing )
Jotaro: Is that so?
And who exactly
would replace me, jotaro kujo?
( Stand user gasps )
Huh?!
♪
Jotaro: Let me guess.
You thought it’d be you,
you road-hog?
( Stand user gasps )
You burrowed into the ground
with star platinum,
so the only thing
that burned up was your jacket!
( Jotaro scoffs )
A little parting wisdom.
What you said earlier
about paths...
Was dead wrong.
You see, in life,
you have to forge your own path.
No one can do it for you.
So i’ll offer you some guidance.
( Stand user whimpers )
Jotaro: But first you have
to go through a little pain.
( Star platinum yelling )
Stand user: I-i’m being crushed.
Anne: Go, jotaro!
( Star platinum yelling )
Ora!
( Stand user yells )
Jotaro: That is how it’s done.
See? You just paved
your own path.
Congrats on being
a fast learner.
Here ends the lesson.
♪
( Stand user screams )
Kakyoin: What an odd guy.
His arms are
the size of boulders,
and yet everything else
is so small.
Talk about a bluff.
( Stand user whimpering )
( Screams )
Polnareff: Hello.
Going somewhere?
Stand user: Please,
don’t kill me.
I’m just in this
for the money, honest.
( All laughing )
( Wheel of fortune squeaking )
All: Huh?
Joseph: Oh,
would you look at that?
I can’t believe
the stand was disguising
such a small car
that entire time.
Kinda reminds me
of a fluffy little sheep
that just had
all of its wool shorn off.
( Sheep bleats )
What a pathetic hunk of junk.
( All laughing )
( Stand user gasping )
Joseph: Well, then, let’s take
his car across the border.
Only fair,
since he smashed ours.
Kakyoin:
It’s pretty beat-up, though.
I wonder
if it’ll last that long.
Stand user: Help! Help!
Jotaro: And you’re
on the next flight to Hong Kong
once we find an airport.
Anne: Aw, no! Why?!
Polnareff: Shut up!
Don’t you understand that you’re
in the way, you little brat?
( Car clunks )
Joseph: Uh, we might
not make it that far.
Stand user: Help!
( Enyaba sobbing )
( Sobbing continues )
My seven assassins have all
been defeated, and so easily.
How could they
be crushed like that?
The shame!
I cannot bear to face lord dio.
( Wails )
Damn you! Curse you, polnareff!
Curse kakyoin!
Curse jotaro
and his wretched grandfather.
( Screams )
I, enyaba, shall be
your next and final opponent!
I will fight
with my very own stand,
the stand of justice!
♪
♪ All the old paintings
on the tomb ♪
♪ they do the sand dance,
don’t you know ♪
♪ if they move too quick
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re falling down
like a domino ♪
♪ all the bazaar men
by the nile ♪
♪ they got the money on a bet
♪ gold crocodiles
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they snap their teeth
on your cigarette ♪
♪ foreign types
with the hookah pipes say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian
♪ The blond waitresses
take their trays ♪
♪ they spin around,
and they cross the floor ♪
♪ they’ve got the moves
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ you drop your drink
♪ then they bring you more
♪ all the school kids
so sick of books ♪
♪ they like the punk
and the metal band ♪
♪ when the buzzer rings
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re walking
like an Egyptian ♪
♪ all the kids
in the marketplace say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian