♪
( Joseph panting )
( All panting )
Joseph: How could this
have happened?
I can’t believe...
We totally fell for it.
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
Narrator: Having managed to halt
the lovers’ horrifyingly
invasive attack,
jotaro and company
choose to avoid
the political unrest
in Iran and Iraq
and instead cross
the arabian sea at Karachi
to arrive
in the United Arab Emirates.
Man: Now then, if you’d be so
kind as to sign this document,
everything
will be squared away, sir.
Joseph: Hmm.
Right here, yes?
♪
Polnareff: Man, oh, man.
You know, if a pretty girl
like you asked me to,
I might even be inclined
to buy them a car.
Woman: My, aren’t you sweet?
Polnareff: How would you feel
about the two of us
having dinner sometime?
- ( Gasps )
- Joseph: Sorry, polnareff.
I hate to interrupt when
you’re obviously so busy, but...
Polnareff: Mr. Joestar!
Joseph: Come on.
It’s time to leave.
Polnareff: Seriously,
try not to mess with the hair.
Do you know how hard it is
to make it look this good?
Joseph: As if anybody
cares about your hairdo.
- ( Polnareff sighs )
- Joseph: You’re driving.
Polnareff: Right-o.
Au revior, mademoiselle.
( Woman chuckles )
Polnareff: Hey, Mr. Joestar,
I don’t get why we’re riding
in such a fancy, expensive car
in this Sandy death trap.
Wouldn’t it be better for us
to get an off-road vehicle
instead?
( Joseph laughs )
Oh, there’s a method
to my madness.
Polnareff: C’est magnifique!
This country’s amazing.
Are you guys seeing
what I am here?
It’s like every house is
a crazy mansion or something.
Joseph: Yeah.
In Tokyo,
a house like one of these,
would cost
three or four billion yen.
However, for most people
in this country,
it’s standard living.
It wasn’t but 20 years ago
that this place
was a barren desert,
though, thanks
to a thriving oil industry,
it’s grown into a playground
for the rich.
Polnareff: The sun is merciless,
but at least
with air conditioning,
it’s perfectly comfortable
inside the car,
so no complaints here.
( Kakyoin sighs )
Huh?
Jotaro: What’s wrong, kakyoin?
Kakyoin: It’s nothing.
I was just thinking
about how open it is here.
I know we could spot
anyone following us,
but I just can’t shake
the feeling
that there’s someone
out there watching us.
Polnareff: Yeah,
can’t say that I blame you.
Joseph: Well, back to business.
I’ve given a bit of thought
to the route we should take.
About 100 kilometers northwest
is a village called yarpline.
The desert and mountains
make taking a direct route
near impossible.
It normally takes two days
to reach by car,
so to expedite the travel time,
the locals use a cessna
to get there.
If you want my opinion,
we should go to the village
and buy a cessna
in order to cross
the vast Saudi arabian desert.
You know, i’ve been apprehensive
about getting
anywhere near a plane.
If a stand user attacked
and the plane went down,
we’d be putting innocent lives
in harm’s way,
but if we had a cessna,
I could be the pilot.
We’d be able to save
a couple of days for sure.
Jotaro: Flying in a cessna
with a man who’s been
in three plane crashes,
yeah, that seems
like a perfect idea to me.
( Joseph groans )
That comment notwithstanding,
our priority
should be crossing the desert
and hightailing it
to the village of yarpline.
It’ll take us one day
on camelback.
( Polnareff gasps ) Camelback?
A cessna is one thing,
but on camelback?
I’ve never ridden a camel
in my life!
( Joseph laughs )
Just leave everything to me.
I know these creatures well,
and i’ll teach you
how to ride them.
You boys sit back,
and watch the magic happen.
( Camels grunting )
Man: You want camels, you say?
Sure, I have them, but they’re
gonna cost you, my friend,
and they need a gentle touch.
Joseph: We’re kind of in
a life-or-death situation here,
so we need them,
whatever it takes.
As for payment, how about
a trade for that car?
( Men gasp )
Man: I couldn’t possibly accept
such a generous offer!
Polnareff: Yeah, Mr. Joestar!
And besides, you literally
just bought that car!
Joseph: What other reason
did you think I had
to buy such
a fancy, expensive car?
It’s true an off-road vehicle
would perform better here,
but we’re not in the big city.
We can’t just write a check
in this place,
and cash isn’t accepted here.
In my experience,
trading is far more effective
in places such as these.
If you try to buy
safety for cheap
in a time of emergency,
you’ll find yourself
even worse off in the end.
Besides, I don’t know about you,
but I think we’ve
suffered enough already.
- Hey, mister!
- Man: Huh?
Joseph: I take it
this seals the deal?
Oh, hey, you know what?
To make things
a little more even,
i’d like the water
in those tanks, too.
Man: Huh?
Joseph: It’s the most
important thing
when you’re in the desert.
Man: But the water
isn’t nearly as valuable
as your car, sir.
You sure are an odd one.
You know that, sir?
( Joseph laughs )
All right, everyone.
Let’s get ready, shall we?
Crossing the desert
will be no easy task.
Brace yourselves, men!
( Camel grunts )
( Polnareff gags )
Merde! That stinks!
Hey, Mr. Joestar, how the heck
are we supposed to get
on one of these things?
It’s, like, three meters tall!
Joseph: Allow me to demonstrate
the proper way to mount a camel.
You have to make them sit first,
and then you get on.
( Camel grunting )
( Joseph grunting )
Like I said, make them sit,
and then get on.
You see? Just like this!
You make ’em sit,
and then you get on ’em!
( Grunting )
Give me a minute! Any second,
this beast is gonna sit
and let me saddle up.
( Grunting )
Hey! Sit down, would you?!
Damn it, you stubborn animal!
Polnareff: Mr. Joestar,
you have ridden
one of these before,
haven’t you?
Joseph: I will have you know
that i’ve watched
"Lawrence of Arabia"
three times now
from start to finish!
I know all too well
how to ride a camel!
Although, two of those times,
I slept through half of it.
Polnareff: You learned
to ride from a movie?!
So you’re saying you’ve never
actually ridden one before?
( Joseph groans )
( All sigh )
Joseph: The saliva
makes great sunscreen.
The more you know...
( Laughs )
Listen up.
When you’re handling an animal,
it’s absolutely imperative to
understand exactly how it feels,
and I mean exactly.
Here. Doesn’t this yummy apple
look absolutely scrumptious?
It’s really good!
Come on. Come on.
There’s a good boy.
( Chuckles )
You see?
I made the camel sit down.
If you just take the time
to get inside its head,
it’ll sit down for you for sure!
- ( Laughs )
- ( Jotaro sighs )
Joseph: Whoa! I did it!
Whoa. It’s so high
off the ground.
By the way, did you know
camels can close their nostrils
to keep the sand out?
And before I forget,
you’re forbidden
from making stupid camel jokes.
Is that understood?
Your turn. Now you greenhorns
get to learn the finer points
of riding a camel.
Listen up.
The first thing you need to know
is that camels don’t walk
anything like horses.
The front and back legs
on either side
move forward together,
so these things can sway a lot,
but don’t let that
throw you off.
If you find a way to ride
with the camel’s rhythm,
I know you’ll be just fine.
For example--
- yah! Hey, wait!
- ( Camel grunting, clopping )
You’re going too fast!
Slow down!
Listen to me, damn it!
Yah! I didn’t tell you
to go that way!
- Yaah!
- ( Thud )
Okay, then.
Now that everyone’s
gotten the hang
of mounting and
riding their camels,
( all groan )
Joseph: All right, we have
a desert to get through!
The time has arrived, men!
Onward toward the northwest!
Hey, now!
Wait just a minute! Hey!
♪
( Kakyoin grunts )
Something’s wrong.
Polnareff: Huh?
Kakyoin: I still haven’t been
able to shake the feeling
that someone out there
is watching us.
Polnareff: Hmm?
Kakyoin, don’t you think
you might be worrying
a bit too much?
I mean, the palm leaves
will erase our tracks.
Plus, we can see for kilometers
in all directions.
If someone were here, we’d know.
Jotaro: Actually,
I think he’s onto something.
I feel some sort
of presence, too.
Joseph: Hey, jotaro,
why don’t you go take a look?
How about it? Do you see
anything suspicious out there?
Jotaro: No, nothing,
nothing whatsoever.
Even so, something’s
not right here, but what is it?
( Polnareff swallows )
Hey, let’s hurry up and go.
Joseph: Yeah.
Let’s get as far away as we can.
We’ll keep pressing forward
until the sun
goes down this evening,
then stop to pitch our tents.
It’s much too dangerous
for us to travel at night.
Polnareff: I only wish we could
get out of this freaking heat.
Just look at this.
It’s reading 50 degrees celsius.
Joseph: Yeah,
it is hot out here.
But then again,
the weather is at its hottest
right around now.
Huh? 8:00?
Wha?
Jotaro, check your watch.
What time does it say?
Jotaro: Hmm?
It’s 10...Past 8:00.
( Gasps )
Hey, old man!
Joseph: My watch is correct.
We lost track of time,
but what the hell’s going on?
According to my watch,
it’s past 8 P.M.
( Both gasp )
Joseph: So why
isn’t the sun setting?
Polnareff: This is impossible.
The thermometer is jumping
to 60 degrees celsius!
♪
Kakyoin: No, the sun isn’t
setting at all. It’s actually...
Polnareff: It’s actually
rising higher in the west!
Joseph: Wait. Could it be
that that sun is really...
Joseph: A stand?
Joseph: I don’t understand how
such a thing is even possible.
How could this sun
actually be a stand?
Quickly, take cover
behind those rocks!
Polnareff: How the hell
could that sun be a stand?!
We’re such fools.
How did we miss this?!
Kakyoin: I knew that we
were being watched,
but I never thought this is
why I couldn’t see our stalker.
Polnareff: At this rate,
that sun is gonna burn all day--
no, all night long.
Ah,  nom de dieu!
It’s going to roast us like
a bunch of rotisserie chickens.
We’re totally screwed!
Joseph: Yeah,
though I doubt
it’ll take that long.
The thing is
a sauna can dangerously
raise the body’s temperature
in minutes.
Polnareff: Okay, then,
how do we fight it?
C’est des conneries!
It’s 70 degrees celsius!
And to add insult to injury,
we can’t tell
if the stand is close or not!
The distance is
impossible to judge!
Jotaro: Our only option here
is to quickly take out
the stand user.
Joseph: Indeed, the user.
He has to be nearby.
We have to find him.
He must have a way
to conceal himself,
and somehow he’s been
following us all this time.
Polnareff: Hang on a minute.
What if it’s like the lovers
we encountered in Pakistan?
Maybe this guy has a stand
he can use from far away.
Joseph: That’s not
the case this time.
Sure, a weak stand can be
controlled from a distance,
but this sun is just too strong.
The energy it’s emitting
is incredible!
The stand user has to be nearby.
♪
Jotaro: Hey, check it out.
The camels
are starting to collapse
from exposure to the heat.
Kakyoin: And this waiting
isn’t getting us anywhere.
I’ll use hierophant to do some
reconnaissance around the area.
Joseph: Kakyoin.
Kakyoin: I’m only searching
for the stand’s rough location.
Once we know how far away
it actually is,
we might just be
able to locate the user.
20 meters. 40 meters.
60 meters. 80 meters.
100--( Gasps )
Jotaro: Something’s not right.
Kakyoin,
have hierophant come back!
Polnareff: There’s something’s
coming right at us!
Kakyoin: Before that happens,
emerald--( Grunts )
Joseph: No! Kakyoin!
Joseph: The camel!
( Polnareff yells )
You bastard!
( Star platinum yells )
Jotaro: I’m gonna bust a hole
in the ground,
so everybody get in!
Star platinum: Ora!
♪
( All panting )
Joseph: You okay, kakyoin?
Kakyoin: Yes, I am.
I was in the middle
of initiating my emerald splash,
so that protected me
from any major damage.
More concerning
is this intense heat.
I feel like it’s
gonna drive me insane.
Polnareff: Did any of you notice
that attack
was perfectly aimed at us?
And that could only mean that
the enemy has been watching us.
But from where? Where is he?
Joseph: Polnareff,
keep your voice down.
If you keep shouting,
the enemy will find us.
Just lay low for now.
We’ll sit tight for a while
and see what happens next.
Hmm?
( Gasps )
Oh, shit!
♪
( All panting )
Joseph: Things can’t
go on like this.
Come on. Think, damn it.
It’s time for this old-timer
to take the bull by the horns.
But this isn’t
the most ideal spot.
I can’t even use
my best technique.
It’s crucial that I
get more information.
Jotaro.
♪
Yah!
Son of a bitch!
Where the hell are you?!
How are you watching us?!
Are you invisible or something?!
Show yourself, you coward! Damn!
♪
( Kakyoin laughing )
Joseph: Huh?
Joseph: Hey, kakyoin,
what’s the matter?
( Kakyoin laughing )
Joseph: Kakyoin!
What the hell
are you laughing about?
Hey, snap out of it already.
Control yourself, man.
- ( Jotaro chuckling )
- Joseph: Huh?
( Jotaro and kakyoin laughing )
Joseph: J-jotaro!
This is happening to you, too?
( Gasping )
( Polnareff laughing )
Joseph: P-polnareff, no!
Not you, too.
( All laughing )
Joseph: Oh, my god, no!
They’ve all lost it!
This damn heat has driven
them all completely insane!
I have my sanity,
but what can I do?
Hey, jotaro!
Get ahold of yourself, man!
You have to settle down!
You need to listen to me,
jotaro.
Sometimes things get rough,
but when they do, you have
to remain in control. Eh?
Kakyoin: Please,
please don’t get
the wrong idea about this,
Mr. Joestar.
Have a look at that rock
over there.
It’s large enough for someone
to hide behind. Don’t you agree?
Joseph: Eh?
Joseph: What?
I don’t follow you.
Kakyoin: Oh, you will.
Now take a look at the rock
that’s sitting
on the opposite side.
Joseph: Opposite side, huh?
Um...
You still don’t see it, sir?
Have another look.
There’s a rock that’s
shaped exactly the same way,
but it’s on the opposite side.
The shadow is also reversed,
which means...
( Polnareff laughs )
What a stupid trick!
Jotaro: Move.
Stay here, old man.
Joseph: Jotaro!
If you go out there now,
you’re all but asking
for the enemy to attack you!
It’s dangerous!
( Jotaro scoffs )
♪
Star platinum: Ora!
- ( Man yelps )
- ( Joseph gasps )
How’d a hole
suddenly appear in thin air?!
Jotaro: Good grief, old man.
You really are pathetic.
Well, i’ll just assume
that the intense heat
was too much for you,
or else i’d find it very hard
to believe
that you’re my grandfather.
Kakyoin: Since we defeated
the enemy stand,
night’s finally fallen.
Or maybe I should say
it’s back to being night.
Polnareff: However you wanna
slice it, we’re safe at last.
Jotaro: Just how long do you
plan on hiding in that hole?
Joseph: Oh, yeah, right.
Jotaro: Good grief.
It’s finally
gotten dark around here.
Joseph: Well, what do you know?
It’s a mirror.
Kakyoin: And look at this.
Check out the little car
he’s got behind the mirror.
It looks like it’s rather comfy.
There’s even air conditioning.
Polnareff: Man, I had no clue
he was reflecting the desert
and tailing us from behind
in this nifty little thing.
He was smarter than I thought.
Jotaro: I see he has
a tank of water, too.
How about
we take it off his hands?
Polnareff:
Oh, and here’s a drink.
( Slurping )
( Sighs )
Joseph: Huh?
Let me understand all this.
You mean we’ve already
defeated the stand user?
There’s nothing else to do?
We don’t even know
this guy’s name,
but somehow we’ve already
made short work of his stand?
Kakyoin: Yes, you’ve hit
the nail on the head.
Jotaro: So this was
the sun card’s stand, huh?
At first,
he was pretty impressive,
but once we figured the guy out,
he actually kinda sucked,
didn’t he? Heh.
Kakyoin: So off
to our next destination.
It’s pretty chilly in the desert
at night, isn’t it?
Joseph: Hold your horses.
Traveling at night is dangerous.
If we’re not careful,
we could lose our way.
Polnareff: Yeah, and with
that idiot out of the way,
it’ll be sweet dreams tonight.
Ah-choo!
( All laughing )
Narrator: Ba-dum-tss.
♪
♪ All the old paintings
on the tomb ♪
♪ they do the sand dance,
don’t you know ♪
♪ if they move too quick
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re falling down
like a domino ♪
♪ all the bazaar men
by the nile ♪
♪ they got the money on a bet
♪ gold crocodiles
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they snap their teeth
on your cigarette ♪
♪ foreign types
with the hookah pipes say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian
♪ The blond waitresses
take their trays ♪
♪ they spin around,
and they cross the floor ♪
♪ they’ve got the moves
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ you drop your drink
♪ then they bring you more
♪ all the school kids
so sick of books ♪
♪ they like the punk
and the metal band ♪
♪ when the buzzer rings
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re walking
like an Egyptian ♪
♪ all the kids
in the marketplace say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian