♪
( Clattering )
( Polnareff gasps ) Is anyone
else here getting nervous?
Joseph: Try to stay calm.
Times like these require us
to keep our heads on straight
and be prepared.
Ooh. Putting this stuff on
with only one hand
is a lot harder
than I thought it’d be.
All right, before we leave,
has anyone here
ever scuba dived before?
- Polnareff: Not me.
- Jotaro: No.
Kakyoin: No, I haven’t.
Avdol: It won’t take long
for the high priestess
to locate us here.
You have to teach us
how to dive before she does.
Joseph: Try and
calm yourself, avdol.
You must never panic,
no matter what.
That is the most important rule
when scuba diving.
When you’re
traveling underwater,
for every ten meters
you go below the surface,
the corresponding pressure
increases along with you.
The surface pressure
starts at one atmosphere,
and since we’re
40 meters below the surface,
we’ll endure five atmospheres
of pressure.
If we surface too quickly,
the pressure’ll cause our lungs
and blood vessels to burst.
We have to rise slowly
so our bodies can adjust.
Since we’re nearing
the Egyptian coast,
it’s best to ascend
along the seafloor.
Okay, i’m letting the water in.
♪
Now pay very close attention.
What you’re looking at
is a regulator.
The valve inside
only allows air in from the tank
when you inhale.
The air you breathe out exits
through the piece on the left.
( Kakyoin breathes deeply )
Polnareff: Wait a second.
What about spit?
What happens if I need to drool
or have to hock a loogie
or something?
Joseph: Stuff like that just
comes out of the opening here.
By the way,
this should go without saying,
but we can’t talk underwater.
Instead, we’ll use hand signals.
Let’s keep things simple
and only use two.
When things are going smoothly,
we’ll use this to say, "okay."
But when they aren’t, use this.
Avdol: Mr. Joestar,
couldn’t we just use our stands
to communicate underwater?
Joseph: Huh? Oh, yeah.
I didn’t think about that.
Polnareff: Aww, man.
And I was just about to say
that I know
a really good hand signal.
♪
Kakyoin: He says,
"your underwear is showing."
Polnareff: Yeah, nice.
Joseph: We could be attacked
and killed at any time!
Stop fooling around,
and let’s go!
This room is about to be filled
to the brim with water.
Put on your masks and regulators
while you still have time.
( Polnareff gagging )
( All gasp )
Joseph: P-polnareff!
( High priestess laughs )
( Polnareff screams )
♪
( Singing in Japanese )
( Polnareff gagging )
Avdol: But when did it...
( High priestess chattering )
Kakyoin: That’s it.
The stand had already
integrated with the regulator.
Jotaro: That bastard.
( Polnareff gagging )
Jotaro: It’s gonna rip him
apart from the inside.
We’ve gotta drain the room
while we still can.
Avdol: It’s too late.
It must have been lying in wait
for just this moment.
( Polnareff screams )
Star platinum: Ora!
Jotaro: Damn it.
Avdol: It managed
to get inside polnareff.
Now it can attack him
without resistance.
( Polnareff gagging )
Avdol: What should we do?
Kakyoin: Hierophant green!
Joseph: Hermit purple!
Polnareff: What are you doin--
Joseph: I grabbed it before it
went too far down his throat.
Kakyoin: Me, too.
Let’s pull it out
before it transforms.
( Polnareff gagging )
Kakyoin: Success.
Jotaro: All right,
keep it just like that.
Avdol: Look! It’s transforming
into something else.
♪
Joseph: You gotta be kidding me.
It turned into a spear gun.
Hierophant green:
Emerald splash!
Polnareff: Silver chariot!
Let’s get moving.
Kakyoin: It’s already reloading.
Avdol: It doesn’t quit.
Kakyoin: H-hurry.
♪
Jotaro: Move it, old man.
Joseph: Yeah, i’m coming.
Kakyoin: That was
too close for comfort.
Joseph: It’s too soon
for us to relax,
especially since that bastard
knows exactly how to hit us
where it hurts most.
Avdol: Polnareff,
are you all right?
Polnareff: Yeah, i’ll be fine.
You guys saved my life
back there.
Merci beaucoup.
Wow, just look at how beautiful
it is down here.
This would’ve been a spectacular
place to visit on vacation.
Joseph: This isn’t time
to plan your next getaway.
We have to surface
before we run out of oxygen.
Kakyoin: Think we’re safe?
Avdol: I believe so.
The high priestess can transform
into metals and glass,
but it can’t take the form
of bubbles or fish,
so I doubt it’ll come after us.
Joseph: Just keep
your eyes peeled.
If it pursues us,
it’ll probably transform into
a screw on our gear to do it.
Be careful of moving pebbles
and stones, too.
Avdol: Hmm?
Look up there!
I think it’s a sea tunnel.
Joseph: We’re at seven meters.
We’ve finally reached
the Egyptian shore.
Avdol: We can swim along these
rocks to get to the surface.
♪
( High priestess growls )
( All gasp )
Jotaro: What?
Polnareff: Is that the...
Avdol: Yes,
it’s definitely the stand.
It merged with the seafloor,
and it’s gargantuan!
( All yelling )
Joseph: Damn!
It’s sucking us into its mouth!
( Jotaro groans )
Kakyoin: This is impossible!
( Polnareff yells )
Avdol: How is it so gigantic?
( Joseph yells )
( High priestess laughing )
Polnareff: What the hell?!
It was so small earlier.
What’s this stand’s power?
Merde, i’m so confused!
Rose: You boys
are so slow on the uptake.
Didn’t it ever cross your minds
that if the rocks are mineral,
it would mean the seabed
is mostly mineral as well?
Kakyoin: Yes, of course.
That’s why the stand
has suddenly gotten stronger.
It’s user must be nearby,
and i’d wager
she’s closer than we think.
Rose: You guessed it,
and to be more precise,
i’m seven meters
above you on the shore.
But since you’re about to be
ground to bits
by my high priestess,
you’ll never have the chance
to see my face.
So long.
- ( High priestess roars )
- ( Men yell )
♪
Kakyoin: It’s so dark in here.
I can’t tell what part
of the stand we’re in.
Joseph: Seems like we’re
still inside its mouth,
but luckily we weren’t sucked
down its gullet.
Rose: Yoo-hoo, jotaro.
Believe it or not,
you’re actually my type,
so this is going to be
as painful for me as for you,
but despite my feelings,
I still have to make
the high priestess digest you.
- Polnareff: Huh?
- Rose: How sad.
If only our encounter had been
under different circumstances.
- ( Polnareff whispering )
- Rose: But if I kill you,
lord dio will no doubt
shower me with praise,
- so don’t hate me.
- ( Jotaro groans )
Good grief. Do I have to?
Polnareff:
Would you just say it?
Come on.
Hurry up, and get on with it.
Avdol: Say what?
Joseph: Huh?
Kakyoin: Ah, I see.
Jotaro: It’s a shame
things turned out this way.
I would have liked to have seen
your face, if only this once.
You might have
been my type, too,
and if you were, well, I just
might have fallen for you.
( Rose sighs )
Polnareff: Oh, hey,
you know what, guys?
I bet she’s a beauty.
I can tell from
that gorgeous voice of hers.
Avdol: She comes across
as an elegant woman.
My fortuneteller’s instinct
senses it.
Kakyoin: Well, if you ask me,
she sounds
just like Audrey hepburn.
Joseph: Man, if I were
only 30 years younger.
- ( Rumbling )
- ( Rose groans )
( High priestess growls )
Rose: You bastards didn’t mean
a single word of that!
I’ll kill you all!
( Men yell )
Joseph: Holy shit!
Kakyoin: Everyone, look!
Joseph: What is that?
Kakyoin: It looks like a tongue,
the stand’s tongue to be exact.
Here it comes!
Rose: Jotaro!
( Jotaro groans )
Joseph: Jotaro!
♪
( Jotaro gags )
Avdol: No!
Jotaro’s going to land in--
Joseph: He--he landed
right on the molars.
Polnareff: Jotaro,
get out of there now!
Kakyoin:
You’re about to be crushed!
Star platinum: Ora!
Rose: Ooh!
You want to pit your strength
against mine, do you?
Jotaro: Damn,
what ridiculous power.
Rose: Oh, give up, jotaro.
Those teeth are
as hard as diamonds.
You’ll never
be able to break them.
It’s time for you
to meet your end.
Joseph: We have to save jotaro!
Rose: Stay out of my way!
Polnareff:
That damn tongue again!
Avdol: Magician’s red!
( Magician’s red squawks )
( Rose screams )
Joseph: We’re out of time!
We have to free him!
♪
( All gasp )
All: Jotaro!
Eeth
pulverized him.
Joseph: J-jotaro.
( Avdol groans )
We didn’t make it in time.
( Star platinum’s
muffled shouting )
( Joseph gasps )
( Shouting continues )
Joseph: Hmm? Hold on a sec.
I think I can hear something.
Avdol: It sounds like it’s
coming from rather far away.
Kakyoin: Listen again.
I think it’s getting closer.
Polnareff: Wait.
That voice belongs to...
( Star platinum yelling )
Polnareff: The teeth. It’s
coming from inside the teeth!
Joseph: Huh?
Everyone, get down,
and brace yourselves.
Polnareff: Huh?
( Star platinum yelling )
♪
Polnareff: Those teeth
were hard as diamonds,
but he managed
to punch his way out.
Joseph: Oh, my god!
And would you look at that?
He’s breaking the other teeth
while he’s at it.
Kakyoin: That showoff.
Avdol: His stand’s immense power
never ceases to amaze me.
Jotaro: Come on. I’m getting us
out of this hellhole.
( Star platinum yelling )
Ora!
Jotaro: Ah, good grief.
Well, you were right
about those teeth being sturdy,
but they weren’t sturdy enough.
Too bad.
I guess your so-called diamonds
were a little low on calcium.
♪
( Joseph panting )
You couldn’t pay me
to do that again.
Hmm?
( Rose gasping )
Joseph: Hey, there’s a woman
passed out over there.
Avdol: I assume it’s Rose,
the user of the high priestess.
Kakyoin: She doesn’t
seem dangerous.
Should we just leave her?
Polnareff: I think i’ll
go see if she’s hot or not.
From the looks of it,
she’s got a pretty nice body.
Let’s see.
Joseph: How’s it going
over there, polnareff?
( Polnareff yelps )
Nothing to see here, folks!
No comment whatsoever!
Trust me,
you don’t wanna see her.
Her teeth are all ugh,
so there’s no point in looking.
- Joseph: I see.
- Polnareff: Ugh!
♪
Avdol: It hasn’t been easy,
but we finally made it to Egypt.
Joseph: Indeed.
A trip that would have taken
a mere 20 hours by plane
ended up taking
a whopping 30 days.
Kakyoin: It’s been
quite the adventure.
We’ve gone inside a brain
and even inside our dreams.
Jotaro: Our dreams?
What do you mean, kakyoin?
Polnareff: Why are you
talking about dreams?
It’s morning. Wake up already.
Kakyoin: Oh, right.
You guys don’t remember that.
- Polnareff: Huh?
- ( Jotaro scoffs )
Whatever. Let’s go.
♪
Narrator: Four mysterious
and otherworldly stands
powered by the mystical
and symbolized by the tarot.
Joseph joestar
once described their journey
as "around the world
in 80 days."
From Tokyo to Hong Kong,
they faced tower of gray.
In southeast Asia, they tackled
dark blue moon and strength.
In Singapore,
they encountered ebony devil
and yellow temperance.
In Calcutta, India,
it was hanged man and emperor,
in varanasi, India, the empress,
and near the Pakistani border,
they fought wheel of fortune.
In the mountains of Pakistan,
they battled justice,
in Karachi, Pakistan,
the lovers,
in the desert of the united
arab Emirates, the sun,
and in Saudi Arabia, death 13,
on a small island
in the red sea, judgment.
And now, on the red sea floor,
they’ve just defeated
high priestess.
With several of dio’s assassins
vanquished,
they have finally
arrived in Egypt.
Only a few of the tarot cards
still remain.
But little do
jojo and company know
new threats lie ahead in Egypt
ready to take our heroes on.
♪
( Man grunts )
That’s...
One, two, three...
Nine.
There are nine in all,
both genders.
- ( Bubbling )
- Eh?
- ( Gasps )
- ( Splash )
What the--
what the hell was that?
Dio: Have the meddlesome flies
swarming around been swatted?
That speedwagon foundation,
for pity’s sake, I can’t
let my guard down for a minute.
( Chuckles )
I must say i’ve gotten
quite used to this body.
Tell me, Jonathan,
can you feel it?
Your descendants
are inching ever closer.
It can be so cruel
and unforgiving,
this wretched
little world of ours.
Suzie q: So that’s
what’s been going on.
Why didn’t you just tell me
jotaro was helping you
with your work?
- That’s fantastic.
- ( Joseph scoffs )
The boy still has a long way
to go, compared to me.
Suzie q: So this work
is important enough
for you to ask for help?
Joseph: That’s right. It’s
my most important mission yet,
and it’s imperative
that we don’t mess up.
But as long as we work together,
we should get it done
without too much trouble.
Suzie q: Hmm.
Say, Joseph,
could I speak to jotaro?
Joseph: Eh? Sure, but what do
you want to talk to him about?
Suzie q: Nothing much.
Is it wrong that I want to hear
my darling grandson’s voice?
Joseph: Well, no.
Jotaro, it’s for you.
Joseph: Hmm?
Hey, it’s me.
Suzie q: Grandpa told me
everything, jotaro.
Work hard, and take care
of your grandfather for me.
Jotaro: Will do.
Suzie q: I know in my heart
if you work together,
you joestar men can overcome
just about any hardship
that comes your way.
Jotaro: Eh?
Suzie q: I truly believe that.
Jotaro: Grandma Suzie, you...
Suzie q: What’s the matter?
You sound so serious
all of a sudden.
Jotaro: It’s nothing.
Suzie q: All right,
i’m hanging up.
I look forward to good news.
Ciao.
( Humming a tune )
- Rosas: Madam.
- Suzie q: Hmm?
Rosas: It’s hard
for me to believe it,
but at this point,
it’s already been 30 years
that i’ve worked
for the joestar family,
but I can honestly say
that we’ve never faced
something of this magnitude.
Suzie q: Oh, come now.
You’re overreacting.
Didn’t he say it was
just a little business trip?
Rosas: Ah. Well, I suppose so.
Suzie q: It’s so troublesome
when men act selfish
and refuse to tell us anything.
( Sighs )
But i’ve grown accustomed to it.
The joestar family has been
like this for an entire century.
I’m sure if she were here,
she’d say the same thing
and laugh it all off.
♪
Joseph: Hmm?
What’s the matter, jotaro?
Jotaro: Hmm?
It’s nothing. I’m fine.
Joseph: Hmm?
All right,
it’s time to head out.
It’s time for us joestars
to bring an end
to the ties that dio
has had with us for a century.
Jotaro: But we don’t
have to do it alone.
( Car horn honks )
Kakyoin: Hey, Mr. Joestar!
We got the car
that you asked us to buy!
Polnareff: Let’s hurry,
and hit the road.
Kakyoin: We should probably
get to where we’re going
before it gets too dark!
Jotaro: Well, old man?
Jotaro: Okay, you’re right.
Guess we’re pretty lucky, huh?
Polnareff: We’re gonna
leave you behind!
Joseph: Yeah, yeah,
hold your horses! We’re coming!
♪
Narrator: This is
the land of Egypt,
a nation that’s 97% desert.
However, thanks
to the blessings of the nile,
beautiful, fertile green
spreads across the entirety
of its riverbanks.
In addition to the culture
of the ancient Egyptians,
Egypt is also home
to persian, Greek,
Roman, Muslim,
and arabian cultures,
and all have left
their indelible marks.
What bizarre adventures
and challenges
await jotaro and the others
in this eternal land
as they continue
their perilous journey?
♪
♪ All the old paintings
on the tomb ♪
♪ they do the sand dance,
don’t you know ♪
♪ if they move too quick
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re falling down
like a domino ♪
♪ all the bazaar men
by the nile ♪
♪ they got the money on a bet
♪ gold crocodiles
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they snap their teeth
on your cigarette ♪
♪ foreign types
with the hookah pipes say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian
♪ The blond waitresses
take their trays ♪
♪ they spin around,
and they cross the floor ♪
♪ they’ve got the moves
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ you drop your drink
♪ then they bring you more
♪ all the school kids
so sick of books ♪
♪ they like the punk
and the metal band ♪
♪ when the buzzer rings
♪ oh, whey, oh
♪ they’re walking
like an Egyptian ♪
♪ all the kids
in the marketplace say ♪
♪ whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ ay, whey, oh, whey, oh
♪ walk like an Egyptian
♪