The morning of December sixteen.
It was so cold, and I mean cold,
that if you took an ice pick, plunged it into the ground,
you'd shatter the earth into a million pieces.
Shut up...
It's cold... cold, cold...
Hey, Kyon!
Wakey wakey!
Mom told me to tell you to make sure you eat breakfast.
And you'd better eat yours too, Shami!
Shami! Shami! Breakfast time for Shami!
Cold... So cold...
Stand.
Bow!
Thank you for the lesson!
That's all for today.
It was nice and warm up until the School Art Festival.
But when December hit,
the temperature dropped super fast,
like it was making up for lost time or something.
It felt like Japan just decided to skip Fall this year...
Or better yet, maybe the guy upstairs
confused the prayer for more business
with a spell to change the weather or something.
Siberian air mass...
Seriously, I know you have to stick to your route and all,
but you could skip us once in a while.
It's like the seasons are out of whack or something.
Oh, great. Now I'm worried about the environment.
Yeah, well, I might be worried,
but it's not like I'm gonna do
anything about it, too much work.
Hey, Koizumi.
Oh, hello there.
Class duty, huh?
That's right.
Hm?
You've got that worried look
on your face again. What's wrong?
Haruhi's sort of been hyped up all morning.
Oh? About the you-know-what?
You know it.
Come on, Koizumi. Hurry!
Right, coming.
Pardon me.
See ya.
The you-know-what, huh?
Oh, brother...
Man, everyday's been cold.
Tell me about it.
With all the exercise we're getting climbing this hill,
who needs gym class? They should just cancel it.
That will be the day.
You guys sound like a couple of old fogies.
Look at this, see? Not even a sweater!
Winter's perfect for me. I'll let the suckers have summer.
Where do you get your energy from?
Sprinkle some on me some time, would ya?
Hm?
Do either of you guys know what day it is today?
It's December the sixteenth.
What about it?
What do you mean "What about it"?
There's a week left before the
one day that's guaranteed to make
any person's heart dance with joy!
Oh, you mean the year-end assembly.
Yeah, I'm definitely looking forward to winter vacation.
No, no, no, not that! Come on, try and remember.
Eight days from now... An important day...
Hearts dancing with joy...
You know what day I'm talking
about just do the math. Eight days.
Humph, of course I know.
Ah, hey, Kyon! How's it going?
Hello there.
Miss Asahina, Miss Tsuruya, how are you?
What's up with your face today? You look all bummed out.
Young man, you'd better turn
that frown upside down, nyoron!
See you later, Kyon!
Sure. Bye.
I'll be there in a bit. I have to
take care of a couple of things first.
Oh, okay.
Do I know what's happening next week?
This so-called event that's making everyone freak out.
Of course I do.
It's easy when the person in the seat behind me
makes it her mission to keep track of such things.
She's the general manager of all the
trouble I've gotten into since April.
She's the root of all evil in the universe,
the person behind every threat to my existence.
Yeah... Her...
What am I doing? Miss Asahina isn't even in there.
Just you, Nagato?
Come on, heater, do your thing...
Kept you waiting, didn't I?!
Not at all.
Does any one have plans next week for Christmas Eve?
I freaking knew it.
I'm pretty sure you've got nothing going on, right, Kyon?
We all know you don't have much of a social life.
And I'm only asking because I
didn't want you to feel like a loser.
Yeah, what if I did have something going on?
Tell me what you're planning first!
You're free, I knew it.
How about you, Koizumi?
I bet you got a date with a girlfriend, don't ya?
It would be wonderful if that were indeed the case.
However, believe it or not,
my schedule prior to Christmas Eve is
completely open and flexible at present.
To tell the truth, I was getting a little worried
about how I was going to pass the time.
Liar! You made yourself free on purpose! Admit it!
Well, now, you don't have to worry about it!
Besides, this will be way better.
How about you, Mikuru?
You've probably got plans too,
like maybe someone ask you to go watch
the moment that rain turns to snow in the dead of night!
Suddenly, she's from the Showa era.
Actually, I don't have anything planned next week.
Dead of night?
You could go out with me, Miss Asahina.
Yuki?
Nothing.
Awesome!
Wow!
Okay then, it's settled!
Since nobody has plans for next week,
we're gonna throw an SOS Brigade Christmas Party!
As usual, if there're any objections,
you can file them after the event,
I promise I'll take them into consideration.
And as usual, she's doing whatever she wants.
She did ask if everyone had plans though.
I guess she's making a little progress.
Um, what are we going to do with this party?
That's exactly what we're going to figure out!
Today is the sixteenth,
so that gives us eight days to get ready
for the plan all the fun we're gonna have!
Anyway, I went ahead and picked up some stuff.
Check it out!
This will help everyone get into the Christmas spirit
and make this party the coolest thing we've ever done!
Oh, great, more knick-knacks!
Where did she find that junk anyway?
This will help brighten up our
drab little club room like never before!
Didn't you used to do this when you were a kid?
Yeah, well, I never really wanted to,
but every year I was forced to help
my little sister get her room all Christmas-up.
Even though she is eleven years old,
she still believes in Santa Claus.
And it looks I'll have to do it again for her this year.
You know, you could learn a lot from
your kid sister's pure and innocent heart.
You have to believe in a dream if
you wanna have one in the first place.
If you don't believe, even the
dreams that can come true won't!
You're wearing it now?
When in Rome, do as the Romans do.
When it's Christmas, it's only logical
that we follow the rules of Christmas!
Getting into the vibe is gonna be easy,
'cause everybody likes birthday parties.
And I know for a fact, when Mr. Christ
looks down and sees us all having fun,
it's gonna make him so happy!
Uh...
And who's gonna clean that up?
Me, that's who...
Uh-huh...
Sweet!
Not that I care, but if you look at
that from the outside, it's backwards.
I almost forgot!
I bought Mikuru a kind of early Christmas present.
Really? How you shouldn't have!
Tada!
Miss Suzumiya, please wait!
Whatever, come take it off!
I-I can do it myself, Don't…
I feel bad for Miss Asahina...
But as long as she lets Miss Suzumiya have a way,
I don't have to worry about anything worse happening.
Closed Space and Shinjin, is that right?
Those are the two things myself and the
organization fear more than anything else, for real.
Since the spring, the number of
occurrences has dropped considerably.
But we're still on high alert.
So they're still happening every now and then?
Of course. However, the phenomena now take
place exclusively between midnight and dawn.
One theory is that when she's
dreaming if she has a nightmare,
she creates Closed Space subconsciously.
Man, she's trouble when she's awake and when she's asleep.
No, not at all!
Ever since she started high school, it's been
my job to observe Miss Suzumiya's every action.
And at the beginning, I never would have imagined
I'd see her smiling and having fun like she is now.
The fact is, ever since she met you,
Miss Suzumiya's mental state has been
more stable than ever was in junior high.
Yeah, sure.
There's no doubt in my mind that Miss Suzumiya is changing
changing in a good way, of course.
And it's obvious that everyone around
her is also changing for the better.
I'm talking about you and me and Miss Asahina.
And probably Miss Nagato, too.
He picked up on that too, huh.
I'm surprised he noticed the little ways
in which Nagato's been changing recently.
Okay, come in!
Ow!
What're you doing, you pervert?!
I've dived and gone to heaven!
Oh, Goddess Asahina, shine your grace on me!
How dare you peep at Mikuru's panties like a creep!
I never thought in a million years you dare to do that!
You did it on purpose, didn't you?
Would you knock it off? I didn't
see anything. It was an accident!
Oh, okay then. I'm sorry I overreacted.
Wow, that's some outfit.
I hope that you don't think I'm being too forward here,
but I have to admit that costume suits you to a T.
Yeah.
You hear that! You're crazy cute, so stand
up straight and carry yourself with confidence.
Now you're the official Santa Poster-girl
for the SOS Brigade's Christmas Party!
It's an honor to be a sex symbol, don't you think?
I guess so...
Holy beings! This is way sexier than the maid outfit!
Well, there you have it. That's
how I spent December the sixteenth.
It's the morning of December the seventeenth.
A Christmas Party, huh?
Definitely sounds like something Suzumiya would pull.
And in the club room.
Just make sure the teachers don't find out about it.
Or you'll just cause trouble again.
So you're gonna come hang out or what?
Haha! You gotta be kidding!
Super sorry, Kyon, but I don't have got time
for one of your chintzy little get-togethers.
What's up with the creepy laugh, man?
Believe it or not, I've got plans.
Hanging out with your freaky
friends at the school on Christmas Eve.
Man, that's what losers do.
And I hate to break it to you
buddy, but I'm not a loser anymore.
Are you telling me you got a...
That's exactly what I'm telling you.
Christmas Eve, December twenty four.
If you happen to see my calendar,
I've got a big red heart drawn around it, baby!
Sorry, I can't make it, bro!
Totally sorry, yeah.
So, who's the unlucky girl?
She's a freshman at Kouyouen Academy.
Yeah, but I still have to figure out
where we're gonna go and what we're gonna do.
Decisions, decisions!
Kyon!
Hm?
Anyway, since we didn't have
anything better to do after school
we were corralled into helping with the decorations.
Humph!
I totally forgot about it this time,
but next year, we should put together
birthday parties for Buddha and Mohammad too.
We've gotta keep things fair and square.
It's sort of insincere throwing birthday
parties for folks you don't believe in.
Hey, what should we do about the food? Hotpot? Sukiyaki?
As long as it's not crab.
Getting the meat out of the shell is such a hassle.
Honestly I think every crab
should have a shell you can eat.
I mean it's called evolution.
And that would be the next logical step for them.
Why do you think they evolved
with shells in the first place.
News flash, natural selection isn't about
accommodating the appetizer of human beings.
Hey, Haruhi. I just noticed we're all out of tinsel.
Then go out and buy some more.
Who me?
Yes, you.
Whatever we decide to eat,
we should make a reservation with
a restaurant as soon as possible.
We might not get a table if we wait much longer.
Oh, don't worry about that! We'll eat here!
Huh?
In the club room? A hotpot?
Why not? We've got everything we need,
all that's left are ingredients!
But no alcohol allowed!
I swore I'll go my whole life without touching the stuff!
Hold it!
No open flames are allowed in this building.
So then we'll cook it in secret, it'll be more fun!
If any teachers or the student council come by,
I'll wow them with my incredible
awesome hotpot cooking skills!
And when they taste it, they'll be so
emotionally overwhelmed by the deliciousness.
They are bound to give us special
permission to cook in here whenever we want.
Nothing could possibly go wrong. My plan's perfect!
Okay, people, let's get cracking!
Decorating will help get us in the spirit!
We're gonna make this party the best ever!
For a prologue, that was way too long, I know.
But you really can't call it
anything else. Trust me on that.
Hey, Kyon.
This story starts here. Actually it starts tomorrow.
Maybe it started that night. Wait, maybe it started
whatever...
The next day, December eighteenth,
the wind blew down hard from the mountains
like it was trying to freeze everything in its path.
Something happened that pushed
me down into a sea of despair,
right down into the very pit of hell itself...
Just giving you a heads-up,
there's nothing funny about
what was gonna happen to me next.
Hey, Kyon! Wakey wakey!
Shami! Shami! It's breakfast time...
Yo, Taniguchi.
Hey, Kyon.
Huh?
Wow, you catch cold?
Yeah. I wanted to stay home
but my old man bitched me out of the house.
Must have hit you fast. You were all fired up yesterday.
I felt like crap yesterday too. Don't you remember?
I remember you going off about
your hot plans for Christmas Eve.
Well, make sure you get better fast.
You might not get another date
with that girl if you cancel…
Wait. What date?
I don't got any plans for Christmas Eve.
What about that girl from Kouyouen
academy you'll have a date with?
Don't tell me she broke up with you before your big night.
Seriously, guy, what the heck are you talking about?
I have no idea what you're saying.
That's weird. I guess his date
got cancelled for some reason.
I bet he's plan cool 'cause of all
the bragging he was doing yesterday.
And probably feels horrible.
Yeah, that's what's going on.
There'll be others.
Huh?
You know, you should come join
us for our party at the club room.
I'm sure we haven't reached the maximum capacity yet.
Party in the club room? What party?
Okay then, suit yourself.
He's in shock from getting dumped.
That's it. No matter what I said, he'd ignore it.
If that's what he wants, so be it.
I'll just leave him alone, and time
would work its magic on his wounds.
Hm?
A lot of people from my class were absent.
Probably the work of that cold that was going around.
After he got to school, Taniguchi
went straight to the nurse's office.
He never showed up to class.
I wasn't too surprised about that. He looked terrible.
What did surprise me though was the
seat behind me stayed empty all day.
Wow, even Haruhi was absent.
I didn't realize this year's cold was that serious.
Think about that for a second,
you got a virus, then you got Haruhi.
Virus infiltrates her body and gets the best of her
that's gotta be some cold.
We don't really get a chance to
go in the water this time of year.
They got us doing weight training,
and stuff like that instead.
At least you're warm.
Hm?
Looks like she's absent today. Can I sit behind you?
Yeah, sure.
This cold that everyone's come down
with came out of nowhere, didn't it?
Huh?
What do you mean?
It's been going around the campus
for at least a week or so now.
You're kidding me, a week?
They're pretty sure it's not the flu.
But if you want my opinion,
the flu would have been better.
At least they can give you vaccination for that.
Back up. You just said this cold has
been going around for a week, right?
At least that there're a lot of people who were absent.
Don't tell me you're just noticing.
Yeah, I don't know. I guess I am.
It got worse at the beginning of the week.
Man, I hope they don't cancel school.
They'd probably take it out of
one of our vacation, you know?
I bet it sucks to be Taniguchi right now.
His dad thinks that unless he's gotta
fever of 104, he sucked up and go to school.
He's a heal-it-with-willpower kind of guy.
Kunikida, this is probably gonna sound weird
but I didn't notice that he was
that sick until I saw him this morning.
What? You're kidding, right?
Didn't you see him on Monday? He was already in bad shape.
He missed gym class yesterday, remember?
What's the matter, Kyon? Not hungry?
What the heck is going on around here?
This is clearly an omen that
some crisis for all of humanity,
but not for Haruhi, kind of thing was about to happen.
Later, I found out my intuition was not off.
It was definitely an omen.
The only part my intuition got wrong was the crisis part.
This wasn't a crisis for all
of humanity but not for Haruhi.
This was a crisis only for the person
who noticed it in the first place.
You guessed it... Me.
So, I sat there confused a blank look
on my face, totally alone in the world.
Good morning.
I thought you were sick.
Yeah, I'd heard you weren't coming.
You look okay, but you should take it easy.
They put me on an IV drip at the hospital this morning.
But I'm feeling better now and I was really bored at home,
so I thought I'd come to class.
I'm gonna put this away. Back in a sec.
Oops, I'd better move.
What's the matter? Why the weird look?
Why are you staring like that?
Is there something on my face?
Sorry, I'll clean this up.
It's okay. I'm just dropping off my bag.
Okay. Thanks.
Please, take your time.
Hey!
What is it?
You're not supposed to be here.
What are you talking about?
Is there something wrong with my coming to class today?
I hope you don't think I'm
contagious, because I promise, I'm not.
I don't care about your damn cold!
You know that's not what I'm talking about!
Kyon. You're acting really weird.
Do you even know what you're saying? Are you okay?
Of course I am, but don't you think it's
a little weird to see her standing there?
You know who she is, don't tell me that you don't!
And you know she shouldn't be here!
I don't know what you're talking about.
She's been in our class since day one.
She's only been gone for a day or two,
so how could you forget? You're being rude.
Of course I didn't forget.
That's the face of the person who tried to kill me!
Oh, I think I get it!
You must have dozed off while eating your lunch.
Did you have a nightmare or something?
Why don't you go wash your face?
I'll let you borrow my handkerchief.
No!
Oh...
Who knows what she's gonna
pull out of that pocket of hers?
I don't know what you're up to, but I'm gonna find out.
Why did you hang your bag on Haruhi's chair?
This has never been your seat, admit it! Haruhi sits here!
Haruhi?
I'm sorry, but I don't know any Haruhi.
Huh?
Well, do you?
Someone named Haruhi?
Come on!
No, I've never heard of her.
But Haruhi is Haruhi...
This isn't real... he doesn't remember Haruhi Suzumiya...
This can't be happening, how can
anybody forget someone like her?
Kyon.
There isn't anybody in our class with that name.
Miss Asakura's been sitting in this
chair since the last seat rotation.
Are you sure you're not thinking of some other class?
This shouldn't be happening...
I don't know anyone with the name "Suzumiya".
Maybe she's not in our grade.
Kunikida, would you please have a look inside my desk?
Take out the class roster.
No worries, I'll get it.
Kunikida.
Uh-huh?
Could you pinch me on the
cheek? I really wanna wake up now.
Seriously?
Seriously. Hurry!
Ow!
Hey, you know who Haruhi Suzumiya is, right?
No, I don't. I've never heard of her.
Asakura transferred out of the class, didn't she?
What are you talking about? She never transferred.
You know Haruhi, right?
No. I've never heard of her.
That's Haruhi Suzumiya's seat, isn't it?
No, it's not. Miss Asakura sits there.
Why is everyone staring?
Stop it…
I can take you to see the nurse.
Maybe you have a fever or something.
Haruhi is gone. Nobody remembers her.
Is that possible?
Wasn't the deal supposed to be
that the world revolved around her?
Wasn't she the one the universe
was interested in? Wasn't it watching?
Nagato...
Nagato.
Nagato!
Not here.
She'd be in the club room right now.
Oh yeah, Koizumi!
Wait a minute...
Where did class nine go?
They're gone. Koizumi and everyone in class nine... gone.
What is this?
What's happening?
Hey, you.
I think class has started, young man, so get going.
People who shouldn't be here are here.
People who should be here aren't.
Either the world's gone totally insane, or I'm insane.
Who did it?
Haruhi, was it you?
The afternoon lectures went in one ear and out the other.
I was scared.
And not just because Ryoko Asakura was back,
but also because Haruhi and Koizumi weren't here.
Before I knew it, school was over.
Kunikida and Asakura were worried and tried to talk to me.
But I don't even remember what I said back to them.
What are you gonna do for your
New Year's calligraphy project?
I don't know. I can't make up my mind yet.
Hm...
I know how about if I come up with something for you?
Oh, it's okay.
You know I'll pick something cool, Mikuru.
Miss Asahina!
Miss Asahina, I can't find Haruhi anywhere.
And Koizumi's class has turned
into the drifting classroom.
I haven't found Nagato yet. But Asakura is here.
And everyone in school is acting weird.
But you are the Miss Asahina
I've always known, aren't you?
You are right?
You are the Miss Asahina, the one
came from the future, aren't you?
I'm sorry but I'm not from the future.
Could you let go off my hand now?
Hold it there, buddy.
Watch your manners, got it?
You're scaring my little Mikuru here.
Aw, Miss Tsuruya, that hurts!
What the... How do you know my name?
It can't be... No!
I've never met you before. Who the heck are you, huh?
Mikuru, do you know this guy?
No, I've never seen him before.
Well... I, uh...
I don't know you.
Are you okay, Mikuru?
Miss Asahina, don't do this.
There is no way I'd ever mistake
anyone for you, Miss Asahina.
Not in a million years.
Wait.
That's it. I think I know how I can
prove she is the Miss Asahina I know.
Miss Asahina!
Yes?
I know for a fact you've got a tiny star
shaped mole on your breast right about here.
You have to let me see it.
Mikuru!
You've got a lot of nerve pulling
stuff like that with her, nyoron.
She freaks out super easy.
And if you do something like that again,
you're gonna have to face my wrath, got it?
Wait up, Mikuru.
It's over. Everything's over.
I've finally run out of options.
I don't have her number anymore.
And since I don't know her address,
I can't find it by calling information.
Now that I think about it,
I've never even been to her house.
So just showing up is out of the question too.
There was only one place for me to go.
A fortress of final refuge, my last line of defense.
If we are defeated there, it's over. The end of the line.
Please...
Thank God. You're here.
Why is she wearing glasses?
And why is she looking at me like that?
Nagato.
Yes?
I was wondering...
This is gonna sound weird but, do you know who I am?
I do.
I was hoping you'd say that. I
know a few things about you too.
Uh...
Mind if I tell you what I know?
For starters, you aren't human.
You're sort of an android created by alien species.
Uh.
And you've got these powers kind of like
magic, that you used to save us every now and then.
You made a bat that hit home runs, and you
fought a giant cricket in another dimension.
Anyway, that's the stuff I know about you.
Am I wrong?
I'm sorry.
Why'd she say that?
What's Nagato apologizing for?
I know you are a student here and you're in class five.
So yes, I've seen you around.
But I'm afraid that's pretty much all I know about you.
Actually, this is the first time I've ever spoken to you.
So what you're saying is you're not an alien.
Ali... en?
And the name Haruhi Suzumiya... You don't...
You don't remember it?
No.
But, you have to.
Think back and try to remember.
Hey.
Don't you remember this past summer when we
had to repeat the same two weeks 15,000 times?
Come on, try to remember.
Everyone we know changed between yesterday and today!
Haruhi's gone but Asakura's here!
You know who's responsible for it, don't you?
Was it the Data Integration Thought Entity?
If Asakura's been resurrected,
you'd know about it, wouldn't you?
She's the same as you, right?
What the hell's going on?
You're the only one who can tell me what's happening.
You've always been able to, remember?
Stop it...
I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to freak out on you like that...
I just wanted to be sure...
That's all.
Damn it...
Game over.
If this is someone's attempt to try and drive me crazy,
it's working.
Man, is it working.
I wonder who's behind all this.
Is it Haruhi?
The Data Integration Thought Entity?
Or some new enemy we haven't seen yet.
Sorry.
This is just the literary club room.
It looks the same as it did back in
May when Haruhi dragged me here by force,
and I saw Nagato's face for the first time.
Wait... No...
The only thing that's different
about this room is the computer.
The literary club never had one.
And that's not the one Haruhi swiped.
She's definitely not the Nagato I know.
She would never act like this.
Nagato, would it be okay if I use your computer for a bit?
Not yet.
I guess before she lets me use it
she has to move some files around.
I bet it's stuff she doesn't want anyone to see.
And I get that.
I wouldn't want another people to see those
pictures I have of Miss Asahina, you know.
Okay.
Thank you.
I couldn't find any files about the SOS Brigade.
Or the pictures of Miss Asahina that I'd hidden.
I couldn't find the SOS Brigade website, either.
There wasn't any proof of
Haruhi's existence on it anywhere.
I was hoping to find some clue
or hidden message left by Nagato.
Like the time Haruhi and I were trapped in a Closed Space.
That's what I was hoping.
Sorry to bother you.
Are you finished?
Yeah, I couldn't find the
things I was hoping it was there.
Wait.
Take one, if you want.
The one good thing about experiencing a metric
ton of weirdness since the beginning of school
is that I become used to it.
If I hadn't, I would've gone crazy
talking to the school's counselors by now.
Where the heck could she be...?
Tossing me out into a world like this.
I wonder where she is and what
kind of trouble she's causing.
Damn it. Why do I have to be
the one who's gotta look for her?
Welcome home, Kyon!
Mom said dinner's almost ready.
It's dinner time, Shami.
Di-dinner, di-dinner, di-dinner, dinner.
Dinner, di-dinner...
What was that for?
Do you remember Haruhi?
And Miss Asahina, and Nagato or Koizumi?
You remember we all played baseball together,
and went to an island and made a crappy movie?
What? I don't know.
Okay. How long have we had this little guy?
Do you know who brought him here?
Did you forget? You got him about a month ago, you silly.
A friend of yours moved overseas and gave him to you.
Isn't that right, Shami?
Give me Shami back!
There's things I need to talk to
him about. Alone if you don't mind.
Huh?
I'm gonna have to ask you to leave right now, Sis.
You're gonna talk to Shami? Seriously?
The floor is cold!
Hey, mommy. Kyon's gone crazy!
He's trying to talk to Shami.
Listen up, Shamisen.
Now I know I told you before
that you should never, ever, talk.
But I'm revoking that order.
So come on you little furball. I
wanna hear your voice right now.
Go ahead, Shamisen. Say something.
Anything.
Talk about philosophy or science, anything you want.
Doesn't matter if I don't understand.
Say something.
Do you understand anything I'm saying?
Maybe you can hear me, but for some
reason you can't reply. Is that it?
If the answer is yes, I want you
to hold out your right front paw.
If the answer is no, I want you to
hold out your left front paw okay?
That figures.
I can say for a fact now that
this is not a world where cats talk.
Now I'm weird for trying to have a conversation with him.
As of today, this particular world I'm in is normal.
And I'm not.
Is that really true?
It's December the nineteenth.
Starting today, the school days are shorter.
The cold has spread all over the school.
Good morning. I hope you are awake today.
I guess.
You know, just because your eyes are open,
that doesn't necessarily mean you're wide awake.
You have to accept the reality that's in front of you.
And that'll help you start to understand everything.
So, how about it then? Do you think you can do that?
Asakura.
You're just acting like you don't know
what's going on around here, aren't you?
Be honest. Hasn't the thought of
killing me ever crossed your mind?
I think you should go to the hospital as soon as possible.
You should do it before it's too late.
Consider this if you will.
You have a very unhappy person living in a certain place.
Then he opens his eyes one day,
the whole world has completely changed.
It's a beautiful world.
Calling it Utopia doesn't even
do it justice, it's that wonderful.
And this person will never be unhappy ever again.
Over night, he was snatched from the
jaws of Hell and taken straight to Heaven.
The thing is, this person didn't do this himself.
In fact, he had absolutely no idea who
is responsible for changing his world.
It was a total mystery.
And that's how he stayed. Never knowing who it was
or why they did it, forever.
So, I ask you. Is this something
this person should be happy about?
Up until the other day,
I've been run ragged by all the
weird happenings going on around Haruhi.
But none of that matters to the
person I'm right now. In this world.
There's no Haruhi, no Koizumi.
Nagato and Miss Asahina are normal humans.
There aren't any aliens, time-travelers or espers.
Not to mention the fact that cats don't talk.
It's a normal world.
But here's the thing.
Was I happier in a world with Haruhi in it?
Or am I happier here in a world where she's disappeared.
Well, am I happy now?
After school,
my legs automatically took me to the literary club room.
When class ended, I'd always head over to the SOS Brigade.
I'd play games with Koizumi and
sip on a cup of Miss Asahina's tea.
And I'd listen to Haruhi talk
crazy about some new plan she had.
It's like a bad habit.
Let me tell you. Trying to quit it
cold turkey isn't easy believe me.
Today feels different for some reason.
What am I gonna do with this?
I guess Nagato gave it to me because
she'd like me to join the literary club.
But even in this world, the
literary club doesn't have any members.
I wonder if she's trying to recruit people.
Sorry, I didn't...
Mikuru!
If anything,
I hope there comes a day when I can
have a cup of Miss Asahina's tea again.
Come in.
Hi.
Is it okay that I came?
Thanks.
Well, here I am. And I have
no idea what I'm gonna do next.
Are all those books on the shelf yours?
Some of them have been here all along.
I, uh...
I borrowed this one
from the city library.
Really.
Um.
So, just wondering, have you
ever tried writing a novel yourself?
I just read them.
For a second there,
I thought that the files she was hiding
yesterday was a book she was writing.
That's something I'd like to read.
Maybe it's sci-fi. It couldn't be a love story, could it?
Are you know one who wrote this?
Collect the keys necessary to activate the program.
The time limit is two days.
Did you write this?
It does look like my handwriting.
But I don't remember writing anything like that.
You don't, huh?
Of course, you don't.
No, it's fine. I'd be more worried if you did write it.
Sorry, don't mind me.
Nagato!
You left a message for me after all.
I'm considering this a present from you to me.
You gave me a hint to break out of this mess.
That's what this is, right?
Program.
Necessary.
Keys?
Time limit.
Two days.
Today is the nineteenth. Does
this mean, two days from today?
Or two days from when the world turned upside down for me?
I guess in the worst case scenario,
it would mean the dead line's tomorrow.
I don't really understand, but it says some keys
are needed to start kind of program or something.
But, what are the keys?
And if I find all the keys, am I
supposed to turn them in for prize?
And if I figure out how to start this program,
does that mean the world goes back to the way it was?
These key things are pretty vague when you think about it.
They're probably not the kind you use in locks.
Maybe they're key words or key persons or something.
I mean, they could be anything.
Are they things or a bunch of words?
Am I gonna have to carry them?
Seriously, Nagato. I would've appreciated a
little less mystery and a lot more info in a clue.
Key, key, key, key.
It's no use. I have no idea.
I guess the Nagato in this world is really shy.
Or maybe she's just not used to people noticing her.
Maybe joining the literary club,
having fun in a world without Haruhi wouldn't be so bad.
Who am I kidding? I can't bail yet.
I haven't tasted Haruhi's hot pot.
And an image of Santa Asahina hasn't
burned itself onto my retinas yet.
I guess I'll go home now.
Okay.
You weren't waiting for me to leave, were you?
Walking home with Nagato.
I don't remember ever having done this before.
Hey, there, Nagato.
Yes?
Well, I was just curious. Do you live by yourself?
Yeah.
I bet you're wondering how I knew that.
You know, I've been to your
place quite a few times, actually.
But, I bet if I told you that now,
you'd think I was talking nonsense or something.
Since you live by yourself, have
you ever thought about getting a cat?
You know, they're pretty cool.
The weird thing about them is that sometimes,
it's like they can understand what you say.
Pets aren't allowed.
Oh, I see.
Uh…
Hmm?
Will you come?
Where to?
Where I live, tonight.
Come in.
After you.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
I have no idea she's being shy or timid or aggressive.
It looks like the layout of her room changed a bit.
Nagato, is it okay if I take a look in here?
Yeah, go ahead.
I'll... just be a sec.
Thank you.
I, uh...
Hmm?
I met you…I mean, we met before.
Outside of school, once.
We did?
Do you remember?
I don't.
We met at the library.
Back in May, this year.
You got me a library card.
Yeah, I remember.
The first SOS brigade's search for mystery and phenomena.
And if I recall correctly,
I could barely pry you away from the bookshelves.
But, this version of Nagato shouldn't know about that.
Excuse me, Nagato.
Could you tell me more about that day?
It was May, or rather it was the middle of May.
It was my first time going to the public library.
I didn't know what I had to do to get a library card.
There were lots of people that day and the
librarians looked like they were really busy.
I didn't wanna bother them.
I have a hard time in situations where I
have to talk to people and ask for something.
So I just stood there feeling sorry
for myself and then someone came up to me.
He went through the whole process
for me even filled up the form.
When I got my card I just left.
I didn't know what to say to this person who helped me.
That person was you.
It always bothered me that I didn't
thank you for your help that day.
So I was surprised when I was
at school and there you were.
So, thank you.
Saying "I remember" would be easy right now.
But that's not how the story goes.
We were just killing time at the library.
Because we were all on one of Haruhi's so-called missions.
And there's another detail you left out.
Haruhi, you don't even mention her.
I wonder where's the Nagato I used to know.
Hello.
Well, right now is a little...
Uh-huh. Okay.
Wait here.
Oh? What are you doing here?
What am I doing here? What are you doing here.
Well, I guess you could say I'm doing volunteer work.
But I think the fact you're here is what's more unusual.
So, did you cook all this up yourself?
Every now and then I whip something
up to eat and bring it over for Nagato.
It's the only way I know to
make sure she's eating properly.
Do you guys get along?
We both live in the same apartment building.
How about you? Why did you decide to stop by?
Umm... I, uh...
We were walking, and we both
happened to live out this way so…
I'm kind of on the fence right now about
whether I should join the literary club.
And I had a couple of questions for her.
So she invited me up here and we talked about it.
But I didn't force her.
I just can't picture you in the literary club.
You don't seem like you'd be too interested in it.
Do you like to read books or do you wanna be a writer?
I don't know. That's what I'm
trying to figure out, I guess.
Really…
Wait. Aren't you going to stay for dinner?
You should, you know. I think I outdid myself this time.
Sorry to bother you.
You know, I think I will stay for dinner.
Food sounds really good right now.
Yeah, if I don't eat something
soon I might not make it home tonight.
If I went home now, it would be like
meeting someone and unintroducing yourself.
Besides, it's rare to see Nagato actually want something.
Whoa, look who's back.
Food tastes better when it's
eaten with company. All right?
So guess what I saw today.
I was with some friends at the train
station and we were looking at some clothes.
I saw the scarf, Yuki that would look great on you.
I wasn't gonna say anything, just going
to buy it and give it to you for Christmas.
But then I didn't because I was
worried you weren't going to like it.
Anyway, if you want, we could go check it out together.
If you end up liking it, I'll get it for you.
I'll think about it.
While we're out and about, we could
go check out some Bathroom supplies.
Looks like this version of
Asakura is on good terms with Nagato.
She's kind of annoying, too.
So, is it good?
I feel like I'm camped out in front of the gates of hell.
Make sure you put the leftovers in a separate
container and remember to put it in the fridge.
I'll be back tomorrow for my dish. See you then.
Hey. Can I come back to the club room tomorrow?
I don't really have any place else to go.
Hey.
Hey!
Welcome back.
I've been talking to you this whole time, you know.
I don't know what's wrong but you
look like you saw an alien or something.
That wouldn't be unusual for a guy like me.
Besides, I just saw something even more unbelievable.
Huh?
Nothing.
So, what were you saying?
I wasn't saying. I was asking
if you had a crush on Nagato.
Well, I certainly don't hate her.
I owe her my life. She saved me
that time you were trying to cut me up.
But I can't tell you that.
Maybe I'm overreacting.
Besides, you're into even weirder girls than her.
Nagato isn't really your style, is she?
How do you know my tastes in women?
I asked Kunikida and he told me.
He said you were like that in junior high.
What a jerk. He's got no
business talking about that stuff.
If you decide to go out with
Nagato, don't play around with her.
Take it seriously, okay?
If you don't,
I will never forgive you.
Why are you so concerned about me hurting her feelings?
I don't know.
Well, maybe because she's a neighborhood friend.
Or maybe because she's the type of
person who needs someone to look after her.
Right.
See you later then.
Bye.
I wanted to hurry home and get to sleep.
If I get to see you again,
even if it was only in a dream.
I bet she could show up in people's dreams,
subconsciously of course.
Damn it. You're still causing
trouble whether you're here of not.
Just for once, couldn't you at least
butt in when you are really needed?
Seriously, it would be so awesome if
you help me out once in a while, you know.
Why me?
I really, really missed Haruhi.
December the twentieth.
I wake up from a dreamless night.
Today should be the time limit.
But I haven't found the so-called keys yet.
If I don't do something about it today,
things could stay like this forever.
Or they might even get worse.
Nagato, why did you set a time limit?
With your power you should've
been able to give me plenty of time.
Hey, Kyon!
So about Chemistry next period.
Today's our row's turn to give the answers…
I need your help.
Huh?
Hey, Kunikida.
What's up?
Do you think you could teach
this guy about sodium hydroxide.
I think he's stuck in how it relates to hydrochloric acid.
Well, for starters, if you mix the two of
them together, they neutralize each other.
Get it?
Explain this part to me.
You don't get that one?
It's really simple.
Um,
Okay. First you have to calculate the number of moles.
Mm...
So anyway Kyon.
I heard you spazzed out the other day? Care to comment.
You should know. You were here that day.
I was in the nurse's office trying to sleep off my cold.
And I got stayed home yesterday. Finally.
Anyway, you were saying stuff like how
Asakura shouldn't have been here or something?
What's up with that?
I don't know.
You were saying it was weird Miss Asakura was
here and some other girl should be here instead.
Someone called Haruhi?
Who is this girl supposed to be anyway.
I don't wanna talk about it anymore.
Haruhi? Wait, are you guys talking about Haruhi Suzumiya?
Wait a minute. You know who he is talking about?
Yup.
Oh, this too.
Come on. Are you even trying to figure these out yourself?
What did you say?
But I really don't get it, man.
What did you say? Before.
Huh? I said I didn't understa
Not that.
Oh, Haruhi Suzumiya?
She was the gonzo girl of east junior high.
The two of us were in the same class in middle school.
I didn't know you guys knew each other. It's a...
You slimy octopus!
Huh?
Who're you calling an octopus?
If I'm an octopus, you're a dried-up old squid!
You know Haruhi? You really know who she is?
Huh?
Of course, I know her. Even after fifty
years you don't forget someone like her.
All the kids who went east
junior high know that crazy chick.
Let me go, man. What the hell?
Where is she? Where the hell did Haruhi go?
Hey, Kyon. Come on, stop it!
That hurt!
Where, where, where. You're like a broken record.
What's wrong with you? You see her
somewhere and fall in love with her?
Give it up, guy.
Sure she's got top-class looks but
her personality is totally haywire.
I mean in the first year she went and painted
all this weird graffiti all over the campus.
Yeah, I already know that!
Where is she? You better tell
me where Haruhi is right now.
She's at Koyoen academy.
She's a student at that up-tight prep school, man.
She's at Koyoen academy?
Are you telling she's some kind of snobby rich kid now?
Isn't that an elite all-girl's school?
Kyon.
That school's been coed for a while now.
Yeah, he's right. As long as you
got the grades, anyone can go there.
You don't have to be a chick.
Are you okay? If you've got a
fever, I could take you to the…
Wait, Kyon.
I'm leaving early!
Tell Okabe whatever you want. I've
got the plague, dysentery and typhus too.
I felt like I was dying so I left.
And Taniguchi.
What?
Thanks, buddy.
What? Sure.
Shoot. I miscalculated.
The school is really quiet. The
classes must still be in session.
This time of year, all the high schools
in the city are on a half-day schedule.
I'm early. And there's still
an hour before classes let out.
Maybe I should just force my way in there.
I'm sure that's what Haruhi would do.
I wonder if I could pull it off.
Who am I kidding? I don't have the guts.
Besides, unlike Haruhi, I know
when it's better to play it safe.
No way. It's that girl from class nine, Koizumi's class.
I thought she disappeared but it
looks like she goes to this school now.
I hope I can see Haruhi from this spot.
I've got a fifty-fifty chance.
But if she's in some after school club,
then I'll have to stay in here for god knows how long.
I could be prank scarecrow you for a while.
Wait. Maybe there's another SOS
brigade right here at Koyoen academy.
Maybe she's found a whole new group of people to be in it.
Damn it. Just that thought, that makes me sick.
Is it possible that me, Miss Asahina,
Nagato and Koizumi have outlived our usefulness?
If that's the case, I'm out of the picture.
I'm not even a supporting character in this crazy setup.
I couldn't live with that. Anything but that.
Damn it. What would I believe
in? Who am I supposed to pray to?
Christ? Buddha? Mohammad? Zarathustra? Lovecraft?
I don't care who it is. Just get
me out of this... whatever this is.
There you are.
I found you.
Haruhi Suzumiya.
And look. Koizumi is there too.
It looks like they're walking home together.
I guess in this world, they're pretty close.
Whatever. I don't care about that now.
Just seeing Haruhi's face again brings back memories.
Her face looks exactly the
same as the beginning of school,
before she came up with the SOS brigade.
Like a wrestler... looking for someone to fight.
But I shouldn't be thinking about the past right now.
What's this?
Hey, come on, guy. You're not turning chicken, are you?
Move.
Move!
Hey!
What do you want?
Well, what do you want? And who are you anyway?
I don't think a total stranger has ever yelled "hey" at
me before so get to the point and tell me what you want.
And if you're here to pick up girls, you better leave.
And I guess you've never met me before either.
I can't say I have. Would you mind telling us who you are?
You're a transfer student here, aren't you?
You're right. I transferred to this school in the spring.
But how did you know that?
Do you remember something called the Organization?
Organization? Which one?
I mean, there are lots of organizations.
Haruhi.
Nobody gave you permission to call me by my first name.
I don't know you,
so stop bothering me and get out of my way.
Suzumiya!
Hang on.
Don't call me by my last name, either.
How do you know my name, anyway? I don't know you.
What are you wearing? A North High uniform?
You don't belong here so go home.
Come on, Koizumi. Let's go.
Okay.
Wait! Haruhi!
Take your hands off me.
Miss Suzumiya.
Are you coming or not, Koizumi.
Yes.
Wait! Wait a minute!
Halt.
What's going on here? You don't go to this school.
What's that, a North High uniform?
Well, uh...
Damn it.
Whoa, hold on, son! You...
Get off. Get off me.
Haruhi!
Just tell me one thing.
Tanabata, three years ago. Remember?
You drew a bunch of hieroglyphs on the
campus grounds that night, didn't you?
So what if I did? That's not news. Everybody knows that.
But what they don't know is that you weren't the
only one who snuck into the school that night, were you?
The guy carrying Asa…
I mean, carrying a girl on his
back. You remember that guy, don't you?
You made him draw those things, right?
And I know what those drawing were saying.
They said "I am right here."
I think we've had enough...
Hey!
Calm down, son. Calm down!
Miss Suzumiya?
Haru…
That hurts!
Why? How come you know about me?
Who have you been talking to?
Hang on. I never told anyone before about that night,
back when I was...
North high?
Who are you? What's your name?
John Smith.
John Smith?
You? That's impossible, you can't be.
Then you're the weird high schooler
who helped me three years ago...
Miss Suzumiya.
Hey, somebody call a teacher!
Bingo.
Are you okay?
It matched.
That's it. I finally found something I can call a lead.
I found the one person in this upside down world
who has the same memories as me.
Actually I've met John Smith twice.
Twice?
On my way home that night,
after doing those drawings, a voice called out to me.
He said "John Smith wishes you the best
of luck in making the world more exciting."
Really? I don't remember saying anything like that.
Great. Her memories aren't the same after all.
And of all the things to say, why
did this other John Smith say that?
I mean, he was giving Haruhi
advice that was totally unnecessary.
Um, excuse me.
I just wanna make sure I understand everything.
Yeah, sure.
To summarize, you said you're from a
different world than the one you're currently in?
Yeah.
In this other world myself and
Miss Suzumiya go to North High,
and are members of something called the SOS brigade?
Uh-huh.
And with us there is a time traveler named
Mikuru Asahina and an alien being named Yuki Nagato.
I'm supposed be an esper, and the three of us were
sent by our respective groups to observe Miss Suzumiya.
That's pretty much it.
Hahaha.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
It's just that I think it's a great story.
And I'd like to believe you...
And every time I would get
bored, Closed Space would appear.
Yeah.
And if that happened, it meant
the whole universe was in danger?
That's right.
But the me in that world didn't know she had that power.
I was the only one who didn't...
That's how it was.
And you really didn't care about having just a normal day.
And I was always causing trouble, right?
Yeah.
That is so cool!
No way. Do you believe me?
Sorry, but the version of you that comes
from my world never believed anything I said.
That's because that me is a complete idiot.
But I believe you.
Because that kind of world is
way more unbelievably cooler!
After I met John Smith, I did some
research on the students at North High.
I staked them out,
but I never saw anyone who looked like John.
But now I know that's because three
years ago you weren't a student there yet.
What are you smiling about?
Who me? Nothing.
Anyway, I've got a question.
Why didn't the you in this world go to North High?
'Cause it didn't really matter where I went.
For one thing, John would've graduated
by the time I started high school.
Besides, I couldn't find him anywhere.
Also my teacher kept bugging me about how Koyoen
had the best record around for college acceptance.
Those are good reasons.
So why are you going there?
I guess for the same reasons.
I selected this school because it
complimented my educational aptitude.
The SOS brigade. It sounds like fun.
Yeah, well to be honest, you
were the only one having fun there.
If I were to believe the story you've been telling us,
the situation which you claim to or found
yourself in can be interpreted in one of two ways.
I'll explain. The first interpretation to consider
would be that you've been transported to a parallel world.
Like this.
The second interpretation would
be that the actual world you live in
thank you,
the world is the thing which has been completely altered.
Everything except you, of course.
But either interpretation presents its own dilemma.
In the first case, we have the question of
what happened to the version of you in this world.
And the second, there's a question of why you
were the only person not affected in the world.
If this is a parallel world,
then somehow you have to find a way
to return to the world you come from.
But if the world has changed,
then your task would be to find a way to change it back.
If that's so and you're successful
at changing the world back,
I would be concerned that this version of
Miss Suzumiya and myself would disappear.
Be that as it may,
the quickest way to figure out the puzzle would
be to find a one responsible for changing the world.
But other than Haruhi, who's got
the power to do something like that?
Perhaps invaders from a parallel
dimension are playing a trick on you.
You never know. They could pop up when you least expected.
Okay, now you're pulling my leg.
If I were you, I wouldn't rule out that possibility.
At any rate,
you now seem to have the keys that were
inferred in that message Yuki Nagato wrote you.
I don't know about you but I
wanna check out this club room.
And I wanna meet Miss Nagato and Miss Asahina too.
If I'm the one who changed the world, maybe if I
go there and meet them, I'll remember something.
Right, John?
That's the only way we can be sure, right?
When you say John, are you referring to me?
Why go with Kyon when John's a much cooler name.
Besides, it's really common in the west.
What kind of idiot would give you
a lame nickname like Kyon anyway?
Okay, guys. Hurry up. We gotta go.
Uh...
Where?
Where else? North High, of course.
I'll go out and grab us a taxi.
Thanks! Have a good day!
Typical behavior from that one.
But seeing it again makes me feel better.
I'll take care of mine and Miss
Suzumiya's portion of the bill.
So are you guys... you know, close?
As a matter of fact, I am in love with Miss Suzumiya.
Are you serious?
Yes. I happen to think she's a charming person.
Oh, I've heard that line before.
Unfortunately, Miss Suzumiya isn't
interested in someone as ordinary as myself.
The only reason she started talking to me in the
first place was because I was a transfer student.
And lately I can tell she's getting bored with me.
So let me get this straight. In your world, you
weren't the type of person who attracted her attention?
Hate to break it to you,
but the only special ability I have was
getting myself mixed up in weird happenings.
Very interesting.
Then the Miss Suzumiya in your
world is only interested in you,
not some unique characteristic or special power.
Of course, that's assuming that Miss Suzumiya
of your world has the same personality as mine.
Makes me jealous.
What are you doing? Don't just stand there. Hurry up!
Shall we go?
Uh…
Come on. Hurry. Let's go!
Crap! School's been out for a while now.
And I told Nagato I'd be coming to the club room.
Please wait a little bit longer.
We're here. Now what?
I don't mind you guys crashing my school, but
your uniforms would stick out like a sore thumb.
That might be a problem if a teacher catches us, you know.
Yeah, good point.
I got it. Here's what we're gonna do. Come on. Huddle up.
You got it?
That's the Haruhi I know.
I sure hope you wash these things.
Yep. About a week ago.
Okay, is there a good place to change into the these?
Right here is fine.
I didn't think your legs were so long.
Hey, John, make sure no one's watching.
Yeah.
Uh…Hey!
What are you worried about.
I've got a t-shirt on underneath.
Yeah...
All done!
Aren't you a little cold?
Not at all!
Hey, could you put your hair in a ponytail?
Why?
No reason. Never mind.
Yeah, sure. Why not?
It doesn't look like it takes much effort
but it's annoying trying to get it right.
I guess that makes me look like I'm really working out.
How's this look?
Spot on.
In fact, I think it makes you look
thirty-six percent more charming.
What an idiot.
Hey, Koizumi, are you ready?
Yes, I am, I think.
Now, you look cold.
Yes, well,
Miss Suzumiya, if you are not
planning on wearing the jacket,
would it be possible for me to wear it?
Nope.
I have to use the jacket to hide our bags.
Here you go, John, catch!
Okay, we're gonna sneak into the school
by pretending we just came back from a run.
Ready?
Here we go! One, two, one two!
Stopping Haruhi from running
off is pretty much impossible.
And I mean that in absolutely every sense of the word.
I certainly knew it.
And present circumstances prove this Koizumi knew it too.
What's happening now is kinda
funny when you think about it.
It's taking so much work for these two
trying to get onto the North High campus.
Just three days ago, they were students here.
So she stayed out today.
This was a lot easier than I thought.
Don't be silly.
It's getting late. Are you sure Miss
Nagato will still be in the club room?
She will, but we have to hurry up.
Wait a second!
What now?
Change our plan. We should capture Miss Asahina first.
Wait. We're supposed to...
Miss Nagato can wait for a little bit longer.
Hey, don't worry, we'll be in and out in a flash.
Okay, to the calligraphy club!
I'm sorry, Nagato. Please wait a little longer.
Is there a Miss Asahina in here?
That's... me?
I told her not to make a scene.
Hey, is that her over there?
Is she really a junior?
No mistake at all. That's definitely her.
You there. I'm Suzumiya, Head of the
Student Council Intelligence Agency!
Mikuru Asahina, I'd like to have a word with you.
Please gather your things and come with me.
Student Council lntel... Have I done something wrong?
I'm so sorry, Miss Asahina.
Nagato.
Sorry I'm late. I got a...
Watch out. Coming through.
Pardon the intrusion!
Sorry about this.
Well, hello there.
Where are we?
I haven't done...
Why did you lock the door?!
What do you think you're doing...
Just be quiet.
It's like before. I'm getting all misty-eyed.
Ah, nostalgia.
So you're Miss Yuki Nagato?
Hi, there. I'm Haruhi Suzumiya!
And this cutie with the big boobs is Miss Asahina!
And the guy in the gym clothes is Koizumi.
Hello.
That's not suspicious or anything.
And I think you already know John Smith over there, right?
Who's John Smith?
Yeah, just let that one go for now.
So this is the SOS Brigade club room.
There's nothing here, but it's got potential.
We can start filling up the
empty spots with all kinds of stuff.
I, uh...
Okay. So, what's the first thing we're gonna do?
Huh?
Wait, You came all the way over
here and you don't have a plan?
Man, you are exactly like Haruhi.
You know, on second thought this place might not work.
What are you talking about?
Look, I really like the idea of
using this room as our headquarters
but it's gonna take me forever to get over here.
Hey, wait a minute.
What if we pick a time and meet over
the cafe in front of the train station?
Hang on. I have a question.
Are you trying to start up an SOS Brigade in this
world because it sounds an awful lot like you were.
I haven't really decided what I'm gonna call it.
Come to think of it though, that's not such a bad idea.
Whatever I call it, the first mission is
going to be getting you back to your world
assuming you're from a different one, of course.
If not, then...
Okay, but before you...
What did you do that for? You scared the heck out of me.
Don't go turning it on like that.
You mean you didn't turn the computer on?
Perhaps someone adjusted the
settings to automatically turn it on.
Let me see that!
What's happening? What's going on?
I don't know. Hang on a sec.
John?
Are you gonna tell us what's going
on or have you gone totally crazy?
I'm okay. Perfectly sane.
Yeah. You're definitely not, Nagato.
You got it. Everyone present and accounted for.
I can't take credit for this one. No.
Haruhi dragged Koizumi and
everyone else here all by herself.
By the way, Nagato, it's been a while.
What's up with the computer?
What's that weird message supposed to mean?
Well, say something, John.
Nagato, does any of this stuff ring a bell?
It doesn't.
You sure about that?
Of course, I'm sure.
Nagato figured out the way to send a message.
I don't know what this emergency escape program is.
But if she's behind it,
I have to trust she knows what she's doing.
I mean, at this point doubting
her would be like doubting my sanity.
Hey, John. What's wrong with you?
You've got a funny look on your face.
You're not telling me what's going
on and it started to freak me out.
I mean the...
Just be quiet for a second!
I'm sorry. I just need a little time to think about this.
How rude!
What's that look for?
Nothing.
It's okay.
Nagato.
You can have this back.
I'm sorry.
Okay.
You see, Nagato.
In my world I was already a member in this club.
It'd be kind of redundant if I went
through the process of joining in again.
Try to understand.
The truth is, in the place where I come from
I'm the first official member of the SOS Brigade.
Right. Okay. Here goes.
I will never forgive you.
Makes me jealous.
Is this... the literary club?
Funny. It doesn't feel like I've returned to my old world.
This is the same room I was in before.
But it doesn't have any of the SOS
Brigade stuff that Haruhi brought in.
It's hot.
Damn, it's like summer in here.
Wait, when is this?
When I looked, my shoes weren't in my locker.
And this was definitely the middle of summer.
I get the feeling I've been
thrown into another time again.
First thing is first. I gotta figure out what year it is.
And what month, what day, hour, down to the minute.
There's a big difference for me
whether it's the past or the future.
Welcome to the store, sir.
So that's it, huh? Nagato.
Today is Tanabata.
July the seventh, three years ago.
That can only mean one thing.
That's right. That day in the club room,
when Haruhi had us make our tanzaku.
After everyone left, I time
traveled here with Miss Asahina,
and met up with the adult version of her.
I got stuck that night helping the middle school version
of Haruhi draw all those weird symbols at the school.
After that, Miss Asahina found out
she couldn't get us back to our own time.
So we went Nagato's house to ask for help.
And that can only mean one thing. They're both here.
I've got two people who can help me get back.
After time traveling on that crazy day of Tanabata,
I showed up in this world at about nine o'clock.
Miss Asahina fell asleep right after we got here.
And then the adult version of Miss Asahina showed up
and told me where to go and what to do from there.
I know where Nagato lives so I can go there any time.
But before I do, I think I'd
better go see someone else first.
There we are.
Wow. This is making me jealous of myself.
Right now I wish I could switch places with that guy.
It would be nice but back then, now,
I didn't meet another version of me.
If I show up now,
it would conflict with the memories I have of that night.
I'd rather not mess with the
space-time continuum any more,
thank you very much.
Miss Asahina?
She's out and if I remember
correctly, a few seconds later...
Yes. The adult Miss Asahina makes her entrance!
Hello there Kyon, It's me.
It's just like how I remember.
After this happens,
I'm supposed to go meet the middle school Haruhi.
But this version of me has other plans.
Miss Asahina.
I, uh. I just...
Good evening, Kyon.
It's been a while since we talked, hasn't it?
I'm glad we were able to meet again.
Although I wish it wasn't due to
another one of my silly mistakes.
Miss Asahina, don't tell me you knew I'd be here tonight.
I mean, that you'd see this other
version of me here in this time.
Yes. I've known about it all along.
You knew about it, huh?
Then the night of Tanabata, three
years ago, that was your doing?
'Cause if it was, then you must've given
the teenage Asahina the order to come here.
Yes. It was necessary to set it up like that.
If I didn't, you wouldn't have
known to come to the park tonight.
Uhh…
Haruhi mentioned something about hearing John
Smith calling out to her when she was walking home.
Right. The mystery voice.
Know who it is?
It's you. This version of you.
Right now my priority is to get you where you need to be.
But after the mission's complete, you'll
have to decide your next step on your own.
All I can do is point you in the right direction.
What happened to the flow of time anyway?
I mean it's like the whole darn
thing's gone completely out of whack.
I can't tell you the details.
Classified information, huh.
Oh, no, it's not that.
I can't explain it to you in a way you'd understand.
I can only give you a general idea of the circumstances
like how I did when we first met and I told you who I was.
Explaining would only complicate things.
Yeah.
I knew you'd understand the situation.
You said something once that was
sort of like what Nagato would say.
Something about how the computers of the
future weren't at all like the ones we have today.
Yes, the computer and network system you
rely on in your time are physical things.
But in my time, we've gotten
rid of their physical properties.
They exist like thoughts inside our heads.
Like the TPDD.
All right, your time machine.
Time Plane Destruction Device. Yes.
Wasn't that classified?
I don't have as many restrictions now as I had before.
And believe me, I had to work my butt off to get this far.
Do you have any idea why this is happening?
All I know is that the time I was living in has changed.
But when did it happen and why did it happen?
The only person who could answer that
question is the Miss Nagato of this time.
But I can say one thing.
The time plane you came from was altered
early in the morning on December the eighteenth,
three years from this point in time.
I see. I guess that means I
didn't wake up in a parallel world.
The whole world was changed.
That seems to be the case.
Let's see.
Look here.
This is the normal flow of time.
But three years from now on December the eighteenth,
the world, your world changed like this.
In one night the STC data,
um, the world itself changed.
The disruption in space-time was so
big, we could see it in the future.
To return it to normal requires Miss Nagato's help.
And your help too, Kyon.
It won't work without you.
Who's responsible for it?
Well, I guess that's obvious. It's got to be Haruhi.
No.
Miss Suzumiya isn't the person behind it.
Although, you do know who the person is.
But if it isn't Haruhi,
then who is it?
I suppose we still have some time.
Do you mind if we talked for a bit?
Back then I didn't know my left from my right.
Miss Suzumiya did whatever she wanted with me.
She made me wear all those costumes.
Yeah.
It was a lot of trouble at the time
but they're all happy memories now.
Kyon, you know what?
What?
One day, you're going to look back on the days
you spent as a high school student with nostalgia.
This time in your life will be
over before you even realize it.
It'll all seem like a dream.
Miss Asahina?
Sorry. What did you say?
Our time is almost up here. We should go.
Oh, right. You mean to Nagato's apartment.
Not just yet. Don't you have
something else you need to do first?
Hey!
John Smith wishes you the best of
luck in making the world more exciting!
Remember him, Haruhi.
Remember John Smith.
Whatever you do, remember I was here.
Hold on, Kyon.
I'm sorry. I still feel uneasy around Miss Nagato.
I think I understand how you'd feel that way.
Nagato, hey.
Listen, something's happened.
It's sort of hard to explain,
but I've come back from the future again.
The adult Miss Asahina's with me.
I really need your help now.
In fact it's because of you that
I've come back to this time again.
Miss Asahina and I should be up in your guest room now.
We are sleeping in there frozen in time.
It's back to room 708 again.
Nagato can figure this out.
She'd better figure this out.
Otherwise, I'm in big trouble.
May we come in?
It's gonna be okay.
I know. You're right.
I'm sure it'll be fine.
No mistake about it. This is the Nagato I remember.
I guess I don't need to introduce myself.
But I'd like you to meet Miss Asahina, the adult version.
I understand.
May I have a look in there?
I mean...
You may not. The room is
designed to freeze time within it.
It sounds complicated I know,
but that's pretty much exactly the way it happened.
This proves that you are the one responsible
for bringing me back here from the future.
U-Um...
I'd like to straighten out this
abnormality in space time as soon as possible.
But you are the only one who can restore
the time-plane back to the way it was.
And so I'm begging you.
Please help.
I'm also begging you, Great God Nagato.
That's my wish, too.
I will confirm.
I failed to sync.
I cannot access my variant in that space-time continuum.
She has erected a system barrier that
does deny my request for synchronization.
I understand the situation now. Restoration is possible.
The one responsible for this space-time alteration
did so by harnessing Haruhi
Suzumiya's ability to generate data
as well as altering specific
sectors of data within the world.
That is why Haruhi Suzumiya was
left powerless after the modification.
And why the Data Integration Though
Entity does not exist in that time-plane.
Haruhi Suzumiya's powers were
stolen and used to alter memory data.
The range of the alteration begins
on the morning of December eighteenth,
three years and five months from
now, and stretches backwards 365 days.
Wait a minute.
You're saying the memories inside this range
have changed, but everything before is the same.
If that's true, then is the version
of you I'm talking to right now,
the three years ago July seventh
version of you the original you?
Correct.
To return the world to the way it was,
return to the December eighteenth of the future.
When the process that alters space-time is completed,
you must activate the program to correct it.
You're gonna come with me, though. Right?
I cannot leave here.
Why not?
I cannot leave the two of them alone.
The versions of Miss Asahina
and me that are frozen in time.
Emergency Mode.
But then, what should I do?
Compositing.
You must inject the correction program
into the one who altered space-time.
Don't you have a less painful way of doing it?
I mean, what if I stuck them in the wrong place with that?
Right.
There you go creating dangerous-looking things again...
The program will be effective if injected through clothing
however, direct contact with skin is preferred.
You're kidding. This thing
doesn't shoot real bullets, does it?
Short needles.
The program is applied to the tips of the needles.
So who am I supposed to shoot with this thing?
Who is responsible?
I want the name of the person who altered
space-time and changed the world and everyone in it.
If Haruhi didn't do this, then who did?
It was...
Are you serious?
Yes.
Is that really true?
I will upload the coordinates of your target.
Okay. Thank you.
I understand.
So then we just go there to inject
the correction program and that's it?
In your present condition,
you will be caught in the alteration of space-time.
I will counteract it.
Your hand.
I have deployed an Anti-Data Reconfiguration Screen
and a protective field onto the surface of your body.
You are next.
Okay.
I never apologized for what happened that day.
I remember the last time you did this.
This is the first time for me.
Oh, it is, isn't it?
Okay, Kyon.
We really should get going now.
Thanks, Nagato.
I do not mind.
Nagato, will you...
Are you gonna wait for me?
I will.
Are you ready, Kyon?
Watch out, this might make you a little dizzy.
Here we go.
We're here.
This is the time and place Miss Nagato gave me.
It's the place where Haruhi and Koizumi changed clothes.
Coincidence? I wonder.
It's cold.
Sorry about this,
but thank you.
No worries. It's the least I could do.
We forgot to put on our shoes.
I hope Miss Nagato still has them at her place.
I don't really think she just throw them away.
That's true.
Let's get going.
We've landed on December
eighteenth at 4:18 in the morning.
The world hasn't been changed yet,
but in about five minutes, it will be.
Which means Haruhi and Koizumi
are still students in North High.
And if I went home, I'd find myself blissfully asleep,
knowing nothing of what was about to happen.
Get ready.
It's who Nagato said it would be.
The person who altered space-time.
I can't jump out just yet.
We wait until the process is finished,
then I shoot them with the correction program.
This is it. It's a disruption of space-time.
What an incredible power.
It's done. The process is finished.
The world has been changed. And
she's just been reborn into it.
Okay, it's our turn now, Kyon.
Hey.
It's me. We meet again.
So it really was you.
What are you doing out here? And why?
Funny, I was just about to ask you the exact same thing.
A walk...
That's not true.
That's not true, Nagato.
You were tired.
You'd had enough of Haruhi's nonsense,
getting dragged all over the place.
You were tired of protecting me.
And you were tired of whatever else you had to do,
stuff we didn't even know about.
The fatigue you felt from all
those things kept building up.
A collection of error data will
accumulate in my memory over time.
The bugs will eventually become
triggers and affect my behavior.
Also these circumstances are unavoidable.
Three years from now on the morning of
December eighteen, I will reconstruct the world.
I cannot prevent it.
Because I am currently unable to
identify exactly what the error data is.
Well, I know.
I know what the trigger is.
That caused your abnormal shift in behavior.
I know what the error data is
that kept piling up inside you.
The truth is it's something completely cliche.
Even though you're a human interface,
and you can't operate beyond
the limits of your programming.
This is something even you aren't into.
Sure you don't understand. But I do.
And I'm sure Haruhi does, too.
You see, Nagato.
They're called feelings.
It figures you wanna experience
emotions, when you never even have them.
I mean, didn't you wanna shout, or cry, or
yell "leave me alone, I've had enough," sometimes?
Well, even if you never thought about that stuff,
it's normal for you to want to.
You should've been allowed to do that.
I'm partly to blame, too.
Good! Now lift you leg like you gonna jump.
Without thinking, I made it a
habit to rely on you more and more.
I wouldn't think for myself. It was always.
"Oh, Nagato can fix this. She can do anything."
Turns out I'm an even bigger idiot than Haruhi.
And all I did was complain.
With all of that stacking up.
It's no wonder you finally went so
screwy that you tried to change the world.
A bug? An error?
Seriously, give it a rest.
Nagato wished for it.
She just wanted to live in a normal world, that's all.
And after worrying about it for the past couple of days.
I finally have the answer I was looking for.
Why did she leave it to me to
get everything back the way it was.
The answer is simple.
She trusted me to make the right choice.
The altered world? Or the original? Which one's better.
And I have to choose. Damn it.
What the hell I was thinking.
All the things that happened around Haruhi.
Every little thing that defied common sense.
How do I feel about them?
I'm sick of them.
I've had enough.
Seriously.
I can't take much more of this.
I am a normal guy who just happened
to get sucked into all this crazy stuff.
A high schooler struggling against the
unreasonable impossible demands of Haruhi.
I should've taken a harder stance against it.
So that's how it is, huh?
Yeah, I'm talking to you.
It's question and answer time.
It's an important question, so listen up, okay?
And I want an answer.
Ready? Then, let's take the quiz.
Think about it. Then, give me your answer.
Come on, go ahead, and say it.
Haruhi forced to do all kinds of crazy things, and
if that wasn't enough you were attacked by aliens,
and you had to listen to weird stories
from time-travelers and espers, too.
One weird unexplainable thing happening after another.
And a cherry on top is the iron-clad rule that Haruhi had
to be kept in the dark about everything that was going on.
The person behind it all can't found out. It's a catch-22.
And none of that was fun. Is that what you think?
You were sick of it.
You had enough.
It was stupid.
You couldn't take anymore.
Huh, Is that right?
If you're having trouble following me, let me spit it out.
Uh-huh? That's pretty much how it is.
Be honest with yourself, you can't stand Haruhi.
She is a huge pain in the ass.
Everything she wants to do sucks.
There's no way you had any fun at all, is there?
You can't deny it, don't even try.
So, explain this.
Why'd you press the enter key?
The emergency escape program.
The one Nagato left to undo everything.
And you answered "Yes" to that question. Isn't that right?
Even after the great Miss Nagato went through
all that trouble to give you a calm peaceful world.
You turned it down.
Why did you do it, man?
Weren't you the one who is always whining about it?
You were always crying about how miserable you were.
If that's the case, then who
cares about the escape program.
You should have ignored it.
Yeah, back in that world you rejected,
Haruhi is just some stuck-up girl.
And Miss Asahina is just a cute sweet moe character.
Koizumi is a normal highschooler.
And Nagato is just a super shy book worm.
Well, most of the time anyway,
but if she heard some stupid joke I
bet she'd laugh, and then she'd blush.
And she got older, her heart
would open up a little more everyday.
You never know, she might have been like that.
But you had to go and throw away a
normal life by hitting that button.
Why is that?
Quiz time is over. Time to answer the question.
Don't you think Haruhi and all the weird
things she made happen were just a little bit fun?
Spit it out!
Yeah, of course I do!
Of course it was fun! And I loved every minute of it.
Don't go asking me stupid questions that are so…
Obvious!
You'd have to be crazy to think it wasn't fun,
only the biggest idiot in the world
would say "it wasn't fun" if they were asked.
They'd be thirty times more dense than Haruhi.
Aliens, time-travelers and espers, man.
One's enough. But no, I got to hang out with all three.
And then there's Haruhi who's
got the craziest power of them all.
And then, there's all these other
mysterious power sprinkled all over the place.
How could I not find all these stuff fun?
Ask me as many times as you
want, and my answer won't change.
Of course I do.
I guess that's it.
The other way's definitely better.
Having the world like this just doesn't feel right.
I'm sorry, Nagato.
But I like the "you" you used to
be more than the "you" you are now.
You look better without glasses anyway.
I don't know what you are saying.
Nagato.
You have to change yourself back,
change everything back to the way it was.
I can help. All you have to do is ask.
You didn't have to use all that amazing
power you have to change the world like this.
I liked things better the way they were.
Kyon,
it doesn't matter what you say.
This version of Miss Nagato doesn't have any power.
Look at her.
She is a normal girl.
Sorry.
Kyon, watch out!
I could never, ever let you hurt Miss Nagato.
What is this…What the heck is going on?
It hurts... It hurts...
It hurts...
Miss Asakura...?
You don't have anything to worry about anymore.
I'm here now.
I'll kill anything that
frightens you or tries to hurt you.
After all, that's my only reason for being here.
You should know.
This is exactly what you wished for, isn't it?
Well?
That's a lie.
There's no way Nagato would've wished for this.
The abnormality that formed inside Nagato's system,
must have caused her to create a malfunctioning Asakura.
That's it. She's Nagato's shadow.
Time to die. It'll be quick, I promise.
You're making Miss Nagato very sad.
Does it hurt? Savor that sensation.
Because a few seconds from now, it'll
be the last memory you'll ever have.
What... but how...
Why?
It's like I've seen this happen somewhere before.
Damn it. I'm blacking out.
Don't die, Kyon. Hang on!
I'm so sorry, Kyon.
I knew this would happen.
That hurts, Miss Asahi... nas?
Oh, I get it.
I'm seeing double...
So cold...
The blood won't stop...
I'm dying...
Sorry about this. But I had a good
reason for not stepping in sooner.
Don't worry. It hurt for me, too.
Who? Whatever. I don't know...
We'll take care of everything. Just go to sleep now.
Damn it...
Nagato...
Weird. I feel like I just had the most amazing dream.
Look who's decided to wake up.
You're in a deep sleep for quite a while there.
I suppose I should say "good morning" to you however,
it's the late afternoon.
I am glad you regained consciousness though.
I was starting to get really worried you wouldn't.
Oh but,
perhaps your mind is still a little hazy.
How are you feeling? Do you know who I am?
You first. Do you know who I am?
Of course I know who you are. What a strange thing to say.
When is it?
Is that really the first thing
you wonder about when you wake up?
Oh, perhaps you're trying to figure out
what's your current situation is. Is that it?
Either way, it's December the
twenty-first, 4:00 P.M. exactly.
It's the twenty-first?
Where am I anyway?
The Municipal General Hospital.
It's a nice room. I bet it's expensive.
The chairman of the hospital happens
to be an old friend of my uncle's.
He personally made all the arrangements.
That's why you get to enjoy this room.
Hate to break it to you, but I know you're lying.
Correct. The truth is, the Organization
stepped in and arranged everything.
You know, you've been unconscious
for the past three days now.
My superiors were so upset. I
had to submit a written apology.
I got quite a grilling.
I'm still wondering what I'm doing here though.
Why was I unconscious?
You don't remember?
I suppose that's normal. You
did hit your head pretty hard.
It's strange. You don't have any external signs of injury.
And your brain and internal organs are perfectly fine.
So do you know what happened to me?
Well, what happened was you
fell down the stairs at school.
In fact, it was the most
spectacular tumble I've ever seen.
I was worried for you if you wanna know the truth.
When you hit the ground, there was a bang so loud, I
wouldn't have been surprised if you'd never woke up.
I fell down the stairs at school on December eighteenth...
It was quite horrifying, really.
An ambulance came and we just watched as they
carried out your limp body and took you to the hospital.
I've never seen Miss Suzumiya go so pale before.
And Miss Nagato was the one who called the ambulance.
Her calm demeanor saved your life.
How did Miss Asahina react to it?
Exactly as you would imagine in that situation.
She was clinging to you, and crying,
and yelling your name, of course.
Do you remember what time on the eighteenth that happened?
It was in the afternoon.
The SOS Brigade was going on a shopping trip for supplies.
Shopping for what?
Oh, you don't remember that either?
On Christmas day, there is a children show
happening in Miss Suzumiya's neighborhood.
So, naturally she suggested we all get
together and put a show of our own for them.
Still making decisions for the rest of us.
Miss Suzumiya would play Santa.
And after drawing straws, you
won the role of the reindeer.
Congratulations.
Then we decided to go buy the materials
we needed to make your reindeer costume.
That was the plan, however...
As we were going down the stairs next to the club room,
you were bringing up the rear and
the next thing we knew, you fell down.
That's a dumb story.
Miss Suzumiya said when she started down
the stairs, she felt someone else there.
She thought she saw a skirt
flitting past in a corner of her eye.
However, at that time of day, we
were the only ones left in the building.
I wonder who the mystery woman is.
Do you remember seeing anyone before you fell?
Do you remember if you were pushed or not?
No, I don't.
I was pushed down the stairs by a mystery woman, huh.
That theory doesn't sound too
crazy compared to everything else.
Are you the only one here?
Were you expecting anyone in particular this whole time?
Perhaps, someone special?
We've been taking shifts and
watching over you while you slept.
That way, when you woke up you'd
always have someone here for you.
Your family's also been here.
They brought you a fresh change of clothes.
What? Why are you looking at me like that?
It's nothing. I'm just a little jealous, is all.
That's not a problem, I hope.
That's a weird thing to say considering my situation?
All the Brigade members have been taking shifts.
Miss Suzumiya said that watching out for the
safety of her subordinates was her responsibility.
She has been here the whole time. For three days.
You really had her worried. And me, too.
And you know what happens when
Miss Suzumiya's mood gets shaken up.
Well, I'll tell you all about what's being going on later.
Don't you have more pressing matters
to attend to besides chatting with me?
What? Like scribbling on her face?
That thought hadn't even crossed my mind.
You are not really going to do that, are you?
Hey.
Hey, Kyon!
Let me know when you're gonna wake up before you wake up.
You can't expect a girl to just
get up and be ready like that.
Haruhi.
Yeah, what?
You've got some drool there.
I hope you didn't do anything
stupid like scribble on my face.
No, but I wanted to.
Well, is that all you've got to say for yourself?
I guess I made you worry, didn't I? I apologize.
Fine! I accept your apology.
You made me worry but as Brigade
Leader it's my duty to worry.
Miss Asahina, how are you?
Oh, stop overreacting.
He just got a bump on the head and fainted. That's all.
I knew all along he was okay.
There's no way Kyon wasn't gonna wake up.
The SOS Brigade doesn't take vacations, guys.
We're in this together till the bitter end.
If you think getting hit on the head and
not waking up excuses you from your duties,
you've got another thing coming.
Abandoning your post for three days is unacceptable.
I'm talking fines here, fines! Plus back-pay!
That sounds reasonable. Do you have any
suggestions for how I'm gonna pay off this debt?
For starters, you have to treat all the members to tea.
For three days too.
Okay, then what?
Then you'll have to come to the Christmas party wearing
the reindeer costume and put on a show for everyone!
And you're gonna have to do it again and
again until everyone thinks it's awesome.
And if it's boring, I'm sending you to another dimension.
And you'll have to do it again at the kid's party too.
You got that?
I was awake, but they wouldn't let me leave the hospital.
They had to run a bunch of tests
so I ended up staying over night just to be safe.
My mom and sis dropped by after the hospital
called, they stayed for a little bit then left.
Now that I was alone, I finally had a chance to
think about all this stuff that had happened to me.
What would've happened if I
hadn't chosen to fix the world?
Nagato, Miss Asahina and Koizumi would
all just be normal human beings now.
And Haruhi would just be a slightly
eccentric borderline obnoxious high school girl.
But I already made my decision, didn't I.
This world is the one I like the best.
If I didn't really feel that way,
then what would have been the point
of almost dying trying to save it?
Sorry about this. But I had a good
reason for not stepping in sooner.
Don't worry. It hurt for me, too.
We'll take care of everything. Just go to sleep now.
Yeah, I guess that sounds about, right?
Hey.
I hope you weren't looking all over for me.
Not that you have any trouble finding me.
I am responsible for everything that happened.
You understand everything then?
That on December eighteenth,
you remade the world we knew and everyone in it.
Everything from April,
actually farther back than that, up to the present.
I understand.
So then why didn't you tell me about it?
I mean, you could have said something.
Wouldn't that have been better?
I don't know. I might have been
able to figure out how to help you.
Even if I did inform you, I
was malfunctioning at the time.
I would've erased the memories of our
conversations from you and restructured the world
regardless of your intentions.
And there is no guarantee that
it's not the current situation.
All I did was preserve the possibility
to return the world to its normal settings.
Allowing you to meet me on December
eighteen was critical for that to happen.
Don't forget you left me with an escape program.
That was help enough.
Nagato.
I'm so sorry.
Yuki.
Means snow, doesn't it?
Options for my punishment are being examined.
And who's gonna be doing this examination?
The Data Integration Thought Entity.
The possibility for another
malfunction on my part is uncertain.
As long as I am allowed to exist in this world,
my internal errors will continue to accumulate.
That would be dangerous for everyone.
Then you can tell them to go to hell!
You can tell this to your head honcho.
If anything happens to you or if they make you disappear,
I'll snap, I'll go crazy, you understand?
I'll do whatever it takes to bring you back. I mean it.
I might not have any power, but
I can whip Haruhi into a frenzy.
That's gonna be the trump card in my pocket.
All I have to do is say "Hi, I'm John Smith."
Oh, yeah, I know what you are
thinking. I've got the power of a loofah.
But Haruhi's got the power of a stubborn old goat.
And if Nagato disappears,
I'd reveal the whole kit and caboodle
to Haruhi and make her believe it.
And then we'd go off on a journey to find Nagato.
And Haruhi would do something big to find out
where the Data Integration Thingy had hidden Nagato.
I'd make her.
And I'd get Miss Asahina and Koizumi involved too.
Nagato's our friend, our ally.
Haruhi would never just stand by and do
nothing if one of her friends went missing.
That's the kind of person she is.
She's egotistical,
she's selfish and be downright pushy sometimes.
Our annoying, wonderful, Brigade Leader.
I don't know what kind of high-level
thing this Data Integration Thought Entity is.
And who knows what kind of horrible
power they can unleash on its enemies.
Whatever it is, I bet it's intelligent
enough to know right from wrong.
If I could talk to it I could find out.
I'd ask it why it didn't see fit to
give Nagato a more complete personality.
Like Asakura before she turns psycho.
A girl who's popular with everyone
at school, who's bright and social,
the kind of girl goes to the
malls with friends on weekends.
It could have made her someone like that, couldn't it?
Why the heck would it make
her some lonely melancholic girl
who just sits by herself reading books all day long?
What? Because she wouldn't
seem like the literary club type?
Because she wouldn't catch Haruhi's eye?
How prejudice can you get?
If it won't listen to me, then I promise, I'll
change the world again, and this time I'll use Haruhi.
It'd know she can do it.
I'll make this world a place where you're here
and the Data Integration Thought Entity isn't.
Even if we have to flip the universe over
on its side, I promise, we'll get you back!
You can go and tell that to your superiors.
Transmitting.
Thank you.
Come on, Kyon. It's morning, so wake up.
Wake up!
A couple of days later I returned home from the hospital.
Today is December the twenty-fourth.
The last day of semester.
Kouyouen Academy is back to being a private
all-girls' prep school it's supposed to be...
Taniguchi never caught that horrible cold.
And Miss Asahina and Miss Tsuruya recognized me on sight.
The world is back to normal. Thank God.
However, another critical
decision has been placed in my hands.
If me, Nagato and Miss Asahina don't
go back to the past one more time,
the world won't get fixed.
We haven't decided when that's
supposed to happen yet, though.
But whether it's now or later on down the road,
we'll take care of it once and for all.
No more looking back for me.
I had to make a choice, that's what I did.
And not in some unconscious fit
of happy insanity like Haruhi does.
Nope.
I chose this world and all the crazy
weirdness that comes with it all by myself.
It's the decision I have to live with forever.
Man, I'm so pathetic.
Now I've gone and become a responsible type.
The days when I thought it was
cool to just sit and watch are over.
And just like the other subordinate
members of the SOS Brigade,
I am an active protector of this world.
Right now Haruhi's having her Christmas
Party, and serving up a hotpot cooking.
By the way, her and Miss Asahina did
the last of the shopping and what not.
I know I'm usually the official bag carrier,
but I was given a special exemption
this time while I got to bed at home.
Haruhi being Haruhi is probably
planning some kind of switcheroo on us.
I wouldn't doubt if she change the menu at the last minute
so that everyone will be all "WOW" when she opens the lid.
I wonder what she is going to do today.
Being Haruhi, she'd go overboard and surprise us
by roll out some funky dish that's never
been attempted in the history of cooking.
This hotpot could be a threat to humankind.
Whatever, right?
A sweet fragrance wafts from the club room.
I guess they've already started cooking.
It's weird, but I feel sort of satisfaction.
I'm sure though that there'd
be more trouble before I know it.
I still have to return to the past and
help change the world back to this one.
Well, I still got some time.
I'm not saying I've got a lot,
but I know I don't have to go
back there right now, either.
You got that, world? You're okay for a bit there, right?
You don't mind if I take a little break
before going back in time and fixing you, do you?
Oh, well.
At least, wait until after I have
some of Haruhi's hotpot cooking, okay?
There. Done.
Thank you.
Here.
Wow.
Come on!
Okay.