Seriously?!
This has got to be like
the fortieth text.
And who the hell
gave her my number?!
It sure wasn't me!
Face it, I've got
a bona fide stalker.
Question is, why?
Well, it wouldn't be much use
to me if it couldn't keep up.
I get the relevant
details on your
future in ten-minute intervals.
The Diary of Future Love.
Ten minute intervals.
Which means she knows
exactly what I'm up
to pretty much all the time.
Hey, sweetie.
♪ opening song ♪
So here's the breakdown.
I've got a diary that lays
out everything I'm going
to take note of before
I experience it.
But I'm just one of twelve
people with a similar way of
sneaking peaks at the future;
all trying to pick
each other off,
because the last man
standing gets to be a god.
Evidently the guy they call
Third drew the short straw.
Did I really kill someone?
Mr. Hiyama is, uh, out sick
today, so I'll be filling
in for him as best I can
if you'll bear with me.
Guess we'll start
with a headcount.
Please say "here"
when I call your name.
What am I supposed
to do with this thing?
Just having it makes
me a marked man.
And it's not exactly like
I can ask anyone for help.
No, no, no.
It's tempting, sure,
but she's stalking you.
First things first,
you might say.
Well put.
Excuse me.
Can we, like, uh.
Talk for sec?
Right now really
isn't the best time.
I'm gonna be late for P.E.
Just hit me up
later on today, alright?
Try to wait it out.
Okay.
Suppose that's
the best I can hope for.
Sorry. Can you
maybe help me?
I'm trying to
find the faculty lounge.
Any idea if I'm getting warmer?
I figure somebody there should
have some answers about Hiyama.
Uh.
What's her story?
Guy's your homeroom
teacher, right?
Hey... did you know he also
happened to be a killer?
Okay, I'm gonna run on ahead.
Sure.
See you 'round.
Word is your grades are up.
And if a gal asks around,
seems most of your classmates
think you've been acting kind
of uppity the past few days.
Don't you think
Hiyama's absence
is a little on the
suspicious side?
I mean, after all,
the killer died yesterday.
His Murder Diary didn't amount
to much at the moment of truth.
He was in the process of hunting
First when he got upstaged.
In case you're having
trouble following me,
the guy shaping your
mind was Third.
No way!
Sweet phone you got.
I was dead-on.
You're First, aren't you?
Pleased to make
your acquaintance!!!
Dead end?!
No!
Too late.
The name's Uryuu Minene, kiddos.
Alias Ninth.
And if Third was the appetizer,
I'm the main course!
Au revoir!
I'm gonna die.
It says Dead End in three hours.
Hey.
We're gonna survive this.
She's not gonna get you
because I'm gonna get her.
How can she talk
about taking a life like
it's some random errand?
I've got your back.
That's what I do.
So you keep telling me.
Well I need somebody
to, least for now.
She may not be stable but
she's better than nothing.
Yuno, I...
I need you to get
me through this.
Hey.
For you, sweetheart.
Anything.
I'm not using her.
I'm utilizing.
Attention all you grub-pawed,
snot-nosed little tadpoles.
This soviet bloc eyesore of
a pen they keep you bricked up
in till you're
hormones burn out?
It's been rigged.
We're talking
demolitions-grade explosives
decked out with motion sensors.
'Less you wanna blow up,
stay where you are.
That's right boys and girls.
The whole student body
is now my hostage!
We better keep moving, huh?
I'll protect you whatever
the cost, my love.
Whatever the cost.
Looks like everybody's holed
up in the other building.
They know she's serious.
Oh crap...!
The stairs are gonna
blow out underneath us!
Then we find another route.
No need to make
this complicated.
My diary just rewrote itself.
Well, yeah.
We didn't do what it said,
so the future changed.
This is why your diary in
particular is so useful...
...you jot down everything.
It's called the Indiscriminate
Diary because you basically
keep a record of
whatever you see.
So, that means?
It means what we
should be doing now is
monitoring Ninth's
activity with it.
Now it's rewriting itself when
I didn't even do anything!
She's making a play.
Our movements
are interlocked now.
If her future changes,
so does ours.
Apparently a bomb is about
to go off in classroom 2C.
Look out!!!
Quick! Read the next entry!
Looks like it says.
There's another
explosion down the hall!
I'm not going to lie.
Yuno is really good at this.
And, the future
branches off yet again.
Got you running
in circles, pipsqueak?
I have officially made a
very good life choice today.
This is a breeze!
Or not?
Kay. What's it say now?
Huh?
Oh.
Oh no!
Are you alright?!
Ow.
Yeah.
I think so.
New tactic.
If it's at all possible.
Focus on how it says you
react to the explosions.
Like, what they do to me?
What is it?
What's the matter?
It's just I...
I don't write about
my reactions.
That's the whole point.
I keep a record of
what's going on
without really
including myself.
I don't get involved.
My diary doesn't have
anything in it about
what actually happens to me.
Squirmy little tadpole,
aren't you?
No sweat.
So your diary isn't much
for pertinent details
about what happens to you.
You might say mine kind
of picks up the slack there.
I'm good at keeping an
eye on my sugar bear.
Okay.
C'mon, pookie!
Use your head.
We can coordinate
the information in
your diary with the
information in mine
to piece together every
little thing that's going
to go down within
a mile of you!
You'll be invincible!
That's brilliant.
Yuki, I told you
I've got your back.
Think of me as a
survival resource
you can tap whenever you want!
The hell's wrong with me?
Look at us.
What is it now?
How pathetic am I?
Thinking I was watching
everything from a safe distance.
I kept to a strict policy
of staying out of things.
But the truth is I'd have
given an eye not to
be so cordoned off.
I was just lonely, you know?
I wanted to be the
guy everybody liked.
Talk to that one girl.
Deep down, though.
I was just too scared
of getting hurt.
Is that irony or what?
I'm always calling
myself an observer.
When really I'm just a coward.
Stop talking like
your life's over, silly.
You got at least an
hour and a half before
your Dead End
becomes a reality.
I say we nix the
mope-fest and get
ourselves over to
the other building.
I mean, think about it;
they're all your friends, right?
They're bound to help us!
Only thing that
worries me is why his
Dead End is scheduled for 2:04.
She could've killed
him at any time.
Why is she putting it off?
Alright then, chief.
We've got the SWAT snipers
in position on the rooftop.
Call them off.
Beg pardon, sir?!
This is Uryuu Minene
we're dealing with here!
What kind of
leverage do we have
if you don't put her
in the crosshairs?
She's too clever.
We wouldn't have
any leverage either way.
The little fury has the
bombs programmed to go
off on mass the
second her heart stops.
She's made herself
into the ultimate trigger.
But that's crazy!
She's right.
What I've got to do right now
is think about my classmates.
They'll have to take
the whole Future Diary
thing at face value, sure.
But if they can
just hear me out,
there's no reason we
can't pull through this.
I don't like this.
It's too quiet.
Too long since my
diary's rewritten itself.
I know him!
I'm sorry, what?
Kousaka, hey!
Hold on.
This isn't right.
Why are they out
of their classrooms?
Oh no.
Yuki!
Here's the deal I'm after Amano.
Pool your resources
and deliver him to me
like the good little
drones you are, and hey...
I'd have to disarm the
bombs for a sec, huh?
Do me that kindness
ladies and germs,
and no one else
needs to die today.
Truss him up and toss his
cell phone out of reach.
Watch out for
his girlfriend, too.
Get him down here,
and we're Even Steven.
This isn't real.
We're supposed to
be in this together!
Why are you doing this?!
I'd stay right there
if I were you.
There's a minefield between us.
Let go of me, please!
I've got to protect him!
That'll do everyone,
much obliged.
Motion sensors are back online,
by the way so get comfy.
They're your friends, right?
They're bound to help us.
It was my idea to reach
out to these people.
I told him they
were his friends.
This is all my fault!
They're monsters.
They couldn't care less
if Yuki lives or dies.
They...
They've made a liar out of me!
End of the line, First.
Too bad so sad.
I can't let this happen!
Whatever the cost.
This is what you all get for
selling out my poor Yuki!!!
Anyone who treats my man like
a bargaining chip can
get blown to hell!
Looks like we've
got a loose cannon.
Chief, look at this!
I'm going in.
Stop it, Yuno.
You're going to kill everyone.
It's all over.
I can't do this anymore!
I'm gonna die.
I'm really gonna die.
Hey, I'm not all bad.
Your backstabbing
friends can go with you.
In ten minutes this place will
go up like a munitions factory!
Ten minutes.
2:04 p.m.
My Dead End.
That's how it happens.
You haven't lived
till you've seen
what I can do with plastique.
You're at 11;
we need you at a 4.
Due courtesy when on my turf.
How's it hanging, First?
Do I know you?
Ah, no worries.
It's not a surprise that
you don't remember me.
Stop wasting my time, Fourth.
Stop wasting mine.
We both know
what you're here for.
Did she say?
It's a little complicated.
All you really need
to know right now
is that she isn't here for you.
It's me she wants.
Say hello to the Case Diary.
It lets me know how
jobs I'm on will pan out.
Being a god doesn't
do it for me.
My cup of tea is bringing
homicidal maniacs to justice.
Excuse me.
Not to break up your
little pow wow over there.
But I'd kind of like to start
laying out a few demands.
I'll just take your silence,
as a green light.
So...
Blow the little
bastard's brains out.
Then do yourself!
It's bad enough I have to
wrangle with a whipped teenager.
I'm not about to
leave a sooth saying
homicide cop on the loose!
No dice, Ninth.
Fine!
Then everybody can go to hell!
Don't take it personally.
She's painted me into a corner.
For what it's worth, your death
is going to weigh on me.
Naturally.
I mean, how long did
I think a wuss like me
would hold out in this game?
I'm just a wallflower.
Terrified of life.
When push came to
shove, I had to use a
crazy girl just to
make it this far.
Death was only a matter of time.
Please.
Promise me my death
won't be for nothing.
Promise me it won't
be as meaningless
as my stupid life's
always been.
Yuno.
Don't just sit there.
Get your diary.
If you really want your
life to mean something,
then get off your ass.
Show us you're a force
to be reckoned with.
And maybe help
your little friend?
Turn that fear to advantage.
Dress it up as a game face.
Sure, that'll do.
Go for it!
He's out of his damn head.
The minefield!
Yuki! Left!
Son of a...
Kay, I don't like
where this is going!
Veer to the right!
Seriously?!
The little tramp's
a diary user!!!
Enough playing cowboy, Fourth!
Now left! Then another
left after that!
Shut up!
Crap!
Now what?!
Fine!
I'll do this manually!
Yuki!
You can do it!
You little turds!
Shit!
Ninth!
Oh shit!
Oh shit, oh shit, oh shit!!!
Shit!!!!
Give up, Ninth.
Only an idiot would
resist in your condition.
Screw you!!!
What the?
My diary's got a name, too!
The Escape Diary!
Ninth and the others will
be falling all over
themselves to get at you, kid.
When they pounce, I'll be there
to put a stop to this madness.
Matter of fact, I
propose the three of us
form a partnership to
ensure exactly that.
We can call ourselves the
Future Diary Alliance or
something like that.
Corny, I know.
But are you with me?
Hell yeah!
What do you say we get going?
I say "sure."
♪ closing song ♪
Hey-o, fans!
I'm Murmur, a
character that you'll
notice doesn't get
much screen time.
Yeah. Sure, they'll
tack me on the end.
But it's really
just for exposition.
See, the point of this
segment is to spell out things
you may not have
gotten on your own.
Nice of them, yeah?
Well, honestly, we're trying to
keep you interested by laying
out the back stories of the
other diary users you know,
in case you're not sold
on the principle cast yet.
For example, it's got
to be bugging you how
Fourth and Ninth
knew who Yuki was.
See, the thing is, both
were originally on
the trail of Third, who,
you'll remember from episode
one, was a serial killer.
Fourth is a cop.
Ninth a hardened criminal.
Familiar with society's dark
underbelly, they both knew some
of the diaries would
be used for evil.
Fourth's diary keeps track of
what the future holds in store
for the cases he's working,
so when he was after
Hiyama, owie, owie, owie.
He knew when
Yuki got questioned.
So, wait why did
you need to know that?
Oh right cause when
Yuki killed Third, he was
already on Fourth's radar, so
Ninth pieced it together.
Anyway, what First is in for
next is anyone's guess.
Unless of course you
had a Future Diary,
in which case you'd
be up to speed.
See you next time!