Ugh, this heat.
Give me a break;
it's like ten below Hell.
This place better have the
AC cranked to arctic.
Hope he's happy to see his dad.
I mean, it's been
the better part of a year.
♪ opening song ♪
One, two, three.
What's the matter, champ?
You giving up?
I've sat on couches
with more upmh!
Have I mentioned
lately that I hate my life?
So... We're good to
leave his recovery up to you?
Look, I'm a lot of things,
but I've never been one to
squelch on a fair deal.
Wait, what deal?
Be gentle.
Our boy's very delicately built.
Ugh.
The hell am I in for?
A world of hurt if you even
think of wussing out on me.
Follow my regimen
and killing Seventh
will be like shooting
fish in a barrel.
But, why do I have
to take them out?
I suck at this!
Which is why I'm molding you?
Now give me another set!
Uh... Sorry.
Kind of flying blind.
I'm looking for my son's room
and the receptionist
wasn't all that clear.
Um...
How's it going, Dad?
Holy crap!
What kind of HMO do you have?
Is she strictly yours or
can you share with pops?
I'm his next of kin!
Now straddle me like a
jockey does a thoroughbred!
The hell do I look like to you?
One...
Oh you are beyond pathetic!
Not even one?
My Dad...
That's right!
Give it to me!
Ah, course!
I must be getting
soft in the pate.
The gal looks good in a nurse's
uniform, you got to admit.
Yeah, well...
Now that that's cleared up.
Thanks for visiting.
No sweat, tiger.
Your dad's got to
keep an eye on you.
Oh yeah!
Get your tentacles off me
or I'll make calamari out
of your manhood!
Glad Mom's not here to see this.
Now there's a thought.
If they'd have just come to some
kind of truce and
stayed together,
we could've gone star-gazing
as a proper family.
Is it stupid of me
to wonder whether or
not they'll ever
bury the hatchet?
Oh, son of a...
Get off!
What if I need the
kind of healing
only a sultry nurse can give?
You want healing?!
Fine!
Consider yourself my boot
camp's newest enrollee!
Let your kid win and I go
medieval on your ass!
Sounds good to me.
I'm in this so my boy
doesn't have to go it alone.
Whatever he needs to
help him through rehab,
I'm totally on board.
That is, if you're not
too old for my help.
Uh...
I'm not too old if you're not to
proud to crawl back to mom.
I mean...
You promised me we'd
go stargazing as a family.
Tough to do with you guys apart.
So, yeah...
Ah, what the hell...
Let's make a deal.
I'll talk to your mother
if you do better than me
at whatever Sergeant
Nurse here cooks up.
Kay!
I got to hand it to you,
that was a hell of a call.
Yeah, well.
Once I let the wheels
turn it seemed obvious
Seventh's strategy would center
on stealing their phones.
The question now is how long
they'll let the
two of them live.
Talk about a reversal, huh?
Who'd have thought Ninth's role
in all this would be what it is?
It makes for good
reading, at least.
Yeah.
I'm not going to start
worrying that their thing
for each other is
stronger than ours.
Dumbass kids.
Spare me.
Easy, don't you think so?
Hey, love of my life.
Mind telling me
what the hell this is?
What?
According to this you've
been out carousing with
some floozy I've
never even heard of.
What's that about?
Who is she to you?
No idea what you're
talking about, babe.
Don't start with the act.
The truth's staring at
me in black and white.
That's not my phone!
Are you nuts?!
Shut your hole!
This bitch is on
cloud nine over some
stupid present you gave her?
Are you kidding me?!
If this is how you cut me loose!
Whoa, tiger lily,
don't even talk like that!
I ain't got it in me.
You swore to me
that I would always and
forever be the only
woman in your heart!
This doesn't make sense.
Does she really think
I'm the kind of
douche bag to
two-time my old lady?
She knows better.
Right?
Oh, and now the skank wants
to talk to you about somebody.
She wants you
to drop me for her!
No way!
I was a notch in your belt.
Oh god...
Look, mama bear, whatever
you're reading, it's not...
"It's a ring.
I almost don't
dare to believe it but...
Here it is.
I'm wearing it right now.
He gave it to me all wrapped up
with a bow and everything."
Wait a sec.
This is my phone.
Ah.
Now I get it.
So much for going
about this all stealth-like.
I was waiting to tell you.
Marco!
I'm so sorry
I lashed out at you!
Can you ever forgive me?
Aw...
No worries.
I love you.
Better get off my
ass and buy a ring.
Alright.
This is going
to be about stamina.
Suck it up.
There's no
bronze or silver here.
Show me how
many pull-ups you got.
Oh, burn.
Hate to tell you
this, son, but...
...in college these
were my specialty.
My phys-ed nickname
was Pull-up Paul.
Your name's Kurou, you doofus.
Ready.
Set...
One.
Two!
Three!
An even ten.
So fast you couldn't see me.
You better wake up
and get with program if you
think I'm dumb enough
to fall for that crap!
Hey...
Your old man moves
like a cheetah on speed.
Sorry, half pint:
this round goes to him.
Moving on now.
This is rigged!
Let's see what you've got
in the way of grip strength.
Good luck cheating on this one.
Hey, what do know?
Another one of my things.
Boy, this takes me back.
The guys at the gym used
to call me Iron Grip Gary.
You're such a freak.
Thirty-eight point O?
That's got to be a record!
Beat that, Gary.
Read them and weep.
Someone want to tell me why
the gage on his isn't digital?!
Iron Grip indeed.
Will you get a grip on reality?!
Oh, I see what you
did there, buck-o.
Nice one.
Don't think I'm not aware
you're itching to see me lose!
Don't get all butt-hurt, champ.
Relax, have fun.
This is about quality
time with your dad.
She's right.
When's the last time he and
I have horsed around like this?
I don't even remember.
Aw, my man's having a blast.
And here I was
waiting for this guy to
lunge for his jugular,
or whatever.
Nah...
His father's just
as cool as his mom.
Which is a good thing.
A very, very good thing.
Okay.
This, gents, is the final event.
I want you to huff it
to the top of this hill.
I've been robbed
in every single category.
But...
Winning this one is
worth a hundred points.
So the person in last place can
still make a big comeback.
So, the other events
were for what exactly?
And this time the judge
won't favor either one of you.
Yuki...
Were you serious?
About your mom
and me hooking back up.
I'm assuming you know why
we got divorced in the
first place, right?
I mean, your mom
told you 'bout that.
Well, uh...
Thing is...
With money...
I'm kind of like a chimp
with a loaded gun.
Which means, right now
your dad's about
three million in the hole?
I had no idea.
Nobody to blame but me.
On your mark.
Get set.
Wow, Dad.
Who am I kidding?
They're over.
I guess I always thought
they'd broke it off over
something mundane;
I didn't know they
were that bad off.
There's really no point
to this race, is there?
Yuki...
Word to the wise.
Give up and you forfeit the
right to bitch
about the outcome.
Ok.
Take it from coach the race
doesn't always
go to the swiftest.
Sometimes it goes to the
guy with the most patience.
If hard is all it
takes for you to bow out
I don't want to know you.
And I'm a frigging terrorist.
Worth bearing in mind.
Okay.
If nothing else,
fight to make him see.
Once he knows
where you're coming from,
his reaction might surprise you.
See you up top!
Huh...
Fight to make him see.
Maybe.
Aw, what the hell.
Alright, Dad...
Let's do this!
Where'd he go?
Hey, kiddo.
I want you to know I don't
take what you said lightly.
And don't worry
about my money issues.
I may have found a
way back into the black.
Sorry to bail on you,
but something's come up.
Be sure to refuel
before you head home.
Thanks, Dad.
Did I do what you wanted?
Sorry to be covert.
We want Yuki
to think Ninth
has a plan to put the
kibosh on Seventh.
It's the only way to
tempt the lovebirds
away from destroying
his phone outright;
if they think there's info to be
had, the pair will hold off
till they can glean
as much as possible.
Yeah, but it's a bald-faced lie.
That it is.
But a good enough one to buy
us some game-plan time.
Believe me; I'll take
whatever advantage I can
get against these people if
it tones down the bloodshed.
Anyway.
Thanks for
helping with the ruse;
it's going to save Yuki's life.
Solid reasoning.
Sounds like you've thought
it through pretty good.
It was Akise's idea, actually.
Well, whoever's
brainchild this was,
somebody owes me
for playing it cool.
Heh...
How about the gratitude of a man
doing his late captain's will?
Stop it.
I hate when people
talk about the
dead like they can be helped.
If they're in the ground, it's a
waste of your frigging time.
Believe me.
Charity is much
better spent on the living.
Unless you're the
kind of moron who
prefers to let the
past consume him.
Well done, love.
I'm proud.
Come on!
Where is it?!
It's got to be here somewhere!
God damn it don't
play games with me,
I need my ticket out
of the rat race!
It's Amano.
Go ahead.
Look, yeah, I know, it's...
Yes! But you're going
to have to give me more time!
I'm closing in on it, I know.
I'm in his room right now.
It has to be here.
Of course!
Listen, I just...
I mean, you're not going
to screw me on this, right,
I can trust you?
You're going to
forgive my debt right?
And all I have do is
destroy Yuki's phone?
I must be hearing things.
Good afternoon.
Am I speaking to
Kamado Ueshishta?
The proprietor of Mother's
House orphanage?
Yes.
You are indeed.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
I have a search warrant here.
Ah...
Well, now.
I'm not one for
getting in the way so.
According to police, the
suspects in the Kousaka incident
have been traced to
a local orphanage
and are thought to be
hiding in the vicinity.
No word yet whether a
substantial link can
be established.
Wow. That guy's a damn
good cop. I'm impressed
he tracked them
down to an orphanage.
Who cares where they've been
hiding out so long as
they're caught, right?
I hope they throw away the key.
No kidding.
Not again!
I mean, I told you they don't
serve cake here, okay?!
Will you please stop
trying to kill my parents?!
You can't stab someone
whenever you feel like it!
And you can't
poison them either!
Question.
Who do you trust more?
Me or your deadbeat dad?
What?
It may be hard to
believe, but I'm pretty
sure your old man's in
cahoots with Eleventh.
Come on!
That's crap!
Think about it, my love.
How far do you think
he'd go to clear his debt?
I saw him going through your
things while you were out.
He's was after your phone.
No.
Uh-uh...
It's wasn't what it looked like.
Honey, it was exactly
what it looked like.
Eleventh is using him to
clear you out of the way.
Maybe your dad doesn't know
what he's got himself into.
I don't care...
I have a call waiting at
reception for a Yuno Gasai.
Hello?
Keep your paws off his
old man, sugar bumps.
You son of a...
Come on, now.
Just 'cause you're mad
we're keeping tabs on you
doesn't mean you
got to get all testy.
Cool that he's connected to
Eleventh and Ninth, by the way.
Keeps him intriguing
enough to be useful.
Do exactly what I tell you
and he'll live a little longer.
Get cute and I'm willing to live
without the info
in your diaries.
I guess it wasn't
a wrong number.
What's up?
So that was one of our new
"friends" from the other day.
For some reason...
they want me to escort daddy
dearest to Sakurami Tower.
Why me?
I don't understand.
Apparently you have
a role to play in all this.
I have no idea what.
But if we want our phones,
we've got to do as they say.
Wait...
What's with your phones?
Oh, you?
Sorry, I figured Yuki
would've told you.
These guys, basically
stole our phones
and are holding them hostage.
If we want them back,
we got to play ball.
And that means bringing
you along for the ride.
Just so you know,
I'm not on board with this.
It's a stupid idea!
I'm sorry.
If you can think
of anything that'd
give us an edge, I'm all ears.
She's just going to waltz up
to them and hand dad over.
Well, I've got news for
her it won't be that easy.
I'll be protecting him.
Don't look so worried;
I've got a few tricks.
'Cause when the going gets
tough, the tough get squirrelly.
This acorn will crack.
Trust me; in
college they used to
call your old man
the Nutcracker.
Yeah...
Sure.
Brave of you to show up.
Respect.
Are you the ones
who wanted my kid
and his girlfriend
to bring me here?
Oh yes.
And the pleasure is all ours.
I really can't thank you enough.
No! Dad!
Not too shabby for
a day's haul, huh?
Having him here
means we don't got to
put up with you being
alive anymore.
Hey... give me back my phone?!
Wait a minute.
You know I've got half a mind to
stomp on the damn things now.
Except that
really ain't our way.
Come at me First.
No tricks.
No talk.
I want to know if you're the
type of guy who'll take on a
dude twice his size to
save his piece of shit father.
I can't let them take him!
I'm his son and it's
my responsibility!
Dad!
I'm coming for you!
Yuki, no!
And the hits just keep
on coming don't they, runt?
It's not all bad.
At least now we all
know you got a spine!
No!
I...
My dad made me promise
that we'd go look at the stars!
Ha!
I'm on the verge of getting
him back with Mom!
Hot damn to that!
I've got this, my love.
Hold on.
They're in here somewhere.
They have to be.
Likely where these
bastards can get their
hands on them fast if
things start getting ugly.
Please don't do this!
I just want us to be a family!
Tough shit, kid.
Dad?
What?
Hold on.
What is he doing?
No...
No, he couldn't.
There's no way.
Think about it, my love.
How far do you think he'd
go to clear his debt?
Stop it.
You're my father!
You can't!
This isn't happening!!!
Wait, I'm...
Ai, look out!
That phone was a fake, Yuki.
You're okay.
These jokers made
a couple of decoys
to keep us on our
toes, apparently.
The real ones are right here.
Good thing they didn't go to the
trouble of duplicating
the scuff marks.
It might've taken me longer to
catch on to the
trick if they had.
Your dumb asshole
of a father fell
for it hook
line and sinker.
Did I do good, pookie?
Please tell me I did good.
Son, please.
Give that to me.
Once my debt gets wiped,
I'll buy you a new phone.
Sky's the limit.
Whatever model
you want, it's yours.
Wait, of course!
Dad doesn't know my
life's tied to this thing!
Look, I wish it were that easy.
I can't.
What the hell?!
Bad news, Marco.
Time's up.
I'm razing this
puppy to the ground.
Ta, you punk!
Them's the breaks, man.
We're ahead of schedule.
You can take it from
here, though, right?
--Yuki!
--Look out!
Wha...
What's happening?
Question.
Who do you trust more?
Me or your deadbeat dad?
♪ closing song ♪
Great...
I didn't get a room number.
Stupid receptionist.
Ugh.
Um, excuse me, nurse?
I'm talking to you.
Is there something I
can help you with, sir?
Uh.
Yeah.
I, need some help?
Ah!
My policy is I only help
on a quid pro quo basis.
Alright...
So, what seems
to be the problem?
Well...
I guess you could say I'm, lost.
Hospital's big.
Existentially.
Oh. Right.
I borrowed something
I'm not able to give back.
Scratch?
What the hell.
Yes.
See, though, I'm what
you might call a free spirit.
Responsibility not your bag?
That's another way
of putting it, I guess.
So your "devil-may-care"
attitude has landed
you in the money pit.
That's the long
and short of it, yeah.
Don't get me wrong
I have no illusions.
I know I can't keep this up.
Why not?
The sky keeps
right on being blue.
The clouds are still white.
The earth renews itself,
time goes in cycles,
we're just inflections of
eternity, blah, blah, blah.
Free spirit.
I like that thought.
Don't think I'm following you.
Of course you aren't, silly!
Whoa.
That was deep.