First quarter moon.
Half light.
Half dark.
We're a lot alike.
Don't you think, my love?
♪ opening song ♪
Ninth is really starting to
grate on my damn nerves.
Bleh.
Let the tramp do her worst.
The day some stupid
Escape Diary holds
a candle to yours,
I'll eat my crown.
Sure... Whatever.
C'mon, don't start
giving me attitude.
If first so much
as takes a leak,
we know about it ten
minutes in advance.
Kind of a hint there.
You might want
to track them down.
Yeah.
I shouldn't be doing this.
The less I interact with Yuki's
second incarnation, the better.
It's not like the playing
field's the same anymore.
I didn't want to kill him
but he wouldn't kill me.
The world would've ended if
one of us hadn't bit the dust.
There'd have been no
more me, no more him.
No more anything.
He lost faith in me;
yet somehow,
I couldn't bring myself
to lose faith in him.
I owe him a goodbye, that's it.
Next up I try my luck with
Yuki's third incarnation.
One way or another, damn it,
I'm going to make this work!
What now?
It's an ambulance.
Yuki called for one earlier.
Yuno!
Dad, what're you doing.
Are you hurt?!
What is this?
The EMT's called me;
I came as soon as I could!
Anybody injured?
Look me in the eye.
If it's something your
mother did, I want to know.
Dad.
Mom.
This isn't right.
You look, different somehow.
It's like.
I can't explain it.
You're taller?
Stop it, stop it, stop it!
Are you trying to
create a paradox?!
What you're trying
to do is beyond dumb!
Only a moron would
dream it up to begin with.
I don't give a damn what
you think my chances are,
I'm saving both versions of her!
There's still time
in this iteration of reality.
So stuff it!
Are you hearing yourself?
Grow up!
I'm telling you the
only way to deal with this
mess is to kill the bad one
outright and be done with her!
Like hell.
Fine, then.
You can ride this
short bus by yourself.
Think about it.
What?
This whole world.
Everything is impossible
here so why shouldn't I try.
Because the world doesn't care.
You can't have your
cake and eat it, too.
You have to choose.
I won't hold it against
you if you want out.
Like I care either way.
Best of luck to you.
She weighs a ton.
Another rewrite.
She's hot on our trail now.
Don't be scared, Yuno.
I'll protect you.
She's going to have
to go through me, first.
I love you.
I mean, after all
we've been through.
What kind of guy would I be if
you hadn't grown on me, right?
Here it is.
The place where it all began.
Seems like forever ago.
It's okay.
I'll be right back.
Time to end this.
Alright then.
Now what?
I'm sorry it's
got to be this way!
So am I!
I know your moves!
Murmur!
He's going for the fire hose!
That's right, you
little bastard dance
like the meat puppet you are!
Ha ha! Show me how
long you can dance!
They're in full swing.
Excuse me?
Forget it.
Talking to myself.
Anyway, listen
carefully, Kurusu.
You're boy has
a heart condition.
It hasn't been detected yet,
but if you wait much longer
he'll die before he's
reached another birthday.
Get him checked out now,
and there might be
something you can do about it.
Who the hell is this?
There...
I kept my side of the bargain.
Try not to be such an
asshole in this universe.
You've got to be kidding!
It's time to die!
Follow him Murmur he's
heading down the hallway!
They've got me bouncing
back and forth like a pinball.
Her diary knows exactly
where I'm going to be.
And you know what?
That's perfect.
She got him.
He's hurt.
Wait.
This is.
Oh god!
This isn't what I want!
I'm on borrowed time
at this point, huh?
She's going to stab me
in the neck before too long.
Except...
I've got just a little
bit of wiggle room.
Wow... You are a
reckless S.O.B., Yuki.
No wonder Ninth
got the hell out of Dodge.
No.
I can't think like that.
I'm talking Yuno out
of this version of Reality.
Period.
Whatever it takes.
She can be Goddess of
the Second Iteration.
Even if I have to
die to make that happen.
Best option, really.
Hell, only option.
So, suck it up!
Enough is enough Yuno!
You have to stop chasing me!
Shut up.
Only one way to make this work.
Get that damn
phone away from her,
and the future will
be a clean slate.
If she's helpless,
she can be persuaded!
Just come at me, bro!
Queen Murmur specializes
in taking out idiots!
What?!
My Dead End comes
by Yuno's hand.
The imp's got nothing!
Yuno!
Damn it, Yuki!
Why do you always
have to interfere?!
Because I love you,
you crazy bitch!
Oh no.
I thought she'd
do it close-range.
How did I only graze him?
Did his words throw me off?
No.
I...
Maybe try this on for size!
Not on my watch!
Time's up, sweetheart
my Dead End's a no-show.
Listen to reason, Yuno.
Go back to the
Second Iteration and rule it.
The sky's the limit.
So that's your
big strategy, huh?
Why you got to be such
a pain in the ass?!
Huh?
Boom!
Good night!
It's so obvious.
I didn't see it.
Denial runs pretty
deep, I guess.
I love you, too, Yuki.
Diaries are generally
about how you feel, right?
Core of Deus, grant me dominion
over the Spheres of Causality!
I so get it now, Pookie.
I'm in love!
Damn it, kid!
So your daughter and your
husband are both missing?
Yes.
The EMT said something about
my husband meeting them, but...
Sorry, give me one moment.
Yes, This is Kurusu.
They're in full swing.
Excuse me?
Forget it.
Talking to myself.
Anyway, listen
carefully, Kurusu.
You're boy has
a heart condition.
It hasn't been detected yet,
but if you wait much longer
he'll die before he's
reached another birthday.
Get him checked out now,
and there might be
something you can do about it.
Who the hell is this?!
Must be something going around.
I've got to get
an unlisted number.
Heads up, chief!
We've got an explosion at
the elementary school!
You got to be kidding.
Odds are I just
listened in on it.
Son of a.
On your feet, sleeping beauty.
I was just resting my eyes!
Get a move on, people!
Somebody help me!
What's going on?
Aw, neat-o!
Lady Tsubaki.
Your mother and father
shall be leaving
with Funatsu in a
matter of moments.
I thought you should know.
Have them wait a while.
I don't recommend
travel just now.
What in heaven's
name is going on?
Miss Matron!
I think we've got a situation!
Some Big Wig
wants to talk with you!
What have we
learned about loitering?
That freaks give
you hell for it!
Dude, you look
like you've seen a ghost.
Dad.
Mom.
Sit down; we need to talk about
where to set up the telescope.
Better warn your appetite;
I made Salisbury steak.
No way.
How is the jacket I've wanted
forever suddenly
part of my wardrobe?
And this dart board.
And a frigging myna bird.
Not a bad place to
hang your hat, right?
Think of it like
a mirror where your
heart's every desire is
reflected flawlessly.
I used Deus' core to build you
a kind of personal
Never-Never Land.
Yu--!
Why can't I say her name?
What've you done to me?
Nothing love.
You're living in an illusion
where I don't exist.
My name can't leave your lips
because you've never
heard it before.
I'm sorry.
This is...
My way of breaking up.
My theory was incorrect.
I thought if I killed the 2.0
version of you
I could end all this.
That I could hop on
over to the Third Iteration
and live happily ever after.
I was wrong.
I didn't think
everything through.
My brain is all over the map.
I'm sorry.
It's the only way to
clear out the cobwebs.
Don't think for a
second I don't love you.
The Second Iteration's simply
out of the question for me now.
No it's not!
Listen... You'll be
its goddess;
you'll have control over
how things will play out!
No I won't!
Not where it matters!
You'll still be dead!
It's like every
other version of the game;
if a winner isn't chosen, the
whole thing goes up in smoke.
This world needs a god.
Think of this like
I'm nominating you.
Please don't be upset with me.
Everybody gets
something out of it, right?
You get to live and I get
to try my luck with the
third version of you in
the universe next door.
Even as a goddess,
I amount to less
than nothing without
you in my heart.
So this is it, then.
You're just going to leave
me marooned here.
And you'll go on
butchering everyone!
Over and over again!
You'll take the same stupid
risks that'll lead us nowhere!
Don't make me.
I don't want to say it.
Think about it.
I'd have fallen for anyone
who'd let me cling to them.
I'm sorry, but
you know it's true.
You needed to be protected.
I needed somebody to fawn over.
We only worked cause
our issues dovetailed.
Hi there, cutie.
The hell is this?!
Good, you're sitting.
Because guess what?
I'm totally gaga over you.
No!
The real Wakaba would
never talk like that!
Take me.
No.
Knock it off!
I've wanted this for so long.
You have no idea.
Get off of me!
This isn't real.
This isn't real!
Yuno made this for me!
She's the one I love!
Not you!
Goodbye.
Stop it!!!
Okay.
I get it.
We were codependent.
I accept that.
But I wasn't just using her.
There was more to it.
So much more.
Sup.
What's with the face?
You look like someone just
stomped your heart into the mud.
Exactly what's in it
for you to help him?
Anyway I slice it, it's
never made sense to me.
I don't know.
I'll get back to you
after I've figured out
why birds fly south
for the winter.
It's probably just instinct.
Might as well ask
why they fly at all.
Kind of like love.
Either you go with the flow or
convince yourself you are.
Enough philosophy for tonight.
I vote we leave the Big
Questions to our fists!
Murmur!
I shatter your restraints!
How's this a thing?
You were half-dead a second ago!
You all pumped up to
play junior astronomer?
The telescope I
got's professional grade.
Seriously?!
Every now and then,
your dad gets it right.
I say we find the
highest plot of land
we can get to and set up camp.
Hell yeah!
Any constellation whose
skirt you fancy looking up?
Dad!
You're such a freak.
Ah.
Here we go.
Meal fit for a king.
Bon appetite!
Stop ogling the chef
and eat while it's hot.
Alright.
Rub-a-dub, thanks
for the grub.
Wow, mom.
This is amazing.
Eat it slow.
I'm packing you black holes
a gut-busting lunch as it is.
You really couldn't
ask for a prettier day
than this to go star-gazing.
How bout we hit Misaka Pass
on the way to the observatory?
The sky practically
touches the ground.
Trust me, we've got
more than enough
food to make the trip on
if you're feeling up to it.
I made that tulip fried chicken.
Wow...
Sounds awesome!
Hey, mind if I get
seconds of this, though?
I swear, champ.
The heck do you put it?
Something wrong, sweetheart?
Uh...
Nothing.
Just thinking
about a dream I had.
Oh yeah?
It was pretty messed up.
I was in this, like,
fight to the death
using cell phones that
told you the future.
Uh huh.
Someone ate
leftovers before bed.
I totally fell in
love with this girl.
She was a stalker, or something.
Those are the best kind.
I got to say I never really
saw you going for that type.
Was she pretty at least,
or are we talking psycho troll?
She was...
She was always there for me.
No matter what.
Like you guys.
And I was...
I was just so mean
to her sometimes.
♪ closing song ♪
Yuno!
Have you...
I don't know...
It's just...
You look taller since
the last time I saw you,
and you've, uh, maybe,
grown into certain things.
Please tell me you meant that
differently than it sounded!
Sorry, sorry!
I, uh.
This is not going to end well.
I need to get in there and
pull some sleight of hand.
Deus, hear my command!
Make Second height
weight proportionate!
Sweet pea, what are you doing?!
I don't know!
I don't know!!!
Yuno...
Have you...
I don't know...
It's just...
You look taller, since
the last time I saw you.
And you've, uh, maybe,
grown into certain things.
Alright, Murmur.
Something a little
less dramatic this time.
I'm not thinking
strait right now.
I just have to watch
my intonation.
Deus, hear my command!
Make Second height
weight proportionate!
Excuse me???
Holy crap, she's a baby!
Yuno!
Have you...
I don't know...
It's just...
You look taller since
the last time I saw you.
And you've, uh, maybe,
grown into certain things.
Please tell me you meant that
differently than it sounded!
Take three.
I'm not thinking
straight right now.
The core best not
screw me on this one.
Deus, hear my command!
Make Second height
weight proportionate!
Oh, hang on.
Know what?
I retract my previous
observation.
Wait!
That's not what I meant!
I take it back!