Look at that sky.
Oh, no. Help me.
My parachute's jammed.
I'm too young to die.
Ka-thunk.
Bon appetite!
Hey, uh.
Next time can we do
something not so terrifying?
It's gonna melt.
Are you listening to me?
Better hurry.
We should totally
go on that one next!
Someone explain to me
why I agreed to come here?
♪ opening song ♪
It's been a long time
since I believed in God.
Thing is, I need your help.
Okay?
If we're going to minimize
bloodshed in this damn game.
The first order of
business is to
identify the other diary users.
I've dredged up
enough Intel to give us
a decent start,
but that's about it.
So I need you to pay attention.
This is what we've
got to work with so far.
There's you, naturally.
Then you, Gasai; a.k.a. Second.
Then of course
there's little old me.
Designated Fourth.
Third was Hiyama Takao,
but he's dead.
And we have Uryuu Minene,
Ninth; currently a fugitive.
So that accounts for five of us.
Seven more and
we're ready to move.
That the low down?
Your mission is
to help me find them.
Mission?
Awesome!
Your school's closed for
repairs until further notice.
That's good.
We can use your free
time to apprehend Ninth.
Ugh... That woman.
Just the thought
of her out there
running around
makes my skin crawl.
Doesn't help she's always keyed
in to the perfect getaway plan,
thanks to her diary.
It's just my luck to
be on her bad side.
You're not going to try to use
us as bait or anything, are you?
Well, uh.
Here's the plan.
Ninth's on the lamb, sure,
she's bent on offing you both.
"Bait" isn't the word
I would choose, but...
Well, you see where
I'm going with this.
We're just dicking around here.
How's is this helping?
Mission my ass.
Bet you anything he's
just trying to keep us
close to the police station.
Still, though:
I can use the time.
Maybe I can wrestle some
kind of sense out of Yuno.
It's just.
When you're being stalked,
how are you supposed
to gently broach the
topic to the stalker?
I'm sorry.
Took a while.
It's alright.
Thanks.
So yeah.
--What's the deal with.
--Notice the straws?
Drink up.
What in the hell
is wrong with you?!
Pull it together.
I've got this.
I haven't left the
party yet, you bastards.
Not by a long shot.
Survival is what I do.
Winning is what I do.
This game has nothing on me.
Damn rain can stop any time now.
"Two cops around the corner,
50 meters ahead.
Turn right to avoid
danger." Got it.
Hey!
Shit!
Hey, stop!
Hold it!
--This is resisting!
--Are you not hearing me?!
Let's go there next!
Okay, she knows damn
good and well this
stuff scares the
crap out of me!
Wha...
What is this?
Let go of my arm!
Wow.
She's actually scared.
That's new.
Ugh.
That place?
No thanks.
Glad to know something brings
out her normal side, I guess.
I was scared.
Crap.
I really want get to the bottom
of her fixation on me, but...
She's just so cute like this.
Hey, hey.
Lookie there.
Last one in the
water's a rotten egg!
Look, please listen when
I say this is not a good idea!
Yuki!
You...
You go on ahead.
I'll, just stay right here.
Stop being such a girl!
I swear!
What's the matter?
Well, uh...
This bathing suit
doesn't quite fit.
This is so wrong.
Clean thoughts!
Make conversation!
They say the amount
of pee in public
pools is like twenty percent.
Nice going, doofus.
Bad news, my love.
My suit's kind of floated away.
Don't worry, I'll get it back!
No!
I'm naked!
You can't leave
me here alone like this!
Ask a lifeguard for help,
it's what they're here for!
Kay. This must be
Yuno's upset side.
Uh, excuse me.
Her top got swept downstream.
Oh.
No worries.
Oh, sorry.
Stay like you are!
Move and I'll be exposed.
You want everyone to see?
Um, no?
Here you go.
I think.
You are a life saver!
Whew.
That could've been a lot worse.
Yuki!
What do you think we
ought to tackle next?
Oh!
A planetarium!
Let's go there!
No thanks...
I don't want to.
Wow!
Check out that view!
The city looks like
a model from this high.
Hey.
Yuno.
Be honest.
Why do you keep following
me around all the time?
How come...
How come you didn't want
to go to the planetarium?
I thought you were like,
crazy over space stuff.
How did you?
Your diary's driving me insane.
Shut up!
I know you like stars
because you told me!
A year ago.
Don't you remember?
Everything okay?
I had trouble with
the survey, too.
I'm sorry about your parents.
Oh, uh, I just saw
that on your paper.
I wanted to go out to
the country with
them to look at
the stars, but they...
The divorce just got finalized.
Sucks cause I already bought
a telescope and everything.
Why'd I write that?
So stupid.
It's not stupid at all.
Well, it's a little stupid.
I mean, I can't hand
this into the teacher.
You could always come
with me to see the stars.
There's an observatory
real close to my house.
Yeah!
I've been dying to go!
It, um, really wouldn't be
the same without my family.
Ugh! Why you got
to be so negative?
I swear, some people.
We could be a family
if we got married.
I totally thought she'd
been kidding about that.
We'll have to
wait till we're older.
How can you be for real?
That was just a
random moment, right?
It can't mean...
Look, I...
You're sweet and all,
but my gut tells me
you're hiding something.
Of course I am.
Great.
Kay...
Here goes.
We've got reports of suspicious
activity, probable public intox,
about a block east
of 5th and Mockingbird.
Holy crap.
This is your house?
Yep.
Well, then... Good
night. I had a lovely time.
Don't go yet.
You could...
...come inside.
Got it.
Thank you.
Notify me the moment
Amano leaves, understood?
Good...
Be careful.
They made it home.
Well, to the girl's house.
That's good.
Think we should add
a few more officers
to their security detail?
Nah.
No need.
She's not going to try to
make a move on them tonight.
They're safe for now.
We have enough uniforms
out there to scare her off.
What the hell's wrong?
You're supposed to
be an escape diary.
Worthless piece of junk.
Try not to make any noise.
Are you able to move?
Don't even try!
Everything's okay.
I'm here to help you.
Sure you are.
Who sent--
Please.
Ha!
I'd look at my
options if I were you.
Yeah. Sorry
about the lights.
We're kind of off
the grid at the moment.
Oh...
It's alright.
Believe it or not, this apple
was grown in our backyard.
Let me go peel it for you.
Um, okay.
This setup is...
I don't know.
Right.
Nature calls.
Something for the pain.
I'd recommend two in your case.
Why are you doing this?
Who are you?
Who am I?
Oh, let's just say I'm
a Samaritan of sorts.
You should pay attention
to who you save.
Your karma might get screwed up.
Ha!
I like that.
I'm actually an instrument
of karma, as it happens.
Your karma.
Weirdo.
You will regret this.
I promise you.
Let's wait to stack
up our regrets
for comparison till
everything's over, eh?
Why hasn't anything changed?
Am I safe here or what?
Talk to me!
I didn't know what would happen.
All I wanted was
to find a bathroom.
They've got to have one.
I was just going to use
my diary to find it
and then head straight back
to where I'd been sitting.
What the heck's that all about?
Okay...
Kind of weird.
You bastard.
What the hell was
in those pain killers?!
Just a little something to
hurry your treatment along.
Stay back!
Why aren't there
any diary entries?!
This doesn't make any sense!
I'm going to count down
from three, after which, well...
You'll be wide awake, Ninth.
Oh shit, no.
You, you're a diary user.
Three.
Two.
One.
And presto!
Haha!
Now that you're up:
Tell me everything you
know about the
other diary users.
--No! Stop!
--I'd like to begin,
--What are you doing?!
--predictably enough,
with First's true identity.
Huh. My diary doesn't
say anything about
me going through this door.
Meaning if I actually
check out what's in here,
then I'll have
rewritten the future.
I had no clue.
Who would've?
Sometimes all you
have to do is walk
through a door and
boom: game changer.
For everyone.
In case you haven't
noticed, Boss,
causality is sort
of collapsing in on itself!
The boy's done it, hasn't he?
He's achieved the unthinkable!
I've meticulously ordered the
causal nexus to ensure all
twelve keepers would
converge upon Sakurami.
And yet, as if in scorn of my
design, something marvelous
has intervened; the
playing field is transformed.
Well done, boy.
Very well done.
I've seldom been so entertained.
It was wise of me to select you.
Why'd you do it?
We were good, right?
You... You just
couldn't stand not to look.
Those couldn't have been
what I thought they were.
Right?
I mean, they looked like...
Good night, sweetie.
I'll see you in your dreams.
♪ closing song ♪
Tell me something, Yuki.
What's up?
I want to be popular so what do
I got to do to make that happen?
Are you serious?
Hey, just cause
I'm supernatural,
it doesn't mean I don't care
what people think of me.
Yeah you're kind of
a social outcast,
but I'm sure you can drop some
knowledge on me right, Yuki?
Uh.
I don't know.
Maybe try being cute?
But aren't I already cute?
I get it.
You think I look all
fugly, don't you!
Huh?! No!
You're, plenty cute!
You've got that part covered!
Maybe being known
as a good cook
would help with your
popularity a bit.
Do you think that'll do it?!
Cause I'm a real
bad-ass in the kitchen!
Behold!
Boiled corn!
That's not very difficult.
How 'bout roast corn
and steamed corn?
You're still doing the
same thing, pretty much.
Fried corn and dried corn!
Earth to Murmur!
Corn doesn't count as cooking!
You really put the "corn"
in "scorned," Yuki.
What a space cadet.
Look, don't worry about cooking.
The real key to popularity...
Is just being kind to people.
I've heard of this
"kind" thing before.
So what's it about?
It's like making someone a
late-night snack just 'cause.
You know?
I asked for no snack.
Or did I?