I had wondered how long
it would be ere your quest
for answers brought you hither
to my chamber, Aru Akise.
Far be it from me to deny that
boon to so dedicated
a supplicant.
Good luck, Aru.
I hope you know
what you're doing up here.
Should Yuki win this game
and ascend to my throne,
you wish to know if
he can rouse the
recent dead from their
sanguinary slumber.
The answer is...
♪ opening song ♪
Can't you type any faster?
I'm doing the best I
can here, slow your roll!
Please be okay.
Why didn't I see it sooner?!
Aw, crap!
Did he just figure it out?!
This is bad.
Yuki needs to hear
about this new wrinkle!
Guess again, Sherlock!
Deus?
What gives?!
I fear such a
mission of elucidation
is not in the cards for you,
as it is your fate to perish
here alongside me, Aru.
After all, you're the Observer.
Under normal circumstances,
nothing can occur
without my knowing it.
But in these days of
war among the diary users,
the future changes
course far too often
to properly gauge from afar.
I needed a man on
the ground, as it were.
Someone to note alterations
as they occurred.
That is why...
I imbued you with such ravenous
curiosity when I created you.
Deus created me?
Is that possible?
You are a construct... a
reconnaissance device that has
been granted the desire and
the cognitive wherewithal
to broaden its body
of knowledge.
Now you will die and return
unto the Akashic Records.
The Akashic Records?
A heavenly storehouse
of knowledge,
wherein all defining
events are duly chronicled.
My body, it's!
Ponder this as you cease to be.
You think yourself
to have tracked
the keepers of your
own volition,
but no such choice
was ever afforded you.
What are you saying?
You collected
information because
it was my will that you do so.
You're wrong!
I'm not a puppet!
I am my own man!
If it's proof you want, I shall
explain how your deeds one and
all were all undertaken at my
unspoken behest, my dear Aru.
But as I am a benevolent god,
I shall grant you this chance.
If you can make
manifest any moment
that speaks to
your supposéd free will.
I'll allow your
existence to continue.
The case of Tenth,
the dog-trainer.
I shadowed him of
my own accord, didn't I?
I needed confirmation of his
actions while he was in hiding.
Thus, you supplied
said assurance.
What about my probing into
Yuno's background?!
She is a key player
in this game.
You really think I would allow
such a creature to
remain a cipher?
I risked my life to save Eighth!
I wanted Second's
murderous ways be kept in
check at that particular
moment, and you obliged.
Dude, it's crunch-time!
C'mon!
I know that, Hinata!
But Aru's handwriting
is really frigging small!
One last chance to
prove me wrong, lad.
What was the
strongest emotion that
drove you during your
time in this world?
The strongest... emotion.
It was my...
My love for Yuki.
It's real.
I feel it, even now.
That love was
nothing but an illusion.
Game over, Aru.
It appears every
action you undertook
was simply that of a thrall.
You're wrong!
Is this Future Diary I'm holding
part of your master plan?!
A diary that exists to keep
tabs on other users.
But how?
I had Eighth turn my phone into
a diary subordinate to hers.
Perhaps I was
your unwitting Observer,
Deus but that changes now.
I'm neither your eyes,
nor a tool of your will.
I'm going back to Earth
to change the future
because Aru Akise
is not a drone!
I'm saving Yuki if
it's the last thing I do!
Those are the words
of one who answers
to no god, one
who has chosen to live.
It would appear you
have slipped free
from your tethers on this day.
Get thee hence, Aru Akise.
Alter the future while there
is still a future to change.
If we're gonna save the world,
there's only one way to do it.
Meet up with Aru and the
others, put a bullet in Eighth,
and undo it all as
soon as I'm god.
I know it sucks,
but I'm glad they ultimately
see eye-to-eye with
me and Yuno on all this.
I mean, it's not like
I'm gonna drag it out.
Yuki, wait.
We got to go, Yuno.
We're kind of
on a deadline here.
I need to ask you
something important.
Okay but make it quick.
Sweetie... if Aru and
the others tried to
sell you out at the last moment,
would you be able to kill them?
Why would you
say something like that?
Be honest with me.
I have to know
what you would do.
No one's gonna betray anyone.
These guys have stuck by
me through everything.
Speak of the devil.
What's up, Yuki?
Where is everybody?
I thought they were here.
We need to kill Eighth.
Where the hell is she?!
Don't make me ask you again.
I have a bit of private
business with Yuki.
Not to be rude, but could you
make yourself scarce?
No!
What have you done?!
You stabbed him.
Up there!
They're moving Eighth
to higher ground!
Go get her!
He wanted to talk to
me and now he's dead.
Now you understand
why I was asking?
Your so-called friends
betrayed you, darling.
That's under some debate.
How did you survive her attack?!
I wasn't sure that I would.
He's wearing body armor!
Armor's not gonna
shield you from this!
A rubber glove?!
But how could you have known?!
What the hell?
This fight should be over.
According to my diary,
she knocks Aru unconscious
with that stun gun.
But that's two for
two he saw coming.
We're not gonna
win this one, Yuno!
Sure we can it's
two against one!
I knew you'd figure it out.
Thanks to Eighth,
and the miracle that is
modern technology,
my cell-phone is now the one
that watches the watchmen.
I know everything your
diaries will say as well
as the changes in the
future your actions will cause.
My Detective Diary, Mark Two.
I'm sorry, but I've been
playing the both of you
like a fiddle since you arrived.
Go, Yuki!
Eighth is getting away!
Don't worry!
I'll keep this bastard busy!
But...
Akise totally called it,
you guys.
Yuno's been lying to Yuki
about all this from the start.
We have to get him out of
that psycho's clutches.
'Cause that's
what friends are for.
Am I right?
I don't get it.
Why are they
helping her escape?!
How could Aru sell
me out like this?!
I want to trust them.
But...
You seemed like
someone I'd want to know.
Hinata.
I'm sorry, but if
you're not behind me
on this all bets are off.
Stop, Yuki!
It's you.
And Eighth!
This has got to stop!
Killing her isn't the answer!
If you do this, things are
only gonna get worse!
Dammit, Hinata!
Get out of the way!
Listen to me!
Yuno has been lying to you!
You can't just kill
people and fix it later!
Even if you become a god,
once folks are dead,
they can't come back!
I have a confession to make.
I tricked you.
You stayed behind under the
auspices of keeping me here,
but really that's
precisely what I wanted.
You see, I had to get
you away from Yuki.
As our stalemate unfolds Hinata
is telling Yuki the truth.
The scales will
fall from his eyes
and your spell on him
will be broken.
How was that of benefit to you?!
I can't get the jump on you
thanks to that diary.
So I let you defeat me here,
just as it predicted you would.
What do you do, smarty-pants?
You could go
traipsing off to Yuki
and leave me here to bleed out.
You know you want to.
But, what's Yuki gonna
say if I die here?
Losing his beloved?
That's gonna crush him.
You're saying...
I couldn't bring back the dead?
But I'll be a god!
What the hell kind of a god
can't resurrect dead people?!
Of course I'll bring them back!
Maybe you can
bring back their bodies
but their souls aren't
gonna be inside them.
Look, it's the truth.
Aru heard it straight from Deus.
Dammit, Hinata.
That doesn't even make sense!
You're saying...
I can't resurrect
everyone I killed?
Face the facts they are gone!
But, if that's true,
Mom and Dad are...
I'm sorry.
Them too.
Why're you lying?!
Some things are too
big to take back.
That's the way life
has always worked.
Don't you get it?
Dead is dead.
But I've got a list.
I never thought she'd resort
to practically gutting herself.
The situation's too volatile
I have to get him out!
A busy signal?
That doesn't make any sense.
Who could he possibly
be talking to right now?!
But of course!
Oh god, Yuki help me!
He's got the knife!
He's gonna kill me!
Yuno, what's going on?!
Aru, no!
Is she telling me
Aru stabbed her?!
Don't be fooled
by their lies, Yuki!
Your future diary doesn't record
anything about yourself,
but mine does, remember?!
Mine watches your back!
Tells me everything!
Please, you have to believe me!
They don't want you to win!
They're the enemy!
You lied to me.
Why would you do that?
What?!
I didn't!
Oh yeah?!
Why did the future change, huh?!
Why did Aru cut up Yuno?!
Yuki, just listen to me!
Don't you say another word!
Shut up!
Hey! Why the hell
would I lie to you, dumbass?!
We're friends, remember?!
Hinata! No!
What have you done, Yuki?!
It's her fault I shot her.
She kept lying
about Mom and Dad.
I'm gonna bring
them back to life.
If we're supposed to be friends,
why'd you keep lying
to me about it?!
I'm gonna bring everybody back.
I didn't hit anything major.
But I'd still be dead if
Aru hadn't patched me up.
That trick's only
gonna work once.
If I'm going to kill Aru I need
to change up my tactics.
Stand aside Mao.
Stand aside, dammit!
Eighth is going to die.
You know what you are, Yuki?!
You're a coward!
Hinata told you the truth,
which is more
than Yuno has
ever cared enough to do!
And you knew she was right.
You knew it!
But it wasn't the truth Mr.
Future Diary wanted to hear!
You helped her patch
things up with her father.
You don't know
what that meant to her.
She thought the world of you.
And you killed her!
I have plenty of bullets left.
Don't make me use them, Kousaka.
I'm not gonna make you do
anything, you piece of crap.
That's on you.
You make me sick.
Always did.
You wanna know why?
'Cause I'll tell ya.
You're always crying.
Sniffling away like
a weak little bitch!
Aw, look at poor Yuki!
What's the matter are you
gonna start crying little baby?!
You don't get to cry,
not after what you just
did to Hinata and Mao!
You killed your own friends!
Has that penetrated--
W-What'd I just say?
You don't have any
right to cry you bastard.
Please, Yuki don't go yet!
Aru.
You shot them down, didn't you.
Yeah, I did and I'm gonna
do the same to you.
Looking at their corpses,
I realize that I
underestimated Yuno.
I regret not killing her
when I had the chance.
Before she filled that
trusting head of yours
with her vile
machinations and lies.
If so, our friends
would still be alive.
I'm here because
I want to protect you.
If nothing else, please believe
that keeping you safe
is my top priority.
According to my newly
prognosticative diary.
I'll be killing Yuno just a
few minutes from now.
What?!
It's for your own good.
Stay back!
Any closer and I'll shot!
You have to face
the facts, Yuki!
When the time is right,
she's going to murder you!
The dead cannot be renewed!
And if you're asking yourself
why Yuno would let you assume
otherwise it's because
she needed you to kill
without hesitation and
endure to the endgame!
She means full well
to succeed Deus!
It seems you're out
of bullets, my friend.
Get away from him!
He's dangerous, pookie!
He tried to kill me!
Yuno.
You deserve someone who
will always tell you the truth.
You kissed me.
When I get a hold of you...
I'm gonna gut you like a fish!
Ah!
I should have let you bleed out
when I had the chance, Yuno.
This time around.
I mean to end you!
No, don't do this!
Aru's diary says it's a
fight to the death this time.
One that he wins.
If you challenge him again.
I'm gonna send you to hell!
You should be dead right now.
She has two?
What's going on?
I broke her phone and
she's none the worse for wear.
A decoy?
No, couldn't have been.
The screen flickered
as it snapped.
I heard it crackle with the
sound of the future
changing course.
"Amano"?!
Yuno always calls
him Yuki in her entries.
That phone was a
Future Diary I'm sure of it.
But not hers, or she
would've twisted into oblivion.
Who the hell's was it?!
Yuno.
You're bleeding.
I've got it bandaged up.
How bad is he?
Later, darling he's
not going anywhere.
Killing Eighth should be
next on our to-do list, right?
I saw Aru break your cell-phone
right before you cut his throat.
Just a decoy.
And thankfully,
he took the bait!
One quick jab to the aorta.
Then you can bring back your mom
and dad as good as new, Yuki!
Don't even think about it.
Either way, Eighth is dead.
Listen to me!
Yuno has been lying to you!
You know what you are, Yuki?!
You're a coward!
Yuki.
Make this a world where the
children can all live in peace.
I will gladly die for that.
There's no turning back.
Yuno and I, are all that's left.
There's the real Yuno Gasai,
and the girl who took her place.
Three bodies in their backyard.
Two were the corpses
of Yuno's adoptive parents.
The last one matched the DNA
from the real Yuno's
umbilical cord.
Ergo, the Yuno we've
known is the interloper.
But, this one had
two Future Diaries.
So did she steal the
real Yuno's phone?
No.
The real Yuno was never
part of Deus's game.
Why were there two diaries?
It makes no sense.
The third corpse.
The real Yuno Gasai.
A death match
to replace a deity.
A pair of Future Diaries.
A pair.
There are two?!
He's alive?
Can't talk with
a severed windpipe.
But I can tell him...
I thought that you killed him.
I can warn Yuki
in another fashion.
Yuno!
Don't do this!
He's not a threat anymore!
I need to warn my beloved Yuki.
♪ closing song ♪
I am known as Deus Ex Machina ♪
the lord and master of
space and time.
As such,
my vigil is never-ending.
On this day, just
as on any other,
my duty demanded the
whole of my attention.
Hey, Deus.
I'm kind of antsy,
so I'm gonna go out
and play for a little while.
Very well.
Do not tarry overlong.
My strength is much
reduced as of late.
I think the boatman will
earn his pay soon enough.
An ambitious human
approached me recently,
proposing a game of
sorts through which my
inevitable successor
could most easily be chosen.
It is a matter of no small
concern, as I well know.
However, it is not
my only responsibility.
What's for dinner tonight?
What would you like?
I want curry!
It's really yummy!
But we had curry
yesterday, you silly goose.
How about meat, then!
A lot of things
are meat, sweetie!
What kind do you want?
Something made of pork!
Murmur thinks Deus
is the bee's knees.
I couldn't spare
the time to pick her up
that day but that
is just what I did.