Here we stand.
Eight prospective heirs to my
throne remain as the gathering
dark of time in
peril sounds its knell.
The game lurches inexorably
toward its logical conclusion.
Sir.
I would like to make a somewhat
controversial request.
I propose transferring
diary ownership.
Temporarily but with
very good reason.
Oh?
♪ opening song ♪
It's been two
weeks since the kid.
Might as well have been a year.
As far as anyone else knows,
Yuno whacked mom over the
head by mistake while
chasing down an intruder.
And Houjou disappeared during
all the commotion afterwards.
Okay, so maybe we
twisted the truth a little bit,
but we didn't
tell an outright lie.
Not one Kurusu's
wised up to, anyway.
Hi, love!
I really like your outfit today.
It's cool.
This is going to
be a total disaster.
I royally suck
at making friends.
So, yeah.
I'm sure you already
thought of this, but...
In the interest of fitting in,
we can probably
assume your phone
and this school
aren't going to mix.
I would put it away before we
even get to the crosswalk.
I mean, that is kind of why
you almost screwed
things up with Third.
Yeah...
Guess you do have a point.
I'll just go without.
Can't be that hard to manage.
And as far as making new
friends, who needs them, right?
You still got me.
We'll be in different classes,
but that doesn't matter.
What's wrong, sweetie?
Scared?
Huh? Oh.
Someone's... staring?
Who was?
Never mind...
I'm seeing things.
Promise me that
we'll walk home together.
I'll wait for you in
the courtyard, okay?
Okay.
Roomful of perfect strangers.
How awesome is that?
What the frak's your deal, man?
You think no one's going to
notice a guy on his tippy-toes?
What's he doing here?
Long time no see, Yuki.
How's the world
been treating ya?
Please tell me he's
in the wrong class.
This reptile thrives on making
life a hell on earth for me.
More than that...
Ninth almost blew me to
pieces because of what he did.
Dude, seriously.
Isn't it a little soon to try
and make your way
in a new place?
I mean...
You did get everyone at our last
school blown up and killed!
What's he doing?
Why's he broadcasting
that to the whole class?
Guess everybody's entitled
to reinvent themselves.
Even little puss bags.
Well good luck
with that, freak show!
You'll have your
work cut out for you
so long as I'm around to remind
these kids of the
good old days, trust me.
Shut it!
What was that for?!
Mind your own damn business!
Settle those hormones,
mister Roid Rage.
It's bad form to
fight on your first day.
Oh Hinata; always intervening
on behalf of the underdog.
Of course in this case,
how're you supposed to
know which of these
two brutes that is?
Knock it off, Mao.
You're being rude.
You're going to be famous
for that soft spot one
of these days.
I told you to knock it off.
Okay, emo kid.
On your feet.
Quit smiling at me like that,
you little delinquent!
I'll thank you all
to take your seats
and at least emulate
civilized behavior.
Alright.
This is very important
so pay attention.
Walk home in groups.
Murders?
Don't you watch the news, twerp?
Bunch of people have
been totally slaughtered
in this neighborhood the
past couple weeks.
Could Third have come back?
They say the
victims died horribly.
As if they'd been
attacked by a werewolf.
Not even their next of kin
could identify the bodies,
they were so torn up and bloody.
We're talking teeth marks,
scratches, the whole bit.
Teeth marks, huh?
Wouldn't forensics have a field
day with something like that?
You've got a point.
Yeah well.
I heard the police are
withholding all kinds of details
about the case to keep
a panic from breaking out.
Then again...
I really ought to
run that by Akise
to see if there's
any truth to it.
Who's that?
Ah, that guy.
Take a look at the
empty desk there
just to the left of you, sport.
The assigned seat of
our class biggest head case.
It's vacant right now
'cause he's probably
ditching to play private eye.
Hey-hey!
Boom.
Okay.
Bear with me this an awesome
idea if you hear it out.
Yuki?
Don't get any ideas about
being the leader; that's my job.
Who're they?
Hey, snooping around the
scene of the latest murders
is as good a way to spend
an afternoon as any?
Nice work sneaking us in, Mao.
It really wasn't as difficult
as you'd think it would be.
A couple of bored-looking
patrol officers
is all they had for a perimeter.
Oh shit!
You can totally
still see the blood!
Official chalk outlines
and everything!
That is effed up!
I don't know about this.
Yuno looks like she's
ready to blow a gasket.
Hey, Amano!
Take a look at this!
Eh.
She'll deal with it.
Hey!
Come on, spaz!
It's not like we've
all got leprosy!
You should really try some
of this juice, I'm telling ya.
I prefer it right here.
I'm not sure what
I expected to find,
but I thought it'd be
cooler than this.
Oh well... What are
you going to do, right?
Hey, Hinata?
Yeah?
What exactly possessed
you to break the ice
with me in the first place?
You seemed like
someone I'd want to know.
Eh?
Do you mean that?
We should go
check the other side!
Okay!
Mao!
I'm heading out.
Catch me if you can!
Be careful!
She's going to be famous
for that soft spot one day.
Such a character.
She's a good judge
of it herself.
I usually agree
with her choices.
As in this case.
Oh and I should probably
tell you this now...
You don't have a
snowball's chance in
hell of ever being
more than her friend.
Ah...
So she has someone.
Maybe she does
and maybe she doesn't.
Come on.
Let's go.
Hold on.
I'm actually enjoying myself.
Fine then.
Jeez.
Bunch of slowpokes.
There's like the coolest
spot just up ahead, people.
What the hell?
The future's rewritten itself!
There's a Diary User
somewhere nearby!
Crap!
What are we supposed to do?!
The others will get
caught in the crossfire!
This is bad news.
On top of everything else,
Hinata's out there
somewhere by herself!
I know I shouldn't,
but this is an emergency.
Yuki, no!
You need to get as far
away from here as possible!
These guys can
look after themselves;
they're not your responsibility!
Shut up!
Hinata's the first
friend I've ever made!
I'm not about to
turn tail and run!
No.
One of you going to tell us
why we're running, or what?
Whatever this is, man,
it'd better be damn good!
Is that?
Don't let it be.
No!
Hinata.
This is a joke, right?
Um, okay I'm going
to vote we run like hell
just in case it's not.
Yuki, c'mon!
Need a hand?
Who the--?
Akise! How long
have you been there?
Longer than you,
to go by your panting.
Let's not stand on
ceremony just now, alright?
If you don't accept my help,
you're dead meat.
Unless we fancy
being doggie kibble,
the thing is to get out
of here before sundown.
The question is how.
Don't take this wrong...
...but your shaking is adorable.
Don't you worry hot stuff...
I can be trusted.
Name's Akise.
And I'm about to
be your best friend.
Through crumbling?
What's his game?
I'm on to you.
I'm sure you've got a lot
of questions, Yuki, but...
...there are, kind of more
pressing things to worry about.
There's an observation
deck just up the way.
We should make a break for it.
Watch it, he's not
your dance partner!
Now's really not the
time for petty jealousy.
I don't understand.
Why is this happening?
We just wanted to
see a crime scene.
My four-legged lovelies have
certainly indulged themselves.
Why can't I follow
their example?
No shame in self reward,
I should think.
Don't you agree Mary?
Ah, the sizzle of
Matsuzaka steak
rings out like an
electric charge.
Served with stew
slow-cooked to perfection.
And, naturally,
the finest vintage
from my special reserves.
And voila!
A banquet not
only fit for a king,
but ripe for eternal tribute
via my internet blog!
Alas, I must quell
the urge and hie
this repast to yon dinning hall!
Everyone...
Fill thy superior
gullets to satiety!
Ah, yes...
Such sweet indulgence.
Excellent.
The wheels are in motion.
Indeed.
May the road rise
to meet you, poppet.
Protect my diary as you
would my perspicacious pack.
Going to be alright, Yuki?
You look exhausted.
Hinata.
Oh, sweetie.
So... Is there like a part
B to this plan, or what?
We're safe for right now.
At least, I think so.
Let's have a proper
introduction this time.
My name's Aru Akise.
And my dream is to be a world
famous detective someday.
Oh, uh.
--I'm...
--Yukiteru Amano.
I know.
Look, if I came on a
bit strong back there,
it was just my way of saying
I've been sort of
keeping tabs on you.
C'mon, a guy's got to do what he
can to make himself interesting.
I'm an information
junkie of sorts.
The murders around
your old school.
The bombings that shut it down.
And the Omekata cult.
I've been following
it all closely.
It seems that you happen to be
the common denominator here.
Thing is and please don't
take this wrong... anybody with
that kind of screwed up luck
has to be hiding something.
Does this guy
know about my diary?
Dude, you have my solemn oath
I'm not trying to be a creeper.
It's not like I think you're the
evil architect behind all this.
I mean...
I know a bloodthirsty madman's
target when I see one.
Believe it or not.
My whole reason for keeping an
eye on you in the first place
was to try and spare you
from more of the same.
Thanks, I guess.
Hey, we weirdoes have
to stick together, right?
Well, it could be worse;
this guy could be
someone else trying to kill me.
Are you really out to help him?
No offense...
But we should really consider
the situation we're in.
Whoever's controlling the
dogs has got to be close by...
...meaning for all we know
they're hiding
somewhere in here,
waiting for the
right moment to strike.
Maybe it's the photog girl.
Maybe it's the jerk.
Don't even try
to pin this on me!
Or of course the pervert, who
was kind enough to lead us here.
Knock it off, Yuno!
Oh shit, they're getting in!
This is messed up!
How are we supposed to not die?!
I don't like this.
If they attack en masse, we...
If they go for the windows
simultaneously there's
not enough of us to
keep them all blocked!
They'll get in if we
don't do something.
I've got to tell everyone
which windows to guard.
You know...
If we use them as decoys,
we stand a pretty
good chance of
getting out of here.
Besides one of them
is probably trying to kill you.
Don't even start!
To hell with this crap!
And to hell with the two of you!
This is bad.
They're almost in.
If I don't use my diary,
we're dog chow.
But if I let them in
on my dirty little secret...
...they're not going to want
anything more to do with me,
even if I save us.
Still...
I... I can't just
let my friends die!
Kousaka!
Two windows to your right! Move!
What?!
Sweetie, no!
Shove it.
You're not the damn boss of me!
How'd you do that?
Somebody block the third window
left of the entrance, hurry up!
Gotcha!
I'm all over it!
Mao! Take the window
just to your left!
If you say so!
Now what?
Hey, psychic!
Where should I be?
C'mon, we don't got all day!
Are you serious?
Whoa...
We're in the clear, right?
Hellz yeah!
That's some serious
magic you're working with.
Hey! You should
be on the tube!
Everyone and their dog'll want
a piece of this mind-freak!
Ha! I can totally
be your manager, dude!
Ah, it's was nothing.
So what's your phone
got to do with this?
You keep staring at it.
Well, it basically told me what
windows the dogs would go for.
I just read off the
text to you guys.
It's like a diary.
Wait, what?
Cell phones have come a long
way in the past few years,
but this is the first I've
heard of an app that
clues users into what
the future holds.
Oh wow.
Is it possible they're
taking all this in stride?
You are some piece
of work, Amano.
You won't mind if I borrow
this for a little while, right?
What the hell are you doing?
You can't take that.
You bitch!
Freeze!
At least tell us you're
surprised before
you make a move.
No way.
I'm surprised, too,
though I didn't think
Yuki'd reveal
himself so quickly.
Sorry, Amano.
You've been had.
But... you were...
How is she still alive?
Don't even...
You're good.
But I know what
you're going to try to pull.
She's a User.
Don't get your panties
in a wad, sister.
I'm not after
your little boyfriend.
None of this crap
was for either of you.
It's not your
future diary I'm after.
It's the boy detective's.
♪ closing song ♪
The name's Aru Akise;
hardboiled gumshoe in training.
Lately, a number of screwball
"happenings" in Sakurami
have been drawing me
in like a dark whirlpool.
Twisted things.
Uncanny things.
This cavalcade of the bizarre
has a convergence point:
Yukiteru Amano.
I'm en route for a friendly how
do ya do with him now.
A sleuth worth his powder
always knows when
he's on to something big.
I am so sorry!
Please tell me you're okay!
I've, had better days,
to be honest with you.
Hold tight.
I'll call an ambulance!
No hospitals.
There's only one place that
holds any hope for me now.
People look like
ants from up here!
How awesome is this?!
So, uh...
Throwing yourself
in front of my bike
was the best way to get here?
How'd you know?
Elementary, my dear Watson.
You are, after all,
in the company of
a future internationally
renowned detective.
Yeah?
But part of your
gambit still eludes me.
Go on.
What conceivable
purpose was served by
making off with my bicycle seat?
No idea what
you're talking about.