Time to choose, Yuki.
Choose what?
Stick with me and
get out of this alive.
Or stay with that
whore and say goodnight.
Better hurry.
Uh. Now?
What the hell?!
Look, whoever's behind
this is after Sixth, not us.
And there's no reason
we can't just ditch her.
So leaving means we live!
I gave my word I'd protect her.
What gave me the idea I could?
♪ opening song ♪
There are two worlds:
one visible, one invisible.
The second is a
wellspring from which
my misery flows in
dark torrents.
My sight was poor from birth;
I could scarcely
see beyond the reach of my hand.
But God bestowed on
me the gift of second sight;
the future was
always known to me.
My parents were quick to work
this talent to their advantage,
proclaiming me
The Clairvoyant Maiden
and anointing me with
countless, eager devotees.
Though to all outward
appearances powerful,
my role as the Omekata
Cult's leader was a pantomime;
I was little more
than a mouthpiece
for my parents' designs
though happy all the same.
They were kind,
my visitors often delightful.
Of the world beyond
the shrine I knew little,
but even so loneliness never
presumed to touch me.
Then came the accident.
Pain inevitably flows from
that which we cannot see.
We lurch along the path of life,
spine bent with sin!
To unbind our burden, one must
withdraw from the road!
My chamber became a prison cell;
paradise, a living hell.
My only comfort was a
plaything of my mother's
a small vestige of
the visible world.
Then one day.
The invisible world claimed
this, too, for its own.
No, It's not fair.
I need it.
I have nothing else!
Why must the
darkness torment me?!
I hate you!
I hate you!!!
Right, we have an exit!
We're getting you out of here!
I was right to put
my trust in you.
Sorry it took so long,
damn sprinklers are
more complicated than
they need to be.
Get out of there!
Things getting uglier?
Somebody's hypnotized
all the cultists!
Come again?
As if the situation wasn't
bizarre enough, right?
It's okay backup's
been called in.
I want you kids to make
a b-line for the front gate
and tell them you're with me.
What are you gonna do?
I'm going to find Ninth.
6:47pm.
I enlighten Ninth as to my
personal concept of Justice.
She isn't especially impressed.
Is that his diary?
Hey.
What are you doing?
Enjoying a sneak preview.
Or, pre-listen, rather.
Say hello to the Diary of
Justice a record of
unspeakably wicked deeds all but
begging for swift retribution!
It's how I descried the
Cult's unseemly agenda;
why I took it upon
myself to infiltrate this nest
of vipers and subdue Sixth.
You, unlucky wretch,
were merely a token of
my pretense at loyalty
to the enemy!
Through the prognostications of
this magnificent contraption
I knew where and when to
"rescue" you and
how to give you "first aid."
6:47pm.
Errant litter behind a desk.
What?!
Aaaaahhhh.
Harmony restored.
What is it now?
I'm off to make good use
of your explosives.
What'd the diary tell you?!
That righteousness
will be satisfied!
I'd abscond if I were you.
Crossfire, you understand.
Wait. That's it?
If I didn't know better, I'd
swear you did that deliberately!
Whatever, keep your shirt on,
we're practically there!
Yuno?
Greetings, milady.
Truly, you honor us.
I can't believe it's her!
I don't like where
this is going.
Wondrous to see you,
your ladyship.
Please tell me
they've snapped out of it!
They're acting normal
for cultists, I guess.
Look, my love!
Almost there!
We're on the homestretch
of getting out of this!
I beg you, wait!
We should pay the
villains back in kind.
Huh?
My adherents have been restored
to their senses, have they not?
We have numbers on our side!
Really?
Yuno, please!
Just stop!
Whatever it is
you're about to do.
There's nothing to
worry about, sweetie.
It won't take long.
What do you mean?
Oh crap she's in psycho mode!
I'm on to you.
I'm not about to stand here
and let you trick my man.
Delusional.
Do you see, Yuki?
What's going on?
What are you farting around for?
Twelfth is about
to be on top of you.
Wait.
Say that again?!
Son of a bitch.
Guy's bad news
top to bottom...
...blind as a mole rat
but ears like radar.
He's got explosives with him and
he fully intends to use them.
Of course he does!
So get the hell
outta Dodge already!
Yuki!
Someone's on the roof!
Aw, damn it!
Twelfth Red!
Twelfth Blue!
Twelfth Yellow!
Twelfth Green!
Twelfth Pink!
Together, we form.
The Twelfth Five!
This is ridiculous.
Pleasure to meet you.
First.
Surprised.
I'll bet.
Not that I blame you.
I have absolutely
no response to this.
Mind your manners, miscreant!
You're being addressed
by an adult!
Sorry!
Hi!
Heed my warning, boy.
Sixth is playing you for a fool.
The initiatory ritual for
membership in this
cult is a blight on civilized
behavior everywhere!
Neophyte acolytes are
forced to share the
burden of this
cult's evil secret,
thus cinching unwavering
loyalty from all who join!
In short, this sect is a
brainwashing factory!
I don't.
I don't know what to do.
My purpose here tonight
is to terminate Sixth.
As I cannot guarantee your
safety, you should leave.
Be advised that one of me
has ingested a timed
incendiary device.
And that me will
be going kerplooie.
Okay.
What about the other four?
Mesmerized
decoys all, I'm afraid.
Desperate times,
desperate measures.
I've had the
demoralizing bad fortune
to be notified of a Dead End.
I cannot say I'm shocked, being
deep behind enemy lines.
But I can at least take said
enemy with me when I go!
You've got to be
out of your mind!
If by surrendering my life
I advance the cause
of Justice, Fate's terms
are acceptable!
Okeydokey, then.
This would be a pretty good time
to get out of here,
don't you think?
I've told you,
I can't leave Tsubaki.
Showtime!
There's got to be something
in my diary that I can use!
Second guy from the left!
Aw, come on!
That's totally cheating!
The real one's blind, right?
That means four
of the five can see.
Gotcha.
Wait Yuno!
Surely you're not gambling
with odds like these?!
Watch and learn, sister!
Heh...
Gotcha, you bastard.
Victory is yours.
Let Justice prevail.
Okay.
Yuki was right; it was the
second one from the left.
7:07pm.
Hirasaka Yomotsu, a.k.a.
Twelfth, perishes.
Dead End.
What the hell's going on?!
Explosion.
Give me my damn cell phone back!
Do you want to make
it out of here on your legs
or in a body bag?!
Yuno?!
Oh man, she's burning up!
She's been pushing
herself too hard!
Kudos, Second.
You have my respect.
Huh?
What are they doing?
What are they doing?!
Sorry, Yuki.
Tsubaki, please!
Call them off!
You've really not put it
together yet, have you?
Foolish boy.
I mean to kill the lot of you.
Ninth was bait from the
beginning; wheels within wheels,
as our Game Master might say.
Damn you, Twelfth!
No, you...
You're like a beacon of hope to
people you can't be this way!
No doubt you think me virtuous.
I was relieved of
my virtue long ago.
It's far too cruel
a world to be naive in.
Or for that matter a virgin.
We could do something about
your virtue, if you'd like.
Now, then.
Child... Let us see
if the appropriate Dead End
has yet appeared on my scroll.
Impossible!
How can this be?!
I refuse to believe.
You kissed my Yuki!!!!
Stand firm!
Protect the diary!
YOU WHORE!!!
Yuno!
Are you...?
You have to take this.
My arm!
Make a run for it.
Yuno!
Oh no!
Talk to me!
Don't let him get away!
Somebody cut him
off at the gate!
Call me a whore?!
The girl's been reigned in and
Yuki scrambled for
a hiding place.
We have zero chance of
staying out of sight.
And of course.
The backup I called
for can't get further
than the hedgerow out front.
We're screwed.
Will you shut your face already?
And while you're at it
get this thing off me!
I'm not about to bite the big
one cuffed to a damn pig!
Fine.
I'll take 'em off.
But you gotta do
something for me.
My lady, you've lost a
dangerous amount of blood.
We must take you to a hospital.
Shut your mouth!
This is an inconvenience,
nothing more!
The invisible world yet
again claims something
dear to me for its own.
I loathe it.
I'd destroy the darkness,
if I could.
I'd destroy everything
it encompasses!
Mark me, Second.
My first act as God will be
to end this wretched world.
But you can't!
This world is where Yuki
lives that would kill him!
I've just had a minor epiphany.
Let's use you as bait.
If he loves you,
he can't resist.
You'll know he reciprocates
and then you'll get
to watch him die
before your eyes.
Hey.
See anything?
Nothing yet.
You check under here?
No, but he'll hear you.
C'mon.
Where's he gonna go?
Just try to be discreet.
Am I safe here?
Watch where you step.
Tsubaki was leading me
on the whole time.
I should've just taken
Yuno's word for it.
Sure she's nuts, but,
at least you know where
you stand with her.
I think.
Whoa.
The amusement park
thing was a date to her?
Yuno's definitely not
your average girl,
but what am I gonna do?
She's totally serious when she
says she's gonna protect me.
She's crazy about me
and like it or not that's
turned out to be a good thing.
Better hurry.
What am I gonna do?
I ran off like a total wuss
without even trying to save her
I'm pathetic!
What's that?
Here is the microphone,
your ladyship.
What are you gonna do?
I'm going to draw out your man.
Now, you can't tell me you're
not curious to see
if this works.
Let's get his attention!
No!
I want all the men
to form a line.
Testing.
One-two.
Listen up, First.
There's about to be a fire sale
on Second's maidenhood.
No!
Are you going to man-up
and try to intervene?
Stop it!
I was saving myself for Yuki!
Get your hands off me!!!
She wants me to come
out so she can kill us both.
But I can't just let Yuno be...
What am I supposed to do?!
No!
Look, I...
You're sweet and all,
but my gut tells me you're
hiding something.
There he is!
Get him!
Of course I am.
Why'd you just kiss
me on the forehead?
'Cause it's your move if you
want one on the lips.
Don't think I'm protecting you
out of the goodness of my heart.
A girl has the right to expect
compensation for her trouble.
Yuki!
Get off of her!
Get off of her!!!
You're more of a man than I
thought you were, First.
Nicely done.
Thank you.
A worthy sacrifice on
my path to godhood.
Believe me...
When I attain the throne of time
none of this pain will matter.
Don't bother.
You're in full view of my
adherents, imbecile.
All your movements
are right here.
There's no option open
to you that I can't see.
More eyes are on
you in this room
than can possibly be evaded.
I know.
My diary says that in more
or less the same words.
Funny.
And yet somehow no Dead End
has been triggered for me.
Which means I'm
not checkmated yet.
I still have options.
Options like this.
I choose to live.
I choose Yuno!
You idiot boy!
I can do this.
All I need is a second.
Look at this!
No!
Their eyes are all
drawn to the same thing!
Don't touch my scroll!
My hand I...
Why on earth?
Of all the things.
Where have you been?
Oh Yuki.
I should've come sooner.
I'm so sorry.
Who are you, Yuno?
Who are you really?
You stalk me.
Switch gears at
the drop of a hat.
Your house has
dead people in it.
I mean, how's a guy supposed
to feel about all that?
Ah, who cares right now.
Did that cop seriously
hit me up for my number?
Whatever the hell he's up to.
I don't like it.
♪ closing song ♪
More tea?
Why yes, thank you.
I begin to think Justice
no more than a fiction.
Just the other day.
There was an elderly woman
struggling with her groceries.
Allow me, oh
world-weary babushka.
Stay away from me!
No,wait!
You misunderstand!
She ran in terror as though
I were a common thug.
Well, have you looked
in a mirror lately?
Haven't you eyes
in your head, sir?!
I tried drawing a policeman's
attention to a burglar.
It was myself
arrested for the effort.
I'm not the one you want!
I can't walk down the street
without children
throwing rocks at me.
See?
I'm surprised it's only rocks.
Alas...
Perhaps I'm just not
of the vigilante mold.
I suppose it is all
rather absurd, isn't it?
Stop that!
You're just going
through a bad patch!
I am?
What you need is
the Diary of Justice!
Sorry, what?
With this baby.
You'll know precisely where
you're needed and by whom!
No more misunderstandings!
Surely you jest!
It's too good to be true!
You want it?
With every fiber of my being!
But I am so poor!
Ho-ho!
It's on sale for the amazing
price of Whatever You've Got!
Yes, yes, yes,!!!
I shall pay you, Fifty!!!
There's a sucker
born every minute.
Did my good deed
for the day, though.
Hi there.
I'd like this, please.
That'll be sixty even.