--Yuki!
Question.
Who do you trust more?
I love this tower.
It's one of my favorite places.
Fourteen years ago.
Mama left for parts unknown,
depositing me on
the observation deck.
Hurry up, Daddy!
I wanna look through
that telescope, too!
"You sit right there, Ai.
I'll be back in a jiffy.
"I'll be back in a jiffy.
I'll be back in a jiffy."
Today's the worst.
That's a good thing.
If today's the worst day of
your whole entire life then
tomorrow automatically
has to be better, right?
So cheer up!
My name's Ai.
What is your name?
Did you come here with your mom?
Where is she?
I don't know.
That sucks.
How about you
come with me, then?
And the rest is history.
His name was Marco Ikusaba.
He'd lost his folks to the
same kind of wanderlust.
What gives?
Why the hell've
you been tailing me?
Just because, I guess.
Your classes aren't
even up here.
This is where you are.
You can't keep doing this.
You gotta learn to stand
on your own two feet, Ai.
Fine, I guess I'm okay with it.
What are you putting in there?
Stuff about you.
Like that silly fight we had.
Come on.
You wanna grind
your phone keys to dust,
go nuts but write about
something else for a change.
There's a whole
big world out there.
It's okay.
I'm only here because of you.
You're the whole
big world to me.
Hey, Marco?
Yeah?
Someday, I'm gonna
marry you right here.
Here?
But isn't this place
a little touristy?
You were right all
along, you know that?
When you found me it
really was my lucky day.
That's why it's gotta be here.
Just look at her.
Little Miss Stuck Up.
I know, right?
"My name is Ai an'
I'm a stuck-up whore!
I don't talk to anyone
from my class"
Her boyfriend's a loser, too.
You mean that scrawny
guy with the stupid hair?
You know, I think we should
help her loosen up a bit.
Marco?
I got your note.
This is creepy.
Say something.
Shit, man...
She really came.
Uh-huh.
And she's pretty hot.
That's a plus.
What if she runs to the cops?
Use your head, man.
They said she's an
orphan, remember?
Cops ain't gonna give two shits.
And we're all
minors, so whatever!
Hey...
What the hell?
Let go of me!
No! Marco!
Marco!
Pick up, Ai.
What the hell.
Why isn't she answering?
Why's she even there?
That place's deserted!
Whatever's going down, I got a
real bad feeling about it!
I'm so sorry.
I never should've let
you outta my sight.
I should've been with you today.
Why can't I undo
what they did to you?!
It's 'cause I, 'cause
I wasn't there to protect you!
This is all my fault!
I hope you can
forgive me someday!
Don't!
I'm begging you.
If you cut your
throat you're gonna
hurt me worse than
they ever could.
The day we met,
you saved my life Marco.
So tonight let me save yours.
Please, just don't
leave me alone.
Ai.
I love you so much.
I swear to God.
I'll keep you safe.
It's gonna be you and me, Ai.
Forever.
I love you.
♪ opening song ♪
I've got you.
Oh, thank God.
Oh no you don't.
I ain't ready to let you
slither away just yet.
I still can't wrap
my head around it.
How could my own dad
just lie to me like that?
Yuki, look!
I think they're heading
to higher ground!
Huh?
That doesn't make sense!
It does if they've already
planned some kind of escape!
Come on!
Wait, they're gonna
use parachutes?!
That works out.
All we have to do is defeat
them and take their
parachutes for ourselves.
You want a rematch don't you?
We already lost to
them once, remember?!
And that time, we weren't
even all banged up!
I hope you don't take this
the wrong way, darling,
but I know why they were able to
beat us back at Kousaka's house.
The fight was two against one.
Yeah, and it
never should've been!
Sorry I'm so useless.
Don't be so hard on yourself.
I have faith in you.
Yeah?
All we have to do it take them
on Yuki-and-Yuno style!
Slow down.
What's happening at the tower?
Something up there exploded,
set the upper levels on fire.
Whole damn thing may collapse.
What's worse, Amano left a note
in his hospital room that
he was heading there.
Whatever's going down at
the tower, his life's in danger.
Get his mother on
the horn A-SAP.
Let her know what's up.
On it.
Son of a bitch.
And no sign of
her hidden server.
Look at her.
She knows I'm stumped.
We need to get out of here
they're coming up after us.
Yeah, I figured they might.
Why do you keep
toying with First?
He's a nothing but a weakling.
You should have
curb-stomped his cell-phone
as soon as you had
the upper hand.
Mea culpa, baby.
There's something
about that pathetic
mug of his that yanks
at my heartstrings.
Well, you did just make an
honest woman outta me,
so I'll let it slide.
That I did.
My dream just came true.
Uh-huh...
Don't you mean our dream?
Me and you to the
end of the world, baby.
No more playing.
It's time to finish them off.
What if we lose?
We're firing off 300 rounds
of true love a minute, baby.
Those fakers are toast.
When you put it that way.
You know if First has learned
anything from our little fracas,
he'll go balls-to-the-wall
this time around.
Huh?
Speak of the devil.
You ready, Ai?
Yeah, let's do this.
The chick, huh?
Come on out, Pork-chop!
Sorry, no can do.
I'm not tall
enough for this ride.
The hell?
The only reason you beat
us last time is 'cause
Yuno had to worry about
keeping me in one piece.
I can't believe my ears!
Could you be any
more of a wuss?!
Hey, Seventh...
Good luck.
Hey, Seventh.
You're wishing us luck while
you hide like a little punk?!
After I finish with her
I'm coming for you!
Marco!
She's gonna slash
at you from the right!
Got it!
He's gonna kick
from the right, Yuno!
Thanks!
Bring it on!
Knife beats leg, slowpoke!
My stitches burst!
Knowing the future
didn't do you a
whole lot of good just now, huh!
First is hiding
out in the PA room.
Keep an eye on this one.
I'll go grab him!
Wait!
What the hell?
Are you really that stupid?!
You can't beat us when
it's two-against-one!
Yeah, you're right.
One of us can never
win against two of you.
Yuno's been captured!
Show yourself!
I know you're here!
No sign of him.
What the hell?
The diary says he's
here, so what gives?
Son-of-a-bitch!
I know this phone!
What if it's two of
us against one of you?
First?!
Damn it!
They punked us with
our own fake diary!
Ai, no!
He's gonna kill her!
Yuno's plan is working!
Look out!
He's about to
throw a dart at you!
I missed!
Ai Move!
If today's the worst day
of your whole entire life,
then tomorrow automatically
has to be better, right?
So cheer up!
When you found me it
really was my lucky day.
That's why it's gotta be here.
Marco.
Ai!
It's coming down!
Yay it worked!
I'll take this off the dead girl
and we can use it to
parachute to safety!
Then Yuki will tell
me how wonderful I am!
What the hell did you just do?
All you had to do
was take her diary, Yuno!
But she tried to hurt you,
my love she had it coming.
Is that your solution for
every problem, just kill them?
Dad?
What're you?
Sorry, kid!
But your old man isn't
ready to die, not today!
No, wait!
Dad!
Please be okay!
Kurou?!
Now what?
I didn't get a chance
to break Yuki's phone.
Without proof, they're
never gonna erase my debt.
What were you doing up there?!
Rea?
Aw, this isn't good.
Where's Yuki?
Why isn't he with you?!
I know you were up there!
What do I do if she starts
putting it all together?
I can't take that kind of risk.
You're coming with me!
Hey where are you
trying to drag me off to?!
What the hell?!
You are going to
tell the cops everything!
Just what are
you trying to imply?!
Stop it, okay?
Just stop!
The detective told
me you were with Yuki!
We're getting to
the bottom of this!
Let it go, Rea!
Oh yeah?!
Or what?!
Let go of me!
Damn you Rea.
I told you to just leave it!
It's no use.
This concrete isn't
moving an inch.
Are you okay?
Sorry, kiddies.
Says here that
Marco's gonna escape.
You're still alive?
Marco knows everything that
happens down here
thanks to my diary.
He knows I don't have much
longer before I bleed out.
And that the two of you
will be turned into red paste
when the rest of this
tower crashes down on us.
He's gonna jump to
safety any minute now.
My baby's gonna survive this.
He's gonna win.
The game isn't over yet.
Yuno, what are you
doing?! Stop it...
Just cause you're
gonna die doesn't
make you magically
immune from pain.
If I start flaying you,
he'll dig down here.
Have you lost your mind?!
It's the only way
we're getting out.
You can cover your
eyes if you want to.
Oh... Come on!
She's already gonna die!
What's that sound?
Just hang on, baby.
I'm getting you
outta there I promise!
Marco?
We're gonna become
gods, remember?
We're gonna win this
thing and live forever!
I ain't letting you
get cold feet, Ai!
I'm dying Marco, just stop.
You need to get out
while you still can.
Better hurry it up!
My knife is getting
thirsty again!
Still plenty of places to cut!
Yuno! Stop it!
What the hell is
wrong with you, First?!
You let that crazy little bitch
do all the dirty work for
the two of you and then you tell
her to show your enemies mercy!
How've you gotten
this far First?!
I can't lift this rubble!
First!
Stop being useless and help
me move this thing already!
Is that a good idea?
That's just what Yuno
wants you to do.
You forget who's been keeping
your ass alive this whole time?!
Who's been doing all
the damn wet-work, huh?!
But there you are, little man
warning me not to fall for
her trap 'cause you ain't
got the stones for all this!
Hey!
Second!
Help me move all o' this!
I'm the one giving the
orders around here!
You're as bad as that kid.
You talk a big talk about
protecting your man,
but all you do is run
roughshod over him.
You ain't working together
you know that, don't you?
You're selfish little brats!
Hey... you don't know us!
You think I'm digging her out
'cause you said
so, you're crazy!
You think you had
to lure me down there
with the threat
of hurting her more?!
Don't make me laugh!
Leaving without her
was never even an option!
Marco, please stop.
It's okay.
Just go while you still can.
I'm not going to
live much longer.
You say that like...
...it makes a difference!
Whatever time you got
left is precious to me!
You posers don't know
the first thing about love!
What me and Ai got
going you can't even touch!
Oh my God.
Look at you.
Sorry, baby.
Guess I zigged when
I should have zagged, huh?
Give me a hand up here, Yuno!
The three of us
can move this thing!
But, Yuki...!
Yuno!
Yuno, do you love
me the way you're
always saying that you do?
Or are you just nuts after all?
Why do you ask?
The way you act, how am
I supposed to know?
I wanna believe you, Yuno.
So help me.
That's twice now.
I was too late.
You bested us fair and square.
Here, you earned it.
Seventh I'm sorry.
Shut up, Porkchop.
We don't need your damn pity.
Now go!
So much for the plan.
We both tried our damndest
to become gods, baby.
But I guess it wasn't
in the cards was it?
You know what, though?
This is all I wanted.
You and me
together until the end.
Yuno.
I wanna sit Mom and Dad down
and have a serious
talk with them.
What about?
I realize that Dad's not your
favorite person in the world.
There are lots of issues
we got to work through.
But...
I'd really like it if I could
convince Mom and Dad
to give it another shot.
And it would be cool
if you could help me.
Okay.
Yuki!
Stay right there!
Nishijima?
Listen to me!
I'm sorry there's no
easy way to say this!
A few minutes ago,
your mother was...
His mouth moved
like he was still talking.
But, I couldn't
hear anything else.
'Cause what I was
seeing blotted out everything.
Did you hear me?
Your mother, she's...!
♪ closing song ♪
"Cause I'm a one-woman
man and that woman is you"
I hope you're ready for love,
'cause I'm primed
and ready to go!
Hey!
Why's a midget
chick in our bed?!
Marco?
Who in the hell is
this half-pint hussy?!
Oh, like I would know?!
I was just taking a shower!
C'mon help me out here!
Sure thing!
My name's Murmur,
and I specialize in taking
care of my master's needs.
Her master's needs?!
You...
...son-of-a...!
Are you trying to
get me killed?!
Tell her we don't
know each other!
I thought you were different,
but you're just a filthy horn
dog like the rest of them!
Baby, nothing happened!
I've never seen her
before this very moment!
Give me a sec.
I've got something
that'll calm her down.
Your own Exchange Diaries!
Now you'll know what happens
to each other in the future!
Pretty convenient, yeah?!
You're my prince
in shining towel, Marco!
You're the only woman
in my universe, Ai.
Honest.
Do I barf or
bust out the popcorn?
--Oh, Ai.
--Oh, Marco.
She was ready to kill him and
now she's all lovey-dovey?
My dating sim didn't
prep me for any of this!