Yuno!
Stick to the plan.
Once they all run for it, we'll
meet up on the 25th floor.
Right down to the letter, baby.
God, I'm in love with you.
Awesome.
'Cause I love you, too.
You're telling me that
girl is running amok
downstairs with a katana?
Yes, sir but I'm afraid
we've lost track of her!
We're live on the
scene at City Hall
as the crisis
continues to worsen!
It would seem
that the terrorists
have made good on their threat
to take hostages
in order to leverage
their way into
the mayor's office.
They've just released their
demands to the media which we're
only broadcasting in the
name of journalistic integrity.
"Unless you want corpses
on your hands, you'll release
Kousaka Ouji, Hinata Hino
and Mao Nonosaka
and the Mayor
has to kill himself!"
Using the media to
thin out Balks's options?
Clever.
Be a dear and
retrieve our friends
from those guards, would you?
Yeah!
Be back in a jiffy!
It's high time I dealt with
Eleventh once and for all.
That look.
When did First grow a pair?
If I'm going to bring
Mom and Dad back.
I need to win this thing.
Sorry but there's
something I still got to do.
I promise, Nishijima.
You won't be the last to bleed.
♪ opening song ♪
We have to hurry!
We've only got an hour before
the cops storm the building!
This had better work out.
Don't tell me it
slipped your mind.
You hitting the bulls-eye.
Also...
Nishijima had no
business dying today!
You're alive right now 'cause
you're gunning for Eleventh.
But the second that your
little plan doesn't work.
I'm gonna put the
daylight through ya!
Looks like ya got
us cornered, Officer.
I surrender.
If we get outta this,
remind me to kick your ass!
When you said you could
handle this I thought
it meant you
actually had a plan!
Listen, up!
If you get the three
of us eighty-sixed,
it is definitely not gonna rock!
Yeah it will!
Eighties rock!
So what do you think
we should do with them?
The mayor made it very clear he
wanted these three disposed of.
Wai-wai-wait!
Hold on a sec!
You don't wanna shoot us,
man we're just a bunch of kids.
We won't blab about Holon,
so we're cool, yeah?!
I'd have let him go if
he hadn't said Holon.
Guess we got to kill them, then.
--Dumbass!
That girl just ambushed
two of our men!
Get her!
There you are!
Gasai Bank?
But...!
This bank breathed its
last about a year ago.
Ever since it went bankrupt,
it's belonged to the city.
I believe it was
owned by the parents
of your little chippy
in better days.
I'm not done with
you yet, Balks!
The irony is delicious.
This vault was a holding
of the Gasai family.
Now this steel will
shield me from
a pretender to their throne.
No the door's
already rolling shut!
We're gonna lose him!
Bastard!
"Please enter PIN code?!"
What is it?!
Spill your guts,
or I'll spill them for ya.
Why settle for a single door
when you can have two?
Hold up, Yuno.
Holon isn't down that hallway!
Where're you even going?!
Gasai Bank, huh?
Why aren't the keycard and pin
code working on this one?!
I got to hand it to ya, First.
You had a pretty good run.
What the hell are you doing?
Remember me saying
you were dead meat
the minute your
plan stopped working?
Wait...
There's got to be some
way to get it open,
just give me a minute!
Use your head!
We're talking
about Eleventh here.
That bastard doesn't
leave anything to chance.
Nishijima's the one man who ever
promised to make me happy
and if he hadn't gotten
wrapped up in this shit,
I think he
could've pulled it off.
But we'll never know, will we?
See you in hell!
I have to put that rabid whore
down before she murders my Yuki!
This doesn't rock.
I got no idea where this nutty
chick is leading us off to!
Why's Akise calling?
Don't drag this out, First.
Yuno's coming for me right now.
All I have to do
is survive 'til then!
A Dead End!
You might as well show yourself.
Killing you's gonna take
the last of my strength.
I bet you I'll bleed out
before your body's even cold.
Your reason for wanting to
win this was bullshit, anyway.
If I'm going to bring
back Mom and Dad,
I need to win this thing.
I got a newsflash for ya, kid!
Parents die all the damn
time but what you don't see
is other people going on killing
sprees to bring them back.
You're sad 'cause you lost your
mom and dad just now, right?
Well cry me a river.
I lost my folks
in the Middle East,
thanks to a
sixteen-hundred-year-old fight
about three takes
on the same damn God.
I couldn't speak the language.
Didn't know a soul.
I had to steal to survive.
Getting caught would have
meant death or something worse.
Don't know why
I'm telling you this, but...
I've kind of got a
soft spot for you, Yuki.
When I think of
you running through
that minefield like a damn fool,
or getting outsmarted
by a toddler,
you remind me of how pathetic I
was back in the day when
I was just a little girl
and my losses were still fresh!
But you gotta face the facts!
You ain't never gonna
get them back, kid!
Your parents are dead!
I hit you with both
barrels, and not a peep.
Kudos for having the
good sense to hold it all in.
I need to change
the future, fast!
Unless you kick off a rewrite,
you're gonna take one to the
head in about a minute.
But if you do change the future,
that static sound will
give away your location.
She's right!
They hunt each
other to extinction
as I watch from a
fortified perch.
It's too easy!
They really outdid
themselves...
...outfitting the second door
with a retinal scanner.
And the only eyes it
will accept are mine
the deceased Gasai couple's.
And those of their
adopted daughter, Yuno.
The impostor shall not
be granted access.
Eighth!
Time to cut a whore in half!
That cop is Aru!
Get out of my way.
Now.
"Sorry, Yuno." "If I die, I want
you to bring Mom and Dad back."
Yuki's gonna die?!
Buckled under
the pressure, did ya?
Seems about par for the course.
No offense.
I think I'm gonna
miss the way you
squirm through life
without a spine.
Only his cell phone?!
I messaged Yuno
like I was about to die.
She panicked, just like I
figured she would,
causing the future to change.
You wanted static.
You little shit.
I know that resurrecting
my parents is selfish.
But I can't just
let them stay dead.
Why aren't you
pulling the trigger?
I don't want to kill you.
Huh?
Listen to me.
I swear on my soul I
didn't want to kill any of them.
But I did.
More than I can count.
This game left me
no other choice!
The hell it didn't!
Why don't you tell me, then?!
If you're so smart,
tell me what choice I had!
Stop being such a bitch!
Own your sins!
You murdered them because
it was better them than you!
The gun!
Minene! No!
It's like I told you,
better you than me!
He and I, we're the same.
He's just a scared
little kid crying
for Mommy and Daddy to get up.
I'm sorry.
Right considerate of them
to kill each other off.
I'm betting you're ready
to throw in the towel.
But seeing as
how you've given me
so much data over the
course of this fracas.
I'm going to do you the honor of
asking for your opinion, First.
You lost your parents,
and as one might expect,
you tried to avenge them.
But you failed due to your
inefficient use of your diary.
How very banal of you.
All hail the conquering zero.
I can't imagine
the hubris that let you
think you were fit
to attempt this.
You and your family
were nothing more than
lab rats running through
a maze of my design.
What did you say?!
I must admit, your killing
Ninth was a pleasant surprise.
Still, she was nothing more
than a bush-league anarchist.
I've got your "pleasant
surprise" right here, Eleventh.
How're you still alive?
I'm stubborn.
First is lucky that I am.
I've got one
hell of a bomb...
...and it's hooked up to a
dead-man's switch.
As soon as my heart gives out,
it's "pop goes the weasel" time.
If you think that door's
gonna save your ass,
you're even dumber
than most politicians
and that's saying something.
You're crazy!
You're gonna blow yourself up?!
You're a trip.
Shooting me is fine but now you
get your panties in
a wad over this?
Then again it's not
like I've been operating
under the most logical
rules of engagement lately.
So I'll take care of
the open sesame part.
But whatever goes down
after that is on your head.
So own it.
If I break my diary, the bomb'll
go off as soon as I flat-line.
Been a while, huh.
I finally did that thing you
always wanted done.
I hope you're happy.
This is where we
go our separate ways.
Now you understand.
Yeah, I guess I do.
I just wanted
someone to save me.
After all I've lost.
I got my humanity back.
Nishijima.
Not even a scratch?!
What've we here?
Ninth blows herself to hell,
yet the door is standing firm!
Shut your mouth!
Yuki!
She's dead.
She sacrificed herself
to give me a shot at him.
But it didn't work!
It's okay.
We just have to get over to the
South Tower and destroy Ho-lon.
If we do that, Ninth's death
won't have been for nothing.
Right?
Yeah.
I guess you're right.
I'll keep an eye on Eleventh,
so you go on ahead.
Thanks.
Such a tantrum won't affect
my plans in the slightest,
so have at it.
Your best, eh?
I must be seeing things.
She couldn't have
gotten inside the vault!
Yuno killed Eleventh
as soon as I was gone?!
Why would he let her in?
Huh?
Oh...
Hey, Yuki.
Good morning.
I thought you were
gonna sleep downstairs!
Whatever!
Just put some clothes on ASAP!
Okay!
All right.
Eighth is the
only keeper left to kill.
And from the looks of it,
Aru might just hand
her right off to me.
I'm in the home stretch.
Honestly, I've got
half a mind to march
you up to his doorstep
and ring the bell.
I think that Yuki's the best
candidate for godhead by far.
What's the other
half of your mind say?
There's the rub.
Identity confirmed.
Lock Disengaged.
Yuno Gasai does
not inspire trust in me.
Yuki's motive for wanting
to win this game is pure.
He wants to revive his parents
and undo the events
of this bloodbath.
Yuno, on the other
hand, remains such an
enigma that we don't
even know her real identity.
I wonder.
Sorry, but I need
to ask a favor of you.
Sweet pea.
What're you writing in there?
Oh...
It's all the people I've gotten
killed over the course of this.
As soon as I win, I'm
gonna bring them all back.
Take a sec and think
about how far you've come.
Once, there were twelve of us.
Now, all that's left to
do is put a bullet in Eighth.
And one in yours truly.
Yuno.
If you're going to bring your
mom and dad back from the dead,
you can't afford
to get all sentimental.
Besides, I'll be alive again.
'Cause you're gonna undo
everything else, remember?
Yuki, look!
What is this phenomenon?!
The fabric of reality
is starting to tear!
But why is it happening to the
whole city instead
of a dead user?
Why now?!
I don't wanna be the
voice of doom,
but you know Deus's
time is almost up.
If he doesn't pick a successor
before he crumbles
into oblivion,
his death is gonna take
the whole world with him.
But you can save it.
Then I promise you,
here and now...
I'm gonna put it all
back the way it was.
And I promise I'll
make you happy.
Well isn't this funky.
He's not supposed to
kick the Deus-bucket
for a little bit longer.
Did the Big Guy forget to
carry the one or something?
Not to be a diva,
but the global kaput
is set for a hard date
of July 28th.
He's gotta soldier
on until then.
You like surprises, Murmur?
What the hell?
Don't you keepers ever knock?!
Aru Akise?!
And we've stepped
through the looking glass.
Does this mean I've been
granted an audience with Deus?
So sorry, but this
chamber is invitation-only!
Murmur from the top rope!
Deus, right?
Thank you sir for the
divine intervention.
I'll cut right to the chase.
If Yuki becomes god,
can he really undo
everything that's happened?
♪ closing song ♪
"Future Diaries," huh?
It is pretty catchy.
What did you expect?
I hope you don't take offense,
Mr. Mayor, but how come
your diary is the only
one that has a weird name?
What are you talking about?
Well, you've got
First's Indiscriminate Diary,
the Diary of Future Love,
the Murder Diary, the Case
Diary, the Clairvoyant Diary and
Exchange Diaries,
the Propagation Diary,
the Escape Diary, the Breeder's
Diary and the Justice Diary.
And then there is yours.
The mighty Peeper.
Dude, really?
"The Peeper?!"
My diary's not The Peeper.
Watcher.
Its name is The Watcher.
My mistake.
I don't know how
I got those two mixed up.
I notice you didn't mention
Fifth's Hyper Vision Diary,
the name of which is worlds
clunkier than The Peeper!
Now we're gonna field some
e-mails from your
loyal subjects!
Let's see what folks
have to say about ya!
If they're complaining,
just delete them.
Here's our first message.
Sent in by "I'm Pretty Kick-Ass
and Everybody Knows It."
"Your Peeper diary
is a little too pervy
for an elected official, man.
Let's call it the
'Full Head O' Hair Diary,'
and no one will know it's yours!
Oh snap!"
And the survey says no.
Our next one was
sent in by someone
calling herself "Gimme
Back My Fake Arm."
"Hey Mayor.
'The Peeper' makes me
thinks it's made of eyeballs.
How about 'The Creeper'
for the name of your diary?
It basically means
the same thing, so yeah."
Verdict?
Zero for two.
Next up, a helpful
suggestion from someone
going by the name
"I Dream of Hinata's Boobies".
"Mr. Mayor,
how about you call your
diary the 'I'm Always Watching
You Because I'm a Weird Old
Man With a Funky Hat
and Delusions of
Grandeur' diary?
That sums it up pretty well."
Sorry, "Boobies"
don't hold your breath.
You know what?
Now that I think about it, maybe
we're gilding the lily here.
'The Peeper' is just fine.
It's The Watcher,
you little maniac!