It was just a coincidence.
I'm not a stalker.
I mean, yeah I was kind
of maybe spying
on him, sure, but...
I didn't mean to see it.
I'm going to be late.
Ugh.
Was that a love letter?
♪ opening song ♪
I'm telling you,
that chick is on fire.
Well go on put the
moves on her, dude.
I'm just window shopping here;
I'm not outta my mind.
If I was feeling
suicidal, then maybe.
Or when your balls finally drop.
Shut up!
Stupid boys.
Wipe the drool off your chin.
I know what you're
after... no thank you.
I have a man.
One who's going
to love me for me.
One day, Yuki.
I started following him
about a week ago now.
Nothing creepy,
just keeping an eye out.
This cheesy survey they
handed out in class was throwing
me off for some reason;
I could tell he was
having issues with it, too.
So, I made conversation.
Like you do.
Long story short... the promise.
We could be a family
if we got married.
We'll have to
wait till we're older.
Alright, the votes
have been tallied,
let's read out the results.
I don't really know how else
to describe how I feel.
It's like I'm trapped in a
pit and he's my rope ladder.
So you know...
That crap has to go.
No valentine for her.
But it looks like the majority
has opted to do a Maid Cafe.
So...
Holy cow we'll need enough stuff
that it looks like one of you
will get to go on
a shopping spree.
Actually, I need two people.
Gasai, Amano, you're up.
Oh wait.
Never mind, Miss Gasai.
I forget your parents like
you home right after school.
Can I get someone else to
help Yuki with the schlepping?
I'm happy to do it, sir.
My folks are cool.
Good.
It'll be Wakaba and Amano, then.
Thank you very much.
No problem.
That sneaky little bitch.
Abusing her power to
put the moves on my man.
The letter's for her, isn't it?
She knows, too.
She's working
the angles so he'll
muster up the
courage to give it to her.
This place should
have everything we need.
Yeah.
Sure.
Wow. In a single afternoon
I go from zero friends,
to hanging out with her.
How's that happen?
Ah, who cares, right?
I just got to not screw this up.
Today is the day.
Stationary store first, yeah?
Denied!
That was way too close.
Mommy, I want to pet
the giant bun-bun!
Another millisecond
and they'd have
been skipping like
this was a musical.
Here, let me help.
You okay?
Yeah.
Thank you.
Found it.
And that takes care of our list.
You ready?
I really need to do this right.
Buy her a soda first.
Get her in the mood.
Let's see...
Did I sit on your frigging
eggs or something?!
Why am I being
harassed by a furry?
Where the hell is it written
that I don't get to
have a love life?!
Catastrophe averted.
Break down her defenses
with a cold beverage
over my dead, fluffy body!
Why'd the hoppity have to
make growlies at me, momma?
It's okay son.
He's gone.
Cheer up.
I don't want it!
I'm not out of the woods, yet.
He might give her
the letter anyway.
Kay. I'm going to give her the
letter after I do my business.
No skimps on the hand-washing.
Damn it!
You're kidding me.
Why the hell do you want this?
There he is!
Arrest that rabbit!
Screw you guys,
I've got a letter to burn!
Don't give her the letter!
She's the wrong girl for you!
She's a whore!
Wakaba!
Where've you, been?
Yuki, don't!
I can't lose him!
Without Yuki,
I don't have a future!
Wakaba.
Um.
Yeah?
This is for you.
What happens at the bottom?
It's important for
me that you read it.
Oh no.
I broke my curfew.
Wait.
Why do I care?
It's not like it matters now.
No one's around to get mad.
I'm home, guys.
How was, your day?
It's been about a
month since they died.
Keep your GPA up.
Absolutely no junk food.
Backtalk is one demerit.
Breaking curfew is three.
I know.
Three demerits gets the cage.
And the cage means no food.
Not so much fun
when you're the ones
locked in there pleading
for scraps, is it?
What can I say?
You get tired of being little
Miss Perfect after a while.
Birdie's got to leave the nest.
Or, next best thing,
lock up the folks.
See to it momma and
poppa bird get a taste
of the worms they've
been feeding you.
You little bitch!
I curse the day you were born!
Doesn't end well, though.
Not really.
I don't know if I meant
for them to die, but...
Oh well, I guess.
Thanks for helping
me out, up there.
If she'd taken
the letter, I'd be...
For now I still have a future.
All I have to do is
protect him from himself.
Got to keep him honest about the
promise he made me, don't I?
It's the only way.
The only tomorrow.
You wish to sift your mother
from the common dust?
Yes.
You're a god; it should
be a walk in park for you.
I cannot bring her back.
Why the hell not?!
My stewardship of
causality has diminished to
the point where such a
task is no longer possible.
My strength leaves me.
Lo!
When I am folded
into our common dust,
reality as you know
it will crumble for
lack of a successor
to this throne.
Yep.
Take a look at
the bigger picture kid;
mommy staying dead should
be the least of your worries.
We are talking universal
catastrophe here.
But...
The boss isn't being
totally straight with you.
There is a little workaround.
A way to save your
mom and the universe.
You have got to be kidding me.
Dad!
So what I get for whistling to
myself in a dark alley when
god only knows how many
loan-shark lackeys got to be out
there waiting to pounce the
second I show up on their radar.
How dare you come here!
Come clean.
I know you killed mom.
Turn yourself in.
Hell of a sense of humor
you got there, champ.
This isn't a joke!
Okay, fine.
Suppose I was the
one who killed her.
If you had any proof, why not
just go to the police yourself?
It's not exactly
as simple as that.
Then you might want to put a
damper on the libelous bullshit.
What did you get
that pawn receipt for?
You don't have anything to sell.
The hell you know
about what I have?
He hocked something.
I know it.
What, though?
The deadline's tomorrow.
If he thinks I'm on to him,
he'll just yank whatever
is out of pawn
before I can use it.
Unless I tail him and steal it.
Then he's up a creek.
The bastard will have
to confess to what he did!
Relax.
It's just a couple of
routine questions, alright?
The bones we found at
your house, they, uh, well...
Dental records confirm
that two of the skeletons
belonged to your parents.
So that's solved at least.
The third skeleton's
still a mystery, though.
We were wondering if
you might be able to shed
some light on that one for us.
Excuse me?
Don't get too comfortable, girl.
Forensics is working
nights on this one.
Then...
Well, we'll see.
Damn it!
Why didn't my alarm go off?
The bastard's gone!
He's nowhere near
the pawn shop yet, though.
If I hustle I can catch up!
Or not?
To hell with that!
Come on, damn it.
Rewrite!
I have to be closing the gap!
Bingo!
Shortcut!
That's what I'm talking about!
Gotcha!
A bag?
No, no, no, no, no!
Son of a...!
Where's he going?
The shrine?
Alright, then.
Another shortcut.
Man, I'm getting
old if these stairs
can frigging wind me like this.
Guess it's been a while
since I've climbed them, huh?
I know the perfect spot!
The courtyard of this place
is made for star-gazing!
You're going to absolutely
love it, trust me!
Too bad we never got a chance to
do some real sky-watching, huh?
It's over, Dad.
What are you doing here?
You tailing me?
Bastard...
What's in here's going to
prove you're a murderer!
Wait, what?
Dad, Why do you have this?
I bought it back in the day
so we could, you know, use it.
It's been in storage.
Fat chance of that now, right?
Your old man's got a one
way ticket to the Big House.
What did you expect?
Look, just...
Please believe me when I
tell you I didn't mean to do it.
I loved your mother.
I got this thing out of
pawn so you'd know that
I'd wanted us to be a
family again, too.
Dad.
I'm sorry for what
I did to us, Yuki.
Your dad's a monster.
You know they set
up these really neat
viewing stalls all along
here during festivals.
Sounds pretty cool, actually.
Maybe they'll go easy on me.
Maybe.
If I get out on good behavior
at some point down the road,
what do you say you and me...
I don't know, see if
we can't make this
whole father-son thing work?
If you've served your
time then maybe.
Can I get you to work your
charm on the parole board?
Uh oh.
Now what?
Dad!
No! Don't you
do this to me!
Get up! Please!
Dad!
No.
He was...
He was ready to atone.
He was going to face the music.
We had plans for
when he got out.
This isn't fair.
Why?
What if I told you
there actually is
a way to bring her back?
The solution's
been staring right
at you since the game began,
but for some reason
you've missed it.
You have to win the game.
Inherit the throne of time.
The irony's a bitch, I know kill
everyone to save everyone,
but that's the way the
Time God crumbles.
Hey. It's nothing
personal, kiddo.
Oh, it's about to
get extremely personal.
You little punk ass!
"An enemy tries to
stab me from behind."
"The enemy to
my right opens fire."
Look out!
This little bastard is either a
goddamn killing machine
or he's out of his mind!
Sorry, love. I got
here as soon as I could.
Yuno.
Are you alright?
Here.
Drink slowly.
You'll hurl if you chug it.
Talk to me.
There's, uh, been
a change of plans.
I'm going to win this
thing and become god.
Which means, I damn
well better get used
to having blood on my hands.
I have to bring
mom and dad back.
I'm sorry!
As of right now, all you
are to me is a hurdle!
Oh yeah?
I don't need you anymore.
I can fight my own
battles from here on out.
I've got the goods
on Eighth, and Ninth
won't ever see it
coming, not from me.
And for Eleventh,
I'll figure it out.
Go on, then.
Might as well strike
while the iron's hot.
Oh, sugar bear.
I'm ready to cash in
whenever you give the word.
Cause that's how much...
I love you.
The Eleventh Diary User
has just gone all in, chief.
♪ closing song ♪
What's going on here?
Are we on some kind
of stakeout, or what?
Where did that come from?
Oh god, it's following me!
Why is it following me?
Go away!
Do not want!
Who dresses like that in public?
Who cares I don't have
time to play follow the leader.
I've got a confession
of love to intercept!
Stop copying me!
Stop copying me!!
Wait up!
Hello, that's my head!
Kind of need it, thanks!
What a jerk.
Hey! Don't get hands-y
with me, mister!