Don't take it personal, boss.
This is really for the best.
We don't want reality ripped
apart before July 28th, right?
I was right to be suspicious.
Know, recalcitrant imp:
as my servant,
the power you wield
is not yours to control.
The bracelets round
your wrists are not trinkets;
they are restraints.
Oh, we'll see about
that I have a feeling
you're in for an
unpleasant surprise.
There we are...
...as pro tem ruler of
this desolation
I declare my powers
totally unfettered!
All hail Queen Murmur!
♪ opening song ♪
What the hell do you mean
reality ends on
July Twenty Eighth?!
Indisputable fact
sweet pea it's in my diary.
Don't take my
word for it, though,
yours is bound to
say the same thing.
Holy crap.
This can't be true!
Afraid so.
But it's not all bad news.
There's a silver lining,
believe it or not.
The day we all die will be
the happiest of our lives.
That's when we'll truly
belong to each other.
Is that water I'm hearing?
Funny.
The plumbing was shut
off last time I was here.
What's up with that?
Don't tell me she's tapped
into a neighbor's mainline.
Then again, why does it matter?
No one's gonna complain.
Frigging world's about to end.
Damn.
It's really gonna happen.
Hey.
Are you here or what?
Oh!
Good morning Yuki!
Are you bathing in
a trash can?!
There's room for one more
if you want to come in.
Wait, you mean, like...
Feels really good.
Wait! Ugh.
Silly.
Lighten up huh?
Sheesh.
You were so picturing me naked.
No I wasn't.
Oh yeah, sure.
Liar, liar pants on fire.
Just give me a couple
minutes to get the
water temp back up
and you're good to go.
I'll just skip today.
Oh, don't be a grouch,
you gotta take
a bath at least every
twenty four hours.
We're the only two users left.
Weird not to have to keep
looking over my shoulder.
Still though, feels like
maybe I should anyway.
What if they were right?
What if it's true that no
one can be brought back?
What if Yuno really
has been lying?
Couple more pieces.
Out to do it.
She's hiding something,
I know she is.
But at this point, why bother?
When the time is right,
she's going to murder you!
Who knows?
Maybe she's
just killing me softly.
I've got to stop
thinking like that.
She's nuts about me.
I'm fine.
I wanna trust her; I really do.
But it'd be stupid not to
keep checking my diary.
Dad was built a little bit
different than you, but...
A few alterations, and presto!
Hey, I was serious about
us taking a bath together.
I, don't think that'd
be a good idea.
Why'd you say that?
Well, because of the water.
I mean, without my cell phone
it'd be like shooting
fish in a barrel.
After all this...
You still aren't
able to trust me.
No.
It's just.
Dinner was great.
Well, I'm off to bed.
Good night.
Damn it, Yuki!
Why do have to be like this?!
Hold up!
What is this about?
Look, I know it freaks you
out that I'm crazy-good
at killing people,
and that I may not be
as pretty as some of
the other girls, okay?!
But goddamn it,
cut me some slack!
Everything I've done
I did to get the bad stuff
over with so
we could be together.
And what do I get?
I get "dinner was great,"
and "good night."
I'm sorry.
Don't be like this.
It's nothing personal;
I just feel in over my head.
She loves me, right?
I mean, this is real?
Hell, even if it is, doesn't
mean I'm not still in danger.
Hey, Yuki.
You asleep yet?
Come on, if she
really wanted to off me
she'd have done it by now.
It's not like she hasn't had
about a dozen opportunities.
Why wait, right?
Damn it, I don't know.
Where'd you go?
Seriously.
I'm sorry.
She's an unknown quantity.
Plain and simple.
There is no uncomplicated
way to feel about her.
Takes me back.
This is where I first
got the courage
to break the ice with you.
Remember that?
Yuno.
Even back then, I knew
we would end up together.
Cheesy?
Sure.
But it's...
Whatever.
If you want me to stay
in the wings, I'll do it.
Please, Yuno.
Tomorrow, the world ends.
I deserve to be alone.
I've treated my guardian
angel like a fly.
I'm a jackass.
She deserves someone better.
I want to be that someone.
The end is here.
I can't let her spend it alone.
I've got to go to her.
Time to man up.
Hey there.
Yuki?
If your offer stands...
I'm in.
July twenty eighth isn't going
to be our Happy Ending.
Tonight is.
Hey, uh pookie?
Yeah?
What's up?
What do you say we get outta
here before the water gets cold?
Oh, um.
Sure.
--So, yeah.
Sorry.
Didn't mean to interrupt you.
You go first.
No, no.
Please, you first.
I insist.
I just wanted you to know it's
my first time doing
this sort of thing.
So please be gentle.
That makes sense.
No prob.
It's my first time, too.
Don't worry, love.
We'll be fine.
I know we will.
Your lips feel
like butterfly wings.
Yuno.
Yuki.
I love you so much, Yuno.
I...
I love you, too, Yuki.
Sure took us a while
to get here, huh?
Whole thing finally
feels right, though.
Like we were always meant to be.
So romantic.
Since we've made it this far.
What do you say we adopt
a policy of full disclosure?
Why did you tell me
I'd be able to bring
everyone back when you
knew that wasn't true?
She's going to murder you!
No, wait!
It was just a question!
What the hell?
I'm sorry if I was dishonest.
All I wanted was to
ease your mind, love.
Your parents were
weighing on our conscience
and I didn't want that.
If I had to tell a lie
to make you happy.
So be it.
I've known since this mess began
that you can't bring
back the dead.
I asked Deus and
he leveled with me,
said it just wasn't possible.
I want you to kill me now
before this moment ends.
Before the truth unravels our
happiness any more
than it already has.
You know I can't do that.
What would be the point of
winning the throne of time
if I'm nothing but some
schmuck sitting there
pining over the lives I wasn't
able to bring back, huh?
At least you'd be alive,
wouldn't you?
No!
Being god isn't worth shit
if it means I have to kill you!
We're facing the end together!
Huh some things never change.
It's good we're being
open about everything.
I wanted to be able to
trust you, and now I can.
I don't think Aru
could've really meant
what he said in his message.
Wait...i
What message?
He was babbling off of his head.
It means nothing.
I don't care.
What'd it say?
Well we hammered something out
on his phone and
showed it to me.
It was about you.
He said this wasn't the first
time you've played the game.
That you'd actually won
and become a goddess
in some universe that
existed before this one.
Oh crap!
No...
It's too soon for this.
What's wrong, sweetie?
What's going on?
Damn it.
Was it really so much to
ask that I get to spend
one single day in bliss
with the man I love?
She's insane!
I've got to get out of here!
This is crazy.
A minute ago...
We were in love.
Why are you doing this?!
Careful what you ask for, kid.
No!!!
What is this?
Wait, I'm in our class.
The survey.
Hey, Yuno.
Everything okay?
I had trouble with
the survey, too.
I wanted to go out to the
country with them
to look at the stars, but...
They...
She's immaterial.
No touchy.
It's you!
The difference here is
the same as between
a live taping and a rerun.
What is this?
What am I seeing here?
It's a very important
point in the timeline.
Your girl's already
axed her parents.
You could always come
with me to see the stars.
There's like an observatory
real close to my house.
This is where her
life takes a turn.
Poor little thing didn't have
much in the way of hope
before you came
into her life, studmuffin.
Impossible.
We could be a family
if we got married.
We'll have to
wait till we're older.
This isn't real.
So you're gonna be
what they call a hard sell.
Kay.
Wait, where're you going?
You mean where are
the two of us going.
Did I read too much
into things or aren't you
curious 'bout why
she's trying to kill you?
Don't listen to her, Yuki!
She's a lying whore!
What she's showing
you isn't the truth!
Don't watch!
I'm begging you not to watch!
Please!!!
What are you doing?
Where are we?
Think of it as a
sort of repository
of all things past and future.
These are private memories.
What are you trying to pull,
showing me stuff like this?
Well it just so happens that
one of my many responsibilities
is to make sure the
game stays interesting.
Boom.
Hey mom.
Hey dad.
Soon I'm gonna
introduce ya to the guy
I intend to marry one day.
Akise was right.
She needed me
to keep her stable.
The one thing that's sustained
her through the hardships of her
life has been the idea that
one day she'll be your wife.
But alas, it wasn't meant to be.
How come?
The contest started not
long after that day in class.
As you know only one player
was decreed to survive.
But she was determined
to be happy at any cost.
All she wanted out
of you was one day
of untrammeled bliss
before it was all over.
Given that, the poor
thing was willing to
forfeit her life and
let you win the throne.
Once upon a time you
were dead set to be the victor.
What happened with that?
I got...
I don't know.
Then...
I promise you, here and now.
I'm gonna put it
all back the way it was.
Things changed, I guess.
I thought I could
bring everyone back.
That I had a chance
to make Yuno feel loved.
Pointless now, though, isn't it.
Always was.
If you ask me, seems like
if you wanted to die with her,
you might as well let her
kill you and be done with it.
But let's focus
on the topic at hand.
You need to know how the first
version of the universe ended.
So...
You mean there was one?
Of course.
I thought that
Akise fella explained
that to you in his dying text.
Pay attention you
might learn something.
Wait, these, these are like
clips of the past but different.
Good eye, kid.
Those are snippets from
this timeline's first iteration.
Technically, the timeline you're
caught up in now
is the second iteration.
Mind officially blown.
Say hello to your incarnations
from the first universe;
a couple of love struck
teenagers who killed all their
rivals in the game and decided
to go out hand-in-hand.
No.
I don't believe it.
Second is about to make the
mistake that kicked
off this whole mess.
It's okay, my love
just you watch.
Once I'm sitting
at the throne of time,
not even death
will keep us apart!
Okay... aha...
This is the bit where she
learns the dead stay dead.
No exceptions.
Tragically, she wouldn't
discover the truth until
she'd already
convinced you to die.
That's not right.
She learned the truth from Deus.
Oh please.
That talk never happened.
She lied to keep
you from knowing
how she really
found out.
She knew from experience.
The first thing she
did when space and time
became hers to command was make
a relatively
straightforward wish.
"Transport me to a past
where Yuki is still alive."
That, as you might've guessed,
was her second mistake.
'cause the wish was granted.
This is how it has to be.
I'm sorry.
This world isn't big
enough for the two of us.
Paints quite a picture, huh?
This is the dirty little
secret your woman's
gone to such pains
to keep buried.
Oh yes!
You, you're telling me
that my Yuno is a
version of herself
from another universe?
That's why...
Why her DNA was a
match for the third body.
There were two of her.
So she killed the new one.
I knew she was a murderer,
but I never would have thought
she could do
something like this.
Yuno!
Don't die on me!
Please!
Like I said: no touchy.
What you're looking at is
just a replay from the past;
you can't interact with it.
This isn't happening.
This is the Yuno I promised
to take star-gazing;
the one I promised to marry
when we were old enough!
Why?
Why would you cut her down
in cold blood like this?!
Yuno.
Please don't die!
Is that, is that you?
I know that voice.
You're really here.
No way!
That's impossible!
H.
e.
L.
p.
Help me please.
I, I, will wait for you.
No.
Yuno!
♪ closing song ♪
Coming to me for relationship
advice was a smart move.
Old Murmur's got the menfolk
pretty much all figured out.
Good to know.
You're gonna knock him dead!
Yuno.
You in here?
I'm so glad you're
here, Yuki-san.
Don't I look sugoi?
Uh you look very "different."
I'm just gonna go now.
My bad sister.
But I really thought Yuki would
go for something like that.
Hey, enough with
the waterworks already!
I have a super backup
plan up my sleeve.
Talk to me.
Why on earth was she
all dressed up like that?
You've been oh so naughty, Yuki.
Now get on all fours
like a good boy.
Wait... No, what,
what I meant to say was!
Aw, what're you
running away for?!
I dunno, Yuno.
That S&amp;M outfit should have
sent him straight to boner city.
Maybe I should be
having this convo with Aru.
Ah, so he's a cat person, huh?
What the hell?
It's like she's
extra nuts today.
Hey, Yuki.
Wanna pet me?