The hell you trying to pull?
Believe it or not, I've come
here to make a deal with you.
What did you have in mind?
I'm offering to call the
uniforms off you
for the foreseeable future.
I can also give you
a direct line to
the latest intel we have.
Won't your peanut
gallery get mad
if they find out
I'm on board, too?
Why do you even
need me when you've
already got Bonnie and Clyde?
Because my back's
against the damn wall!
I can trust Yuki
and Yuno because
they're not in this to win.
But a couple of teenagers
aren't going to do squat
against a nutty
bitch like Sixth.
I realize you're a monster,
but at least in your own
twisted way you abide by
something like principles.
I've only got one
condition in return.
♪ opening song ♪
If I'm the closest
thing Yuno's got to a
stable relationship,
what's that say about me?
Man...
Do you understand?
You're a stabilizing
influence on her.
She needs you.
I'm in this up to my eyeballs.
If I so much as breathe wrong,
she's going to come unglued.
Shouldn't a kid your
age have a curfew?
Oh, uh, hello... Sir.
Sorry, but I've got orders
to take you downtown.
Let's make this easy, huh?
Kay, boss; the kids have been
rounded up and processed.
I had a feeling.
Bring Yuki first.
Give it five minutes and escort
him in here by his lonesome.
Done and done.
Wish they'd clue us in
about what's going on.
All I know is that we're
part of an investigation.
Don't be nervous, sweetie.
Hey...
As long as I'm in your corner
these guys have nothing.
Yeah, sure.
Whatever happens, I'll
have your back understood?
We've been corralled here
like lambs to the slaughter.
We've what?
We have to keep
our diaries safe at all costs.
First things first, though:
find a weapon.
Oh god, not now.
She's in full-on psycho mode.
I have to put the brakes on this
before things get
seriously ugly.
Come on.
Snap to, son.
Looks like the first person
up for a little Q&amp;A is you.
Wait? Not right now!
Please!
I mean we're in a
police station, right?
And we're kids what
are they going to do?
If you say so.
We're just on edge, you know?
Besides, Kurusu's proven
to be a man of his word.
We've got nothing
to worry about;
he probably needs
our help is all.
You stay out here, be cool.
It's all you, hotshot.
Okay.
Good evening, sir.
Pull up a chair, Yuki.
Let's have a chat.
Speaking hypothetically...
What if I had witnesses
that can place you
and the girl at the
scene of a homicide,
specifically the shooting death
of one Karyuudo Sukishima,
world-class dog trainer?
I'd call B.S.!
Whoever's told
you that is lying!
Yeah...
Lot of folks like
to stir the pot.
But I know innocent
when I see it.
No worries.
Dude, are you trying
to give me heart failure?
I've got a right to cover
my own ass, you know.
Sorry to make you sweat.
Could've been worse.
Guy's got to keep his diary
out of the paper trail, I guess.
Before I let you
outta here, though...
How about we,
play a friendly little game?
You familiar with
Russian Roulette?
Fourth has it in for us!
My love.
Later.
Excuse me.
I'm talking to you!
Oh shit!
The hell's going on in there?!
Use your head, champ; what
is there to be scared about?
Seriously?!
What do odds have on being
able to see the future, right?
You've got the advantage; your
diary takes note of everything.
Imagine being in my position.
I've only got the
goods if what's
going down happens
to tie into a case.
Ah, know what?
If you were found shot
in an interrogation room,
that'd start a
case, wouldn't it?
Of course the last
thing I'd want is to have
Internal Affairs up my ass.
Yeah.
Kinda my job to
only kill bad guys.
So I can't be the
one to shoot you.
But...
One chamber left.
Afraid it's just not your
lucky day. shit happens.
Look...
This isn't funny okay?
It's not meant to be funny.
Sorry, kid.
We formed an alliance.
You need our help
reigning in the other
players so things
don't turn any worse
Change of plans.
I have a vested
interest in winning.
But you...
Heads up, Yuki!
Drop it!
Yuno, wait!
No.
What have you done?!
Cut it out, Yuno; he's down!
Chief!
Please tell me you didn't...
That's enough!
Please, Yuno!
You've got to get a grip!
Calm down!
Come back to me!
I want the Yuno
who's not in kill mode!
Oh pumpkin, you're such a dork.
We're okay.
I told you I'd have your
back, and that's what I did.
We've got shots fired!
Sounded like they
came from Interrogation!
Right.
Now we find a
way outta this joint.
Detective!
Someone get downstairs
and call an ambulance!
I'm on it!
Talk to me, sir.
Can you hear me?
Tell the paramedics
he's conscious!
The girl's good.
Most people wouldn't
have the chutzpah
to try for the head
on their first shot.
So much for this damn thing.
She's a live one.
It's sheer luck
I only lost an ear.
Heads up, there they go!
Damn it.
They took the right!
Think about what you're doing!
They're going to throw
the goddamn book at you!
If they don't kill you first!
Hey, it's not like I set
out to do this, okay?
I was a patsy, that's all;
I had no choice!
Listen up!
Either surrender or get shot!
Son of a bitch.
Sir, you're hit!
Don't worry about me;
go get those bastards!
Stop or I'll shoot!
Don't make me do it!
That's right; now turn
around nice and slow, okay?
I didn't mean to do this!
Yuki, put the gun down!
That was a warning shot;
they're not trying to kill...
Oh my god... I didn't mean.
Nicely done, kid.
Your attention, please.
Yukiteru Amano and Yuno
Gasai are not to make it out
of this building under
any circumstances.
Whatever you got to do
to make that happen, do it.
If they try to resist in
any way shape or form.
Consider it open season.
That's it we're dead.
What choice did I have?
I'm a cop; I can't just frame a
couple of innocent teenagers.
Now, paint them into a corner
till they're not so innocent
and it's a different story.
Not like I forced Yuki
to date a time bomb.
It's an ugly world out there.
My job is to make it a little
less so; to take out criminals.
Everything's falling into place.
Wait! It's not
worth it! Don't!
I'm sorry.
It's my fault
we're in this mess.
I should've tried harder
to keep you under control.
Oh, Yuki.
You're so sweet.
And from that moment on...
...we were fugitives.
In a statement to reporters,
officials confirmed that a gun
used by the teenage couple
in their escape belonged
to the homicide detective
interrogating them.
According to police, a dragnet
is in full force until the
underage perpetrators
can be apprehended.
The search has been exhaustive.
However, the suspects
are still at large.
How you holding up?
You good?
It's just a scratch.
No need to worry, darling.
I'm going to starve to
death before this is over.
C'mon...
Power through it.
We got to lay low for now.
Least till the
diaries get revised.
They're still saying
tomorrow's a dead end.
As long as the cops are counting
on us to sneak out for food,
the only thing to do
is sit here and wait.
The good news is if
they've changed their tactic
to a waiting game
then we'll be safe here.
If I don't eat something soon.
Back in a second, love.
I won't go far.
Sorry.
Just try to ignore it.
Girls got to do what
a girl's got to do.
And don't worry...
I know we can't hole up
in this shack forever,
nor do I expect us to.
Donuts.
Dad's specialty in the kitchen
used to be homemade donuts.
Why exactly
did your folks split?
I mean, not that
you have to talk about it.
Who the hell knows why
grownups do anything?
Take Kurusu.
One minute he's
our friend, the next.
Oh, sweetie. I...
What is that smell?
I'm sorry!
No!
I...
can smell donuts!
Is that?
Kurusu's wife.
What are the chances
she'd come to this hospital?
Whoever she's here to see,
it's not her husband.
We need to get
to the bottom of this.
Ah,wait.
Yuki, look out!
What're you made of that
you're still in one piece?
What in the hell
are you doing here?
Oh, come on...
Is that any way
to kick off a reunion?
Ninth.
Be careful!
I got to hand it to you,
you're timing's dead on.
I was getting bored
out of my mind.
Let's blow up the
floozy first, shall we?
Nothing personal.
Don't want you feeling
like a third wheel. Eh?
To hell with you.
Shit.
You dumbass!
Are you out of your damn mind?!
Help!
Somebody!
I'm here!
Never touch my board!
Here! Use this to
cross over to my side!
Knock it off!
You're going to kill us!
We've got an explosion
at the Sakurami hospital!
Get all available
forces over there!
Of all the places to show up!
What the hell
brought them there?
I don't think so.
Like you and your
little girlfriend aren't
going to leave me
stranded if I let you go first.
I won't kick it away.
Fine; and I won't
give you a reason to.
To hell with that?
If I let you go first, you'll
pull something sneaky!
Look, I give you
my word, alright?
As if that's good for anything?
And for your info
she's carrying a gun!
I won't use it if you behave.
Would it make you feel better if
we called a temporary truce?
Let me cross.
And I'll explain why your
friendly neighborhood cop
sold the pair of you out.
Really?
Ugh.
Seriously?
I swear to god.
What?!
It's me.
Nice try, but my diary's
keeping me up to date.
Just do your thing.
I'll be there in a few minutes.
Nice try, indeed!
You're in cahoots with him!
Quit being a spaz!
I don't care how nice they are,
I'll never trust another
adult as long as I live!
Knock it off!
I called a damn truce, didn't I?
Don't you do it, Ninth.
Turn on me and it's your ass!
You got that?
I'm buying you time!
I knew it, you were lying to us!
You're on his side!
Just shut up for a second!
You don't have to worry
about what side I'm on.
That's a promise!
Could you both please
stop talking to me
like you're on a
babysitting gig?!
Darling, I love you!
I'd never betray you!
What's the story, Ninth?
How am I supposed to pick
between two psychos?!
Both of you treat me like a kid!
If they're not either
with you or dealt with
by the time I get there,
so help me you'll rue the day!
Is that clear?!
If you double-cross me,
you're dead!
Fuck you!!!
Kay...
That feels better.
We're doing this.
Not that it matters now.
Fourth will be here any minute.
There...
Oh, I'm so glad you're okay!
Come on...
We need to try
and even the odds.
What's in there?
The reason Kurusu
nullified the pact and
sent you both
running for your lives.
I've only got one
condition in return.
It's simple really.
If this stupid game proves
to be the end of me.
Sorry, ma'am.
Staff.
Hey.
You're from the wedding expo.
But...
Out of your element?
We're all about
young couples!
Kid's name is You.
Kurusu's little boy.
I don't understand.
Few weeks ago,
the doctor's said he had
three months to live,
at the outside.
The prognosis gave
Kurusu second thoughts
about the game, and now
he wants to be god.
Do you mind my asking
how you know all this?
Because I made a deal with him.
He'd burn my dossier
in return for a favor.
Of course that's all
off the table now.
Only way out of this
is for us to team up.
Use his family against him.
Chow down.
You're going to need it.
I'm not taking
something meant for him.
Makes more sense they
should go to us than to
some brat who's
about to be food himself.
How can you talk like that?
Now you've seen what drives
a man to betray his friends.
As of this moment
you're an adult.
No going back.
First order of business as
an adult is to eat what you can.
Scruples mean starve.
He's not going to have any
qualms about eating you.
I have to be strong for Yuno.
But...
Do I really have
to resort to this?
Three players all with
Dead Ends in their diaries.
What a group we are, eh?
Damn.
And by the way
just so we're clear.
When I said temporary
truce back there.
I meant till Fourth's
out of the picture.
♪ closing song ♪
Ah, chief.
There you are.
Been looking for ya.
It's, uh...
Well...
Kind of time for
the weekly pow wow?
I didn't realize
it'd gotten so, late.
Hey, before we head in
there, can you give me a
status update on
the Minene search?
I'm afraid there's really not
much else to report, sir.
Something wrong?
No...
Nothing.
It's just...
Are you wearing a new suit?
What are you talking about?
This is same suit
he always I mean,
the same suit I always wear.
And for that
matter the same hair.
No, you're right.
Guess I'm just out of it.
I haven't been
sleeping well lately.
Sorry, sir.
Well, I recommend you
get a grip on yourself.
If this were a crime scene,
you'd be knee deep
in viscera before you knew it.
Uh...
Yeah, like I said.
Eh, nobody's perfect.
Buy me a katsudon
and we'll forget it.
Oh, sweet mother of...!
Authentic
policeman-style katsudon!
Same as always, actually.
So good there
ought to be a law.
Did you know, it's actual
protocol for homicide detectives
to have a bowl of this while
they're putting the screws
to an especially hostile
murder suspect.
Is that a fact?
Fess up!
C'mon, we both know
you're hiding something.
Out with it, sport.
Now.
We already know the truth;
make this easier on yourself.
Do you, want me
to say something?
No, no...
Not like that.
You're supposed to be hostile.
Oh...
Sorry?
No...
You're killing me, Masumi.
Killing me.
There's like a million cop
shows you could be referencing.
Why even have this job if
you're not going to imitate TV?
Well, I...
I...
Don't know.
That's enough.
I'll talk.
I'm the man you want.
There's blood on my hands!
That's it.
Be a man and get it
all off your chest.
Why don't you start
from the top and
tell me exactly what you did?
Yes, sir.
I've been carrying
this weight for so long,
I just didn't know
how to come clean!
Yo, Masumi.
Want to grab a bite to eat?
I'm way ahead
of you there, chief.
I've got a big hot bowl
of katsudon waiting
for you in the
interrogation room.
And I think you'll like the role
play I throw at you today.