It's been a while, Rhantolk.
I'm glad you're all right.
Thanks, the feeling is mutual.
I have to ask, though.
What's with your hair?
Uh, well...
And you. Who are you?
The name's Willem Kmetsch, the
new fairy warehouse caretaker.
It's nice to meet you.
I see that you're a disfeatured, too.
You aren't, by chance, a troll, are you?
You mean Nygglatho has a husband?!
No, she does not!
I'm human.
Huh?
An emnetwiht?
If that's a joke, it isn't funny.
Well, never mind me.
There's something I wanna know about you.
Stop it! That tickles so bad!
I knew it. She's showing
symptoms of venenum poisoning.
Just try to suck it up.
What do you think you're doing to her?
Relax, it'll be fine.
How is that "fine"?
Ah! My gosh--! Please!
I can't handle this anymore.
Stop! You unhand Nopht immediately, or else!
Ah!
I sense dirty thoughts.
Feel better now?
My body feels so light it's almost creepy.
I happen to find it unsettling to have
my fatigue disappear so suddenly like that.
I said you'd be fine. But how fine was she?!
How fine, what?
Let me guess, you're finding it hard to trust me, right?
Of course.
You are an emnetwiht.
Others might be able to have faith in one of
the sinners who destroyed the world, but I cannot.
Well, I've been surrounded by
those "others" for a while, now.
I must be a very lucky man.
I find your nonchalance suspicious, as well.
Masking your evil intentions and
tricking people must be a habit for you.
Yes, I'm grateful you helped Chtholly survive
a battle in which she was supposed to die.
However, your being an emnetwiht raises a flag.
We have no guarantee you are not dangerous.
Need I remind you that it was
your people who were responsible
for spreading the seventeen beasts across the world?
Hm?
A few days after the beasts appeared,
two islands vanished from the map.
By the following week, five countries,
four islands, and two oceans were gone.
The week after that, the world map had lost all meaning.
And then, before long, all humanity was wiped out.
How did the beasts increase so rapidly in number?
I don't know for sure, but I've heard they
were originally some kind of biological weapon.
Biological weapon?
Meaning, they must have used some organism as a base.
What creature, exactly, did the
humans use to construct the beasts?
Dunno.
Biological weapons.
That's why they were made.
Their only purpose was to fight.
Like us. We just fight on the other side.
You don't have to know everything about them.
They're archenemies who make you suffer, that's all.
Isn't that right?
I suppose so, but I also wish to learn the whole truth.
For what it's worth, I don't mind people
like you, but I gotta walk away with her so, bye.
I'm sorry about that.
She's usually such a nice girl.
I get her point.
I'm gonna check on things out there.
Stay on the ship for me, okay?
What? But, I...
Didn't I say not to push yourself?
Please just stay put.
Don't worry, he's in good hands.
I'll be keeping an eye on him for you.
Why would you keep an eye on me?
Obviously, because you had dirty thoughts about Rhan.
Oh, don't start!
Rude.
Always treating me like a kid.
Who cares if Rhan has a more mature aura.
All right! Last one!
Which way will it go?
Now, which one is it?
Gotcha!
Oh, come on! Not again!
Ribbit all to hell!
Quit croakin'. What are you, a baby?
A tadpole? You ain't got legs down there?
Get out of the doorway.
Oh, right, sorry about that.
If it isn't Madam Secretary.
What brings you in here, sweetheart?
Wanna join us for a drink?
Who knew she'd just be a disfeatured kid?
Kid or not, she's an esteemed secretary.
She sure is.
She helps out our honorable technical officer, in...
...more ways than one.
Hey, would you help us out in more ways than one, too?
Just ribbing!
You most likely do not need to
worry much about Nopht and Rantolk.
Neither of them have ever been
the kind to seriously hate someone.
Yeah. I get it.
Thank you, though.
You've always got my back.
I really do appreciate it.
I do so because you might break otherwise.
Do I really seem that fragile?
Well, thanks anyway.
And keep looking out for Chtholly, too, would you?
Mm.
You moron!
Do you even know what you've done?!
I know that I'm a first-grade technical officer.
Not to mention also being the
highest-ranking officer here.
I don't care!
Who died and made you the boss?!
Well, look who's as loud as ever.
Hm?
Willem!
Oh, good.
Do you know this man, Second-Grade Officer?
Yes.
Okay?
This idiot sent an additional
excavations squad underground.
We have to grab as many relics
as possible before we leave.
I don't believe you realize how crucial this operation is.
Sending too many men underground
at once is considered a bad idea.
Huh. That's probably just a silly myth.
It's real! From what I've been told,
no group of more than seven
salvagers has ever returned alive!
There's a reason why we work in small groups.
You must respect the surface!
They've already left, so no point in complaining now.
All we can do here is prepare for the worst.
Isn't that right, sir wise First-Grade Technical Officer?
Yes, you're right that you're right.
You see how bighearted a first-grade technical officer
I am? Take care of those things for me.
I will. Thank you, sir.
I wasn't expecting you of all people to show up.
Well, I wasn't expecting to see you here. Huh, Grick?
Huh? Wow, another cutie pie.
Met Nopht and Rhantolk, yet?
You could say that.
You didn't lie, these fairies really are nice girls.
I'm kinda still in shock.
I won't walk one down the aisle.
Back up, you weirdo.
Whatever. So, is the plan to load
the entire haul onto the Plantajinesta ?
Yep, including everything on the Saxifraga .
Why?
I'm looking for something.
Adviser, we need your help here, please.
'Kay! I'll see ya later.
You, too, Missy.
Meow.
Done!
Ribbit?
Finished.
I'm all done on my end, boss.
Thank you!
Well, I did tell her not to push herself.
My, if it isn't the technical officer.
What brings you all the way down here?
What, indeed?
Shouldn't you be with your esteemed secretary?
My esteemed secretary is busy.
Hey, where did you store the dug weapon that you found?
No idea.
We followed our orders, which
were simply to carry it back here.
A lot of men were lost in the attack, you know.
There's just no way we can keep track of everything.
'Course not.
So, I'm looking for a needle in a haystack?
Earthquake?
Careful, boys!
It's a big one today.
There have been a lot of tremors lately.
Lil...
Lillia...
Uh.
Who are you?
What do you want from me?
Lillia... Asplee...
I'm the brave who is going to kill you and save the world!
That sounds like it must be a pain.
You have no idea!
And why would you want to save the world?
I'm doing this for one reason.
It's for my love.
Time to say goodbye.
Rest in peace!
My name is Chtholly.
I guess I'm still fine.
And here you are.
I can't remember the last time I had soup this delicious.
Seconds please, oh, dear Madam Secretary!
Sure! Comin' right up!
This is yummy!
I mean, wow!
The kick of the pepper's a nice touch,
and the richness of the texture is next to perfect.
Impressive.
How did Chtholly become such a good cook?
It's the power of love.
Hey, you seem awful mad.
What are ya, scared someone's gonna
take your Chtholly away from you?
Oh. Hi there, Officer Casanova.
Better make that secretary of yours happy, you got it?
That girl is gonna make a perfect wife.
But if you go and break her heart,
don't make me spell it meowt.
Screw them!
Perfect wife, my foot!
Make her happy, my ass!
They don't have to tell me, because I already know.
I already know what?
Don't start cryin' if you trip.
But since you're reading, what's that part say?
"Carried the corpse of a god to the city," I believe.
The text is blurry after that, so I cannot read it.
Sure hope that god has mercy on their souls.
I love it. I just love it.
Thank mew!
You're very welcome.
Who's up next?
Hm?
Nice work. You're really good at that, too, Chtholly.
Thanks! I've been working on a bunch of my skills.
Chtholly, may I ask you something?
Of course.
Why'd you come to the surface?
Was it perhaps for that Willem person?
And if so, is that because he saved your life?
I dunno.
He's rather calm for someone who's walking a tight rope.
He's certainly awkward, and he over thinks everything.
The point is, I guess I just...
She just wants to be with him.
Ren, c'mon!
Damn him. Damn that man!
She's way too good for that stupid jerk!
Don't mind them. I'm rootin' for you two!
Oh, really? So that's how it is, then?
Don't you start with me, too!
Oh, my!
Hm?
Did you sort all of this out yourself?
What are you two doing here?
We've decided to come help.
Looking for that dug weapon, right?
Really?
What brought this kindness on?
We've been hearin' a bunch of stuff about you.
Like that you're taking good care of the little ones.
Oh, no.
You haven't been told anything too weird, have you?
Hm... uh... You mean like how you
and Chtholly are close to couple-hood?
Or like how Ithea thinks you're into young girls?
Never mind! I got it.
Don't think we're doing this for you. It's for Chtholly.
Well, that's nice.
And thanks, but I'm pretty sure I'll be fine.
This is my job.
I kinda want to find it myself.
Oh, right.
Bring me your swords, girls.
I'll tune them while I'm at it.
What the heck?
What is this? It wasn't on the list.
Hm?
Hey, there you are.
Oh, Chtholly.
What's up?
I'm giving out lunch boxes to those
who can't make it to the mess hall.
I brought this one for you.
Thank you, but the secretary thing is just an excuse.
You didn't have to.
If I just sat around doing nothing,
then it would appear that you really had brought
along your lover instead of someone with a purpose.
So what? Who cares though?
I happen to care, thank you.
Is that so?
Is that one Nopht's sword?
Yep, and I found the other one, too.
The "other one"?
That's Lapidemsibilus.
I'll have to take a closer
look at it once we get back home.
You did it.
You really found it for me.
Do you still remember that night when I tuned Seniorious?
Or have you forgotten?
I remember.
I also remember who Nephren and Nopht are, and Rhantolk.
I know her. And I remember Ithea, too.
I remember them.
Although I'm not sure if I still remember everything.
I see.
Well, now that we have the sword,
we don't have to worry about it.
Uh?
What's the matter?
There isn't anything wrong with it.
Of course there isn't.
If there were, we'd have known
because Nopht would've been struggling.
No. This sword is known as the Kinslayer.
And what does the "Kinslayer" mean?
It specializes in killing one's kin,
one's own kind.
You see, this is a sword that can only
be used by humans to kill other humans.
How can that be when Nopht's fighting beasts with it?
That's exactly why I thought
there must be something wrong.
This sword can only kill humans.
How does she kill beasts with it?
Uh. Willem?
It can kill... only humans.
Meaning, they must have
used some organism as a base.
What creature, exactly, did the
humans use to construct the beasts?
Oh, God.
A few days after the beasts appeared,
two islands vanished from the map.
By the following week, five countries,
four islands, and two oceans were gone.
The week after that, the world map had lost all meaning.
And then, before long, all humanity was wiped out.
How did the beasts increase so rapidly in number?
It can't be...
You don't have to know everything about them.
They're archenemies who make you suffer, that's all.
I suppose so, but I also wish to learn the whole truth.
That would mean the ones making the fairies...
The ones making Chtholly suffer are...
Correct.
And they're not wrong.
Humans did destroy the surface.
What's wrong?
Willem? Seriously, what's the matter?
Talk to me!
You're not freaking out?
For what it's worth, my heart is about to explode.
But while I don't know what happened,
you're showing me your vulnerable side,
which is rare, since you usually act so tough.
It's not that complicated.
It's my joy plus my desire for you to be happy.
I feel really lucky.
You...
Besides that, you look like you
might vanish if I left you alone.
Sure, this is embarrassing, but
I'm not going to push you away.
You are amazing.
Sorry. I couldn't hear what you just said.
What was that?
Never mind.
Hey, come on!
Please don't be like that!
Say it again.
Just one more time, please.
Marry me.
Thank you.
Uh! Wha--?
You are what I needed.
You gave me something that I want to protect.
You gave me a home I could return to.
You gave me hope.
You gave me a reason to live.
You helped me realize that
it's all right for me to live on.
So, I promise you this...
I swear.
I will make you happy, Chtholly.
I want to stay by your side, too.
Now, we can be together forever.
No! N-No, please!
Next Episode: evidence of existence.