We swore never to part.
With our vow came euphoria.
My love for him was undeniable.
There was no greater happiness.
Yet, he offered more...
...and I delighted in it.
The gifts of love and bliss he presented
to me were unlike anything I'd ever known.
My life became his, and his mine.
He blessed me with his world.
He rewarded me with assurance.
There is no joy ever known that can compare with my own.
Uh?!
Careful! You trying to hurt someone?
That wasn't me, so calm yourself!
Oh, for crying out loud!
You better stop!
I've got you, now!
Stop! You're gonna make me fall!
Not enough time for venenum!
That hurt.
I'm sorry!
Are you, um...
Are your organs intact?
Come back!
She looks weird, Mommy.
Don't stare, it's rude.
Now, what's this?
Wonder why someone without
any fur would be on this island.
Oh no, I lost my hat!
Get out of here, you freak.
Yeah, get out.
We don't like your kind, disfeatured.
Yes, I'm aware.
Hold on a second.
I'm leaving, okay. Let go.
Seriously, hold on.
I pulled this out of that little cat's mouth.
Yours, right?
Yes, thanks.
Are you all right?
I'm good. I gather you must be new here?
Yes.
Hope you tolerate intolerance well.
Is he one, too?
Looks like it.
Seems suspicious to me.
Heh. Come on. This way.
That'll do the trick.
Thank you. So, are you...
This island has no good food or local specialties.
But you...
You may have noticed it's not very welcoming
to those of us who lack fangs or horns.
Not great for tourism.
Yes, I already know that.
Follow me.
I'm sure you've had it with this place by now.
I'll show you to the port so you can get off this island.
No, wait!
I appreciate your help.
And I'm...
I'm sorry for all the trouble I've caused you.
It's just, I--
Well, I realize I have no right to ask anything of you,
but, um, would you...
All right, where do you want to go?
Is this the view you were hoping for?
I've seen sky islands from
higher up and farther out before,
but gazing down on one from the heart
of the city like this is brand new.
I've always wanted to do it,
just never really had the chance.
That so?
But now, I've officially made my wish a reality,
and I got to make some great memories, too.
Thank you again for today.
So many wonderful experiences,
and it's all thanks to you.
I think you're giving me too much credit.
What about them? I'm guessing they're here for you?
Today's been kinda like a fairytale, but time's up.
Mind if I make one last request, fairy godfather?
It's a small one.
I'd appreciate it if you'd forget you ever met me.
Forget I ever met you...?
Farewell!
Curious, but I suppose it's none of my business anyway.
Long time no see, Grick.
How's Anara doing?
He screwed up big time last month.
Wound up becoming Third food.
I'm so sorry to hear that.
Well, don't be. That's the life of a salvager.
From the moment we choose to treasure
hunt on the surface, we're prepared to die.
That's true.
No need to be sad! Now, on to happy news.
I think I might be able to land you work!
Yeah, it's for the military.
Come on, kid!
You could at least pretend to be excited about this.
They're not lookin' for special skills or experience.
The only quality they require
is someone who's trustworthy.
Hm...
No.
Sorry, but I gotta pass.
You'll have to ask a different loser.
Look, they're also insisting on a disfeatured,
with no horns or fur. You're perfect for this.
In fact, you're the only one they could hire, and you.
I said no.
I appreciate how you try to look out for me,
but I choose to live here of my own free will.
I understand.
You wanna keep living like an outcast.
Dead man walking and all that, right?
Why try to find something that makes you
happy when you've already decided not to be?
I get where you're comin' from, kid, believe me.
But I can't help it.
I want you to be able to live
a normal life up in these skies.
I want you to accept what I know.
The dead won't come back.
But you're not dead, you've still got a life to live!
Look, you can make a ton of cash on this thing, okay?
Why not at least get all that debt off your back?
Give yourself a chance to find the right path.
What's going on with this coffee, it tastes salty.
Oh, damn it all. Ok, Fine!
So you'll take the job, then?
Yes. You positive they'll want me?
Did you tell the military I can't
even fight, let alone kill someone?
Don't worry about that.
You're just gonna be the caretaker of a
warehouse that holds some special weaponry.
Already sounds like a bad idea.
Wonderful! I'll tell them you're coming!
Get 'em to fill you in once you're there.
Ah. Whoa, you're not kidding, this coffee is salty.
Would've been nice to know that the
warehouse was on a different island.
It's Cold.
Oh, no.
Wolves are the last thing I need.
It's been a long time since I felt being a
disfeatured may not be in my best interest.
And now the bridge is falling apart.
This is great... Stuck in the middle of nowhere!
Attack
Wait!
Pannibal, what do you think you're
doing running off on your own like that?
I've taken down a suspicious individual.
Right, like there's even anyone else here.
Hey, it's you.
I, what, wait, what are you doing here?
Me? Whoa, so many questions.
First things first. Help me.
Something's wrong.
This is nothing like what Grick said.
Just a minute.
Ahh! Ha, ha, ha!
It's been forever, Willem!
Welcome to the secret weapons warehouse!
Oh, my. Have you grown a bit taller?
Why are you here of all places...
...Nygglatho?
Why, you ask.
Why wouldn't I be here, silly?
This is my job, where I work!
Damn it. Grick set me up!
I take it you two are still good friends?
Were good friends is more like it.
Try to keep it down while we're inside.
Everyone's in bed this time of night.
"Everyone"?
Mm-hm! This warehouse is run jointly by the
Guardian Wings Military and the Orlandry Merchant Guild.
So, at least on paper, it requires
caretakers from both parties.
I represent the Orlandry.
You are the military caretaker.
Yes, that much I know.
Oh, you look so yummy in your uniform!
I feel like I'm choking...
Now, there's really no need
to rain on my parade, is there?
Everyone knows good toppings only accentuate the flavor
of a dish, which means to me you're, at the very least,
twice as appetizing as I believe I've ever seen you be.
So you're saying my life is in twice as much danger.
Oh no, oh, ye of little faith.
Have you already forgotten?
While, yes, I may be a troll and while, yes,
you may be an extremely rare feast in my eyes,
I have no plan to dig in.
Not yet.
Wow. Thanks.
Can you imagine the shame?
You're the last of your kind, after all.
I know better than to waste you on a
passing burst of craving, no matter how strong.
Of course, if you were to give me permission
to eat you, I would certainly consider it.
Do I have your permission?
Hell, no.
No? Oh, won't you please consider it some more.
I'd be fine with a non-dominant arm.
Even a finger would do for now.
Stop it. Can we get down to business, please?
So, what exactly am I supposed to do?
Not a damn thing.
Huh?
Wait, you're not planning to stay
on this island, as well, are you?
Well, obviously. How else will I do my job as caretaker?
I'm legitimate military, now, so I'm sticking around.
I only ask because the previous two caretakers
didn't bother showing up after the first day.
Really?
What do you want to do?
You don't have to stay here, you know.
I can arrange something.
Off-island accommodations, maybe?
You say that like I won't get stabbed in
the back the moment I take my eyes off you.
Wow, so mean!
What kind of monster do you take me for?
The kind that eats people.
Anyway, I'm just not one of those guys
who quits a job they've committed to.
I fully intend to stay right here.
Uh! Oh, I had a feeling I could count on you!
It'll be fun after so long to
get to take care of you again.
That makes me kinda happy.
Don't get the wrong idea, Willem.
This isn't about a man and a woman spending time together.
It's about a troll trying to fatten a
tasty-looking lamb before she devours it.
Care to share what that scary look is for?
Just to confirm.
You're not planning to eat me, correct?
No, I'm not.
Genuinely, my only desire is to take care of you.
Don't you know that trolls are bound by their
natural instinct to serve every guest with dedication?
Trust me. I swear I won't try to eat you, yet.
So, in return...
Let me use my other instinct!
Can we get back to the topic?
This building is the weapon warehouse
I'm supposed look after, is that right?
You're so mean to me.
And yes, this is the building.
But it looks nothing like a warehouse.
Where do they store all the guns and artillery in here?
Let's continue the discussion tomorrow.
It has gotten rather late.
Plus, the naughty walls have ears.
--I'm sorry! --Hey! Stop shoving me!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Oh, hi, Nygglatho.
Thanks for having us!
Yes! Please, have us!
Get back to your rooms, ladies.
'Kay, but before we do, we think it'd be
nice to properly greet the new caretaker.
Go now, or I'll eat you.
Goodnight, Miss Nygglatho.
Goodnight, girls!
Well, how about I show you to your room, then?
It kinda seems like I'm not the only one allergic to you.
Oh, you big meanie.
All, right.
If anything, this place is unexpected.
Poppa!
Hey, Pops?
Sheesh, Poppa, how long are
you planning to stay asleep for?
You think he's asleep?
Don't ask me. I've never seen a man before.
We should probably keep it down, guys.
Why do you always have to shove me around like that, gah!
Hey, caretaker. Beautiful night, isn't it?
We're here!
Shh! Nygglatho will hear you.
Shh!
So, who might you girls be?
--My name's Collon! --I'm Pannibal.
If you talk at the same time, he can't hear you!
Sorry, I'm Lakhesh.
Collon, Pannibal, Tiat, and Lakhesh.
Okay, I think I've got your names down.
Where'd you come from, mister?
What's your name?
And out of all these questions you've been asked,
which one will you choose to answer first?
I guess I might as well go with
your question to start this thing off.
Spicy meat dishes are usually my favorite,
and I can't stand reptrace cuisine.
Nygglatho and I are basically a farmer and her lost lamb.
And I lived on Island Twenty-Eight until this morning.
My name's Willem Kmetsch.
You can call me Willem.
I hope you girls like me.
I'll be living here.
Wait, you mean you're gonna stay?
Probably.
Ohh!
It's not that big of a deal.
Oh, but it is.
You have to understand, none of the caretakers
with the military have ever lived here before.
Yeah, Nygglatho did mention that.
Oh, good grief.
How could you possibly think this was a good idea?
You were clearly told to give him space, weren't you?
Um, we sort of, uh...
Curiosity got the best of us!
You should have known better. We don't
have the kind of power to resist Curiosity!
Should I let Nygglatho know?
--Have a good night! --Goodnight!
Nice to meet you, Willem. See you tomorrow!
I swear, those girls.
Sorry about that.
The little ones tend to get pretty worked up.
I don't mind at all.
I'm actually used to dealing with children.
But, what are they doing here?
Well, whatever you do, try not
to spoil them too much, okay?
We don't want it going right to
their heads, and it will, so...
I'll try.
Huh?
Oh, um. So, about Pannibal.
Sorry she attacked you.
She didn't mean anything by it.
For what it's worth, I'm not mad.
You provided hot water immediately,
so I even avoided getting a cold.
Good. Good.
One more thing.
Um...
Chtholly.
That's my name. It's Chtholly.
Mm?
It's really belated.
You know, because the time we've spent in the town
with the fairy tale thing and the cat, and never mind...
Oh, right. Gotcha.
It's a pleasure. I'm Willem.
Oh, yep.
I know.
I was told that.
Anyway. Sorry to disturb you.
Good night.
Wait, just for a minute.
There's something I'm kind of confused about.
Real quick.
My understanding is I'm a caretaker
for special military weapons.
Correct.
And we're in a warehouse,
a warehouse that's used to store those weapons?
That's right.
Then why does this look absolutely nothing like a
warehouse? Why don't I see a single weapon anywhere?
And, for the love of all things
confusing, please at least answer this...
Who are you girls?
And why are you living in a military facility.
Did you take this job without knowing we were here?
Yeah.
And you spent time with the
little ones without knowing anything?
Yeah.
Let me, take a wild guess.
You're one of those people who
just goes with the flow, aren't you?
Oh, very well.
I can clear this up.
The answer to the first set of questions lies in
the second set, and the answer to the second set,
well...
It lies in the first set!
Yeah, real clear.
Try not to over think it.
The truth is, it's us. We are the special
weapons you were sent here to care for.
What...?
Make sense?
We're all so glad you've come.
Starting tomorrow, you'll be our new caretaker!
Here you go.
Thank you, looks good! I'm so hungry!
Should be as good as it looks.
Come on! It's the night before the final battle, Pops!
Nothing interesting to say?
Huh, like what?
"Once this war ends, I'll get married
and have kids," you know, somethin' like that?
Yeah, I dunno.
Seems like asking for bad luck.
Why, because it's the kind of thing characters
always like to say right before they're killed?
When they get taken out in the beginning
it's supposed to be more dramatic.
I understand that reasoning. I really do,
but I think it's sadder when
characters you're attached to die.
Either way, though.
Must be awful to get killed off because the
creator's just an idiot. No matter their absurd reasoning.
Well, yeah.
Now, Pops, you're heading into the final
battle, which means we need to find you inspiration.
Something concrete you can hold on to in order to survive!
You know, like a reason to come back here.
Anything'll do.
You've gotta find one.
You've got to. Because if you don't, I'm afraid
I won't be able to send you off with a smile.
Butter cake.
Do what?
Yeah, your butter cakes are pretty incredible.
You should bake an extra-large one for my next birthday.
For real?
You'll fight to return alive just to eat some cake?
Why, you got a problem with that?
No, I don't. I just thought that maybe...
Fine, whatever.
I'll settle for butter cake.
In return, since you suggested it,
I'll feed you so much of that cake
you're bound to get heartburn.
Unfortunately, the young fighter would never return home.
Less than a year later his world would be gone,
and humanity would be decimated.
Next Episode: late autumn night's dream.