Solitude in white darkness.
Prayer echoing across a cramped room.
It gets worse every day.
What am I gonna do?
Oh, it's just you.
That's right!
Ithea Myse Valgulious here!
Now. Mind telling me exactly who you are?
Who am I?
What do you mean?
I want you to tell me who you are.
Spell it out for me.
My name is Chtholly Nota Seniorious.
I didn't need to worry!
You're definitely still my friend Chtholly.
Worry, about what?
I don't understand.
Why would you worry?
Look, you need to ignore all those nonsensical
visions, words, and memories of that past life.
Otherwise, they're gonna just eat away at
you until you start losing your own memories,
and I really don't want it to make you forget who you are.
So all these memories, they're true, they're real?
A girl with red hair keeps telling me that.
Do not think about her anymore!
She doesn't matter.
That girl has nothing to do with you.
She's a total stranger, and of no relation.
I want you to think about who
you are, like as much as you can.
Cling to every memory you still have now.
Don't let them be swept away by someone else's.
And no generating venenum anymore.
Jeez, what were you thinking?
But, I had to help her, I...
No "buts" allowed, Chtholly.
Yes, you were very lucky one time.
You came back!
But, who knows what might happen next time, though.
Avoid anything that might trigger a memory of a past life,
and do not generate venenum.
If you wanna stick around for as long as
possible, you need to follow these two rules!
I knew it.
My stupid disintegration never actually stopped, did it?
So, you still decided to live on, yeah?
Listen. I've got a story for ya, okay?
It's about a girl I once knew. We were really close.
Just like you, the girl's past life slowly but
surely ate away at her until her own persona vanished.
Meanwhile, the other girl who woke up
in her place felt pretty lost, herself.
She'd thought she'd died,
but here she was in a place she'd never been before,
and in a body that wasn't hers.
Lucky for her, she came across a diary that
belonged to the girl who'd completely disappeared.
She'd written in it every single day without fail.
Ithea?
She was a bubbly, nosey girl.
I think she focused on everyone else
so she wouldn't have to reveal her feelings.
Yep, that's the kind of girl Ithea Myse Valgulious was.
When it happened,
I thought perhaps killing myself was for the best.
But then, we'd both be gone.
It would mean nothing.
I realized there was only one way for me to atone.
I'd stay.
I'd have to take over being Ithea,
and I'd never, ever let anyone know I wasn't really her.
Funny, somehow I've made it all the way to
today just by saying that to myself over and over.
I see.
I'm so sorry.
She had a diary. Maybe I should start one, too.
Try asking yourself this, first.
Do you want someone to take over your life?
How does the Chtholly here,
the you right now, how does she want to live? Hm?
The me here.
The me now.
Uh.
It's getting kinda chilly out.
I'll help. I'm not as warm as Nephren,
but I'll do my best to keep you comfy.
You're just gonna have to make do.
Thank you, but y'know,
you actually seem pretty warm to me.
It makes me happy to hear that.
Chtholly.
You think you can keep this from the T.O?
Yeah.
Besides, knowing would only make him worry even more.
And I refuse to be the damsel in distress type.
That's it.
I know what I want to do.
Right now, I just want to savor the joy of being with him.
I want to revel in being normal.
See, there's that whole "look
at me, I'm in love" thing you do.
Told ya. I knew you were
definitely still good ol' Chtholly!
Oh, stop.
You're the only one.
About Ithea and the diary.
You're the only one I've told.
Then, it can be our little secret.
Are you gonna ask me?
Like, don't you wanna know my real name?
Or find out what kind of person I was before?
You're Ithea, too, though.
A bubbly, nosey girl. One who focuses on everyone
else so she doesn't have to reveal her feelings.
She's a fellow fairy, and one of my best friends.
That's all that really matters.
It is. Thank you.
That's such a relief.
Let's go!
Mm?
Oh, was that just you, Chtholly?
I'm sorry. Was I being too loud?
Your hair is still changing.
Yeah. I'm really starting to like it.
Yes, I can tell. I mean, you're owning it!
Thank you!
I'm done being all mopey.
But even when I'm sad,
even when I feel like I'm being torn apart,
even the tears that are always ready to flow,
they all prove I'm still here.
All the worry, the frustration, the sorrow, and the joy.
They're all different parts of what
make up the person standing right here,
the person alive right now.
The girl who is, without a doubt, me... Chtholly.
Yes, at least for now.
You're knitting?
It's gotten pretty cold lately.
The little ones don't have anything
warm enough to wear, so I thought I'd help.
That's nice.
So, whatcha say?
Some people think this color suits me, do you?
Okay, what's the matter?
You don't have to worry.
All right, then. If you say so.
Thank you, Ren.
How's Collon's cold?
Is she gonna be okay?
Still not over the hump yet, I'd say.
I'm gonna pick her up some medicine later.
Sounds good.
Oh, yes, this is great!
You're improving so much!
Chtholly. When you get a chance, will
you put this under Collon's pillow for me?
It's an ancient talisman to prevent
nightmares when you have a cold.
Is that okay? I'm worried about her.
Her cold has lasted so long.
Oh, right. That's fine.
Collon. Got it.
Uh.
How neat! I didn't know you had something like this.
Not me. Seniorious provided it.
Did you say Seniorious?
Yeah, I told you that dug weapons were
comprised of several different talismans, didn't I?
Uh...
The other ones prevent cuts when
the blade isn't imbued with magic,
or they raise an alarm when the wielder uses an alias.
They're kinda useless at the moment,
so I figured we might--
You put that talisman back right now!
What has gotten into you?! Do I have
to remind you that dug weapons aren't
every day little charms that we can hand out
willy-nilly for whatever we want whenever we want it.
They're ultimate weapons, ones that
should be prioritized better than this!
You're being overdramatic, and you know it.
Unless you think Collon's not a priority,
and that she doesn't need a good night's sleep.
What am I gonna do with you?
Oh, fine. Of course, I'm worried about her, too.
Just promise me you'll put it
back before you go to the surface.
I promise.
Speaking of the surface, do
you think they're okay down there?
What were their names again? Nopht and Rhantolk, right?
Yes, and there's currently no need to be troubled.
For what it's worth, the military is
rushing to finish the ship's remodeling.
Well, that's reassuring to hear.
I'm concerned about that artifact they recovered, too.
Oh, that's right.
Lapidemsibilus.
You're worried about it 'cause you
worry about me which you do too much.
He's an overprotective daddy, this one.
Uh. Shut up.
What? It's better than being
an overprotective sugar daddy!
Oh, come on. Not you, too.
You both should shut up. Neither of you are making sense.
Uh... Here we go.
Huh...
What?
You've been doing more stuff like that lately.
It gives you that traditional, girly girl charm.
I have to count the stitches, so I'd
appreciate it if you didn't distract me!
What? I was just trying to compliment you.
That was a compliment?!
You're still up, Rhan?
Wow, yes.
I wonder how long this rescue squad
is gonna take, it's been like forever.
I just got the word.
It's gonna take them even longer to get ready.
You're trying to read that again?
I am.
Figure anything out?
I haven't.
But I believe I can come up with an alternative
interpretation for this passage. Humans by the surface.
No...
By the humans, the surface...
The surface's...?
Nopht, will you kindly and immediately get off me.
It's open.
Staying up late again?
I guess, kinda.
Um, so uh.
You know all those things that you do?
Hm?
All those things that you do.
Can you teach me how to do them, too?
Like how to tune the swords, and
that weird thing you did for me.
You know, the thing you did with your hands.
Why are you looking at me like that?!
What's gotten into you?
Lately, you haven't given me much attention,
probably because you didn't have a reason to.
I thought you'd make time for me if I was
learning, and any time spent together works for me.
You can't be serious.
Although I can't fight, I'm still forcing you to take
me to the surface with you, so I would like to be useful.
None of those skills are
something you can master overnight.
You would have to put in a lot of time and effort first.
Mm.
Don't get too worked up.
I know how you feel, but I'm still
not going to make you push yourself.
Don't be silly. I wouldn't push myself.
And don't you play dumb.
You've been losing your memories, haven't you?
I didn't realize that you knew.
I could tell from watching you.
So you were watching me.
But, if we have Lapidemsibilus,
we won't have to worry about that.
Is that map of the surface?
Yep, it's the area near the ruins,
where the survey team was attacked.
Isn't this where the rescue squad is supposed to land?
That's a bit close to camp, don't you think?
Oh, but I suppose that would
make it easier to transfer the haul.
Well, aren't you
quick on the uptake?
I am your secretary, after all!
Where we're going is your home, isn't it?
Five hundred years ago.
Would you want to go back?
This island has become my home now.
Our home.
It is. Yes.
Hey. What was your city like?
Did it have really amazing food?
Were you in love there?
What's all this, why the sudden interrogation?
It's my understanding that one needs
detailed intel on their destination beforehand.
But wait!
I'm gonna go get some more tea, first.
Be right back.
Give me a break, you're just curious.
This is so good.
Rather than worry and be stagnant,
I'll keep moving forward, one step at a time.
My footsteps may fade behind me,
and the path ahead may be dark as well.
But, I won't regret the past,
or be pessimistic about the future.
I will simply live here in the moment.
Because no matter how I fight it,
the clock keeps ticking down on me.
11... 12... 13... 14...
Perfect!
Auntie Nee!
And time, it keeps on passing by.
I'm glad I finished in time.
Uh, this is for Tiat.
Me? Really?
Thank you so much! I'll love it forever!
This one is for... Lakhesh!
Wow, um, thank you very much, Chtholly!
What about Collon?
Hey, what about me, where's mine?
Collon needs to wait her turn.
Here you go, sweetie.
Oh, it's so warm!
The rest of you better hurry
and get your butts over here, too.
Chtholly's giving out presents!
All right, so what's the deal with this party?
It's a snowfall fest.
It's for snowy nights, when you can't go out.
Instead, you wine and dine all night long.
Huh.
It's a popular event these days,
but originally, it was one of our troll festivals.
Uh... I think I'll pass on the details.
But, let's say it's also a send-off
for those of you headed to the surface.
It's really not that big a deal, is it?
Um, so we have presents for the older fairies, too.
Although, I guess they aren't exactly from us.
Gosh, you look so lovely, I
could eat you up right now!
Let go! You're squeezing me too tight! I
can't breathe, and you're gonna wrinkle my dress!
Mm! I'm telling ya, that there is one high-class lady.
I tip my hat to Lady Phyra's good taste.
Why would she send us all this?
It's for the snowfall fest, apparently.
Oh, um.
"Thank you all for your help when you were here last.
I know this isn't much, but I wanted
to send some gifts for the snowfall fest.
I hope you all come to visit
me in Corna di Luce again soon!"
What is it, Ren?
There is something for you.
Cheer up.
I can't believe that little...
Gorgeous!
Look at that.
Get over there. If there's ever been a
time to compliment her, this is that time.
Yeah, but that doesn't mean I know what to say.
Say everything you want.
Ask everything you need.
Putting it off can be a bad idea,
and you know that better than anyone.
Hey, Chtholly.
Uh?
You look absolutely beautiful.
I...
I know!
This should be enough clothes.
What about books, though?
Chtholly, it's almost time to leave.
Oh, okay.
Who am I, really?
See you later.
We're off, girls.
I can't stop it.
My memories are slowly fading.
The person I am is crumbling away.
You girls better be good for Nygglatho, okay?
Be safe.
We'll prepare a "welcome back"
party for you while we wait.
Don't push yourself.
It's a promise, right?
It's a promise.
I'm...
I'm so sorry.
It's sad.
I've forgotten more than half of what I knew about them.
I can relearn the names I can't remember anymore, however,
I know the memories I've lost will never come back.
As everything I am falls apart,
can I even be called Chtholly at this point?
It's heartbreaking.
I'm hurt and just so sad.
But right now, I want to hold all these
feelings as close to my heart as I can.
Because the moment they disappear, too...
...that's the moment there will be nothing left of me.
Ren!
Heh! I never expected you to
be a part of the rescue squad!
I swear, you're just as teeny-tiny as ever!
Hey, since you're here,
that must mean the massive timere you guys
were fighting ended up being taken out, huh?
Which then means Chtholly opened the Fairy Gate.
Um.
I guess that's, uh...
You know, Chtholly and I never got along that well.
But now.
I feel like I should have tried
harder --talked to her more.
Um...
Don't "um" me.
I need to grieve for Chtholly.
So, long time no see, Nopht.
You!
Eh?
It's a ghost!
Hey, wait up!
You don't understand, I'm still alive!
Well, that's a good way to start.
Next episode: my happiness.