We've received a message for you.
You've officially been ordered to report to
the base on Island Forty-Nine at noon tomorrow.
About the surface thing?
Makes me wonder if they plan on using one
of our girls to help with the rescue effort.
Not exactly excited.
Oh, no, forgot the pepper.
Okay. Which is pepper?
Get a move on!
Need medicine here!
We've sent word to the Guardian Wings Military.
Just gotta take it easy. Help should arrive fairly soon.
Yeah, that's a lot easier said than done.
It'll be fine.
Legitimitates, or the Fourths.
Won't run into them for a while.
Here!
And why do you think that?
I think that because I know they tend
to avoid living close to their own kind.
There shouldn't be any of 'em around here now.
Huh, had no clue.
Rhan, did you know about that?
Humans unleash the beasts,
and fill the world with...
They fill it with ashen truth.
Seriously, Rhan!
Your bad habit is showing!
What does Nygglatho always tell you?
When it comes time to eat, you need to focus on food!
Eat up already! Open your mouth wider!
They really are just a couple of children, aren't they?
Willem was right on the money.
We want to send a rescue squad to the surface.
But the Plantaginesta, the Moby-class transport airship
we would use, is currently being remodeled.
It won't be ready for 15 days.
What the heck do you need to
have such a big ship for, anyway?
What?
Watch your mouth, Second-Grade Technical Officer!
I'm a First-Grade Technical Officer, you know!
I'm your superior!
Pardon me, First-Grade Technical Officer, sir!
Please excuse this country boy's lack of manners.
Forgiven. I may be a first-grade technical officer,
but I still have some compassion.
Now, let's get back on topic.
The survey team on the Saxifraga was commissioned
to excavate specific ruins of the emnetwihts.
They were rather successful and retrieved numerous
relics, so we need a big ship to bring everything back.
Understand, Second-Grade Technical Officer?
Yeah-huh.
Understood, First-Grade Technical Officer, sir!
But the longer the rescue op is delayed,
the more danger the survey team faces.
We know, that's why we sent two swords with them
in the first place. And I hope they do their jobs,
even if they must sacrifice their own lives.
Huh?
Is there anything wrong?
No, not at all. You're absolutely correct,
oh wise First-Grade Technical Officer, sir.
I can't read a disfeatured's facial expressions.
Here.
I want you to go through this.
"Ground Level K96-MAL Ruins.
The second Survey Report."
Once you read it, you'll be able to
appreciate the importance of this survey.
Hang on.
Streets with thick stone paving.
Jerry-built housing blocks...
No doubt about it, this is
Gomag City, in Imperial territory.
It's... It's my hometown.
On the next page,
you'll find a list of their findings.
You know, talismans
and the like.
Those objects are precious and informative.
They're awaiting our rescue.
"Dug weapon Lapidemsibilus"?
This is it!
This sword can...
Sir kind First-Grade Technical Officer, sir?
What is it, Second-Grade Technical Officer?
A favor. I would like to ask one.
Well, that took forever.
Sorry. It's kind of a long story.
Give me a second. I just need to finish this.
There's no need to rush.
That was delicious.
You ready?
Why did you come with me again?
I wanted to buy myself something, silly.
I also have a huge list of things from the girls.
Well, you seem to be enjoying yourself.
It isn't often you and I can take
a leisurely stroll all by ourselves.
In fact, I don't think that's ever happened.
What about when we first met?
We ran all over the place that day.
Uh?
Um, that's true, but it didn't like, you know...
It didn't have the same feel back then.
Ready to go?
Chtholly...?
Oh! Is that a cute missus I see?
A "missus"?
Newlyweds, huh? I'll give you a discount.
No, you've got this all wrong...
Yes! We are, thank you very much!
Huh?!
Are you finished shopping now, "missus"?
Yep, and thank you for all your help.
Newlyweds, huh?
So we look like a couple.
Are you really happy right here?
You're finally free to roam outside
the island practically anywhere you want,
so why come with me just to shop?
Oh, come on.
Quit playing dumb when I know you know the answer.
Mm?
You see, I don't care where we are.
I just want...
I mean, all I want is to be with you.
I honestly have no clue what you see in me.
I was ordered to send a fairy soldier to the surface.
Yeah?
I picked Nephren.
And I'll be going with her.
Right.
I don't think I can sit around and
wait for someone to return anymore.
Also, I'm interested in a sword they found on the surface.
A sword?
It's called Lapidemsibilus.
I believe it has a special ability to
keep its wielder in optimum mental condition.
Mm.
So listen. I know you're putting on a brave face.
The disintegration might worsen at any moment.
My hope is that this sword could help.
If it ever came down to it.
You're worried about me, then?
Did you really think I would not be?
I don't think there's any reason to worry.
Nothing has happened since that one time.
I even sparred for a while with Tiat
the other day, and I was fine afterward.
I feel great, so don't worry so much.
You realize you're not a leprechaun anymore?
So there's no telling what's
happening inside your body right now.
I'm begging you, please don't push yourself.
So then, when are you supposed to be leaving?
Oh, not for a while yet.
You'll look after the girls?
I'm going, too.
Huh?
I said I'm going with you.
Did I not just literally beg you not to push yourself?
Yes, you did!
But I won't sit around waiting for you to return.
I don't think I could bear it.
Absolutely not.
That excuse isn't gonna fly with me.
You are not a fairy anymore, and there's no sightseeing.
You think I'd want to go with you
just to do some sightseeing?!
Wait. No, that's not what I'm saying at all.
What I mean is, it's not a place to go for fun.
You think this is all about fun?
Now, you've made me mad!
Now, I'm going with you, no matter what!
Calm down.
You know that's not gonna happen!
Looks like it's gonna happen, after all!
Yay for permission!
Yeah, if you say so.
Hold on, are you mad at me?
Don't you realize why you got permission to go?
Let's see, isn't it because you vouched for me?
Sort of, I guess?
To be blunt, he thought you were my lover.
Your lover...?
Apparently, officers often take
lovers on trips as their secretaries.
That is what he thinks I'm doing.
Ha!
Your lover.
I'm okay with that!
Well, that's great, but I'm not.
All right.
Then we can go back to "missus."
Oh, for pity's sake.
Look, truth be told, I would rather
not be separated from you, either, okay?
Wait a second!
I'm happy, but also sad because
it wasn't a proposal, was it?
Of course not.
"I would rather not be separated from you, either."
Oh, no, I totally forgot the pepper!
It's second from the right, window side.
Pepper!
T.O.
Hey, T.O.
Is that Ithea?
You betcha.
Your beloved Ithea Myse Valgulious.
If you want anything for breakfast,
best to hit the mess hall soon.
Yeah, okay. I'm up. I'm up.
Owie.
You were being my blanket, Ren?
That's why I felt so warm. Thanks.
You're welcome.
It gets chilly this time of year,
and I didn't want you to catch a cold.
When you think about it, shouldn't
this scenario be ridiculously scandalous?
Why doesn't it seem that way, though?
That's because your mind hasn't been corrupted
by what they call "the gutter" as of yet.
Not to mention Nephren basically has pet status.
Are you okay with that?
Providing emotional support is crucial.
It's a worthwhile role.
Is that so?
Anyway, what were you researching all night?
It was a dug weapon, Lapidemsibilus.
That sword could stop Chtholly's mental disintegration.
Jeez, what now?
Nothing, just wondering if she has a real chance with you.
Does she?
Don't be ludicrous, she had a chance this entire time.
Some may hold out longer, but no man can
remain unfazed forever when a cute girl likes him.
But I still can't give in, which is why
I'm trying to keep her at arm's length.
Wow.
You tell her, I'll end you.
You slept with Nephren?!
Why does everyone have to make it a big deal?
You know Nephren is just like a daughter to me.
Why are you being so weird about it?
Spare me. You're not that much older than she is!
Yeah, well, people tend to assume I'm young,
but I'm actually over 500 years old.
True, and I imagine Nephren must have
snuggled up in there with you herself.
No need to imagine.
But I still have a hard time accepting this!
I know you can sense people sneaking up on you!
I can only sense the hostile people, though.
I don't notice the mostly harmless ones.
Then let me ask you this.
What if the person crawling in your bed was Nygglatho?
Defenestrated in two seconds flat.
That's not how it went with Nephren.
Nygglatho might not technically be hostile,
but she is what I consider a
dangerous woman, a very dangerous woman.
M'kay.
What if it were me?
Uh. I don't know, let me think.
I'd have to throw you out, obviously.
Please be more careful in the future.
You don't want the little ones
to start jumping in your bed.
At least I assume you don't.
Right. No.
I give up.
I have no idea why Chtholly isn't a leprechaun now,
or why her hair changed color.
What about you?
Will the dug weapon on the surface really come in handy?
Willem?
Oh, sorry.
It's just... Chtholly was acting...
I dunno, kinda weird this morning.
Huh?
So I said I'd throw her out, obviously.
I thought she'd be mad over why
it's okay with Ren and not her,
but she just walked away. You think she's sick again?
You know, for such a perceptive
guy, you can be unbelievably obtuse.
What's that supposed to mean?
She's not sick, she's just elated that you
put her in the same category as you put me.
And that would make her elated because why?
Because I'm the rival in
love she's most worried about.
And if you treat both of us the same, that would
mean you also see her as more than just a little girl.
Hold on. Her rival in love?
Yes.
Are you saying she believes you and I
could get together, like in a relationship?
That is the implication.
She's so young.
I suppose at that age you have the tendency to
get the wrong idea about these kinds of things.
I wouldn't say it's the "wrong idea," exactly.
You may find this rather difficult to accept,
but I actually do rate you quite highly as a man.
Honestly, I wouldn't mind being with a man like you.
After all, our races aren't too terribly different.
And because of that, I might even be able to
provide you with children of your own someday.
If I could be a part of your
happiness in five or ten years' time,
well, there is nothing I would love more.
Now, that being said, Chtholly's
happiness is a priority for me.
So, don't worry. I'm not about to
go all out for the kill just yet.
Nevertheless, she simply can't
help but consider me a genuine threat.
Oh, I hope that makes sense.
I'm gonna make a really despicable request.
What might that be?
Can I pretend that, like, I didn't hear any of that?
You're right, that is despicable.
However, it's fine. I completely understand.
--Hurry! --Yeah!
Last one there's a loser!
Wait for me!
Hey girls, be careful. Don't run!
Do not run in the halls!
What do you think's gotten into them, now?
Shooting stars.
So pretty!
Look over there!
And over there, too!
Oh, yes, spectacular.
Oh, wow. There are so many tonight.
Did you see that?
Here comes a whole bunch!
Hold it right there!
But we're gonna miss all the shooting stars!
Your hair's still wet!
You're supposed to dry it right after a bath!
Do you wanna catch a cold?
Tiat's got that down.
She's playing "big sis" to perfection.
It's hard to believe not too long ago
I was the one running after her.
In fact, she's probably imitating me.
Ah, yeah. I can totally see that.
Thank you.
Hm?
For looking out for me. You know,
taking me to the surface and all that.
Nah, I'm just doing it for my own peace of mind.
Don't worry about it.
I don't care.
Thanks, anyway.
Look!
What are you doing, Almita?!
Almita!
Make it!
Chtholly!
Chtholly?
Goodness.
Do you realize how ridiculous you sound?
It's embarrassing.
Some grown-up you are.
You okay, sweetie?
It seems like she's all right, too.
Chtholly!
What are you doing?
Not that I mind.
But let's try this again, from the top!
You're not a leprechaun right now.
You can't generate venenum like
that anymore, don't you get it?
What if things were to go wrong?
What--! What if you...
I thought I was...
I thought I was gonna lose
you, even though I was right here!
Well, you're one to talk, aren't you?
I mean, with your wreck of a body.
I'm perfectly fine.
I am a bit numb perhaps, but it
will go back to normal in no time.
You're not pretending, are you?
No faith in me at all, huh?
You're all banned from the roof!
Get everyone downstairs immediately!
All right, got it!
What's going on? What happened out here?
Nothing too bad.
I'll take her up to get a bath, now.
Think you can handle the rest with Nygglatho?
Oh, yeah.
You ready to go?
Yes, ma'am.
I'm sorry.
Tiat is the one you should apologize to.
If you'd listened to her, you
wouldn't have put yourself in danger.
Right. I know.
I'm sorry.
Cover those ears.
Ready to switch?
Yep!
Chtholly?
What's wrong?
Elq.
Next Episode: moonlit sorcery.