I feel like I must know you.
It's been a while, hasn't it?
Forgive me.
Seems it's a bit too long.
I can't quite put a name to your face anymore.
Tell me.
You wanted to fight them.
Yes, I did.
I believed that was the only way I could help people.
I fought so I could protect what was important.
The truth is, though, I was being delusional.
I never protected anything.
I let it all slip through my fingers.
What I'm doing now doesn't actually matter.
Nothing is going to change.
How many times will I have to suffer through this lesson?
All I know...
All I've ever really known is to fight.
What am I doing here?
I wish I knew.
You! Stabilize the ship, and do it now!
In case you haven't noticed, I've got my hands full!
Attention, everyone on board!
The bridge and power circuits are top priority.
Defend them at all costs.
The ship will crash otherwise.
Grit your teeth and fight, soldiers!
Yeah, that's easy for you to say!
Oh, God!
Get off! No!
Thanks! Just in time!
Stay back.
Wait. You sure you're okay?
We can fight with you!
Do what I said.
Stay back. This is what I'm here for.
Come on! There's no end to them!
That said, my sword is
performing better than it ever has.
I guess the T.O.'s skills must
be the real deal, after all.
My body's in incredible shape, too.
Historia and I can do this.
Oh, no!
Hey. You all right?
What in the world did you just do?
Save you. How's it look up there?
Nopht and Nephren? Are they still fighting, too?
I saw Nopht not very long ago.
And, yes, as far as I know she's still fighting.
Nephren, though, I haven't seen in a while.
I can only assume she must be in the
hold guarding the people trapped there.
No.
How did you get that kind of wound?
What have you been doing?
I've been... fighting.
Whether in the past, or now.
Fighting... is the only thing I've ever been good for.
The only thing I've... been good at.
Not you, too.
Even you had to go and die.
I still don't get what you meant by that line.
The "our lives are more important" thing?
And if they are, why?
Wonder how the girls are doing. Hope they're okay.
Got any idea how long I've been out?
Oh, not terribly long.
A couple of minutes at most.
That's not too bad.
You shouldn't be moving around like that.
Not with those injuries.
Does this mean you're worried about me?
I simply would prefer it if you did not commit suicide.
Or use my friend as an excuse.
Understood. I'll try not to.
You're awfully strong, aren't you?
Even unarmed, you can hold your own against timere.
Suppose so.
Were all humans like you?
Was "ridiculously strong" a common attribute?
It wasn't.
I was because... I used to be a brave.
I was special, one of the chosen warriors.
We took out enemies to save people.
Being a brave was a dream of mine.
So I trained in sword and hand-to-hand combat.
I even learned how to tune carillons.
I gained as much strength as a
person could through sheer effort.
But it wasn't enough.
Whatever "strength" I had was useless.
I couldn't save who I cared about.
Not Almaria.
Not Lillia.
Not Chtholly.
Doubtful.
Winning in battle is not the only way to save people.
Sit tight here.
Just for a little while.
Generating more venenum now would be suicidal.
And you don't like that.
Say what you will.
You were a source of salvation for Chtholly,
even if you can't see it.
Hey.
What?
I need a favor.
It'll be the last one.
No way!
Oh, please?
I think I made a promise to him.
It was a promise that he wouldn't have to fight anymore.
And I... I would take on the rest of his battles.
I would fight them for him.
No means no, and I said no!
I also need to tell him something.
I have to go.
No matter what?
No matter what.
But, you'll disappear entirely if you go back there again.
I don't mean just your memories.
Your most important feelings will go!
All of it.
All of you will be gone forever!
I don't want to let that happen.
Sounds awful. But letting things end this way?
To me, that would be worse than anything.
Chtholly...
Please say yes.
Let me go.
One last time.
Let me go back to him.
She's been hit!
Damn it!
...thing's gonna pay!
Get the bastard! Keep her safe at all costs!
I'll get this side!
I'm over here!
Get back.
What's wrong?
We gotta help her!
Damn you. Get off!
Go away! Get off!
Get off, get off, get off!
Will you go away?!
We've regained control of the main rotor.
Good work, soldier!
We've lost altitude-control
wings three through five.
Seven is done for, too.
What?! Agh, you!
You need to fix this!
Oh, fine. I will. Now! Listen to me!
We're leaving this area at top speed!
All hands, grab on to something
so you don't get thrown off!
It's our girl!
Hold tight.
Comin' to get you.
Don't...
Please stay away.
It's too late.
The Gate's opening.
I... I...
I can't hold it off...
You just hang in there, missy!
And hurry up, toad, grab her!
Ren!
Willem?
Yes! It's me!
You're okay!
I think--
I think I maybe managed to finally save someone.
Huh...
Hold on.
I'll pull you up now.
Willem...
Please, don't say it.
I generated too much venenum.
It's too late.
I'll figure something out!
The Gate will probably open soon.
If it does, this entire ship will blow.
I said I'll figure it out!
Willem, saving people is my job.
It's the job of all Leprechauns.
Ren, what are you--?
It's all right.
Don't worry.
You've already saved us plenty of times.
So please, you have to let me go.
Don't say that.
Ren, I can't let you go.
This isn't right.
I can't... Ren!
Okay, this is real bad.
It's almost funny how much I can't move now.
Hey. What are you...?
Don't be stupid!
If you can get up, then you
need to hurry and hide somewhere!
Chtholly!
What am I gonna do with him?
Please stop, Chtholly! Come back!
We'll handle the fighting, even your share.
You don't have to fight anymore, so please, don't do it!
You're free to pursue your happiness now.
So go grab it, and don't let go.
Be happy for us!
Otherwise, we'll never be able to live with ourselves!
You're wrong.
I can't find happiness.
Meaning there's really no reason for me to pursue it.
How can one pursue what they already have?
Why would I try?
Don't you understand?
I'm the happiest girl in the world.
Books burning down.
Snake swimming in the flames.
Crumbling silver moon.
Princesses fighting to the death.
Lies of the dead. Big bell ringing.
Pillar of milk pouring...
Ribbon drifting in the sky.
Chtholly. Hang in there!
I'll save her if it kills me.
Chtholly...?
We swore never to part.
With our vow, came euphoria.
We swore to be together forever.
With our vow, came peace.
My love for him was undeniable.
What she meant to me was undeniable.
There was no greater happiness.
There was no greater joy.
Yet, he offered more.
I promised to make her happy.
And I delighted in it.
And I-- I was comforted.
The gifts of love and bliss he presented
to me were unlike anything I'd ever known.
She granted me more than I ever believed possible.
But I...
My life became his, and his mine.
He blessed me with his world.
There is no joy ever known that can compare with my own.
Will... em.
Thank you so much.
You goddamn fool.
I'll never get used to it.
No matter how often it happens,
losing warriors never gets easier.
The struggle within your hearts
must have been the most difficult.
There's no battle more merciless and painful than that.
Well done on staying fighters until the very end.
I've never been so angry!
I told that girl not to fight
anymore! I said that it was our turn!
But no, of course not!
She just couldn't help her stupid self! Damn!
Whatever, the happiest girl in the world, my ass!
How could she possibly think
we'd be okay with this situation?!
She goes out in a blaze of glory,
and all's well that ends well?
There's nothing well about any of this, okay?!
Nopht, please be quiet.
One's happiness is one's own to define and to decide.
Looking down on someone else's decision or trying to
make that choice for them is nothing more than oppression.
Well, then, pardon my oppression-ness!
You know.
All things equal, if anyone can bestow happiness,
it's people like you.
People who will always stay true to
the good within their oppressive natures.
It looks like spring is coming.
Five more laps!
Hard work and spirit!
Well, they're certainly full of energy.
Yeah, you can say that again.
Apparently, the girls are working hard today.
They sure are.
Although, kinda sad their favorite
older fairies aren't here to help 'em.
They might be getting a little too worked up.
This does take me back.
Chtholly was just like that, too.
She lost her older sister figure like they did.
And she also used her sorrow and loss
as motivation to grow even more powerful.
Ah, the joys of youth.
I don't know. I don't think I could ever do that.
I'm sorry, could you maybe
pretend you didn't see this?
It's not the best example to set.
You know, as the eldest.
See what? I don't know what you're talking about.
No response at all?
My pulse tracing is sure to locate anyone,
so long as they're alive, that is.
Come on, now.
Black Agate Swordmaster.
Excuse the interruption, Great Sage.
Of course, that's it!
Oh, no, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to frighten you again.
Please forgive me!
Listen to that!
Poor thing hasn't let go of her
feelings from her past life yet.
She must have a really pure heart.
By that, do you mean simple and naive?
That is one way to look at it.
Good evening, sweetheart.
It's so nice to meet you.
So stubborn.
Ugh. Here, let me try something.
There we go.
See? She got tired and is now silent.
That's enough of that...
Welcome, little one.
Welcome to this fragile, dying world
with no redeeming qualities whatsoever.
We're happy to have you.