I'm so glad you're here!
Welcome home!
Chtholly?
I'm back home.
Jerk.
You mean there's a man here who can tune dug weapons?
No, no, no, no.
Sorry, it was not my intention to frighten you.
I know this scary face doesn't help.
However, it still seems like
you're telling me a tall tale.
I once knew a monster that could
tune dug weapons, but he's long gone.
In there, huh?
Yes, Great Sage.
According to what I've been told, he can tune dug weapons.
You've brought him this far to meet me,
so we might as well get on with it.
It's been a long time since I've met
a con man with this much originality.
Hello? Souwong?
Really good to see you.
Wow, you look different. In like a super old way.
No, that can't be Black Agate Swordmaster?
No one's called me that in a long time.
Magus of the Pole Star.
You look delighted to know that we're both doing so well.
You spent 500 years petrified on the surface?
I assumed you were dead because my
pulse tracing never got any response.
None, ever!
Well, you wouldn't. I was petrified,
so my heart wasn't beating.
Give me back the tears I shed that day!
Ah, you mean you cried for me.
No, I did not.
Don't be silly.
I would never waste my time crying over someone like you.
Sure.
So, what's your deal? Why are you still alive?
What's it been... 500 years, now?
You...
What is that?
You weren't the only one
killed during battle, you know.
I was taken out at the same time as Emissa.
However, just before I passed, I was able to place a
curse on myself, a curse that would alter my life force.
What I am now can no longer be considered human.
But that's mainly because I
can't die of injury or old age.
I see.
Don't get the wrong idea, your pity isn't necessary.
I'm actually very happy with
the way my life has turned out.
No. It's not about your story.
I'm more shocked that Emissa was killed in battle.
Look at 'em go.
Ya think that's Emissa?
Nah. It's most likely Hillgram.
Saw some gaping ridgelines on the way here.
Makes sense. Will you look at this
party? It's practically full of monsters.
You're one to talk.
Huh, Black Agate Swordmaster?
How many times do I have to tell
you to stop calling me that, Souwong?
Also, you seriously need to stop
wearing that cape. You look ridiculous.
Now, that's not fair.
I mean, he's so itty-bitty, how are we
supposed to spot him if he's not wearing it?
But it is ridiculous.
I guess that means it really does
suit the great Magus of the Pole Star.
Ah! You two are so good at getting on my nerves!
Mm?
Well then, eat this and try to relax.
It's one of Almaria's special ginger cookies.
Almaria baked something for me?!
No, for me!
No, you're both wrong. It's for...
Good grief.
What am I gonna do with you guys?
I haven't been able to reminisce,
at least not before now.
Seems this job's helping me deal with the past.
Yes, of course!
That makes perfect sense!
You are the only one who can tune carillons.
No one is more perfect for the
fairy warehouse caretaker job!
But now, I don't know if I should leave you there
to rot or give you something more fulfilling to do.
Not to interrupt your brainstorm attack,
but you don't have to worry. I'm perfectly fine.
And I swore to return soon, so I need to get back.
Get back? To where?
Are you talking about the fairy warehouse?
Yeah.
I'd love to stay and chat, but I just can't right now.
It's nice to know we're both still alive, though.
No so fast.
Before you leave, there's
someone I'd like for you to meet.
Uh?
But I should warn you, this is probably
someone you never imagined you'd see again.
You can't be serious.
You don't mean another one of our friends survived?
We will be heading for Island Two.
Ready an airship for us immediately.
No, hang on a sec. I never said I'd go!
Souwong! Wait!
Room without an exit.
Black cat that doesn't stop meowing.
Who's the unfamiliar blue-eyed girl?
That was a weird dream.
Please come back, Willem.
Please.
Oh, no.
She's gonna be so mad at me.
Fun, feels like we're entering
the temple of an evil clan.
I may have known you forever, but I
still don't get your bizarre style.
Look who's talking.
Five hundred years, and you're
still wearing a ridiculous white cape.
Don't make it sound like a disease.
It's a part of my very heart and soul!
I would never cast my cape aside, not in a thousand years!
Thank you.
Where did that come from?
Why would you thank me?
Just felt like saying thank you.
Don't worry about it.
No, no, wait. Why not?
What are you grinning for? Don't be weird.
Out on a walk, are we?
Well, it is a pleasant day.
I'm meeting her?
Not her. Look lower.
Greetings, you oversized piece
of trash, I've come to see you!
Uh! If it isn't the great Sage.
Wonderful timing. I was getting unbelievably bored.
Mm...
I've brought an old acquaintance I'd
like you to meet. All right, Eboncandle?
Ah! Yes, of course, I recognize you!
Yes, but where do I know you?
Oh! We fought...
Tell me, Souwong, please tell me this
isn't real and it's all just a bad dream.
If you want, I don't mind slapping
you so you can make sure you're awake.
I think I'll pass.
It's been eons, has it not, human brave?
I never imagined the day would
come when our paths would cross again.
Although I wish very much that it were not so,
sadly, we are fated to always cross swords, too.
Warriors like us are not given such luxuries, uh.
Look, you can give all that warrior crap a rest.
Really? How dreadfully boring.
Not to be rude, but why the hell do you look like that?
The Eboncandle I fought in the past had skin,
flesh, and you know, an actual body from the neck down.
You ask as if you weren't the one
who burned my remains to a crisp!
Can you imagine my shock when I awoke in this state?
This is your fault!
Although, it is not your fault that I
have had to consistently use much of my power.
I've not had the strength to heal myself completely.
I get it.
The "paradise" or islands in the sky,
they were built by the two of you.
That is correct.
In order to escape the seventeen beasts, I used
brute force to elevate surface land into the sky.
Somehow, it's managed to last 500 years.
Eight-tenths of it is thanks to my powers.
At this point, you have to know
what the seventeen beasts are, right?
What the hell happened to make them appear?
Where did they come from?
Hm... The beasts are the true sin of humanity.
To begin with, they're ancient--
Do you remember True World, by chance?
Uh. Now that you mention it, yeah, I think I do.
Are you talking about that really old,
militant cult we were ordered to take out?
Yes. The beasts are biological weapons
that were born as a result of
True World's failed research.
Makes sense.
That's why emnetwihts are
blamed for destroying the surface.
It's because of them.
Correct.
And they're not wrong. Humans did destroy the surface.
But wouldn't you like to take the surface back now?
You may be one of the most annoying
guys I ever met. Rotten to the core,
I'm talking personality, heart, and soul-all of it--.
But you also have the best and most reliable skills.
Which means you're more than
worthy to be a part of our plan.
In fact, you're a crucial factor at this point.
Indeed.
I thought the surface was overrun.
Isn't it a danger zone with beasts everywhere?
What are you planning?
We will attack them ourselves.
What?
Now that you're here, we also have the ability to
use carillons that couldn't be tuned or wielded before,
giving us more power than we'd expected.
This is significant progress for us.
The battle will more than likely require
all resources from every Règles Aile city.
It will be a long road. Dangerous.
However, we stand a good chance
of coming out on top this time.
We can procure as many fairies as we need.
The only problem previously was
the shortage of usable carillons.
What?
I--! Uh. Nothing. Uh, nothing at all.
Said too much again.
We are the special weapons
you were sent here to care for.
It's you.
You're the ones who've been producing the girls.
Attention operatives: move on the double!
Unknown beast detected.
Island Fifteen will hereby be abandoned.
Strategic HQ is to fall back to Island Sixteen.
Hardcover picture book.
Black and white zigzag.
Swaying boat.
Damaged cocoon.
Red water. Ashen wind.
Seven-eyed frog.
Endless orange road.
Fabric with a silver glint.
Stop it, stop!
Who are you?! Shut up! Shut up! Get out of my head!
Chtholly...
I promised.
I will go back.
I promised!
I promised. I promised him!
These weapons use the enemy's own force
against them as soon as contact is made.
Lion eating a snake.
Round rainbow.
Pile of gold coins.
Tiny bowl filled with sweets.
Burning signpost.
Fish flying between the stars.
Just shut up!
It doesn't matter what you say!
I'm going back!
I... I have to go back, to go...
Go back... to him.
Go back to him.
Those fairies are borderline unstable ghosts,
they're souls of children.
Souls who aren't aware they're
dead when they wander into our world,
still trapped in the immaturity of their former youth.
Remember, they're not really life forms.
And one of my necromancy skills allows me to
produce fairies from wandering spirits like theirs.
Since they do not fear death,
they make ideal, mass-produced weapons
that can cause venenum explosions.
Their life-spans are very short.
And their spirits are so fragile that if
they generate too much venenum during combat,
memories of their past lives can come
back, causing mental disintegration.
But we're trying to protect the world here,
these are simply sacrifices
that can and must be overlooked.
How are you girls feeling?
You three slept in pretty late today.
We did, yeah.
Can you blame us? That battle was rough.
I think I'm dead.
We'd like to take it easy for a while, if that's okay.
Right, Chtholly?
Chtholly?
Well, that's fine with me.
No need to push if you're still so worn out.
On that note, you should excuse
us from chores for the time being.
Not happening.
Sorry. I think I need to go get some more sleep.
Flat spider.
Used-up candles and burned envelopes.
Please stop...
--Half-eaten cookie. --Please.
Metal bird and rainbow-colored arrowhead.
Vivid mine.
Stomach with a thorn.
Please, shut up.
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Shut up! Shut up!
We made a promise...
What if I, what if I'm the one who breaks it?
Aw. I was really looking forward
to eating all that butter cake.
Threads made of morning dew.
Breaking world. Father.
Yellow plushie.
Shining skylark nest.
Pebble in a paper packet. Carnival in water.
Black cat that doesn't stop meowing.
Dazzling gray sky. Kiss of a golden butterfly.
But who are you?
Who are?
Who am?
Who am... Who?
I don't know who I am.
The fairies are our only way to make use of the
carillons, and this is a fact even you cannot deny.
Yes, I realize they're needed for basic defense.
But their lives shouldn't be thrown
away to satisfy imperialistic urges!
What would you have me do?! The world
as we know it heads steadily toward ruin.
Règles Aile's existence is already
on borrowed time and borrowed power.
We have no choice, we must find
a way to return to the surface.
Must we? Are you sure there's not a better way?
All those people living out there, now,
they consider Règles Aile their home!
Not the damn surface!
You know that!
What about you, do you consider these islands your home?
Don't pretend like you don't want to go back!
Souwong, let's say we do take the surface,
who are we gonna find there?
Will there be any of our family
or our friends to welcome us home?
Mm.
Great Sage, I would give this fight up for the
moment, if I were you. That is one resolute man.
Once he makes a decision to protect something, he will
protect it, even if that means sacrificing his own life.
You mean to tell me you care more about
fairies who will soon die than this world's future?
I do.
Now I need to go.
I promised to get back to them quickly.
Then, Willem Kmetsch, I take it this
is your decision on the matter today.
Yes, it is.
I always thought you took the hero part
of heroic brave a little too seriously.
So did I.
I've come with an urgent report.
It's about the wielder of the dug weapon Seniorious.
Memories of her past are returning.
Her mind has begun to disintegrate.
And just like that, he is gone.
Why did you not tell him the truth about the beasts?
I used to look up to him
like he was an older brother.
So if there's any way I can help it, I'd rather
not make him hate me more than he already does now.
No, it's mine!
Nuh uh, because I took it first!
Hey, do you guys know where Nygglatho is?
She went up in the mountains!
Whenever someone doesn't come back, she goes up
into to the mountains to fight bears for a while.
Oh, right.
Then I guess we'll be having
stewed bear for dinner tonight, huh?
Hey, what's wrong with you, Tiat?
You seem gloomy.
Uh, I dunno.
It feels like there's a big hole in my head.
Why? Because Chtholly broke?
Maybe, yeah.
You should know she kept her promise.
She wasn't supposed to return from battle,
but because of you she somehow made it home.
And she did everything she could to make
sure she had a little bit of time left.
Yeah.
I knew she'd keep her promise,
even though I wouldn't say or do what she wanted.
I did nothing for her.
Chtholly!
Are you looking for something?
Uh-huh. Jade-ebo!
"Jade-ebo"? I see.
Hey, who are you?
My name is Elq!
Elq, huh?
I can help you find Jade-ebo, if you want.
I don't mind looking with you.
I mean, this place seems huge.
Who, me?
Oh, yes, my name is... huh.
I think I forgot. Who am I?
Huh?
I don't know,
but I remember there's something important.
Oh, yeah. I remember I have to go back.
No matter what?
No matter what.
Even though it's only gonna bring you bunches of pain?
Yes, even then, because I have a promise I have to keep.
Okay.
It's rare to see you drinking anything other than tea.
I'm glad you're here, Willem.
I'm so tired of being forced to cry all alone.
In the past,
I wanted to fix things that couldn't be fixed,
like unhappiness or the tragedies people went through.
But I was always too powerless.
In the end, I couldn't do anything.
I started to wonder why I even tried.
Still do.
You'd think I would've learned my lesson.
But I wanted to make Chtholly happy.
I'll never understand it.
What did she ever see in me?
How do you not know the answer to that?
Just think about it.
You gave me so many of my firsts.
At that market, you became the first stranger to help me.
You were the first to take me somewhere with a great view.
The first to inspire all these different emotions in me.
You're the first person who let me lean on them,
and the first opponent I lost to.
There're so many, I can't keep count.
Which is why, well, it seems pretty obvious that
you'd be the first person I ever fell in love with.
Take the hint already, you dummy.
What happened to me, anyway?
I remember getting to the
warehouse and having a weird dream.
And then I was mad that you wouldn't come back.
Why are you looking at me like that?
Welcome home, Chtholly.
Welcome home.
It's a miracle of love.
I don't know about it being love or not, but, yeah,
I'd say this is definitely a miracle.
Knowing Chtholly, though, she
probably ignored the consequences
and paid a huge price to make whatever this is happen.
Next Episode: home, sweet home.