New count.
217!
Yeah, I think Chtholly's got this.
The rest of us can just go home.
The next one might sprout from inside.
Stay focused, Ithea.
What is that thing?!
I've never seen it before!
Do you see that?
It isn't a timere.
Maybe it's a new beast.
I've never seen anything like it before.
All hands, retreat.
We've detected the appearance of a new, unexpected beast.
As such, I'm declaring this operation a failure.
Island Fifteen is to be abandoned.
All hands, retreat.
We can't!
Oh no, you don't! Have you completely lost it?
I promised to stay alive.
I promised to make it home!
I was supposed to celebrate, too, and
eat all the butter cake I could handle.
How I can I do that if I let this world end!
Chtholly!
Trees vanishing in morning mist.
Milk stains. Dazzling petals.
Air mass.
Herring on a wall.
Hedgehog standing on its head.
Organ in a bag.
What is this?
What could we do?
Whatever that new enemy was, it
sent the whole battlefield into chaos.
It was ridiculously strong and we
had absolutely no idea how to fight it.
We had no choice, you know?
The island had to be abandoned.
That sounds awful.
It was awful!
Which is why we're all totally exhausted.
Well, I'm proud of you for hanging in there.
Success would have cost more
lives than the island was worth.
A strategic defeat.
Mm-hm!
But as for your work. The blades you forged shone
brilliantly, so you are due our praise and thanks.
Yep, that's right. This lizard is seriously dead on!
Oh, and I wish you could've been there to
see Chtholly fight, T.O... It was unbelievable.
The loss was all my fault, though.
I failed.
I should've just blown myself
up and neutralized the enemy.
But instead, I decided to be selfish.
You're wrong.
It wasn't you. The tactical projections
failed to account for the other beast.
If you'd self-destructed to take it out,
we would've been forced to try and
eliminate the new one without your help.
That would have yielded a far worse
outcome than a strategic failure.
Yep. I can't agree more.
It was no one's fault, we never
had a chance to defeat them.
So stop. You don't have to blame yourself.
Thank you, Ren.
By the way...
What are you two doing?
Willem will feel quite a bit better if we warm him up.
I'm actually pretty warm already.
Please get off me.
You're just saying that to be nice. Not yet.
Come on!
A little help over here would be appreciated, Chtholly.
I bet it would.
Uncle!
Uh, you're her uncle?
Uncle?
Of course not, she's the daughter
of an old friend of mine. Now then.
How many times have I told you not to come here, Phyra?
I am fully prepared to face the consequences, Uncle.
I sincerely apologize, but there
is no one for me to turn to but you.
Someone has threatened to kill Father if
we refuse to cancel next weekend's ceremony.
Really?
It's because of his policy as the mayor.
He's trying to ensure peaceful
racial coexistence within the city.
We're well aware that many do
not look favorably upon that,
but I'm appalled they would resort
to murder to impede his stance.
Listen. I won't be able to help you.
Forgive me, Phyra.
But why not?
I have a favor to ask you, Willem.
I won't.
I have yet to tell you what it is, though.
Yeah, I can guess what it is.
Let me apologize, now, because I'm not about to play hero.
Besides that,
I'm up to my neck in babysitting.
Huh?
Uncle, due to its sensitive nature, I
would prefer to keep this between us.
No need to worry.
Now, I can't vouch for his dependability
or trustworthiness, officially,
but he's earned the benefit of the doubt.
Right.
We gotta go. It's time to pick up Tiat.
Good luck, though. I hope you find someone to help.
Truly.
Will you at least listen?!
At next weekend's ceremony, my
father plans to unveil a new policy.
It should open the door for those of all races.
However, the Annihilation Knights oppose the idea
because they oppose tolerating anything disfeatured,
so they're plotting to assassinate him.
I have a feeling they're seriously
gonna regret that name in five years.
They destroy property,
kidnap children, and assault people.
Their intent is to rid the city of all disfeatured
races, and they'll seemingly stop at nothing to do so.
Uh...
That's why I felt I had to request assistance.
Still no.
The Guardian Wings Military's singular role is to
defend Règles Aile from any and all external threats.
It is not allowed to interfere
in political affairs of cities.
Archipelago Military Charter, Chapter Four, Article Three.
This is cruel!
We're clearly in the right, how can you simply do nothing?
Being right doesn't make the use of force appropriate.
In fact, righteousness is merely a tool
used for legitimizing one's own violence.
Don't you understand,
the other side feels the same way.
They believe they're justified
just as much as you believe you are.
We can't all be right, can we?
That's how wars start.
But I--
Officer Limeskin turned you down because of this,
and it's why I won't help, either.
Nope! It wasn't even a little
scary, and it didn't hurt!
I laugh in the face of injections, ha, ha.
I'm so proud of you, Tiat.
We all are.
Thank you, Chtholly!
You're not a child, though?
No, I'm not a child!
Sure you're not.
Quick question, T.O.
Don't you think you were awfully cold to the lovely lady?
Let me guess, it's because of her age, isn't it?
Like maybe girls older than me
might as well not be girls, am I right?
No, it's not like that at all.
It doesn't matter whom I'm dealing with.
I just don't want to accept anything,
you know, if I can't accept it.
Huh?
Wanna try that again?
Sorry, it sounded better in my head.
And what's goin' on over here with
you smiling, what's that about, huh?
Oh, nothing.
I will never understand you two.
I swear!
Uh.
Something smells really good!
Look, they're wrapping meat in
leaves over there, and it looks yummy!
It's wrapped ram.
I am pretty hungry, now that I think about it.
We can grab lunch here, if everyone wants to.
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
They're obviously using far too much spice, and
they do not have their permit clearly on display,
as is the legal requirement.
I have little doubt they'll feed
you meat that is barely edible.
If you ask me, it's not worth the risk.
What's worse, their prices are higher than normal!
That's worse?
Come this way.
I'll show you genuine Corna di Luce
wrapped ram that won't make you ill.
That's weird. Did she morph into someone else?
Maybe.
So good!
I can't stop wolfing it down!
Let me see, if I had to guess, I'd say they
used less spice and incorporated some herbs
to give this wrap a little more balance.
Either way, the flavor makes it
easy to eat a whole bunch of it.
I know, it's so, good!
What's wrong?
You haven't taken a single bite.
Just thinking.
Well, don't force yourself.
I'm sure the girls will take any leftovers.
We sure will!
You may not know this, but
wrapped ram is a tradition here.
And this restaurant makes the
best wraps in the entire city!
Of course, all the locals know about this place.
Even a five-year-old would tell you that.
Wow, the local five-year-olds are intense.
To top it off, where we are is so legendary,
countless movies have been filmed right here!
Oh! Like the scene in Clockwork Love and
Dreams, where the golem accidentally gets drunk!
That's right!
You know, I think I've also
seen it before in Let Me Trick You,
and The Return of Detective Curio , and Howl, Lazioni !
My, how delightful. I am very impressed!
As for us, our ten-year-old's intense.
My beautiful Corna di Luce.
It's been the setting for many, many stories.
No surprise, though.
The rich cuisine, featuring classics like wrapped ram,
and the artistry, history and luminaries are
all well known to those across Règles Aile now.
I'm just so proud of it!
Wow, I can tell you really love this city,
like a whole lot, don't you?
Yes. Corna di Luce
is my home, after all.
I suppose it's my favorite city ever!
Ha, ha! I like that because I love it, too!
Favorite ever, huh.
I'm impressed you can say that with a straight face.
And what does that mean?
Nothing. I like your style, that's all.
I just wasn't sure we'd ever get you to lighten up.
Don't mock me.
I hate it when people always speak casually.
I gathered as much.
Whaddaya think. Somethin' weird in her past, right?
Maybe?
This is Perjurer's Grave.
A legendary con man from around
200 years ago rests in this location.
I've seen this in movies, too!
Of course you have.
The stone says, "Here lies an honest man."
I know this is gonna be a bit off topic,
but how did we end up on a sightseeing tour?
Is there a problem?
We have time until the airship's ready to take us home.
It's just kinda weird to take weapons sightseeing.
I mean, talk about special treatment!
If you ask me, we better thank the lizard and the lady.
Locked red grimoire.
Sweet cry of death.
Headless clown, wandering in twilight.
He laughs, laughs, laughs, laughs, laughs, laughs.
Chtholly?
Wh-What is it?
Are you sure you're feeling all right?
You've been so quiet today,
it's like having a statue among us.
As far as quiet goes, statues are the quietest.
If you're too tired, please tell me you're too tired.
I don't want to push you and make it worse.
Right.
It isn't like that, though.
Didn't mean to worry you.
I'm sorry.
If the venenum your body generated during
combat is still lingering somewhere inside you,
do want me to do the deal again?
No, thanks!
And will you please stop doing
that, you're freaking me out!
What's the deal?
None of your business, so back off!
Next up, we have the Lovers' Staircase.
This is where a legendary couple
whose love transcended social status met.
I've seen this in so many movies!
Yes, of course she has.
The two accidentally bumped into each other at the top.
They rolled down the stairs together,
marking the start of their romance, but now...
There's a "no rolling" rule?
You mean we can't roll down the stairs?!
Hey.
All right, it's time to set the bait.
Well, what do you think?
Do you like the city so far?
Yes, I'm enjoying my time here.
I already loved it, but now I like love, love, love it!
That's wonderful.
Hey, is there a fun spot we can head
to that's a bit more isolated than this?
I know just the place.
Welcome to the Well of Wishes.
Oh! I've never ever seen this before!
The Well of Wishes?
Hold on, is this one of those throw your coin
in, and get your wish granted kind of places?
That sounds like it came straight out of a fairy tale!
Forgive us for interrupting your fun,
but your tour has come to an end.
We're surrounded.
What are you doing? Who are you people?
Oh, come on, you can't tell me you don't
know the Annihilation Knights when they appear!
Annihilate! Destroy!
Annihilate! Destroy...
So it is you!
Really...?
Apparently.
We have come here for all that is right and for
the greater good, we must assassinate the mayor,
assassinate the mayor for all that
is right and for the greater good!
As an insurance policy, we will take you into
custody, take you into custody as an insurance policy!
He talks weird.
All that effort for such an awful show.
You disgust me, there are children present!
Ha, ha! Those filthy disfeatured
cannot understand our righteousness,
our righteousness. Those filthy
disfeatured cannot understand!
Now, hear me!
For the sake of all I know and believe right,
I shall not give in to the likes of you!
Take her.
Not yet.
Bang!
Ow!
Bang.
Bang!
What just happened here?!
First of all, I've known you've been following us.
So we kept to rather public places.
When we moved to a desolate one, you
saw your chance, but you never had one.
Please don't tell me.
Did you use me to lure them in?
Yes. You were what's called bait.
To be clear, I could not care less
about either your politics or justice.
I'm only taking your side for personal reasons.
You've been extremely kind to us,
and it helps that the little ones seem to love this city.
Uh! Whoa.
Who would've known our precious
T.O. could be one scary man.
A con man.
This is how he actually is.
Know your place, disfeatured,
disfeatured, know your place.
Bang!
Try to hide that bloodlust.
You're pros?
Damn! Move it, boys!
Boys, move it right now!
Cease and desist.
--Arrest. Arrest. --Cease and desist.
Arrest. Arrest...
Cease and desist.
Willem kind of seems like a bad guy.
Well, he does happen to be the sole
survivor of the terrifying emnetwiht race, so...
Con man.
I may be extremely grateful for your help,
but I, I simply cannot accept your methods!
All right. I figured as much, though.
Also, I've been trying not to bring this up again,
but upon our initial meeting, you touched my belly.
Huh...?
Don't play dumb with me!
To us lycanthropos, our bellies are sacred
places that we may only reveal to our spouses.
Ah, okay?
I hate you with every ounce of my being!
Thank you so much, girls.
I hope you come back to visit us again someday!
It is a beautiful city.
I can see why the lady wanted to
protect her home with such, uh... passion.
Yes.
But she hates me, and it seems she hates me a lot.
I imagine she'd probably rather
not ask me for any help again.
It's for the best, though.
She's genuine,
and people like that should be able to stay that way.
You're ridiculous.
Excuse me?
The finger guns were nothing more than camouflage.
Sure, you attacked them, but you did it by throwing coins.
Good eye, Chtholly.
It's not a good eye.
I just most likely know your fighting style and strength
better than anyone else in this world, or any other.
Did you forget?
I could see it because you taught me to
fight in the exact same way. I paid attention.
Yes, you certainly did.
I think you were such a good
student you may have made me forget.
Temporarily.
Tell me, you wanted a fight.
I don't know what you're trying to do,
but I wish you'd stop.
You don't have to fight anymore.
You're no longer alone.
We've taken on all of your battles, so you're free.
I'm extraordinarily grateful.
For years, I've waited for death to release me.
While I've waited, all I wanted was to go back home,
to go back to the people that waited for me.
But after meeting you all, it seems
well, I've changed a little.
I started to feel happy. I wanted a home again.
Meeting you has brought me a slice of salvation,
and when you returned alive, that brought me...
Well, it's like a joy I'd been missing.
Hang on, don't try to back away from me like that!
Come on, don't look at me as if I'm
embarrassing you! I'm tryin' to be nice here!
Okay, whatever.
I was surprised you noticed, and I'm done.
How could I not?
I'm in love with you.
Finally! We get to go home!
Aw, I wanted to check out a couple more places.
Remember, you're a fairy soldier now.
So, I'm positive you'll get the chance to come back.
True! You're so right!
You are Technical Officer Willem Kahmesh, is that correct?
Yes, and who might you be?
First-Grade Officer Burohnny Maxi.
I'm military police.
Interesting.
I see Officer Limeskin's report was quite accurate.
"A tall, black-haired disfeatured.
Likely has a thing for young girls."
Nah, if he actually did, someone I know
wouldn't always have such a tragic expression.
Am I right, Chtholly?
There is an individual I'd very much like for you to meet.
Come with me.
No, thank you. I have plans already.
It's Souwong Kahndel.
Willem?
I'm sorry.
I can't walk away after hearing that name.
Burohnny, was it?
Yes.
I need to ask a favor, take care of these girls.
I can most definitely do that.
Wait a second! I won't let you stay here!
We make you happy.
Come back home!
I can't go, not just yet.
If you stay, I'll get really angry!
Chtholly...
I won't let you stay!
You jerk. You're a big jerk!
I'm so sorry.
Come back.
I'll be waiting, so you'd better come home, okay?
Yeah. I will come home.
I swear that I will.
Good.
It's a promise.
I never welcomed them back from battle.
I probably shouldn't say this,
but you make the most peculiar
face when you cry, Officer Kmetsch.
Next Episode: no news was good news.