[NARRATOR] In the year 845,
[NARRATOR] two terrifying
new breeds of Titan appeared:
[NARRATOR] the
Colossal and the Armored,
[NARRATOR] barreling through
the outer walls as if
[NARRATOR] wholesale
destruction was child's play.
[NARRATOR] The
territory couched within
[NARRATOR] the circle of
Wall Maria was abandoned.
[NARRATOR] Twenty percent
of the human race perished.
[NARRATOR] As the
Titan onslaught advanced,
[NARRATOR] our only choice was
to withdrawal behind Wall Rose.
[NARRATOR] In the year 850, the
Colossal Titan again appeared
[NARRATOR] and decimated
yet another barrier
[NARRATOR] between us and them.
[NARRATOR] Once more,
mankind retreated in panic
[NARRATOR] before the
advance of its greatest foe.
[NARRATOR] Brave soul
after brave soul perished.
[NARRATOR] Eaten alive.
Eren! No!
[NARRATOR] Cadet Eren
Jaeger, tragically consumed
[NARRATOR] early
on in the battle...
[NARRATOR] later
emerged miraculously
[NARRATOR] from the
fallen body of an Abnormal.
Attention!
[NARRATOR] Dot Pyxis,
unconventional commander
[NARRATOR] of the entire
Southern Territory,
[NARRATOR] witnessed firsthand
Eren's Titan form in action.
[NARRATOR] Taking note of
the boy's incredible strength,
[NARRATOR] a plan
worthy of the commander's
[NARRATOR] fabled
eccentricity was hatched.
[PYXIS] Recall
the massive boulder
[PYXIS] roughly a
league from the gate.
[PYXIS] Having assumed
Titan form, Cadet Jaeger
[PYXIS] will hoist said
boulder on his back,
[PYXIS] schlep it
to the hole, and voila!
[PYXIS] Should we succeed,
history will be made!
[PYXIS] Today is the day!
[PYXIS] Trost regain
shall stand as a reclamation
[PYXIS] of pride
and hope beyond measure!
[PYXIS] A leap greater
than we have ever taken!
[roaring]
[NARRATOR] And yet, despite
Eren's ironclad resolve,
[NARRATOR] the plan teetered
on the brink of collapse
[NARRATOR] even as it began.
[GUSTAV] We've managed to
corral most of the Titans
[GUSTAV] in the corner
furthest from the breach.
[GUSTAV] Combat has been
avoided as much as possible.
[GUSTAV] But still,
20% of our forces are lost.
[PYXIS] Not lost.
[PYXIS] They did not
die of losing their way.
[PYXIS] They were sent
to their deaths. By me.
[PYXIS] This is the threshold
of our extinction, soldiers.
[PYXIS] If my actions
ensure mankind's survival,
[PYXIS] history may call
me "butcher" all it wants.
Ackerman, look out!
Hey! Ackerman!
Stand down! Now!
Get away from him.
That's an order!
Eren! I know you're
in there somewhere.
I know you recognize me!
[MIKASA] That's
right! Come on!
[MIKASA] Snap
the hell out of it!
[MIKASA] We've got
a breach to seal up!
[RICO] We've failed.
It was foolish to pin our hopes
on something we
didn't fully understand.
[gun shot]
[MIKASA] Eren! Listen
to me! You're human!
Get out of there!
[MITABI] What the hell?
You tellin' me the kid was
a regular Titan all along?
Eren!
[ELITE E] Captain!
[ELITE E] We've got two
Titans bearing down on us
[ELITE E] from the front;
a 10-meter and a 6-meter!
[ELITE F] Heads up!
There's a 12-meter
[ELITE F] closing in
on us from the rear!
Ian, that's it.
Please. Just look at him.
We need to get out of
here; the plan's a bust.
Agreed. Full withdrawal.
We have to leave him as he is.
[ELITE A] Red smoke.
That's not good.
Sir, at best
I'm afraid it means
the elite squad
hit quite a snag.
[ELITE B] This was pointless.
[ELITE B] My friends
died like animals.
[SOLDIER 1] No!
Look! Over there!
[SOLDIER 2] What?
What's happening?
[MARCO] It's over.
They failed.
But, how?
[MARCO] Whoa! Armin!
Where are you going?
[ELITE A] Commander.
I recommend we revert
back to defending the gate.
Just give the word, sir.
[PYXIS] Denied.
Sir, shall I order a retreat?
[PYXIS] Absolutely not.
Continue luring the
enemy to the edge of town.
The Elite Squad is well-helmed;
they have leave to
make their own decisions.
[PYXIS] We proceed as planned.
[PYXIS] This was an
all-or-nothing proposition.
[PYXIS] I will allow those
at the vanguard to determine
[PYXIS] if and when we deviate.
[PYXIS] We are not in a position
to deliver a verdict of defeat.
But, we are in a position
to fight to the last breath.
It's humanity's debt.
It's what we owe the fallen.
[MITABI] Ian! Snap out of it!
What are you waiting for?
[MITABI] Give the order!
Hey, it's not like
this is your fault!
Come on! Look, this plan
was doomed from the start!
[MITABI] We all get that.
Was it worth a shot?
[MITABI] Sure, whatever!
[MITABI] We did the
best with what we had!
[MITABI] But all
we've got left now
[MITABI] is going
back over the wall.
[IAN] Stop!
Easy. Now's not the time.
[IAN] Team Rico,
take out the 12-meter
[IAN] approaching from behind.
[IAN] Team Mitabi and I will
handle the two front-runners.
Are you nuts?
[IAN] In case you've forgotten,
I'm the one in charge!
Now do as you're
ordered, soldier!
We are not leaving
Jaeger defenseless, period.
[IAN] Change of plans.
Our job now is to keep
[IAN] the others off him
until he can be recovered.
Whether we like it or not,
he's still our last best chance.
[IAN] We're not
about to abandon him.
[IAN] We're
expendable; he isn't.
[IAN] He can't just be replaced.
Please! Don't talk to me
about our last best chance!
He's a failure countless
soldiers have died because of!
Just look at him,
Ian! Are you saying
you want more of
us to die saving that?
That's right.
Down to the last man!
If that's what
it takes, so be it!
What the hell's
up with the red smoke.
What happened to him?
I don't know, but
Armin's gone to see.
But I-- I think
it'll be alright.
Yeah?
Of course! I mean...
[MARCO] this is Eren
we're talkin' about.
Right.
I don't wanna be that guy,
but this whole thing
feels kind of pointless.
Hell, when's the last time
a fight against the Titans
didn't feel like that,
huh? The best thing now?
Do what we can
from losing any more.
[CONNY] I don't like
the idea of so many of us
[CONNY] being dead for nothing.
[JEAN] We have
to pick our battles.
[JEAN] If we want to
wage all-out war someday,
[JEAN] we have to conserve
all the manpower we can.
[JEAN] This was the right call.
Just be patient.
[CONNY] Was it the
right call, though?
Yes! Of course it was!
[CONNY] Live to fight
another day, is that it?
Right. I'm in.
[RICO] Ian, you
can't be serious!
[IAN] What other hope
against the Titans do we have?
[IAN] You know
something I don't?
This is it.
This is all we've got,
and you damn-well know it!
I am making a
judgment call here.
If you have a
better plan, speak up!
[IAN] How else are we
ever going to get out from
[IAN] under their feet?
I'm all ears here!
If you're asking me how
else we'll defeat the Titans,
obviously I have no idea.
See? That's why we can't
afford to beat a retreat.
Not just yet.
[IAN] We may not know
what else is in there,
[IAN] but there's hope.
And as long as that's the case.
We're gonna fight
to the bitter end.
[IAN] Look at us.
Always scraping by.
[IAN] Always on the run.
[IAN] Don't you-- Don't
you want it to be over?
[IAN] Don't you
want to make a stand?
[IAN] Well, this
is how it's done!
This is just-- This is madness.
Hey!
[RICO] I think you're right.
[RICO] If we're to stand,
this is the only way.
Just this once.
Let's fight a fight that's
not just a battle of attrition.
Let the bastards
taste humanity's wrath.
Right. My team will
address the 12-meter Titan
[RICO] coming from the rear.
[MITABI] Well? We got the
two in front or don't we?
Right.
Thank you, Captain.
That was brave.
No, it wasn't.
There's no thanks needed.
Fact of the matter
is I was petrified of
the mess you were
about to get into.
But you're free
now. So do your thing.
Make good use of
that inborn skill.
Sir.
[IAN] Go save the man you love.
It's not like that.
[MIKASA] What? Why haven't his
injuries repaired themselves?
[MIKASA] Did the earlier
damage compromise him?
[MIKASA] Oh, Eren. What
is this doing to you?
[MIKASA] Oh god, what if you
won't be able to change back?
[MIKASA] No, I've got to stop.
[MIKASA] I'm thinking about
it too much, that's all.
[MIKASA] I need
to focus on doing.
[ARMIN] Eren. Misaka.
What's going on?
[EREN] What's-- Where am I?
[EREN] What am--
What am I doing?
[EREN] Am I sitting?
[EREN] I can't see.
[EREN] What day is it?
[EREN] Wait.
[EREN] Oh. That's
right, of course.
[EREN] Weird.
[ARMIN] Eren.
Come on, what are
you doing? Wake up!
[ELITE C] Here's the plan:
[ELITE C] we don't let
a single one of these
[ELITE C] ugly S.O.B.'s
wander outta this corner.
[ELITE C] Focus
on luring them here
[ELITE C] and keeping
them here, understood?
[ELITE C] Do not, I repeat,
do not engage them in combat
[ELITE C] unless you
absolutely have to.
[ELITE C] I want you on the
ground, three cadets per team.
When you reach the
wall, jump. That clear?
Die, and you'll piss me off.
[ELITE C] If a Titan goes
astray, we'll put him down.
Whaddya mean "if"?
It's not like we can
count on them
to follow protocol.
[ANNIE] What if our
situation gets risky?
Are we free to act at
our own discretion or what?
[ELITE C] Whatever'll
make it easier on you.
[ELITE C] Team
Kirschtein, move out!
[JEAN] Yes, sir!
Son of a bitch-- Behind us!
[ELITE E] It's a 13-meter!
And from the looks of it,
[ELITE E] he's about
to pounce on Jaeger!
[ELITE F] Heads up!
We've got four more
[ELITE F] coming
through the gate!
[ELITE F] All of
them 10-meters at least!
Right. Rear! Ackerman! Yours!
Sir!
Keep it away from
him at all costs!
Hold the rest off here!
Will do!
[MIKASA] Elite or
not, two teams can't
[MIKASA] take on
four Titans at once.
[MIKASA] What's going on?
[MIKASA] Where are they
coming from all of a sudden?
[MIKASA] There aren't enough
of us to attract this many.
[MIKASA] Unless-- Unless
they're coming for Eren!
[ARMIN] Mikasa!
Why'd the plan go belly-up?
[MIKASA] Armin?
Why on earth is he
just slumped here like this?
[MIKASA] Get away.
It's dangerous!
[MIKASA] Something went wrong.
[MIKASA] He lost control
and wound up like that!
[MIKASA] I tried
to snap him out of it,
[MIKASA] but I couldn't
get him to respond.
[MIKASA] He's been out like
this for the past few minutes.
[ARMIN] But the plan?
[MIKASA] We've had to shift
tac. Right now all we can do
[MIKASA] is protect him.
He's defenseless.
[MIKASA] And there's--
There's just so many.
I don't know how much
longer we can keep this up!
♪
[ARMIN] From the back of the
head to the nape of the neck,
one meter high and
ten centimeters across!
[MIKASA] Armin!
[ARMIN] I'm pulling
him out of here!
You just hold off the other
Titans as long as you can!
[MIKASA] But--
[ARMIN] When Eren first
emerged from this form,
[ARMIN] it was
from the weak spot.
I dunno. But something tells me
that's a big
part of the picture.
[ARMIN] How these
damn things work.
It'll be alright. As long
as I don't hit the center.
This won't kill him.
But, well, it is going to hurt.
[ARMIN] A lot.
No!
[roaring]
Stop it! You'll
get yourself killed!
I'm fine! Just do what you
can to keep the rest at bay!
Trust me, there's
tons of other people
you should be worried about!
[ARMIN] Now leave Eren to
me and go do what you do best!
Eren! Can you hear me?
[ARMIN] You've got
to pull it together!
[ARMIN] If you stay like
this, we're all going to die!
[ARMIN] Whatever this
body's doing to you, fight it!
[ARMIN] You're Eren
Jaeger, damn it!
[ARMIN] What's this steaming
lump of flesh have on you, huh?
[EREN] What is
he talking about?
[EREN] Fight it? What?
[EREN] I'm tired.
Come on. Damn it!
Wake up! Get out of there!
We need you! Eren!
Your mom, remember?
Remember what they did to her?
[ARMIN] You were bent
on avenging her death!
[ARMIN] You swore to
massacre the Titans!
You're not making
any sense, Armin.
[EREN] Open your eyes.
Mom's not dead.
[ARMIN] Eren! Eren, please!
You have to push through it!
[ARMIN] I know you're
in there! Listen to me!
[ARMIN] If you don't get
a move on, the Titans are
[ARMIN] going to kill us!
It'll all end right here!
Armin. Seriously, what
the hell's gotten into you?
[EREN] What's this
"get a move on" crap?
[EREN] I don't
wanna "move" anything.
This right here's
good enough for me.
It's not like I
want to be a Scout.
[screaming]
Fantastic. Well, like it
or not we're on our own now.
[screaming]
[IAN] Die!
Yeah! That's what I
thought, you bastard!
Get some distance!
[MIKASA] I've got this, Captain!
I'll help Team Mitabi!
What the--?
Jean!
Get up the wall!
[JEAN] I'm sick and tired of
people dying because of me!
[JEAN] You malfunction now?
♪
[CONNY] Jean!
[CONNY] What's he doing?
And why the hell
isn't he using his gear?
Hang on!
[CONNY] Don't tell
me it's not working!
I am not going to die today!
Way to go. Draggin'
everybody down. Great job.
♪
[JEAN] Maybe I won't die today.
Eren. Please. For me.
Wake up.
Remember when we were kids?
All we could talk about
was the world outside.
[ARMIN] You know,
beyond the walls.
[ARMIN] Frozen tundra
that stretches to the skies.
[ARMIN] Sand dunes.
[ARMIN] Oceans.
[ARMIN] Forests.
[ARMIN] The world my
parents wanted to see.
I'd always thought
you'd outgrown that dream.
I was kind of sad it
didn't come up anymore.
But then I realized
you let it go because
[ARMIN] you didn't want
me to join the Scouts.
No, I... just...
[ARMIN] Tell me. Honestly.
[ARMIN] Even
though your first step
[ARMIN] beyond the wall
meant the difference between
[ARMIN] a warm hearth
and hell on earth.
Even though it meant
risking your life.
Gambling against the possibility
of dying like my parents.
[ARMIN] Why? Why throw
caution to the wind
[ARMIN] and venture outside?
What kind of question is that?
Don't play dumb.
You know damn well why.
Because the world beyond
the wall is my birthright!
♪
[NARRATOR] Run like
hell. Stay alive.
[NARRATOR]
Words run in circles;
[NARRATOR] lives end in
blood and ear-piercing screams.
[NARRATOR] But Eren
soldiers on, a beacon of hope.