[ORUO] I hate being right.
No time to lose! Move it!
[ELD] She's coming for us!
[NARRATOR] After making
a sudden reappearance,
[NARRATOR] the Female Titan
wiped out the Levi Squad's
[NARRATOR] most elite
soldiers, one by one.
[EREN] I'm gonna--
Kill you!
[NARRATOR] Blaming
himself for their deaths,
[NARRATOR] Eren turned
back to face the enemy,
[NARRATOR] unleashing a furious
assault in his Titan form.
[NARRATOR] Yet for all
his rage, Eren was defeated,
[NARRATOR] and taken
by the Female Titan.
[MIKASA] Do you
hear me? Give him back!
[Mikasa power yell]
[MIKASA] I know
you're in there.
And after I kill her,
I'll carve out her insides,
and pull you out
again. I swear I will.
Just hang on a little longer.
Don't give up, Eren.
Never give up!
Get back here!
[MIKASA] What?
We'll stay back for now.
Maintain current distance.
[LEVI] She's slowed down a bit.
[LEVI] That fight
wore her out, too.
It looked like she may have
bitten the entire nape off.
It's unlikely Eren survived.
He's still alive in there.
[MIKASA] This Titan is
different; it acts with purpose.
[MIKASA] If she
wanted Eren dead,
[MIKASA] she could've
simply crushed him.
[MIKASA] No, she needs
him for something.
[MIKASA] But she also
needs her hands to fight,
[MIKASA] so she's been
holding him on her tongue.
It is possible she just
wanted to savor her quarry.
In which case it's likely
he's already been swallowed.
[LEVI] If so, he's dead.
He's alive.
Someone's optimistic.
[MIKASA] If you had
just done your damn job
and protected him like
you were supposed to,
we wouldn't be having
this conversation!
[LEVI] Oh, I see now. The
"childhood friend", right?
Suddenly it's all making sense.
[LEVI] Right. For
the sake of argument,
[LEVI] let's narrow our goals.
[LEVI] First, we forget
about taking her down.
[MIKASA] No way.
She's killed too many
[MIKASA] of our
people for that. She's dead.
She's got defenses
that neither of us
has been trained to deal with.
I'm telling you
it's a lost cause.
[LEVI] Instead, we'll
act on your assumption
[LEVI] that Eren is alive,
[LEVI] and focus only on freeing
him before she exits the forest.
[LEVI] I'll handle
all the cutting.
[LEVI] You find a
way to distract her.
[MIKASA] Right.
♪
[MIKASA] He's fast!
She can't even react!
[MIKASA] Her skin
can't harden in time!
[MIKASA] Her nape.
It's wide open!
[MIKASA] It looks like
her whole body's gone limp.
[MIKASA] Now's my chance!
Don't do it!
[warcry]
♪
[MIKASA] Eren!
[LEVI] Got him!
[LEVI] Time to go.
Eren.
[LEVI] He's alright.
Disgusting, but alright.
What'd I tell you about trying
to take her down? Now come on.
[LEVI] We've got Eren. That
means our work here is done.
[LEVI] Don't screw this
up by making it personal,
[LEVI] you understand?
We all get that you love him,
but try not to act crazy.
I-- I was just--
♪
[CITIZEN 1] They're
already on the way back?
[CITIZEN 2] Is that bad?
[CITIZEN 3] Probably.
Odds are they'll have
[CITIZEN 3] a stack
of fresh corpses in tow.
It sounds like Eld will be
home sooner than we thought.
Is that so?
[MAN] Think they'll
give Oruo enough time
[MAN] to pop by and say hello?
I suppose in any event we can
set a place
for him at the table.
[WOMAN] They say
Gunther's coming back.
[MAN] Do they?
[camp chatter]
♪
This is the part of our
job I'll never get used to.
[ARMIN] You're
not alone in that.
Seems like death's
just everywhere.
All I can think
about is how it'll end.
Which one of us is next
and whether it'll be me.
[ARMIN] Try not
to obsess over it.
Only thing that train
of thought's good for
is breaking your
nerve. Believe me.
[ARMIN] Push it
out of your mind.
I s'pose you're right.
[JEAN] Nah, I know you're right.
So how much longer 'til
our number's up, you think?
[SASHA] I dunno, but
we've made it this far.
Yeah, luck of the draw.
[SASHA] So what? We're
alive. Be glad for it.
Sorry, it's kinda hard to
celebrate around so many bodies.
[CONNY] They'll never see
home again. Why should we?
[PEER] Almost done, sir.
[PEER] We estimate about
five to be unrecoverable.
[ERWIN] Not even
an arm or a leg?
[PEER] Sadly, the Titans
didn't leave much behind.
And honestly sir, I think it
would be best for the families
if we didn't bring
back what little there is.
We'll put them
down as "missing".
[PEER] Sir.
Also, sir. Our spotters
report several Titans
have emerged from the forest.
Fortunately, none yet seem
to be headed in our direction.
We move out immediately.
Inform the squads.
Sir.
[DIETER] No! I refuse!
It's inhumane!
[PEER] Damn you, shut up!
We can't just leave
'em out here! He was there!
I saw Ivan's body.
He was right in front us!
And if you didn't notice,
there were Titans nearby.
Go back and we could
wind up dead ourselves.
So if they attack, we'll
fight! It's what we do, right?
Ivan and me, we grew up
in the same town together.
His parents are
like family to me!
[JURGEN] I can't face
them again if we leave him!
[PEER] Sentimental garbage!
[LEVI] Stop shrieking.
[DIETER] Captain Levi!
If you've already
confirmed his death,
then there's
nothing more to do.
[LEVI] Whether we have his body
or not makes no difference now.
He's still just
as dead either way.
That's cold.
Ivan and the others will be
listed as missing in action.
That's my decision and
it's final. Now let it go.
You heartless bastards!
That's the kind of
respect you show the men
[DIETER] who give
their lives for you?
[PEER] Unless
you want to be MIA,
[PEER] I suggest
you shut your mouth!
[DIETER] Wait!
[DIETER] Heads up!
We've got company!
[SOLDIER] Titans!
Is that--?
[PEER] Dieter!
That damn fool.
[MESSENGER] Enemy
spotted at the rear!
Full speed! All soldiers!
Our best chance
might be to circle back,
make a beeline for the trees.
We can't put up much
of a fight out here.
No, our best option now
is to continue to the wall.
♪
[worried shreik]
[soldier screming]
♪
[ARMIN] It's about to
be right on top of us!
Looks like we've got
no choice but to fight!
Ground's too flat to engage
ODM gear. And not only that--
[ARMIN] We'll soon
be outnumbered.
[sigh] Perfect. Then what
do you suggest we do, genius?
The only thing we can.
[struggling]
[Dieter screaming]
[Mikasa warcry]
♪
[SOLDIER 1] We're done!
It's gaining on us!
I'll jump behind the
bastard and distract him!
Give you a chance
to put some distance--
[LEVI] Don't bother.
You've got to jettison
the extra weight.
Dump the bodies.
[SOLDIER] B-B-But, sir!
Do you know how many corpses
we've already left behind?
These aren't
special. Dump them!
[LEVI] Consider it their
last service to the cause.
[SOLDIER] Are we doing
this? We can't seriously
be doing this!
[LEVI] Damn it.
I'm sorry, there's
just no other way!
♪
[SOLDIER] That's it!
We're losing him!
[SOLDIER] Alright,
soldiers, look sharp.
[SOLDIERS] We
head out the moment
[SOLDIERS] our
positions are confirmed.
A minor course correction
to the East should work.
[DIETER] Captain, I--
I wanted to say.
We can't always carry
our fallen comrades home,
but we carry their memory.
[LEVI] This was Ivan's.
Thank you, sir.
[ELITE] Let's move 'em out!
[MIKASA] Eren. You should let
the Scout Regiment thing go.
[EREN] Seriously? Why does
everybody think they're a joke?
What people think about
'em isn't really the issue.
[bell ringing]
[EREN] Perfect
timing! They're back!
We can make it if we hurry.
Get a move on!
I want a good view!
[sparse chatter]
[shocked whispers]
[MAN 1] Sure taken
a hit, haven't they?
[MAN 2] Yeah. Rest
of 'em got eaten.
[MAN 2] That's what
happens when pride
[MAN 2] takes you
outside the walls.
Nothing like seeing our
hard earned taxes go toward
keeping those bastards
fat and happy, right?
[MIKASA] Eren.
[MIKASA] What is it?
[Eren shaky breath]
Talk to me.
Eren!
[gasp]
Easy.
[MIKASA] Don't try
to move just yet.
[MIKASA] You need rest.
Where's the Female Titan?
She got away from us.
What do you mean?
She-- She was-- We were--
What about the mission?
It didn't go as planned.
But don't worry
about that right now.
How'd I get here?
Did you have to
step in and save
me again? Is that it?
[MIKASA] Look. We're
almost home, okay?
♪
[shocked whispers]
[MAN 1] Am I
miscounting, or are there
[MAN 1] fewer of 'em
than when they left?
[MAN 2] No,
there's a lot fewer.
[MAN 3] Must've been a bad one.
[MAN 4] I don't get it.
They were all piss and vinegar
[MAN 4] this morning.
They're already back?
[MAN 2] Hell, why bother
leavin' in the first place?
[MAN 1] No idea. I'd say
by the looks on their faces
[MAN 1] they hoped
to be gone longer.
[MAN 1] Our taxes hard at work,
ladies and gentlemen. Bravo.
Eren. Ignore it.
[BOY] Awesome! Beat, but
they're still ready to go!
You gotta be made of nails
to ride with these guys!
[BOY] They're unstoppable!
♪
[MAN] Excuse me, Captain Levi?
[MAN] G-Good evening.
I, uh-- Yes.
I'm Petra's father, sir.
[PETRA'S FATHER] Might I bend
your ear before she sees us?
I received this letter
from her somewhat recently.
Apparently you
handpicked her yourself?
She's very excited,
I can assure you.
In fact, it sounds like
she's utterly devoted to you
in every way.
[PETRA'S FATHER] So devoted
that, well, to be honest
[PETRA'S FATHER] her mother and
I are a bit concerned, you see.
[Petra's father chuckling]
Now, I-- I know that fathers
can have trouble letting go.
[PETRA'S FATHER] But still,
I can't help but feel she's
[PETRA'S FATHER] far too young
to be thinking about marriage.
[PETRA'S FATHER] She has
so much yet to experience
[PETRA'S FATHER] before
settling down.
[MALE 1] Give us some answers,
damn you! We have a right!
[FEMALE] How many lives
were lost on this mission?
[FEMALE] Was it worth it?
Was is really worth it?
[MALE 2] You think the last
thing going through their minds
[MALE 2] was "for the
good of humanity?"
[NARATOR] The causalities
incurred during
[NARRATOR] the Scout
Regiment's latest excursion
[NARRATOR] beyond
the wall were profound.
[NARRATOR] So much so,
that what little public favor
[NARRATOR] they still
held was all but crushed.
[Eren crying]
[NARRATOR] Within
hours of their return,
[NARRATOR] Erwin and
the battle-weary survivors
[NARRATOR] were
called to the capital.
[NARRATOR] The Scouts' custody
of Eren was summarily revoked.
[NARRATOR] Having
been assigned to the
[NARRATOR] elite security
escort team the day
[NARRATOR] Eren is
summoned to the capital,
[NARRATOR] Annie faces
a dilemma when Armin
[NARRATOR] emerges from the
shadows, imploring her help
[NARRATOR] in a secret
mission of vital importance.