[LEVI] C'mon. It's an easy
question. So answer it.
What the hell is
it you want to do?
I want to become a
member of the Scouts,
and slaughter every
Titan that crosses my path.
Huh. Well played.
[LEVI] Alright, then. I'll
take responsibility for him.
[LEVI] Let the higher-ups
know what's going on.
Not that I implicitly
trust him, of course.
It's more a matter
of me trusting myself
to deal with him.
Kill him, if I have to.
The big wigs aren't
likely to raise a stink.
My record more than speaks
for itself, I'm pretty sure.
[LEVI] Good news, Jaeger.
[LEVI] You're now officially
a member of the Scouts.
[MAN 1] Hey.
You think it's true?
[MAN 1] There's a Titan
fighting on our side now?
[MAN 2] When did you start
believing everything you heard?
[MAN 2] More likely the
recapture plan failed.
[MAN 2] And now
refugees from Wall Rose
[MAN 2] are going to
start flooding in here.
[MAN 3] And once
those people swarm us,
[MAN 3] our supplies'll
run out in a matter of days.
[MAN 1] Wait. So if the
Wall Rose people really do
[MAN 1] have a Titan with them,
[MAN 1] you don't think
they'd be crazy enough to
[MAN 1] bring him
in here, do you?
[MAN 4] Hey. Have you
heard the good news?
[MAN 4] The military
has a Titan on the team!
[MAN 4] Can you
believe it? Who knows?
[MAN 4] We might even be
able to retake Wall Maria!
[MAN 4] Finally,
humanity has a Savior!
[various joy]
[MAN] Saviour, huh?
Since the dawn of history,
commoners have
always been a rash lot.
These rumors get any
more out of control,
we'll have a
revolt on our hands.
Not today. This
so-called "Savior"?
We'll make an
example out of him.
[MAN] I'll be damned if he's
allowed to join the Survey Corp.
Form ranks!
All hail to the Premier!
Damn, hot day.
[ERWIN] Commander Pyxis.
You're the C.O. of
the Garrison Regiment.
And I'm the
Commanding Officer of
the Survey Corp and the Scouts.
[ERWIN] Some people
might disapprove of
[ERWIN] our meeting like this.
[PYXIS] Ha! You're as straight-
laced as your reputation.
[PYXIS] Nothing untoward
here. We just coincidentally
[PYXIS] bumped into one another
while out for a morning stroll.
[PYXIS] Protocol
doesn't prevent us from
[PYXIS] chatting under
the circumstances.
You are aware the
Military Police plan to
take custody of
Eren Jaeger, I presume.
[ERWIN] Yes. I received
word yesterday.
[ERWIN] They plan to hold
a deliberation on the matter.
[PYXIS] Hm. The decision has
been left to Premier Zachary.
[PYXIS] Whether Cadet Jaeger's
future lies with the Scouts,
[PYXIS] or in the hands
of the Military Police.
[ERWIN] Zachary? You mean
Premier Dhalis Zachary?
[PYXIS] The Military Police.
The Garrison Regiment.
[PYXIS] And the Scouts.
[PYXIS] All three fall
under his jurisdiction.
[PYXIS] His decision will be
based entirely on one factor:
[PYXIS] Is Eren Jaeger's
existence a benefit
[PYXIS] or a handicap
to our survival?
[PYXIS] If deemed
detrimental, Jaeger will be
[PYXIS] executed
without a thought.
[PYXIS] Right then
and there, if need be.
[PYXIS] I, for one, do
not want to see him die.
[PYXIS] However, many
in the Garrison Regiment,
[PYXIS] I'm sad to
say, are fearful of
Eren's unique ability.
My hands are tied.
The most I can do is avoid
agreeing with the M.P.'s.
[PYXIS] Do the odds favor you?
No, they don't.
And yet, we do have
a proposal prepared.
[ERWIN] Whether it
will work or not,
[ERWIN] all depends on
how the debate unfolds.
You mean, you're
going to play it by ear?
Our job is reconnaissance
beyond the walls.
Playing things by
ear is all we ever do.
Ha! [laughing]
[PYXIS] You're not so uptight
after all, it would seem.
[PYXIS] Thank you for
the pleasant conversation.
[PYXIS] And
good luck, Commander!
[MIKASA] A debate over Eren?
What for?
[ARMIN] I'm not
really sure, but,
it might be about what
they plan to do with him.
And what does that mean?
It means...
they may not let him live.
Cadet Mikasa Ackerman. And
Cadet Armin Arlelt. Hop to!
[MIKASA] Sir!
[OFFICER] You're ordered to
attend and act as witnesses
at today's deliberation.
[EREN] 'Scuse me. I gotta pee.
No, you just went.
Then can I have some water?
[GUARD] Hey!
You're not getting a
thing, got it? Damn monster.
[EREN] Monster. I guess he's
not too far off the mark there.
[EREN] Frightened
of me or not, though,
[EREN] I don't deserve this.
[EREN] Except how
can I blame him?
[EREN] I don't even
understand what's going on.
[EREN] On the bright side,
at least these guards
[EREN] haven't
tried to kill me yet.
[EREN] When I think back,
they weren't afraid of me.
[EREN] Even after
everything they'd seen.
[EREN] I wonder what
they're doing now.
[EREN] And all the others.
I wonder what happened to them.
[ERWIN] Just hang on
a little longer, Eren.
[ERWIN] We'll keep trying
to sort all this out.
[EREN] I've been
in here so long.
[EREN] What's been happening
outside of these bars?
[EREN] I'm-- I'm
not going to spend
[EREN] the rest of my
life like this, am I?
So then, you're Eren?
[HANGE] Are you well?
How're things?
[HANGE] I'm really sorry
you've been waiting so long.
[HANGE] But here's your
chance to finally get out.
Uh.
One thing. You'll have to
put these on for me, okay?
[HANGE] My name is Zoe Hange.
I'm a section
commander for the Scouts.
This is a fellow
commander in the Scouts,
[HANGE] Miche Zacharius.
Uh...
[HANGE] Oh. Don't mind
him. He makes a habit of
[HANGE] giving new
people a thorough sniff.
[HANGE] Tends to laugh
through his nose a bit.
[HANGE] But I don't think
he intends it to be derisive.
[HANGE] Quirks aside, he is
a skilled section commander.
Oh, poo! Sorry. I've
just been prattling on
[HANGE] with the small
talk, and now we're here!
[HANGE] Well,
I'm sure it's fine.
[HANGE] It's probably better
if I don't explain, anyway.
Hey! Hold on!
[HANGE] It might seem
callous, but remember...
we've all put our
faith in you, Eren.
Best of luck!
[EREN] Wait!
[EREN] A courthouse?
[EREN] I was in the basement
of a courthouse this whole time?
[GUARD] All right. Move it!
On your knees. Now!
[EREN] Why're all of these
people here, just staring at me?
[EREN] Somebody gonna explain
what the hell's going on?
[EREN] My friends.
[door opening, then closing]
All right. Shall we begin?
Your name is Eren
Jaeger. And as a soldier,
you have sworn to give
up your life when called to,
[ZACHARY] for the good of
the people. Is that correct?
Yes.
[ZACHARY] As an enlisted
soldier during a time of war,
[ZACHARY] military doctrine
demands your tribunal
be held as a court-martial.
As Commander of
our armed forces,
this matter is
left to my discretion.
Thus, I will decide
whether you live or you die.
[ARMIN] I knew it!
[ZACHARY] Any objections?
No, sir.
[ZACHARY] Your astuteness is
appreciated. Let us proceed.
As expected, covering
up your existence
has proven quite fruitless.
[ZACHARY] And unless we publicly
disclose your existence
[ZACHARY] one way or
another, we risk the outbreak
[ZACHARY] of widespread
civil unrest.
[ZACHARY]
A choice must be made.
[ZACHARY] And the regiment
that takes custody of you
[ZACHARY] will
determine your fate.
[ZACHARY] The Military Police...
[ZACHARY] or
the Scout Regiment?
[ZACHARY] To begin.
The Military Police
[ZACHARY] will now
present their case.
[MAN] Thank you.
My name is Nile Dawk.
[NILE] I am Commander
of the Military Police.
Our recommendation, following
a thorough examination
of his physiology,
subject Eren Jaeger
should be disposed
of immediately.
[NILE] We acknowledge that
Jaeger's ability played a part
in turning back the
latest Titan incursion.
[NILE] However, as has been
stated, his mere existence
[NILE] is creating a swell
of rebellious sentiment.
For the greater good,
after we have gathered all
the information
that we can from him,
we would see him made a
fallen warrior of humanity.
[MAN] Unacceptable!
This verminous fiend has
defiled the mighty Wall...
[EREN] Another deranged
Wall Cultist.
[EREN] Five years ago,
everyone ignored them.
[EREN] Now they've
actually got some clout.
And now I'd like to hear the
Scout Regiment's proposed plan.
[ERWIN] Yes, sir.
As the commander
of the Survey Corp,
I, Erwin Smith,
propose the following:
Let Eren join our
ranks. Reinstate him as
a full member of the
Scouts, and we will utilize
[ERWIN] his Titan ability
to retake Wall Maria.
That is all.
[ZACHARY] Hm? Is that it?
[ERWIN] Yes. With
his assistance, sir,
[ERWIN] I'm certain we
can reclaim Wall Maria.
[ERWIN] Ergo, I believe our top
priority is perfectly clear.
Quite bold. Assuming
you were given clearance,
where do you plan to
launch this operation from?
Commander Pyxis.
The wall in Trost District
has been completely sealed,
is that correct?
[PYXIS] Yes. I doubt its
gate will ever open again.
[ERWIN] We'll depart from
Calaneth District, to the east.
From there, we'll
make for Shiganshina.
A new route can be
establish as we proceed.
But that's ridiculous!
Our time and money would
be better spent
sealing up all the gates!
They're the only
parts of the Wall
that the Colossal
Titan can break, right?
Let's reinforce
the blasted things
and wash our hands
of the entire affair!
[SCOUT 14] Shut your mouth,
you spineless merchant dog!
[SCOUT 14] With a
Titan on our side,
[SCOUT 14] we can finally
return to Wall Maria!
[MERCHANT] We can't afford any
more of your childish antics,
[MERCHANT] or your
delusions of grandeur!
Squealing louder
won't help your case, pig.
[LEVI] While we're
bolstering our defenses,
do you think the Titans
are going to stand idly by?
And when you say "we can't
afford," do you speak for
anyone other than
your fat merchant friends?
[LEVI] Do you pigs even
realize that most of our people
[LEVI] are struggling
just to survive off
[LEVI] what little
land we have left?
I'm simply saying
that sealing the gates
is the only guaranteed
protection we've got!
Hold your tongue, you
vile, belligerent heretic!
Are you really suggesting
that we lowly humans
meddle with Wall Rose,
a gift to us from on high?
[MAN] The Wall is a miracle.
[MAN] And its divinity
transcends human comprehension.
[MAN] Don't you understand?
It's that cult's fault.
They're the ones who
delayed the garrison's
arming of the Walls.
That shows you the
sick amount of support
and power they've got.
I don't trust them at all.
[MERCHANT] ...to pieces!
[MAN] Such sacrilege!
[MERCHANT] Oh, you're
insane. Shut yer trap!
[MAN] How dare you!
[ZACHARY] Order! I ask
that you save your personal
[ZACHARY] sentiments for
a more appropriate venue.
[ZACHARY] Now then Mr. Jaeger,
I have a question for you.
[ZACHARY] As a soldier,
you have made a solemn pledge
[ZACHARY] to answer
humanity's call.
[ZACHARY] Can you still serve
by controlling your ability?
Yes! I will, sir!
[ZACHARY] Oh? Is that so?
But this report from the
Battle for Trost
contradicts that statement.
Just after transforming,
[ZACHARY] it seems
you made an attempt to
[ZACHARY]
crush Mikasa Ackerman.
[ARMIN] He doesn't
even remember.
[ARMIN] He completely
lost control.
What'd you expect? You want
me to lie in the report?
Glossing over that
important fact could
potentially spell
disaster for us all.
[ZACHARY] And who is
this Mikasa Ackerman?
Me! That would be me, sir.
Alright, then. Is it
true that Eren Jaeger
assaulted you while
he was in Titan form?
Answer the Premier honestly.
Eren's future depends on it.
Yes. All of that's true.
[whispers and gasps]
[MERCHANT] I knew it! He's
a wolf in sheep's clothing!
[EREN] I-- I tried
to kill Mikasa?
[EREN] What's happening to me?
[MIKASA] However, he also
saved my life twice before.
And in each circumstance he
was using his Titan ability.
The first:
shortly after Trost fell.
[MIKASA] I was nearly
killed by a Titan.
[MIKASA] But then Eren came.
[MIKASA] He stepped
in and protected me.
[MIKASA] The second
time: he transformed to
[MIKASA] shield Armin
and me from cannon fire.
I implore you to take these
facts into consideration.
[NILE] Objection!
I have reason to believe
that personal feelings
play a large
part in her testimony.
Let the record show
that Mikasa Ackerman
was orphaned at a young age
and was subsequently taken
in by the Jaeger family.
[NILE] What's more,
our own internal
[NILE] investigation
into this matter
led to a most
shocking discovery.
Eren Jaeger
and Mikasa Ackerman,
at the tender age of nine,
dealt with three adult
[NILE] kidnappers by
stabbing all of them to death.
[NILE] Granted, this
was done in self-defense.
[NILE] All the same, one
cannot help but question
[NILE] the violent
nature of the act.
[Nile] Knowing all of this,
should we really invest in him?
[NILE] Money, manpower. Perhaps
the very fate of us all?
[MAN] Maybe he's a
Titan that snuck in here
[MAN] after taking the form
of some little child he ate?
Maybe she's one! I bet
she's not human either!
[MAN] Yeah, you're right!
[MAN] Dissect her too,
just to be safe!
Now hold on a second!
Maybe I'm a monster
that you want dead, but
you leave her out of this!
[EREN] She's innocent!
[MAN 1] Like we'd trust you!
It's the truth!
[MAN 2] She must be
one if you protect her!
Stop it!
[EREN] You're wrong.
About it all.
[EREN] But you're so intent
on pushing selfish agendas,
[EREN] you're blind to
what's in front of you.
Wait. What do you mean?
What does it even matter?
[EREN] What am I saying?
None of you have
even seen a Titan,
so why're you so afraid, huh?
[EREN] Maybe I should
just keep quiet.
[EREN] No. If
they wanna kill me,
[EREN] I'll let them
know exactly what I think.
There's no sense in
having power if you're
not going to use it to fight!
[EREN] If you're too scared
to fight for your lives, fine.
[EREN] Let me do it!
You-- You're all cowards!
[MAN] What?
Just shut up. And put
all your faith in me!
Take aim, dammit!
Right! Yes, sir!
[EREN] Huh?
[Eren wheezing]
[gasp and growling]
Mikasa, wait!
[LEVI] You know, personally,
[LEVI] I think nothing
instills discipline like pain.
You don't need a
good "talking-to".
What you're in need of,
boy, is to be taught a lesson.
[LEVI] And you happen to be
in perfect kicking position.
[Eren gasping]
N-Now hold on, Levi!
What is it?
It's dangerous.
[NILE] What if he gets
angry? Turns into a Titan?
Don't be silly.
After all, you guys just want
to dissect him, don't you?
During the time that
he was transformed,
they say that Jaeger was
able to kill twenty Titans
before he finally
ran out of strength.
As an enemy, his
intelligence makes him
all the more dangerous.
[LEVI] But I could still take
him down without a problem.
[LEVI] How many of
you can say the same?
[LEVI] Before you torment
the beast, you'd better think.
[LEVI] Can you
actually kill him?
[ERWIN] Sir.
I have a proposition.
Proceed.
There's still too
much we don't know.
And no doubt, his danger
will be ever present.
As such, I suggest this:
[ERWIN] Eren Jaeger
will be placed under
[ERWIN] Captain
Levi's supervision.
[ERWIN] And we'll
conduct a recon mission
[ERWIN] outside of the wall.
[ZACHARY] Jaeger will join
you in this excursion?
[ERWIN] Yes, sir. Then you can
[ERWIN] look upon the
mission's results yourself.
And if he successfully
controls his ability...
Eren will have proven
his value to mankind.
Eren Jaeger will
be closely supervised?
And if he should lose control?
[ERWIN] I can definitely
kill him, if it comes to that.
[ERWIN] The only downside is,
[ERWIN] there's absolutely
no middle ground.
Hm. Then I
have made my choice.
[HANGE] Well that went
better than I expected.
Does it hurt?
Yeah.
Yeah? Describe it to me!
Huh?
[ERWIN] Sorry for all that.
[ERWIN] But the
theatrics did get you
[ERWIN] placed in our custody.
[EREN] No, I understand.
[ERWIN] I can assure
you the pain was worth it.
[ERWIN] We played our trump
card at the perfect time.
You have my utmost respect.
Eren, I'm glad that
you're on our team.
Uh? Me, too!
Glad to be here, sir!
So, Eren.
[EREN] Sir?
You don't resent
me now, do you?
N-- No. I can see that what
you did was necessary, sir.
Good. Then you understand.
[HANGE] Still, don't you
think you went too far?
[HANGE] I mean, you
knocked his tooth out!
Neat, huh?
[LEVI] You picked
it up? How disgusting.
[HANGE] This is a precious
sample I'll have you know!
Hey, just be glad people
like that aren't dissecting you.
[HANGE] Don't you dare
to compare me with them.
[HANGE] I would never
even dream of killing him.
Hey, Eren. Let me take a look
inside that mouth of yours!
[HANGE] Your tooth...
[HANGE] it grew back.
[NARRATOR] After achieving
his long-held dream
[NARRATOR] of joining
the elite Scout Regiment,
[NARRATOR] Eren finds
the vaunted Scouts are
[NARRATOR] an eccentric band
of soldiers and searchers.
[NARRATOR] A haven for oddballs,
misfits and iconoclasts.