[NARRATOR] They first appeared
over a hundred years ago.
[NARRATOR] Giant,
humanoid creatures
[NARRATOR] with a
taste for our blood.
[NARRATOR] The brute
strength of these aberrations
[NARRATOR] trumped an average
person's many times over.
[NARRATOR] We were
shoved to the brink
[NARRATOR] of extinction
almost overnight.
[NARRATOR] The survivors erected
Walls Maria, Rose, and Sina;
[NARRATOR] withdrawing behind
them in frightened huddles
[NARRATOR] for what was to
be a century of uneasy peace.
[NARRATOR] And then...
[NARRATOR] The Titan assault
on Trost left us reeling.
[NARRATOR] Owing
at least in part to
[NARRATOR] the Scout
Regiment's absence at the time,
[NARRATOR] military
causalities were profound.
[NARRATOR] Ironically, they'd
embarked on a reconnaissance
[NARRATOR] mission beyond
the wall that very morning.
[MAN] Heads up! The main unit
of the Scout Regiment is back!
[MAN 2] That's right,
Commander Erwin!
[MAN 2] Did you give those
ugly bastards a thrashing?!
Look! It's Captain Levi!
[COMMONER] They say he's like
an entire brigade unto himself!
Spare me, please.
That scowl will crush your fans.
Not that it's any of
my business, but from a
public relations standpoint,
you might wanna lighten up.
[Levi scoffing]
[HANGE] Lo! The
threshold of Titania!
Can't you just
envision the horrors
in store for us, comrades?
I'm on pins and needles!
We bag an Abnormal,
I'll burst with tears of joy!
[LEVI] I think we've bagged
the craziest abnormal already.
What? Seriously? Where?
I mean you.
[ERWIN] Move out!
[NARRATOR] The Scout Regiment's
primary function is to
[NARRATOR] establish
bases of expansion.
[NARRATOR] Acting as a
spearhead for human knowledge.
[NARRATOR] Theirs is a
solemn and dangerous honor.
[NARRATOR]
Thanks to the ingenuity
[NARRATOR] of its
exemplary members,
[NARRATOR] the regiment's
survival rates have improved.
[NARRATOR] That
said, excursions into
[NARRATOR] long-relinquished
territory still commonly
[NARRATOR] result in a
death-toll exceeding 30%.
[NARRATOR] A stark illustration
of the disparity between
[NARRATOR] our own strength
and that of the Titans.
[SOLDIER] One day... One day
you'll all just be a bad memory.
Mankind will
destroy all of you!
Mark my words: the last
ones standing will be us!
[soldier screaming]
[SOLDIER] Gorge
while you can, you bastard.
Just wait 'til Captain Levi--
♪
[LEVI] One on the right.
[LEVI] Two on the left.
Captain! The reinforcements
are here, sir!
[LEVI] Good. Tend to
our comrade below, Petra.
[LEVI] You two, take out
the Titan to your right.
The pair on the
left belongs to me.
Captain, wait!
[Titan roar]
[excited holler]
Don't be scared, big
guy! I won't hurt you.
[HANGE] Cross my
heart n' hope to die!
[Hange laughing]
Points for tryin', but you're
a li'l slow on the uptake!
Hiyah!
See? Bet you
barely felt a thing.
[LEVI] I know you probably
can't help being hideous.
[LEVI] But I can't help being
tired of looking at you.
♪
[pained screams]
[LEVI] Uh oh. Easy, big stuff.
[LEVI] Nobody's got
time for a crybaby.
Let's take it like
a man, shall we?
Ugh. Disgusting.
[PETRA] Captain!
I-- I can't stop the bleeding.
[SOLDIER] Captain Levi.
I'm here.
[SOLDIER] Did-- Did this
make a difference?
[SOLDIER] Was I--
Was I helpful?
Please, sir. Don't tell
me this was for nothing.
Tell me this'll
advance the cause.
[LEVI] We've made great
strides today, soldier.
[LEVI] And tomorrow,
because of you,
[LEVI] your strength
won't die with you;
[LEVI] the torch will
be carried on by me.
This I swear on my very life.
The Titans will be eradicated!
[PETRA] Sir.
I'm sorry. He's--
Did the man hear what
I had to say? Any of it?
Yes, sir. Matter of fact
I think he heard all of it.
Look at him.
[PETRA] That's a face at peace.
We can hope.
[ERWIN] Levi!
We're pulling out.
Sir.
What do you mean?
You damn well know
that we can push further!
My men didn't die
to pave our retreat!
There's a swarm of
Titans moving north.
They're bearing
down on the city.
It's just like five years ago.
Something tells me
this is going to be bad.
For all we know, the wall's
already been reduced to rubble.
[EREN] Damn you.
[Eren breathing]
[screaming]
This-- This isn't real!
[EREN] We were ready.
We were ready.
[EREN] We hit the
books. We trained.
[EREN] These things weren't
a mystery to us anymore.
[EREN] We knew how to
beat them. How to survive.
[GIRL] Help me. It's so hot.
[GIRL] I need to get
home. Mom'll be worried.
[GIRL] I know she will.
[EREN] Mom.
[EREN] Oh, Mom.
Help me. Pleas--
[EREN] How has it come to this?
[EREN] Why has everything
been taken from us?
[EREN] Our lives. Our dreams.
Everything.
[EREN] Damn you.
Damn you all to hell!
[EREN] I refuse
to die like this!
I'll drive them all out!
Kill them with my bare hands!
Do you hear me?
With my bare hands!
[roar]
[thud]
♪
[roar]
[TITAN EREN] This isn't
your world. Not anymore.
[TITAN EREN] I'll kill
every last one of you.
[TITAN EREN] Get up. Get up!
[TITAN EREN] Let me kill you
again! And again, and again!
[TITAN EREN]
You're mine. All of you.
You're all gonna die.
[ARMIN] Eren?
You alright?
[ARMIN] Look at me.
Eren, hey, can you move?
[ARMIN] Can you hear
me? Say something!
Listen, you've got
to tell them everything!
They're terrified,
but they'll understand!
Armin, what--
[ELITE] You catch that?
He said we're all gonna die.
There's not much else
you can make of that.
Son of a bitch wants
to eat us. You watch!
[EREN] What the hell
are they talking about?
[EREN] What is this?
[EREN] Why are all their
blades pointed at us?
[EREN] Those are meant
for taking down Titans.
[EREN] What's going on?
[EREN] And what's
with that look?
[EREN] Are they
terrified of me?
[SOLDIER] I want all you
cadets on standby. Look sharp!
[CONNY] If we hadn't
found the gas,
[CONNY] we'd have never
gotten out of Trost.
Basically, we
got lucky. That's it.
That sounds terrible.
I'm so sorry.
We volunteered to run
supplies out to everyone,
but the situation was so bad.
We'd even found some gas we
were gonna dole out to you guys,
but then everything
went to hell.
So, you're
saying everyone who
isn't here now
didn't uh... you know.
Yeah.
Wait. What about Mikasa?
[CONNY] No, no. She's good.
[CONNY] She made it in after
us with the group Jean led.
Hey, Jean! Where
in the world's Mikasa?
[YMIR] She get hurt or what?
[CONNY] Hey. Talk to us.
[JEAN] I'd tell you if I could.
[JEAN] They slapped
us with a gag order.
[CONNY] Whoa.
You're joking, right?
[YMIR] That's nuts.
[JEAN] They're nuts if they
think people aren't gonna talk.
[JEAN] Word'll get out,
and when it does...
Well, that is, if we survive.
[HANNES] You gotta hand it
to the Engineering Corps for
[HANNES] puttin' the heap
of rancid Titan corpses
[HANNES]
to good use, I suppose.
[HANNES] Still just
a barricade, though.
[HANNES] We can't
get too comfortable.
Stay on your toes.
Whatever happens next,
it's bound to happen here.
This is the proverbial
line in the sand--
Hey, something wrong?
Sir. My apologies.
I completely agree.
I'm just a little
preoccupied about
my friends in the Vanguard.
There was a messenger
on the way to HQ
with this look on his face.
Kid. Difficult as it may be,
you've got to wrangle your mind
to stay focused on
what's here in front of us.
[ELITE] Is it true what they
say about you saving those
[ELITE] kids five
years ago, sir?
[ELITE] They're
cadets now, right?
[ELITE] Won't they be
at the Vanguard, too?
That's right.
I'm really sorry, sir.
Don't know why I felt
the need to bring it up.
They're good.
Some tough little bastards.
Believe me, they know
what it takes to stay alive.
One of 'em's just about the
best fighter I've ever seen.
The other's so stubborn
it can drive you crazy.
Loads of inner strength.
And their friend's
a certifiable genius.
They'll be fine.
Not a doubt in my mind.
[WOERMAN] Cadets Eren
Jaeger, Mikasa Akermann,
[WOERMAN] and Armin Arlelt!
[WOERMAN] The three
of you have jointly
[WOERMAN] committed
an act of high treason!
Whether or not a swift execution
is the result depends on you!
What?
[WOERMAN] Any attempt to move
from where you stand now,
[WOERMAN] anything I deem
the least bit suspicious,
[WOERMAN] will be met with
cannon fire. Do not test me.
[WOERMAN] Answer carefully.
[WOERMAN] Eren Jaeger.
What exactly are you?
[WOERMAN] Human? Or Titan?
[EREN] Wh-What is
that supposed to mean?
[EREN] Why are they all
glaring at me like that?
[EREN] It's like-- Like
they're looking at a monster.
[EREN] Oh god. Is
that what they think?
I'm sorry, sir!
I don't understand!
Son of a bitch
is playing innocent.
Answer me, damn you!
Evasion will get you nowhere!
[WOERMAN] Don't try to
stall with pretend ignorance!
[WOERMAN] You won't stand a
chance! You'll be blown to hell
[WOERMAN] before you can
assume your true form!
What true form?
Please! Scores
of us saw it happen!
[WOERMAN] You emerged from
the carcass of a fallen Titan
[WOERMAN] in full
view of your comrades!
[WOERMAN] A creature of unknown
origin, ability, or allegiance
[WOERMAN] has slipped through
and infiltrated Wall Rose,
[WOERMAN] and that
creature is you.
[WOERMAN] Under
the circumstances,
[WOERMAN] your being sanctioned
by His Majesty is neither
[WOERMAN] here nor there.
You are a risk I am
[WOERMAN] well within
my rights to eliminate!
I will not let
the situation stand!
[WOERMAN] Every moment I
squander mulling over your
[WOERMAN] supposed innocence
puts us all in further
[WOERMAN] jeopardy from attack
by the Armored Titan!
Hell! For all I'm aware,
you're a tactical diversion
precisely for
that purpose! I'm sorry.
Humanity's fate
hangs in the balance!
[WOERMAN] I cannot waste any
more time or manpower on you!
[WOERMAN] Do you understand?
[WOERMAN] My conscience will
not falter to watch you die!
Nor should it.
As soldiers, they all know
the price of their position.
If they're this
committed to defiance
under threat
of death, so be it.
They won't be persuaded.
And as you say, it's
just a waste of time.
Sir, please! This may
be our best chance!
[ELITE] We'll expend far less
artillery if he's in human form!
[MIKASA] Excuse me!
I wouldn't. Not while
I'm standing here.
[MIKASA] Unless anyone's feeling
up to the task, in which case,
well, I 'm happy to
demonstrate my own technique.
On you. And every last inch
of your traitorous flesh.
Sir. There's something
you should know.
She was assigned to the
elites fresh out of training.
Equal to a hundred
soldiers, easily.
[IAN] If we lost her,
it'd be quite the tragedy.
Okay. Somebody talk to me now.
The hell is all this?
Mikasa! You can't
take them all on!
Even if you took down a few,
there's nowhere
left for you to run!
Whoever comes at
Eren, deals with me.
I'll take on the entire
regiment if I have to.
I don't give a damn what
they try to throw at us.
[ARMIN] This isn't the only
way! They're just scared.
[ARMIN] They don't
understand what's happening!
[ARMIN] We need to calm
down and just talk it out!
[EREN] Am I the only one here
who doesn't think I'm a Titan?
[EREN] Damn it! Why can't
I remember how I got here?
[EREN] I'm too weak to stand up,
and if I say the wrong thing...
[EREN] Is this it for me?
[EREN] Killed by people.
[EREN] What was that he
said about me coming out of
[EREN] a Titan carcass
in front of everyone?
[EREN] Is he insane?
[EREN] Why is no
one making any sense?
[EREN] That was
all just a dream!
[EREN] Or...
[EREN] No. My sleeve. My arm.
[EREN] Am I really one of them?
[EREN] That's not possible.
It's just now I--
[WOERMAN] One more time!
Are you a human
being or a Titan?
[EREN] I-- I don't
know what to say.
[EREN] My life's not
the only one at stake.
[EREN] But, I mean I've
always been one of you.
I'm human!
So you say.
[WOERMAN] I'm
left with no choice.
[WOERMAN] Forgive me.
[WOERMAN] When push
comes to shove...
[WOERMAN] all
of us are monsters.
Armin! Head for the
wall! I've got Eren!
Wait, no--!
[GRISHA] Eren.
[GRISHA] Behave while I'm
gone and I'll let you in on
[GRISHA] what I've been
doing in the cellar.
[GRISHA] Listen to me.
It's vital that
[GRISHA] you keep this
key on you at all times.
[GRISHA] Whenever
you look at it,
[GRISHA] let this
thought flood over you:
[GRISHA] "I must
return to that cellar."
[GRISHA] I'm going to give
you a little something
[GRISHA] to make you
forget for the time being.
[GRISHA] I'm sorry.
I wish there was more
time to explain all this.
[GRISHA] When the time
comes though, know that you
[GRISHA] must reclaim Wall
Maria and head for the cellar.
[GRISHA] It won't be
pleasant, but in my heart,
[GRISHA] I know what
I'm doing is for the best.
When the ability confuses you,
let their memories
act as your guide.
[GRISHA] Eren!
[GRISHA] One day, the truth
will come out. I swear to you!
[GRISHA] The journey
will be a painful one.
[GRISHA] But it
is yours to make!
[GRISHA] Mikasa's life.
[GRISHA] Armin's life.
[GRISHA] Everyone's life...
[GRISHA] hinges on your being
able to control this power!
[WOERMAN] Did we get him?
Dear god.
[distant screaming]
[NARRATOR] Armin pleads
for the life of his friend,
[NARRATOR] desperate
to convince their comrades
[NARRATOR] Eren isn't
the monster he seems.
[NARRATOR] But however
eloquent, however passionate,
[NARRATOR] reason finds no
hold in minds wracked by fear.