[NARRATOR]
I'll save you!
Hurry! Reach out
your hand to me!
Trouble in the
Netherworld? Shocker!
You should tell me
your name, now, pervert!
What's a human doing
in the world of the dead?
It's Kirihito.
Talk about a cool name!
Greetings, we have
been waiting for you.
Our lady and mistress
is Lady Izanami,
the presiding goddess
of the underworld.
Please, come with us.
Our mistress is anxiously
awaiting your arrival
at the shrine.
I've got a bad
feeling about this.
[footsteps]
[NANAMI] Uh, hey. I know we
got into this world and stuff,
but that was, like, totally
not on purpose at all.
If you could maybe point us
at the exit to the surface,
well, that'd be really great!
I ask of you to be careful
where you step, human god.
The residents within
this corridor are not
what you may consider polite.
Huh?
[SKELETONS growling]
[NANAMI screams]
Is there a problem?
You know, only some
creepy skeletons!
[NANAMI] What the heck
is your deal, Kirihito?
We're practically in hell,
and you seem like you're right
at home, not phased one bit.
Meanwhile, I'm freaking out,
and I'm the one
who came to save you.
My mistress is just
beyond these doors.
[gasps]
[IZANAMI] It is a pleasure
to meet thee, human god.
I am the lady and goddess
of the Netherworld, Izanami.
I welcome thee.
[NANAMI] So this is
the Netherworld's god.
Pardon our intrusion. I am
the land god, Nanami Momozono,
and my companion is
a human named Kirihito.
We wanna get back to
the surface, but, uh,
we got lost down here,
and can't find the exit.
Maybe, if you could
tell us how to get there,
we'd really
appreciate your help.
--[stomach growls]
--[NANAMI grunts]
[clap, clap]
[NANAMI groans]
[IZANAMI] A token of my welcome.
I doubt thou can partake,
as it is of the Netherworld, but
thou may still enjoy its sight.
[NANAMI gasps] And I thought
I was in hell before.
[IZANAMI] If indulgence is thy
wish, thou art free to do so.
The exit to the surface, was it?
If thou wishes to know, I would
not mind guiding thee. However,
I am afraid thy companion
shall not make the trip.
He is forbidden to leave
my kingdom henceforth!
[AKURA-OH gasps]
Kirihito!
No, but why?
[IZANAMI] Because he possesses
the body of a dead man.
He is human, and yet,
he is no longer human.
A spiritual being resides
within that husk of a corpse.
Did thou truly not
notice, human god?
[NANAMI] I don't know if
you're telling the truth,
but if what you said is right,
then I have to find out why.
There must be
a reason behind it.
Now please, give
Kirihito back to me!
[IZANAMI]
His reason is of no consequence.
A deceased being shall
not be allowed to leave
the Netherworld. My word
is final. Make no mistake,
this is a ruling of fairness,
unbiased by emotion.
Dost thou not realize
the dangers that may befall
the surface world should that
creature be unleashed upon it?
Such naivety.
[IZANAMI]
It would appear thou art
still not a full-fledged god.
Return to thy surface.
[NANAMI]
She's got me beat.
I don't know anything
about Netherworld stuff.
But, I can't leave!
There's no way that
I'm going to back down
without getting to
the bottom of this.
[NANAMI]
Lady Izanami?
[IZANAMI]
Hm?
[gulp]
[IZANAMI]
Oh my word!
[NANAMI] Now I belong
in the Netherworld, too.
Will you please allow me to
remain here, your highness?
[IZANAMI]
Very well, then.
Thou art welcome
to stay in my realm.
[NANAMI]
It actually worked!
I really made it taste
like a sweet potato donut!
[AKURA-OH] Why, are you
not confident in your power?
[NANAMI]
Talk about a confidence boost.
I'm gonna save you for sure
this time! I know I can.
Come on, white talisman, work
with me so I can find Kirihito.
[AKURA-OH] I was trapped
in the cold darkness.
How many decades had gone
by since I gave up counting
each passing second?
How many centuries had been lost
since I last bathed in light?
That insatiable darkness
nearly consumed
the entirety of my being.
[MAN] Excuse me!
Is someone over there?
[AKURA-OH]
Who are you?
It's good to meet ya!
You can call me Kirihito Mori,
'cause that's my name.
Anyway, I'd climbed about
halfway up this mountain,
when I got caught in an
avalanche and ended up buried
in the snow. Digging my way out
didn't really work that well.
I've hung in there
for a couple a days now,
but my body's beginning
to give out.
Ha. I mean, this is only
my first time dying,
so I sorta, kinda panicked
and used up a lot of energy.
[AKURA-OH]
A disembodied human spirit?
When was the last time
I even saw a human?
It seems they are still
as frail as I recall.
[KIRIHITO]
I'll cut to the chase.
Y'see, I'm a little
past due moving on,
because I have a regret, and
I can't seem to let go of it.
Right as I was about
to leave the house,
I got into a fight
with my mom.
It was just a really stupid,
no-big-deal thing.
If I had known that was
gonna be the last time
I'd ever talk to her,
I wouldn't have been so mean.
I'm sure my mom must
think the same thing,
and I don't want her
to blame herself.
I can't let things end that way.
So I was hoping I could
ask you for a favor.
If you can, would you mind
letting my mom know that
I'm sorry about everything?
[AKURA-OH] What is
he going on about?
This human isn't making any
sense. He's already dead.
What could possibly be gained
by passing on this message?
And, well, I thought about
writing her a farewell note...
[AKURA-OH] However, this
is just the type idiocy
I've come to expect from humans.
Exactly as I recalled.
[AKURA-OH]
You ask the impossible.
[KIRIHITO]
Huh?
[AKURA-OH]
I am bound to this spot.
My own body has been stolen by
scoundrels, and now, here I sit.
Merely a pathetic
soul knocked down,
left clinging to some
rocks in these mountains.
'Kay. In that case,
take my body.
It's buried in the snow
and won't move at all.
But, hey, if you can use it,
it's free for the taking.
If that works, would you give
my mom the message for me?
[AKURA-OH]
Sure.
I only agreed on a whim.
Couldn't give a damn
about his situation.
Chances were I was going to die
right along with his body.
But if it had any potential,
then there was
no harm in trying.
Anything to escape
from that nightmare.
Even if I met my end,
I no longer cared.
'Cause if this worked,
there'd be no more darkness.
[KIRIHITO'S MOTHER]
I was so angry with him.
[AKURA-OH]
Who are they?
What are they
talking about?
My hand.
[KIRIHITO'S PARENTS gasp]
Kirihito!
[AKURA-OH]
I can feel. I can move.
[AKURA-OH] It had been centuries
since I'd seen the light.
Kirihito. Everything's okay.
You were trapped
in that avalanche,
but now you're all right!
I was so scared.
My brave little boy came
back to me, safe and sound.
[AKURA-OH]
After years of isolation,
at last there was warmth.
[AKURA-OH]
Mother.
I want to apologize for
the fight we had, I'm sorry.
Don't you worry. I could
never stay mad at you.
Oh, I'm sorry, too.
[AKURA-OH] Bit by bit,
I started to remember my past.
I had to get myself
back to normal.
This weak body
is inconvenient.
I must sleep once a day or this
form doesn't sustain itself.
Worse yet, Shikigami are the
extent of my capabilities,
and they take a total of
seven days to produce.
[AKURA-OH] However, I will
continue to bide my time,
concealing my true nature.
I cannot arouse
unwanted suspicion.
As my senses return, so does
my desire to strike back.
Those damn gods.
To seal my body
within the Netherworld.
I was too much
for them to handle.
[KIKUICHI] What shall
we do, Master Akura-Oh?
[AKURA-OH]
Do not call me by that name.
There is no chance the
Netherworld's poison could
dispose of my body.
I just have to find someone
dumb enough to fetch it for me.
[AKURA-OH gasps]
Why is it so dark now?
No, not again!
Tell me I wasn't dreaming!
Am I delusional?
All that time can't have
been just my imagination!
No more! I won't be in
darkness! Not anymore!
Hey! Kirihito!
I came to save you!
[AKURA-OH whimpers]
[AKURA-OH] Where-Where am I?
What happened to me?
What, you mean
you don't remember?
Izanami totally jumped you,
and locked you away in the
dungeon of her dumb shrine!
It was a really big deal!
Ya' know, finding you was
kind of a pain in the butt.
Feel free to ask me
how I pulled it off.
Ask me! Go ahead! Never mind,
I'll just tell you.
Sha-bam! The great Nanami's
white talisman to the rescue!
Huh?!
[AKURA-OH]
You're so warm.
[NANAMI screams]
Whoa, no perving out
on me again, okay?
My heart belongs to Tomoe,
the most beautiful
fox in the world ever!
Tomoe?
What's the matter?
You're lookin' kinda pale there.
[NANAMI groans]
--[NANAMI screams]
--[AKURA-OH] You should've made
a break for the exit
while you had the chance.
Why did you go through the
trouble of coming to save me?
[NANAMI]
Huh?
You're a god, you should be
able to get back to the surface
on your own strength.
Well yeah,
but that would kinda defeat
my whole saving you thing.
[NANAMI]
We need to get moving
if we don't want
them to find us.
I hate to think what'll
happen if they do.
I don't wanna be a skeleton.
A skeleton?
I swear, humans are
incomprehensible.
[AKURA-OH]
They are such a foolish race.
[ONIKIRI]
Goodness!
The Lucky Mallet certainly is
not a divine tool for nothing!
We can grow bigger or grow
smaller, whenever we please!
[KOTETSU] Gold, silver,
and other treasures
flow in abundance,
as though from a spring!
[ONIKIRI] I had no idea this
was still here at the shrine.
Lady Narukami entrusted
us with its return
to Lord Daikokuten so long ago.
But returning it would
be such a waste!
[KOTETSU] Quite true.
Well, no one is watching us,
perhaps we can pretend
we had forgotten about it.
[barking]
[KOTETSU, ONIKIRI]
Hm?
[pants]
[ONIKIRI]
Master Tomoe!
[TOMOE]
Huh?
[KOTETSU]
We have terrible news!
[TOMOE]
Revert back! You look hideous!
[KOTETSU, ONIKIRI groan]
[KOTETSU]
I hate to tell you this,
but we just got word
from Lord Otohiko.
[ONIKIRI] Lady Nanami has gone
missing in the Netherworld!
Uh! Uh... Where?
[ONIKIRI] No one has any idea
where she could possibly be!
[TOMOE]
Snake?
[KOTETSU] Master Mizuki
was doing something else,
and was apparently acting
separately from Lady Nanami.
[TOMOE]
That idiot!
She was only supposed to
attend the Divine Assembly,
for what reason could
she possibly be going
to the Netherworld? Even gods of
the surface rarely travel there.
One false move, and it
becomes the kind of place
from which you
never return. Ever.
We leave at once!
Make the preparations, Kotetsu!
[KOTETSU gasps]
Are we going to the Netherworld?
Obviously. I will bring back
that fool of a girl, I swear it.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting,
Lady Izanami!
Tonight is the welcoming party
for the lady human goddess,
and I, Hiou, will be
purr-viding entertainment!
[IZANAMI sobs]
[HIOU]
My Lady Izanami?
What's the meowtter?
[IZANAMI] Nanami fooled me,
and fled with a dead human man!
[HIOU]
Meow?
[IZANAMI]
Seize her for me.
I want her to be
my new playmate.
Do not allow her to escape!
[HIOU]
Meowger!
[footsteps]
[sniffs]
[IZANAMI]
Nanami.
Dost thou truly believe thyself
capable of saving someone?
[NANAMI pants] We're pretty
far away, I think we're safe.
It won't be much longer
until we're back home.
I dunno about you,
but I feel really good about
my divine powers right now!
And I bet that I can get
this white talisman to lead us
the rest of the way to the exit.
Well, whaddaya say?
[NANAMI gasps]
Kirihito! Hey, are you okay?
[AKURA-OH]
Yeah, I just felt dizzy.
Like I'm gonna believe that one,
you shouldn't push yourself!
[NANMI] My friend Otohiko said
the air in the Netherworld
causes the human body
to rot and stuff.
[AKURA-OH] Then I have
nothing to worry about.
[gasps]
The poisonous nature
of this world can't affect me.
At least not so long as I
happen to be touching a part
of a god's body. I realized
this earlier today when I took
a lock of your hair while
you were unconscious.
No way! What a relief! I'm--
[screams]
That little bit of hair
is what saved me
from having to walk
while holding your hand.
[NANAMI] Okay, but if you
need to take a break,
just let me know.
[NANAMI]
Uh!
[AKURA-OH grunts]
Get down, I think
someone's out there.
[HIOU on megaphone]
Ahem! Testing! Testing!
Attention humans: god and man!
I know that you are hiding!
You have five meownutes
to reveal yourselves!
If not, Hiou, that's me,
will smoke you out.
And I mean that literally,
because I'll burn the
place to the ground.
[NANAMI gasps]
If she's going to burn us
along with the forest,
then she probably
hasn't pinpointed
our actual location yet.
Then we gotta get outa here.
[NANAMI] Okay, talisman,
don't let me down!
Please show us
the way to the exit!
[gasps]
[NANAMI panting] As fast
and as quietly as we can.
This might be our only chance!
[NANAMI yelps]
[AKURA-OH grunts]
[NANAMI gasps]
[NANAMI] Tomoe,
I don't know what to do!
Tomoe!
Their time's meout!
Set the fire.
[NANAMI]
Oh no!
'Kay. Go, maximum headwind!
Meow! The wind changed, why?
That should buy us some time.
Let's not waste it!
[NANAMI] There's no one here
to tell me what I should do,
or how to get out of this.
[NANAMI]
So it's up to me to handle it!
[AKURA-OH panting]
[NANAMI]
What's wrong, Kirihito?
Looks like a dead end.
Your white talisman has stopped.
No! Where'd all
my divine power go?
Wait, I'm pretty sure
we've been this way before.
This is where we started out.
We're in the vicinity of
the Yomotsu Hirasaka entrance.
What? Was it always
this dark, though?
No, before there was light
from the surface shining
down through the hole.
Looks like someone went and
plugged the damn thing up.
[NARRATOR]
Meanwhile, in the upper world.
[TOMOE] Hey, you.
Move aside, please.
I have business down below.
It has been a while
since we last met.
You are of no interest to me.
Yet you wish to go to the
Netherworld. Quite the dilemma.
I sealed this hole with
a new barrier boulder.
[TOMOE]
Move the rock at once.
My lady and mistress
is still inside.
If you mean to assert
that maiden is a god,
then she can free herself.
Such a feat would
be child's play.
Should she merely be human,
this mistress is sure to
be long past dead by now.
Going to her rescue would
be an utter waste of your time.
[TOMOE]
Move aside!
[grunts]
[TAKEHAYA]
You believe a familiar
can win a fight
against a god, fox?
[KOTETSU shrieks, gasps]
[TAKEHAYA]
In all likelihood,
you are using that maiden
to do as you please,
just as you have
done in the past.
As would befit a fox, I shall
remove you from this plane.
[KOTETSU] Please wait
a moment, Lord War God!
As a familiar, Master Tomoe
is a most excellent fox,
devoid of his past ways!
I beg of you. Please spare him!
[TOMOE]
Kotetsu.
[KOTETSU]
Huh?
What he has said is the truth.
I cannot possibly win as
a familiar. It is a plain fact.
[MIKAGE]
Tomoe, from now on,
you should live here at
this shrine as a familiar.
I'm certain the spirits of the
shrine will welcome you, too.
[TOMOE] I am a yokai. I cannot
live in such a stifling place.
[MIKAGE]
You'll be fine.
Once the contract to make
you my familiar is sealed,
you'll be able
to live here with ease.
However, becoming a familiar
means that even what is dark
will be overcome with light.
It means that you will be
under the constraint of gods.
[KOTETSU]
I understand, Master Tomoe.
If you long for your mistress,
I will send you to her!
[KOTETSU]
Return to being a yokai!
[TAKEHAYA grunts]
[KOTETSU]
Even in this form,
though he may have
dissolved the contract,
Master Tomoe is still a loyal
familiar of the Mikage Shrine.
Curse that damnable fox!
Heh.
[NANAMI]
Netherworld gate, open!
[NANAMI] It didn't work?
Why not? What do I do?
[panting]
[HIOU]
Meow!
Kirihito, run as far
away as you can.
I'll act as a distraction
to keep them off your tail.
That won't work.
[NANAMI] It'll be okay. I still
have one white talisman left.
We'll be getting back
to the surface real soon.
Just hang in there for me, okay?
[AKURA-OH] One talisman?
What can she possibly do?
[AKURA-OH]
Damn it!
My head is spinning.
What is wrong with this body?
It kills me to back down,
but right now I need to return
to the surface and regroup.
However, it wasn't a total loss.
With her hair,
I can return as I please.
She's of no use to me now.
[NANAMI] We'll be getting
back to the surface real soon.
Just hang in there for me, okay?
[NANAMI]
The farther I get,
the more time I buy
for Kirihito's escape.
I have to be the one
to handle this.
I have to!
[HIOU]
Meow!
[gasps]
[HIOU]
Found you, meow!
[gasps]
[HIOU]
Too bright! [groans]
[NANAMI]
That light!
Huh?!
[TOMOE]
Nanami!
[NANAMI sighs]
Tomoe!
I missed you so much!
[NANAMI cries]
Are you well?
Yeah.
Thank goodness.
You had me so worried.
[NANAMI]
Tomoe. Tomoe!
[HIOU]
Meow. Meo--
[HIOU yelps]
Now, Nanami.
Why would you go so far
as to miss the Divine Assembly
to play around with a cat
in the Netherworld?
I am sure you have
a wonderful explanation.
[NANAMI] His hair's so long.
What's that about?
[AKURA-OH]
How I've missed you.
It's been a while, Tomoe.
[KOTETSU]
The sun'll be setting soon.
I sure hope Master Tomoe
was able to find Lady Nanami.
[KOTETSU]
Hm?
Hi, Kotetsu!
[KOTETSU]
Lady Nanami!
I am so glad you are safe!
[NANAMI] Same to you, Kotetsu.
Thank you for coming!
We're finally back. Just like
I promised you, Kirihito.
Whoa! What the heck do
you think you're doing?
I brought him with us
because he was there,
but I have no earthly
idea who this man is.
He appears to be human,
yet he lacks life.
'Tis as though he is dead.
If need be, I could always
return him to the Netherworld.
Uh!
[NANAMI snores]
Nanami, what is wrong?
[KOTETSU]
What happened to her?
[TOMOE]
She fell asleep.
[TOMOE gasps]
I'm curious, what is
this woman to you?
[KOTETSU]
Master Tomoe!
[TOMOE] So, is this the thanks
I get for saving you?
Hardly. To repay you in full
would cost much more,
but I have grown tired as well.
So let's call that
a down payment.
[MONJIRO]
So long!
[KIKUICHI]
Shikigami, eh? Hmph.
[KOTETSU] Master Tomoe,
who in the world was that man?
A paltry matter. Ignore him.
We are going the grand shrine.
I shall carry Nanami there.
[KOTETSU]
Yes, sir.
I'm curious, what is
this woman to you?
[KOTETSU] Master Tomoe?
What is the matter?
[TOMOE]
Nothing.
Nothing at all.
[NARRATOR] Nanami has returned
from the Netherworld.
Tomoe has returned
to being a yokai.
It's as though an invisible
wall now stands between them!
Although it may divide them,
the one thing it can't
stop are all the feels!
Next time, "The God Makes Her
Second Romantic Confession."
I'll say it as many
times as it takes!