[MIKAGE]
Tomoe believes that humans
are fleeting and
frail creatures.
Because of this, he fears
becoming involved with them.
I think you can teach him
that humans are not as weak
as he believes they may be.
My goal is to rekindle
Tomoe's bond with humanity.
To have him take
your hand, and not mine.
I want to give him the
opportunity to choose you.
Mikage!
But he still has
a long way to go.
Nanami, I want to know what
he said to you, please.
It wasn't anything important.
Just a little bit of small talk.
I see.
[MIKAGE]
They live for a very long while.
Their souls do not waver,
and they will never forget.
To fall in love with someone,
and to need that person,
is, in and of itself, a highly
risky proposition for yokai.
[NANAMI]
I'm human.
Which means I'm gonna die a
long time before Tomoe does.
I really do want him to love me,
but it seems so selfish now.
[NANAMI]
I don't get it, Mister Mikage.
Why would you want
Tomoe to choose me?
You shouldn't be so down,
Lady Nanami.
If you're having
trouble saying goodbye,
I'd be more than happy to give
you a reason to stay here.
It's not like you have
a busy social life.
No, but I still have school.
I guess there's no
changing your mind.
You did fulfill your jobs
marvelously, though.
You should go home with
your head held high, Nanami.
Lord Okuninushi, thank you,
that means a lot.
Now, then.
I was supposed to tell you
the location of Lord Mikage.
Sadly, I will have to
make that up to you
because I was
unable to find him.
Don't worry about it.
Hm? Do not worry? Why?
Have you given up
on looking for him?
You see, until Tomoe completely
ceases to need me in his life,
I have no intention
of seeing him.
For now.
By the way, I got
you a memento.
Seeing as you didn't take
any time to buy souvenirs,
I thought you could make use of
these special Izumo face wipes.
Maybe now you'll finally
rock some girl power.
[NANAMI] Actually, Tomoe and I
went out for a while yesterday.
[OKUNINUSHI]
Oh, good!
I'm sure you found
Izumo to be a fine city.
Speaking of fine,
having already completed all
of my important assignments,
it's time for me to do
some sightseeing too,
and by "sights", I mean ladies!
[WOMEN]
Oh, Lord Okuninushi!
[NARRATOR]
At least you can't say
he doesn't know
what his type is.
[OTOHIKO] You are absolutely
terrible, Lord Okuninushi!
Tell me what do those human
girls have that I don't?
[NANAMI] Wait, the girls he's
going out with are human?
You think I'm shallow?
Gods, humans, yokai, I love
them all! I should mention,
that is provided the being
I am loving is female.
I love all equally.
I will not choose.
Ah! Lord Okuninushi,
you're the greatest!
[NANAMI] Well in that case...
humans and yokai,
could they ever be
joined together?
Afraid not.
[OKUNINUSHI] Trust me,
a love like that is doomed
from the start.
The bonds are too fragile.
Even the strongest connections
will come undone,
depending upon whom
they are, of course.
[KOTETSU] What could be
bothering Lady Nanami?
She has seemed listless
since the banquet.
I assume she's
feeling worn out.
The other land gods
will be staying in Izumo
for another seven days.
I wish Nanami could have
enjoyed the hot springs
before the assembly ended.
Utter nonsense.
You speak as if leaving
the shrine unattended
is a small matter.
It would be if you'd
go home already!
Then I could help
Nanami enjoy herself!
Here is a better idea,
I will stay and you will go.
[roaring]
[NANAMI] Big surprise.
They're fighting again.
--[MIZUKI] Nanami,
--[TOMOE] We are leaving now!
--[MIZUKI] lets go take a bath!
--[TOMOE] Get in.
You guys go ahead.
I'll just catch up.
We'll meet back
at home later on.
[gasps]
[NANAMI]
I can't be close to Tomoe.
Not right now.
It's like a wall's between us,
and I can't get past it.
I know Nanami has already
booked a return flight home,
so I'm sure she'll
be fine by herself.
However, I'm kind of surprised
that you're actually letting her
stay somewhere so
far away from us.
That's not like you at all.
[NARRATOR] Meanwhile,
at the Mori residence.
[KIKUICHI] Uh-oh, looks
like someone is ticklish!
--[MONJIRO] No, stop!
--[AKURA-OH] Damn.
--[KIKUICHI] Tickle, tickle!
--[MONJIRO laughs]
[MONJIRO, KIKUICHI yelp]
[AKURA-OH] Cursed fox!
I'm going to kill him!
But I can't! Not yet.
So I'll kill you instead,
and then remake you!
[KIKUICHI] Please reconsider,
Master Kirihito!
[AKURA-OH gasps]
[KIKUICHI]
Master Kirihito!
[MONJIRO]
What's wrong with you, sir?
Nothing, I'm fine.
[AKURA-OH]
Tomoe.
[KIRIHITO'S MOTHER]
Kirihito, dear?
[gasps]
I'm coming in.
Where did he go?
[sighs] I bet Tomoe doesn't even
know why I wanted to be alone.
I wonder if he cared.
[HIMEMIKO]
Nanami!
[NANAMI]
Hm?
Himemiko!
[AOTAKE grunts]
What brings you all the
way out here to the city?
[HIMEMIKO]
Oh, some shopping.
[AOTAKE grunting]
[NANAMI] Hey. Looks like you've
got your hands full there,
Mister Masatake!
I'm Aotake!
How art thou? Didst thou
just return from Izumo?
Yeah. Just now.
I can't thank you enough for
being there when I took off.
It was nothing.
Where the hell's that pain in
the ass fox of yours, land god?
Have I not said, "do not speak
with thine mouth full," Aotake?
I'm on my own. 'S'all good.
[HIMEMIKO]
Huh...
Nanami.
[NANAMI gasps]
Wouldst thou go on
a date with me?
Date?
[AOTAKE muffled talking]
[AOTAKE grunts]
[HIMEMIKO] Deliver her bags
to the Mikage Shrine.
Let us go, Nanami.
Uh, sure.
[AOTAKE] Wait, what?
But Lady Himemiko!
Hello, welcome to our-- Oh!
Kota!
It's been a long time,
hasn't it, Kotaro?
Hi, Himemiko!
I would like my usual.
Sure. You got it,
anything for you.
Hey. I'm here, too, y'know.
[KOTARO] Manager!
I need the usual!
You come here a lot?
Yes. Quite often.
Things are still going
well between you two.
I'm so glad.
Nanami, did something
happen in Izumo? Tell me.
Huh?
I found something out.
The severity of our feelings is
different for humans and yokai.
You guys hold onto one love
in your hearts forever.
That's a long time
to be all alone.
Ever since I found
out, I know that...
I can't keep saying
frivolous things to Tomoe
like I did before.
[HIMEMIKO]
Thou art incorrect, Nanami.
Uh?
If thou dost not speak,
no one shall be happy.
[NANAMI]
Mm.
My darling Kota and
I are only together
because thou took action.
It has brought me such joy.
Your blessing allows us to
share these forbidden feelings.
'Tis true Kota's lifespan
differs greatly from mine own.
Our time is short,
which is precisely why
it is so dear to me.
Were that time wasted,
all that I would feel would
be despair and regret.
I will not. Dost
thou understand?
Yeah, I do.
You're right.
I don't want regrets.
[HIMEMIKO laughs]
[NANAMI]
The time we have is short.
I should cherish the moments
I have with Tomoe,
not push him away.
[NANAMI]
I get it now.
[NANAMI] I think I should
tell him that I love him.
[NANAMI]
I'm home!
[MIZUKI]
Oh! Welcome back, Lady Nanami!
[TOMOE]
You are late.
What manner of drivel
delayed you this time?
[MIZUKI] Don't mind him.
He's been impatiently awaiting
your return like
an abandoned little puppy.
[TOMOE]
Shut your mouth, snake!
[NANAMI giggles]
It's okay, Tomoe!
[AKURA-OH]
Yatori? It's not anyone I know.
A letter from
a third rate yokai.
How low have I truly sunk?
And he thinks he
can meet with me.
[KIKUICHI]
The unmitigated gall!
To simply write you
as if you were pen pals!
Please, Master, permit me
to research his past!
[AKURA-OH]
Ignore him.
He's just some punk
who isn't worth our time.
[MONJIRO]
Master Kirihito.
Can I eat my snack?
I don't want it getting cold!
I don't care.
[MONJIRO]
Hooray!
Oh! Those look good!
Do you think that I might
be able to try one?
[MONJIRO, KIKUICHI]
Ah!
How did you get in here?
[YATORI groans]
[YATORI]
Please forgive me!
[AKURA-OH]
Explain yourself!
[YATORI]
Right! Of course!
I'm Yatori. I hope
you got my letter.
[AKURA-OH]
Hmm.
[YATORI] The word on the street
is you are trying to revive
Master Akura-Oh from his
confinement in the Netherworld.
I am in favor of that!
Allow me to assist you in
his righteous restoration!
I would gladly go get
his body for you!
You would? Why?
[YATORI] A world under Master
Akura-Oh would be ideal.
Only he is worthy of ruling!
And I want to see
him return to power.
I have to admit,
I approve of your motives,
but can you make good
on your claims?
[AKURA-OH] So he hasn't
discovered my true identity.
How blissfully ignorant.
He asserts loyalty,
but there's no fire in his eyes.
What a joke.
Can you prove that you're
not all talk, Yatori?
I understand your apprehension.
Makes sense, but I have a plan
that's sure to blow you away!
To show you my dedication,
I plan to present
Master Akura-Oh
with the sacred
mountain of Kurama!
Then, once all the native
tengu are under my control,
I want to lead them
as an unstoppable army
under his command!
What do you think?
[AKURA-OH]
He must take me for a fool.
I'll be waiting to hear
the good news. Best of luck.
[AKURA-OH] However,
he may yet prove useful.
[YATORI]
Yes, sir! You'll see.
I'll go above and beyond
your expectations!
[YATORI] Those guys were
friendly, weren't they?
They even shared their
snacks with me.
[DEVIL MASK]
Don't be so naive.
I could tell right away.
No matter how much he pretends,
that human is Akura-Oh.
It's comical how easily
we snuck past his guard.
Oh, how the mighty have fallen.
And yet from a small seed
a mighty trunk might grow.
Sounds like it's time for
a new tree to take root.
[NANAMI] Hey, you remember
that Kirihito guy? Who is he?
He was so calm
in the Netherworld.
Y'know what I mean?
[TOMOE] I doubt that you
will ever see him again.
Yeah, but, the thing is,
I ran into him in town right
before I took off for Izumo.
[AMI]
Hey, Nanami!
I wanted to go to
Kurama's concert today,
so I totally won
a ticket for you, too!
[NANAMI]
Really?
[AMI]
Yup. I also got one for Kei,
but she says she has a date
tonight and can't come with.
How 'bout it, Tomoe?
We are so going!
Like hell!
[NANAMI]
We should totally go, Tomoe!
How many times must I tell
you no? My ears would bleed!
[KURAMA]
♪ Gleaming like stars ♪
But Kurama's really cool
when he's singing!
And I mean you're both yokai,
you should get some tips
from him, you know,
ask how he learned to blend
in with humans so well!
I said no!
Come on!
I'm just sayin',
it's gonna be a fun show!
[BOTANMARU groans]
[gasps]
[BOTANMARU]
Why'd ya step on me, lady?
I thought I was going
to pop just now!
I'm sorry! I didn't think
anyone would be sleeping
in the middle of the road!
Uh!
[TOMOE]
Huh?
I am trying to hear sounds
coming through the earth.
It's not time for a nap.
My name's Botanmaru
from Mount Kurama.
[NANAMI]
A little tengu? So cute!
Aw!
Why are you in the
mundane world, tengu?
[BOTANMARU]
I am looking for an older tengu.
He is the son of Master Sojobo
the Third. Master Shinjuro!
This is what he looked like when
he ran away to the mundane world
about seventeen years ago,
but his current whereabouts
are unknown. By now,
he should've grown to be
a fine specimen of a tengu,
such as you see here! Well?
Have you seen him anywhere?
No. Go fly to Mount Takao
and ask your fellow tengu.
[NANAMI]
Tomoe, don't! No!
Botanmaru!
You okay?
Are you hurt?
You mean old fox!
If I was bigger, I would
spank you for that! [cries]
What do we have here?
You cannot fly?
[BOTANMARU]
Uh...
[whimpers]
[NANAMI]
Wait! Don't leave!
Oh, ignore him.
[NANAMI]
No! I can't do that.
Go home without me, Tomoe.
And take care of Mamoru!
[MAMORU squeaks]
[NANAMI]
There you are!
Why don't you let me help you?
Tell me everything
you know about him.
We'll find Shinjuro together.
[SUIRO]
Botanmaru.
Botanmaru!
Do not tell me you
are crying, not again.
Did you receive another
beating from Jiro?
Here, let me see.
[BOTANMARU cries]
I hate myself, brother!
One of the kids that
was born last year
is already much taller than me.
I'm six years old, but my
wings are still so itty-bitty.
[SUIRO]
Shinjuro was like that, too.
[BOTANMARU]
Who is Shinjuro?
A child like you,
who grew too slowly,
but this particular
child was the son
of Master Sojobo the Third.
He was the first tengu
born in five hundred years,
and the elders judged
him harshly because of it.
He, too, received beatings from
Jiro, but Shinjuro never cried.
[gasps]
[SUIRO] He would always
sit atop that rock. Right there.
The very same where
you are now perched.
[BOTANMARU]
Mm. Uh?!
Can I meet him?
Where is he now?
[SUIRO]
I do not know.
He was badly injured
at the age of twelve.
So he descended the mountain,
and no one has seen him since.
[SUIRO]
You must grow strong, Botanmaru.
Enough have been lost already.
We do not wish to
lose you as well.
[BOTANMARU]
They told me that tengu
who go down the mountain
are worthless failures,
but I do not believe that.
Normally, tengu become
grownups in just eight years.
But then, there are others like
me who do not grow as fast.
I am seven years old,
and I cannot even fly.
Master Shinjuro must
have felt really sad
back when he was my size, too.
I want to meet him and see the
tengu he became when he grew up.
You see? I have to.
[NANAMI sobs]
[BOTANMARU]
What is wrong?
Your life's been so hard,
and you're only seven!
I promise we'll find
Mister Shinjuro!
Don't worry, 'kay?
I'm positive that he's grown
into an awesome tengu
for you to look up to.
Just you wait and see.
I know he has.
[gasps]
Look! Up there! We found him!
Uh?
[gasps]
No way.
I knew it!
The picture they gave me
looks exactly like him!
He is here!
[NANAMI]
No, no, no, no!
No!
[NANAMI groans]
[NANAMI]
It's Kurama?!
[GIRLS scream]
♪ Gleaming like stars
against the midnight sky ♪
♪ With wings of deceit, in the
embrace of joyous rapture, ♪
♪ I fall into delirium! ♪
--[GIRLS scream]
--[KURAMA] ♪ Glorious! ♪
--[AMI laughs]
--♪ All is within my grasp ♪
[KURAMA]
♪ This world will be mine ♪
♪ Kiss you. Kiss me. Paradise! ♪
[GIRLS screams]
[screaming continues]
Shadow Die.
[GIRLS scream]
It really is him.
I found Master Shinjuro.
For my next number,
how'd you like a brand new
song I wrote just for today?
I call it:
Wings Fling Hazard.
[GIRLS scream]
[piano plays]
♪ This one, final wish,
that's all I'm asking for, ♪
♪ One chance, one simple moment,
where no one's keeping score, ♪
♪ A spool of red-black thread, ♪
♪ to stitch my wings
so they can spread. ♪
♪ And fly away, oh baby,
fly away once more. ♪
♪ Every night, yeah, every
night my heart breaks ♪
♪ Drownin' in darkness
and pain. ♪
♪ Waiting to soar above the
pettiness, and bitter tears. ♪
♪ On wings fanned out
like a raven's in the rain. ♪
So the guitar's just a prop?
♪ Oh-oh-oh! ♪
♪ High in the sky,
I'm persuaded ♪
♪ These wings are made for
bringing forth my destiny! ♪
♪ Hope stays alive, even though
the dream is faded. ♪
♪ My heart is free. To make
this plea: Take me home. ♪
I'll be back.
Wait for me.
This place, it's all I've got.
Or fly with me.
Don't be afraid, baby.
[KURAMA]
I'll only bite if you want.
[NARRATOR] Who'd've thought
Kurama was Sojobo's son?
With his old home is
in a state of crisis,
Kurama makes his long
awaited return!
Nanami and Tomoe join him up
the mountain, but along the way,
they become enveloped
in a suspicious fog?
Next time,
"The God Goes to Mount Kurama"
I'll only bite if you want.