Ah! I feel alive again!
After not eating or drinking
anything for two days,
this rice porridge is
like a dream come true!
I'm so glad you made
arrangements for me
to have a room while
I was gone, Mizuki.
It's killing me. I was the
one here to accompany you,
but I couldn't even manage to
come to the rescue when you
were in danger and needed me.
Oh, please, grind this hopeless
waste-of-a-familiar under
your boot forever and ever!
Stop being dramatic.
Where's Tomoe?
He carried me here, so he's
still gotta be in Izumo.
Where is he?
Uh! Maybe out for a walk?
Cool. This is crazy, I know
it's only been a couple days,
but I feel like it's
been an entire month.
[NANAMI grunts]
Mizuki! What day of the
Divine Assembly is this?
[MIZUKI]
It's uh...
[OKUNINUSHI] It's the
fourth day, Lady Nanami!
[MAMORU, NANAMI, MIZUKI groan]
I grew tired of waiting,
so I had to come to you.
You did rather well to return to
the great Okuninushi only one
day late, my darling little
girl. Just as I expected.
[NANAMI] Okuninushi!
He brought a throne?
--[MIZUKI groans]
--[NANAMI] Ow!
Of course, I have already
heard about your deeds
in the Netherworld, dear.
In fact, the phone at my desk
has been ringing off the hook
with complaint after complaint.
Ah! I'm so sorry!
All is well.
And, Poof! I can't tell
you how happy I am
to have my missing Lucky
Mallet returned to me.
I will overlook your
tardiness as a thank you.
However, Tomoe's actions upon
using the Lucky Mallet to reduce
himself to a yokai were
deeply reprehensible.
He'll be kept in the
east prison for now.
[NANAMI gasps]
[OKUNINUSHI] Leave it to
me to deal with Tomoe.
You must now devote
yourself to your duties
at the Divine Assembly.
What?
[MIZUKI gasps]
He's in prison? Why would you
wanna go and put him in there?
[OKUNINUSHI]
He is no longer a familiar.
With the bonds of the contract
undone, he has reverted to
a dangerous wild fox.
I can't allow him to run loose.
[NANAMI grunts]
[OKUNINUSHI] Do you mean to go
see the wild fox, Lady Nanami?
I must say I would
advise you against it.
[MIZUKI] I think she's
too far away to hear you.
[KOTETSU] This breaks
my heart, Master Tomoe.
To be locked away
in a place like this.
[TOMOE] You need not waste your
sympathies on me, Kotetsu.
Besides, these tight bonds
are sadly necessary.
When I was a familiar, I was
able to exercise self-control,
but I find that difficult now.
[TOMOE] I believed it was
because I was a familiar that
--I protected her, but...
[NANAMI] Tomoe!
[KOTETSU]
Lady Nanami!
Kotetsu. [gasps]
Tomoe!
Okuninushi told me you were
being kept in the prison.
Are you okay? They haven't
done anything to you, have they?
What happened to your hand?
It looks like you've been hurt!
[TOMOE] Why are you here during
the middle of the Assembly?
You are wasting your time.
Uh... I am not, I came to
make you a familiar again.
I kinda figured you
didn't wanna be stuck
in this place forever.
[TOMOE]
'Tis not your business.
I shall be the one to make
decisions regarding my future.
[NANAMI gasps]
Allow me a bit of time
to consider becoming
your familiar again, please.
I understand.
Well, the least I can do is
try to talk to Okuninushi.
Maybe I can convince him to
let you out of this place.
[door slams]
Oh, no.
I have been looking for you
everywhere, Lady Nanami!
The fourth day of the Divine
Assembly is about to begin!
[NANAMI]
I wonder...
Did Tomoe ever think
being a familiar was hard?
Did he feel he had no choice
but to put up with it?
If that's true,
then I should probably think
this out some more, too.
That way I can be sure I'll be
fine if Tomoe decides to leave.
[NANAMI] Other than keeping
myself from begging him to stay,
I don't know what else
I can do for him.
This is so hard.
Please excuse me.
The matchmaking talisman.
[groaning]
[screams] He's been killed?!
Oh War God, no!
[MAMORI]
Not to worry.
[NANAMI]
Huh?
The War God is recovering from
his wounds at the moment.
He's been given the Peach
Pill, a miracle cure.
It will heal any wound.
[gasps]
Would you mind sharing a little
of that medicine with me, too?
Please?
[MAMORI]
In exchange for what?
You weren't expecting to
get it for free, were you?
Uh, yeah?
How about the legendary limited
edition sweet potato donut?
It's a deluxe peach flavored
one! Doesn't that sound yummy?
[MAMORI]
Uh! Peach sweet potato donut?
[NANAMI]
For Tomoe...
I found something I can do.
[MIZUKI]
Hello?
Well, it seems the fox
is still in a cage.
How long are you
gonna stay in here?
How did you manage to get in?
I crawled!
Then crawl away.
I wish to be alone.
I heard that you might not
wanna be a familiar anymore.
It made Lady Nanami very sad.
I'd rather you didn't cause
my lady and mistress
too much grief.
When I was a familiar,
if she was smiling,
I immediately felt reassured.
I always kept track
of her whereabouts,
and rushed to her
if she needed me.
No matter how far away
Nanami might have been,
there was not a day when
I did not think of her.
That was surely because
I was a familiar.
'Tis the contract between a
god and a familiar, right?
However, our contract
is now broken,
and my being is no longer under
the constraint of any god.
And yet,
she is merely a human girl,
why am I so consumed by her?
What is Nanami to me?
Um, your contract
and being a familiar
have nothing
to do with it.
Face it. She's just
a girl that you like.
[TOMOE gasps]
Now that the big
mystery is solved,
here you go. A parting
gift from Lady Nanami.
The Lord Mamori's Peach Pills.
She asked me to
give them to you.
[NANAMI]
He may choose a different path,
but I don't want things
to be difficult for him.
And he has a lot of enemies,
so at the very least,
I want Tomoe to have something
that will keep him safe.
[TOMOE]
I cannot accept such a thing.
How could I have
feelings for Nanami?
One touch, and I shall know
the truth. Do I desire her?
This maiden?
Tomoe.
[gasps]
Please don't leave.
[NANAMI, MAMORU snore]
[TOMOE]
So it is true.
I have feelings for Nanami.
[NARRATOR]
Tomoe's verdict is in!
Extenuating circumstances!
What a relief!
I'm so happy you're back
to being a familiar!
Oh, I knew it,
you really did come into my
room last night, didn't you?
You were awake, then?
Nope. I dreamed about it.
And um, in the dream you
kinda, sorta kissed me.
--[NANAMI groans]
--Never mind that,
you must eat, now!
Breakfast is rice porridge
with your favorite, shiitake!
Ah!
I made sure to tell the cook
that shiitake mushrooms are your
absolute most favorite
food in the world.
Lies! You are such a jerk!
[TOMOE]
This is a problem.
When Nanami's cheeks begin
to blush as she speaks of her
feelings for me, I cannot help
but want to be cruel to her.
[MIZUKI] Hey Nanami. Is it
all right if I start sleeping
in your room tonight, please?
What?
Well, back when I used
to serve Lady Yonomori,
she always let me
sleep by her side.
Sure thing!
He may not.
[MIZUKI] I wasn't asking you,
and there's plenty of room.
He's right. I don't see
what the big issue is.
[TOMOE] Familiars have
their own sleeping chamber.
Observe the rules.
I know, what about if you
slept in there with us, too?
All three of us!
[cup shatters]
I said no, and that
is the end of it.
[sighs]
[NANAMI] Tomoe's in
such a bad mood today.
I wonder if he didn't really
want to become a familiar again.
--[crash]
--[NANAMI gasps]
Ah! Oh no! Are you all right?
[FUMIGAE GODS]
Eh?
I have not slept very much
in the past few days
thanks to my matchmaking work.
[ALL]
That's a lie!
There are so many of them.
If you'll let me,
I could help you out.
But don't you have
your own work to do?
Not a problem.
I only have thirty parishioners,
so I'll be done in a flash.
[laughs]
[FUMIGAE GOD A]
Inaho.
Why do you sleep every year,
knowing this will happen?
[KOTETSU]
This incident,
charging you to feed the
carp and calling it water
under the bridge? The Lord
Okuninushi is most magnanimous.
[NANAMI]
Tomoe!
They're finally allowing
me to take a little break!
What'll it be, you
wanna go shopping?
[NANAMI] I've been in the world
of the gods ever since I got
here, so I haven't had time to
go sightseeing in Izumo at all.
[gasps] The Grand Shrine
here in the mundane
world is super busy, too.
[TOMOE] The Gods in Residence
Festival is right now.
[claping]
[NANMI]
We're in the same place,
but everything's different.
It's kind of magical.
The mundane world.
I love this place!
It's so funny being here,
visiting a matchmaking shrine,
and now we're having lunch.
It's almost like we're on
a date. How crazy is that?
[TOMOE]
Nanami.
Do you still care for me?
What?
I... Well, of course.
[TOMOE] Oh. It is different
from before, though.
I see.
But, it's okay.
I get this is one sided.
You don't have the same
kind of feelings for me,
and that's totally fine.
I won't freak out on you
because I think I can
change how you feel,
and you don't have
to freak out on me.
[grunts]
I can just pour this
into the other-- Ah!
Excuse me, sorry
about that, dear.
Gross! I smell like
soba broth, now!
I knew I should've washed my
other one. How bad do you think
it would be to show up to the
Divine Assembly in a tee shirt?
[TOMOE]
Hell if I know. You realize,
this situation is exactly why I
tell you always be prepared.
Panicking does not
help, either, so, uh!
[TOMOE gasps]
What are you doing?
I'm changing.
There's a camisole underneath.
I could wear this all by itself.
What female in their right
mind starts undressing
in front of a man?
Have a little modesty!
[NANAMI gasps]
Gah. You don't have to yell
at me about it, you know.
What's your deal?
You've seen me in camis around
the shrine plenty of times!
You've been acting
like a jerk all day!
And that is completely
your doing!
Think about it, this morning,
you spoke of sleeping in the
same room with the damned snake.
You lack discretion,
what if he were to jump
you as he did before?
Yeah, and what if you
didn't worry so much?
Besides, that's why I said you
could sleep with us, too!
Enough of this already!
Do you honestly still have
so-called feelings for me?
[gasps]
[TOMOE] If you are content
to merely speak of being
in love and whatnot, go recite
it to a wall on your own!
[NANAMI cries] What is it?
Why are you mad, Tomoe?
I don't understand what I did,
or why you're so upset.
Please explain it to me. [cries]
Whatever I did, I promise
to never do it again!
[cries]
I'm very sorry, Nanami.
I was unbelievably wrong. Please
do not let this concern you.
Here, you will catch a cold if
you remain in this wet shirt.
I will remove it for you.
[NANAMI gasps]
[NANAMI shrieks]
No! I can do it by myself!
You do not have to, though.
'Tis a familiar's duty to look
after his lady and mistress.
What is wrong?
You are wearing a cami-whatever
underneath, so you do not mind.
Am I not correct?
[NANAMI gasps]
And tonight, per your request,
I will stay by your
side the entire evening.
I am a familiar, so there should
be nothing wrong with that.
Well, Nanami?
[gasps]
Do you still think this is okay?
[NANAMI]
Go to hell, Tomoe!
Why do you think that
foxes don't consider
possible consequences, Tomoe?
Oh. This isn't about
you, by the way,
it's about this friend I
have who's also a fox.
Excuse me.
You can listen to me gripe
without falling asleep.
[TOMOE]
Touching her, I can tell.
--The sweet warmth of her body.
--[MIZUKI griping]
[NARRATOR] Day Seven
of the Divine Assembly.
At long last,
we're at the end.
[NANAMI] There! I've finished a
hundred of them, Lady Inaho.
[INAHO snores]
She hasn't gotten a single
person done since two hours ago!
We did try to warn you.
Nomi was the one who fell
victim to her last year.
[NANAMI]
Ugh.
Hey! What's up? I decided
to get you a souvenir
for probably getting
all your work done.
Thanks, but what
about your work?
Oh, honey, I've been
done a while.
Once you finish, you
gotta go have fun, quick.
Otherwise you get stuck doing
the work of other gods, too.
What a joke, am I right?
[NANAMI] Crap, that's exactly
the situation I'm in.
How's the Divine
Assembly been for you?
Tell me that you at
least learned a few things.
Yeah. It's been incredible.
A person's destiny
is one thread.
And that single destiny is
linked together with other
people's destinies.
That's right. They intertwine
and create bonds.
All things are linked from
the past to the present day.
There are steps leading to
every encounter one will have.
Which means that even you
talking to me right now is
the result of something
that's been long in the making.
Come on, today is finally the
last day of the Divine Assembly.
Let's finish up our
work beautifully,
and have a well-deserved
drink at the banquet!
[INAHO sighs]
[FUMIGAE GODS gasp]
She has risen!
[NANAMI] I hope I managed
to fulfill your duties
the way you would
have, Mister Mikage.
[NANAMI]
I think I'm ready!
Otohiko got me this to
wear at the banquet,
but I'm not sure
I've done it right.
How does it look? The sash
was super complicated.
[MIZUKI]
Hmm, it's a bit big on you.
[TOMOE]
Incompetent.
[MIZUKI, NANAMI grunt]
You cannot attend the
banquet looking like that.
I will dress you. Strip.
[NANAMI gulps]
[TOMOE]
Uh!
No. I'll just ask
Lady Inaho for help.
You realize you're an idiot,
don't you? So, how does it feel?
I'm curious to know
what that's like.
You have been awfully
belligerent of late, Snake.
Yeah, well, it's because
I don't find this funny.
The last thing I want is to lose
the lady and mistress that I've
finally found. Don't get
carried away and elope
with her or anything, okay?
Do not worry about such
nonsense. I have no intention
of ever involving myself
with a mere human.
A-ha...
[NARRATOR] The Divine Assembly
has safely come to a close,
and tonight will be their
last evening at Izumo.
[NANAMI]
This is amazing!
It's a grand gathering
of the gods!
Everyone looks like
they're having fun!
Maybe I should let
my hair down, too.
Oh, you should!
You must be so exhausted.
I wouldn't mind
being your escort!
[OTOHIKO]
Hello, darling!
[NANAMI, MIZUKI]
Hm?
[OTOHIKO]
You're like a doll in that!
Otohiko! Thank you
for the kimono!
You're welcome!
And what a relief,
after all those tacky
clothes you wore every day,
I thought you were
just a lost cause!
[NANAMI]
Uh...
[RABBIT SERVANT]
Lady Human Goddess,
your hard work in carrying out
your duties is appreciated.
Sake? Oh, I don't know.
[RABBIT SERVANT] It is a sake
cup from the Lord Okuninushi.
Go on. You must drink.
[NANAMI]
I don't wanna be rude.
[TOMOE]
Nanami cannot drink yet.
I shall have it instead.
What is wrong?
Be a lush, why don't ya?
[MIZUKI] I genuinely
wish Tomoe would die.
Why? What did I do?
Nothing at all! I just want
something to drink, too.
[NANAMI gasps]
[NANAMI]
It's here.
The butterfly.
[NANAMI] In the darkness, you
were the one that guided me.
[NANAMI]
I was right. It was you.
[MIKAGE] Hello. We meet
again, Miss Nanami.
[panting] Hello.
Thank you very much for helping
me out of the darkness...
[NANAMI]
...Mister Mikage.
Your efforts here are
appreciated.
You're a whole different person
compared to a week ago.
You did great work, Miss Nanami.
[gasps]
[NANAMI]
Nothing could make me happier
than hearing you say that.
[MIKAGE] I'm grateful to you
for being good to Tomoe.
Thank you. Please keep
looking after him for me.
Oh. Does that mean you're
not going to see Tomoe?
He won't say it in
so many words,
but he would like to see
you, Mister Mikage.
I can't do that yet.
[gasps]
[MIKAGE]
If I were to visit Tomoe now,
my twenty years of absence
would go to waste.
Until he completely
ceases to need me,
I have no intention
of seeing him.
[NANAMI
Uh...
Do you know why it is
that love between humans and
yokai is considered taboo?
No, I don't.
[MIKAGE] The reason humans
can fall in love over and over
is because their hearts
change with time.
The human lifespan is
so short they do not have
the opportunity to become
bogged down by one attachment.
But it is different
for the yokai kind.
They live for a very long while.
Their souls do not waver,
and they never forget.
They can endure
with the same love
in their hearts
for centuries.
And so, their feelings will not
change without good reason.
There are many who grow old
without ever loving another.
To fall in love with someone,
and to need that person
is a highly risky proposition
for the yokai.
That was certainly
true for Tomoe.
Mm. Of course.
You must be talking about
the woman named Yukiji.
Yes. Tomoe has quite a bit of
history behind him as well.
I've used my powers to make him
forget his past temporarily,
but I'm sure you understand
that things can't remain
this way forever.
[NANAMI] Then, why did you
bring Tomoe and me together?
[MIKAGE]
Tomoe believes that humans
are fleeting and
frail creatures.
Because of this, he fears
becoming involved with them.
[TOMOE gasps]
[MIKAGE] I think you can teach
him that humans are not as
weak as he believes they may be.
My goal is to rekindle
Tomoe's bond with humanity.
To have him take
your hand and not mine.
I want to give him the
opportunity to choose you.
Mikage!
[gasps]
But, he still has
a long way to go.
[NARRATOR] With the
Divine Assembly over,
Nanami agonizes over
her love for Tomoe.
That's when Himemiko invites
her over for a girls' day thing,
to go do girls' day thing stuff.
This kid she ends
up stepping on.
What the what, he's got wings?!
Next time, "The God
Meets a Little Tengu".
Wing Fling Hazard!