[YOKAI A laughs]
[YOKAI A]
Oh, yes. I know you.
You're those bastards
who've been trying
to make a power grab.
Akura-oh and Tomoe.
Why don't you show us
what you've got?
[AKURA-OH]
Why not?
We have time to kill, so we
might as well indulge you.
[TOMOE chuckles]
[YOKAI A yells]
[YOKAI A groans]
[YOKAI C growls]
[TOMOE] Should have
left well enough alone!
[YOKAI B screams]
Heh. Nicely done.
Tomoe?
Tomoe!
[birds chirp]
Tomoe.
[ONIKIRI] Ah, peaceful,
is it not, Kotetsu?
[KOTETSU]
Indeed, it is, Onikiri.
[ONIKIRI]
I believe Lady Nanami
has grown more aware of her role
as the land god of the Mikage
Shrine, for she has been
busily practicing
using white talismans.
[KOTETSU]
That is gratifying to hear.
The Mikage Shrine
should be secure now.
Your food grows cold, Nanami!
How late do you intend to sleep?
[NANAMI snores]
--[TOMOE] Wake up!
--[NANAMI screams]
[ONIKIRI, KOTETSU]
So peaceful.
[slurping]
[NANAMI]
Oh, no!
I was writing white talismans,
and I fell asleep!
Why were you writing so many?!
[MIZUKI] And why such
bizarre subject matter?
No! I'm gonna be late!
[NARRATOR] Nanami Momozono,
high school girl.
When her father
ran away from home
and left Nanami without
a place to live,
she found her way to the park,
where she meet a land
god named Mikage.
He decided to dump that
whole god thing on her,
and told Nanami to be
the new master of his shrine.
Along with Tomoe and Mizuki,
who serve their
land god as familiars,
and Onikiri and Kotetsu,
the will-o'-the-wisp
shrine spirit attendants,
Nanami came to live
the life of a god.
But there was just one problem.
[TOMOE] The new term starts
tomorrow, you hasty fool.
[MIZUKI laughs]
[NARRATOR]
The problem?
She had fallen in love
with her familiar, Tomoe.
I think I'm just gonna
stay here all day.
[gasping]
What is going on with me?
I can't sleep,
I'm a nervous wreck!
[MIZUKI]
Oh, a butterfly.
Do you think that
might be Lord Mikage?
His avatar is a butterfly.
Avatar?
Each god has the ability to
dwell in a particular vessel.
Lady Yonomori's avatar
was plum blossoms.
Lord Mikage,
has a butterfly.
[NANAMI]
Tomoe.
I wonder...
Does he miss Mister Mikage?
Hey, girl, what's up?
Long time no see!
[NANAMI groans]
[NANAMI]
You're the he-she guy!
Who are you calling
a he-she guy?
[NARRATOR]
He is the wind god, Otohikogami.
Exactly, thank you.
I haven't seen you
since the kagura dance.
Yes, your festival.
I watched you dance, you know.
It wasn't awful, per se, but I
can't give you passing marks.
At least not yet, sweetie pie.
[NANAMI]
Hm?
[TOMOE] You are being
circuitous,  Lord Otohiko.
Are you not here to simply
deliver the summons from Izumo?
Indeed, I am!
I've missed you,
my darling Tomoe!
[NANAMI yells]
[ONIKIRI, KOTETSU]
Okay, clink.
[OTOHIKO] Every year,
for one week in October,
gods from all across the country
gather at Izumo for a meeting.
With Mikage gone, there's
one seat currently open.
Funny story.
We all got to chatting
about inviting you,
the great unfortunate successor,
but, the problem is,
even as a human god,
you're lacking in skills.
Whether we like it or not,
though, you are presently
the land god of the Mikage
Shrine, so you can come.
Of course, you have
to pass a test first,
but such is the life of
a whatever you are.
We're talking the
Divine Assembly, here.
And it is divine.
Try not to screw it up, honey
this is a huge deal for you.
Now, shall we discuss this test?
No, because I'm not going.
What did you say?!
First of all, no one asked me,
second of all, you're a jerk,
and third of all, I'm not going!
You sure that's
the wisest choice?
Gods from all across
the country gather
at the Divine Assembly in Izumo.
There's a decent chance
one of those deities might
know the whereabouts of Mikage.
--[NANAMI] What?
--[OTOHIKO] Later, doll!
Is that true?
There is no need for
you to go to Izumo.
Nor is there any need to
know Mikage's whereabouts.
Hey, Nanami! Check it out!
Kei and I got these adorable
matching phone cases!
Oh, I love them!
--[NANAMI gasps]
--Momozono!
First day of the new term,
and you're already here!
Do not touch her so familiarly.
[ISOBE groans] I just got
the craziest déjà vu!
Are you all right, Nanami?
Oh, yeah.
[NANAMI]
Tomoe.
What if he does
miss Mister Mikage,
and he's just trying
to hide his feelings?
Hey he-she guy!
Where are you?
--[OTOHIKO] Wind god, Otohiko!
--[NANAMI screams]
Why can you not remember that?
[OTOHIKO]
Hmm?
So you want to go, then?
And you're ready for the test.
--Color me not surprised.
-- [NANAMI] Hurry up!
Give the test. He-she guy.
Shut up!
The test is this.
You must raise a shikigami.
You want me to raise
one of those?
[OTOHIKO]
This is a shikigami egg.
It grows rapidly,
drawing sustenance
from its keeper's chi.
Until the tiny darling safely
hatches seven days from now,
keep it with you at all times.
If you can successfully raise
a shikigami to my liking,
then you shall pass.
[NANAMI]
Um, I have a question.
[OTOHIKO]
Hm?
What's a shikigami?
[OTOHIKO]
I cannot even.
You're supposed to be
a land god, look it up,
and figure it out!
[NANAMI]
This is a shikigami egg,
and I just have
to get it to hatch.
Easy enough.
I can totally do that.
[NANAMI]
Probably.
"A shikigami is...
...power from the spirit world,
converted into a physical form,
allowing it to act
upon things in this world."
Hm. Yeah, I still
don't get it at all.
The one who does
not get it is me.
I remember telling you there
is no need to go to Izumo!
And I remember not asking you!
You must return that egg!
No way! I do what I want!
Guess what, Nanami?
We got two worshippers today!
[crack]
[NANAMI gasps]
Shikigami!
--Oh, no!
--[MIZUKI cries]
It's only the first day,
and my egg got cracked!
[TOMOE]
Calm down.
--Mizuki did not mean anything
--[MIZUKI cries]
by it, try not to hurt his
poor, poor feelings.
[cracks]
[ALL gasp]
Whoa.
Uh, is this thingie being born?
[squeaks]
[MIZUKI, TOMOE, NANAMI gasp]
Oh, wow, a baby monkey.
That's weird.
An unfinished brute.
It has hatched too soon.
You are not likely to pass
Otohiko's test with it.
You should give up.
[NANAMI]
It hatched early, so what?
It'll be fine.
[TOMOE]
Do not run, Nanami!
[NANAMI] Like I have a choice,
we missed the bus!
Can you move a little faster?
Why did you bring
that monkey with you?
Oh!
I know it hatched, but I
still have seven days to go.
Otohiko told me shikigamis
draw all of their
sustenance from your chi.
If I'm careful raising you,
I bet you'll grow up
to be a great shikigami!
[monkey sighs]
[NANAMI gasps]
This tiny vermin?
No matter how you raise it,
I doubt it will be much use.
[monkey grunts]
I really don't care if
it'll be "much use" or not,
this little one needs
me to survive,
and that's all that matters!
I'm good as long as
it grows up healthy.
[monkey cooing]
I am the one who shall
be of use to you.
Huh?
I'm yours.
I shall be the one
of use to you.
[TOMOE gasps]
True!
That's true.
Great, so, we better hurry.
We don't wanna be late!
[TOMOE]
That is... true.
My own words shock me.
What the hell was that?
I am utterly thrown.
[TOMOE] I am yours.
I am yours. I am yours.
What's up with her?
She's in a puddle of smiling.
[NARRATOR]
Technically, Nanami's research
at the library was still
related to the shikigami.
[OTOHIKO]
Little girl.
[NANAMI]
Huh?
He-she-guy!
Stop calling me that!
Honey, tell me you've
heard the news.
[NANAMI]
Huh?
There is some major jealousy
targeting a human god
determined to go to Izumo.
[NANAMI]
Huh?
Oh, what ever will you do?
What?
[OTOHIKO]
Hang in there, presh!
Hold on!
[NANAMI gasps]
[TSUCHIGUMO hisses]
[TOMOE gasps]
Yo, yo, yo! Momozono's
not here today?
[ISOBE yelps]
[TSUCHIGUMO hisses]
'Kay. Can't just stand here.
[TSUCHIGUMO growls]
[NANAMI screams]
[NANAMI whimpers]
Tomoe?
How are you, Nanami?
Unharmed?
Yeah.
[TOMOE]
I am yours.
I shall be the one
of use to you.
[NANAMI]
Why?
Always.
I'm just being protected.
If this is the shape I'm in,
I can't go to Izumo.
[cooing]
[huffs]
What is wrong with you? Why
are you raring to go so early?
I need to get my divine
power built up, so, look.
I need you to stop fussing
over me for a little while.
Are you still planning
to go to Izumo?
Yes, of course I am!
If you attend as
helpless as you are,
you shall only be humiliated!
Which is the point of what
I said, I'm serious here!
Stop always fussing over me!
[gasps]
Why are you guys
always so mean?
You didn't wait for me at all,
and you know that I'm
going to school, too!
[TOMOE]
Fine, do what you want!
But do not look to me if
another yokai shows up!
[NANAMI]
Fine, I will, and I won't!
[MIZUKI] What should I do?
The shivers just won't stop.
[NARRATOR]
Mizuki's a dirty bird.
Morning, everyone!
Oh, cool. I'm the first
one here today.
Yay! Ami's number one!
Uh?
That tsuchigumo may be loitering
about the school again.
Oh, not to worry.
I anticipated as much,
and brought with me some white
talismans I made yesterday.
[TOMOE sighs]
[NANAMI] Wow. Thanks for
the vote of confidence.
My divine power has gone up
a lot compared to before.
It better have.
[AMI screams]
Nanami, help!
--[AMI] Hurry!
--[NANAMI] Ami?
It showed up out of
nowhere! I saw a yokai!
What?
[AMI]
Wait. It's not here.
I swear I saw it!
I believe you, Ami.
You don't have to
be scared, though.
Take this, it's a
talisman against evil.
--[TOMOE] Nanami, we must talk.
--[AMI] Wow! A talisman!
[AMI]
That is so, neat!
[TOMOE]
This is exactly as I feared.
It is tsuchigumo miasma.
You are not strong enough.
Yes, I am. Purification is
the job of a land god, silly.
I'm going.
[TOMOE]
Rely upon me.
No, I can't.
Please, stay out of this.
[NANAMI] Poor tree,
the miasma made it wither away.
See?
Told ya. I can do it.
I'm getting better.
[NANAMI] The source of
the miasma is coming from
where the tsuchigumo vanished.
[AMI]
Nanami.
Hey, what's up?
Will you be okay?
I'm really worried.
Mm-hm. I'll be just fine, but I
want you to stay here for me.
I'll be right back!
'Kay. Be careful, though.
[NANAMI]
This devastation is awful.
Nothing has changed
since yesterday.
That should do it.
[TSUCHIGUMO] I am not one
to trifle with, child.
[NANAMI gasps]
[TSUCHIGUMO] After living
over a hundred years,
such a trinket will
not work on me!
[NANAMI screams]
Nanami? You all right?
[AMI screams]
--[TSUCHIGUMO] Yes! Delicious.
--[NANAMI] Stop!
I am restored. My strength
is coming back to me!
[NANAMI]
Stop it! Let go of me!
[TOMOE grunts]
[NANAMI gasps]
No. You stinking wretch!
Come out! I shall
tear you to pieces.
[TOMOE]
Damn! Where did it go?
Has it grown from
feeding on Nanami?
[TOMOE] The darkness is
spreading. I must find it soon.
[gasps]
[NANAMI]
What? Where am I?
The nurse's office?
[NANAMI]
I don't remember anything.
Except the warmth of Tomoe
as he was holding me.
[NANAMI]
That was terrifying.
[TOMOE] The darkness has
soaked into my hands,
it cannot be washed off.
[MIKAGE]
What happened to you?
You're covered in blood.
[MIKAGE] Come with me.
Let's get you washed up.
It'll be okay.
You're already clean.
[TOMOE]
I was in a rather terrible state
when I first met Mikage, too.
But, I do not recall back then
why I was covered in blood.
[TOMOE gasps]
[gasps] Where'd Ami go?
[AMI]
Ami's right here.
[NANAMI gasps]
I'm glad you're okay.
That was scary.
What happened?
I got swallowed up by that
black thing in the library.
I feel fine, now, though!
All it did was make
me feel kinda sick.
The doctor said I'll get
better if I just lay down,
and take it easy
on myself for a bit.
How are you so full
of energy, Nanami?
Although, mediums
must be used to this.
[NANAMI]
Ami...
I'm sorry the
talisman didn't work.
[OTOHIKO]
You should be ashamed!
[NANAMI gasps]
Three days since
the test started,
and look at this disaster.
You hatch the egg and then
do this to the shikigami?
You're going to demolish
my reputation! [cries]
You! Why are you here?
I told you that
this precious thing
draws sustenance from your chi!
The vile miasma it absorbed
has made it unbelievably sick!
Mass-producing your
cheap talismans
is preventing it from healing!
And the same goes for
that poor girl lying there.
If you're going to
get them involved,
at least be capable of
taking responsibility for it.
Who knows what would've happened
if Tomoe hadn't come along?
I'm sorry. I can go
try some more!
[NANANMI screams]
You need to stop
talismanning, honey.
If you tried now,
you'd only make scribbles
and waste more chi.
But, that's my only skill.
Writing talismans
is all I can do!
[OTOHIKO]
Yes, I'm aware.
Which is why I want you to
think of Cutie as a talisman.
And just like what
you write down,
make sure you give
this shikigami a name.
The name will become
its ability,
and will allow it to
carry out your wish.
Tell me, what is the
power you most desire?
A power.
I dunno, what do I desire?
[TOMOE]
How many of them are there?
The smell of blood
will not go away.
I may not be able
to purify them,
but I can drag every last
one of them into the open.
[NANAMI]
Mamoru!
[coos]
To keep anyone
from getting hurt,
and to keep anyone
from having to be scared,
I think I wanna
call him Mamoru.
Oh.
So it's a boy.
[gasping]
[MAMORU]
Meep!
Hey, where are you going?
He knows what his job is now,
because he finally
received a name.
You're the caster, babe.
Take some ownership.
Time to do your thing.
[NANAMI gasps]
[NANAMI]
Mamoru.
There's a trail of golden light
coming from under his feet.
It's clean!
He's cleaning everything!
[TOMOE grunts]
[TOMOE grunting]
[NANAMI]
Tomoe!
[MIKAGE]
Come with me.
[gasps]
[MIKAGE]
Come with me.
Let's get you washed up.
[MAMORU squeaks]
Yay, success!
[TSUCHIGUMO screams]
You did this.
A barrier against evil.
Tomoe!
Did you just see that?
It was Mamoru and me.
We had the most perfectly
synched running parade!
[TOMOE]
Mamoru?
Uh-huh, that's what I named him.
Otohiko taught me how I'm
supposed to use a shikigami.
You saved me again.
Thanks, Tomoe. You're amazing.
[gasps]
No. You are wrong.
This time, that is my line.
And, you pass.
[OTOHIKO]
That settles it.
She's going to Izumo.
[NARRATOR] Gods from
across the country will
gather for the Divine Assembly.
Nanami's mastered a new
skill with Mamoru,
so it's onwards to Izumo!
Wait, what's the deal
with these scary gods?
And who in the
world is that guy?
Next time,
"The God Goes to Izumo."
I have a feeling this
is gonna be dramatic!