[NARRATOR] We've made it.
Beyond these doors
is the chamber of
the Divine Assembly.
[NARRATOR]
Oh! Don't go yet!
Please, at least
tell me your name!
[NARRATOR]
Get ready!
Because we're going into
the sacred chamber of the gods!
[GODS cheering, laughing]
--[NANAMI gasps]
--[TAKEHAYA] You.
[NARRATOR]
That's the War God.
You are not welcome here.
And yet you still came anyway?
[NANAMI] Oh, crap.
Scary god alert!
[NANAMI quivering]
Proudly speak your mind.
It's your right.
Participate in
the Divine Assembly.
[NANAMI gasps, sighs]
[NANAMI] Yes.
I'm staying, too!
I'm an attendee of
the Divine Assembly,
just like everybody else!
[TAKEHAYA] How dare you use
that insolent tone with me!
[NANAMI screams]
--Calm down, handsome!
--[TAKEHAYA groans]
[OTOHIKO]
Who draws their sword
on the very first
day of the Assembly,
I mean, take it down a notch,
War God. Come on.
Otohiko!
[MAMORU chirps]
Nanami, I've been
so worried about you!
Mizuki!
[MIZUKI cries]
Was it you, Otohiko?
Did you invite she who
does not belong here?!
[OTOHIKO]
A drab thing like that?
[NANAMI grunts]
If you did not invite her,
then who did?!
I did, naturally.
[ALL gasp]
OMG! It's Lord Okuninushi!
[OKUNINUSHI chuckles]
[NANAMI] He's the lord and
master of the Grand Shrine,
and the host of
the Divine Assembly.
Lord Okuninushi! I hope that
I find you in excellent health.
You do, Otohiko, for it is
a beautiful day today.
It is rare for you
to make an appearance
so early in the Assembly,
Lord Okuninushi.
A situation developed recently
that has need of
an urgent resolution.
Nanami, dear?
[NANAMI]
Huh?
A favor please.
Before the Divine
Assembly gets started,
I want you to go to
Yomotsu Hirasaka.
What's Yomotsu Hirasaka?
[TAROMARU, MIZUKI,
TAKEHAYA, OTOHIKO gasp]
[OKUNINUSHI chuckles]
Yomotsu Hirasaka is the entrance
to the Netherworld, my dear.
Ordinarily, there's a god who's
in charge of guarding the gate,
and determining who is and isn't
allowed to cross the border.
However, he is currently
in attendance
at the Divine Assembly.
[GATE GUARD]
And drinking today, moo!
[NANAMI]
Okay?
For all seven days of
the Divine Assembly,
Yomotsu Hirasaka
becomes undermanned.
Every year, yokai and the like
target this opportunity
to try and break
through the border.
They only have seven days,
so the attempts generally
end in failure,
but there was apparently
quite the ace
among the yokai
this year, meaning...
Oh, we're in a terrible state!
The gate that's been closed
since the beginning of the world
has been opened, now!
If we do not hurry,
the filth of the Netherworld
will sully the earth!
Unfortunately, gods are
fond of cleanliness,
and generally dislike
having anything to do
with that bottomless pit!
No one will go scout for me.
But now you have appeared
with the pure gaze
of an unfailing spirit.
Surely you can go exorcise the
filth of the Netherworld for me.
Yeah, no problem.
Uh? What, seriously?
In exchange, though,
I have a request.
Mm. Yes, and what would that be?
[NANAMI] I want to know the
whereabouts of Mister Mikage,
the true lord and master
of the Mikage Shrine.
There's somebody who
wants him to come back.
You must understand that Mikage
gave you his personal mark
of godhood and has
since gone into hiding.
Without that mark, finding those
who don't want to be found
is no easy task, even for me.
But, if you promise
to take care of the
Yomotsu Hirasaka situation,
then I will promise to
look for Mikage for you.
Do we have a deal?
Yes, we do.
[OKUNINUSHI chuckles]
Then I shall assign a
guide to you forthwith.
[OTOHIKO]
No!
I don't get it, why me?
Guess it's punishment
for being late.
[OTOHIKO] It's mean!
He's just being cruel to me!
[NANAMI] Apparently, the first
two days of the Divine Assembly
mainly consist of
drinking parties.
The crucial part doesn't
start until the third day,
so as long as I get back
before then, it'll be fine.
Nothing is fine about this,
you stupid, fashion-less fiend!
I'm your guide, and that's all,
get it straight.
You're on your own figuring
out the rest of this sitch.
Seriously!
Why, Nanami? Why do you
continuously accept
one nearly impossible,
messy task after another?
You're staying behind, okay?
[MIZUKI]
Why?
Because I need you
to do something.
Think you can find
the god who showed me
the way to the hall
of the Divine Assembly?
[MIZUKI gasps]
[NANAMI]
I've been thinking.
What if that was Mister Mikage?
[NANAMI screams]
Oh, honestly, what is
taking you so long?
Move it, so we can get
this nightmare over with!
[OTOHIKO]
A word of warning.
The Netherworld is a land on
the edge of death and rebirth.
When a flesh and blood
human breathes the air there,
they immediately begin to decay.
Soulless shikigami and
low-level yokai turn to dust.
Only gods are able to
come and go as they please.
[NANAMI]
Decay?
[MAMORU, NANAMI groan]
Technically, you are a god,
so more than likely
you'll be just dandy,
but under no circumstances
should you pass through
the Great Boulder Gate
at Yomotsu Hirasaka.
[TEKKIMARU laughs]
The Great Boulder Gate's
been cracked in
half like an egg!
This power is incredible!
Looks like the rumors are true.
The legend known as Akura-oh
had to have used this before!
You're the legend now, Boss!
That's right!
You're the new Akura-oh!
[laughs] You certainly know
a lot for a stupid human.
Now who the hell are you?
[AKURA-OH] That cudgel siphons
off years from the life
of its bearer. In order
to carry it and survive,
you'll need to have an immortal
body like that Akura-oh guy.
But if I'm not mistaken,
his body is still
in the Netherworld.
I bet if you went
to the Netherworld
to retrieve Akura-oh's
body for yourself,
no one in this world would be
able to stand up against you,
Tekkimaru. Imagine that.
[TEKKIMARU chuckles]
You should go for it, boss! Even
the celestial nymph, Reirei,
would probably fall in
love with you if you do.
[TEKKIMARU]
Ah, Reirei!
[REIREI giggles]
Come on, you're making
me blush, you idiot.
[OGRE C screams]
[TEKKIMARU, OGRES gasp]
He must've been
a lightweight yokai.
They turn to dust when they
touch the Netherworld air.
Only the highest-level
yokai can withstand
the poison of the Netherworld.
Well, Tekkimaru, are you
going into the Netherworld?
Don't you want show us all
that you're a high level
force to be reckoned with,
or is it too scary?
[OGRE A]
Watch your mouth, human scum!
Our boss is a force
stronger and braver
than you'll ever know!
No way he'll ever
turn into dust!
Don't you worry about us, Boss!
Go and show that
human what's what!
[OGRES shout]
Oh, you guys.
I'll never let ya go!
Oh, just hurry up
and do it already.
[NANAMI]
Wow.
Looks like there're a lot of
yokai down there, Otohiko.
The Great Boulder Gate is open
as wide as a cherry
blossom in April.
It's a shame it doesn't
smell as sweet.
Who are they?
Oh no! The wind god!
It's Lord Otohiko, Boss!
--What? But I thought
-- [OGRE A groaning]
the Divine Assembly was supposed
to be going on right now!
[KIKUICHI]
Master Kirihito.
The two of you should
make yourselves scarce.
[AKURA-OH] This is the last
place I need to let myself
fall under suspicion. Damn it.
I was so close to
getting my body back!
Heck yeah! This is where Mamoru
and I show 'em what's up!
[gasps]
[MAMORU groans]
What's wrong,
my sweet little monkey?
We're too close to that
hole into the Netherworld.
[NANAMI groans]
[OTOHIKO] Move aside,
you waste of time.
I'm the wind god, so I can
take care of this problem
in a flash, sweets.
[TEKKIMARU]
You put that wind away!
[NANAMI, OTOHIKO gasp]
Unless you want me
to kill this human!
And I don't figure a god
would want that to happen!
[OTOHIKO]
A human?
What the heavens
is he doing there?
[NANAMI gasps]
I've met that guy before!
With the way things are going,
I think I better jump in to the
Netherworld like you told me.
And you have the honor of coming
with me to keep me company.
Aren't you glad you
were so full of advice?
You get to be my
good luck charm!
[AKURA-OH grunts]
--[OTOHIKO] What?
--[NANAMI] Let him go!
[TEKKIMARU] I'm coming back from
there with an immortal body!
[TEKKIMARU yells]
[AKURA-OH gasps]
[NANAMI]
I'll save you!
Hurry, reach your
hand out to me.
[NANAMI] If only gods
can come and go,
then I should be able
to bring him back.
[TOMOE]
This is preposterous,
you are telling me there
is a blizzard outside,
and I still have to trek
to that horrid classroom
while dressed as
a high school girl?
[KOTETSU] Master Tomoe,
you are home far too early.
[ONIKIRI]
It is not even noon yet.
I made an appearance
at the morning assembly!
Do you have a
problem with that?!
[KOTETSU]
No...
[TOMOE]
Damn it! Curse Nanami!
Foisting trivial chores
onto me and going on a trip
with the snake. How nice
it must be for her!
[grunts]
[TOMOE sighs]
[ONIKIRI]
Goodness!
Your hard work in this cold
weather is most appreciated.
[KOTETSU] Please sit back
and enjoy the yuzu bath,
Master Tomoe.
[ONIKIRI] There are seconds
of the sake as well.
You are an excellent familiar,
Master Tomoe, so it is only
natural that you would be
concerned for Lady Nanami.
[KOTETSU] You serve devotedly
day, after day, after day!
This is the least
we can do for you
while Lady Nanami is not here.
[TOMOE]
You are right.
Nanami... is not here.
[KOTETSU, ONIKIRI]
Buh?!
[ONIKIRI] Don't worry,
everything will be all right,
Master Tomoe!
Lady Nanami is sure to
return in six days hence!
[KOTETSU] She would never
run away like her predecessor.
Of course. 'Tis wonderful.
Nanami is a handful
in so many ways,
but she is not here now.
This is a golden opportunity
that I shall not waste!
Will-o'-the-wisps,
I shall return!
I'm going out to have fun!
Do not expect me back tonight.
[ONIKIRI, KOTETSU]
What?!
No way? Master Tomoe
is back for a visit?
Haven't seen him in nine months!
I hope he's doing well.
[PROSTITUTE C] Sister Hatsune
is entertaining him right now,
but Master Tomoe is
acting really weird.
[PROSTITUTE A, B]
Like how?
[PROSTITUTE C]
No matter what she asks him,
he seems distracted,
and all he does is drink.
He's gone through eight whole
bottles by himself already.
[PROSTITUTE D] It is as if his
mind is totally somewhere else.
Why hasn't he tried to
even touch one of us
since he got here?
Maybe he's is not feeling well.
He's so beautiful
I think I'm gonna die!
This house cannot
allow its customers
to drink themselves unconscious.
We have to go in, girls.
[PROSTITUTE A]
Master Tomoe!
Please welcome us! We're all
terribly desperate to join you!
Let us have fun, Master Tomoe!
Sakurako wants to hear the
story of your heroic deeds!
Heroic deeds? What do you
mean, Miss Sakurako?
I heard it earlier
from Sister Mizutama.
Apparently, a long, long time
ago, Master Tomoe was on
friendly terms with that
notorious yokai, Akura-oh.
[PROSTITUTES gasp]
[PROSTITUTE B]
What?
Master Tomoe?
[PROSTITUTE B]
Oh. He fell asleep.
[PROSTITUTE C sighs]
So back to the story.
You're saying he was friends
with Akura-oh, yeah?
The same yokai who went on a
murderous rampage forever ago?
How could our Master Tomoe
have anything to do with him?
I didn't even know
he really existed.
Okay, spill it, what did you
hear from Sister Mizutama?
Does she know how
old Master Tomoe is?
From what I heard, back in
the day when Sister Mizutama
was just a little girl,
she totally met Akura-oh when
he went in to the house
where she was apprenticing.
That must have been scary, did
he go in to buy a prostitute?
No.
[NARRATOR] For this story, we go
back in time six hundred years.
[SAKURAKO]
He was a mass murderer
in the guise of a customer.
Is this the house rumored
to always be busy due to
its numerous beauties?
Every one of you is stunning.
I simply cannot choose.
I know. I shall hire any of
you that survive this day.
[PROSTITUTES screaming]
[PROSTITUTES scream]
[AKURA-OH laughs]
[MIZUTAMA]
Oh no.
Oh no!
Someone help me!
Please! Help me!
[gasps]
Keep running.
[MIZUTAMA gasps]
[AKURA-OH] Oh, yes! This has
been adequate amusement, indeed!
I waited for you, but
sadly it began to snow.
Of course, you know I cannot
abide the cold. Alas, Tomoe.
I was too frisky this eve,
so there is none left for you.
Such a shame.
[AKURA-OH]
Hm?
It is true I enjoy turning the
tables on those who try to rise
against us, but I dislike
slaughtering the unresisting.
[SAKURAKO]
Back then,
countless communities fell
victim to Akura-oh's cruelty.
Evidently, Sister Mizutama's
establishment was among
those many casualties.
The next time she saw
Master Tomoe was supposedly
over five hundred years later.
[PROSTITUTE B]
What? Master Tomoe?
[TOMOE snoring]
[MIZUTAMA]
What are you girls doing
just standing there and
neglecting your customers?
[PROSTITUTES gasp]
Sister Mizutama!
Is it the truth, Sister?
About Master Tomoe?
And Sister! Did Akura-oh
really attack you?
[MIZUTAMA]
That is ancient history.
It just goes to show
that this Master Fox has been
completely defanged by Mikage,
and has grown to be quite
good at getting attention.
You girls leave us now.
[MIZUTAMA]
I owe a debt to this Master Fox.
During the twenty years
of Mikage's absence,
Master Tomoe would carry on
about not wanting to go back
to the shrine, and every time
I wrapped myself around him...
Oh, how happy that made me.
I doubt that he will ever know.
[TOMOE]
So warm.
That place is cold,
and chills me to the core.
So I will just stay here
to forget about everything,
and sleep, and sleep.
[NANAMI]
Tomoe!
[NANMI]
[TOMOE gasps]
What're you doing, jerk?!
If you don't come back to
the shrine right this minute,
I'll make you hold
down the fort forever!
[TOMOE gasping]
[TOMOE]
I must go home!
Master Tomoe, what in the
world has come over you?
Sorry, Mizutama.
[gasps]
It's not a problem.
I'm glad you finally have
a place to go home to.
Nanami!
[KOTETSU] Welcome home,
Master Tomoe!
What seems to be the rush?
[TOMOE]
It is nothing.
Nanami could not have
possibly returned home,
so why did I feel the need
to come back so hastily?
[KOTETSU]
By the way, Master Tomoe,
I was entrusted with a message
for you, from Lady Nanami.
[TOMOE gasps]
[TOMOE]
She sent me a message.
For my heart to be so warmed
by that must be because she took
all the warmth of the shrine
away with her when she left.
Nanami.
[NANAMI]
"To Tomoe.
Thanks for going to
school! On Wednesday,
there's an English vocabulary
test in the morning,
so make sure you study so you
can score over eighty points!
Nanami."
[KOTETSU]
There are four hours left
until the test in the morning.
[TOMOE]
What?!
[IZANAMI] Oh. An unexpected
and very interesting party
seems to have joined us
here in the Netherworld.
[yawns]
I haven't slept
that well in a while.
Uh?! Where am I?
[NETHERWORLD OGRE A]
Did god wake up?
Surface god did woke up.
Her woke up.
[NANAMI gasps]
Ah! Where did all
of you come from?!
[NETHERWORLD OGRE A]
Surface god, you eat this.
Uh?
It's a dumpling, right?
[NETHERWORLD OGRE A grunts]
Thank you.
[NANAMI grunts]
You do not want to eat that.
What the heck did you do that
for? You almost hit my face!
Don't put any food from the
Netherworld into your mouth.
Well, that is if you ever want
to return to the surface.
[NANAMI]
Netherworld?
Oh right, I fell in the hole
to the Netherworld with him.
Hey! How are you feeling,
is everything still in place?
Y'seem fine.
I don't see any rotten spots!
[NETHERWORLD OGRES growl]
That's a whole
lot of gross guys.
And if any more of them show up,
we'll be in big trouble.
So do something.
[NANAMI]
I'm on it!
I brought these white
talismans in case something
like this happened!
All I need to do is make an
"evil spirits begone" one.
Oops. I messed it up.
--[NANAMI yelps]
--Oh, never mind.
To let myself be saved by
such a pathetic woman...
I think I can officially say
I have hit rock bottom.
[grunts]
[NETHERWORLD OGRES growl]
Now, run!
[NANAMI]
Who is this guy?
[AKURA-OH]
Swim to the opposite shore!
They won't chase
us into the water.
[NANAMI] I'm freaking out.
How can he be so calm?
[NETHERWORLD OGRES growl]
[OTOHIKO]
Where is she?
They should have fallen
here somewhere.
I am going to kill that
silly ninny when I find her.
This is way more work than
anyone should be expected to do.
[TAROMARU, JIROMARU bark]
[OTOHIKO] Oh, don't tell
me it's that late already.
[TAKEHAYA]
Otohiko!
[OTOHIKO]
War God?
Have you still not wrapped
up the Hirasaka situation?
[OTOHIKO]
Not exactly.
Nanami went missing
along with a human.
Mind helping me find them?
[TAKEHAYA]
I do not have time.
It is the beginning of day
three of the Divine Assembly,
and everyone has gathered
at the Grand Shrine already.
Do not bother with
that awful thing!
She is a human god,
so she should be able
to return without help.
[OTOHIKO]
Come along, Taromaru, Jiromaru.
[TAROMARU, JIROMARU bark]
[NANAMI shivers]
I never expected to be
going for a midwinter swim
in the Netherworld. The insides
of my shoes feel disgusting.
If you can't swim, then
you should say that first.
[NANAMI screams]
I'm sinking!
[AKURA-OH gurgles]
I can swim! I was just surprised
that I didn't float, that's all.
Anyway, the good
news is I'm here,
so everything is gonna be fine.
As soon as we find the exit
to the surface,
we'll be able to escape.
--[stomach growls]
--[NANAMI] Easy as pie.
Wait! Don't tell me, you're
like crazy hungry, aren't you?
[AKURA-OH]
I don't know, am I?
[NANAMI]
Don't worry, I've got this!
I'll write out a white talisman.
All I need to do is slap this
guy onto one of the wild
mushrooms around here,
and we'll be set!
You see, it's transformed into
a delicious sweet potato donut!
Yay! Doesn't it look yummy?
Still looks like
a mushroom to me.
Well you gotta try it first,
and then it'll taste different.
I hope.
Which means even if I eat this,
I won't become a denizen
of the Netherworld,
maybe I'll give it a shot.
[NANAMI]
Eeh! No, wait!
You don't want me to? Why, are
you not confident in your power?
You're a good-for-nothing woman.
[NANAMI] Yeah, like
you're such a hotshot.
Come on, good-for-nothing,
let's get out of here.
My name is Nanami
Momozono, okay?
You should tell me
your name, now, pervert!
It's Kirihito.
Kirihito.
Love the enthusiasm, but do
you actually know the way?
I mean, you're human, so how
would you even know where to go?
[gasps]
Greetings, we have
been waiting for you.
Human god and party.
[FEMALE SERVANT A]
Lady Nanami.
[FEMALE SERVANT B]
And the gentleman there.
[FEMALE SERVANT A] Our lady
and mistress is Lady Izanami,
the presiding goddess
of the underworld.
[FEMALE SERVANT B]
Please, come with us.
Our mistress is anxiously
awaiting your arrival.
[NANAMI]
Izanami.
Goddess of the Netherworld.
[NARRATOR] Nanami and Kirihito
are invited to Izanami's shrine.
But Kirihito is taken prisoner!
What? Is that what
the deal was with Kirihito?
As he and Nanami get chased,
will they manage to
escape unscathed?
Next time, "The God Races
Across the Netherworld."
Give me some headwind!