[NARRATOR]
Gods from across the country
gather at the Divine
Assembly in Izumo.
There's a decent chance
one of those gods might know
the whereabouts of Mikage.
I wonder where in the world
he could have schlepped off to?
What's say we test your worth
by having you hatch a shikigami?
Oh no, watch out!
Thus, Mamoru was born!
And with her barrier against
evil, Nanami is Izumo-bound!
[TOMOE]
A thought has occurred to me.
That egg was supposed to take
seven days to hatch, and yet,
when it cracked on the first
day, it already had a base form.
[MAMORU]
Meep?
I can only assume you planted
that monkey from the start,
and your true intention
was to raise Nanami
to godhood all along.
[exhales]
Oh, pooey, you figured me out.
I guess foxes really are sly.
Why would you do
something like that?
[NANAMI]
Tomoe!
Ugh, where the heck are you?
You called for me?
It's about time you showed up,
I seriously need your help here.
My necklace is
caught in my hair,
and I can't get it out to
save my life! Get it off me!
[sighs] You require
such coddling.
[MAMORU squeaks]
[TOMOE grunts]
Y'know if all you're lookin'
for is a good grooming,
you should ask me!
Whoa! You're Mamoru?
No way!
You look like a cutie-ootie-
wootie little kid, now!
Yup! You cop a squat,
and I'll get that off for y--!
'Tis quite enough
monkey business.
Lest you forget your place,
she came to me looking
for assistance.
Now behave yourself
and keep quiet, chimp.
You leave Mamoru alone,
he's trying to help me!
Forget it! I'll get Mizuki
to help me take it off!
You really shouldn't be making
your lady and mistress
angry like that.
[TOMOE]
Ugh.
Based on how much this trip
is gonna cost per person,
I don't think we can afford to
take everyone with me to Izumo.
[TOMOE]
That is of no consequence.
Being that we cannot leave the
shrine completely unattended,
I shall accompany you to Izumo.
The snake can
hold the fort here.
That's quite the plan!
Especially considering that
between the two of us,
I'm the expert on
all things Izumo.
You may be the land
god's familiar,
but you've never attended
the Divine Assembly even once,
now have you?
[TOMOE grunts]
He's never been?
With Tomoe's past as a wild fox,
he'd surely be harassed
if he ever went to
the Divine Assembly.
He's spared that disgrace
by playing the housewife.
--[TOMOE grunting]
--[MIZUKI] Oh, Lord Mikage.
--He was so kind and generous.
Wait, the attendees of
the Divine Assembly are
all gods though, right?
It doesn't matter how bad
you might've been
in the past, Tomoe,
there's no way they
would harass you.
'Cause that would be ungodly!
Of all the lackadaisical
nonsense you have ever said!
Between us, you would
surely be the one to get
--the worst of it in Izumo!
--[NANAMI gasps]
Agreed, you should be more
concerned with yourself, Nanami.
What? Why?
You see, with me by
our mistress's side,
Lady Nanami will carry
a greater air of prestige
and general
elegance about her.
And avoiding such attention
is the reason that I should be
the one to go with her.
In addition,
I cannot entrust her safety
to an unreliable snake.
You'd have no idea
where you're going!
You'd only slow her down!
You know full well that
you can barely navigate
your way through
a human crosswalk!
Okay, you two that's enough.
There's no need to fight. Ah!
[NANAMI]
I said stop fighting!
Violence is prohibited!
If we absolutely must
leave one of you at home,
then I'll decide who's
going to go by...
...a game of Shogi!
Winner takes all!
I'm off to go buy my plane
ticket, and the two of you
better have this sorted
out peacefully by the time
I get back to the shrine.
[TOMOE] Nanami, there is
no reason for you to have
to fly in a plane when you
have the Night Fog Carriage.
[MIZUKI] Better yet,
my shiki will carry you!
No way.
Those things weren't designed
with human riders in mind,
so I'm gonna go with comfort.
[BOTH grunt]
[NANAMI] Jeez, Tomoe and Mizuki
really need to chill out.
Get real, why would a god
care what I do or don't do?
[WOMAN] My apologies for
the wait, Miss Momozono.
As you requested,
one ticket headed for Izumo.
[NANAMI]
Great, thanks!
[MONJIRO] Whoops!
--[NANAMI gasps]
--[MONJIRO] My bad, sorry, lady.
No problem! Ah!
[MONJIRO]
Uh.
[NANAMI]
Weird. He's in a fox mask.
Dude! No friggin' way!
[KIKUICHI] You are making
a racket, Monjiro.
[NANAMI gasps]
[KIKUICHI] Our current mission
is to acquire airplane tickets.
Cease being distracted by the
filthiness surrounding you.
Yeah, I know,
but airplanes are lame!
[KIKUICHI] Perhaps, but that
is what he has asked of us.
[NANAMI]
Talk about a pair of weirdoes.
[MONJIRO] What's so great about
a big, flying hunk of steel?
[NANAMI] Okay, all I gotta do
is stop by the drug store
for a few things,
and I'm set to go.
Oh, I might as well
get snacks, too!
[MAMORU sighs, gasps]
--[MAMORU] Nanami!
--[NANAMI] Ah!
There's four evil auras.
My spider monkey
sense is tingling!
Like right here, right now?
Yeah, and I don't think they're
feeling very friendly, either!
We've gotta find a safe place,
they're almost on top of us!
Run for it!
[NANAMI]
Run? Where to?
[NANAMI gasps]
Tomoe!
Wait, that piece right there.
How did I not see it before?
[MIZUKI chuckles] It looks like
you've finally noticed, Tomoe.
While you were preoccupied
with the movement of my Rook,
I seized the opening
to secretly strike!
My Bishop is primed
for checking your king
into an early grave, ha!
--[TOMOE] No secret moves!
--[MIZUKI] Ow!
[TOMOE]
We are starting over.
Like you care about
this match anyway.
It's not as if you actually want
to go to Izumo, so why bother?
Whether I want to attend or
not is of little consequence
at the moment.
I can't help but
worry, you know.
What if those around
her spoke badly of you?
Nanami wouldn't
be able to bear it.
But I would just laugh it off
as it would serve you right.
You may laugh all you like,
but your concern for Nanami?
She has proven she
can handle adversity.
[NANAMI panting]
[MAMORU] Nanami, they're
totally gonna catch us!
[NANAMI] There's no sign of
anyone in the park up ahead!
That's perfect! I'll try to
drive them back there!
[NANAMI pants]
[gasps]
[NANAMI]
Where did he come from?
Um. Hello.
Nanami, what the heck
are we gonna do?
[NANAMI gasps]
[gasps]
Excuse me, I'm really
sorry about this!
Please don't move, okay?
[NANAMI]
They're here.
Man! You think they brought
enough miasma with them?
Nanami! These guys
are former gods!
Badder than yokai!
[NANAMI]
Former gods?
[MAMORU] That's what they call a
god when it's not holy anymore!
[NANAMI]
I'm facing gods?
[FORMER GOD A]
Are you the human?
The one that has been invited
to the Divine Assembly?
I... Yes, I am.
[FORMER GOD A]
Unforgivable!
I've never seen such gall!
Just a filthy human,
and you dare try to set foot
in the realm of the divine?
You seek too much for yourself.
So decline! Don't bother going!
Do this, and I shall
not disembowel you
right where you stand!
But, technically,
I've been invited
because I'm the Land God
of the Mikage Shrine!
I have to accept!
There's no other choice!
[FORMER GOD C]
The Mikage Shrine?
[FORMER GOD B] The one that
houses that barbaric wild fox.
What did you just say?
[FORMER GOD A] An ignoble
fox serving as a familiar,
what rubbish! As if a mere
dumb beast has any value.
[FORMER GODS laugh]
[chuckles]
[FORMER GOD A] Human male,
what is so amusing?
[AKURA-OH]
A bunch of has-beens,
no longer counted among the
gods, reviling a human god.
It's amazing how pathetic
you bastards look when you're
laid off. I would've thought
you were all primitive yokai!
[FORMER GOD A]
You shut your mouth!
[NANAMI gasps]
[AKURA-OH grunts]
[FORMER GODS laugh]
[FORMER GOD C] Look! Finally,
a human right where it belongs!
[FORMER GODS cackle]
Mamoru, go!
[MAMORU chirps]
Stop! What do you
think you're doing?
Laughing at a man who didn't
stand a chance against you.
It makes me sick to think
you guys could've ever
been called gods!
Trash like you should
be thrown away!
So now I'm going to send you
back where you belong!
Barrier against evil!
[FORMER GODS scream]
[gasps]
Are you alright? I'm so sorry.
I didn't mean to get
you mixed up in this.
You're annoying me. Go away.
[gasps]
[AKURA-OH]
This is no big deal,
just forget about it,
and move on.
[NANAMI]
No, hold on! You're hurt!
[AKURA-OH]
Don't touch me.
But you need help.
Let me get you to a hospital!
[sighs]
[AKURA-OH] I know something
more effective than a hospital.
[gasps]
[NANAMI gasps]
'Kay! You seem fine,
so I'll be on my way, bye!
[NANAMI] Creep.
What was up with him?
[AKURA-OH]
Hmph.
Fickle woman.
Says she wants to help,
--but doesn't cooperate.
--[MONJIRO] Master Kirihito!
[MONJIRO] Mission complete!
Airplane tickets acquired!
[KIKUICHI] For your convenience
of preference, master,
we obtained one of each variety,
window and aisle seating!
[AKURA-OH grunts]
[KIKUICHI] Master Kirihito, how
did you come by those injuries?
Never mind, I'll be all right.
[MONJIRO]
We can't "never mind"!
[KIKUICHI] You have a human
being's body! It requires care!
Enough, you two.
[KIKUICHI, MONJIRO gasp]
[AKURA-OH]
I'm aware it's fragile,
but I won't be tolerating this
condemned existence much longer.
I'll regain my original
form without fail.
[KIKUICHI] On that day, this
world will again belong to you.
Once more under the reign
of Master Akura-Oh.
A filthy human that seeks
too much for itself!
And an ignoble fox
serving as a familiar!
[NANAMI]
I can't believe how they acted.
Hey, what's wrong?
You seem kinda down.
[gasps]
If it's what that pervert
did back there,
don't let it get to you.
It's cool, I'm fine.
[NANAMI] I don't care
what they say about me,
but no one talks
bad about Tomoe.
[NANAMI]
We're back!
[TOMOE]
Behold, Nanami.
I warded off the snake's
expedient tactics to secure
--a brilliant victory.
--[MIZUKI cries]
This settles it! I shall be
accompanying you to Izumo.
No matter what may happen,
I shall be there to protect you.
So you may rest easy, Nanami.
--[NANAMI] No.
--[TOMOE] Uh.
Mizuki will be coming
with me to Izumo,
and you're gonna stay here
and hold down the fort.
We all clear?
--[TOMOE] What?
--[MIZUKI] Yay!
[NANAMI] If anything
ever happened to Tomoe,
I would never forgive myself.
[HIMEMIKO] Oh no!
The land god is about to depart
for Izumo and no one else came
to see her on her journey?
It's okay. You being
here today is all
the encouragement
I need, Himemiko.
[HIMEMIKO] Had I known,
I would have brought
the entire clan with me.
Where art thy familiars?
Mizuki's already gone
ahead on his shiki.
We're gonna meet up
when I get there.
How unexpected.
Master Tomoe is to stay at home?
Yeah, Tomoe has to
disguise himself as me
and go to school in
my place while I'm away.
I thought he'd never
stop complaining about it.
Oh! That reminds me.
We recently took something
called a "photograph,"
and I am giving out copies
to all those I consider
"close friends."
[NANAMI]
Wow, talk about romantic!
That's so cute!
We took it the other day,
when Kota and I were
out on a date together.
It looks adorable, does it not?
Seems like things are
going well for you two.
Yes, and 'tis all thanks to you.
No way! You didn't
really need me!
As a yokai, repeatedly
meeting with my beloved Kota
should be impossible. However,
we have the blessings of thee,
the god of matchmaking,
behind our encounters.
And now, thou art about
to present thyself before
the Divine Assembly as well.
The very thought
fills me with pride.
Thou wilt surely make
a difference there, also.
Take care upon thy voyage.
Thank you.
[NANAMI]
I'm off!
Is it just me, or is this
classroom kinda cold?
[GIRL STUDENT B]
Yeah.
Ah. I can't stop shivering.
Man, the mood in here
is super depressing.
[TOMOE]
Damn you, Nanami.
Passing me over to
go alone with a snake.
And for a whole week at that!
Seven days alone
with a snake.
That bastard once attacked her!
How can she go on a trip
with him so nonchalantly?
[TOMOE]
And until just the other day,
she was blubbering about
having feelings for me.
[TOMOE gasps]
[TOMOE]
Heh. What utter nonsense.
'Tis no matter.
Good morning, my little kittens.
[GIRL STUDENTS scream]
Hi, Kurama!
Morning, Nanami.
Just you today?
Decided to leave that nagging
fox back at the shrine, huh?
[KURAMA yells]
[GIRL STUDENT D]
Kurama's face is on fire!
[GIRL STUDENT E] Put it out! Put
it out! Put it out! Put it out!
[NANAMI] I'm really in Izumo,
the land of the gods!
Oh, cool! It's a tourist spot.
[MIZUKI] They don't just
have notable sights.
Freshwater clams!
Eel!
Prawns!
Having come all this way, it is
our duty to fill our bellies
with a bounty of
aquatic delicacies!
If there's anything you would
like to know, you just ask.
'Kay, how about
when did you get here?
Oh, just about an hour ago.
Pity! It's unfortunate that we
don't have time for me to show
you around at the moment,
but you're running late
for the Greeting of the Gods.
"The Greeting of the Gods?"
[MIZUKI]
Mm-hm.
The gods are streaming ashore
to meet at the grand shrine.
We had better hurry along if we
wanna make a good impression.
[NARRATOR] The grand shrine
is the annual meeting place
of the myriad gods.
It is the highest-ranking
temple in the Province of Izumo.
Oh wow, it's so beautiful.
Your host will be Okuninushi.
So this Okuninushi guy
is the god in charge
of the Divine Assembly?
Indeed.
[NANAMI]
Wow, to have such a large shrine
dedicated in his honor.
Makes me wonder what he's like.
[MIKAGE]
Oh!
[NANAMI screams]
Nanami!
[NANAMI groaning]
[NANAMI]
Where am I?
Mizuki?
[NANAMI gasps]
[INAHO] This bothersome
Divine Assembly has begun.
Yet again I am required
to meet face-to-face
with bothersome folk to
discuss bothersome matters.
You need not worry yourself so.
You will be sleeping through
the entire meeting
anyway, Lady Inaho.
[chuckles]
I expect that no one will
arrive late this year.
[NANAMI]
These are the myriad gods!
They're amazing!
[TAKEHAYA]
Are you that new human god?
[gasps]
Show me your divine powers.
If you have come to
the Divine Assembly as
living flesh and blood,
I presume you must
have some skills.
Show them to me!
My skills? Sure, uh...
What happened to Mamoru?!
[MAMORU]
Meep!
What is the delay?
Uh! Well, uh...
My greatest skill is making
barriers against evil.
Although, it seems my shikigami
is missing right now,
so I can't really
do that at the moment.
But I do have white talismans!
No! My bag!
I don't have anything!
[drum beats]
[FEMALE GOD C]
The drum to gather has sounded.
Let us all make our
way to the banquet hall.
[NANAMI gasps]
[ISA] You will benefit nothing
by spending your time
on the human, Takehaya.
We had best be on our way.
Wait, stop!
[TAKEHAYA] Then it is true
what Narukami said.
You are nothing but a mere
human. No talent, and no value.
You are pathetic! You will
stay out of my sight!
Ah!
[NANAMI]
It's time to go.
Divine Assembly, here I come.
[MIZUKI] How many times
do I have to tell you?
You must be the stupidest
Guard Bunny ever!
I'm a familiar who came to
the Divine Assembly
to accompany my god! Okay?
[GUARD RABBIT] Familiar though
you may be, I must deny you.
Oh! If I don't get inside soon,
I'll stand no chance
of finding Lady Nanami!
[GUARD RABBIT] Without the
accompaniment of a god,
you shall not pass
through this torii gate.
You will remain here until
your god comes to fetch you.
--[MIZUKI] Like I said!
--[MAMORU yelling]
My god is still
too inexperienced,
so she has no idea
what she's doing!
[MIZUKI] How could I,
of all people,
have become separated
from Nanami?
She's probably all alone
and scared to death!
[GUARD RABBIT] You can
always enter by attaching
yourself to some other god
who happens to arrive late.
Do you know how big of an
airhead a god would have to be
to turn up late for
a once a year show?
Guard rabbit, I'm so late!
Please open the gate!
My skin was just not
cooperating today,
and my make-up took
me forever to do!
Oh, my, Mizuki.
This is all terribly sudden.
So not having fun.
[NANAMI] I have no clue
which path is the right way.
Where did the gods go?
No matter how far I walk,
everything looks the same.
I'm alone, and without Mizuki,
I can't even get
to the meeting hall,
never mind the Divine Assembly!
I am pathetic.
The flame is going out! No!
[NANAMI gasps]
[NANAMI]
Some-Someone?
Is anyone there?
[NANAMI]
Please, anybody?
[MIKAGE]
Have you become lost?
[NANAMI gasps]
[MIKAGE] Come with me.
Let me show you the way.
[NANAMI]
Who is this?
[MIKAGE] We've made it.
Beyond these doors is
the chamber of
the Divine Assembly.
And you, aren't you attending
the meeting as well?
[MIKAGE]
No, that I am not.
Are you afraid, miss human god?
[NANAMI] The other gods
are amazing, and I'm not.
Why am I even here?
[MIKAGE]
No god is truly omnipotent.
They each have strengths
and weaknesses.
As well as their
own roles to play.
[NANAMI]
Their own roles?
[MIKAGE]
Lady Inaho is not industrious,
and while the Three Fumigae
Gods are well learned,
they have poor penmanship.
The War God is foreboding and
aggressive, but he can't sing.
[NANAMI]
Huh!
[MIKAGE] For every shortcoming
is a virtue, the same as you.
[gasps]
[MIKAGE]
Of all the myriad gods,
you alone can see
through the eyes of man.
You can sympathize with
humans, sit next to them,
and put your arm
around their shoulders.
That is your strength,
and so you are amazing.
Enter these doors, and you
will see for yourself.
Proudly speak your mind.
You are a participant
of the Divine Assembly.
It is your right.
I will! Thank you
for everything.
Oh! Don't go!
At least tell me your name!
[gasps]
[inhales, exhales]
[NANAMI]
Once I walk through these doors,
I'm gonna show them
what I'm made of.
Please excuse my tardiness.
I'm here now.
From Mikage Shrine,
the land god Nanami Momozono.
[OKUNINUSHI]
Ah, that is the human god
Otohiko recommends most highly.
Now I see. Her eyes
are so beautifully pure.
I choose you, dear little
Nanami Momozono.
[NARRATOR] Here we are
at the Divine Assembly,
and every which way,
they're gods!
Here's a god! There's a god?
And the host is the
imposing Okuninushi.
Meanwhile, staying at home,
Tomoe attends school.
Wowzers is he
ever in a bad mood.
Next time, "The God Falls
into the Netherworld."
Slip to hell.