[CHIHIRO]
Ever since that day,
I can't help but ask myself
if this is really for the best.
[DAN'ICHIRO]
I have decided
I shall leave
my daughter in your care.
[CHIHIRO] I'm happy that
Rea finally has her freedom,
but now that her creepy
dad's left her here with me.
I can feel the weight
of that responsibility
bearing down on me
like a ton of bricks.
[JOGORO] No!
Mero, why is there slimy green
stuff floating in my miso soup?
Calm down.
Those are just
green peppers, Grandpa.
Well, I'll be damned.
Mero?
Is something wrong, Father?
Rea's dinner looks interesting.
What is it?
Lady Rea has a taste for leafy
greens of the poisonous variety.
She requested boiled
hydrangea leaves.
Stir-fried hydrangea leaves.
And hydrangea leaf
broth for dinner.
I've never had
them, are they good?
I wouldn't know, I simply
followed brother's directions.
Even though it hurt
my heart to do so.
Mero just doesn't like
cooking for a vegetarian.
Since when are hydrangea
leaves considered vegetables?
I can always just
go eat by myself
so my diet won't be a
distraction at the dinner table.
Oh no, it's not a distraction,
I was just asking
out of curiosity.
Geez, would you
cut it out, Dad.
Why do you have to be so nosy?
I'm sorry, I've just never heard
of anyone eating
hydrangea leaves for dinner.
There's no need to apologize.
I understa--
Kiyo?
Kiyo!
When Grandpa goes cuckoo,
just hold your arm out and
he'll clothesline himself.
Um, okay.
Our quirkiness isn't going
to scare you off, is it?
No, sir.
[CHIHIRO] What have
I gotten myself into?
This is brutal.
I can tell Dad and
Mero are freaked out
that Rea's been
left in my care,
but they're not gonna say
anything because
they're too nice.
I never realized it'd be so
difficult to care
for another person.
Especially a zombie.
Hey.
What's up?
I know it's not much,
but I'm afraid that this
is the best I can do
considering your
current "condition."
It's okay.
I just wish.
I could take you someplace
nicer than this, y'know?
No need to beat
yourself up about it.
I'm having a great time.
When I was living at home,
my father would never let
me do things like this.
Are you serious?
Oh, yeah!
Hey Chihiro?
Check it out!
There's a fireworks
show tomorrow night.
Yeah, they do that every year.
I've never actually
seen it, though.
But it's so pretty!
I've only ever seen
it from my window
but I've always wanted
to see it up close.
I think it would be thrilling
to watch the fireworks
explode overhead.
Do you wanna go?
Yeah, I'd love to!
Well, it's not gonna
start until after dark,
so yeah, I guess it's okay.
Thanks, Chihiro!
I don't want to ruin
this opportunity
so I'll do everything
in my power
to keep my body from decaying
before tomorrow night!
Calm down, it's not gonna
happen that quickly!
I can't believe you're gettin'
all worked up over fireworks.
What are you, a child?
Yeah, we both are!
So don't act like
you're better than me!
Whoa, I never
said that, did I?
I've researched
different methods
of preserving dead bodies,
such as embalming or
evisceration,
but I haven't found anything
that'll work in this situation.
I shouldn't be surprised.
It's not like I'm gonna
find a hypotheses
on how to keep a zombie from
decaying at the local library.
Hey, are you coming
upstairs with me?
I'll be up in a bit.
The only person I can turn to
right now is Grandpa, but...
How'm I supposed
to preserve Rea's body
and make sure
she's enjoying herself?
Brother, why are
you up at this hour?
Just.
Checking on Grandpa.
I've been meaning to ask you.
Do you know when Lady Rea
plans on returning to school?
Don't have a clue.
but I don't think she's
ready to go back just yet.
And may I ask why not?
Well, because she's got some
health complications, okay?
I didn't notice that there
was anything wrong with her.
It's not somethin' you'd notice,
but I'm tellin' ya,
on the inside, she's a big mess.
If that's true, why'd she stop
me on my way out this morning?
"Are you going to school?
I'm so jealous, Mero" she said.
Dunno.
If she's ill she could leave
early or go every other day.
There's no reason
to keep her from going.
You've got a point but
I don't think it's a good idea.
So you're going to force Lady
Rea to stay at home from now on.
Is that it?
It's not fair for me to keep
her from going to school.
In fact, it makes me
no different
than the father she despises.
All she wants is to be
treated like a normal girl,
but that's a lot
easier said than done
when you're dealing
with a zombie.
As if mother nature
was trying to echo my mood,
the fireworks show
was called off, due to rain.
It was cancelled, huh?
I guess there's
nothing we can do about it.
Yeah, I'm really sorry.
It's not your fault so
why are you apologizing?
I just felt like it.
I don't get you sometimes.
Chihiro.
I know this is farfetched but
if I'm still around next year,
I would love to see it with you.
We'll make it a date, okay?
You know, I still can't believe
they cancelled the fireworks.
I'm pissed that
I didn't get to hang out
with a bevy
of beauties in yukatas.
As far as I'm concerned,
that's a huge life experience
for a red-blooded high-schooler
to miss out on
'cause of a little rain.
What do you think Mogi?
I think this has
less to do with yukatas
and more with
you being a horn dog.
Oh, gimme a break,
you know you
were lookin' forward
to it too, ya little fink!
It would've been nice
to see 'em all dolled up.
You agree with me,
dontcha Furuya?
Uh.
What are you talkin' about?
There are Sanka girls
dressed in yukatas
dancing around in
your head right now, huh?
No, because I'm not a perv.
Hey, wait up!
Good mornin' Chihiro!
What do you want, Wanko?
What's got your panties
in a bunch?
I dunno. Your presence?
Please don't tell me
you and your lady friend
are on the rocks already?
Do you really think
I would tell you if I was?
Aw, c'mon!
Why don'tcha
tell me all about it
and I'll try to ease
your pain, you poor boy!
Gotta admit, I'm jealous.
Wow, you really will
take it any way you can get it.
I suppose there's
no denying it, is there?
You were gonna go
watch the fireworks?
Yeah, Rea was really
looking forward to seeing it.
I was looking forward
to seeing it, too.
In fact... I was hoping
we could go together.
There's always next year.
Here's an idea.
Why don't we all put on
a fireworks show of our own?
Lady Rea.
I don't know if
this is a good idea.
Brother's gonna be upset
when he finds out
you've been helping me.
Don't worry.
I'm sure that he won't mind.
He doesn't want
you exerting yourself.
How could a little
sweeping hurt?
Uh-oh.
I don't know, by
breaking my broom maybe?
I guess I don't know
my own strength.
What're you two doing?
Hi Chihiro, how was your day?
Brother, you're
home awfully early.
Rea, why're you outside
cleaning in broad daylight?
And with a broken broom,
no less.
I was helping with the chores.
It shouldn't be a big deal
because it's cloudy out,
and besides,
you worry too much.
Oh, really?
Yeah, really.
Fine, just be sure
to get some rest later.
Yes, sir!
Seriously, you need to
rest up 'cause you don't wanna
miss the big fireworks
show later tonight.
Wait, I thought it had
been cancelled.
Yeah.
But we're having our own.
I figured we could shoot off
some bottle rockets
or somethin'.
I prefer the dainty flame
of a sparkler but count me in.
Yeah, that sounds
like a lot of fun!
Well, I guess that settles it.
Wanko's gonna bring an extra
yukata over 'specially for you.
She said she'll
help you get ready.
I know it's not the real deal
but it'll still be fun.
Miss Wanko's coming?
You're right that'll be a blast.
Yeah, they're her fireworks.
I'm gonna change.
When she gets here,
make sure she doesn't
come barging in on me.
Well, I should go inside
and start getting supper ready.
Oh, okay.
Do you want me to
clean this up for you?
Yes, but try not
to break anything else.
She's coming too?
Neat.
Is anybody home?
Hi Ranko, it's a pleasure
to see you as always.
Are you kids gonna
shoot fireworks?
Yes, sir!
We were all pretty bummed
they got cancelled.
So we decided we should take
matters into our own hands.
[CHIHIRO]
Perfect timing.
[RANKO] I thought you said
yukatas were tricky?
I can't figure 'em out
but Mero's a pro.
[MERO] True, but
it's taken years
of wearing them daily
to master the art.
So, uh, where's Rea?
She's upstairs.
Rea!
[REA gasps]
I'm not gonna hurt you
when I tie the obi, am I?
Oh.
No, I doubt I'll even feel it.
In fact, I'd actually prefer it
if you'd wrap me up
nice and tight.
You got it.
May I ask you something?
Have you and Chihiro
always been this close?
You betcha.
We've been friends
since we were kids.
It's funny, 'cause
when I first met him
he annoyed the crap outta me.
I'd never met an oddball
like him before.
But once I got to know him
I saw his good points.
He may be weird
but he's a sweetheart.
I think so, too.
He's not the type
who's into fireworks,
or any outdoor activity, really.
So I was surprised
when he was on board.
And that's when I realized.
He's doing it because
he thinks it'll make you happy.
I know he can be kinda weird,
but when it comes down
to it, he's a good guy.
Once you get past
the freaky stuff.
Considering my situation,
that's pretty easy.
All done!
How's that feel?
Do you think it's tight enough?
Yeah.
Wow, it's still
so hard to believe.
What?
If I saw you on the street
I'd never think you
were a living dead girl.
Are you tryin' to pull
a fast one on me?
No, I'm most
definitely a zombie.
I don't have
a pulse or anything.
But, other than that,
you're just like a normal girl?
Yeah, I guess so,
but I don't know how longer
I'm going to look like this.
I'm afraid
I'm running out of time.
My body has already
started to decay.
[RANKO sniffing]
[REA gasps]
Uh... wait.
What are you doing?
You smell perfectly
lovely to me.
Kinda like hydrangeas.
By the way, how're
they workin' out for ya?
I'm sure it won't
be long 'til Chihiro
comes up with
something better.
Uh, yeah, I hope you're right.
Don't you worry, you're
not goin' anywhere, missy.
Oh.
I'm not worried because
I don't intend to stay.
Wait a minute, I thought you
were gonna be living
here for good.
Unfortunately, that's
still kinda up in the air.
At least for now, anyway.
Besides, I don't want to be
rude and overstay my welcome.
You know what I mean?
I get it, but if you left
I know Chihiro would miss you.
He would?
I didn't think about that.
Miss Wanko, there's something
I've been dying to ask.
Do you have
feelings for Chihiro?
Yeah, I love him.
How about you?
[REA gasps]
Who, me?
I dunno.
I mean, I think he's
a nice guy and all.
Well, if that's the case.
I assume you're cool with
me keeping him to myself?
Fine with me.
I know how much
he means to you.
C'mon, don't lie to me.
I can tell you're just trying
to be polite, 'Miss Sanka'.
I may be a lot of things
but I am not a liar!
You may think you're
hiding your feelings
but you're like an open book.
You know what this means.
Now that you and I are rivals
we're gonna be
fighting over Chihiro.
[REA gasps]
But why?
I don't see any reason
for the two of us to fight
when you're so
much closer to him
than I could ever be,
Miss Wanko.
The only reason he's
even interested in me
is because of his
fascination with zombies.
Oh, for cryin' out loud!
Why the hell are
you holdin' back?
You care about him, dontcha?
Then don't give up
on him so easily!
You've gotta stay in the game
to get the most outta life!
You've gotta live
like you're dyin'!
Yeah, I get that,
but I don't think that
works if you're already dead.
[RANKO and REA laughing]
I'm sorry.
I'm no good at the mushy stuff.
I don't think it
really matters that
we're in love with the same boy.
We'll let him choose.
That way we can
go on being friends.
But I'm not gonna
give up on him.
Got it?
Just so you know,
I don't think you should
give up on him either.
Okay!
[CHIHIRO]
Are you having fun?
[REA] Yeah,
I'm having a blast!
Sorry I wasn't
able to pull off
something more
spectacular for ya.
Why do you keep apologizing
when you don't need to, Chihiro?
Well, I dunno.
Sorry.
Seriously, there's
no need to apologize.
I know it might seem
kinda lame to you,
but this is the most fun
I've had in a long time.
Are you sure
we're not boring you?
Not at all.
Is there anything
I can do to make it more fun?
Not a thing.
I think our little
fireworks display
is better than any big show.
I've never held one before.
Now that I think about it,
I can't imagine
sharing this experience
with anyone other
than you and your family.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Don't be silly,
you're always welcome.
May I ask what brings you
to the mansion today, Miss?
I've decided to
go back to school.
So I've come by to pick up
some things that I might need.
Is that okay with you ladies?
Yeah that's fine.
Go tell the madam.
Yes, I'll do that right away.
[door opens]
[REA gasps]
Oh. Hello, Mother.
I hear you've decided
to go back to school.
Yes, ma'am.
I don't see any reason not to.
You've got some
nerve if you think
you can just waltz right
back into Sanka Academy.
Let me guess, you've had
me expelled from school?
Don't I wish.
Dan'ichiro made me promise
that I wouldn't prevent
you from attending.
You're still enrolled there.
For now, anyway.
Thanks.
I appreciate it, Mother.
Don't be too grateful,
you're going to be on your own.
Don't approach me, don't call
me, and don't ask me for money.
I can handle that.
Very well.
If you've got what
you need hurry up and get out.
I'd be more than happy to.
Hey, are you alright?
I'm fine.
I wanted to thank you, Chihiro,
for letting me
go back to school.
It's not like I can stop you.
But, you sure
you're okay with it?
Yeah, I mean,
if that's what you wanna do.
I'm happy to hear that.
It's funny.
I don't think I'd have the right
to call myself a normal girl
unless I was going
to school every day.
I've actually
started to miss it.
I guess you weren't really
as happy as you let on, huh?
I wouldn't say I was unhappy.
More like unsatisfied, you know?
I know you're excited,
but will you promise me
that you'll be careful?
I promise.
Try to be as cautious
about preserving
your body as I am, okay?
I'll do my best.
Rea?
What's up?
Can I be completely honest
with you about something?
Of course you can.
If I had it my way, I'd keep
you from going to school
until I figure out how
to preserve your body.
In that case, can I be
completely honest with you, too?
Sure.
I don't want to leave
behind a legacy of regret.
I don't know how much time
I have left in this world,
so I've got to make the most
of every moment that I've got.
And that's why I have
to live like I'm dying!
No point arguing, huh?
Nope, neither of us will win.
She's got a point.
Why couldn't I see it?
We don't see eye to eye.
Everything that makes me happy
only brings her down
and vice versa.
I get it.
It's not fair. but I get it.
Remember that crazy idea I had?
The one about fixing
that coat I got you
so you can put a bunch
of dry ice in it?
You don't have
to wear it all day,
just to school and back,
but I bet it would help.
If that works, you could even
wear it in the summertime!
So does that sound good to you?
But at that moment...
I...I got the feeling
Rea and I were sharing
our happiness and sadness.
At that moment...
Next time Sankarea,
Episode 13,
"I, Too, Am... A Zombie..."
Tune in to see Mero!
Woo hoo!
Alright!
You did it!
Woo hoo!
Well thank you, but I couldn't
have done it all by myself.
Let me take this opportunity
to thank you, the little people,
who have helped me to
get where I am today.
You like me,
you really like me!