[RANKO screams]
Sounds like Wanko!
[CHIHIRO panting]
Please just let her
have seen a spider!
Even a tarantula!
I don't know why
I'm attracted to zombies.
But I've always fantasized
about being with
a girl like you.
So...
I could've sworn
you were a zombie before.
What happened?
Rea?
What's going on?
What're you doing here?
Are you really surprised to
see me pop up in your fantasy?
After all, this is where
all your wishes come true.
I thought a pretty zombie
in nothing but a towel
would be a big
turn on for you.
Yeah.
She's right, this is my fantasy.
But I always thought...
It was so farfetched
it would never come true.
[DO'ON] Mero, did you
just hear another scream
coming from inside the house?
Uh-huh.
It wasn't Grandpa
so it must've been Ranko.
I saw brother
running towards the house,
presumably to check on her,
so I wouldn't worry.
Hmm. Okay.
[CHIHIRO panting]
You're sick.
I've always
questioned your sanity
but I never knew
you were this crazy!
[CHIHIRO gasps]
If anyone finds
out Rea is here
you could get in big
trouble for harboring a runaway!
[CHIHIRO] Well, yeah,
but you see--
As if that wasn't bad enough,
she's been seriously injured!
What is wrong with you?
Look at how much
blood she's lost!
Why haven't you taken
her to the hospital?
[REA panting]
I think I've figured out
what's happening here,
you're in no rush
'cause she's a zombie.
Exactly.
But I promise it's
not what you're thinking.
It was an accident.
You murderer!
[ZOMBIE CLOCK laughs]
I can't believe you killed
a sweet, innocent girl like Rea
just so you could perform
your creepy zombie
experiments on her!
No, that's not true!
Would you let me explain, Wanko?
You've got it all wrong! Hey!
I don't wanna hear
your lame alibi!
I want this murdering
bastard arrested!
Have fun spending
your last days
rotting away
in a jail cell, you sicko!
I know it looks bad but
I swear I didn't do anything!
Fine, let's hear it!
How'd that poor girl become
one of your zombie experiments?
She stole some of
the potion I mixed
and drank it
without telling me!
She's never
attacked before.
Sorry you were
her first victim.
Okay?
Oh crap.
Ah. Babu.
Where do you think
you're going, Rea?
Don't make me follow you!
Damn it.
I need you to go downstairs,
pull Grandpa out of the
bathroom, and bring him here!
Huh?
What do you need him for?
I don't have
time to explain.
Why me?
Can't Mero do it?
You know how much
the geezer creeps me out.
Gah!
You're gonna owe me
big time for this, you hear me?
Hey!
Everything okay?
I heard screaming
coming from the house earlier.
Should I be concerned?
Uh.
Oh, that was just Wanko.
She wanted to
watch a horror flick
but I guess it
was too much for her.
May I ask why you're on the roof
when you're supposed
to be helping us clean?
You're not getting off
the hook that easily.
I'll get right back to work
as soon as I find Babu.
What am I gonna
do with this boy?
Make it fast.
Yes, sir!
Aw, man.
Where'd she go?
Don't tell me!
She's eating hydrangea leaves.
But why?
This goes against everything
I've ever read about zombies.
That's weird.
The color of her eyes.
It's starting to change.
What the--?
Where am I?
Chihiro. Hey.
[CHIHIRO] Looks like
she's come to her senses.
You okay?
[REA screams]
[REA] Why am I out of
the house like this?
I don't have any clothes on!
Sorry!
I'll go grab a shirt for you!
Here ya go!
[CHIHIRO] She ate some leaves
and she's back to normal.
Wait, that's it!
They're eating hydrangea
leaves because it was one
of the ingredients we used
in the reanimation potion.
Ingesting the plant's poison
must be what's
keeping them coherent.
I know it sounds weird
but eating hydrangea leaves
is a good thing
because the poison
is what's keeping you lucid!
Really?
Are you sure?
[JOGORO] I've never been
more proud of you, my boy!
Would you tell him
to let go of me?
Grandpa?
I wondered who'd
given my beloved Sada
the reanimation potion
and brought her back to life.
I should've known
it was you.
Yeah, I've never met a Sada.
Wait, are you talking about Rea?
You must be confusing
her with someone.
I should warn you.
My reanimation potion
was never perfected.
There are a few
things you can do
to slow down the decomposition
but they must
be done diligently.
Otherwise the resurrected
will deteriorate
until you're left
with nothing but a corpse.
Get this old man off of me!
Now why would I go
and do that, Otoki?
After all, you're my missus!
[RANKO] How many times do I have
to tell you I'm not Otoki?
Get your hand off me,
you creepy perv!
Three things will slow the
decomposition of the reanimated.
First, they need
moderate exercise daily;
second, they should
avoid warm and humid climates;
and third, they must
eat plenty of hydrangea
to replenish the poison.
Stop it.
You know, it would've been
helpful if you'd taken the time
to write that stuff
down in your notes.
Quit whinin', boy!
I don't see why I have to
share that information with you
when I'm the one who
did all the hard work!
Go do your own research,
ya lazy bum!
You're supposed
to share your findings!
What are they talking about?
Dunno.
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but you're telling me that
all it takes is a steady flow
of hydrangea poison
to prevent decomposition?
Not at all.
As I mentioned before,
my reanimation potion
is far from perfect.
While the tips I gave you
will help slow down
the decomposition,
it's impossible to
stop it completely.
There is one other
thing you should know--
Oh wow.
On the first try.
Can you hear me?
Hey, Grandpa?
Just my luck.
Horse walks into a bar
and the bartender asks,
"Why the long face, buddy?"
It looks like the poor guy's
gone back into dotty mode again.
He was finally
starting to make sense, too.
Sorry, but he deserved it
for getting frisky with me.
C'mon Grandpa, let's get you
inside before you catch a cold.
If only I'd had a few
more minutes with him.
Oh well, I should
just be thankful
for the information
I did get out of him.
Even if it's not much.
If I wanna figure out
a way to preserve Rea's body,
I'm gonna have
to do it on my own.
Who is that young lady?
Is she a friend
of yours, Chihiro?
Uh, yeah!
But she's a girl friend.
I mean, she's not my girlfriend.
All I'm saying is
we're not, you know, intimate.
She's having a hard
time at home right now.
Which brings me to a question
I've been meaning to ask you
but I'm kinda nervous
about how you're gonna respond.
Those must be members
of Chihiro's family.
This is terrible!
Now they know about me
and it's my own fault.
What am I gonna do?
I doubt they'll let me
stay here after today.
Well, I'm waiting.
So let's hear it.
I wanted to know.
If you'd mind...
If Rea...
Would you mind if I invited Rea
to move in with us for a while?
[REA gasps]
[RANKO gasps]
Would you mind if I invited Rea
to move in with us for a while?
I'm sorry.
It's a lot to ask, and I can't
really go into detail right now,
but she doesn't have
anywhere else to go.
I've gotta help her, Dad.
Because I told her
I would take care of her
and I'm not the kind of guy
who can break a promise.
So would it be okay with you?
Well... let me think.
So you promised her, huh?
She must be a special girl.
This is the first time
I've seen you enthusiastic
about something
other than zombies.
Uh yeah.
If he knew the truth
he'd be so mad at me.
I don't know why
your friend ran away
but she came to
the right place,
because Shiryoji Temple
was originally intended
to be a safe haven.
She's welcome here.
Wait... You mean
she can move in?
Sure.
I can't think of
any reason for her not to.
[CHIHIRO laughing]
That's awesome!
I promise you
won't regret it, dad!
Hey Rea, you wanna come
up here and meet everybody?
My dad said it was cool
for you to move-in with us
so you don't have
to hide from my family anymore!
When you made
your plea on her behalf,
you failed to mention you've
been secretly cohabitating.
Uh...
We shared a room, but I wouldn't
call it cohabitating.
Really?
What would you call it?
It's not like we slept in
the same bed or anything.
If you say so.
That girl again.
She is beautiful, isn't she?
What's wrong with you?
How could you not
hook up with her?
Crap, I gotta go!
I'm supposed to be helping my
Mom out at the restaurant today.
She's gonna be so pissed
when she sees what
happened to my apron.
I have a feeling I'm gonna
get quite the tongue-lashing.
I hope you don't mind
if I borrow a shirt.
See ya!
Oh, and please give my
regards to Miss Sanka!
Now that Rea's
officially living with us,
I figured it'd be a good
time to start keeping a diary.
Unlike Grandpa,
I see the importance
of writing down
my daily observations.
We'll spend each day together
and I'll document every
single thing that happens.
My hope is that if I keep a log
of how the decomposition
process is affecting her,
it might help me figure out
how to preserve her body.
It's hard to fight
its effects when--
Uh... Chihiro?
Yeah?
Sure you don't
want to sleep in here?
I feel absolutely
horrible kicking you
out of your bedroom
two nights in a row.
Nah, I'm good out here.
I'm not gettin' too much sleep.
but it's cool 'cause now I can
empathize with the walking dead.
Uh... I'm worried.
About what?
Sleep deprivation can affect
not only cognitive function
but the brain itself.
Keep talking about brains
and I'll be too scared to sleep.
Oh, sorry.
Well, we could share your room.
The bed's big enough to sleep
both of us comfortably.
Huh?
Sorry, that's too risky.
I'm not sure I could control
myself if we shared a bed.
'Specially after
that kiss today.
What kiss are you talking about?
Apparently, Rea doesn't
remember anything that happened
while she was in
her zombified trance.
If we kissed why don't
I have any memory of it?
Look, I must've
been imagining things
so just forget
I ever mentioned it, okay?
I can't believe
you used my moment of weakness
as an opportunity
to take advantage of me!
I would never!
If anyone "took advantage"
it was you--
That was smooth.
You can't say something
like that and then try
to drop the conversation
without filling me in!
Please tell me!
I knew I should
never've opened my big mouth!
It's really not that big a deal.
I doubt you'd feel that way
if you were in my shoes.
Ow!
You don't have to be so rough!
She doesn't know
how strong she is.
The mental limiters
that suppressed her
strength must've
completely shut down.
If we had kissed, you wouldn't
lie about it, would you?
No, never!
My brother's becoming a man.
Took him long enough.
I've decided to keep
a video diary as well,
in order to document any and
all changes to Rea's condition.
No change to her thighs or feet.
[BABU meows]
No change to her upper arms,
or the nape of her neck.
Would you mind telling me why
you're following me around
with that video camera?
[CHIHIRO] I'm filming you.
I wanna document your condition.
No way!
You're filming me?
But you know how
painfully shy I am!
[CHIHIRO] Don't be embarrassed.
It's for your own good.
From now on, I'm gonna
videotape every nook and cranny
on your entire body
for my daily records.
C'mon, flash me that
pretty smile of yours!
You know you wanna!
Sometimes we have
to make sacrifices
in the name of science.
[JOGORO yells]
What are these
chunks of green pepper
doin' in my miso soup, Mero?
Calm down.
It's eggplant, Grandpa.
Well, I'll be damned.
Where's Rea?
Isn't she going to join us?
No she's terribly shy and
would rather eat by herself.
I made extra food
because I thought
she was going to be here.
[CHIHIRO] Sorry, but don't worry
about it in the future, okay?
She told me she
doesn't want to have
an impact on
the family budget.
I wouldn't have let her move-in
if I thought we couldn't
afford to feed her.
Please let her know
I don't mind doing the shopping
and cooking for the house
because I enjoy taking
care of those around me.
Yeah.
Sure, I'll let her know.
And here I thought
it'd be smooth
sailing once she moved-in.
They'll get suspicious if she
never joins them for a meal.
I suppose she could always
just go through the motions.
Here ya go.
I brought over a couple of
things I thought she might need.
You mean like
underwear and stuff?
I'm not letting
anybody borrow my underwear.
I can pick some up
for her tomorrow.
Later.
Hey, Wanko?
Rea and I aren't
a couple or anything.
Honestly.
Why are you offering me excuses?
Look, I'm telling you,
it's not an excuse!
Whatever you say. Ciao!
Hold on a second!
Don't yell at me!
Thanks for bringing this.
While I appreciate
her generosity,
I guess Rea doesn't really
need a change of clothes.
Now that she's a zombie,
she has no metabolism.
Then again, she's still a girl,
I'm sure she'd like
to wear something
other than one of my shirts.
I can't help but
feel kinda sad for them.
They used to be so full of life.
But now, they're
completely devoid of it.
They're no longer a part
of the world of the living.
What's up, Chihiro?
Nothing.
Can I come in?
Got a change of clothes for you.
Oh, thanks!
I appreciate it!
And in a way, I'm the one
who did this to them.
Hey, Rea?
This is all I have to do?
Just walk normally?
[CHIHIRO] Pretty easy, huh?
According to Grandpa, all
you need is moderate exercise
so there's no reason
to overdo it.
If the people around us knew the
truth, it'd be mass hysteria.
But I suppose we look just like
any other couple out
for the evening.
They'd never
suspect she's a zombie.
As much as I'd like to think
I could recognize one,
I'd probably be fooled, too.
If I've learned
anything from this experience,
it's that there isn't much
difference between them and us.
Time passes the same for both
the living and the undead.
[REA] You know
what's weird?
[CHIHIRO] What's that?
I hope this
doesn't gross you out,
but I don't have to use
the restroom anymore.
Oh. Really?
And I never get
sleepy, either.
Yeah.
I kinda figured as much.
I'm really dead.
I guess it's finally
starting to sink in, you know?
It's funny.
You'd think I'd be depressed
but I'm actually quite happy.
I don't know what
happens to us when we die.
If we turn into ghosts or
whether there's an afterlife.
Honestly, I don't
think I'd want anything
to do with either
of those things.
I feel like they'd
make me unhappy
because I'd miss out on this.
What could be better
than taking a walk
and chatting with a friend?
I'm starting to think I'm cut
out for this zombie stuff.
I hope you know
how grateful I am.
If I hadn't run into you
I would've lived my whole life
without ever knowing
what it means to be free.
It's all thanks to you, Chihiro.
[CHIHIRO thinking]
Thanks to me
you're a rapidly
decomposing walking corpse.
It's only a matter of time 'til
you're back where you started.
I'll be here for you.
I promise.
I gave you my word
that I'd take care of you
and that's exactly
what I intend to do.
I know.
I only ask that you
treat my delicate body
with the utmost care.
You promise?
Geez, Rea!
Why'd you have to say it
all flirty like that?
Did I?
I didn't realize it
came out that way.
Yeah right,
you knew what you were doing!
C'mon, let's head home.
Yes, sir!
There's gotta be another
way for us to slow down
the decomposition of Rea's body.
At least long enough
for her to experience
the things she's missed out on.
Hydrangea leaves help
but what's gonna happen
when they
go out of season?
I'm determined
to keep her around
as long as I possibly can.
It's just a question
of how long that'll be.
Watch out!
That was a close one.
I'm so glad
I got to you in time!
Oh, Chihiro!
You've been injured.
What have I done?
I'm so sorry.
Just a little banged up.
I'm guessing those
strength inhibitors
aren't coming
back anytime soon.
Okay.
Are you sure?
Oh, no!
Hey, what're you doing?
That's nasty!
Cut it out, Rea!
Don't be a baby.
I'm just disinfecting it.
[MERO] You want me
to pick up the pace?
You got it.
My timing was off last time we
recorded one of these bad boys
but I'm gonna
get this in one take.
Watch and learn, gentlemen.
Next time on Sankarea,
Episode 7,
"Childhood... Friends..."
Can you guess which famous
Italian zombie film director
is the inspiration behind
my brother Chihiro's name?
The answer is Lucio Fulci!
Tune in to see Mero!
That was too fast?
Oh... What should I say?
Uh... Bye?