We thank you
for this meal.
[JOGORO] And now
we speak in unison.
Thank you for this meal.
[CHIHIRO] Ever since
Rea's resurrection,
I've been keeping a diligent
observational record of her.
And while it's an incredibly
important chronicle,
it's also a really sweet
gig for a high school boy.
C'mon.
Can't you at least take
a little break from filming
while we're
trying to eat dinner?
[CHIHIRO] It'd be a terrible
observational record
if I didn't detail
your eating habits, too.
True, but that doesn't
make it less irritating.
You mean thorough.
Now let me get a close
up of you chewing.
[DO'ON] Cut it
out, Chihiro.
Your sister didn't
labor over this meal
just for you to ignore it.
That's quite
enough with the camera.
Fine.
I take it that you're
a rather strict vegetarian, Rea?
Uh... you could say that.
[JOGORO yells]
No!
Whatever you do,
don't eat the miso soup
'cause it's been infested
by an army of mud snails!
Calm, down.
Those are shijimi clams.
[JOGORO gurgles]
I'll be damned.
Okay.
[REA giggles]
I've already made some
surprising discoveries
about Rea's condition.
First off, zombies don't need
any sleep to function normally.
I know it sounds great
to have that much
time on your hands,
but Rea says
it gets super boring
when the rest
of us are sleeping.
She showers out of habit,
but she no longer sweats.
And apparently...
...she doesn't even need
to use the bathroom anymore.
The effects of
the hydrangea leaves
seem to wear off
pretty quickly,
so she has to eat them
every few hours.
It was surreal
watching Babu spit out
an undigested wad
of hydrangea leaves
like he was coughing up
a normal, everyday hairball.
It made me wonder if Rea
was gonna do the same thing.
I decided it would be
best to have my camera
at the ready just in case.
You'll let me know
if you're about
to cough up anything
weird, won'tcha?
Are you saying I should expect
to cough up something?
Look.
I've had enough of your
never-ending surveillance thing.
I feel like I should get
something in exchange, you know?
[CHIHIRO] Like...?
[REA] I'd like to do something
a normal girl would do.
[CHIHIRO] What'd
you have in mind?
[REA] Check it out, Chihiro!
Don't you love these ruffles?
Yeah.
Nothin' I love more than pink,
ruffly girl crap.
C'mon, Chihiro.
Can't you try
to take this seriously?
I don't get to pick out
new clothes that often.
I get this is
a big deal for you.
But you haven't been able to
decide on a single outfit yet.
Because I need your help!
You're the one who's paying
for this stuff after all.
I want to make sure I get
something that looks nice on me.
Yeah, yeah, I know,
but do you have any idea
how much longer that'll take?
Would you mind if
I got a hat, too?
Yeah, that's fine I guess,
just try not
to break the bank, okay?
Mmhmm!
Well, there goes
this month's allowance.
It's a good thing
it's overcast today.
We need to keep her out of
the sun as much as possible.
We shouldn't risk speeding up
her body's decomposition.
But that's how badly
she wants to be a normal girl.
There's really no point keeping
a record of her shopping spree.
S'not like I'm making this
video for the sake of memories.
Oh, totally,
that is such a cute dress
and the color will look
fabulous with your complexion.
Hey, no fair!
Give it back!
See?
It looks sick
with your skin tone.
Thanks.
She's so excited just shopping.
It's nothing to me,
but I guess Rea's
never had the freedom
to do the stuff that
normal girls do every day.
I do believe I deserve
a nice, long bath.
That's the stuff.
I didn't know it was so quiet
in here in the middle
of the day.
Maybe even a little too quiet.
Look, guys.
I made a promise to Rea
that I would take care of her!
"The water's fine"
what a load of BS.
I've never seen
Chihiro so serious.
It's kind of unsettling.
I know that Miss Sanka
is technically a zombie
and that's, well,
a pretty big deal to him.
But regardless,
she's living with him now
and he didn't even bother
to say anything to me about it.
And I've gained some weight.
Damn it!
What is with him?
All he thinks about anymore
is Rea this and Rea that!
Can't he at least
try to think about my--
What're you doing here, Ranko?
Oh crap, it's Mero.
[RANKO laughing]
What a coincidence!
How's it goin'?
Hello, Ms. Ranko.
[RANKO giggles]
Sorry to barge in on you.
You must also know that it's
less crowded this time of day.
Yeah.
Nice and quiet, and I'm in
serious need of some relaxation.
A busy morning
at the restaurant.
[RANKO laughs nervously]
Are you just
starting out the day
or are you headed
home after this?
I'd think you ladies would
be out shopping or something.
Not today.
We thought it'd be
nice to go to the bathhouse
instead of the mall for once.
I don't suppose
you have any idea
what Chihiro's up to today?
Well, I haven't seen him
since this morning
but he told me he
was gonna head into town
to go shopping
at that new mega mall.
I think he said he was gonna buy
some new clothes for Lady Rea.
Oh, that sounds lovely.
I'm glad the two of them
are having so much fun lately.
You know what?
You just convinced me that I'm
in need of another bath, Mero!
Let's drown our troubles!
All four of us!
You can keep me company
for the rest of the day!
Bombs away!
[bath water splashing]
I think the steam
is getting to you.
I finally found something!
Sorry it took so long.
You look really nice.
Huh?
I couldn't quite hear
what you just said.
Maybe that's because
I didn't say anything.
Did too.
I saw your mouth moving.
That doesn't
mean I said anything.
But you did.
C'mon, why don't
you want to repeat it?
Huh?
I didn't realize you bought
something too, Chihiro.
Oh.
Yeah.
Really?
What did you get?
You mind if I take a peek?
Can it wait until we
sit down or somethin'?
Okay.
So, is there a particular store
you want to check out next?
Wait, you mean we're
not done for the day?
Of course not, silly!
We've only been to one store!
I thought you'd
want to hear this.
We've located the
target and followed her
to a mall just outside of town.
She seems to be alone
with the Furuya boy.
How would you like
us to proceed, sir?
Hmm.
Maintain your
clandestine vantage point
and continue
surveillance as before.
Look over there!
That looks fun. C'mon!
There's no need to rush this.
We'll only have one chance.
Stand by until the Furuya
boy leaves her side.
And then execute.
As you wish, sir.
[ZOMBIE growls]
[GIRL yells]
Ooh.
This is pretty well-made
for the most part.
It's particularly
convincing from a distance.
But it looks rough
when you look up close.
The stitching is a bit messy
and you can see
the seams in a few places.
It's not quite
movie quality, huh?
[CHIHIRO whimpering]
Chihiro?
[REA laughing]
You can't be serious!
You're telling me
that you of all people
were spooked by a hokey
haunted house inside the mall?
Geez, you don't have
to be such a jerk about it.
I know it seems ironic
since I love zombie movies.
But face-to-face is
a different thing, okay?
Oh, yeah?
Well, you're doing
just fine now.
You know what I'm saying.
It really isn't fair that
nothin' seems to scare you.
[REA laughing]
Come on!
If you're gonna laugh
don't do it to my face!
You don't like haunted houses
but you went in one anyway.
'Cuz I wanted to.
That means a lot to me.
Thanks, Chihiro.
Well, don't think that's gonna
be an everyday occurrence, okay?
I know.
Oh!
I forgot.
Here.
It's only gonna get hotter
throughout the summer.
So I figured we could
put dry ice in here.
I think it'll help
prevent you from decaying.
And that way you can feel
free to go outside and do stuff.
And, y'know you can even go back
to school, and do all that.
If you want.
If it works the way
I think it will
you can do
whatever you feel like.
You'll be able to act
like a normal girl again.
Oh, Chihiro.
Yeah?
[REA crying]
What.
Uh. Hey!
What's the matter?
Oh, crap, I didn't do
something wrong, did I?
Not at all.
Nobody's ever done
something so thoughtful for me.
And I can't begin to tell
you how happy it makes me.
But...
You won't believe this.
Apparently zombies aren't
capable of producing tears,
even when they want to.
Really?
You can't?
No, I can't.
Why are you laughing?
I'm sorry.
I just thought
you knew everything
there was to
know about zombies.
But hold on...
It just occurred to me
that I'm the first
zombie you've actually met.
That's right.
There's plenty I don't know.
So this gives you
the chance to learn from one.
A real-live dead girl.
[DAN'ICHIRO] Rea.
I'm certain you imagine you've
gained some form of freedom.
But you're mistaken.
It's nothing but
a counterfeit freedom!
You may have felt that
your stringent upbringing
was an infraction
upon your individuality.
But if you think you can
simply obtain your freedom
by absconding
from your loving home.
You're wrong!
Forget this nonsense
and come home to me.
Come back.
I will show you what
it truly means to be free!
[REA's stomach growls]
Uh-oh!
Not good.
I should eat before
it gets any worse.
Oh, yeah.
I should probably
grab a bite to eat as well.
You go ahead and start
and I'll be right back, alright?
Oh, okay.
I have to admit I kind
of miss eating regular food.
It does sort of suck
watching Chihiro eat
anything he feels like.
Food's the last thing
I should complain about.
I am dead, after all.
Obviously things
could be a lot worse.
Excuse me, Miss?
Rea Sanka?
[REA gasps]
Oh, it is you!
I was just thinking
about you and here you are!
Surely it can't
be a coincidence!
Uh.
So I guess it must be fate.
I'm sorry,
but have we met before?
Okay, you're
clearly joking, right?
You don't remember our
beautiful conversation?
Three whole sweet minutes!
I'm Chihiro's
best friend, y'know!
Oh, yeah, from
the school the other day.
Yep, that would be me!
So what're you up to today?
I was just doing a little
shopping but I'm done now.
You're already done?
What great news!
That means you have
time to hang out with moi.
Excellent!
I know a wonderful spot
where we can relax,
but it fills up quickly
so we'd better get there fast!
[REA ] Hold on.
Oh, my.
You must be
freezing cold in here.
Your arm feels like it
was carved from a block of ice.
No, it's normal.
Well don't you worry!
The place I have
in mind is nice and hot!
We'll warm you right back up!
Uh.
Where are you taking me?
Hold on!
I didn't agree to
go outside with you!
But it's so nice out!
It's a bright
and beautiful day!
Let's grab a seat and soak up
some sunlight while we talk!
What do you say?
No.
I'd rather not.
C'mon!
Let's grab that open bench
before someone steals it!
Look...
I would just...
I don't want to...
I'm not a big fan
of the sunlight.
Okay?
What?
You must be joking.
How could anyone
possibly not love the sun?
I mean, look at how
gorgeous it is out here!
Look!
You have a lovely
fair complexion,
but you could use some
more color in your cheeks.
She's still got
that kid with her,
but this could
be our only chance.
She's by the exit and
there aren't many witnesses.
Come on!
It looks good to me.
What do you think,
should we go?
Let's make our move
while we can.
Execute!
I'll deal with
the obnoxious kid.
Make sure to keep
the timing tight.
Three.
Two.
One.
It's go time.
What the--
Where'd she go?
She is freakishly powerful!
Her old man wasn't kidding
when he said she'd
be hard to capture!
Get off of me!
Somebody help me!
I can't even get her to budge!
Dammit!
Where the hell is she?
Stop!
Help me!
That's her.
I'm coming!
Rea, are you okay?
Get away from me!
No!
Uh.
It's alright now, Rea.
Oh, I was so scared!
I just don't know
what I would've done
if you hadn't
come to save me!
Well uh.
Looks like you did
all the saving yourself.
Except for
the bench you killed.
Man, how did you not
dislocate your shoulders?
It's like you
got even stronger.
It was so scary, Chihiro.
Those creeps picked me up
and tried to kidnap me.
Are you still alive?
I don't know.
You have any idea who they are?
None at all.
Don't tell me
Yasutaka's in on it.
Guys, we don't have a choice.
We've gotta resort
to Plan B at this point.
Alright.
Why don't you tell me
who you guys are?
And why you
tried to kidnap Rea.
Talk or I call the cops.
Did you hear me?
Start talking!
You work for
her father, don't you?
No, look out!
Chihiro!
Rea.
Geez!
No!
Don't take him away from me!
You have my deepest apologies.
We waited until
your daughter was alone
and before we tried
to apprehend her it's just.
Lemme go!
Untie me you freakin' jerks!
Who are you people?
You're not gonna
get away with this!
To be perfectly frank, sir,
she easily overpowered
us and managed to get away.
We had no other choice but
to move forward with Plan B.
How would you like us
to proceed, Master Dan'ichiro?
Should we get rid of the boy
and pursue Rea again?
Actually I'd like you
to bring him to me.
As you wish, sir.
This works out perfectly.
There is much he
and I need to discuss.
Isn't that right, Furuya?
Mero?
Oh, Mero?
I think it's clear.
Here goes.
Next time--
Next time, on Sankarea,
Episode 9.
"A Mother's... Hand..."
Tune in to see Mero!
That's how it's done.
Well, it would've been better if
Ranko hadn't dropped her line,
and let's not overlook the fact
that this script is terrible.
Ugh, it's bad enough
having to read this crap once
and now we have
to do a second take?
Sorry, Mero.