[CHIHIRO] I've gotta
help her somehow.
[BABU meows]
I have to do whatever
I can to preserve Rea's body.
[BABU meows]
Sweet dreams, Rea.
[CHIHIRO sighs]
[REA giggles]
Rigor mortis has already
begun to take hold of her body.
If this keeps up,
it won't be long
before she's been
eaten by decay.
First thing I need to do,
is figure out how
to maintain her body,
starting with reversing
the effects of the rigor mortis.
[birds tweeting]
[gong dinging]
[MERO] A book explaining
how to preserve a body?
[CHIHIRO] Yeah.
I remember seeing you read one.
I kinda need to
urgently borrow it.
Oh.
You must be talking
about the medical book
on various methods of embalming.
I don't have it,
I loaned it out to a classmate.
One of your classmates?
What kind of
middle schooler is this?
One who is currently between
elementary and high school.
Yeah, thanks for
breaking that down for me.
Maybe I should be asking
what you need such a book for.
Uh, just uh...
The usual reasons.
You know what, never mind.
[door slides open and shut]
What's up with him?
He's been acting weird.
[CHIHIRO writing
with permanent marker]
I don't think it
should be too hard
to get my hands
on some formaldehyde.
But I've heard it gives off
a really powerful,
really awful stench.
[CHIHIRO sniffs]
So the smell
would make it tough
to hide her from my family.
The way she is right now,
she just looks
like she's sleeping.
Alright, kids,
it's getting pretty late.
You've gotten
enough sleep, get up.
Uh, yeah, one more minute!
I can't just leave her
out in the open like this.
I guess that's my only option.
There.
Y'know.
This situation is making it
kinda tough to be a gentleman.
Ow.
[CHIHIRO gasps]
[CHIHIRO heart beating]
C'mon, Chihiro,
what's going on up there?
[CHIHIRO] Aw man,
this sucks.
I'm on my way, okay?
I know it's
a little uncomfortable,
but the stiffness should
be gone by this evening.
I'm sorry it's
so cramped in here,
but we've gotta try
to keep you out of sight.
Okay?
[REA's stomach gurgles]
Geez.
What the hell was that noise?
Your stomach?
It's been a while
since you've eaten.
You must be hungry, huh?
Well, uh...
We've gotta get
you moving first.
But as soon as you can,
I'll get you something to eat.
I'm comin' down now, Dad!
[hands clapping]
We're thankful for this meal.
[CHIHIRO] Thank you
for all the grub.
[JOGORO] Thanks for
the green stuff.
[CHIHIRO] Our usual
breakfast routine.
What's the big deal?
Why'd you put all these fish
eyeballs in the miso soup Do'on?
Now calm down, Dad,
that's nothing but tofu.
[JOGORO yells]
[CHIHIRO]
It's the same as always.
Despite the undead girl
in my room.
I want to experience life.
To do things other girls
do that I haven't yet.
Hey Mero, what would
you consider "normal"?
Could you phrase that
question in even broader terms?
Right. Just forget I asked.
Alright, which one of you put
fish eyeballs in the miso soup?
Seriously Dad,
that's just tofu.
[RANKO] Thank you.
Have a nice day.
This is bad.
I can't believe
she's gone missing.
Oh hey, Ranko!
I wasn't expecting
to see you here.
Really?
You're the one
surprised to see me?
So what brings you here?
Do you know the Sankas?
I was making a delivery.
Should I ask why you were hiding
out in their bushes or what?
I was just trying
to check on my friend.
Their daughter Rea
is one of my classmates
and she didn't
show up at school today.
I was worried something
bad might've happened to her.
So I just wanted
to see if she's okay.
From the bushes?
What, are you allergic
to front doors or something?
Why don't you just
go ask them how she is?
No way, I can't do that!
Rea is like the most
popular girl in our class!
I mean, as far as
the entire school goes,
you're definitely more
popular but in our class.
well, you know, she's--
[RANKO] It's cool.
No need to explain.
[HELEN] It's strange.
I can't quite
put my finger on it,
but something about
Rea has been off lately.
I mean, she's still just
as awesome as she's always been,
but she seemed kinda
sad the last few days.
And this was
an unexcused absence!
It just feels like
there's something really wrong.
[RANKO] Ya don't say.
[HELEN] She may not seem
like a big deal to you,
since she's just a freshman,
but trust me,
she's pretty incredible, Ranko.
I can't think of
a single person in our class
who doesn't wanna
be her best friend.
And she treats
everyone like they are.
Here!
Just look at some
of these pictures.
Wait, hold on.
I've got so many of
'em in here, let's see.
Wow, it's like she's incapable
of taking a bad picture,
but I'll show you my favorite.
Amazing, huh?
She just looks so beautiful and
approachable in this picture.
This one's a pretty good
shot of the three of us.
And this one's
a runner-up for my favorite.
I couldn't really get close
enough to the house to tell
but it kinda looked to
me like her family's maids
were freaking out
about something.
I don't know.
How'd it look on the inside?
[RANKO] Well, there was
definitely a commotion.
[HELEN] What do
think is going on?
Now I'm really worried.
Do you suppose something
could have happened to her?
Ranko! I was talking to you!
Geez.
[CHIHIRO] No school today!
That's right, I've got
the whole day to hang out
with my family,
and clean the temple.
This really sucks.
Doesn't Dad know
there are bigger things
I could be dealing
with right now?
So, Chihiro.
I couldn't help but notice
there's been another
cat hanging around lately.
Wouldn't you rather
take a little more time
to properly mourn
Babu's passing?
Geez, it's not like that, Dad.
Babu's returned
from the dead, that's all.
Well, denial is
a stage of grief.
Hey, Grandpa,
you saw Babu, right?
Sure, I saw him.
It was unmistakably Babu.
Ya hear that?
Grandpa Jogoro can
back me up on this.
[JOGORO laughing]
[CHIHIRO laughing]
That's right, it's true!
Dadu and my Sada have
both returned from the dead!
Yeah, y'see,
Dadu and Sada have--
Hey, wait a minute,
who's Sada?
And it's Babu, not Dadu!
[MERO] Nobody told me
dementia was contagious.
The reanimation potion I made
deserves to be recognized
throughout the world!
Yeah, you're right!
Your reanima--Huh?
Whoa, wait, Grandpa.
Can you repeat
what you just said?
Well, sure.
"Throughout the world."
No, before that!
Repeat the entire sentence!
The reanimation potion?
Are you trying to tell
me that you know about it?
Wait, does this
mean you're the one who...
Quit putting words in my mouth!
I didn't!
Yes, you did!
Doesn't sound like me.
I'm gonna take a bath.
What?
Hey, hold on!
[DO'ON] Alright, I admire
the creative excuse.
But you're not getting
out of cleaning that easily.
[MERO] For shame,
Brother. For shame.
[CHIHIRO] Fine, sorry.
[BABU yawns]
[CHIHIRO] Okay,
let's sort this
out. Grandpa obviously
knows something
about the reanimation potion.
And knowing him,
he's definitely
capable of creating it.
If that's the case,
he's gotta know a method
for staving off
the decomposition process.
A way to preserve Rea.
[MERO] Hey, Brother?
[CHIHIRO yelps]
[CHIHIRO] Don't sneak up on me!
[MERO] Something occurred to me.
It's been a matter of weeks
since your room was
last cleaned properly.
As always.
I figured I would offer
to clean it for you later.
[CHIHIRO] Uh, yeah, thanks.
Wait, Mero, not so fast!
I'll do it myself.
You've already got
enough cleaning to do.
[MERO] I am officially
worried about you now.
[CHIHIRO] Uh, no, no.
I just...
I know it sounds weird,
but I've actually
started to enjoy cleaning.
Crazy, huh?
I just never realized
how much fun it was before.
So, really...
I got it.
[CHIHIRO laughing]
[MERO] Alright,
I'm not gonna argue.
Weirder every day.
[RANKO] Someone
call for delivery?
[CHIHIRO] Ugh, not you again.
[DO'ON] Oh, look, it's Ranko.
[CHIHIRO] Why are you here?
This is two days in a row.
I was in the neighborhood
making a delivery
and thought I'd stop by.
I brought some
lunch for you guys.
That's one less
meal to cook today.
Indeed.
Thank you, Lady Ranko.
Your generosity
is quite remarkable.
And somewhat rare.
This one's too busy
thinking about zombie movies.
He could learn
a thing or two from you.
But with the time
it would take him to learn,
you might as well marry him.
Oh c'mon, don't
tease him that way!
There's no way he'd
ever land a girl like me!
[RANKO] Oh yeah,
I almost forgot.
Did you hear
the news, Chihiro?
I doubt it.
I've been here all day.
That girl Rea you
were asking about?
Well, apparently, she ran
away from home yesterday.
Really?
Well, I'll be.
[CHIHIRO] Weird, huh?
Her family are
customers of ours,
so this is first hand info.
I dropped off a delivery earlier
and their house
was complete chaos.
I guess rich girls have their
share of problems, too, huh?
Uh... Guess so.
Or maybe.
Maybe she was forbidden
from seeing her one true love
and they decided
to elope together
in an act of defiant romance!
Well that's a positive spin.
Unlikely though.
Picture it!
The two of them alone
together in a small guest room
with a view of the sea.
They were destined
to live separate lives,
but chose to fight it.
They refused to
accept their destiny.
Determined to share
their love forever.
Y'know.
I just realized
she could've run away
to come live with you, Chihiro.
Huh?
It does make sense.
That creepy friend of yours
said you were spending
a lot of time with her.
Be honest, you're her
star-crossed lover, aren't you?
How many times do
I have to explain this?
I happened to bump
into her one night
while I was walking around town.
We had, like,
maybe 20 minutes
of polite conversation, if that.
Geez, what's with
the interrogation;
why do you care who I talk to?
I'm practically
your older sister.
It's only natural I'm concerned
with the type of people
you associate with.
No, it's not natural,
but I hardly know the girl.
Alright.
Fine, I believe you.
Well I've gotta get home to help
out, so I'll see ya later.
Don't go and do anything stupid.
What the hell's
that supposed to mean?
Somebody's in a real mood today.
[DO'ON] Hey, Chihiro!
Don't forget you've still
gotta scrub out back, too!
Yeah, I know, Dad, I remember!
Hey, wait a minute.
I'm already here, I might as
well borrow another zombie DVD.
She said Rea's home
was a total mess.
Well, their daughter did die,
come back to life,
and then run away.
I doubt that's the kind of thing
parents take lightly.
Anybody in here? Nope.
Holy crap, it's cold in here!
You can't be serious.
He's running
the air conditioning
in the middle of the day?
Hmm, let's see, there's gotta
be a few I haven't borrowed yet.
They really don't get very
creative with the titles,
they all kinda sound the same.
Maybe this one?
What?
Why's it in the wrong case?
[BABU meows]
Eeny meeny miney moe,
pick a zombie by the toe.
If it's rotten and falls off.
Why can't I decide
on a damn movie?
Geez.
I keep picking
the ones I've already seen.
Why's there a long
black hair in here?
This can't be Chihiro's,
it's way too long.
Wait.
[RANKO gasps]
I felt like
I was being watched.
Oh yeah, I totally forgot
about Rea being hungry earlier.
I wonder what food
is good for an upset stomach.
But if she's a zombie,
does she eat?
No way, that's just fiction.
Whoa.
What's going on?
Who the hell are you?
That hurts!
Are you a freakin'
body builder?
Hold on!
I know who you are.
You're Rea Sanka, aren't you?
What are you--?
Stop!
Do you hear me?
[RANKO yells]
Get off of me!
Enough already!
Are you okay?
Were you in
an accident or something?
Your smile is creeping me out!
Let me up and
I'll call an ambulance!
There's something...
Not right...
Wait... No.
There's no way.
[RANKO gasps]
[RANKO yells]
Sounds like Wanko.
Oh crap.
Please just let her
have seen a spider!
Even a tarantula!
Hey Wanko!
Are you... Okay?
[RANKO moaning]
I guess this means
she's past the rigor mortis.
Hey!
What the--?
What's up with her?
It's kind of a long story.
Chihiro.
Just stay calm.
[RANKO screams]
[BABU meows]
[MERO] A ratings stunt?
This whole show
strikes me as a ratings stunt,
pandering to people's
base desires and blood lusts.
So what is this ratings stunt?
It's gratuitous nudity,
isn't it?
Next time on Sankarea,
Episode 6, "It's because I...
Ran into You."
Who can guess which famous
zombie movie director
inspired my name?
I'll give you a hint,
his first name is George!
That's right, George Romero!