[DAN'ICHIRO panting]
[SITUJI] Dear God,
how could this happen?
Master Dan'ichiro, sir?
[DAN'ICHIRO] Rea?
Rea!
[SITUJI] Master!
[DAN'ICHIRO] I can't
believe you're alive.
I was worried
I'd lost you forever.
You're drenched in blood.
Come, we need to
get you to a hospital.
[DAN'ICHIRO gasps]
[REA] What is it?
Is something wrong?
Rea... I can't seem
to find your pulse.
Don't tell me that you're...
[REA giggles]
[DAN'ICHIRO gasps]
[REA] You can't find my pulse
because I no longer have one.
I died but I've been reborn.
[DAN'ICHIRO] What is
that supposed to mean?
Wait!
You can't just
walk away from me.
You're my beloved daughter!
[REA] Not anymore.
Now that I've been reborn,
I'm not the daughter
you once held dear.
No amount of pleading
can bring me back to you
because I'm no longer
a living being.
[DAN'ICHIRO panting]
[REA giggles]
That can't be true.
It's not possible.
[MAIDS] Did you hear the rumor?
Which one?
Apparently, the reason
Miss Rea's been sneaking out
each night is to
meet up with a boy!
Yeah, yeah, that's old news.
I've got the latest
if you wanna hear it.
Yeah, of course
we do, Natsukawa.
One of the other maids told me
Miss Rea ran away from home.
She did?
[ARIA drunk] Would you
care to elaborate?
[MAIDS gasps]
Please excuse us.
We didn't realize you
were home yet, ma'am.
Good afternoon,
Madam Aria.
Start explaining
before I lose my temper.
Yes, ma'am.
One of the other maids told
me she heard Master Dan'ichiro
say Miss Rea wouldn't
be coming home again.
Where is he?
As soon as he walked in,
he went straight
for the bathroom
and he's been
in there ever since.
In the bathroom?
Out of my way!
Look busy!
Last time I checked,
you get paid to work,
not stand around and gossip.
Middle of the day and
she already reeks of booze.
I didn't know host clubs
were open in the afternoon
'til I started working here.
That's where she's been going?
Can't say I blame her,
Master Dan'ichiro
practically ignores her
so she probably enjoys
the attention, you know?
[door slams open]
Darling!
What's this I hear
about Rea running away?
She fell off a cliff and died,
but she got back up again.
What?
I watched her die,
and I watched her get up
and walk away from me.
What is with you?
Look.
If word got out our daughter
ran off, I'd be ruined.
I could lose my position
as Sanka Academy's chairman.
Well?
Do you have any
idea where she went?
[SITUJI] Madam.
Though I don't know
her exact location,
I would venture to guess
she's with the Furuya boy.
And who's that?
Never heard the name before.
He's... the one.
She chose him over me.
He is the wretched boy
who seduced my little girl.
None of this would've happened
if it weren't for him!
Furuya!
I won't surrender
to the likes of you!
You may have her heart now.
But I won't rest
until my beloved daughter
has returned to me!
[CHIHIRO] One of
the more unique courses
at Sanka Private Girls' Academy
is "Meditative Needlework."
Before their
first period class,
students sit quietly
for ten minutes
as they pass a needle
through a piece of cloth.
School officials claim
it's a beneficial form
of mental gymnastics
and therefore require
that it be done every day.
I guess if nothing else,
it teaches the
girls basic sewing
and the value of meditation.
[REA] It's relaxing.
I used to get up early
so I could do "meditative
needlework" before school.
I've done it every morning
since I was just a little girl.
[CHIHIRO] That explains it!
I was wondering how you
were so calm about this.
Bet you never
thought you'd use
your skills to sew up
your own skin, huh?
Ugh, that's so gross!
Sorry but I need
you to hold it closed.
It shouldn't take
me much longer, okay?
[REA humming]
[REA giggles]
It's kinda nice not being
able to feel pain, you know?
Maybe it hasn't
completely sunk in yet,
but do you realize
you died today?
Your skin's cold,
you don't have a pulse,
you've lost all feeling,
and your pupils are dilated.
So why in the hell
are you so happy?
I'm sorry.
I guess I can't help myself.
It's silly but
this is the first time
I've been in a boy's bedroom,
so I'm a little bit giddy.
[CHIHIRO] Okay.
[HELEN sighs]
It's good to be
done for the day!
Do you wanna hang with me?
Let's stop by a café on our way
home and get something sweet?
There's a place
around the corner
that has the prettiest
pastries in the window.
[RANKO] I wish I could,
but I've got a score
to settle after school.
[HELEN] Oh, that's a shame.
Maybe tomorrow then?
You're gonna pay, Chihiro.
Being worried about
Babu was no excuse
for leaving me
stuck in that hole!
It took me forever
to wriggle out on my own!
I am so gonna wring your neck!
Why? I just asked if
you wanna go tomorrow.
Sure, I'd love to go
to the café with you!
[REA sighs]
I can't get over
how beautiful it is outside.
[CHIHIRO thinking]
I know she can't go home
but I hope she doesn't think
she's staying here tonight.
There's only so much
temptation a man can take.
You think you're
pretty slick, don't you?
I wasn't looking!
I swear I wasn't!
What? I just
spotted Babu in a tree.
Look!
Over there!
[CHIHIRO] Yep, that's him.
Good grief.
What the heck is he doing
all the way up there?
Hey Babu!
C'mere kitty!
Huh.
His eyes aren't cloudy
like they were before.
[BABU meowing]
Is it just me or does
it sound like he might
be suffering from
a case of the sniffles?
No, I named him Babu
because of that weird meow.
When I first took him in
I was worried he might be sick
but the vet assured me
he was perfectly healthy.
That's just the way he meows.
Aw, the poor little guy.
I can't believe I was so worried
and he was probably
chillin' in a tree all day.
[REA giggles]
[BABU meows]
He says that tree is the most
comfortable one he's found.
Huh?
Are you telling me you
understand what my cat's saying?
Well, not word-for-word,
but I get the general idea.
Right, Babu?
[CHIHIRO thinking] Apparently,
zombies have the ability
to communicate
regardless of their species.
I find it interesting
that their transformation
hasn't seemed to affect
their personalities at all.
Is something on your mind?
Well, yeah,
but it's nothing, really.
Ah.
Bet I know what it is.
You're disappointed I don't
act more like the zombies
you've seen in
the movies, aren't you?
"Brains" I'm not very good
at this but you get the idea.
[REA giggles]
As if I didn't find
her hot enough as it is.
I don't understand how
you can be so lighthearted
about becoming a zombie.
I mean, doesn't
it make you anxious?
Of course.
At the same time, I feel better
knowing you'll take care of me.
Lemme ask you something,
when you say I'm going
to "take care" of you,
what do you mean by that?
What exactly do
you want me to do?
I'm almost afraid to hear
what her answer's gonna be.
I don't know guess
I hadn't thought about that.
I'd like for us to
go shopping together.
Maybe take a trip to the museum?
Huh?
And I would love for you to
show me some more zombie movies!
I feel like
I'm forgetting something.
Oh yeah, I want to go
to the amusement park!
And the summertime
festivals, too!
If I didn't know any better,
I'd think she's
looking for a boyfriend.
I'm so sorry,
it sounds like a lot
but it's really quite simple.
I just want to experience life.
Do things other girls
do that I haven't yet.
Lemme get this straight,
you wanna have the same
experiences as normal girls
even though you're a zombie?
Yeah!
Is there some reason I can't?
If there is, please tell me!
No, that shouldn't be a problem.
I just wanted to clarify.
Holy crap is she strong.
[CHIHIRO's heart beating]
Oh, Chihiro.
I don't know.
What's come over me.
Are you sure about this?
[CHIHIRO'S heart beats faster]
[RANKO] Where are you, loser?
Chihiro!
Get your ass out here!
Aw crap, what
does she want?
I'm surprised you're brave
enough to show your face
after you ditched
me this morning!
Do you have someone
in your room, you perv?
No, I'm all alone
up here, I swear!
Then it's okay
for me to join you?
I didn't say that!
Just wait there
and I'll come out!
Why can't I come in?
'Cause you might see
something you don't wanna see.
It's not like finding your porn
stash is gonna scar me for life.
You wanna bet?
Fine, I'll wait here.
I'm gonna see what she wants
but don't leave this
room while I'm gone.
I'll make it quick.
All right, if you wanna talk,
follow me down to the riverbed!
What the hell?
Why can't we talk here?
Because I don't want my family
to hear your filthy mouth.
Now come on, let's go!
I'm so confused, what was
I about to do to Chihiro?
I don't know what came over me.
What is this strange feeling?
Sorry, I didn't
mean to ditch you.
How was I supposed
to know you were stuck?
How did you not
hear me calling you?
All I could think about
at school was kicking your ass!
Geez!
I said I was sorry!
Well, did you ever find Babu?
Yeah, he hasn't
attacked anyone yet
so I guess he's
gonna be okay.
Good grief.
I don't get why you
refuse to carry a cell phone.
It certainly would've
come in handy this morning.
I don't have enough
friends to need a cell.
What's gonna happen to Babu
now that he's become a zombie?
Do you think he's immortal?
Huh.
That's a really good question.
Hey!
Furuya!
What's up, Yasutaka?
Why are you glaring at me?
Damn you, Furuya!
You betrayed me!
Why didn't you tell me
you're friends with Rea?
Teach me your ways!
How'd you convince
a hot chick like her
to hang out
with a chump like you?
What kind of mojo
did you work on her?
Boys are weird.
Yeah, Yasutaka's
been in rare form today.
Excuse me.
Do you happen to be
talking about Rea Sanka?
Yeah, she's the only
Rea that matters in my book.
If you know her why
did you ask me about her?
I'm not sure what you're
trying to pull here Chihiro,
but I don't like it one bit!
Geez, she's barely
an acquaintance.
What's wrong with you guys?
Gimme a break!
Look, I couldn't
care less about
whatever's going
on between you two.
I just wanna know how
you landed such a hottie!
Well, that's a relief.
At least now we
know he's interested
in more than just zombie girls.
Not true, dude.
They're the only
females who do it for me.
There's no way I'd be interested
in a girl who's not a...
What's the matter?
Wow, it just hit me.
Now that Rea's a zombie,
she's basically my dream girl.
And she's sitting in my bedroom
right now waiting for me.
Talk about living
out your fantasies.
My life suddenly
got much more awesome.
The heck are you smiling about?
Don't be silly,
I'm not smiling.
What's taking so long?
It's getting pretty late.
I wonder how
Chihiro knows that girl.
She was wearing
a Sanka Academy uniform.
I know he said he didn't
have a girlfriend but...
C'mon, it's not
like finding your porn stash
is gonna scar me for life.
It's so quiet.
Guess I can leave
his room if nobody's home.
I should've asked
Chihiro if it's okay
for zombies to take a shower.
But what could it hurt?
I don't know why, but this
feels different than it used to.
Oh, I know.
It's because I can't feel
the temperature of
the water anymore.
Ah.
Still nice though.
I didn't know they
built bathrooms this small.
but I think it's kinda cute.
Well, this thingy's
weird looking.
I wonder what you use it for.
I don't think I've ever
seen anything like it.
I think maybe you use it
like this to do exercises with.
Where did he come from?
I thought nobody was home!
My dear Sada!
Is it really you?
Oh, how I've missed you!
I never imagined
you'd come back
from the dead and return to me!
I'm not Sada!
Let go!
I know it was my fault,
but I hope you can
learn to forgive me!
You've got the wrong person,
now please let go of me!
Is anybody home?
Sada!
What has gotten
into you, Grandpa?
My precious Sada
came back to life!
It seems our bond
of love is so strong
that not even death
could keep her away from me!
If that was true
you'd be in big trouble.
Grandma wouldn't
like hearing you
call her Sada when
her name was Kiyo.
I dunno.
Name doesn't ring a bell.
Hang on...
what was I doing just now?
Oh, for Pete's sake.
Thank goodness I got
away from him when I did.
If I were home, I'd be sitting
at the dinner table with Father.
But I'm in someone else's home.
Not only that,
I'm sitting in a boy's bedroom
in nothing but a towel.
It's hard to believe how much
has happened in just one day.
I'll admit, it's a little scary.
I couldn't be happier
because I'm free.
But most of all, I don't have
to suffer my father's abuse.
Ever again.
That took a lot longer
than I expected.
I don't think I've ever met
anyone with as much
energy as Yasutaka.
If only I could
convince him to use it
for something productive
instead of always pestering me.
Welcome home, Brother.
For dinner, we'll be
having a delicious stew
made from the innards
of various animals.
I'm gonna have to pass.
I don't have
much of an appetite.
I'm surprised
Mero hasn't found her yet.
I'm back.
Hey.
Chihiro, you're back.
Do you wanna explain why you're
wearing nothing but a towel?
I'm sorry, it's because I took
a shower while nobody was home.
Yeah, I figured.
You're still soaking wet.
You're gonna catch a cold.
Nah.
You don't have
to worry about me.
After all, zombies don't
catch colds the way people do.
I guess you're right.
Wait a second, it just hit me!
The conversation
we're having right now.
It's the same kind
of loveable banter
I've always fantasized about
having with a zombie girl!
So how are you keeping up, Rea?
Your stomach's not bothering
you or anything, is it?
I don't feel any pain.
Bud I guess that's only
normal for a zombie, huh?
I can't take it!
This is too much!
Is there
something wrong, Chihiro?
Nothing at all!
Just trying to keep
myself in check now
that all of my wildest
dreams are coming true.
It'd be easier for me
if you'd put some clothes on.
Yeah.
I'd love to, but...
I'm afraid I'm not
really able to do much
of anything,
other than lay here.
I don't know what's wrong.
All of a sudden by body got
stiff and I couldn't move.
Is that why your
speech is slurred?
I just thought you were talking
funny because I woke you up.
No, it's because I can't move.
How could this happen?
Is the reanimation
potion wearing off?
I need to check something.
They won't budge, which means.
Rigor mortis is setting in.
Rigor mortis?
Never heard of dat.
Oh. It's not a big deal.
Just a natural phenomenon.
There's nothing to worry about.
Chihiro, you're so smart.
That makes me feel better.
Thanks for taking care of me.
Yeah, sure.
Rea's so full of life
I forget she's dead.
Her body's deteriorating.
It's a good thing
she can't feel pain
'cause I bet
it'd be excruciating.
Thank you, Chihiro.
I've got to find
a way to slow down
the decomposition process
before her flesh starts to rot.
Otherwise,
she'll be nothing more
than a skeleton
within a few months.
I can't let that happen.
I just want to experience life.
Do things other girls
do that I haven't yet.
I have to do whatever I can.
To preserve Rea's body.
Let me get this straight,
you want me to "dial it back"?
What do you mean by that?
My read doesn't
fit the character?
Do you realize
how ridiculous that sounds?
Hello, I am the character.
Next time on Sankarea,
Episode 5, "If She's
a Zombie... That Means..."
Tune in to see Mero!
I'm in this for the long haul,
and I'm not gonna let
your less than constructive
criticism break me down.