[birds tweeting]
[WALLA: SCHOOLGIRLS]
[REA giggling]
[REA] It would be a lie
to say I never had any fun.
Oh, don't act surprised.
I totally told you so.
[REA] But I always assumed
everyone else was like me,
hiding their painful
secrets behind their laughter.
Yeah, that doesn't
make me any less surprised.
I'm outright shocked.
[WALLA: MOVIE ZOMBIES]
[MOVIE NURSE 2A screaming]
Why don't you relax?
Oh. It's just
an intense movie.
So um...
Those people...
They're ripping open
her stomach and eating her
but I thought
they were her friends.
Well, they were, but
zombies are more concerned
with things
like eating people.
Seriously?
[CHIHIRO]
I'm kinda surprised.
This is her
first zombie movie
and I picked a pretty damn
gruesome one to break her in.
But, man,
she is really into it.
So much blood...
and guts...
[CHIHIRO] Not what I expected
from the sheltered rich girl.
Anyway, I sure could use
some help right about now.
Oh, geez, I'm so sorry.
I must've zoned out.
[CHIHIRO] You mind
plucking these?
[REA] Sure.
Mind if I ask which type
of poisonous plant
you're going to try
in the potion today?
[CHIHIRO] Eh, I couldn't
think of one.
Huh?
Even if we follow
this recipe to the T,
I sincerely doubt
that we're ever
gonna reanimate
the dead with it.
And besides, we don't even
know what it says on this page.
But... Chihiro.
Don't tell me
you're giving up on Babu.
[CHIHIRO] I should
just bury him again.
[REA gasps]
I guess that would
be kinda wasteful.
On second thought,
maybe we should eat him instead.
No!
How could you
even think that?
I... I couldn't
do that to Babu.
[CHIHIRO] It's like she's
never heard a joke before.
We've hit
a brick wall here.
I'm pretty sure
I've thoroughly exhausted
all the poisonous plant
options in our town.
Morning glory,
lily of the valley,
water hemlock,
Chinese plums...
and that's all
I can think of.
[REA gasps] I just
thought of something.
Wait here,
I'll be back in a minute.
Hey... where
are you going?
[REA gasps]
[CHIHIRO gasps]
[CHIHIRO] She's full of
all sorts of surprises.
[REA] My father's affections
had always felt
calculating and unbalanced.
Come over here,
Mistress Rea.
The pretty pink bunny rabbit
says she wants
to play with you now.
[YOUNG REA gasps]
That's it.
You can do it.
[YOUNG REA giggles]
Oh, be careful now, Mistress.
It's okay, Mistress Rea.
Don't cry now.
You're big and strong,
you don't need to cry.
[REA] It wasn't long
before that maid
was released from
our employment.
[CAT meows]
[REA] That was the last
time I'd see a cat...
or those maids near our home.
[REA] The only
constant in my life
was my mother Aria's
spiteful disdain for me.
[DAN'ICHIRO] Okay, Rea.
Are you ready to take
your annual birthday photo?
[DAN'ICHIRO] Now, open your eyes
and give me a smile.
[REA] This was around
the time I began to realize
how absolutely not
normal these photos were.
[REA] My mother was
no longer hiding her resentment
for my father's
feelings toward me.
[REA] The treatment
was unbearable on both sides.
[REA] No matter where I went...
my father kept me under a
constant state of surveillance.
I could always feel their gaze.
Crawling over me like insects.
[JURI] Rea!
Hey, good morning!
[JURI] Are you okay?
You seem down.
[REA] I'm fine.
Just a little tired.
Good morning.
[REA] Juri was my first
true friend.
The first one I felt like I
could be myself around.
[REA] I only got to know
her because she came
from an affluent
family as well.
So my father approved
of our friendship.
[REA] I had always believed
I was perfectly normal,
and that everyone was hiding
their painful secrets
behind their laughter.
But my friendship with
Juri challenged this belief.
I began to see
their happiness was real.
[REA] And I realized
I was just unhappy.
[JURI] You're not joking?
[REA] No.
This is the first time I've...
I've told anyone.
[JURI] What he's doing
is just wrong, I mean.
Naked pictures of his daughter?
[REA] Yeah, I know.
[JURI] You can't let
him keep doing this.
You've gotta tell him to stop.
[REA] It's just...
[JURI] Look, don't be afraid.
My dad and I argue
all the time.
You've gotta tell him to stop
even if it causes a fight.
[REA] I don't think my dad
is like yours, though.
[JURI] What's the worst
he can do?
You're his daughter.
[REA] I soon came to regret
ever mentioning this to her.
And even more so...
listening to her advice.
[WALLA: ZOMBIE MOVIE HORDE]
What's the deal?
I sure hope she didn't get lost
in the mountains or something.
Great, now I can't stop
picturing her
falling off a cliff.
[MALE ZOMBIE MOVIE VICTIM 2A]
No. Please... God. No!
Calm down, she's too smart
to try anything dumb.
Or not!
What the hell is she
doing climbing up there?
[REA gasps and yells]
Chihiro? How?
Geez princess,
you need a full time nanny
to keep an eye on you.
What?
Don't be rude,
I was doing
perfectly fine
climbing up by myself.
So I should
let go then?
Well... since
you're here.
So... what was the point
of risking your life?
Well... it's just...
The only place I noticed
that these flowers were blooming
was down in that graveyard.
And I thought it'd be easier
to climb the slope
than take the long way.
You're pretty ballsy
for such a pampered princess.
I survived.
Besides, even if
you hadn't been there
to catch me, you could
just bring me back as a zombie.
[CHIHIRO] Hey, hold on.
I can't even successfully
reanimate my own dead cat!
And even if I could,
I don't remember ever saying
I would bring you back to life.
[REA] Fine.
I'll say it for you.
[CHIHIRO] Say what?
[REA] I want you to bring me
back whenever I die.
[DAN'ICHIRO] What was that?
[REA] Well, I...
I think I'm too old for this,
and I want you to stop.
[DAN'ICHIRO]
Where's this coming from?
It's only natural for a father
to keep a detailed record
of his daughter's
development my dear.
[REA] No, there's
nothing natural about it!
Why can't we just have
a normal relationship?
I want to be
a normal father and daughter.
That's all I'm asking.
[DAN'ICHIRO] Did you talk to
one of your friends about this?
[REA] Of course not.
[DAN'ICHIRO] I want you
to tell me who it was.
[REA] It doesn't matter who,
anyone would think it's wrong!
[DAN'ICHIRO] Rea, it really
hurts me you don't understand...
but I'll try
to explain it to you.
There's only one thing
in this world that's right.
[DAN'ICHIRO] And that
is the undying affection
a father feels for his daughter.
Father?
[REA] I knew that
couldn't be the end of it.
[WALLA: SCHOOLGIRLS]
[REA] Transferred?
[CLASSMATE 2A]
Yeah, something weird
happened with her father's job.
[CLASSMATE 2B] I heard
he was forced to resign.
I have no idea why.
[REA] He did it again.
He took someone
else I cared about.
[REA] You're still here!
I was so scared
I would never see you again.
[JURI] The place we're moving
to has a strict no pets policy.
My parents told me to leave
her at the animal shelter.
I'll never get to see her again.
[JURI]
Both of my parents
are acting really
messed up right now.
Treating me like
I did something wrong.
But I didn't.
Oh, don't act like
you don't know what's happening!
[JURI] What did you say
to your father about me?
Did you lie to him and blame me
for something horrible?
[REA] No! Of course not!
I would never!
[JURI] Being your
friend is the worst thing
that's ever happened to me.
[REA] He takes
everything from me.
Everything I care about.
[DAN'ICHIRO] I can tell
you still don't understand.
Happiness isn't one thing...
it's different for everyone.
The transcendent purity of
the affection I feel for you.
Other people can't fathom
that kind of happiness.
[REA] I never said
I wanted to fathom it.
[DAN'ICHIRO]
I'm sure someday you will.
Someday you'll see
how much I love you.
And you'll understand that
it's a one-of-a-kind love...
unlike anything
else in this world.
[DAN'ICHIRO] Rea, refusing
to understand the love
that I feel for
you is only going
to make someone else unhappy.
[DAN'ICHIRO]
You're my extraordinary girl.
Can you not see
how loving and happy
the home we've given you is?
Far happier than
any of your friends.
[DAN'ICHIRO]
Now then... Undress.
[REA] If my attempt
at happiness
is only going to ruin
it for someone else...
[DAN'ICHIRO] Happy birthday,
Rea... my love.
[REA] Then... I'll have to
accept a life without happiness.
[REA] Well? What are
you waiting for...
let's go ahead and mix
in the flowers I picked!
[CHIHIRO] Are you
sure that's poisonous?
[REA] Yeah, it's a hydrangea.
[CHIHIRO] Whoa, hold on,
are you telling me
that even normal old everyday
hydrangeas are poisonous?
[REA] Yep. You're right.
I guess it isn't such
a well-known fact about them.
But they're on
the Sanka family crest.
On top of that.
They bloom in most of
the gardens on our property.
My father is
obsessively protective of me
so he's wasted a lot
of breath warning me
not to eat them ever
since I was a little girl.
[CHIHIRO] Really?
But... I'm pretty sure
I've caught my grandfather
snacking on
hydrangea leaves before.
[REA] What?
Oh... Um...
Maybe some people
are immune to them?
Well, it doesn't matter,
we might as well
give them a shot, right?
Yeah, I guess
we might as well.
[CHIHIRO] There it is.
Would you mind
holding it for a second?
I'll get Babu.
C'mon little buddy.
Come back to life.
Please.
I'm ready
for the potion.
Here you go.
Okay Babu,
today's the day.
I'm sorry it
didn't work.
Uh, but, we can
still make it happen.
There's always tomorrow.
I bet we can find another
poisonous plant by then.
[CHIHIRO] No...
It's time to give up.
I feel bad putting
Babu through all of this
just 'cuz I want him back.
I miss him, but this has
already gone on for too long.
I'm really sorry,
little buddy...
but it's time to
put you in the ground.
Yeah...
I guess you're right.
It's a little
late to bury him tonight.
Let's meet here tomorrow
and give him a nice service.
I really appreciate all
you've done these past few days.
You've been a huge help.
[REA] Sure.
Well, I guess this is it.
The last time I'll ever see you.
Uh, joking.
So... time to head home.
Have a good night.
I'll see you tomorrow.
[CHIHIRO] Hey, are you alright?
[CHIHIRO] I just
noticed you're limping.
[REA] Oh. Oh...
I guess I must've
twisted my ankle
a little when I fell earlier.
But it looks worse than it is.
I'll be fine.
[CHIHIRO] Geez.
[REA] Hey, wait a minute...
just what do you
think you're doing?
Careful!
Watch where you
put your hands!
[CHIHIRO] There.
[REA] I can't help but ask
why I was born into my family.
Why couldn't
I have been born
into a normal home
like everybody else?
I just want
an ordinary life.
I want my smile to
be genuine... not a mask.
Greetings, Mistress Rea.
Welcome home.
[REA] Thank you so much.
[REA] And that's why
I want to be reborn.
I want another chance...
free from my family.
[REA] And if I can't be
reborn... I'd rather be...
You sure this is okay?
Yeah.
[CHIHIRO] Your house
is all the way
at the top of the hill, right?
I don't mind
taking you closer.
[REA] No, it's okay.
I'm not supposed
to be out right now
so I can't go
in through the front door.
I have to sneak in and out
using this secret path
through the bushes back here.
Thanks, though.
[CHIHIRO] Oh... gotcha.
[REA] The only
reason I'm out now
is because my father
hasn't caught on to me yet.
I think I really would need
your zombie potion
if he caught me.
[CHIHIRO] Her old
man is sounding
worse and worse
by the second.
[REA] Oh, I almost
forgot to give Babu back.
[CHIHIRO] Right.
[CHIHIRO] Well... see ya.
Try not to be late for Babu's
funeral tomorrow, okay?
I won't! I promise!
See ya!
[DAN'ICHIRO] Who does
she think she's fooling?
[DAN'ICHIRO] Rea!
[RANKO slaps REA]
[REA gasps]
[RANKO humming]
[gate opening and closing]
[RANKO] It's about time
you got home.
[CHIHIRO] You scared
the crap outta me, Wanko!
What the hell are
you doing here so late?
[RANKO] I came to return
the DVD I borrowed from you.
[CHIHIRO]
And somehow found yourself
hanging out
the bathroom window naked?
[RANKO] So I'm suddenly not
allowed to use your bathroom?
[RANKO] Now, then...
You gonna tell me where
you've been out to this late?
Or am I gonna have
to beat it out of you?
[CHIHIRO]
She caught me off guard!
What should I say?
[CHIHIRO] Well I bought
some ice cream earlier today
and then I kinda
fell asleep by the river.
[RANKO] That's the best
alibi you've got?
Shame it doesn't match up
with what Mero told me.
She said that you've been
running off and disappearing
until late in the night
ever since Babu died.
[CHIHIRO whimpers]
[RANKO] And she said
you're always carrying
that cooler with you.
[CHIHIRO] Oh...
Yeah, that...
Ya can't go to
the river without a cooler.
[RANKO] Alright, fess up...
what's in this thing?
[CHIHIRO] Don't touch it!
I'm serious!
[RANKO] Don't tell me
your obsession with zombies
has pushed you to do something
sick with Babu's body.
[CHIHIRO] No, don't!
[CHIHIRO and RANKO gasp]
[BABU screaches]
[RANKO] That did not just happen
because it's not possible.
[CHIHIRO] Wow.
I can't believe it
actually worked.
[REA] I'm sorry,
Chihiro and Babu.
I can't make the funeral.
He said he'll never let
me leave the house again.
He won't even
let me go to school.
And I know my father.
He means every word of it.
I'm so sorry.
I hope you don't mind...
but I took a little bit
of the potion.
I know it doesn't actually
bring the dead back to life.
But still...
I'm more concerned
with the poison in it.
I just want it
to work in reverse.
If I can't be reborn...
I would rather be... dead.
[MERO] Hey...
Why don't you just
go ahead and call it quits?
There's no way you're ever gonna
get people to watch this thing.
What?
It was well received in Japan?
You've gotta be kidding me.
[MERO] Next time, on Sankarea,
Episode 3, "Sanka... Rea..."
Tune in to see Mero!
[MERO] Let me speak to the
illiterate creep who wrote this.
I'd like to have
some real words with him.