I'm sorry about this.
Sorry about what? No,
what did you tell them?
Yahiro! What did you do?
They're arresting Shu?
It may not seem like it
now, but your friend
just did you a big favor.
No, Inori. Don't do it.
But, Shu, he's--.
Gai said to leave it be.
I won't feel guilty.
I can't apologize
for the world we live in.
So, Shu, maybe
you can answer this.
Here is the clue:
close-fitting underwear,
leggings, or tights.
Primarily for women
four characters long. Any
suggestions spring to mind?
I don't know.
Why? He set me up.
I'm so stupid.
How could I be so stupid?
It's panty hose! Well hose
for short. Nothing I hate
more than leaving blank spots
unfilled. And I've got
a few blank spots that I could
use your help filling in.
I've prepared
a nice little room
for you to think in.
It's a bit small,
but you'll be comfortable
enough. And you can take all
the time you need to help me
figure out this puzzle of ours.
What? What do you mean
Shu got taken in by GHQ?
What do they want with him?
I was there and I could hardly
believe what was happening,
but the teacher confirmed
that they arrested him.
He didn't do anything wrong.
I know he didn't.
You arrested Dr. Ouma's son?
Yes. I brought him
in on suspected ties
to Funeral Parlor.
Did I make the wrong call?
Not if you're right.
What's your impression so far?
Oh, he's guilty.
Aside from the evidence,
he's barely trying
to hide his complicity.
His buddy Yahiro
is quite the shutterbug.
Here we have Gai Tsutsugami,
self pronounced leader
of Funeral Parlor.
And here you are together.
Now what's a boy like
you doing hanging out
in the middle of a battle
zone with a known terrorist?
Good question.
You should be asking Gai that.
Look, Shu. It's no
exaggeration to say
that the food here is bad.
Much worse than
the school lunch line.
And I can't imagine
anybody would want to eat it
for the rest of their life.
I suggest you think about that
before you say anything else.
As you can see, he's trying
to keep quiet. He's familiar
enough with the group's leader
to call him by his first name.
But he doesn't display
any of the ideological
fixation characteristic
of most terrorists.
His involvement seems tangential
at best. In short, it's odd.
Take a look at this
and give me your analysis.
It's a pirate feed
simultaneously transmitted
to multiple news portals
seven minutes ago.
A warning to GHQ.
Funeral Parlor will raid
your Isolation Factory
number Four tomorrow.
You're welcome
to try to stop us.
But I can assure you that
we will rescue our comrade.
My, my. You can't get
more cocky than that.
You know what, sir. I think
I just had a bright idea.
There've been some
unexpected developments.
So I think its time
to let you in on everything.
Sorry about these
elaborate precautions.
We're in a heightened
state of emergency
right now and we've had
to double our security
to protect a certain prisoner
being held beneath that tower.
However, I'll get into all
of that later. It'll be easier
to explain after I show
you a few things, first.
This is our isolation ward.
Our entire compound was
initially built as a means
to facilitate this one ward.
It's also home to the reason
Yahiro sold you out to us.
Things aren't quite as black
and white as they may seem.
He's not a Norma Gene
addict like you thought.
He's a dealer.
Sugar is the name he gives to
his clients. He was inside
the Roppongi blockade that day
to sell drugs, not to buy them.
It's dirty money, sure,
but his motives are pure.
Look down there.
You'll understand.
What happened to these
people, are they--?
Yahiro! Who's the kid
he's sitting with?
That's his younger
brother, Jun.
And the reason
Yahiro ratted on you.
Pretty shocking, huh?
That's what happens
when the Apocalypse
Virus reaches Stage 4.
One of the most important
roles of this facility
is our effort
to provide cutting edge
medical attention to these
people who were accidentally
infected or developed
immunity to the vaccine.
I doubt you've forgotten
but only ten years
have passed since the
pandemic struck.
That little time since
the massive riot known
as Lost Christmas broke out
and this country unraveled.
GHQ was the only organization to
successfully develop a vaccine.
And thanks to it,
we managed to get
the outbreak under control.
Without that vaccine,
I doubt the world
would have recovered
any real sense of order.
So I can't forgive Funeral
Parlor. Not when they carelessly
disrupt the peace and stability
we've desperately worked
to create. And I can't
wrap my head around you.
You seem like a smart kid
who cares about people.
So why would you want to
dismantle all of our goodwill?
Goodwill? Really?
The stuff I saw wasn't goodwill.
I'm not sure what
you're talking about.
What am I--, I saw
innocent people killed
right in front
of me! By your men!
That was a hideout
for unregistered citizens.
People that refuse
their regular inoculations and
it's basically
a hotbed of infection.
Well that still doesn't
make it right to kill them!
You must know our soldiers
were killed, too?
Far away from their families.
Think they wanted to die
protecting people who
won't protect themselves?
Gai said we had to save
the civilians. He said,
that what we did was
for the greater good.
Is that what he said?
Then explain this to me.
Why is he trying to
free a mass murderer?
Kenji Kido.
The man responsible
for the Sky Tree bombing.
Funeral Parlor has declared
their intent to take him from
us by force. Him, not you.
Listen, Shu. This is some
advice you should take to heart.
When someone tells
you to be selfless,
you can bet it serves them.
I want you to take this
transmitter. The next time
you're with Gai Tsutsugami,
press the blue button
two times and then the red
button once. It'll alert us
to their location and we'll
move in before they can
cause more harm. That's all
I need you to do for us, Shu.
We know about Inori Yuzuriha.
Most people know her as a famous
musician from the internet.
It's a shame that she's become
so ensnared in Gai's web
of deception. If you
refuse to help us,
that'll leave me with no
choice but to bring her in
for questioning.
Blooming wildflower,
I beg you please tell me
Why do people fight
and hurt each other?
Why do I feel cold?
What's wrong with me,
Funell? I don't understand.
I wish Shu was here.
Maybe he could tell me.
Come on. Your lawyer's
here to see you.
You must be Shu.
I'm pleased to meet you.
Your mother hired me to act
as your legal defense. I'm
going to do everything I can
to get you out of here.
Oh, you can call me
Mason by the way.
Ga--!
Let's get right down
to business.
Right! Initiating mainframe
hacking sequence.
They don't give much
time for consultation.
So we have to work fast.
I only need three minutes.
Do you feel ready to talk to me
about what happened?
I've diverted their video feed.
You're safe to start.
Good. Everyone stand by.
I know this has been
a harrowing experience
but it's almost over now.
You just do your best
to hang in there and I'll
have you out of here
in no time at all.
Talk about pathetic.
All right, I know,
you think I'm stupid!
Just tell me why the hell
you've come here!
There's a certain someone
being confined here
that we need free. So we're
going to break him out.
You mean Kenji Kido?
The murderer?
That's the one. Ogumo and
the others are set to attack.
Kido's in solitary.
Once we're done in here,
I need you to find him and
immediately draw out his void.
Thirty seconds afterward we'll--
Quit assuming I'll do
anything you want me to!
I am not one of your followers!
What exactly did
they tell you? Who was it?
I'm guessing it was Galty?
Look, Gai. Why are you
so determined to fight them?
What's the point of it?
You really need
to ask that question?
Answer me, damn it! Come on!
Quit keeping me in the dark!
Attention all personnel.
The system has been temporarily
corrupted by an outside
source. We are currently
rebooting from a backup
array. Please stand by.
Initiate the operation.
It's all yours!
It's go time.
Raise the shields!
Move out the Endlaves!
All right, Aya!
Enemy units have launched!
Roger that. I'm ready
whenever you are, Shibungi.
You've got an angle
and the flight path is clear.
Can you make it, Ayase?
Only one way to find out.
We don't have time for this.
Decide. You can either
move now, or you can lie down
and go back to playing dead.
Shu!
Inori?
Just hang on!
I'm coming to get you out!
You mean you're here?
I gave you an order to hold your
position. What are you doing?
Gai, I can see her now!
She's infiltrated the facility
and she's downloaded
the location of Shu's cell.
It's pretty clear she's
trying to rescue him.
She what?
But I'm not in my cell!
I can't reach her;
she's shut off her feed.
And the tower's defenses
are at full blast!
The meeting is over!
Get back to your cell!
What the-- Hey!
Reckless idiot.
Hands up! One move and--
Hey, Tsugumi.
Patch me to Shibungi.
You got it.
I was starting to worry, Gai.
We're all in position here
to send Ayase
in for your escape.
Things haven't exactly
gone as planned.
I'm switching up our strategy.
I'm bringing Kido in on my own!
That's too risky, Gai.
Go ahead and launch
as planned, Ayase.
Get in here and help
Inori and Shu!
Roger! Shibungi,
I'm heading in!
Shu, Inori,
just try to sit tight!
Hurry it up!
Gai, it looks like
they're moving Kido.
Perfect timing.
Send me his coordinates!
On the way!
I've secured the escapee.
Request immediate back--
What the hell
did you do to Inori?
What are you talking about?
You must've done something
she would never disobey Gai!
You've messed up
the whole operation!
If something happens to Gai,
you are on my shit list!
Major, we have a message from
the head of Facility Four.
He says that they can
protect the facility
and he's asked you
not to interfere.
Fine by me. I'm going
to get some fresh air.
Yes, sir. They specifically
asked you not to step in,
though, sir.
Yes, I heard you the
first time you said it.
I'm only going to watch.
Nothing wrong with that.
I promised that I'd protect
you no matter what happens.
So you just sleep tight, Jun.
Go run and hide for a second.
Kenji Kido.
It's a gun.
Behind you!
What is this thing?
I get it. It makes
things weightless.
You see, don't you?
Kenji Kido's Void has
the ability to
manipulate gravity.
It's like there's
an endless supply of them!
Damn, there's too many!
You're outnumbered! Surrender!
Shu!
Inori!
Hey! Stop!
Give me enough!
Hang on!
Shu.
Inori.
Inori, you--you're here.
You came for me!
This is far more
important than your life.
It's beautiful!
Kido's fine, he's over there.
I noticed, Ayase.
Collect him, please.
Oh, yes sir!
What're you going to
do now? Come with us?
Or try to make it on your own?
I can decide for you
if you can't.
You can leave everything
to me. Just know, if you do,
I call the shots.
All right. I'm with you
from now on.
Let's go.