Shu, honey! Be all manly,
would you? Wait a sec!
What are you
packing that bag for?
How many times
do I have to say it?
The AV Club is going on a trip.
Huh? That does ring
a bell. A little one.
You're sure you told me?
No, you're psychic.
I'm not going to be
back home for a while, okay?
What? You're running off
to leave me all by myself?
Stop being all co-dependent!
You don't want me to die
of loneliness, do you?
Guess I'd better pack
a bag and come along, huh!
Are you trying
to break my neck?
Did you hear, Inori? Shu's
abandoning me! His own mother!
Huh?
Enough with the
clingy-mom sleeper-hold!
You're going to Oshima.
See? I remember.
Yeah.
Well then.
Have fun. And go
say hi to your dad.
Welcome to paradise!
It's so beautiful out today!
Nothing but sunshine!
Hey, you sure you're
not pulling our leg
with this whole
"vacation home" thing?
Nah, it's real. I actually lived
out here back when I was a kid.
Yeah? Well thanks, man!
Souta Tamadate?
You mean the guy in my class?
That's the one.
Bring him to Oshima.
We're going to infiltrate
a GHQ facility there.
We'll need Tamadate's Void
on hand to get through
their security setup.
Of course it's got to be him.
All you have to do is ask him on
a trip. How hard could that be?
Yeah, I'll do it.
That's the spirit. Hey, your
friend will be perfectly safe.
My friend, huh?
Shows what you know, Gai.
This place is the bomb.
It's a full-on mansion!
Yeah, no kidding! What do
your folks do for a living,
anyway Shu?
Hey, why's my
vacation home so big?
The Kuhouin Group told Gai
that we could borrow this one.
There a problem?
Stop getting all
lovey-dovey, you guys.
Save it for home, would you?
Who says we're
getting lovey-dovey?
Don't play dumb, man!
You know you're shacking up!
Are you saying
they live together?
Yeah, I saw them
going home together.
Secret is out, dude!
You're busted! So how'd your
torrid romance begin?
The public wants to know!
Give it a rest! Look, there's
nothing going on between us!
Her older brother's
kind of a jerk,
and she needs
a place to crash. So-
Yeah, right. You are
totally full of crap!
The lovebirds need some
privacy, guys! Which means
there's more beach
for me! Come on!
Hey! Shouldn't we
at least unpack?
We didn't come out here
to unpack! You nerds can just
stand around if you want to,
but this bad boy is in
vacation mode!
You get back here, Souta!
Last one in's a rotten egg!
Hurry it up, slowpokes!
Why's he got to be
so ridiculous all the time?
Souta's just being himself.
What's his deal?
Man, Souta drives me nuts.
He's pushy, and loud,
and he's always getting
in people's faces.
If it weren't for this mission
I wouldn't go anywhere with him.
Of course, it isn't all bad.
This is what I get
for not making my move.
You can do it, Hare!
Heya, Shu!
I think it's high time
we got in the water already!
Actually, I was just going to.
Hurry up!
Oh, oh man!
Hare, you got to let go!
Running is hard right now!
Against all odds,
Tamadate seems to have
made it here in one piece.
Shu's having way too much
fun to be on a mission.
My assignments never
involve bikinis.
A little R&amp;R never hurt
anyone. The real issue
is how we're going to get
around security tonight.
Tsugumi and Ayase are
looking into it as we speak.
And we just cool our jets
in the meantime, huh?
I wonder what kind of
"buried treasure"
we're out here
to dig up, anyway.
"Theirs not to reason why,
theirs but to trust in Gai."
Tell me, Argo.
Yeah?
Aren't you hot in that attire?
Hot and bothered.
Does that count?
No!
Hey, uh, where's Shu?
He headed out before us,
said there was somewhere
he needed to go.
Oh, I forgot. Shu's dad
is buried here on Oshima.
Wheelchair girl!
Is this yours?
Thank you, good sir.
Ta ta, then.
That chick must be way loaded!
She had a maid and everything!
Tsugumi, tell me again
why we're dressed like this?
Your outfit is adorable!
Surely my mistress doesn't
object to that!
Kurosu Ouma was
a brilliant man.
You've heard of him?
Sure, he worked as a professor
at Tennozu College.
And he was the world's
leading expert
on the Apocalypse
Virus when he died.
Wait, are you kidding me?
You don't know
your own father's work?
We don't really talk about
the past too much, I guess.
I knew he was Haruka's
teacher, but that's about it.
Haruka?
Oh. I call my mom by her
first name. To be honest,
I hardly remember my dad at all.
I mean he died ten years ago.
During the Lost Christmas?
A lot of lives were
forever changed that day.
Tell me, Gai, what're you
doing up here anyway?
Not visiting anyone.
You here for the view?
Indeed.
Straight ahead.
A shrine gate?
At first glance.
Trip lasers.
A GHQ lab is hidden inside. I'm
here to take what lies within.
What would that be exactly?
The rock that started this.
Taking possession of it is our
number one priority right now,
period. You and the Void you can
draw are key to our success.
We can't do this without you.
Or without him.
Because Souta's our
equipment. Yeah, I get it.
The mission begins at 2200
hours. All you have to do
is get him to the rendezvous
point by then and we're good.
You make it sound so easy.
What's so difficult about it?
Just bait your hook properly.
Excuse me?
Souta's an ardent fan
of Egoist, isn't he?
So, Inori's the bait? Is
that what you're suggesting?
But of course. You lure
a person in with whatever
it is they desire.
It's not rocket science.
You can't make her
a bargaining chip!
It's like trying to reason
with a brick wall.
If this is beyond
your capabilities, Shu,
don't bother showing up.
Hey, wait!
I didn't say that!
I haven't gone on a trip
with friends in forever!
Thanks for coming along, Kanon.
I'm really glad you did!
Of course I came. I mean I am
a member of the club, you know.
Just not officially,
that's all.
Yeah but since Yahiro's
not here, I thought.
So what if he's here?
Like I care about that!
Anyway, I'm happy
that you tagged along.
I don't even know what I'd do if
Inori were the only other girl.
Whoa! Inori, look at you!
Your skin is gorgeous!
Can I touch it?
Huh? Um.
It's so soft! What do you use
on it? Is it that soft all over?
Please, don't, I-
If she has any feelings for Shu,
I don't stand a freaking chance.
So, Shu. Spill it.
Huh? About what?
Is there really, like, nothing
going on between you and Inori?
It's like I
told you before, man.
Inori and I are just friends.
Then I'm going for it.
I'm going to make a move.
I like her, so screw it.
I'll give it a shot.
You know what you should do?
A mission in which
one uses one's friends.
Not very well suited
to our Shu, would you say?
Friends are an asset,
like anything else.
It's a waste not to use them.
How very "Gai".
Besides, a life without
turmoil is a life unlived.
He's doing his friend a favor
by stirring up some emotion,
just this once.
So your name is, Gai.
Excuse me, sir.
What you want?
Are you sure about this?
It doesn't matter;
I'm not even convinced
I'm the little
bastard's real father.
His mother was a woman
of less-than-sterling virtue,
I fear. Nothing
like you, my dear.
Hey, thanks for coming out.
The stars are
real pretty out here, huh?
You hardly see them in Tokyo.
I mean, the part of Tokyo
that isn't this.
Just calm down. You can
leave them alone together.
Nothing's going to happen.
Look, there's something
I want to show you.
I was watching the new
Egoist video the other day.
And it really got under my skin,
like in the good way, you know?
So I borrowed your song
and made one of my own.
What's he doing?
Blooming wildflower
I beg you, please tell me--
That's something I would do.
Does he think she'll just fall
for any guy with
editing software?
It's pretty.
Uh listen, Inori?
I know that, that we only
met a little while ago,
and we don't talk much.
But whenever I hear you singing,
it feels like my heart's
going to miss a beat!
You don't know me!
But I think you should!
Because I, Well, I think
you should know! I'm! Inori!
I'm in lo-!
Hold it right there!
Shu?
What the hell
are you doing, man?
Inori's my everything, you jerk!
Shu?
Geez, way to drop the ball!
You weren't supposed
to pull his Void yet, Romeo!
How long have you been watching?
You have no self-control,
you know that?
Ayase?
"Inori's my everything,
you jerk!"
Hey! Forget that!
Well, this is
an unexpected turn.
What do you recommend, Gai?
We stick to the plan,
is that understood?
We can still pull
this off. And we will.
Got it!
"Inori's my everything,"
huh? Pathetic.
Good, you're finally here.
Tsugumi's blinded the
guards, but they're of
little importance. The real
challenge lies within. Ogumo!
Yes, sir.
Bad form, interrupting
a guy's confession like that.
Shu! I want you
to shoot the gate with
that camera you pulled.
I didn't realize this was
a Void for opening things.
Let's go!
Hey!
Didn't realize it
was you, Keido, sir!
Don't you worry about it.
I'm just a ghost,
as are you now.
It sounds like they're onto us!
No! They can't know
we're here! Which means-
Hurry!
Shu!
Come on!
Why would Souta have a camera
for a Void? I don't get it.
I don't know, and frankly,
I couldn't care less.
I just know that we need him.
Souta's Void's the only
thing that can cut through
this security mechanism.
We just point and shoot.
So this whole room
is one big lock?
Our objective lies
just beyond us, Shu. Do it!
You first.
It's empty!
Gai? What are you?
We're leaving!
Keido, I should have
known you'd pull this.
Dante said, "The double
grief of a lost bliss,
is to recall those
happier hours while in pain."
Kurosu, I will not be deterred.
You okay?
Shu? Wait! Where's Inori?
She's back at the house.
So, what happened?
Look, Souta. I'm sorry, but I
can't help with Inori anymore.
Oh, I get it. You're
going after her now too, huh?
If that's how you feel, why
didn't you say something.
I even asked if there was
anything was between you!
I don't understand you
at all! What the hell?
Like you're one to talk!
You're so damn pushy and loud
and clueless all the
time, Souta! Seriously,
you bug the crap outta me!
Sorry! But that's
really how I feel, okay?
He must hate me now.
I can't blame him.
But I'm glad
I told him, at least.
It was the right thing to do.
I thought that
might be the case.
What?
Hey, thanks for giving it to me
straight. 'Cause sometimes,
you can be kind of distant.
You know what I'm saying, dude?
Anyway.
Hell, if we're being honest
here, sometimes you bug
the crap outta me.
It's cool, that you told me.
It means a lot, for real.
Guess that we're friends
at least a little bit,
or why bother?
It's a little late to be asking.
But what exactly
are Voids, anyway?
I don't really understand
what they're all about yet,
but I think at some point,
I'm going to have to.
I should know. I mean,
I'm reaching in and
touching their hearts.
Gai told me they change.
Just like a person's heart
can change,
their Void changes, too.
He said that?
Guess that's good to know.
So, if I form
a bond with someone.
Does that mean,
my power will change, too?