This is where you lose her,
forever. Say goodbye, Shu.
This is why I can't
trust you, on your own.
Gai?
A Void? The entire district?
Correct! The tower standing
over Roppongi Fort
is a phantasm given form
from a single girl's heart.
I'm guessing
that girl is Mana Ouma?
I promised you information
on Voids as payment
for your services.
Consider yourself paid.
I appreciate the
work you've done
but I'm afraid you can't
go any further than this.
It's all business with him.
Impossible, you can't be!
So it's finally
coming back to you.
You're just as dense
as you were back then. Shu.
I remember!
The grave keeper of Daath.
So you finally show yourself.
Grave keeper?
I couldn't help but admire
Shuichiro's dogged effort.
So it only made sense
that he and I work together.
Shu, follow him. They're
planning to sacrifice Inori,
in order to awaken Mana.
Mana? Get down here!
Bring her back!
Shu!
What's going on up there?
Inori!
You know, Shu, you can't really
understand where you're going
until you know where it is
you've been. It's time you
open up those memories,
and quit hiding from them.
Shu. We're here now.
You can open your eyes, go on.
Wow, this is so cool!
Really, Mana!
You like it? This is my
secret place to get away
but I'll share it with you
since you're my brother.
Hey, look. What is that?
Is he dead?
Are you okay? Can you hear me?
My name is Shu, Shu Ouma.
And I'm his sister,
Mana. What's your name?
Maybe he can't remember.
Do you know who you are?
What's your name?
I'm not sure.
Triton.
You must've come from the ocean.
So we'll call you Triton.
It's a pretty cool name, right?
That's right. That day on the
beach, my big sister Mana
and I found a boy,
washed up on the shore.
A boy we came to know
by the name of Triton. Gai.
Unsure of his own
identity, he spent a summer
living with us. The year
of Lost Christmas.
The last time any of us felt
like we had a reason to smile.
Hey! Are you serious
about jumping?
Yeah, it'll be fine.
Just believe in me!
Okay, it's your turn! Come on!
See, I knew you could do it.
Yeah.
After all that time
we spent together.
It was only natural that
we became best friends.
Almost brothers.
My life felt complete.
I had my gentle and
loving big sister, Mana.
And my best friend, Gai.
That summer together
was easily the happiest time
of my entire life. So why then?
Why did I forget about something
that meant so much to me?
About Gai? And my sister.
So you've woken up?
Where are we?
Inori!
What the hell are you doing
to her? Give her back to me,
you bastard!
You should understand that
this girl has never been
anything more than a temporary
body that we created
to use as an interface for
communication with Mana.
Why would we give back something
that was ours to begin with?
Created?
Your sister was the
first person to touch
the creation rock and
therefore the first one
to succumb to the Apocalypse
Virus. She is our Eve.
Although her soul had
lost its body, it's now
being siphoned into a new form.
Thanks to our diligence,
she'll soon set foot
in this world again.
Her resurrection
will bring with it
the finality Lost Christmas
lacked. The Apocalypse Virus
will coat the face
of the earth like a scab.
It is my purpose in life
to witness that event!
For some reason,
Daath is convinced
you have some potential.
Although you strike me
as nothing more than a
clueless child. Now stay put!
Keep your mouth shut,
and observe!
Inori!
This is not
the time to interfere.
It's rather rude.
He's about to ask
for Mana's hand
in marriage, after all.
What are you talking about?
Her chosen partner
is a lucky man.
He will be the father
of the new human race.
Not that she has much say
in the matter. Even Eve,
with all her selfish ways,
can be controlled by the stone.
I do hope we can count on
her brother's blessing
for this union?
I don't understand.
Marry?
That's right. You won't feel too
lonely if I marry someone else.
Will you, Shu?
Marry who?
I don't know yet.
Maybe it'll be Triton.
Triton? You can't marry him!
Oh, don't be silly. I'm only
joking. I wouldn't do that.
Although I have caught him
looking at me a few times,
you know. Leering at me,
the way a man would.
You don't want him to do that?
I don't want him to, but you
can look at me that way.
Why can I?
Because, Shu, I love you.
You've got the virus.
Those spots are from the virus
in that rock, aren't they?
It makes people crazy.
I overheard your dad
talking about it.
Tell me, Mana. What do you
want to do with Shu?
If it wasn't for me, you'd
be lying dead on that beach.
I saved your life,
which means you're mine.
And I can do anything
I want with you. Can't I?
Um, Mana?
Listen, Triton,
I'm going to marry, Shu.
And no one's going to get in
my way. That understood?
Hey, Shu? Promise me something.
Promise, that you'll marry me.
With this perfect pairing,
we sanctify the chosen union.
By performing the bond of blood.
That will shape the new race.
Stop it!
Now, now, Shu.
You really have
no right to get jealous.
After all, you were
the one to shun me.
I was completely devastated.
But you knew that, didn't you?
What do you mean?
Was I that unimportant
to you? That you'd forget?
Let me share my pain with you.
Are you okay, Shu?
Ayase!
And this is why I can't
trust you on your own!
Gai! You're still alive!
He missed my vital organs. The
cancer crystals shielded them.
Gai Tsutsugami.
This is the moment I've been
waiting for! All this time,
I've finally got you and
Mana in the same place!
The hidden camera feed
is a bit staticky.
It was just as bad the first
time I got footage of
a Void in action. It's clear
enough to see, though.
It's Sephira's prototype
filter. I'd like to know
just why you let us through?
It hurt my feelings that
I didn't get invited
to the party. I figured
I'd let you crash it for me.
You're too late, Tsutsugami!
This is the course of destiny.
Shu, get moving!
Shu!
Tsugumi! Emergency bailout!
No! I can still fight!
We form with these vows,
an unbreakable chain.
Shu, dig deep. You have
to remember! Some part of you
must know what
happened that day!
What day?
Lost Christmas.
December Two Thousand
Twenty-nine. We had left
your summer home and come
to Tokyo. Your new mother,
Haruka, had brought us here.
And on December 24th,
I asked you to meet me
at a church in Roppongi.
I wanted to tell you about
the Mana you didn't know.
But,
to my surprise. You weren't
the one who showed up.
Merry Christmas, Triton.
Oh, uh, thanks.
Open it.
You're my little knight,
aren't you, Triton?
This way you can
always protect me.
Let's see you shoot the
star on top of the tree.
Poor Triton. You do know
that I loved you, right?
Just kidding.
Triton? Triton!
What happened? Triton!
Forget him. Come here
and take this, Shu.
If you and
I intertwine our DNA,
we can create a beautiful
new world together.
It's okay, Shu. There's
nothing to be scared of.
Don't you want to do something
fun? Just you and me?
Get away! Stay back!
You monster!
Mana?
No!
I'm sorry, forgive me,
please, Shu.
Please don't be frightened.
I need your help!
It's all so fast.
I'm becoming somebody else!
Her fear boiled over.
And she destroyed herself
with her own
out-of-control power.
That's right. I remember.
She asked for our help that day.
She asked, but there was nothing
we could do to help her.
We were useless.
Then you said something.
I'm going to get stronger.
Goodbye, Shu.
I'd forgotten. I was
hiding from the past.
Trying to protect myself.
You're whole again.
So now you know, Shu.
You know exactly
what we have to do.
We have to take
Mana's soul back from them.
You got it. They've forced her
to awaken against her will.
And you and I are going
to put her back to sleep.
Use the Void's power, Shu.
Send her back to oblivion!
You've unlocked the shackles
of memory and now you think
you're ready to take your place
as king. Is that it, Shu?
We're running out of time.
Draw out my heart, Shu.
Take my Void! And then
I want you to hand it to me.
With the power you're feeling,
I know you can do it!
Don't let go of
my hand until it's done.
So this is Gai's Void.
All right, Shu.
I need you to cover me
while I make
a beeline for Mana.
I've got your back.
Let's go!
Inori!
Shu. Are you trying
to make me jealous?
Gai!
It's a Void that forces other
people's Voids to manifest!
Of course, I should expect
nothing less from him.
Do it! Get going!
Right!
Stop!
Shuichiro, you've done
enough. You did your best,
and you failed.
Gai!
Put the blade through me
and stab Mana, Shu!
I'm a dead man anyway
you look at it. So do it!
No!
Shu. Who do I remind you
of right now?
You were always so
decisive when we were kids.
You were brave and strong.
More than anything,
I wanted to be like you.
What? What are you
talking about, Gai?
You haven't lost the
ability to be that person.
If I can change myself,
then so can you.
You don't need me
to do this anymore.
Come on. Hurry up and do it!
Gai.
Shu.
It's you. Triton.
Mana. I've finally
repaid the favor.
Oh god! Gai!
It's okay. This is
how Gai wanted it.
I heard him, Shu.
He said thank you.