Medic! Unit 322 performed
an emergency bailout!
The 2nd Lieutenant was
injured in the process!
What the. What the
hell just happened?
You're not
getting away with that!
Get away!
Well now we know
what a Void can do.
Ogumo. Go.
Roger that, Commander. Over.
Inori.
Inori! Wake up!
What was that?
Shu Ouma.
You've got fifteen seconds.
Grab Inori and get out of there.
Wait. What?
Tsugumi. Where's
the next target?
Direction, 10 o'clock,
distance of four hundred.
That far off?
There's nothing closer?
Why don't you just call it a
day? Don't overexert yourself,
Aya. Your poor craft
can barely take anymore.
It's not my job to give up.
Well look at this
stocky little bastard.
Talk about perfect timing.
He's fast!
Bailing you out!
Where are the accompanying
screams? Aw, man.
What a buzz kill.
Impossible! There's no way! How
could a foot soldier do this?!
I don't know. The battle
footage is too distorted
to say for certain,
but that's way it looks, sir.
A handheld anti-Endlave weapon?
Dammit! I can't report that!
Second Lieutenant Daryl Yan.
Kill it. Lieutenant Yan,
this is quite a nice surprise!
A visit from the Major
General's only son.
It's an honor to finally
have a chance to meet you.
And clearly you live up to
your reputation for bravery.
Did your father's orders
bring you to our post here?
No. It was my decision. I was
on my way to deliver a new
model Endlave to the operations
center. I got the report
a battle had broken out and
I don't know. Sounded fun!
Is that so? Well!
We couldn't be more grateful
to have your assistance.
Lieutenant.
Who do you think I am?
You expect me to touch
that greasy pig hoof?
Listen. I'll do as I please,
you got it? And if you get
in my way. I'll have to report
your fat ass to my father.
That little shit! Expand the
search perimeter! Apprehend
and question anyone you see!
Women, children, everyone!
God.
Reporting in as ordered, Gai.
Ayase. What's your status.
I lost my vessel.
And I apologize.
It was completely my fault.
I see. And I am disappointed.
Your mission. Was to stand your
ground for eighteen minutes
in a rundown older
model Endlave.
And you rose to that task.
But here you are claiming
that your mission was an utter
failure. It sounds to me
like you think that I've
failed you as your commander.
No, no! I failed you!
I'm the failure here! Not you!
I'm joking.
I'm glad you made it
back alright. You did well.
I can hear your heart fluttering
clear across the room, Aya.
Shut up, Tsugumi!
So, uh. Should I?
You're finally awake.
Inori.
Gai. Did I accomplish
the mission?
No. And I'm very
disappointed with you. Inori.
Hey!
Don't you think
you're being a little harsh?
I know it's none
of my business, but.
She tried as hard as she could
for you. And she even got hurt.
I realize that.
But results are everything.
And in the results department
she screwed up in a big way.
Screwed up? What do you mean?
She made the decision to share
the Void Genome with you.
You mean the cylinder?
That's right. It was supposed
to be for me to use.
The cylinder she gave you
was one of only three
enhanced genomes to be
successfully cultivated
by Sephira Genomics.
It allows the user to harness
what's known as
the king's power.
And what is that?
A way to analyze intron
sequences in the human genome.
And extract the
power within them
by converting it into Voids.
What's a Void?
An idea given corporeal form.
That's what the sword
you used was. That was Inori's
Void. Every person contains
their own unique version.
Void technology has
one foot firmly planted
in the realm of the Gods.
And you've just obtained
its crowning achievement.
Which means you're no
longer allowed to sit idly
on the sidelines and turn
a blind eye to the desperate
lives of those in need. From
now on you fight with us.
I what? Wait!
Remember this, Shu Ouma.
There are only two paths left
in this life to choose from.
You can be selected
out of this world. Or you
can adapt and make a change.
What is it?
Things have taken
a turn for the worse.
The damn whitecoats
have quarantined
the underground lot
in Area 14.
The underground lot?
Yeah. Word got out
that it was a safe spot.
There were nearly one hundred
people hiding in there
when they raided. And that new
model that took down Ayase?
Belongs to Kill-Em-All Daryl.
Things could get
tricky, then. Daryl.
So the Kaleidoscope's in play.
It's bad. The situation
is untenable. There's too much
of a disparity between
our forces. A rescue mission
is simply too dangerous.
I recommend we pull out.
No. We aren't backing down.
No way. This is an opportunity.
This is providence.
Attention all members.
As of now we move to
wipe out the Anti Bodies.
And rescue the
residents of the fort!
Furthermore. We're going
public. This will not be
a covert operation. As of this
moment the Funeral Parlor
is making itself known
the world over.
So go! And give it
everything you've got!
Right on!
About time!
So much for caution. I guess
I'll get a script prepared.
Although, are you sure
this isn't too soon?
Depends on his answer.
Tell me who your leader is!
Go on. Spill your guts
or I will. Tell me!
The Special Virus Disaster
Response Bureau,
commonly known as the Anti
Bodies. They've been granted
the unilateral authority to
diagnose people as symptomatic
and then exterminate them for
the safety of the population.
Please don't do this! My husband
hasn't done anything wrong!
I need to go, Mama.
Wait just a little longer,
Ryo. Please, I promise,
my husband isn't sick!
Let him go!
What a tragic spectacle.
My heart hangs heavy.
Officer! Please!
Spare my husband's life!
Get off of me,
you filthy hag!
Are you trying to infect me?!
You festering gutter rat!
The lynchpin of GHQ's
public security.
Their cruelest, sharpest fang.
And now you know.
That's the true face
of the enemy we're fighting.
No questions.
Just get it done.
Execute every one of them.
Mama! Mama! Mama!
Your offspring is annoying me.
Thinks you'll protect him
just 'cuz you
gave birth to him.
This can't be real.
Alpha team,
are you in position?!
Not yet.
Well hurry!
We're trying!
Gai!
Launch the operation!
Incoming missiles!
Well intercept them!
So they're making a move.
I want them dead or alive!
Time for some fun!
It's started.
Listen, Shu. Alpha Team
will strike first with
a long-range attack and
then we'll lure the Endlaves
as far from the enemy
camp as we can.
Once they've reached
the determined checkpoint.
Charlie Team
will make its move.
Checkpoints Red, Blue,
and Yellow, now secure.
Distance to final point Seven.
Alright, you better
take care of my babies, Aya!
You've got it.
You're about to get
stomped on, little buggy!
The target has reached D-line!
And now. You die.
Now!
Abort! Abort the attack!
What?!
Multiple missiles locked on
your bay and there's too many
for us to shield!
A friendly word
of advice to Major Guin.
Commander of GHQ's
Anti Bodies squadron three.
He's on an open channel!
We are The Funeral Parlor.
Release your hostages
and surrender. If you comply,
we'll allow you to live.
What do we do?
How do we respond?
We're holding the
trump card in this game.
Attention, terrorists!
We will never agree
to the demands of terrorism.
If you don't immediately
withdraw your forces.
We'll set off the gas
we planted underground.
Show yourselves
and we'll refrain from doing so.
We want to meet your leader.
Bring us the head caretaker
of your little parlor.
I'm the one in charge.
That's kind of a sinister name
you've chosen for yourselves.
The world offers up
the choice to live or die.
Survival of the fittest.
That's the only governing law
this world recognizes.
As a result. We'll
always offer funeral songs
for those selected out.
Hence the moniker.
It signifies that we'll
always be the ones singing.
And that we'll always
be the ones to survive.
You don't quite understand
the position you're in.
We've got the power to decide
the selection process here.
Now you've taken
something of ours.
A dangerous genetic weapon.
We'd like it back.
Sorry. This is the first
I'm hearing about it.
You've got until
the count of ten. Give it up
or we'll wipe any trace
of you from existence.
Right on schedule.
It's crazy. Everything's
happening just like
he said that it would.
All of these people
will die if I mess up.
Believe, Shu.
You can do it. You can.
I know you can.
Because I belong to you now.
Ten! Nine! Eight!
Seven! Six!
Five! Four!
Three! Two!
Initiate... Kaleidoscope!
One!
Time's up!
What?!
You've done well.
You moved past your fear
to do the right thing
and help those in need.
No small feat
and you should be proud.
Join us, Shu. We can use
your ability. You know that
you could make a difference
if you come with us.
I wonder. How much my
life would've changed if
I'd chosen to take his hand.
But I know I made
the right decision.
I don't have it in me
to live some crazy
life of adventure.
As of today. I'm just
an average kid again.
Oh, and one last thing before
we get started. Our class has
a new transfer student
joining us. Come on in!
Whoa. Check it out!
Hey, she's hot!
Everyone. This is Inori.
No way. This can't be real.
Of course it is.