I'm glad to see
you're finally awake.
Your queen will be happy.
Her chosen king has returned.
Welcome back, Gai.
King?
Mana's on her way,
soon to be reborn in Cocytus.
Just as the law
of nature demands.
She is the mold
of the new human race.
The embodiment of
its will to evolve.
And she has deigned you
to be her king.
Neither of us can stop it.
There's not a person
alive that can stop it.
Not even Mana herself.
What you're saying is,
I'm not allowed to end this.
Master Gai.
The United Nations forces have
begun their advance on Ward 24.
Alright.
Stand by until I get there.
Yes, sir.
Are you sad, Gai?
What makes you think that?
I don't think it, I feel it.
Just now.
It's like your heart
reached out for mine.
My wish is about to come true.
So you see, I couldn't be
any happier than I am now.
You're wrong.
We've moved in this close and
they haven't fired on us yet?
Strange.
Their threat to use
the 256 Leucocytes
was nothing but a bluff.
They've only got the one
we failed to destroy
the first time.
The rest that show up are
nothing but digital phantoms
and decoys that have been put
in place by their hackers.
So they were buying time.
And everyone who could've
stopped them fell for it
like a bunch of fools.
The whole world, including us,
just sat on our hands,
until it was too late.
But we've still
made it in time.
True, it may not be very much
time, but we've still got
the chance to fix this.
The chance to stop Gai,
and to save Inori.
Precisely.
If we can retrieve Inori,
Gai's plan goes up in smoke.
And more importantly, we might
even be able to wipe out
the Apocalypse Virus
all over the world.
Things look bleak, but we have
the opportunity to illuminate
the way for a new future.
And so we will. I never
thought I'd say this,
but the fate of humanity
may very well be resting
in our hands. Well, guys.
You know what's at stake here;
let's win this. Agreed?
I'm gonna borrow this.
Okay, Ogumo?
You think this protocol will
work. Take a look for me?
I think so. As long as
they don't discover us.
Would you mind helping me
into the chair?
So, Shu.
Yeah?
Could you shoot? If he was
standing right in front of you,
could you pull the
trigger on Gai?
Yes, I could.
You're a good person, you know.
Where the hell
did that come from?
I'm the one whose job it is
to get dirty. Not you, okay?
You stay just the way you are.
Shu.
Although. If I wind up in
a jam during the battle,
I will have to use your Void.
I'm sorry, but I can't
get this done without
making you my accomplice.
That's fine with me.
I knew what I was getting into
when I loaned you my heart.
Just remember. I didn't give
it to you for keeps, okay?
I do want it back. So you better
not go off and die with it.
I'll do my best. Thank you.
Attack units on course.
Approaching Point Delta
without interference.
Commence with the attack.
Launch all Endlave units!
All units begin descent!
Repeat, begin descent.
Go, go, go!
They brought
every one they could.
Boy, they must really hate
your guts. Huh, Gai?
I'm doing it.
That's cool with me.
87 percent of
their fleet destroyed!
No sign of retaliation!
The outcome is predetermined.
It's our job to efficiently
clear the path
leading to the end.
Activate all Endlave forces.
I want the Ghost Unit on
the front lines.
Lieutenant, we're
counting on you.
Hey. Tell me this. What
are you even doing here?
It's clear the whole
thing leaves a bad taste
in your mouth.
What about you? Why volunteer
to be their guinea pig?
You haven't really done
much to hide the fact
that you want to destroy Gai.
Can you really blame me?
I'm pissed they used
my own Void against me.
Also. This is my life.
I wanna decide how it ends.
Isn't that right, Gespenst?
I wish the U.N. hadn't
fallen so quickly.
We really could've
used that distraction.
We better hurry.
Let's move!
We're registering
a new enemy in block 7!
And it's not the U.N.!
Funeral Parlor!
Send in the Ghosts!
Are they down?
'Fraid not. You just
attacked a Void.
They took out the copies!
Just as I had expected.
And hoped. Tsugumi.
That should've given you
a strong enough reading
to analyze their security
banks. Can you do it?
You forget who
you're talking to?
Tell me one time
I haven't blown your mind.
There it is! The
backdoor Haruka left!
What's happening?!
They've infiltrated our system!
They're not moving.
They've shut down.
Don't throw away this
chance! Get our troops
on the ground and put
them down right now!
Souta!
Their forces have
penetrated Area 4!
The U.N. fleet is
resuming their advance!
Get our system up!
Well this is it. Here's
where we have to part.
But that doesn't mean
I won't be with you.
I'll royally screw them
over on the digital end.
Thanks.
Sounds good. We'll need it.
You just do your part and save
Inori. That's not a request;
I demand a happy ending.
Your time's up. I'm erasing all
of your memories and emotions.
Every part of you that
made you an individual being.
It won't be long now
before you're reborn as Mana.
Go on and resent me, Inori.
If I hadn't woken you, none of
this would ever have happened.
You'd have remained in stasis.
And then, you never would have
known the meaning of loss.
No. You're wrong there. I can't
resent you. I'm grateful.
Because of you,
I got to experience life.
If you hadn't woken me,
I never would've met Shu.
Ayase!
I've got the rest!
And what was so precious that
Shu gave you? I'm curious.
What wonderful things
did he show you?
He showed me the world.
All of its sadness,
it's pain and its beauty.
Shu suffered, doubted
himself. He hurt people.
And made mistakes. And he
felt remorse and shame
for his actions. That's why,
that's the true reason
I love him.
His boundless humanity. Shu
showed me how to be human.
Shu! That's too much!
It's okay. I promise.
Idiot!
He showed me how to live. Even
though I'm not a real human,
he gave me the chance
to fall in love,
just like a normal person.
Tsugumi. We've reached the
checkpoint. What's next?
Tsugumi! You there?
Looks like they've got
their system back up.
They must've recovered
control somehow.
Inori. Where are you?
Is that so? Shu means that
much to you, does he?
Who is Shu?
I guess that's the name of
the only man you ever loved.
Wildflower, boldly blooming
Tell me how--
I hear you.
Inori's singing.
Is there something
wrong with him?
I can't hear anyone singing.
Follow me! I know the way!
It doesn't make much sense, but
still, I believe he hears her.
Right then! It's not like we
have anything else to go on.
Just remain calm,
and please walk, no running!
Valiantly blooming flower
What can you see
from your field?
Why can't people
forgive each other?
Where are we?
This is the hub
of Central Command.
We can take the elevator
straight to the top from here-
Welcome, Shu. Glad you could
make it. And how nice.
Some of your followers
tagged along.
We're comrades!
Not his damned followers!
Is that what you believe?
The illusion of camaraderie
is an effective tactic.
Enough of this.
You and I need to have
a private conversation, Shu.
You might wanna say goodbye.
This is probably the last time
you'll ever see them.
Shu!
Don't worry, I'll be fine!
You focus on protecting
everyone else!
Well you've certainly got
your confidence up these days,
don't you? Those are
some pretty big shoes
you're trying
to fill, oh savior.
Who are you? Or should
I ask what are you?
Simply, I am the
living incarnation of Daath.
In fact, I am the impetus behind
the will of the human race.
To be clear, you could
even say that I am Daath.
You've impressed us. We never
expected that you would
recover the kingly
power stolen from you.
And you made us rethink
examine our intentions.
Maybe Gai's not it. Maybe
you are the rightful heir,
the one meant to be
Adam to Mana's Eve.
And therefore, Shu Ouma,
we have a question for you.
Think carefully
before you answer.
There's only one way for
mankind to progress from here.
Complete obliteration
at the hands of Adam.
And it's all in your hands. Will
you spend eternity with Mana?
And shape the next phase
of humanity?
You can't be serious.
Just a simple yes
or no answer will do.
Hell no.
That's what I figured you'd
say. But Gai? No hesitation.
He said yes before I could
even finish the question.
I suppose that's the
difference between you two.
Oh, well. In the name
of Daath's reign,
I strip you of your right to
the succession of the throne.
Yahiro!
Is that an exit?
It sure is, but good luck.
The chances of you even
reaching it are kind of slim.
Don't tell me it's you?!
You better believe it,
sweetheart. Let's settle this,
Funeral Parlor.
Once and for all!
Selection and evolution,
an inescapable process
for every living thing.
Resisting it is futile
and yet here you are.
You've got some nerve
to refuse Mana twice.
She so badly wanted you.
And look who you've devoted
yourself to. A soulless
test-tube child.
Shut up!
Argo!
You're wrong about Inori.
You know nothing about her.
I'm the only one
who understands her.
She's real. She fought the
ugliness you planted within her.
And she suffered.
Even when I hated myself for
making the same mistakes,
she gave me the love I needed.
No matter what happened,
she was always there.
She always had faith in me!
And this time, I'll be
there to stand by her side.
I won't let you
take her. I won't!
Go ahead and try your best,
then. If you're really
that determined, Shu.
Try to resist your despair.
I'm sorry, but you
just missed her.
Mana must devour Inori to
be reborn. Our fallen Eve
has been resurrected.
The time has finally come.
The Apocalypse is now upon us.
I'm too late.