Cut the crap!
We're sick and tired of you
dancing around the issue!
I'm not avoiding the issue!
All I'm saying is that we
shouldn't take any action
until we have more information.
We should be hearing from
the head of the Kuhouins, my
grandfather, at anytime now.
We just need to be patient.
Come on! You need
a reality check!
As far as the rest of
the world is concerned,
we don't exist anymore!
They're gonna wipe us out
along with the virus,
isn't that obvious?
They're gonna kill us!
We're all as good as dead!
Will you shut up! None of
us knows what's going on!
She's right, please stay calm!
Everyone, try to wait for
your turn to speak until
you have the microphone.
As you've admitted, the biggest
problem we're facing here is
that we don't actually know
what's going on outside.
Someone needs to step up,
and directly inspect
the Loop 7 wall.
Why the hell is little
miss president even giving
those idiots the
chance to speak?
Her integrity's
making her look weak.
She's just being democratic
and hearing everyone out.
What's wrong with that?
Nothing, in peacetime.
Shu. Something wrong?
Oh.
I can't help but wonder how
Gai would handle all this.
Y'know?
Please!
You have to do something!
I just want to see
my mom and my dad!
This is all we're asking
of you. Make a decision about
our course of action.
Telling us to sit around
and wait for your Grandpa?
We want more from
our leader than that.
Isn't that fair?
Pursuant to Article 32, Section
3 of the council charter.
I'm filing a no confidence
resolution. Fellow students.
I request the election
of a new president.
It's vaccination time again,
guys. If it's your turn
to receive a dose this
week. Please report to
the council room.
Again, everyone on
the vaccination list,
report to the council room.
Here.
That's a whole week's worth.
I get the feeling
the dam's finally burst.
Dude, what're you
talking about?
What dam?
This dam. It's the
school's unofficial site.
Take a look.
The internet's back up?!
Whoa, it is?
Well, not entirely.
They suddenly stopped jamming
the school's local network.
But we're still cut off
from the outside.
Hey, let me see.
They're really going for
the president's jugular,
aren't they?
She's working her ass off!
They're just being mean.
You've gotta admit
they have a point though.
Let's be frank here.
She's not really
cut out to be a leader.
Hey!
That's a crappy thing to say!
She's one of us
and we should stand by her!
One of who?
It's circumstance
that forced us together.
You are not as cute
as you think you are, you know!
Jerk.
So sorry I hurt your feelings.
Tsugumi, wait!
What's her problem?
Tally up and collect
a list of every student
that wants to leave.
Ammo for the assembly.
Why worry about that, let's just
get rid of the uppity bitch.
Don't be hasty.
We'll save the trump card
as a last measure.
Hey, Inori.
Can I ask you something?
You don't have
any family, right?
Well, do you um,
ever feel lonely?
I have before.
Shu wasn't there.
And I felt cold.
Gai said that was loneliness.
So yes.
Oh, one time, huh?
What about you?
Tsugumi?
Are you lonely?
What?
Of course I'm not
lonely, come on!
It sucks Funeral Parlor's
gone and all, but still.
I was living on my own way
before I joined them.
So I'm a little past
getting lonesome.
My whole life, I've always been
alone, as far as I can remember.
So you don't need to spy
on me, Shu, there's nothing
to worry about!
Okay!
Good timing, though.
Got somethin' for ya.
A Genomic Resonance Gauge?
Yep. To put it simply,
it's a gadget for measuring
the strength of a person's
Void. I found it on the ground
after those guys
attacked us yesterday.
Huhh.
From what I can tell, the higher
the number on the readout,
the more butt the Void kicks.
Well look at that.
Not bad at all!
What does that mean?
It's not low, is it?
Actually, what is
Tsugumi's Void?
I've never drawn it out.
I don't know.
Think of what
we're facing now.
We should be prepared and
know what everyone's Void is.
You don't need to worry.
It only hurts
for a split second.
Wait, it hurts?!
Alright, Dr. Ouma, the
patient is now ready.
Hey.
Wait.
Okay, then.
Sorry.
Just hold still.
No, hold on.
Stopppppppp!
Report.
Yes, sir. We've deployed
a clean-up crew based on
the strategy you outlined.
The next step is to begin
the purification and to
diminish the blockade zone.
We're ready.
I've created a Ghost Unit
based on the specifications
you gave me and
strategically positioned
them as our main force.
Well. Your orders?
Begin the cleanse.
Yes, sir!
Commence Operation
Purify Tokyo!
An announcement from the
acting Japanese government.
Please be aware that
as of midnight tonight,
we are minimizing the area
of the quarantined zone.
Anyone attempting to venture
past the red lines will be
immediately purified without
question, so please be mindful.
This is as cheap as it gets.
I don't really give a damn if
it's the president's orders.
There's just not
any sport in it.
And this so-called
Ghost unit, they're not
connected from here, are they?
And they're clearly
not on the scene.
So where are they
operating from?
That's classified.
Is it true?!
It went down at Koenji.
They slaughtered them?
Things are even worse
than we thought they were.
Nanba.
It's a little late
to be up and about.
What're you guys doing?
People are claiming that
there was a massacre in Koenji.
So what now?
You still wanna sit
around doing nothing?
Tell me, Rowan.
Do you have any idea
what caused the ancient
and mighty city-states
of Greece to topple?
What wiped them out?
No, sir.
I'm afraid my major
was in physics.
Demagogy.
I'm lifting the signal jam.
Let's give the people
something fun to discuss.
And, send. Now.
Watch the civil
discourse unfold.
Pretty sadistic, sir.
I couldn't ask for
a better compliment.
Thanks a ton
for the help, Gramps.
We couldn't have survived much
longer on the run like that.
Is there any way
we can repay your kindness?
Keido's been busy
since he took office.
All lines of communication
and transport into the city
have been shut down. But I
know there are still plenty
of survivors within the wall.
They must be saved.
It'll be our pleasure
to assist you anyway we can.
Hey, look!
"This is from a solid source.
Someone who got outside".
"If you hand over
Funeral Parlor members,
you can get outside the wall"?!
Shu. Did you hear about
what happened in Koenji?
Yeah.
It's most likely
just a rumor, though.
But I know it's the kind of
thing the Anti-Bodies would do.
You don't think they'll do
anything to our school, do you?
It's gonna be okay.
I doubt it'll get worse
than it already is.
At least we're all together.
And if it comes down to it,
I promise I'll fight for us.
Well, then I'll make sure
you don't get injured.
Worse comes to worse,
I'll heal you with my Void.
Thanks, Hare.
Y'know, Shu. Don't you
think it would be best
if you were in charge
during all of this?
You should run for
student council president.
Nah, I don't think so.
I'm the last guy in the world
who's cut out to
give people orders.
I just don't think I have it
in me to be a leader.
Yes, you do, I know it!
You've just talked yourself
into believing that.
You could be a king, Shu.
If that's what you want.
Spoken like a supportive
queen. I'm just kidding.
Oh, good. Obviously
you're feeling better.
Yeah, well. There's not really
any point in staying upset.
Even if you trampled
on my privacy.
Get her! She's a member!
Noooo!
Hold her still!
Confess! You're with
Funeral Parlor! Stay down!
It says that members
of the terrorist group
have tattoos on their backs.
Right, let's check.
Get away from her!
What the hell are
you jerkoffs doing?!
It's none of your
business, back off!
Take your hands off of her!
What the hell's
going on? Looks bad.
We've got trouble!
There's a rumor online that the
government's offering asylum to
anyone who turns over a proven
member of Funeral Parlor.
Are you serious?
Inori and Ayase!
Hey, it's no big deal.
We just wanna make sure
you don't have a tattoo
on your back. Okay?
I'll take a look
in the old building.
Sounds good.
Just be careful, Tsugumi.
Inori.
Something wrong? Shu?
There's an awful
rumor going around.
Did anyone try to hurt you?
I'm okay. Nobody's laid
a hand on me. I promise.
Oh. That's a relief.
Come on. Let's go.
Sure.
Y'know, I've had a weird feeling
ever since I first saw you.
So tell me. Your class.
What is it?
Move it.
Thought so!
You bitch!
Misslllllle kick!
Let's go, Aya!
Get back here!
Aya!
You idiot, keep running!
Like I'm just gonna
leave you with these jerks.
What a brave little soldier.
We're moving up the assembly.
The student body meeting will
now be held in ten minutes.
This pertains to all classes.
Please head to the gym at once.
We can't let rumors tear
us apart. Help will come
if we wait for it.
The best thing to do
is for us to sit tight
and weather the storm.
You've been
saying that for weeks!
Can you even say
anything else?!
She's losing them up there.
They're not listening
to her anymore.
C'mon, she needs our support
now more than ever!
I still haven't
seen Ayase and Tsugumi.
There's only one thing
we wanna hear.
Just tell us how we can avoid
being slaughtered, President.
Our only chance for
survival is to hand over
the Funeral Parlor gang.
That's just a rumor!
And I know there aren't
any members of Funeral
Parlor in our school!
That just shows
how little you know!
Let's prove her wrong.
We already found a couple
of members ourselves.
Look! They've got both of 'em!
As you can see, these girls
are wearing our school uniform,
but had anyone here ever
laid eyes on either of them
before the blockade?
I heard they're supposed
to have tattoos on their backs!
Ohhh, they are, huh? Well
You know what that means.
Guess we better check 'em out
right here and right now.
Leave them alone!
Their terrorist organization
is responsible for
biological warfare! So shut
up! We've got no choice here!
Easy. Just be a good girl now.
Yeah, do it!
Stop this-
This is bad. They're goin' full
blown mob mentality here.
We've gotta turn you over!
It's our only chance!
It's for the greater good! So
no hard feelings or anything!
Stop it!
Hey, isn't he-
That's the guy who
destroyed the Endlave.
It's Shu Ouma.
What? What's your problem, man?
Take your hands off of Ayase.
I'm part of Funeral Parlor too.
Everyone relax. We can
figure this out together.
And I know just
how to do it, too.
Hey, hold on!
I'm turning in
Funeral Parlor members.
See! Our high school's
still filled with lots
of students taking shelter.
We'll turn these guys in
if you just let us go home.
It's that obnoxious runt.
She's with Funeral Parlor?!
Go on, get moving.
Whoa, hey. That's just stupid.
So what now? Am I free?
Hey, come on. I thought-
What the hell? They
were gonna let us go!
They said they would!
Why'd they do that?!
It should be obvious by now.
We can't trust anything
the government says.
And now you have an idea
of what Shu's power can do.
This is my Void. The
replicating hand scanner!
It creates an identical
looking human copy and
you can control them remotely!
It's pretty awesome, right?
This situation. I know how
scared everyone's been.
There's a lot you don't
understand. But now you know.
The government's not on our
side. So let's work together
to come up with a new plan.
And let's do it with
a level head.
This is all bullshit.
The government. Your powers.
It's all lies!
I told you to
calm down, didn't I?
Try not to piss me off.
You saw it for
yourselves yesterday.
We're capable of
protecting us all.
So you can rest easy
on that. Regardless.
Whoever's gonna be our leader.
You need to think long and hard.
Think of a way to
get us out of this.
That's all I had to say.
Thanks for listening.
Not so fast, Shu.
We're not done yet. Alright,
guys. I don't think any of us
can disagree with what Shu just
said. So let me ask you this.
Out of everyone in this
gymnasium, who do you think
is most qualified to be
our leader in this crisis?
Shu Ouma!
I vote for Shu!
Shu should lead us!
Hold on. What are you-?
Let's hear a round of applause
from everyone who thinks
Shu Ouma should be our new
Student Council president!
Yahiro. What are you doing?
I'll help you with the job.
Just try it. Admit it, Shu.
You know this is what
you're supposed to do now.
Wait. Run that by
me again. Yahiro.
We'll rank all the students
on a scale from A to F.
It'll be based on their
genomic resonance.
The lower their resonance.
The less use we have for them.
From this point on, the strength
of the Void, will tell us the
value of the person. Basically,
it's a Void ranking system.