We've got trouble, you guys!
What's the matter?
It's the Leucocyte! It was
just fired at Point Delta!
But that's where Gai is.
The Leucocyte. It's a cluster
of Quasi-Zenith satellites
arranged as a constellation
directly over the Earth.
Once the constellation
is completed.
It'll have ubiquitous
coverage of Japan
and be able to strike
any target at any time.
But, why would
they build that?
To exterminate
the Japanese people.
Gai?
You're alive!
Are you injured?
Just a few scratches.
What about Kyo and the others?
They weren't as fortunate.
Our reinforcements
were taken out
and none of the supplies
are salvageable.
Should we delay and
reassess our strategy?
No, we don't have any time
to waste! Nothing stops!
All right. Are you ready, Gai?
Yeah.
I'll get straight
to our objective.
The Leucocyte system.
We're taking it down.
Its control center is at the
base of the Tsukigase Dam.
We will infiltrate through
the ground level entrance.
And then terminate
the control cores.
So what do we do,
just smash them up?
Kenji.
Coming up. Here we
have the Leucocyte.
It's controlled through
an earthbound state
of the art quantum
cryptography system.
And it's 200 meters
beneath a dam.
Here we have the control system
in question. The cores of the
device are housed in a
superconductive "float cage".
It switches to a hibernation
mode in response
to any physical tampering.
And therein lies the rub.
You can't manipulate this thing
from the outside at all.
So, if you want
to signal it to stop.
You've got to manipulate the
cores without touching them.
How is that possible?
That's where Shu and
Kenji fit into the plan.
Shu's ability
to draw out a Void.
And Kenji's
gravity manipulation.
These are the keys
to this operation.
However, our reinforcements have
been drastically minimized.
This is the schematic for
a new strategy. It raises our
projected casualties from five
percent to thirty five percent.
But it can still work. I'd
like you all to look it over.
Hold on. So you're saying
that one out of three of us
will die? That's too many!
Would you prefer to
apply that percentage
to the whole country? We have
no choice but to act now.
Well I don't like it! I don't
want to be responsible
for somebody's death
if I happen to screw up!
Fine. Let it be
on my head, then.
What about Kyo and the others?
Were they just
statistics to you?
Count me out. I don't want
the guilt of your sins.
All right, Shu. Are you done
acting like a spoiled brat?
What? I'm saying
all this for your sake!
Or were you just going
to blindly follow him
to your death, huh?
Okay, enough! Who do you think
sounds like the asshole?
It sure as hell isn't Gai.
Read the social cues, man.
Just look around you.
What do we do now?
Nothing. The strategy
stays the same. Dismissed.
Shu?
Oh, it's just you.
What do you want?
Listen, sorry about
earlier. I should've
known you wouldn't leave Gai.
Nobody would choose me over him,
I was just fooling myself.
Stop feeling sorry
for yourself. I hate that.
You're right.
Listen.
There's something important
that I think you need to see.
Leucocyte 3 will enter
its planned orbit
in four hours, thereby
completing the cage.
You're on standby until
we've secured the process.
It's a shame that
you aren't going
to have time to see it through.
Funeral Parlor will attack
in two hours and
seventeen minutes.
Do you have an informant
amongst their ranks?
No, it's just a gut feeling.
A theory I'm hoping to test.
Little bit of a game.
That would make this the first
time that I hope your instincts
are off the mark, Segai.
Keep me posted.
Why two hours and
seventeen minutes, you think?
Well that's when
the sun sets, obviously.
Oh, good point.
They want the cover of night.
This is your first battle
since you've recovered.
Do you feel up to it?
What?
When the hell have
I ever "not been up to it"?
Those little maggots are going
to pay for stealing my Steiner.
Yes, I'll crush them. Even
if they try to surrender.
I'll line them up and
pull the trigger.
Sir? I'm sorry,
were you talking to me?
Come on! I can hardly wait
to see what you have
in store for me this
time. Don't let me down.
My heart just might break in two
if you don't show up, Shu Ouma.
I'm not sure what the hell I'm
doing. It's been a long time
since something's gotten to me
the way he did. To be honest,
It took all of my strength to
not drop my "leader" act.
I wasn't the only one who
survived the Leucocyte attack.
Kyo was still
alive just barely.
Gai, thank you so much.
I'll never forget everything
you've done for me. I'll never
forget. Thank you, Gai.
She was smiling. She was glad
that I was okay. Glad that she
was dying instead of me.
I couldn't help but ask myself.
Am I actually capable
of repaying such
a great sacrifice? Shouldn't
I be better than this?
The truth is,
I'm a much weaker man
than I've led them all
to believe. I'm worthless.
I should be the first one
selected out, the first to die.
Are you spying on me now?
Haven't you done enough damage?
I'm not sure
I wanted to hear that.
I didn't know there
was that side to you.
Just what kind of person
were you convinced I was?
Sorry I'm human. Sometimes
I lose confidence in myself.
And sometimes I use people.
People like Inori?
Yeah, sure.
Did you think I could
sacrifice them,
and not feel the weight of
their lives on my shoulders?
I'm not indifferent to
their deaths, Shu.
I just know,
what they're worth.
From now on,
you've got my help.
Then you're a fool, too.
We're all set.
Begin the mission.
Black Swan to all units,
combat has now begun!
Enemy approaching!
Where the hell are they?
Major Segai!
Would you kindly tell
the Lieutenant, it's time?
I have missed that sound!
It feels good to be doing
what I do best.
I never got to thank you
for this sweet ride.
Steiner! My Steiner,
give it back! It's mine!
Mine! Give it back!
Thanks, Ogumo!
Gai, the diversion's working
like a charm. Are you in yet?
Yeah. I've got to shut
down the transmission.
Say a prayer for us.
Come back in one piece, okay?
You got it.
Run!
You saving your bullets
for something special, Shu?
I'm kind of focused
on running for my life!
Excuses, excuses. Just kill
some people. And, kaboom!
The cores are in here.
Let's move!
There's too many of them!
I'll hold them off while
you move in. All right? Gai?
If that's what you want.
Thank you.
I don't want to have to kill
you. But I will. It's your call.
Dammit!
All right, this was
your decision.
Inori! You too?
Come on, enough with
the moral outrage.
Let's go ahead and do this Void
thing. Just make it snappy.
It isn't a whole lot of fun.
There's been a breech.
It's the core room!
Go ahead and make the swap.
You just can't make up
your mind, can you?
Now where are my manners?
I really should
say hello to our guests.
Aim for the center?
That's right.
And keep it steady.
Funell will input the shut down
command once the circuit is cut.
Surprise! It's nice
to finally see you, Gai.
I've been looking forward
to paying you back
for making a fool out of me.
What now?
Stay focused on your task!
Daryl! Don't forget the cores
are in there! Be careful!
Shu!
What the hell?
Get off of me!
You piece of shit!
That was a close one. Gai!
Bring it home,
Toku! Hey?
Bad news, Gai!
What is it?
There's something wrong
with Leucocyte 1!
The altitude control
is malfunctioning.
It's plummeting to Earth!
At the rate it's falling,
Leucocyte 1 will crash
with most of its mass intact.
In the center of Tokyo!
Hey, Shu. Give me the pen.
The transmitter pen GHQ forced
you to take. Give it to me.
I guess you had it
all figured out.
So you decided not to push
the buttons, huh, Shu?
Kind of a letdown, but it all
worked out for the best.
You must be Segai?
I'm honored you know
my name, Gai Tsutsugami.
I'll make you a deal.
I'll use this to stop
the satellite's fall.
And in exchange.
You erase every single
piece of information
that you've
gathered on Shu Ouma.
Your pen doesn't send
a beacon to GHQ.
It signals the Leucocyte,
Shu. It was programmed
to fire at your location when
you pushed the buttons.
Which means, if we can manage
to get the firing satellite
lined up with this pen. And
with the falling satellite
in between. Then we can
destroy it before it crashes.
Whoa, hold on!
That means the person who's
holding the pen would be
right in the line of fire!
Why is Gai outside? What the
hell happened to the plan?
I have no idea, but we need
to make sure he's covered!
Am I just going to stand back
and watch again?
Can I really live with that?
You can save them
if you want. Do you?
What do you mean?
First, tell me.
Do you really want to help?
Do you want to save Gai?
Is he worth saving?
I thought you'd say that.
It's come down to this.
I can stand back
and let the world die.
Or I can take its place.
Gai!
What're you doing here?
Where did you get that Void?
Someone thought of
a way out of this without
getting you killed.
So I'm not letting you do this!
Kay, Tsugumi.
How much time is left?
You've only got about thirty
seconds! Everyone hear that?
Thirty seconds and counting!
Roger. Black Swan.
No, you don't!
This is for all of us.
All of our power combined!
Now!
He did it!
Why'd you do it, Shu?
Do you really think the world
would miss one sinner?
I told you I would help,
didn't I? You see?
Now we're in it together.
Thank you, Shuichiro. Cocytus
trembled with your efforts.
It won't be much longer
before she awakens.
She'll rise from her slumber
seeking her beloved king.