Shu!
What the hell is going on here?
Gai?
He's alive?!
Uh, attention units,
protect Gai Tsutsugami.
Protect him? What the hell for?
I don't know but
those are the orders.
Please, just follow them,
Lieutenant.
You can't be serious. That
guy is enemy number one!
Prometheus One to
Delphi. Target sighted.
This is Delphi. Ready the RM
warheads. Wipe them out.
I repeat. Wipe them out.
Hey! Incoming!
Hey, come on, you don't have
to do this! Stop them!
Attack.
What the-?!
What happened to them?!
Gai.
Gai! I can't believe
you're alive! But,
why are you doing this?
You, bastard!
I'm gonna kill you!
I'm no longer the man that
you knew. Now choose.
Either you follow my word,
or you declare yourself
as my enemy, and
you die a lonely death
right here and now.
But Gai.
What did they do to you?!
What happened?
What the hell
is wrong with you?!
Keep away from Master Gai!
Screw this!
There's no way in hell
I'm gonna start
protecting you now!
You're in my way,
runt! Move it!
Time to move!
Right. I know that voice.
Shu!
Gai Tsutsugami! None of
it would've happened.
You're the reason
everything went wrong!
It's all your fault!
Initiate emergency bailout!
Gai!
Are you okay?
Keido. It's me. I'm returning.
Gai. I was useful, right? I did
everything you asked me to.
You've done exceptionally
well, Comrade Arisa.
As a reward, you've earned
yourself the honor of
a permanent rank
serving Master Gai.
It's ironic, isn't it? Our
fleet was mobilized here
ten years ago on a relief and
aide mission. And now this.
I'd rather not think that
our efforts of goodwill
were meaningless.
Regardless, this is not
a hostile invasion. We're
simply suppressing the virus.
Burn it down!
The 7th fleet. It's gone.
But that's impossible.
Attention every human being
living on this planet.
My name is Master
Gai Tsutsugami.
The fate of your
world is up to me.
Your lives are
already in my hands.
I wonder how it must
feel to realize that
your entire planet
is now a cage.
Your each and every move is
being constantly monitored.
You are under the target of
256 Leucocytes. From now on.
I'm calling a ceasefire.
Military action
is no longer permitted.
In addition, Ward 24 is now
a designated forbidden zone.
Trespassing will be considered
a hostile act and you will be
shot on sight by the Leucocytes.
I have only one simple demand.
Don't get in my way.
That is all.
Why?
Three days have passed since
that foreboding declaration.
While the world just waits
in nervous anticipation.
Ward 24 still has not
taken any action yet.
And its odd silence is only
adding to the anxiety at large.
And you haven't received
communication from
your people or Shu Ouma? Their
whereabouts are still unknown?
Yes. We have various
reports from the students
who escaped. Each report
claims that Ouma's Void power
seems to have been stolen
by Gai Tsutsugami.
How very interesting. I would
surmise that the possession
of Void power is the root cause
of this entire situation. Yes.
That means it could have been
what they were after all along.
And by them. You mean
the Daath organization?
Who're they?
They're a secret society who've
been around longer than
the Priory of Sion,
or even the Freemasons.
Long enough that most historians
have written them off
as nothing more than a legend.
Which only made it easier
for them to flourish.
They've steadily acquired more
sympathizers over the decades.
And they've infiltrated every
organization you can think of.
How is that possible?
One more thing. I'm sorry,
sir, but the rumors that
your granddaughter joined forces
with Ward 24 appear to be true.
Is that so?
Can you handle the rest of the
negotiations with the OAU?
Yes. I'll be fine.
But what about you?
I have personal matters
I must attend to.
I'm sorry, Shu, but, at least
I've managed to free you
from the king's fate.
Live your life, Shu. Please.
We have a report from Team E.
Block 3 is locked
down and clear.
Alright.
Are you dissatisfied
with something?
I was told that you specifically
volunteered for this assignment
out of your own volition.
Only because Gai-
Careful, you are speaking
of our great leader.
It's disrespectful not
to call him 'Master' Gai.
Fine. Master Gai.
What do you suppose he
wants with Inori Yuzuriha?
We're the rank and file.
It's not for us to make
suppositions about
his reasoning.
Check, and mate.
Oh, dear! You've bested me. But
I must stay true to my word,
mustn't I? I'll secure you
an audience with Master Gai.
You lost the game
on purpose, didn't you?
Well maybe I'm curious to
hear some of his answers
to your questions.
What's wrong with that?
You have to eat something.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, everyone.
I was wrong about everything.
Dead wrong. I'm sorry.
It appears that
we've located the target.
Excellent. We'll move
out immediately.
It's an ambush!
We're surrounded!
Just stay here. I'll find
out what's going on.
Hold your fire!
Stop it! Stop shooting!
This is difficult to accept.
I never once imagined that you
could be this foolish, Arisa.
Grandfather.
Gai Tsutsugami has no interest
in the world outside of his own
selfish goals, it doesn't matter
how much you do for him,
your feelings will
never be returned.
We don't have time for this,
sir. We have an important
mission that requires
our attention elsewhere.
Why bother hunting
down a helpless boy
who's lost his power? You no
longer have any use for him.
Your assumption is erroneous.
Our top priority is the
retrieval of Inori Yuzuriha.
It doesn't matter.
Especially since
you won't live
to see it through.
I've no choice but to
cleanse my family's shame
with my own hands.
Arisa, I'm sorry!
I can see my skills
have slipped.
No. Grandfather.
Excellent work.
He said that they
were after me, but why?
Take a look at this
flashy piece a ass.
Whatever, man.
Just do her, already.
Inori?
Shu!
Please, help!
Uh. What's wrong?
Inori? Inori! Stop it!
What is it?
Inori Yuzuriha, I don't know
what Gai could possibly
want with you. But I've
got you. Put in a request
for an Endlave battalion!
I've gotta get this
under control. With the way
things are going,
I might hurt Shu.
You got it.
Shu will inevitably die by your
hand. That's just the way
it is. You are a
monster after all.
A monster?
Even your heart is
a mere facsimile.
Monsters aren't capable of
possessing real hearts, y'know.
Give yourself over to me before
it's too late. It's the only
way to stop yourself from
slaughtering him. Right?
I'm a monster?
That's all I am?
There's nothing more
to me than that?
Even my heart isn't my own.
Inori.
Hey, uh. I've been meaning
to ask you something
but I wasn't sure
how to say it.
What is it?
Well, um. I've been wondering
why your Void is-You know what.
Just forget I said anything.
Are you sure?
Yeah. It doesn't matter
what's inside you, y'know?
You are who you are
and that's what counts.
Shu's right. I'm me.
Wildflower, boldly blooming
Tell me how people
live so violently
Inori.
Help me understand
How this cruelty began
Will the fighting never end
Why am- Why'm I crying?
Listen to me, Shu.
I don't want you to
condemn yourself anymore.
You don't have to blame
yourself for what's happened.
I've developed so many wonderful
feelings I didn't know before
from being with you. I am
who I am thanks to you.
Even if the entire world
has turned against you now.
Even if you won't
stop hating yourself.
No matter what,
I'll always be on your side.
What's this about?
You need to know
that before I go away.
I'm the one that
they're searching for, Shu.
It'll be the perfect
distraction. And then you can-
Not a chance in hell! I would
rather die than sacrifice you!
Sleep well, Shu.
She is a monster.
Maybe I am a monster, and
maybe my feelings aren't real.
But I don't care.
I'm gonna protect Shu.
Because he's
a part of who I am!
Even if my feelings for him
are fake, they always felt real
to me. They're the only real
things I've ever known!
Fool. Look what's
become of you.
You've belonged to this cause
ever since they created you.
And yet you think you
could just hand yourself
over to some human. Monster.
Inori?