I'm sorry, but you
just missed her.
No. Inori.
Where the hell is this light
coming from? What is it?
Something big's going down.
I think that much is obvious.
Alright, we're gonna stay
down here and hold them off.
You get up to the top
and help out Shu!
Ayase! You're backup!
I'm on it! Although-
You've rubbed my face
in the dirt too many times,
but it's not gonna
happen again!
Not while I've got
Gespenst here!
Tsugumi. Can you take
back their system yet?
It's like their
defenses are on steroids!
The more code I knock down,
the more shows up!
Someone's rivaling
Tsugumi? Kenji.
Of course it would be you.
Top of the morning, Triton.
Welcome back, Mana.
Shu!
You're here!
You changed your mind!
I've had a rough time, y'know.
There was this awful girl
holding me back, and she
wouldn't let me out.
But it's okay now.
I ground her up into dust.
She thought she could stop me,
but I made her body mine.
She was a headstrong little
beast. Especially for
a man-made monster.
Shut up!
Shu?
Inori is not a monster!
She's got more love
in her than you ever could!
You've taken her face and voice,
but you're the monster!
She's the real human!
You're so mean, Shu.
You can't even see how much
your sister loves you.
I couldn't even stop loving you
after my body was torn apart.
And here you are, still refusing
to give me your love, Shu.
No need to get upset.
You too?
Leave him to me.
You focus on the world.
You've hurt me quite
badly, Shu. Twice now.
You're a cold and heartless
boy. And when you hurt people
like this, you should be
prepared for them to hurt you
just as much. You can apologize,
but nothing will ever make me
forgive you.
What?
So it's begun, Gai.
You've done it.
What the hell's
going on out there?!
We're registering genomic
resonance from Ward 24
that dwarfs the readings
from Lost Christmas!
The high output seems
to be interfering with
the Endlave's remote systems!
What is this?
This is it, Shu. The Fourth
Apocalypse has begun.
The selection and evolution of
all human life on this planet!
Yahiro!
Their frail physical bodies
will be shed in exchange for
an eternal collective mind
within the crystal. That is
the next stage of humanity. The
Voids were only the beginning,
the first of a new world where
all thought becomes matter!
You really think you
can stop me with your guns?
Watch out, little bug!
You're gonna get crushed!
That's as far as you get!
Don't underestimate
my guns! Ayase!
Get the hell outta there!
Tsugumi! We could use
some help here! Tsugumi?
Just die already!
Bastard! What?!
Lieutenant Daryl!
The Void Emulator is still
in its trial phase!
Don't overdo it!
You've gotta be joking. You
give me this power and tell me
to lay off when I haven't
even killed them yet!
Souta!
Gai! Tell me. You sacrificed
Mana's consciousness
to save her soul. Remember?
You gave your life that day
to make it happen! So how?!
How did we end up like this?!
You couldn't possibly
understand, Shu!
Everything's handed to you.
And all you've ever done
is turn your nose up at people.
You'll never understand!
How d'you like this, Kurosu? You
tried so desperately to save
your daughter and now she's
about to end the world.
I guess you lose.
That's why you wanna
see the world die?
That's what this is all about?
I don't see much point
in denying it.
Are you gonna
shoot me? Can you?
I can't let them get past me.
I have to protect him
until the end!
Persistent jerk! It's
too much! At this rate-
Tsugumi.
I need you to keep him occupied
until I give you the signal.
Can you hold out that long?
Just watch me, mister!
I would've let you have
her. Mana, that is.
I would've given up
the throne to the old you.
But now, the man you've
become doesn't deserve it.
Goodbye, Shu.
I feel so heavy.
Is this how I die?
And take all of
my friends with me?
Don't give up, Shu. Not now.
I know it hurts, but you can
still move. You can do it.
Everyone's counting on you.
Everyone. It's alright.
I want you to use me.
What the hell?!
Did the process get reversed?
Kenji. Consider this checkmate.
There are people
who believe in me.
People who have put
their lives in my hands.
And I refuse to let them
down. I'm taking Inori back
no matter what!
You're up and running!
Sorry I left you
hanging there, Aya!
I'm connected!
I'll keep you
linked in remotely.
Gai. If you're gonna try
to stop me, just know,
I'll do everything
I can to take you down!
That voice. I had a feeling
you'd make an appearance, runt!
Tsugumi!
I'm on it!
What?
Killing you is the only
unfinished business I have left
on this planet. Kill-em-All
Daryl's last trophy!
Shut your hole!
You sound pathetic!
Inori?
Nooooooooo!
Did we do it?
Brother!
It's true Kurosu might have
lost, but I never said
that I won. Now, run, Haruka.
Gai.
You've done well, Shu.
The man you've become.
Don't ever change.
Where am I?
This is the point
of convergence.
The world reborn and
shaped by the Apocalypse.
I don't understand.
What you see,
this is Daath's Shangri-La.
Everything on this planet,
it would've become the bones
beneath the new living flesh
of crystal. Even I would
eventually have been encased
within it. Even their king.
I've always been terrified
of falling prey to selection.
So I resisted it, and clung
to Eve. Hid behind Mana.
The day I died. Beneath
Roppongi, when I begged you
to stab me, I believed
I could free Mana
from her curse that way.
And maybe I could have, if it
weren't for the will of Daath.
They won't allow Mana to die.
They'll keep bringing her back
until she's fulfilled her fate.
So I realized there's
only one way to free her.
To let them use her to
accomplish their goal.
I decided to take a gamble.
I became their demon king.
And worked to bring
about their apocalypse.
And I bet on you, Shu.
Bet on you stopping it.
I've finally managed
to give her peace.
No!
The rest is up to you.
Go save Inori.
Shu. Is that you?
Please don't blame yourself.
You've done so much. Taught me
how to feel so many emotions.
All of them. Each one
is thanks to you.
Shu. Are you there? Shu? There
you are. Stay with me forever,
Shu. You know that I'll always
be on your side. Right?
Inori. It's time
for us to leave.
Hey! Was that-
Yeah. I felt it too.
It's our Voids.
No. What's he doing? You idiot,
don't you act like a martyr!
The entire crystalized framework
supporting the structure's
giving out! The whole facility's
gonna collapse any second!
Hey, guys.
Dr. Ouma! Are you okay?
What are you-?
If you get a second chance,
do it right this time!
Don't be Kill-em-All Daryl!
It's not who you are!
I can feel it happening. All
the emotions and the memories
flowing into me. From
my friends, my enemies,
they were all born
innocent, uncorrupted.
Inori.
Take it.
Inori!
Hang on! Shu's not out yet!
I know that! But that
doesn't mean I'm gonna
let you die in there with him!
Shuuuuu!
Hey! Yahiro!
Wow, you guys are early.
Work been keepin' ya busy?
Fairly. But I didn't have
any trouble ducking out
early today. Ayase.
Mind if I sit next to you?
Be my guest.
Hey, Aya, you're okay
with Earl Grey, right?
Thank you, Tsugumi, so polite.
Only for today. The mid-terms
for my students are coming up.
That's when the
real demon comes out.
He's not here yet?
Don't worry. I'm sure
he'll be here soon.
He told me he's been
looking forward to it.
Speak of the devil!
Yeah!
Oh, good! It took
you long enough.
Hey, guys. Sorry I'm late.
Hold 'em up. Cheers, you guys!
To the new year!