We'll rank all the students
on a scale from A to F.
It'll be based on their
genomic resonance.
The lower their resonance,
the less use we have for them.
Basically, it's a
Void ranking system.
Lemme just bandage it
up aaand, all better!
That girl's Void is the most
useful thing ever, huh!
She can fix me up anytime.
Thanks again for the healing!
Ever since you treated me,
I've been just fine.
I really owe you one!
When I compare it to yours, it
seems like my Void is useless.
That's not true.
Nobody's Void is useless.
We're all in this together,
doing whatever we can.
So, uh, just keep up
the good work.
We did go so far as to
conduct a general Void exam,
but I can't get behind Yahiro's
idea to rank everybody by 'em.
I just don't think there's
anything to be gained
by making the students
feel unequal.
That said, though, if I smiled
and told you everything
was perfect as-is,
I'd be lying through my teeth.
'Cause it's not.
Check it, Tsugumi.
Us security guys are starving.
You don't mind fast-tracking
us our grub, right?
Wait your turn!
Yeah, of course! I was
just messin' around!
We've got all kinds of problems.
And that red line is getting
closer and closer all the time.
Just how long can we hold out?
It's not good.
Our resupplying efforts
are running further behind.
That means we're short on
ammo. And our barricade's
nowhere near strong enough.
The ranking system
would clear that right up.
People work harder
with in a hierarchy.
How often I gotta say it?
Look, that's not something
I'm ever gonna be okay with!
Discrimination by Void is wrong!
We'd be categorizing,
that's all.
That's just semantics, y'know?
If they feel like it's
discrimination, then it is.
For whatever it's worth,
I understand how you feel
about it. But that red
line keeps creeping in.
That's the reality.
Yeah, I know it is, but still.
Sympathy will get you
killed, often as not.
That's what Gai always said!
I get it, you don't want people
to dislike you--am I right?
No, you're not! I--
What do you feel like doing?
None of them is in charge. You
are. What do you want to do?
Kay, I'm good. Thanks.
Um. Ayase, what exactly is going
on between Shu and Inori?
Huh? What are you
asking me for?!
Yeah! I wanna know
what's going on, too!
Tell us, Aya--what're
ya waiting for?!
Seriously, how come
you're asking me this?
Back there, I didn't expect
that. I mean, Shu seemed to be
against the ranking system
'til she spoke up.
It's just that she could
see he was on the fence
about the whole thing.
When Shu was put in charge,
I was so happy.
I knew he'd be just like
a king should, kind.
A king, huh?
King Shu! I guess that pretty
much is his job title.
You don't have to
tease me about it!
Sooo, when you gonna
tell him you like him?!
Geez, chill out!
No point rushing her into it!
Hafta! Girl's got a
rival! "Nothing ventured
nothing gained," right?
Cut the crap already!
"Categorizing," my ass! That's
straight up discrimination!
Yeah. That's why
I'm not doing it.
What the hell are you
thinking?! I know you're
my friend and all but
I am really pissed off!
I said I wasn't gonna do it!
Dude. Stop yelling at me.
You did, huh. Dude, my bad.
I'm sorry! I didn't mean to be
a jerk just now! I'm gonna bow!
Forgive me!
Souta, don't bow to me--c'mon!
Put 'er there, then!
No harm, no foul,
you know what I'm sayin'?
Yeah.
Okay, then. Let 'er rip, buddy!
Excuse me?
You know, shout stuff
dramatically into the darkness.
It's a male-bonding thing.
They do it in movies
all the time!
People shouldn't be ranked
cause of their usefulness!
Discrimination really sucks!
What he said.
I love Inori Yuzuriha!
Hey, what's that got to do
with male-bonding?
That's part of it. Baring
your soul an' junk. C'mon!
Fill those lungs and go for it!
Yeah, okay.
I stumbled into
the job of president,
but I'm not qualiiiiified!
The truth comes out!
I don't think there's
anything wrong with
wanting people to like me!
I don't think there's
anything wrong with
wanting girls to like me!
The Void ranking
system is stupid!
Hey, guys! I've decided--
It's not enough. No matter
how you do the math.
Well, what if we
inject less of it?
No point. Anything less than
a full dose is useless.
Problem, Shu. A big one.
Vaccine's running low.
If nothing else, we need
to make sure we have enough
on hand to keep Shu healthy.
Wait a sec. I don't want to
be given special treatment.
You realize if you get
sick, this whole school
is a sitting duck.
For whatever it's worth,
we can give vaccine priority
to all of the strongest Voids.
I've compiled a roster by rank.
Students will get the vaccine,
or not, based on this.
What?! Souta's number
is that low?!
If we don't do this, Shu,
we're all as good as dead.
It's your call.
You're the president.
The student body chose you.
And now their lives are
in your hands.
I found it while I was cleaning
the student council room.
So what is this "Void
ranking system" all about?!
Whatever it is, we're all
buried at the bottom of it!
Wait, does this mean they're
writing us off or something?!
Shu.
You said no ranking,
right? Tell them that.
Yeah. That's right.
We have a favor to ask.
Well, more like a request.
We want you to
pull out our Voids.
Huh? What for?
We need some practice
time. Think about it.
When you used it, my Void was
all badass and saved the day.
But when I'm holding it, it's
all I can do to get dinner open.
I can do better. We all can.
We just need to use 'em more!
C'mon! It's the
least you can do!
Give us a chance!
Hook us up!
Please, Shu!
We wanna be useful, that's all!
Just this once!
Yeah!
Give us the Voids!
C'mon, man!
Oh, they'll come. Now that
they're running low on vaccine,
they've precious little choice.
They're just a bunch
of high-school pukes.
Killing them isn't
worth my suiting up.
My dear Lieutenant, when that
patriotic young hologram
offered to hand over Funeral
Parlor members the other day,
I don't recall
you opening fire.
If I were in your shoes, I'd be
anxious to prove that Daryl Yan
is a man of action.
Rumors can be so harmful. Right?
You want action, huh?!
I didn't mean to offend.
You're quite good at this.
But then, a strategist of
your caliber should be.
Did you mean what you
said to me? If I beat you
in a game of chess, you will
allow me to see him in person?
Wanna know? Better win.
I kinda had a hunch you'd
be here. Everyone's looking
for you, y'know.
I'm feeling pretty low,
Hare. I really screwed up.
What do you mean,
you screwed up?
Hell, you want the full
list? Well, let's see.
I only ever think about
what people want to hear,
and I'm sick of it.
Huh?
First I agree with Yahiro.
Then I pull a 180 with Souta.
I'm so wishy-washy.
Everybody does that a little
bit. It's how folks get along.
I'm the leader.
I don't have that luxury.
I gotta be stronger than that.
Uhh.
It's all right. Because, there
are a lot of wonderful things
about you, too--you know that?
You go through life without
drawing attention to yourself.
Whenever you pull out a chair,
or set something down,
you do it softly.
And that's what
I love about you.
Just means I'm
the wrong guy for the job.
Do you really lo--
Don't say it!
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to say
that again--it just slipped out-
What's going on?!
Some students just went AWOL,
and Souta's one of 'em!
Are you sure?!
Positive. But they're
all holding Voids.
Does that mean you okayed this?
Okay, guys. That clinic
should be just up ahead.
They wouldn't have taken the
vaccine with 'em, would they?
Souta! You know it
isn't safe out here!
Wow--thanks for the heads-up!
What, you think we're stupid
just 'cause we're Rank F?!
We're gonna bring a bunch
of the vaccine back.
We'll see who's
so damn useless then!
Don't tell me this is
what you were planning
when you asked for your Voids!
Sucks when a friend
lies to ya, doesn't it?
Guess that makes us even!
That's not fair!
I meant what I told you!
Oh, crap! The Anti-Bodies!
Run! All of you! They're
gonna kill you, dammit! Go!
They got us cut off!
We're so dead!
You can't just stand
there! Fight back!
With this?!
Are you okay?!
I have to draw them away!
We've found Ouma, sir.
Wait, he's still alive?
You make him
your priority target!
If Shu Ouma
survived the attack,
maybe that girl did,
too- Who the hell cares?
Quick, Hare! Use your Void
to fix that car over there!
Fix a car?
So we can escape!
Shu's distracting them so we
can get the hell outta here!
Souta!
What's he trying to do?
C'mon--hurry up!
Sorry! I'm trying!
Bandages?
You're gonna need way more than
those when I'm done with you!
Hare! Run for it!
Hare!
That idiot! What the hell's he
thinking?! We need him back
at school, where it's safe!
There! We got three choppers!
And four Endlaves!
Backup, huh?
Your orders?
You're asking "Kill 'em all"
Daryl how we're gonna play this?
Weapons hot, moron!
I didn't want this.
I didn't want this!
They're in range!
But so are we!
Shu!
No! Please!
Shu, when you were little,
did you ever read a book
called "The Kind King"?
It's about a king,
who's so good to his people.
He gave them all the money,
and all the land they could
ever want until he gave
the whole kingdom away.
He'd done what they wanted,
but they hated him for it.
It's silly, but I really loved
that storybook king.
I think he was my first love.
And you remind me
so much of him.
You're kind to people,
and all they do is hurt you.
Hey. We still got
a live one down there.
I know that you're
going to be a great king.
I've always known.
Not yet.
Just in time.
You have my heart. Forever.
Huh? What happened?
No! Hare!
Hare!
Shu.
Noooo!
Took you long
enough! Let's play!
How'd he do that?!
Oh my god. Shu.
Get outta there!
You bastard!
Shu! Shu, I-
I'm sorry! It's all my fault!
It's all 'cause I wanted her
to fix up that stupid car!
Yeah, it is.
Shu!
Hare died because
of your stupidity.
You wanted to play the hero.
And Hare paid the price.
I didn't know--!
It shoulda been you
who died out there!
Stop! That is enough!
Hare died
because of you, Souta!
You're sorry, huh?!
Then bring her back
to life, you piece of shit!
I can't! I can't! Just stop!
No one else believed
in me like she did.
She saw through all
my mistakes. Hare!
Shu!
Come on. Let's get
back to campus.
Hey, man.
All this time,
I've been such a fool.
Kindness is just
another word for weakness!
No more giving the students
the ruler they want.
I'll give them
the one they deserve.