The next time you're
with Gai Tsutsugami.
Press the blue button
two times and then
the red button once. It'll
alert us to their location
and we'll move in before
they can cause more harm.
How's Kido?
He's still unconscious. It's
probably the shock of having
his Void used, but we aren't
sure when he'll wake up.
I see.
All right then. Just in
case you've forgotten.
This is Shu Ouma.
He possesses the Void Genome.
And he'll be at the core of our
strategies from this moment on.
With Shu's allegiance
to our resistance.
And with our attainment of
Kenji Kido. The most pressing
of our immediate goals
is finally within reach.
We now have the means
to retrieve the Leucocyte.
The Leucocyte?
This is the proposed plan.
Considering all variables,
there are 145
possible outcomes.
So. Have them memorized
by the advent of the mission!
Time frame?
Three days. If that's not enough
time, then we don't need you.
It hasn't even been
a full day since our raid
on the GHQ compound. Fatigue
is a realistic concern here.
According to who? What drove
you people to sign up for this?
Was it the hope of getting
a good night's rest?
You'll have time to rest
when you're dead. The enemy
isn't going to wait for you
to catch up on your sleep.
Ayase.
Uh, yes?
I'm giving you the
responsibility of making sure
he has enough basic training
to pull his own weight
on this mission.
You want me to do what?
He's bound to drag us all
down if we don't whip him
into shape. So train him well
if you want us to live.
Uh, hey. You really don't
need to worry about me
that much, I'm fine.
Honestly, I'd feel bad
causing trouble for a girl
who's uh. You know, disabled.
Yes, well. That's very
thoughtful of you, Ouma.
You're so kind.
You can just call me Shu.
If you want?
My only disability is dealing
with people like you.
Keep your sympathy
to yourself. Got it?
Hey. Are you serious
about jumping?
Yeah, it'll be fine.
Just believe in me!
What was that?
My clothes.
The pen is gone too.
Starting now, your
whole life is training!
You've had enough time
to sleep, so look alive!
I told you, you don't
have to do this.
Do you think I like this
either? But it's not our job
to ask questions.
Why do you even want to join
Funeral Parlor anyway?
I can't think of someone
less cut out for it.
My pen!
What's that you're
blubbering about? Oh. This?
Uh, yeah, where did you get
it? It looks like a nice one.
I found it. Don't tell me
this is yours?
Um, I did lose one.
It's probably mine;
you think I could have it back?
No.
This is perfect incentive.
How about this?
We're testing you in one week
to see if the training sticks
and if you've got what it
takes to join Funeral Parlor.
I'll give this back then.
But only if you pass.
The name's Argo,
I'm a sophomore at Ryusen.
Now tell me your name.
My name's Shu Ouma.
Yeah, I know.
Come after me like
you're going to kill me, kid.
But this knife
is real, isn't it?
Yeah. What about it?
You're going to face death
everyday from here on.
It's best to get
used to it now!
Your heart rate's
soaring straight into
the next solar system.
Just how little do you
actually exercise, anyway?
I'm more into artsy stuff.
It's kind of heavy.
So what do you think?
Huh? Is there any hope?
I don't think so.
As you can see, she's
pretty good at this stuff.
And that's the same level
of skill I want from you.
Huh?
What am I supposed
to do? Is this right?
Not quite. The slide will take
a chunk out of your hand
like that. Hold your
thumb like this.
You shouldn't get
so close to me.
Oh. Sorry.
I'm still here!
The Leucocyte Plan seems
to be advancing rather nicely.
The "Invisible Cage".
You can't help but like such
a perverse concept.
Enough small talk. How's your
plan to divide them playing out?
I give it a fifty-fifty
chance he'll follow through.
Cool, thank you! So Kyo. I heard
you're going side by side
with Gai on this one.
Yep! He's finally going
to let me join him in battle!
I'm kind of bummed I won't
get to see the test fight.
But I wish you the best
of luck, Shu! You can do it!
Thanks, I hope so!
See you guys later!
She seems so young to be doing
this. Just flocked to Gai
like everyone else. I guess
that's what confidence
can do for you, huh?
I mean anyone else could
do the things he does.
And nobody would follow them
blindly like this. But I guess,
it's always the selfish
people who end up making it
in this world.
There's nothing
selfish about Gai.
You're blind to everything
around you right now. And
at this rate. I seriously doubt
you'll ever see the truth.
But regardless,
that was insulting to Gai
and the people who believe
in him. Apologize.
Fine, I'm sorry.
On a different note.
Can you draw out those
Void things from anyone?
Why am I working my ass
training for these guys?
It's like I'm really
planning on joining them.
--the wind screamed by
The two overlapped
I shall sing the
proof that you lived
For the sake of those
who have no names
You know, this kind of reminds
me of the first time we met.
It's making me nostalgic.
I've been wondering. Why'd you
join Funeral Parlor, anyway?
I've been wondering
the same thing about you.
You have? Well I guess,
really, there're a whole bunch
of reasons. But the
main one. I think it's,
because I was happy.
That day, at the compound.
I was happy
that you came for me!
Hey, Inori? I have
a question for you.
What if I asked you
to just leave all this
and live a normal life
with me? Would you?
Gai gave me
the thing I needed most.
I had nothing.
And he gave me a name.
A world to live in.
A place to call home.
So no, I won't go with you.
But. I thought. I mean before,
all that stuff you said.
"I belong to you".
"I want to stay with you."
I just, I thought,
that's what you wanted.
Don't tell me.
It was Gai.
He told me to
tell you that stuff.
No.
You shouldn't get close to me.
But. Inori, wait! Stop!
Of course.
What's happening? Did
I misread things that badly?
How humiliating.
Why does everyone
love Gai so much?
Maybe you should
run with your eyes open!
Oh! Sorry!
Quit leering at me!
I didn't mean to!
Really, I'm sorry.
Saw their room, did you?
It's obvious how much you like
Inori. You poor, poor fool.
Eyes on the wall!
Oh, sorry, I forgot.
They sometimes spend the
night together in that room.
Usually two or three times a
month. We pretend not to see it,
but I think we've all noticed by
now. Sorry to have to tell you.
So you're cool with it,
is that it?
Why wouldn't I be?
Well I can tell that you like
Gai. So doesn't seeing them--
Where'd you come up
with that stupid assumption?
Uh, the way you act.
You have no idea what's going
on! I have respect for Gai.
That's all!
I just don't understand it.
Why'd she choose him?
The only thing I can think
of is that you girls seem
to have some kind of weakness
for good looking jerks.
But is that really all it is?
Maybe I'm too naïve to get it.
Or just socially illiterate.
I never see the signs.
You can turn back around.
Really want to know
why? Then I suggest
you try your hardest
in the mock battle.
If you pass, then you'll
officially be one of us.
And you'll start to see things a
little more clearly after that.
Thanks, but no. It's a rule of
mine to do this part by myself.
I don't exactly look my most
elegant hoisting myself
into that ridiculous chair. So
I don't like people watching.
Would you mind leaving?
Good night, Ayase.
Good night, Shu.
You look so much like her.
More and more, every day.
Does it bother you?
I'm not sure.
Gai!
Looks like one squadron.
Just what we planned for.
The OAU and the
Leaving Nations.
They're a highly
principled group.
All right. Let's put your
training to the test. This mock
battle is called Scenario
D-14, and it's modeled after
the Leucocyte mission. It
assumes a possible situation
in which you have to face
an Endlave by yourself.
If want to win this
test, just make it past
Steiner and take shelter in the
train car. The paint bullets
are strong enough to
knock you unconscious.
So don't get hit. Got it?
Let's do this!
Good luck.
She's setting him up
to fail. I mean hell,
I can't even make it
past Ayase's Endlave.
And she's even faster now that
she's got Steiner. Okay, Aya.
You ready to connect?
Plug me in.
You ready to start?
Okay then. Ready! Go!
You really want
to show me your back?
Quit running away
like a little coward!
It's ridiculous to ask
me to fight this thing
with just a gun!
Look sharp! You're acting
like you want to get shot!
Now what? I'm out of options!
What the?
Argo!
Sorry about this!
Made it!
Huh?
He did it.
That's impossible.
So, I guess I cheated?
That's debatable.
You just utilized the thing
that makes you unique.
A light that creates darkness.
I didn't realize I was
that gloomy on the inside.
Well, Shu. Welcome
aboard. Starting today,
you're officially one of us.
Ow!
Here, your reward.
If it means so much
to you, you might want
to put it someplace
safer than your pocket.
Right.
Team building drills?
Looks like fun.
So you're finally
awake. Kenji.
Wait, Kenji?
Kenji Kido. He's the one you
rescued from the compound.
Don't tell me you already
forgot about that, Shu?
There's nothing wrong
with team building drills!
You don't seem too quick.
In many ways.
What's up with
Gai's recruiting?
Screw you!
We've got trouble, you guys!
What's the matter?
What happened, Tsugumi?
It's the Leucocyte! It was
just fired at Point Delta!
But that's where Gai is.
This is bad, very bad.
We fired at an output
rate of 3 percent.
Target destruction rate was 110
percent with an error field
of point seven meters.
Through me, the road
among the lost creation.
I am the way to
a forsaken people.
Abandon all hope,
ye who enter here.