Shu Ouma has managed
to obtain the Void Genome.
He's recovered
the king's power.
To make matters worse,
he's materialized his own Void.
I'm aware of this.
Is that so? May I ask how?
How are you
feeling today, Mana?
A little cramped.
This girl has a remarkably
strong will for a clone.
Regardless, I'll possess
every inch of her soon enough.
And there won't be any limit
to the fun we'll have together.
Right, Triton?
Yahiro. I've been
looking for you.
Shu was pretty great,
wasn't he?
Yeah. Have you found time
to talk to him yet?
What could I say
to him after all this?
There's a broadcast
from Ward 24!
Gai's gonna talk!
Come on!
I gave you all very simple
instructions to follow.
To stay out of my way. Despite
this, there have already been
34 attempted
physical infiltrations,
and 42,000 attempted
hackings of Ward 24.
These attempts can
only mean one thing.
Clearly you are all anxious to
die. You want to be annihilated.
Very well. I shall grant your
wish. Each individual life
will be measured
by the world itself,
and your fates determined
by the winds of change.
The world as you know it, will
come to an end on December 25th.
We will clear the way for
the new world to begin.
Kuhouin had one last request. He
left me in charge of his assets
and connections, for the
sole purpose of insuring
that Gai is defeated.
Tomorrow morning, I'm joining
forces with another squadron.
A private military contractor
we're bringing in. All I need
to know is can I count on you
to fight alongside us, Shu?
And all of you. Ask
yourselves that question.
Are you ready to do what
needs to be done to beat him?
That sounds nice. But
first off, answer me this.
What's Gai doing? Just what
the hell is he planning on?
The Fourth Apocalypse.
He intends to spread
a Lost Christmas-type
epidemic across the face
of the entire planet.
That's what.
Shibungi?! I thought
you were dead!
I am quite alive. Shu.
Take this. Gai instructed me
to give it to you.
Isn't that?
The diary of Dr. Kurosu Ouma.
That's my father's?
They have the right to know
the truth before they die,
and the onus to comprehend
it. Especially Shu.
I can't imagine you would
want it any other way.
After all, weren't you Kurosu
Ouma's best friend, Father?
Best friend, huh? There was a
time I thought of him that way.
So long ago, back in the
days of my graduate studies
at Tennozu College. My only
relationship at that time
was with my academic pursuits,
and other people were
nothing but
annoyances. However.
Keido! Your paper is
a thing of true beauty!
Your work has literally
moved me to tears!
When I first met him,
the young Kurosu Ouma.
He opened my eyes to the world.
I realized there were others
who could operate on the same
level of conceptual abstraction
that I did. Others I
could argue theory with
and compete against.
We challenged each other.
It wasn't long before
the Genomic Resonance theory
Kurosu constructed on
the basis of my Intron
RAM Hypothesis commanded
worldwide attention as
the key to unlocking
the mysteries of evolution
and natural selection.
Kurosu! Look!
Your paper was pub-
Saeko Shijou. A renowned
student of the college's
medical school. Little did
I know, she was already
carrying Kurosu's
first child. Before long,
the two were married.
They relocated to Oshima
to be close to her family.
Five years later, fate struck.
Shuichiro! Check this out!
Amino acid bonding?!
The reading.
It's a Genomic
Resonance reaction!
My little Mana's the one
who found the meteorite.
She's the one we
should be thanking.
I was right, this is a virus.
It's not very infectious
on its own, although, when it's
activated by Genomic Resonance.
It inserts itself into the
introns, replicates like crazy,
and causes
structural sclerosis.
Wait, are you saying?
It's an instrument that plays
the notes of Genomic Resonance.
It's a trumpet of
the Apocalypse.
She's progressing nicely,
isn't she?
Who are you?
My name is Yu.
I represent Daath.
Daath?
The meteorite Mana
discovered has planted
the seeds of Apocalypse
across this island nation.
Once the seeds are fertilized,
the people of your country
will serve as the hosts
of their germination.
Mana's maturation into Eve
will serve as the catalyst.
And it will start.
The fourth Apocalypse.
The natural selection and
subsequent evolution
of all life. To put
it in other words,
Apocalypse is god's discerning
hand. Divine providence.
Kurosu, I've been
informed that your wife
is already deeply symptomatic.
But you must spare the life
of her unborn child.
He is our future.
It seems that Eve is intent
to declare him as her Adam.
His warnings were heeded
and Shu Ouma was born.
But at the cost of
his own mother's life.
Eve had chosen her
Adam. In other words,
Kurosu's children were set to be
the progenitors of our future.
His malformed genes would shape
the next generation of Earth.
When I realized that,
something inside me broke.
Kurosu has refused
to work with me.
I'd like to know
where you stand, Shuichiro.
Start talking.
Another illegal immigrant?
Or perhaps the victim of
human trafficking. He was
the only one found alive.
You're awake. Well, boy,
from this point forward,
you can think of me
as your father.
Keido took custody as he
said he would, but only
to treat me as a lab rat.
He took me to a facility.
A place filled with boys
suffering his attempts to find
a mate for Mana.
A hellish nursery of sorts.
Experiment after experiment.
We were pumped
full of Apocalypse.
Each dose stronger than the
last. Until finally, I ran.
Triton.
You must've come from the ocean.
So we'll call you Triton.
It's a pretty cool name, right?
Ironic, isn't it? My desperate
attempt to escape the fate
that Keido had devised for me
landed me in the epicenter
of his grand design.
You understand that.
Don't you, Shu?
Wow. I haven't
seen you in a while.
Uhhh, I'm so sorry,
I didn't hear you come in.
You're one of my
new grad students?
It's nice to meet you.
Well, we've kinda met
before. I used to bring you
blankets whenever I found
you passed out in your lab.
Huh?
I'm Shuichiro Keido's little
sister. Name's Haruka.
Oh! How rude of me!
I had skipped my senior year and
only recently started college.
Just a typical smart ass
with no real life experience.
To put it lightly, I was
curious about Kurosu.
He had left his children in
Oshima to focus on his research.
Sometimes he'd forget to eat or
sleep when he was hard at work.
In my eyes, he was a
martyr taking on the virus
all by himself.
I've decided. I'm
gonna marry Kurosu.
Kurosu? You are?
He needs me. He's such
a lonely person.
You know that, right?
You're his rival, after all.
I'm sure you must have noticed.
Do whatever you want.
Well thanks for
the encouragement.
How's his research coming along?
Any progress on the virus?
A hell of a lot more than you've
made, I can promise you that.
He told me himself.
And later that year, I did
just what I said I would.
I married Kurosu and brought
his children to live with us,
including the boy he'd adopted.
We were going to spend
our first Christmas
together as a family.
But Fate had other
plans. December 24th.
Two Thousand Twenty-Nine.
Papa sure is late.
And where is Shu?
He and Triton are on
their way. He sent me
a text message earlier.
Why don't you go get Papa?
I don't mind staying here to
wait for Shu. Papa probably got
caught up in his research
and lost track of time.
Well. Are you
sure you'll be okay?
Uh huh.
The Apocalypse Virus
attacks the heart first,
crystalizing it and producing
a rampant cellular meiosis.
But my research has lead me to a
genetic code that may be able
to suppress and
contain the process.
I've named this miracle code
the Void Genome.
The Void Genome focuses the
random and capricious nature
of the seeds' selection
process by exteriorizing and
giving corporeal
form to the heart.
So the Apocalypse
is not divine providence.
We can prevent it
with human intelligence.
That's a dirty hobby
you've got there, Shuichiro.
Peeking into other
people's private journals.
Kurosu. So you've
really done it.
You've unraveled the virus.
Without anyone's help,
you've broken the
mysteries of evolution.
I'm a little surprised,
to be honest.
You realize Daath is out of
patience with you, right?
You need to present
this research to them.
Let me negotiate
with them for you.
We can work together
on this, Kurosu.
No. That's really
not necessary.
Other facilities may prefer to
work as a team, but I'm beyond
that at this point. Too
many cooks in the kitchen.
It would only
dilute my thinking.
You think I'm a fool!
Where'd that come from?
I'm just another ignorant
cook who will ruin
your precious recipe,
is that what you're saying?!
No, I didn't mean that!
I'm thinking about you.
I don't wanna put my friend
in the same jeopardy I'm in.
Don't give me that bullshit! You
were jealous of my success.
Everything you've done is to try
to make me look foolish. Yes!
You forged all of
your results, didn't you?!
You sound like a mad man.
Tell me, what reason could I
possibly have to be
jealous of you?
You've got me there.
And I admit it, Kurosu.
You're every bit the
genius people claim.
But there is one thing
that you're wrong about.
I'm not your friend. You've
always been my enemy.
Kurosu!
Noooooooooo!
Looks like
my guess was correct.
Your Void can temporarily
contain the Voids of others.
Not only that, it's capable
of isolating and absorbing
the cancer cells. It actually
consumes the entire strain
of the Apocalypse Virus.
That's great. That must mean
Souta's fully cured then.
Please listen to me, Shu!
You can't use
that power anymore!
I know how determined you are
to get Inori back from Gai,
but there's a good chance
that it might be too late.
You didn't know this, but
they've already succeeded
in transplanting Mana's
consciousness into Inori.
In fact. All they need
to complete the process
is to find the genetic
fragments that were scattered
on Lost Christmas. They
have to collect the shards
of her that were absorbed by
other people's Voids that day.
You weren't aware of it,
but that's what they had
tricked you into doing
these last few months
She's whole now. She's retained
every bit of her lost power.
All of it. That's why Gai
is setting deadlines.
I understand what you're saying,
but that's all the more reason
I should go. Wouldn't you say?
Shu.
The choppers are fueled up
and ready to take off.
You are coming
with us. Right, Shu?
Connect those cables!
Yeah, the APUs,
they're hooked up!
Cargo comin' through!
It's almost time for them to
get going. Hey. Are you sure
you wanna leave things like
this with him, Souta?
Hey, Shu.
Now that everyone's gathered
together, I've made up my mind.
I'm giving you your Voids back.
You're doing what?
Hold on, Shu. That will
deplete your Void
and leave you
powerless, won't it?
I have to give them back.
I can't risk my life like this
while in possession of them.
If I die, they will too.
Don't worry. I can still
hold onto the symptoms
of the virus. You too,
Ayase. Come here.
But.
Hey! Screw that, man!
Yesterday you made a big deal
about how much you needed
them, and now you wanna
give 'em back? How the hell
do you expect to fight
without 'em?!
I've got enough strength in
my arm to aim a gun, don't I?
That's insane! You don't
honestly believe you can
defeat Gai that way. Think!
The only priority I have
right now is saving Inori
and stopping the virus.
Defeating Gai is
an afterthought. Is there
anything wrong with that?
I want you to keep
my Void when you go.
If you were to fail
for some reason,
all of our lives
would be forfeit anyway.
Yep. That about sums it up.
I have to say,
I agree with Ayase, Souta?
What do you think?
It's fine. I never
asked for it back.
Not that I understand it.
But I guess it's fine.
What the hell, just keep it!
I am; I'm not trying
to give it back.
I just wanna shake
hands with you, Souta.
We have to shake
hands to make up.
You're the one who told me
that. We can't say goodbye
and just leave things like
this. I refuse to do that.
Your hand. I'm sorry, Shu.
It's not your fault, Souta.
I was. I was scared of you.
I hated feeling like that.
It sucked!
I was scared of me too.
Just promise me, Shu, that
you'll always be my friend.
No matter what.
Of course. Of course we're
friends. And for the rest
of our lives. Nothing
will change that.
Kurosu could do
anything by himself.
He thrived in isolation.
But it's not that he wanted
to be alone. In truth,
he was a very lonely man
because of it. He knew the
importance of being with people.
And that's why he named you
"Shu". It means "together".