We're entering Tokyo
airspace. Three minutes until
our drop point.
Open the hatch.
We're bound to be tracked,
so this is a one-time deal.
You won't get any
second chances. Got it?
That's all that's left of Tokyo?
So your granddaughter's at
the top of the rescue list?
I know how it sounds, but the
leader of the Ming Hua Group,
the largest conglomerate in
Shanghai, is in love with her.
We have a deal. He'll help
negotiate a peace treaty
in exchange for
her hand in marriage.
Are you sure? You'd basically
be selling your granddaughter.
I never thought I'd have
to make such a compromise.
Nothing could've truly
prepared us for these times.
Prepared us for the many tolls
the decline of a nation takes.
I'll make sure the escape route
is laid out and secure.
We'll rendezvous 36 hours
from now as ordered.
Good luck down there.
Thanks.
Am I really seeing this?
Tokyo got this bad in
a matter of weeks?
It's insane.
Just back off! We found
this before you guys
got here!
Get away from us!
They've sunk to
hoarding vaccines?
What the hell, that's a Void.
We're always on the
lookout for new recruits
to join our ranks. Swear your
allegiance to President Ouma.
It's a quick and easy
way to not get killed.
Wait, President Ouma?
So they're his guards?
Not now!
Ya think we should
ice her, Nanba?
She sure wanted to kill us.
And I bet her Void is trash.
Agreed.
Drop the tough guy act,
you pampered brats.
Ya gonna kill a girl who
doesn't know what a safety is?
Pick another way to show off.
An enemy.
Wait, Miyabi.
Check out that emblem. You think
he's a part of Funeral Parlor?
Could be. Who's asking?
Hold on. You're seriously
tellin' me Shu's runnin' things
round here?
That's freakin' absurd.
How's this place standing?
Watch it.
Oh calm down. Sorry about
her. She worships the ground
the president walks on.
Now that's just weird.
Reporting. Official
Secret Service members.
Ritsu Takarada
and Miyabi Herikawa.
What's the resonance gauge say?
It's higher than
you'd expect. Not bad.
You never know. We've
got one that might be
worth checking out.
Wanna take a look, Shu?
Shu.
I can't draw it out like that.
I need her to look at me.
Wait. Please!
Congratulations. Your
Void puts you in Rank A.
Use your power to work hard for
this school and you'll be fine.
Me? Seriously? I'm Rank A?
Hey. Ouma.
Argo. Can't say I was
expecting to see you today.
I'm glad you're alright, though.
It's quite the setup
you've got goin' here.
Only out of necessity.
We're pretty sure
the government's in possession
of a new genomic weapon.
What makes you think that?
Well, because.
We saw one of our own students
fall victim to it not long ago.
Yeah, well good luck with that.
Listen, I'm here looking
for someone; know where
I can find the old president,
Arisa Kuhouin?
Sounds like you have
some kind of business with her.
Her grandfather's tasked me with
the mission to bring her back
to the other side. So then. Ya
think ya could point me to her?
I'm sorry. Shu's schedule is
pretty full. You don't mind
if we walk and talk, do you?
Sure, whatever.
What the hell are they doing?
Look. It's an army transport
ship that got left behind
during the confusion. It's chock
full of ammunition and vaccine.
So now you're down there
picking the bones dry, huh?
Crafty little buzzards.
What the?! Those guys-
--They're all symptomatic!
--Your suit's not gonna hold.
Figure something out.
It's okay. They get first
priority status for the vaccine
as long as they get
their work done, see?
Are you joking?
Why?
Captain.
Yes, sir.
The records show you're
not hitting your quotas
and I'd like to know
if you have a reason why.
The symptomatic students
are only capable
of so much labor, sir-
Something's wrong!
Pump 12 is jammed!
Who's down there?
It's Souta Tamadate from 2-A!
Do we have a spare?
No, sir. We're already
using all of them.
No choice then.
We've still got that oxygen tank
we salvaged somewhere, right?
We need it.
Hold on.
His diving suit
should be equipped with
a small emergency tank.
If he uses that,
all he has to do is cut
the hose and escape.
There's a switch on
the helmet. He has to
figure it out for himself. Stand
down. This is his problem.
Are you for real?!
You're gonna let him die?!
That's evil!
Just help him!
We simply don't have
the resources to be
wasting on a Rank F.
You what? Why don't you say
that again, you bastard!
Keep your distance.
Try using your brain.
We'll be screwed
if Shu becomes symptomatic.
Alright. I've had enough
of your shit, Shu.
Argo! I've given
them my orders!
Your orders are idiotic,
jackass. Don't go thinking
you're my president.
Listen.
I can't allow you to be
insubordinate. Not right now.
We're in the middle
of planning our escape.
To succeed, I need
every last person to
fall in line and work together.
Dissent is unacceptable.
You want everyone
to stand together.
Yet look how you're
treating these guys.
We're in a crisis, here.
As much as I'd like to, we can't
treat everyone equally
if they don't have the power
to help our cause.
And I can't give you Arisa,
either. Her Void is far too
useful to us. Besides which,
our people escape together
or no one does.
I need to hear you give me
your allegiance. Or else.
I'm gonna take option B.
With this power trip you're on,
I'd rather die
than follow you.
Restrain the traitor.
Yes, sir.
Inori. Don't tell me you've
just fallen in line like
the rest of the mindless sheep.
Not at all. I've chosen
to follow Shu.
I want a guard watching Arisa,
just to be safe.
Yes, sir.
Damn, he pisses me off!
Who the hell does that brat
think he is now?!
One speck of power and
look what he's become!
He's been different since
a friend of his died.
That you, Tsugumi?
Yeah. Good to hear
your voice, Argo.
I heard some rumors that you
were hiding out at the school.
Is Ayase with you?
No. She kinda flipped out
when she heard that Shu
had put you in a cell.
Why are you doing this?!
I'm only following the protocol
outlined for dissidents.
I can't make an exception
just because he's a friend.
Think of how that would look.
I get that you haven't
gotten over Hare's death,
but you've changed so much.
You get it?
I guess people's hearts
are just an open book to you,
aren't they?
I'm glad there's no one else
around. If any other person
had seen that, I would've had
no choice but to punish you,
no matter how high
your rank might be.
That guy is seriously messed
up. The thing I don't get is
why everyone's going
along with all of this.
To be perfectly frank,
they're terrified.
There's the constant stress
of the red line closing in.
The fear of the
Apocalypse virus.
Rampant violence and looting
throughout the streets.
Measured against that, the
Void system is all too easy
to accept. It took Shu less than
a second to gather his kingdom
when he decided
to become their ruler.
A kingdom by the Voids
and for the Voids.
That's what this school
has been reduced to now.
Damn it.
Well, Mana. Take a look at this.
Shu's picking up your pieces
with all his might. He's
finally starting to realize
his potential. But he's still
not quite there. Not yet.
We need to put more
pressure on him.
So our plans are on track.
There's clearly
a direct correlation,
the further the line advances,
the more followers
little King Ouma
seems to accrue.
You're stockpiling Voids,
aren't you?
You surprised me with the
Ghost Unit, but now this?
You prefer not to spare the rod
with your motherly love.
Eh, Dr. Ouma?
I'm only doing what's
necessary of me.
After all, these were
Kurosu's wishes.
Are you ever gonna leave?
I'm afraid that's a question
for the Void prince.
I hear that a Funeral Parlor
member is being detained.
I believe I have every right
to speak with him directly.
The prince is a little uptight
about your wellbeing right now.
He doesn't want you to get hurt
meddling where you shouldn't.
I could protect you
for a cost, of course.
Never underestimate a Kuhoin.
Hey. Yahiro.
Is it true that Hare was killed
by some kind of new weapon?
Yeah, it's true. Why are
you asking me that?
There's a rumor.
People have been saying that
she died because her Void-
Be careful with what you say.
You report to me if you hear
anyone spreading those lies.
Got it?
What should I do, Hare?
It's just everyone's changing.
I'm sure I must look like
some kind of selfish tyrant
to everyone else.
Does that hurt?
It's not like I'm doing this
to get people to love me,
I'm just doing what
it takes to get everyone
safely out of Tokyo.
And I can't stop until that's
done. Or else Hare will have-
She'll have died for nothing
if I don't succeed.
You're all I need, Inori.
As long as I have you.
Really? What about me?
Shu?
I'm sorry to interrupt, sir.
But the Funeral Parlor
member has somehow escaped!
Can I assume
she's in her dorm?
Well, she normally is. Jeez,
couldn't you have told me
you were gonna make a break?
If you can fool your allies,
you can fool your enemies.
What's the freaking point
in fooling us?!
Things are all messed up
thanks to you.
Please forgive me, Aya!
You're just gonna get captured
by the Secret Service
if you rush out and join in.
Attention all
Secret Service members.
Our prisoner is on the loose.
Find him and capture him.
You two search the grounds
around building two.
Yes, sir!
Inori, you hunt down Arisa.
I'm sure she's Argo's
first destination.
You? I didn't know you
joined the Secret Service.
I saw him run toward the gym.
Come with me.
Yes, sir!
That's as far as you're getting.
You're cornered, Argo, face
it! Now surrender peacefully.
Well, I'm surprised you have
the guts to show yourself,
but of course you brought
Voids for insurance.
You seem to think that all it
takes to be like Gai is to wear
a cloak, but you're not even
coming close, you poser!
And you never will!
You and me. And you
better give it your all,
'cuz if you lose, you drop
your little king act!
You've gotta do better
than that, Void Prince!
Argo!
What happened? What turned
you into such a little shit?
I preferred the lost
weakling you were.
At least you were
genuine back then.
Then why the hell don't
you try taking my place?
You know so damn much,
then let's hear you come up
with some other way
I can keep everyone safe!
Back away from Shu!
You, huh?
And I don't have
the soft spot Shu does.
Get up and surrender.
And I mean right now!
Am I, what is this?
Please, stop. I can't, no.
I don't want to die.
This is Yahiro. Red alert
for Secret Service.
Cordon off the gym. Arrest
anyone in a 30-meter radius.
It doesn't matter who
they are, detain them.
I want the gym
completely sealed off,
effective immediately.
Yahiro.
That girl was perfectly fine,
now somehow she's dead,
just because her Void broke?
We don't know that for sure.
It's obvious! You lied
to me about Hare.
You said it was a genomic
weapon. So what happens now?
The thing we're protecting
everyone with could be
the very thing that
might kill them?
It's too late to go back now.
This can't be undone.
I knew you'd hesitate to use
your power if you ever
found out about this,
but if we let the Void
system collapse on us now,
every single one of
us will end up dead.
We have no choice
but to keep going.
We'll sit on the truth until we
begin the operation. Agreed?
What the hell are you saying?!
You need to stop using
Voids right now! You can't
go into a war like this. Do
you realize how many students
will die?!
He doesn't know
what he's talking about!
Open your eyes, Shu!
I know, you're right.
What?
Shu.
If I break this,
Argo will die.
I've gotta warn
everyone right away.
I can't believe
Voids are- It's just-
Found you.
Inori.
You didn't hold up
your end of the bargain.
I'm assuming that
we can both amicably
put this deal behind us?
I suppose we have no choice.
As an old friend, I have to
give you a word of warning.
You need to get out of Japan
as soon as you possibly can.
There appears to be trouble
brewing on the Pacific.
It's finally time.
This is too far.
I doubt Shu will ever
forgive me for this.