[NINYA sighs]
[AINS]
That was foolish.
Hey... About what
I said last night.
I'm really sorry.
[AINS] Mentally and physically,
I've become an undead,
but I still let my
emotions control me.
Uh... This area's got quite
the scenery, doesn't it?
It's so peaceful. Why don't
we just relax and enjoy?
It's important to be on guard.
He's right. Carelessness
gets you killed.
A dragon could ambush
and roast the lot of us
before we'd have time to react.
Give me a break.
You can't seriously
believe that would happen.
There are plenty of local
legends to support it.
Apparently, there's a
dragon near E-Rantel
that's able to control
nature at will.
And north...
I've heard that there are quite
a few living frost dragons
that make their nests
on the other side
of the Azerlisia mountains.
There could be
hundreds up there.
[AINS clears throat]
Um. Ninya.
You wouldn't happen to know
the name of the dragon
with the power over nature?
Huh? Sorry. No idea.
I'll ask when
we're back in town.
[AINS] Please do. That would
be of great help to me.
'Kay! Consider it done.
I won't let you down.
We should be in Carne
Village within the hour.
[MOMONGA] Dragons were
considered the strongest
species in Yggdrasil.
If they do exist in this world,
I should be cautious of them.
[gasps] That's strange.
What's the matter?
[NPHIREA]
That huge fence.
I'm sure it wasn't
here the last time.
Hey, get the boss.
We might have trouble.
[GOBLIN 7B grunts]
[GOBLINS grunting]
I thought I smelled
something foul.
That's close enough, blondie!
[GOBLIN 7D]
Put down your weapons! Now!
[AINS]
Wait a minute.
[GOBLIN 7A]
Everyone calm down.
We'd rather not have to cross
swords if we can avoid it.
Especially with the giant
in the plate armor.
I know a bad vibe
when I feel one,
and he's givin' me a serious
case of the willies.
Who the hell are these guys?
[ENRI]
Mr. Goblin, what's going on?
Boss! You made it!
Enri!
Huh? Nphirea!
Hey. Is she...?
Definitely.
[MOMONGA] I thought I
recognized these goblins.
She must have used one of
the horns I gave her.
But...
I have a friend who
frequents our village.
He's a pharmacist who
also practices magic.
[MOMONGA] To think she
was talking about him.
[NPHIREA]
Sorry. I don't know what to say.
[ENRI]
Yeah.
[NPHIREA] Losing both of
her parents like that.
The world can be a cruel place.
I can only imagine the
pain she's gone through.
[NPHIREA] But now, I'm here.
I can protect her!
It's fine. I still
have my little sister.
Looking after her
has kept me going.
Oh-- Of course,
that's wonderful.
By the way...
Huh?
[NPHIREA]
I... was wondering...
What is it, Nphirea?
Well. It's just...
I thought... you...
...might be interested in...
--...ma... mar... marri...
--[NPHIREA] We're both of
--marrying age now.
With my earnings, I could take
care of you and your sister!
Is something wrong?
No, nothing at all!
Just let me know
if you need anything!
I'd be happy to
help however I can!
How sweet. Thank you, Nphirea.
I'm so lucky to have an amazing
friend like you in my life.
Huh? Right.
A good friend, that's what
I am, and nothing more. Yeah.
Anyway, what's the
deal with the goblins?
They appeared out of thin air.
Well, after I used the
magical item our savior,
Lord Gown, gave to me.
They call me their boss,
and help out around the village
when I ask them.
[NPHIREA]
I see.
So, what kind of person
is this "Gown" fellow?
Really?
I figured if anyone
would know about him,
it would be you,
Nphirea. He's amazing.
Amazing? In what way?
Oh.
Sorry, I was remembering
how he saved our village.
Uh-- I see. That makes sense.
I'm sure it was impressive.
It's a shot in the dark, but
if you give me some details,
I might be able to think
of who he could be.
His magic skills
were incredible.
He made lightning with
just a wave of his hands,
and crushed those marauders
like they were nothing.
Lightning?
In that case, he was probably
using third tier spells.
Is that good or bad?
Actually, it's great.
Reaching third tier magic
is the highest level
a normal person can achieve.
Oh, wow!
I knew he was awesome,
but I had no idea!
From what you've told me,
I wouldn't be surprised if he's
actually a hero class caster.
He might even have the ability
to cast fifth tier spells.
I still haven't
told you everything.
He gave me a blood red potion
that healed my wounds instantly!
[gasps]
[ENRI]
Also,
he had a female warrior with him
that was covered in black armor.
I think, I heard him
call her Albedo?
[NPHIREA]
That name... No way!
Then... Ains Ooal Gown is Momon?
[ENRI]
Huh?
[NPHIREA]
But that would mean
he's an adamantite level warrior
who can also cast high
level magic with ease.
If that's really
the case, then...
...it would make him
a hero among heroes!
He even saved Enri from
certain death and I've been
sneaking around trying
to steal his secrets.
What's the matter?
You look pale.
Huh?
Nphi?
[AINS]
They're really quite good.
If you say so, lord.
[AINS] Hm? All right, I wouldn't
call any of them a natural.
But think about it.
Until ten days ago,
none of them had even
touched a bow before.
They've been through a lot.
They had to watch as
their friends, children,
and parents were murdered.
But instead of giving in to
misery, they're working hard
to make sure that atrocity
never happens again.
If nothing else, it's inspiring.
[NARBERAL]
I hadn't thought of that.
Please, forgive me, lord.
[NPHIREA]
Mr. Momon!
[NPHIREA panting]
[AINS] Do you have
some business with me?
I have a question.
Mr. Momon. Are you
actually Ains Ooal Gown?
[AINS]
Uh--
[NARBERAL grunts]
You saved this village.
Thank you. It really
means a lot to me.
[AINS]
No. You're mistaken. I'm not--
It's okay.
I get that you're
hiding your identity.
And I have no intention
of ruining that.
I just wanted to thank you. See,
if you hadn't done what you did,
Enri might not be alive today.
If she wasn't here, I'd
have nothing to live for.
You saved us both.
[AINS sighs]
Is that all, Nphirea?
Yes, of course. Actually...
There's something I've
been hiding since we met.
[AINS] Nabe, can you leave
us alone for a moment?
Understood, lord.
[NPHIREA]
Here goes.
The red potion, the one
you gave to that adventurer
back in E-Rantel.
it's so rare that none
of our modern methods
could ever hope to duplicate it.
I thought...
If I could learn the secret,
I could produce it on my own.
That's the reason I specifically
asked for your help. It was
dishonest, and I'm sorry.
[AINS]
I see.
[gasps]
[MOMONGA]
I should've known giving her
that potion was a mistake.
Even a n00b wouldn't have
screwed up that badly.
I hope you forgive me.
[AINS] What exactly do I
need to forgive you for?
[NPHIREA]
Hm?
[AINS] You requested
my assistance because
you wanted to get
in contact with me.
I fail to see how
that is a problem.
[AINS]
That said.
I would like to know what you
planned to do with the potion
once you had learned
to craft it.
To be perfectly honest,
I hadn't really
thought that far ahead.
The knowledge was tantalizing
enough on its own.
[AINS] There's nothing wrong
with wanting to know.
As long as you aren't using
your knowledge for evil,
I have no issue.
Enri's right about you.
You're great. I can see
why she admires you.
[AINS]
Be honest with me.
Are you the only one who knows
that I'm Ains Ooal Gown?
Yes, I haven't told anyone.
[AINS] That's good. I'd
like it to stay that way.
Right now, I'm an adventurer
named Momon, nothing more.
I'd appreciate it if
you didn't forget that.
Yes, sir.
I thought that's
how you'd want it.
It's no problem. Thanks again.
On behalf of the entire village,
and especially the woman I love.
[pants]
Sorry, lord. This is
entirely my fault.
[AINS]
You're right.
Saying Albedo's name
has compromised us.
I'll atone with my life.
[AINS]
It's fine!
Everyone makes
mistakes, Narberal.
You just need to make
a concerted effort
not to make the
same mistake again.
You are forgiven.
Now learn from this.
And put down your sword.
[NPHIREA] We'll enter
the forest through here.
I'll be counting on you
if anything attacks.
As long as we have
Mr. Momon with us,
I don't think anything in
there will have the guts.
Oh, yeah. One thing.
If we happen upon the Wise King,
I'd like for you to scare him
off instead of killing him.
Huh?
[AINS]
Care to explain?
[NPHIREA]
This entire area is within
the Wise King's territory.
He's the reason monsters
have never attempted
to attack Carne Village before.
If you kill him,
it could mean disaster.
I'm pretty sure that's
impossible, even for him.
[AINS]
I'll certainly try.
Huh?!
You do realize this is
a legendary creature
we're talking about, right?
You must be confident
in your strength
to have that attitude.
[AINS] Actually I have a
suggestion, if you don't mind.
[NPHIREA]
Please, feel free.
[AINS] Nabe can use magic
similar to Alarm.
I'd like the two of us
to scout ahead for a bit.
I'm fine with that.
But, try to get back to the
group as quick as you can.
[AINS]
Of course.
[AINS] That's far enough.
Now, why don't we talk about
how to spread my great name?
[AURA]
Sounds good!
Careful, Narberal.
That looks dangerous.
Oh, Lady Aura! I'm
sorry, you startled me.
My bad.
How long were you here?
[AURA]
Since you and Lord Ains
entered the forest
by yourselves.
I didn't sense your
presence at all.
[AURA] So, let me guess:
I need to find this Wise King
of the Forest and
send him your way.
A creature like that
could be of use, right?
[AINS]
Correct. Up to it?
Consider it done!
I think I might know where
it's making its nest.
[AINS] Excellent. I'm
counting on you, Aura.
See ya!
What are you planning
to do, my lord?
[AINS] I will fight the
Wise King, of course.
Wasn't the battle with the ogres
a sufficient show
of your strength?
[AINS]
Hardly.
Killing an ogre with one
swing is nothing compared
to besting a legendary
magical creature.
If I want rumors of
the adventurer, Momon
to spread quickly in E-Rantel,
I need to accomplish something
the people can't ignore.
[NARBERAL]
I see.
[yelps]
Fen! Quadracile! Hi!
What's wrong? Were you
two worried about me?
That tickles! Cut it out!
I have an important
mission from Lord Ains.
I can't play now! Whoa!
You wanna help, huh?
All right, I guess
I'll let you tag along.
[roars]
[FOREST KING snores]
[AURA] I really wanted to take
a shot at this thing myself,
but hey, orders are orders.
[inhales]
[FOREST KING roars]
[AURA]
We're done here!
[gasps]
I don't like this.
Guys. Something big is
heading straight for us.
[NPHIREA] Is it the
Wise King of the Forest?
[AINS]
Don't worry. Leave it to us.
Sure. Thanks.
We're counting on you.
[NPHIREA]
Mr. Momon.
[AINS]
What is it?
Try not to push
yourself too hard, 'kay?
[AINS]
Right. Now, go! Quickly!
Why did I say that?
Without them here to witness
the fight, no one will know
I actually took on the
Wise King of the Forest.
[AINS] Maybe I should cut off
one of its legs as proof.
[AINS]
Let's greet our guest properly.
[AINS grunts]
[FOREST KING]
Few can survive my first attack.
Admirable, it is.
[AINS]
The hell?
[FOREST KING]
Abide interlopers, I do not.
Many are the foolish who
have perished by my claws.
If you wish not to join
them, leave this place
and respectfully
withdraw, I shall.
What say you?
[AINS]
Forget it.
Why don't you stop
hiding and face me?
Are you shy?
Or are you afraid that
you won't survive?
[FOREST KING]
Insolent whelp! Very well.
Feast your eyes upon my form,
and tremble with awe!
[AINS]
I don't believe it.
[FOREST KING cackles] Your fear
and dismay are palpable, knave.
Have any last words, do you?
[AINS]
Actually, I have a question.
I believe I've met
your kind before.
Are you a Djungarian Hamster?
I am!
Tell me stranger, how is it
that you came to know
of my species?
[AINS] Well. Uh. Hm.
How should I put this?
One of my old allies
used to have a pet
that looked just like you.
'Tis true?
Then, please, tell me
where I might find
this person and my people.
My duty as a living creature
to make offspring and
continue my species, it is.
[AINS] I'm afraid your
size might hinder that.
[sighs] Truly
unfortunate, that is.
Understand, I do.
[AINS]
Sorry.
[groans] Okay, it is.
As for you, cease your
banter and come at me now.
Fight for our lives
as warriors, we shall!
[AINS groans]
"Wise King" my boney ass.
"Fluffy King's" more like it.
This is embarrassing.
[FOREST KING]
Trespassing in my territory
is a death sentence, it is.
Make a good meal,
the two of you shall.
[AINS]
What a letdown.
This was a complete
waste of time.
What are you
standing there for?
Surrendering, are you?
Disappointing, that would
be, as I expected more
of someone with your strength.
Come!
Fight to the death with me,
the way nature intended.
Survival of the fittest, it is!
[AINS]
No. I'm not doing this.
"Skill, Aura of Despair"!
[AINS]
Level one!
[yelps]
Bested me, you have.
Surrender, I do! Have mercy!
[AINS groans]
He's just a helpless animal.
[AURA]
Are you gonna kill him?
[AINS]
Hm?
If you are, I'd like
to use his skin
to make some leather.
His fur might make
a good rug, too.
Don't. Please, no!
No way...
[ALL]
The Wise King of the Forest?
[AINS]
Be at ease, friends.
You are perfectly safe.
He is under my command now.
He will not attack.
You have my word on that.
My master speaks
the truth, he does!
As long as he wishes it,
I shall not cause trouble
for you, or any human.
Devoted to his will, I am.
Whatever path he chooses,
follow, I shall.
Amazing! What an
awe-inspiring creature!
[MOMONGA]
Huh?
I can feel great
strength and wisdom
radiating from him.
[MOMONGA]
Great strength? Wisdom?
I guess your amazing
feats know no bounds.
It's no wonder someone like
Nabe stays by your side.
No kidding. You're
incredible, Mr. Momon.
We would have been massacred
if we took him on.
[AINS]
What do you make of this?
Putting his strength
aside, his eyes
do have a gleam of
power behind them.
[AINS]
No way!
[NPHIREA]
Mr. Momon?
I realize that this is
none of my business.
But, are you taking him
away from this place?
If you do that,
I'm afraid monsters will
attack Carne Village.
[AINS]
Well?
There is a chance of
that happening, master.
No way. Fine.
In that case,
Mr. Momon, I humbly ask
to become part of your team.
[AINS]
Huh?
I want to be able to protect
Enri and Carne Village.
If I had even a sliver
of your awesome strength.
I know for sure that I
could do that with ease!
My knowledge of pharmacy
will be completely
at your disposal. I'll
even carry your things!
Please! Make me your squire!
[ADVENTURERS gasp]
[AINS] In other words, you want
me to accept you as part
of my team and teach you
how to become stronger
as a magic caster?
Yes!
[AINS laughs]
[AINS]
Forgive me.
I'm not laughing at
your determination.
I understand how you feel,
and I'll remember it.
However, I'm afraid I have no
use for a squire at this time.
Oh. I understand.
[AINS]
But, please, do not fret.
I have every intention
of lending my strength
to this village
whenever they need it.
[gasps]
[AINS] Can I count on your
help when the time comes?
Yes! It would be my honor!
[ADVENTURERS chuckle]
[PETER]
Hey, Momon.
We're going to escort
Nphirea the rest of the way
to his shop and help him
unload all this stuff.
Should we wait for you?
[AINS]
Go on ahead.
Once I register this magical
creature with the guild,
I'll catch up with you.
I've never had a haul
this plentiful before.
I'll be sure to add
extra to your payment.
Your haul was possible because
of my master's strength.
Don't forget that.
[NPHIREA]
See you soon!
Though we'll be apart
for only moments,
I'm sure it will feel
like an eternity.
Be strong for me, Nabe, my love!
Don't worry. That
won't be a problem.
--Come on, get moving.
--[LUKRUT groans]
See ya later.
[MOMONGA]
My pride is ruined.
I look like an old man
on a merry-go-round,
not a monster-slaying hero.
This is so embarrassing. Dammit.
Oh, right. I should probably
give this guy a name.
Donut? No! Hamtaro!
Come on in!
There should be plenty of
room for everything here.
Sounds good to me.
I wonder why it's so quiet.
[gasps]
Hi. Welcome home, kiddo.
[cackles]
[AINS]
After taming the legendary
Wise King of the Forest,
I return to E-Rantel.
The people shower me
with awe and praise.
The Swords of Darkness
will undoubtedly spread
the tale of our heroics to
other members of the guild.
It won't be long until the
names "Momon" and "Nabe"
spread across the land.
However, I soon discover that
the shadows of this new world
hide far more sinister forces.
Chapter eight: "Twin Swords
of Slashing Death."