Um. Mr. Peter?
Yes?
Why don't we take a break,
around that area?
[PETER]
Good idea.
Mr. Momon.
[AINS]
I understand.
[PETER]
Enjoy this.
Things will get a little
dangerous from here on out.
[AINS] Don't worry about
us. We'll be careful.
[MOMONGA] I'll have to be,
considering I can't use
most of my magic in this armor.
Playing the tank role was
never really my speed.
[MOMONGA] If things start
to get out of hand,
Narberal will use
fifth tier magic.
I'm not sure what
we'll be facing,
but hopefully, that
will be enough.
If not, I may have
to get serious.
Try not to look
so worried, Nabe.
Everthing'll be fine
as long as I'm here.
I'm the best set of eyes
and ears this side
of the Re-Estize Kingdom
Don't be shy. You can praise me.
Can I squash him yet?
[AINS]
Nabe.
Mosquitos should be
handled without mercy.
Please, sir.
Harsh!
But it's okay, gorgeous,
I so can tell you want me.
[PETER, NINYA, DYNE
laugh nervously]
You know, I just
realized something.
We've crossed into the Wise King
of the Forest's territory.
[AINS]
Who is this "Wise King"?
It's a very old and
powerful magical creature.
At least, that's
what the legends say.
Not only can it cast magic,
but it's physically strong.
And if its four razor claws
don't finish you off,
its snake tail will.
[AINS] Interesting. I think
I'd like to meet it.
[DEMIURGE breathes deeply]
[door clicks]
[ALBEDO sighing, moaning]
[DEMIURGE]
Albedo.
[ALBEDO gasps]
You have your
own accommodations,
why are you in Lord Ains' room?
I was rubbing my scent
into everything I could.
I wanted it to be the
first thing he smelled
when he finally returns.
[DEMIURGE] Considering he
doesn't require sleep,
I doubt that will happen.
Fine, just, don't overdo it.
I'm sure I don't
know what you mean,
but we'll try. Right? Lord Ains?
Uh-- Ugh.
Is that... a life-sized
body pillow?
Yeah. Isn't it great?
--[DEMIURGE sighs]
--[ALBEDO] I made it myself.
Now I'm working on
the socks and clothes
for our first child.
I need to be prepared.
It won't be much
longer. I can feel it.
I've made enough for
the first five years.
Boy or girl,
they'll have everything
they could ask for.
Wait a minute, what if the
child doesn't have a gender?
If the elf twins
are any indication,
the Supreme Beings have no issue
with their
servants crossdressing.
Yes! You're right.
Thank you, Demiurge.
That's exactly what
I needed to hear!
[sighs] I'm always
happy to help.
[AINS] Such things are
actually possible?
[NINYA]
Yes.
You can make a lot
with creation magic,
even basics like salt and sugar.
There are also spells like
Alarm that can warn you
when danger is nearby.
[AINS]
I see. May I ask something else?
[MOMONGA] The more I know,
the more questions I have.
It seems their technology level
is that of the Middle Ages,
but the sophistication
of their magic
is on a completely
different level.
[LUKRUT]
I just realized.
You always seem
super relaxed, Nabe.
Is it because you know
that I'm keeping you safe?
It has nothing to do with
you. I'm with Mr. Momon.
[LUKRUT] So, what you're telling
me is that the two of you
are lovers after all?
[gasps] No, I never said that!
Stop putting words in my mouth!
Lady Albedo is the
only one he needs...!
[AINS] Stop, Nabe!
What are you thinking?
Uh...
[AINS clears throat] Mr. Lukrut,
please stop looking into
our personal lives.
Sure. My bad. Though,
from the sound of it,
you're one lucky
man, Mr. Momon.
[PETER] I'm sorry. He can be
really idiotic sometimes.
Please forgive him.
I promise he doesn't
mean any harm by it.
[AINS] It's fine. As long as
he's careful from now on.
We'll have no trouble.
You really need to stop delving
into people's business--
They're on the move.
[ADVENTURERS gasp]
From where?
Just past the tree line.
I don't think we'll be
able to avoid this fight.
It's going to get
rough very quickly.
The best thing you can do
is stay hidden in the cart.
'Kay. My life is in your hands.
Mr. Momon, what's the best
way to split the group up?
[AINS] All of you should
stay close to Nphirea.
I'll show him that our
services are worth every coin.
That sounds good to me.
But we're not just gonna watch.
You'll have all the extended
support we can muster.
[NINYA] If we go completely
defensive, most of them
will escape back
into the forest.
In that case, I say
we do the usual.
Pull the turtle's head out
of its shell and cut it off.
It's a sound strategy,
but still flawed.
Even though Mr. Momon will take
the brunt of their attack.
What about the ones
that get through?
That's easy.
I'll use my Fortress martial art
and hold back the ogres.
The goblins are yours.
I was hoping you'd say that.
[PETER] Ninya, you'll protect
me with defensive magic.
Once I'm clear, focus on crowd
control and attack spells.
Right. No prob.
Lukrut, you'll take care
of any wayward goblins.
And if an Ogre gets
past me, take it out.
Leave it to me.
Does all of that work
for you, Mr. Momon?
[AINS]
Yes.
[LUKRUT]
Here goes.
[GOBLINS laugh]
Fell for it.
[GOBLIN 6C groans]
"Reinforce, Armor"!
Now, "Twine Plant"!
[gasps]
[OGRES roaring]
[PETER, LUKRUT gasp]
[roars]
[AINS grunts]
[OGRE 6C groans]
Holy...
He's stronger than I thought.
Could he be orichalcum,
or maybe adamantite level?
[OGRES growling]
[AINS] What's wrong?
Afraid to attack me?
[growls]
[AINS grunts]
[OGRE 6F groans]
[AINS]
All right, who's next?
Get ready, Ninya!
[grunts]
[GOBLIN 6E]
Die!
[grunts]
[NINYA]
"Magic Arrow"!
[GOBLINS yell]
Here they come.
About time.
[AINS]
They're a skilled party.
They're aware of
each other's strengths
and work well together.
Still, they don't hold
a candle to my old allies.
[OGRE 6H roars]
[AINS grunts]
[GOBLINS]
Hm?
[AINS]
Nabe, your turn.
Right.
"Chain Lightning."
[OGRES groan]
Uh!
[LUKRUT]
Hey!
Don't let them escape!
"Minor Healing Light."
[AINS]
Are the ears valuable?
Not on their own, but
you can exchange them
and other parts for a
reward from the guild.
It can be pretty lucrative.
[AINS] So crystals or
rare trinkets don't just
randomly drop from them?
To be honest, I've
never even heard
of ogres carrying
crystals or trinkets.
[AINS]
I see.
You were pretty
amazing back there.
The two of you are far more
skilled than we expected.
[LUKRUT] I wouldn't mind
having a sword like that.
I've seen incredible
fighters before,
but I wouldn't be surprised
if you're stronger
than the royal head warrior.
Far stronger.
It's moments like
these that remind me
there is always a
bigger fish in the sea.
[AINS]
Don't worry.
In time, your team
will be able to defeat
even greater odds with ease.
[NINYA]
Uh?
[DYNE, PETER, LUKRUT chuckle]
[ADVENTURERS laughing]
[DYNE]
I think you got the worst of it.
[LUKRUT]
Oh, yeah?
Well, you didn't
see the other guy!
[DYNE chuckles]
[NPHIREA laughs]
[MOMONGA]
Crap. What should I do?
If I drink it, it'll
go between my bones.
What's the matter?
I-Is the soup too hot?
[LUKRUT] If that's the
case, I can let it cool
in my mouth first and
feed it to you that way.
Uh...
[AINS] The food's fine,
we're just observing
a religious custom. In our
faith, it's considered impolite
to eat with several
people the same day
we take another's life.
Oh. You believe in some
interesting teachings,
Master Momon. I respect that.
[AINS]
I've been wondering.
Where did the name "Swords
of Darkness" come from?
Oh, that. Tell 'em, Ninya.
Don't make me!
I was young and stupid!
It really is nothing
to be embarrassed about.
That's easy for you to say.
You didn't come up with it.
[PETER]
Anyway.
It's a reference to the old
legends, The Thirteen Heroes.
We named our party
after the swords
of one of the fabled warriors.
[MOMONGA]
Huh? Is that all?
Crap. He must expect
me to know it.
What do I do?
I don't know them. Who are they?
[MOMONGA]
Oh, thank you!
Here I thought everyone
knew the legends.
Among The Thirteen Heroes,
there was one called
the "Black Knight" who
wielded four powerful swords
known only as "The
Swords of Darkness."
See, when we started
our little group,
our ultimate goal was
to find the swords
for ourselves someday.
But, we needed a
symbol in the meantime.
So we carry these
daggers as placeholders.
I don't care that these
aren't the real deal.
They represent the
creation of our team,
and that's more important to
me than any mythical blade.
You know, I think that's
the first time Lukrut
has said something
mildly meaningful.
[LUKRUT]
Hey! Take that back!
[PETER] Who are you and
what'd you do with our friend?
[LUKRUT]
Shut up!
I'm a silver-tongued
fox and you know it.
[MOMONGA]
I used to be like them.
I adventured with my friends,
collected materials,
and helped build Nazarick.
You all seem very close.
Is it common for
adventurers to get along?
Yeah! We all trust
each other with our lives.
[LUKRUT] It helps that our
team is nothing but guys, too.
Throwing a girl into the
mix would be distracting.
I think our greatest
strength comes from
sharing a common goal.
It keeps us focused
on the future.
[AINS]
You're lucky.
Amazing things happen when
everyone shares the same goal.
Were you on a team, Mr. Momon?
[AINS] It wasn't as an
adventurer, but, yes, I was.
Once, when I was weak
and alone, a holy knight
clad in white armor
saved my life.
He led me to the people
I would eventually
call my comrades.
It changed me forever.
[AINS] They were the best
allies I could ever hope for.
More than that.
They were friends, family.
I will never forget the
days I spent with them,
as long as I live.
[MOMONGA] Ains Ooal Gown,
you were the world to me.
Mr. Momon. Don't worry.
I'm sure that you'll find
more allies just like them,
one of these days.
[AINS]
That day will never come.
Excuse me.
[AINS]
Nabe, I'm eating over here.
Yes, I think I'll
join you as well.
I hope you enjoy it.
[NINYA] I think I might
have insulted him.
[DYNE] Mm. Something bad
must have happened.
[PETER] If I had to guess,
they're probably all gone.
He has the aura of someone
who's lost all of his comrades.
That feeling stays with you.
[LUKRUT]
I bet. It's hard to imagine.
You can't take back
what you've said,
so don't fret over it.
All you can do from this point
is atone through your actions.
Work hard to paint over this
mistake, and move forward.
[NINYA]
Mm-hm. I'll do my best.
I don't understand
how I could have
been so thoughtless.
I know what it's like
to lose someone you love.
Right, sis?
That fight was intense
and Mr. Momon was incredible!
Who knew he was so strong?
I know! He was something else.
I've never seen
anything like it before.
[NPHIREA] He stopped that
ogre with one strike.
It must take serious
skill to pull that off.
Yeah, serious skill.
Momon could probably give
even the Royal Head Warrior
a run for his money.
[NPHIREA]
Huh?
But that would make
him adamantite class!
Do you actually believe
he's the same level
as the strongest
adventurers in the world?
That's what I'm saying.
--[NINYA] Mm-hm.
--Yes.
[NPHIREA]
Amazing.
[PETER] I didn't think much
of him when we first met.
Well, I was a bit jealous of
his full set of plate armor.
[LUKRUT] Fess up, you were
ogling Nabe like the rest of us.
Yeah, right.
But now, after seeing
his skills first hand,
I can't help feeling inadequate.
Hey, he's got a
few years on you.
It's entirely possible
that he's been training
for much longer.
Hold on, how do you know
that he's older than Peter?
Back in town, he
took his helmet off
for a moment, and
we got a good look.
[NPHIREA]
What country is he from?
I need to know!
Sorry, we didn't
ask for specifics.
He's the same race
as Nabe, which might be
why they're together,
but she could get easily
get someone much hotter.
I doubt that his
looks are an issue.
Besides, with skills like that.
I'm pretty sure he doesn't
have trouble getting
with women of any race.
Women instinctively flock
to men with strength,
no matter their looks.
It's a fact of life, my friend.
[sighs]
[DYNE] Master Nphirea?
Is something wrong?
[NPHIREA] It's really
not all that important.
I just feel a bit uneasy.
[NPHIREA] Is Mr. Momon
really popular with women?
Putting aside his
physical looks,
his strength is the real deal.
And, judging by the quality
of his swords and armor,
he's obviously quite wealthy.
Oh...
All right, spill it.
[NPHIREA]
Well. There's this girl.
I can't help being afraid
that she might fall for him
once we get to Carne.
It's stupid, I know.
Is that all?!
Don't worry, I'll teach
you all the ways
to make a woman's knees bu--
Zip it! Or else!
Ow!
That's my money-maker
you just assaulted, jerk!
Uh--
What kind of person is she?
Just keep trying. If you
give up, it's all over.
[PETER] We'll even help support
you, at no extra charge!
--[LUKRUT] Come on!
--[PETER] You can do it!
You guys...
[DYNE]
Be persistent!
[ADVENTURERS laugh]
[laughs]
[CLEMENTINE humming]
[groans]
[INFORMATION BROKER 6A whimpers]
Why are you doing this?
Because you peddle
information, and I need
some on a talented pharmacist.
You want Nphiera Balear.
There, I told you.
Now please, let me go!
[CLEMENTINE]
Oh, silly man.
You could be lying to me.
I should be thorough.
If you want proof,
all you have to do is
ask the other brokers!
They'll tell you the same
thing, I'm sure of it!
[CLEMENTINE] You're taking
the fun out of this.
Fine, I'll put it another way.
Huh?
[CLEMENTINE]
I... love... killing.
Bloodshed is my one
true passion, my art.
And I need practice.
Oh! Did I mention torture?
[whimpers]
Hey! I didn't say
you could leave!
[panting]
What the hell is wrong
with that woman?
--[groans]
--[CLEMENTINE laughing]
My, my, that looks painful.
[INFORMATION BROKER 6A laughs]
It is. But I feel fantastic.
Good. Very good.
Now tell me what I want to know.
[KHAJIT]
"Create Undead."
[MAN 6A groans]
[CLEMENTINE] That Jewel
of Death sure is great
at making zombies.
But, I think you might be going
a little overboard with it.
Because you keep playing around.
I like my work.
[KHAJIT]
You need to focus, Clementine.
I've spent years
preparing to turn E-Rantel
into a city of death.
But, for my plan to work,
I need its people to be alive.
[CLEMENTINE] Oh, right.
That Spiral of Death, thingy?
[KHAJIT]
Precisely.
The same ritual that our
exalted leader once tried.
If done correctly,
it will turn the capital
into a pit of undeath overnight.
If I use this to collect
the power of death
that's left in its wake...
...my dream of immortality
will, at last, be realized.
[KHAJIT] If your antics
continue to cause me trouble,
you'll be the next
zombie I create.
[CLEMENTINE]
Hm.
[CLEMENTINE cackles]
You're more foolish
than I thought.
Don't be mad.
That was nothing
more than a love tap.
[KHAJIT]
We both know that's a lie.
[sighs]
You always manage
to impress, Khaji.
It's sexy.
[KHAJIT grunts]
[CLEMENTINE]
Oh, almost forgot.
I'll be sure not to bring
my playthings home.
That work for you?
[KHAJIT sighs]
[CLEMENTINE humming]
[KHAJIT] Hard to believe she
was once a Black Scripture.
Her power earned her the
ninth seat of their order,
but that corrupt personality
made her troublesome.
I'll have to keep an eye on her.
[AINS] The bodyguard mission
is going smoothly,
but I need something
more than this
if I want to make
a name for myself.
According to Nphirea,
the forested area
outside of Carne Village
where he gathers
his herbs is home
to a wise and powerful creature
that has lived for
hundreds of years.
Conquering such an
ancient creature
could be exactly what I
need to raise my status.
So, I order Aura to
locate it at all costs.
Chapter seven:
"Wise King of Forest."