[ALBEDO] Aura's report
states that there has been
no contact from any
other Yggdrasil players
in our immediate vicinity.
But she is expanding
her surveillance
to the great woodlands
near Nazarick.
Hopefully, she'll have
better luck there.
If they're out there,
she'll find them.
Also, I have information
from the man we captured.
He's from the Slane
Theocracy and commands
their special ops unit.
[AINS]
The Slane Theocracy.
It's a theocratic nation
that wishes to unite humans
against all other races.
If given the chance,
they'd wipe out the entire
population of ogres,
goblins and lizardmen.
I believe it would be
too dangerous to have
any contact with them now.
There's one last thing.
What should we do about
the people we saved?
[AINS] Don't do anything that
would make the citizens
of Carne Village see us
in a negative light.
We gained that foothold
on friendly terms
and I want it to stay that way.
Understood, master. That's it.
There is nothing left to
discuss from the daily report.
[AINS]
Good job.
I am unworthy of such
praise. You are too kind.
I need you to take me
right here and now.
Please, do whatever you
want to me, my love.
[AINS] Albedo. I'm not going
to take advantage of you.
I programmed you to have
these feelings towards me.
That's all.
I honestly don't see
what the problem is.
[AINS]
Ah?
Tell me something.
Are you truly disturbed
by my feelings?
Is my love a burden, master?
[AINS]
No. That's not it at all.
Wonderful.
Our relationship can
move to the next level.
[AINS]
Uh...
I'm so happy that we both
agree on this issue.
[AINS]
But I messed with the settings
Tabula designed for you.
[ALBEDO]
Lord Tabula wouldn't mind.
After all, I'm like
a daughter to him.
He'd be happy to know that I
found true love after he left.
[AINS]
You really believe that?
Uh-huh.
[knocking]
[SHALLTEAR]
Lord Ains.
I hope you are doing well
on this beautiful day.
[AINS] I am doing very well,
as I hope you are, Shalltear.
Is there something
I can help you with?
Oh, no.
My day has already been
improved just by laying eyes
on your exquisite form, my lord.
Well, if that's all
you needed, why don't you
go bother someone else?
Lord Ains and I are
busy right now,
and your pathetic flirting
has interrupted us.
Shriveled old ladies
can be such a bore,
don't you think? They cling
to whomever they can
because they've
passed their prime.
You're trying to
pass yourself off
as young and perky.
But I know the truth about
your two little friends
that have suddenly appeared.
It's pitiful, stuffing your bra.
I will rip your hag face off!
Remind me, which one of
us is a walking cadaver?
[SHALLTEAR growls]
[AINS]
Knock it off, you two!
You're acting like children.
[ALBEDO, SHALLTEAR]
Sorry, Lord Ains.
[AINS]
Well? Why are you really here?
Right.
I'm getting ready to depart
for my assignment with Sebas.
As I understand it, we may
be away from Nazarick
for quite a while.
I wanted to make sure
I said a proper goodbye
to my lord before
I make my exit.
And I couldn't leave
without one last look at you.
[MEN]
Hm?
[MAN 5C]
[BRITTA]
Huh?
Need a room?
Cost ya five bronze pieces
each. Meals are gonna--
[AINS]
I only need one room, thanks.
Forget the meals.
[SHOPKEEPER 5A] Hm? Oh, you're
a low level copper plate.
This place is gonna
be too expensive--
[AINS]
It's our first time registering.
Unfortunately, they make
you start at copper.
Now it's seven bronze pieces.
Payment due up front.
[AINS]
That's not a problem.
The room is upstairs
in the back.
[AINS]
Hm?
[THUGS chuckle]
[AINS]
Hilarious.
[THUG 5A]
Hey!
Watch where you're
going, you big oaf.
How can I work with
a busted ankle? Hm?
Lookie here.
Perhaps your little vixen can
kiss it and make me feel better.
[AINS laughs]
Not even in your dreams.
[THUG 5A]
Hm?
[AINS] Your uncivilized
behavior is quite amusing.
I can't help but laugh.
What?
[gags]
[AINS]
Look at that.
You're not so funny when
you can't breathe, are you?
Weakling.
[THUG 5A yells]
[gasps]
[AINS] So? Does anyone else
have something humorous
they want to say about
my companion? Because I--
[BRITTA screams]
[BRITTA]
I cannot believe this!
What the hell, man?!
You just spilled my potion
all over the floor back there.
It wasn't cheap y'know!
[AINS]
Potion?
[BRITTA]
Yeah, that's right.
Do you have any idea how long
I've been waiting to buy that?
I had to skip meals
and stop drinking
until I could afford
it. Took months!
You better pay for it,
or things are gonna get ugly.
[AINS]
Excuse me.
But I believe these men
should reimburse you.
You really think these
drunks can pay me back?
I doubt they've ever seen a
piece of gold in their life.
You on the other hand.
You're wearing some
expensive looking armor
and I'm betting you have a
healing potion or two in there.
I'd be happy with
getting one of those.
--[AINS] Actually, I do.
--[NARBERAL growling]
[AINS]
Uh--
Wait! Wait!
Here you go.
[BRITTA]
A red potion?
[AINS]
That makes us even, right?
Sure. For now.
Lord Ains. You
shouldn't have to stay
in such a small
and disgusting place.
[AINS]
It's not that bad, Narberal.
But the guild doesn't seem
to set any member standards.
Hopefully, all adventurers
don't act like hooligans.
Then again, when you're
fighting monsters,
brains aren't much
of a requirement.
What are we going
to do about the woman
who took your potion?
[AINS] As an iron level
adventurer, she currently
outranks us in this city.
It's best to let her be for now.
We'll deal with her
later in private.
I am curious about something.
What are your
thoughts on humans?
Complete garbage.
[MOMONGA]
Seriously? Her, too?
[AINS]
Narberal.
I can't order you to change
your feelings towards humans.
But I need you to
control your hostility
while you're in public.
If you wish, then, I will try.
[AINS]
Oh, and don't call me Ains.
Remember, I'm Momon
in this city.
Of course, Lord Momon.
[AINS]
It's just Momon!
And I will no longer
call you Narberal Gamma.
You are now Momon's
partner. Nabe.
Sorry, I won't forget
again, Momon... sir?
[AINS]
That's still a bit too formal.
But it'll work for now.
Anyway, we should discuss
our plan of action
while in E-Rantel.
[NARBERAL]
Yes!
[AINS]
Uh-- Okay then.
Our main objective in
this city is to gather
knowledge about this new world
we've been transported to.
In order to obtain
said information,
we will go undercover as
low-level adventurers.
We will gain experience
by completing quests.
With our skills, we should
quickly reach the highest
ranks of mythril,
orichalcum and adamantite.
Once there, we will be
assigned harder quests
which should allow us to
access the most useful intel.
Flawless plan,
my lord. I'm in awe.
[AINS]
It's Momon! But you're wrong.
There is one problem.
Our currency is worthless!
The majority of our money
is gold from Yggdrasil.
We can't use it.
It would be publicly
announcing that we came from
somewhere else.
And, if there are other
players that happen to be
living in this city,
there is no guarantee
that they would be
friendly towards us.
Therefore, our first goal is
to make ourselves some money!
Let's find a job!
[NPHIREA]
Welcome!
Ah... Are you
Mr. Nphirea Balear?
Yes. And how may I
help you today, Miss?
I need you to appraise
a potion for me.
[door creaks]
[NPHIREA]
Grandma!
[LIZZY]
Hm?
[NPHIREA]
You've gotta see this!
[LIZZY]
Hm? It's red.
What do you know about it?
First, I need to
examine it properly.
[BRITTA] So this is Lizzy
Balear, the famous pharmacist?
She's the best there is.
Though, I may be biased.
I'll use my Appraise
Magical Item spell.
It should detect
any enchantments.
[gasps]
So? What's up with it?
[LIZZY laughs]
Huh?
Tell me, Nphirea.
The modern manufacturing
process causes
all potions to
turn blue, correct?
[NPHIREA]
That's right.
[LIZZY]
Well, this--
I've never seen
anything like it.
It's made of pure magic like
something from a fairytale.
"A true potion of
healing resembles
the color of God's own blood."
I never believed
it actually existed.
You are one lucky lady.
This is equal to a second
tier healing spell.
Easily worth eight gold pieces.
But there are risks with
having such a rare item.
There are people out
there who would kill
to get their hands on
a potion this powerful.
Huh?
I can help though.
You wouldn't have to worry
if you sold it to me.
But I...
[LIZZY]
Hm?
Uh...
[LIZZY sighs]
All right. I have another
proposition for you.
Ah?
[ADVENTURER 5A]
Wow. Check out that guy's armor.
Looks quite expensive.
And he's just a copper plate.
[ADVENTURER 5A] Typical
rich kid playing pretend.
[ADVENTURER 5B]
A shiny present from Daddy.
[ADVENTURERS laugh]
[MOMONGA] This is bad.
I can't read these postings.
And Narberal isn't able
to read any language.
Hm.
[AINS]
Consider this quest done.
I'm very sorry, sir.
But you are only a copper plate
and this request is
looking for a mythril.
[AINS]
I'm aware.
You'll find me
more than qualified.
I have to follow
the guild's rules.
[AINS]
The rules are wrong.
Guidelines are set for a reason.
Without the
requisite experience,
you could get
someone hurt or worse.
[AINS]
Hah. You see my companion here?
She's a third tier magic user.
[ADVENTURER 5D]
Third tier?
[ADVENTURER 5E]
There's no way!
[AINS] I have the skills of
a fighter comperable to her.
It would be a waste
of our talents
to accept a mere
copper plate quest.
I understand, but the
rules are very clear.
I simply can't allow it.
[AINS] No problem.
You're just doing your job.
Sorry if we came
across as pompous.
Please sign us up for
the most difficult quest
available in the
copper plate field.
Yes. Of course.
Give me just a moment.
[MOMONGA] Perfect! I can't
believe that worked.
[PETER]
Hey, Mister, you two could join
our adventuring group
if you're interested.
[AINS]
Really?
[PETER]
Let me introduce everyone.
We call ourselves
The Swords of Darkness.
I'm Peter Mork, the leader.
Over to my left is our
ranger, Lukrut Volve.
He's our eyes and
ears in the field.
Ha, hi!
[PETER] Our capable Druid
uses magic to heal us
and manipulate nature.
Dyne Woodwonder.
Nice to meet you folks.
And last but not least is
the brains of the operation.
Our magic user,
Ninya the Spell Caster.
Hello there. Peter, stop it.
I keep telling you that
nickname is embarrassing.
Why?
You know you should
be proud of it.
Our Ninya here
is a talent holder.
[AINS]
Seriously? That's impressive.
[MOMONGA] In this world,
that means he was born
with a special ability.
Ninya has a talent
called Magic Affinity.
He's able to learn magic
spells twice as fast
as the average caster.
Isn't that right?
Uh...
[AINS]
That's amazing.
It's not like I did
anything to deserve this.
I'm lucky.
Part of me feels it's actually
kind of an unfair advantage.
Such modesty. He's a
famous talent holder.
We're proud to have
him on our team.
Yeah, well.
Here in E-Rantel, there's a
more famous talent holder.
That would be Master Balear.
[AINS]
Who? Oh, how rude of me.
This is Nabe and I am Momon.
Glad to have you all
watching our backs.
So. About this Balear guy.
What kind of talent
does he possess?
You don't know?
There's absolutely no way you
guys are from around here then,
and that actually
explains a lot.
[AINS] You're correct.
We just arrived yesterday.
Well, his name
is Nphirea Balear.
He's the grandson of a well
known pharmacist in E-Rantel.
He was born with a talent
that allows him to use
any and all magical
items without training.
[AINS]
Impressive.
That could be useful.
[AINS]
Agreed.
Now then.
I'm sure you're wondering
why we need your help.
Our current objective is
to destroy all the monsters
that have wandered
too close to the city.
[AINS]
You were hired to hunt monsters?
Not really.
It's actually an
off-the-books expedition
that we decided to
take on by ourselves.
[AINS]
What does that mean?
We weren't exactly
hired to do it,
but the guild will receive
money from the city
based on the strength
of the monsters we defeat.
We just have to collect
our reward from the guild.
[MOMONGA]
I get it.
It's like earning coins
by collecting item drops.
It's a dull, but necessary
task for us adventurers.
The job is pretty easy,
and we get to keep people safe,
while also bringing
home the tasty bacon.
It's totally a win-win situation
for all parties involved.
So, you interested
in joining us?
Our plan is to start
clearing out the forest
just south of the city and
working our way north.
Whaddya say?
The experience will help you
rise above a copper plate.
[AINS]
Sure. We're happy to come along.
[ADVENTURERS laugh]
[AINS] One thing. I should
show you all my face
since we will be
working together.
I hope it's not a shock.
Oh, interesting.
I've heard of a country
south of here where a face
like yours is common,
but you're the first
that I've met in person.
He's older than I expected.
Don't be so rude.
[AINS] I've been hiding my
face since we came to town.
Sometimes people have
issues with foreigners.
And I didn't want to
stir up any trouble.
[MOMONGA] They have no clue
this face is an illusion.
[LUKRUT]
Just out of curiosity,
what kind of partners
are you two exactly?
[NINYA, PETER, DYNE groan]
[AINS]
We're allies.
That's wonderful.
'Cause I'm in love!
Say you'll go on a date with me?
Watch your tongue, you dog.
Or I shall have to cut it out
and serve it to you for dinner.
Learn your place and sit.
[AINS]
She doesn't mean--
[LUKRUT] That kind of honest
criticism is so rare these days!
You're right. We should just
start as friends, for now.
You disgust me.
Perhaps I'll spoon out
your eyes for fun.
[LUKRUT] That cool gaze of
hers really does it for me.
I'm sorry about
my friend's advances.
[AINS]
Yes. I'm sorry as well.
If you and Nabe are ready to go,
I think it's best that
we head out immediately.
[AINS]
Agreed.
Mr. Momon?
[AINS]
Hm?
Someone specifically
requested you for a job.
[AINS]
Do you know who asked for me?
Yes, Mr. Nphirea Balear.
[ADVENTURERS gasp]
[growls]
[AINS]
Stop and think before you act.
I'm sorry. It won't
happen again.
[AINS]
I know you mean well.
But you have to learn
not to overreact
to harmless
situations. Understand?
[NPHIREA]
Hello there.
I'm the one that
specifically requested you.
[AINS]
I'm sorry to disappoint.
But we have already
accepted another position.
Perhaps after we have finished
this job we can help you.
Don't be ridiculous!
This could be big for you!
[AINS] I agreed to join
up with your group.
What kind of a man would I be
if I did not keep my word?
[NPHIREA, QUEST-GIVER 5A gasp]
But, it's a personal request.
[AINS]
Okay. How about this:
I will listen to
Mr. Balear's proposition,
and then make my choice.
[NPHIREA]
My name is Nphirea Balear.
I'm a pharmacist
here in the city.
Your job would be to
protect me while I harvest
some herbs in the forest
near Carne Village.
[MOMONGA]
Carne Village?
Aside from escorting me
there and back again,
I'd like for you
to help me collect
the medicinal herbs that I need.
[AINS]
A bodyguard assignment.
[MOMONGA]
I don't know about this gig.
My skills and items aren't
great at protecting others.
The reward for doing this is--
[AINS]
Question, Peter.
How would you like to
come on as my hired hand?
[PETER]
What do you mean?
[AINS]
I suggest we take these men
along for this excursion.
A ranger such as Mr. Lukrut
would provide security.
And it would also be smart
to have the skills of a Druid
like Mr. Dyne if we're going
to be working in a forest.
Yes. You possess a keen
insight, Mr. Momon.
I definitely don't
mind tagging along.
It'd be an honor
to escort you both.
More men equals more
protection for me.
[AINS]
That's settled then.
But... I'm still
confused by one thing.
What's that?
[AINS] Why did you
request me for this job?
Huh?
[AINS] I'm new to the
area and don't have
any acquaintances in this city.
I'm very curious how
a well-known citizen
such as yourself
came to know my name.
May I ask how you heard of me?
I caught wind
about what happened
with you at the inn yesterday.
[AINS]
The fight at the inn?
Yeah.
A recent customer of
mine told me about how
you easily took down several
higher ranked adventurers
who were accosting you
and your partner.
The person I used
to hire as an escort
moved away from E-Rantel
not too long ago.
So, now I'm in the market
for a replacement warrior.
And to be perfectly
honest with you,
it's a lot cheaper to hire
a copper plate for the job.
[AINS]
That's true...
Does anyone have
another question?
[PETER] No. We're ready
to leave whenever you are.
[AINS] I can't shake the feeling
that something is off here.
Then let's get going.
There's no time to waste.
[CLEMENTINE giggles]
[CLEMENTINE humming]
This is it.
I'm coming down.
Khaji! I need to
talk to you, old man.
Are you here?
[KHAJIT] I told you
to stop calling me that.
It is disrespectful to
the great name of Zuranon.
So tell me. Why have
you come here?
[CLEMENTINE giggles] I thought
you might be interested in this.
My god.
One of the treasures
of the Slane Theocracy.
A fabled shaman princess
wore that Crown of Wisdom.
[CLEMENTINE]
Oh, I know.
A sweet little thing was
going crazy while wearing it.
So, I did her a favor and
snatched it off her pretty head.
[KHAJIT grunts] As a former
member of the Black Scripture,
you should be well
aware that this item
suppresses the
soul of its bearer
and turns them into
a magical conduit.
It's incredibly dangerous.
Simply touching it could
have meant your end,
and yet you did it anyway.
Boring.
There's a one in
a million chance
you could find a
person who's compatible.
And without a true match,
it's just a very fancy
piece of garbage.
That's why I came.
As a fellow member of
the society of Zuranon,
you have to help me.
Isn't that right,
Khajit Dale Badantel?
[growls] I don't answer
to "Dale" anymore.
Now, what do you want from me?
[CLEMENTINE] I've heard rumors
about a talent holder
in town that can use
any magical item at will.
Do you think he can make this
crown work for little ol' me?
I highly doubt that
you need my assistance
kidnapping a defenseless boy.
Normally, no, but I
intend to cause
a bit of an uproar
in the process.
You plan on using chaos
as your means
to escape the city.
How's this:
I'll participate in your
ritual if you're a good boy
and help me out.
Pretty enticing, right?
I'd be a fool to
turn that offer down.
Let's figure out how to
grab that talent holder.
[AINS] My first job as
the adventurer, Momon,
is to serve as bodyguard
to Nphirea, the pharmacist.
An adventurer group
calling themselves
"The Swords of Darkness,"
accompany me on the journey.
And, even though their
individual specialties
are vastly different,
their teamwork is seamless.
Their strong bond reminds
me of my old comrads
and all that we could
accomplish together.
And the memories fill me
with jealousy and melancholy.
Chapter six: "Journey."