[AINS groans]
This is bad.
I never thought
I'd have to resort
to using a god level item.
--[beeping]
--[NARBERAL] Lord Ains.
[AINS] This better be
important, Narberal.
I told you not to disturb me!
[AINS] It's okay. Forget
about it. What do you need?
[NARBERAL]
You received a message
from the Adventurer's Guild.
The leader, Ainzach,
wants to meet with you.
A vampire has been terrorizing
the area outside of E-Rantel.
The guild needs your help.
They sound desperate.
[AINS]
Hm... I'm on my way.
Let him know I'll be there soon.
[AINZACH] I'd like to thank you,
mythril level adventurers,
for taking time out of your
busy schedule to meet with me.
Now let's get down to business.
Last night, seven
adventurers were attacked.
And five iron class
men were killed.
They claim it was a vampire.
She ambushed them in the
forest outside of town.
Here's what we know:
The monster has blonde hair.
And a large mouth containing
very sharp fangs.
[MOMONGA]
That describes Shalltear to a T.
If this creature is
indeed a vampire, we need
to keep it from entering
the city at all costs.
Left unchecked, it
could turn E-Rantel's
populace into slaves.
Was this foul beast involved
in the recent cemetery incident?
Well, I'm sure Mr. Momon here
would know the answer to that.
Must be nice to get bumped up
to mythril after
only one quest, huh?
[BELLOTE]
Don't be like that, Igvarge.
[AINZACH] After investigating
the cemetery,
We know, without a doubt,
that Zuranon followers were
behind the attack there.
Wait, Zuranon?
The dangerous cult
obsessed with the
undead? Then...
The vampire has to
be involved with them.
We can't say that for certain.
Though, if I had to
guess, it's a decoy.
Sure.
But it doesn't take a
vampire to kill iron plates.
Let's just concentrate
on finding the fiend.
She was last seen
near some caves.
I'll send out a search party.
[AINS] I'm positive
this creature is not
affiliated with Zuranon.
And how can you be so sure?
[AINS] That vampire is
known as... Honyopn...
[AINZACH]
What?
[AINS]
Honyopnyoko!
[MEN gasp]
So is this Honey-pot, uh...
I take it you're familiar
with this monster?
[AINS] Indeed, I have
quite a history with it.
I've been tracking her
for years. She's powerful.
Not just any man could
compete with her strength.
But my team will get rid of this
nuisance for you, no problem.
The hell you will.
You're sure you can kill her?
[AINS]
Definitely. Because I have this.
There is eighth tier magic
within this crystal.
[MEN gasp]
[AINZACH]
That's impossible.
Everyone knows the eighth
tier is just a myth!
No way. That thing's a fake.
[AINS] I can get it
appraised, but we'd be
wasting valuable time.
Your reward?
[AINS] Details can be
hammered out later.
However, I expect a
promotion to orichalcum.
Orichalcum?!
[AINS] Must I demonstrate my
strength time after time?
As you wish.
I'm going, too!
[AINS]
You'll just slow me down.
[IGVARGE] How dare a newbie
like you talk to me like that!
Screw you!
We don't even know how powerful
this vampire really is!
Knock it off, Igvarge!
There's no need
for such hostility.
[AINS] Tag along, if you
must. But I warn you.
It means certain death.
[IGVARGE]
No! You bastard!
I can't believe this.
You monster!
I'm gonna kill you! All of you!
[whimpers]
[AINS] I explicitly said
this would happen.
You have no one but
yourself to blame.
Now, it's time to face the
consequences of your actions.
Death might come swiftly.
Damn you all.
[MARE] I hope that was
satisfactory, my lord.
[AINS] Yes. Excellent job.
Those men were so weak.
It was a waste of time
to call for you.
So, what should we
do with the bodies?
[AINS]
Take them to Nazarick.
Let's see if we can create
high level undead creatures
with their corpses.
It will be done.
[AINS] Mare, I need you
to escort Narberal.
And Hamusuke as well.
[MARE]
Yes, Lord Ains.
Lord.
Afraid to go to
Nazarick, Hamusuke is.
If I do, eaten, I will be!
You are the property
of Lord Ains.
As his pet, no one
would dare eat you.
If you say so,
Mistress Narberal,
in your hands my life is.
[AINS] Hmph. Albedo.
Let's continue our mission.
Lord.
[AINS]
Shalltear.
Shalltear! Answer your master.
You disrespectful little we--
[AINS] Be quiet! Can this
really be happening?
No.
It's impossible. But
Shalltear is clearly affected.
Even though she's undead.
I can see there was a battle.
And the victor took
control of her mind.
Then... She was left here alone
without any orders to obey.
And now she waits.
We need to break this
spell over Shalltear.
Though, it's a shame
to waste such a strong
magical item on a counter spell.
[ALBEDO]
What is that?
[AINS] A super-rare ring.
It's known as Shooting Star.
Three times a day,
it lets the wearer
cast the spell
Wish Upon a Star.
[MOMONGA]
I hope she's impressed.
This thing wasn't cheap.
Cost me my entire summer bonus.
That's powerful.
[AINS] You've never
seen super tier magic?
[ALBEDO] No. I've only heard
rumors of its existence.
And that it's stronger
than a tenth tier spell.
[AINS] Correct. Using it
requires a certain skill set.
One that I happen to possess.
Magic points don't effect
the spell at all.
And there is a
long casting time.
However, we don't have
to worry about that.
This ring cancels out
the casting time.
Plus, it activates
the spell without
using any experience points.
I should be able to release
Shalltear in no time flat.
But, Lord Ains,
Shalltear's a servant.
It's unnecessary to use such
an important item on her.
Oh, your compassion
knows no bounds.
[AINS]
Shooting Star! Now, ring,
cure Shalltear of all her
status effects. I command you!
[AINS gasps]
What's this?
[MOMONGA]
It doesn't make sense.
Someone here is stronger
than super tier magic? No!
[AINS]
We're leaving! Albedo! Let's go!
Lord!
[AINS]
Dammit! Dammit!
[ALBEDO whimpers]
[AINS]
Dammit! Dammit! Dammit!
Are you okay?
[AINS]
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have acted
that way in front of you.
Did something go wrong
with the spell, my lord?
[AINS] The ring was definitely
activated correctly.
However, the wish
was not granted.
Only one thing is
capable of withstanding
a super tier magic spell.
And I honestly never
thought this world
could contain such a power.
No way. You mean...?
[AINS]
A world level item!
[ALBEDO gasps]
[AINS]
Albedo.
[ALBEDO]
Lord?
[AINS]
The security level of Nazarick
needs to be raised to maximum.
Also, every Guardian needs
to return home immediately.
[MARE] Excuse me. Lord Ains
sent orders for all of us.
We are to supervise the first,
second and third floors.
[BRIDES whimper, gasp]
[COCYTUS]
Nazarick is currently following
the topmost alert protocol.
Let's use this situation
to show the Supreme Beings
that we are completely
loyal to them.
[DEMIURGE]
The all-powerful ones created us
to do their bidding.
If anyone fails to meet
their expectations,
then there is absolutely no
purpose for their existence,
and they should be
terminated at once.
What could she possibly
be doing down there?
[SOLUTION] I can't believe
Shalltear would rebel.
Sebas, shouldn't we
return to Nazarick
with all the other Guardians?
[SEBAS]
No.
We were given special orders to
continue on with the mission.
Our presence is
needed in E-Rantel.
You should never question
Lord Ains' wishes.
He is a great man.
I have no doubt
that he will choose
the best course of action.
[AINS] Is this your first
time in the treasury?
[ALBEDO]
Yes.
I couldn't enter without
the ring of Ains Ooal Gown.
It is the only key.
[AINS]
A security feature.
"Glory to Ains Ooal Gown."
Let's see.
"By this means, you
will acquire the glory
of the whole world and
so you will drive away
all shadows and blindness."
At least, I believe
that's correct.
[AINS] We are headed to the
mausoleum. It's not far.
[ALBEDO] Mausoleum? I didn't
know there was one.
[AINS] Hm. I guess it
has been off limits.
Are you aware of
Pandora's Actor?
Of course. I know
of his existence.
But we've never actually met.
Pandora's Actor.
His power and intelligence
rivals my own.
Created by the masters to
be the one true Guardian
of the treasury.
If I'm not mistaken,
you designed him
yourself, my lord.
[AINS]
Yes. That's right.
[ALBEDO]
He is also responsible for
keeping our finances in check.
[AINS]
Yes.
[gasps]
[gasps] Lord Tabula,
is that really you?
Wait a second. It's an Imposter!
Who are you?
And why are you
disguised as my creator?
You may have copied his
appearance and aura perfectly,
but I was able to see
past your façade.
Kill this thing.
Are you sure?
[AINS] Pandora's Actor.
Change your form.
What?
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
Hello, darlings.
It's nice to have company.
[PANDORA'S ACTOR] Greetings to
my creator, Lord Momonga!
[AINS] Um. You look like
you're doing well.
[PANDORA'S ACTOR] Yes! I
couldn't be better, my good sir.
It has been a while.
To what do I owe this honor?
[AINS]
I'm in need of some world items.
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
Oh! World item!
Changing the world
with immense power!
Showing the greatness of
the mighty Supreme Beings!
These sacred treasures
have been asleep for
ages beneath Nazarick.
Has the time finally
come to wake them up?
[MOMONGA]
This dude is so lame!
[AINS]
Yes. You are correct.
I need Billion Blades,
Hygieia's Chalice,
Avarice and Selfless, and
Depiction of Nature and Society.
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
Outstanding!
Great choices, Lord Momonga.
[AINS] Another thing. Address
me as Ains from now on.
I'm known as Ains Ooal Gown.
[PANDORA'S ACTOR gasps]
What a great name.
It fits the wonderful man
who created me. Lord Ains.
[MOMONGA]
Oh, no!
I wonder how hardcore
they're judging me
because of this doofus!
[MOMONGA]
Just look at him.
What the hell was I
thinking when I designed
his personality? It's
beyond embarrassing.
Oh well. At least his
military outfit is still rad.
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
Are you okay, my liege?
[MOMONGA groans]
[AINS]
Let's continue.
[ALBEDO]
Lord.
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
Be careful now, Lord Ains.
And you, too, lovely ladies.
What did you call me?
I am leader of the Guardians.
And Yuri is second-in-command
of the Pleiades.
You will show us the respect
we both rightfully deserve.
I agree with Albedo
on this, sir.
[PANDORA'S ACTOR gasps]
Please forgive me.
I can't control my tongue.
Not around such
beautiful flowers.
[AINS] I need to talk
to you in private.
[PANDORA'S ACTOR yelps]
You are aware that I am the lord
who created you, correct?
[PANDORA'S ACTOR] A fact I take
the deepest of pride in.
[AINS] Then, as your maker,
I demand that you
stop with all this
ridiculous saluting!
That's an order, you hear me?
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
What?
[AINS]
Okay. So.
Here's the problem.
It's unnecessary.
Your outfit works, since
it shows your strength,
but all the saluting
makes you seem unstable.
[PANDORA'S ACTOR grunts]
Das ist meines Gottes Wille!
[AINS] Do not speak
German in front of me.
That's another direct order.
[PANDORA'S ACTOR]
Understood.
[AINS]
Please obey me.
[MOMONGA] I can't believe
I've struggled to keep
my emotions in check because
I created this weird idiot.
This is more embarrassing
than riding a giant hamster.
[AINS] Sorry to keep
you waiting. Now, Albedo.
Lord?
[AINS]
You need to give Yuri the ring
of Ains Ooal Gown that
you're currently wearing.
[gasps]
[AINS] Nobody is able to
teleport to the treasury
without possession
of the guild ring.
However, you can't enter this
specific room with it on.
Or the golems will sense
intruders... and attack.
[ALBEDO]
These golems look familiar.
Are they based off
the likenesses
of the Supreme Beings, my lord?
[AINS]
How perceptive of you.
Indeed, I had them made
to honor the memory
of my old comrades.
They're starting to
look shabby though.
[ALBEDO]
No, they are not. Lord Ains.
You called this place
a mausoleum. So then...
Does that mean the other
Supreme Beings are dead,
and that's why there
are statues of them here?
[AINS] To my knowledge,
they are still alive.
[MOMONGA]
Crap.
I don't know why I
just said that to her.
Truth is, right before
the game shut down,
each of them gifted
me their supplies.
[MOMONGA]
These items should do the trick.
Peroroncino told me
to sell them all.
But I just couldn't
do it. I wasn't ready.
[MOMONGA] I keep waiting
for you all to come back.
[MOMONGA]
Please, guys.
I need to believe that you are
all stuck in this world, too.
That I'm not alone.
[ALBEDO sighs]
[AINS]
What's wrong?
Oh, sorry, it's nothing.
[AINS] Albedo. Do you
see that spot over there?
That's where I'll put a statue
of myself one of these days.
[ALBEDO gasps]
Please don't talk like that.
I can't bear to hear it!
It tears my heart!
[AINS gasps]
[ALBEDO whimpers]
My dear Lord Ains.
You were the only one
with enough kindness
not to leave all
of us alone here.
Master! Please say that
you'll stay in Nazarick
and be our leader
until the end of time.
We need you. I beg of you.
[sobbing] Don't go...
Don't go...
[AINS]
Albedo.
Forgive me.
Promise me something!
Say that you won't abandon us.
We'd never survive on our own.
Not without your wisdom!
[AINS]
I can't promise that.
Why not?
Have I done something
that has offended you?
Tell me what I've
done and I'll fix it!
There is nothing I wouldn't
do to make things right
in your eyes, my lord.
If I am the problem,
I swear I will repent
and end my life here!
[AINS]
Stop it!
[gasps]
[AINS]
Listen closely.
The only way to
combat world item level
brainwashing is to
fight fire with fire.
We have no choice but to utilize
world level items ourselves.
[ALBEDO]
So, you're positive?
There's no doubt that a
world item was used on her?
[AINS]
I'm sure.
And the Guardians
need to be the ones
who wield these weapons.
[gasps]
[AINS] I have a plan. We will
be able to save Shalltear.
[ALBEDO]
But... How?
[AINS]
The answer is down here.
Known as One of 20.
The 20 world items of
unrivaled destruction.
They are currently
in my possession.
However, the power
of a 20 is so large,
it would be expended
after just one use.
I'm not aware of what
other world items
the enemy holds.
So I'm hesitant to cast such
a mighty spell right away.
In the end, we may not have need
for such extreme measures.
What's wrong with me?
Could I be more pathetic?
No. Please don't say
that about yourself.
The Supreme Ones
worked hard to collect
all these world items, and we
shouldn't let them go to waste.
They are more valuable than
all of the Guardian's
lives put together.
[AINS] Albedo. There is a
reason I won't promise you
that I'll come back to Nazarick.
I'm going to fight
Shalltear by myself.
[gasps]
[AINS]
I won't promise.
Because I'm not sure
I'll survive the battle.
Please rethink this!
It's true that Shalltear
has to be dealt with.
It's too dangerous to
leave her as she is.
But, for me-- Don't go.
You have an entire army
under your command.
She doesn't stand a chance
against the forces of Nazarick!
[AINS] You don't understand,
Albedo. I have to.
Let me explain. There
are three reasons why.
First off.
I need to prove to myself
that I'm a competent leader.
Worthy of my title.
It was foolish of me not
to consider the existence
of world level items
in this new land.
Of course they
would exist if other
Yggdrasil players are here.
I completely overlooked this.
Not a sign of a
good leader, is it?
Your destiny is to rule
over Nazarick, my lord.
And, though we may
be lacking, we will do
everything we can
to support you.
[AINS]
The second reason.
I'm not convinced
this isn't a trap.
A trap? Are you sure?
[AINS]
Shalltear may be bait.
The enemy could be waiting
for us to attempt a rescue.
And if they pounce,
I'd rather be taken alone,
than risk having my people
captured and maybe killed.
The final reason is...
I may have to
exterminate Shalltear.
In that case,
let me come with you.
I'll be the one to
kill her instead.
[AINS] You honestly think
you could beat her?
[ALBEDO]
Uh...
[AINS]
She is a strong foe. I'm sorry.
But it has to be me.
Out of everyone who
resides in Nazarick,
I'm the only one that
can overpower her.
[ALBEDO]
That is true.
But you will have a
greater chance of victory
if you are armed
with the world items.
[AINS] Shalltear is the
one who has the advantage
in this fight.
She is a holy magic caster with
strength against the undead.
Her body was designed
for battle. So you see,
there is the possibility
that she will defeat me.
[ALBEDO]
I'm afraid you're right.
[AINS]
You have an urge to protect me.
Which is part of
your programming.
And your feelings
and actions are solely
based on your
configurations we set.
[gasps] Lord Ains.
I do not understand.
[AINS]
It's about time you learn why
I am called the
Supreme Overlord.
You'll see that I was given
that name for a reason.
[gasps]
[AINS] I will not be defeated
by a person's abilities alone.
Remember, Peroroncino and I
used to be very close friends.
The outcome of this battle
has already been decided.
I will win.
[ALBEDO]
I understand your situation now.
But, please, promise me
that you will return.
And I will no longer
try to stop you.
[AINS]
If that's what you need.
Then I promise you,
I will come back alive.
But first, I have
to defeat Shalltear.
[AINS] I've learned the
unfortunate lesson
that an Overlord who cannot
protect his subordinates
is worthlesss beyond compare.
I curse my own foolishness
as I stand there,
seeing Shalltear's vacant,
mind-controlled gaze.
Though it pains me to fight her,
I must, even if it means
using super tier magic.
Shalltear, my most
powerful Guardian,
This battle will
decide our fates.
Well, there's no time to waste.
Let's begin!
Chapter 12:
"The Bloody Valkyrie."