[MOMONGA] Dive Massively
Multiplayer Online
Role Playing Game.
Or, for short, "DMMO-RPG."
It's a type of game
where you can
immerse yourself in an imaginary
world as if you were in it.
Such as Yggdrasil.
Released in the year 2126,
the game sported
an expansive world map
and an unusually high degree
of player freedom. These
features, among others,
made it stand above all other
DMMO-RPGs of its time.
And it became wildly popular
in the country of Japan.
Now, after 12 years
of operation,
the world of Yggdrasil
is about to see its end.
[SKELETONS grunting, growling]
[PLAYERS grunting]
[PLAYER 1A growling]
[PLAYER 1B grunting]
[PLAYER 1E yells]
[PLAYER 1C yells]
[PLAYER 1D growls]
[PLAYER 1F growls]
[PLAYER 1A grunts]
[PLAYERS gasp]
[PLAYER 1A gasping]
[PLAYER 1A groans]
[AINS chuckles]
[AINS laughs]
[MOMONGA] It was fun.
In fact, it was a blast.
[HEROHERO]
Hey, there.
It's been a while
hasn't it, Momonga?
[MOMONGA]
Sure has.
To be honest, Herohero,
I didn't think you'd come.
You've been gone
a couple of years.
[HEROHERO] No way. It's
really been that long? Man.
I guess I've been
working so much,
my concept of time
is out of whack.
[MOMONGA] That sucks.
It can't be healthy for you.
[HEROHERO]
Tell me about it.
I feel like my avatar looks.
[MOMONGA]
Hm.
[HEROHERO]
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have come
here just to complain.
[MOMONGA]
Please, don't worry about it.
[HEROHERO]
Well, I better go soon.
I'm beyond exhausted.
[MOMONGA]
Right. Rest up and feel better.
[HEROHERO]
Wish I could stay longer.
But, gotta say, I'm
kinda shocked to see
the Great Tomb of
Nazarick still standing.
[MOMONGA]
Huh?
[HEROHERO]
Being guild leader suited you.
You've done a great job
maintaining the place.
[MOMONGA] Well, we created
this place together.
I couldn't just
let it go to dust.
[HEROHERO]
Must have been hard work.
Thanks for everything.
I hope we meet again IRL.
[MOMONGA] Today is the
last day Yggdrasil's servers
will be online.
Why not stay?
We could reminisce and
wait until everything
shuts down for good. [sighs]
[MOMONGA]
Oh well.
I'm happy that he
even came at all.
"I hope we meet
again," huh? Right.
Just when and where
would that be?
[MOMONGA]
This sucks!
This is our home.
We built it together,
with virtual blood and sweat.
[MOMONGA] How can he turn
his back on it so easily?
[MOMONGA]
Stop it. He didn't.
No one in the
guild betrayed you.
Our guild's weapon:
the Staff of Ains Ooal Gown.
[MOMONGA]
We played recklessly to make it.
Some of us even spent our
PTO just to have time
to grind the materials.
[MOMONGA] But, among
the original 41 members,
37 of them quit.
[MOMONGA] Then, the three
that were left...
[MOMONGA] Let's go. You're
a testament of our guild.
[MOMONGA] There were two
requirements for joining
the guild, Ains Ooal Gown.
The player's avatar
had to be inhuman
and the player themself
had to be a functioning
member of society.
[MOMONGA] We put our livelihoods
on the line to play.
Some members managed to
make their dreams come true.
In the end, I can't blame
them for choosing real life.
[MOMONGA]
Uh--
[MOMONGA] Oh, yeah. I
forgot his name was Sebas.
And these are the combat
maids of the Pleiades.
We intended for them
to be the last
line of defense to the
throne room, but, in the end,
no player was able
to make it that far.
[MOMONGA]
I should move them around.
One last time. It's
the least I can do.
"Follow Me."
[MOMONGA]
I'm sure the other guild members
will forgive me for doing
whatever I want, just for today.
[MOMONGA]
Albedo.
Hm?
The command was
"Stand By," right?
[MOMONGA sighs]
[MOMONGA]
Hm?
What were her settings again?
"As the highest ranking NPC
in the Tomb of Nazarick,
she supervises all
of the Guardians."
Jeez, this is long!
Well...
Tabula, the settings maniac,
was the one who created her.
Huh? No way. She's a bitch?
[MOMONGA sighs]
[MOMONGA] He did love to make
contradicting characters.
I can't fault a guy for
his tastes, but still.
Normally, you need a
tool to change settings,
but since I have this...
[MOMONGA] Hm... Maybe I
should add something...
"She is deeply in
love with Momonga."
How embarrassing!
I'm such a dork!
[MOMONGA]
What was that command again?
"Bow down."
[MOMONGA sighs]
[MOMONGA] Now these are
relics of the past.
[MOMONGA]
There's mine. "Touch Me."
"Shijuuten Suzaku."
"Ankoro Mocchi Mocchi."
"Herohero." "Peroroncino."
"Bukubuku Chagama."
"Tabula Smaragdina."
"Warrior Takemikazuchi."
"Variable Talisman." "Genjiro."
[MOMONGA sighs]
Well, it was fun.
[MOMONGA]
In fact, it was a blast.
[MOMONGA sighs]
I have to wake up at four AM.
I better crash after
the server shuts down.
I don't wanna be
a zombie at work.
[MOMONGA gasps]
[MOMONGA] Did the devs push
back the server shutdown?
[MOMONGA]
Where's my console?
I can't use chat or call a GM!
What's going on?!
[ALBEDO] Is something
the matter, Lord Momonga?
[MOMONGA]
Hm?
U-Uh...
Lord Momonga?
[ALBEDO] Lord Momonga?
Is everything all right?
You seem troubled, my lord.
[MOMONGA]
Uh...
[ALBEDO gasps]
If there's a problem,
please let me help.
[MOMONGA gasps]
[AINS] The GM call
function isn't working.
I'm sorry, but I have no answer.
This "GM Call"
magic you speak of
is beyond my comprehension.
[MOMONGA]
Her mouth is moving!
[ALBEDO] I realize my failure
to assist you is inexcusable.
I don't deserve it, but I
beg for your mercy, lord.
[MOMONGA] I'm actually
talking with an NPC?!
[MOMONGA] No way. Is this
a bug? A programming error?
[MOMONGA]
Okay, the staff still functions
like it normally does,
but I can't use my console,
or contact the administrators.
What should I do?
[AINS]
Sebas!
[SEBAS]
Lord.
[MOMONGA] Is it okay for
me to give him orders?
Ah, screw it.
[AINS]
Sebas.
Step out of the
Great Tomb and confirm
the surroundings of Nazarick.
By your command,
my lord. I'll return.
Pleiades, I want you
on the ninth floor.
If anyone tries to
trespass, deal with them.
As you wish, my lord.
It will be done.
[MOMONGA] They even recognize
and respond to commands
that aren't native to the game.
What in the world is going on?
Mm?
[MOMONGA]
Uh--
Think. How can I
contact an administrator?
The "GM Call"
function is busted.
The "Message" spell? Maybe.
It's normally used for players
to contact each other,
so there's a chance.
But I'm not sure I
can even use magic.
[ALBEDO]
So, Lord Momonga?
[MOMONGA]
Huh?
Do you have any orders
for me to obey?
[AINS]
Let's see.
I guess, you could come
here for a moment.
Sure!
[MOMONGA]
Whoa! She smells great!
Wait, "smell"?
There was never a function
like that in Yggdrasil.
[AINS]
Albedo, may I touch you?
Yes!
[gasps]
[MOMONGA]
No way. She has a pulse.
This is crazy!
She's supposed to be an
NPC run by an AI program.
Why does she seem so alive?
Okay. Focus. Last test.
I have to confirm this,
no matter the cost!
[AINS] Albedo. May--
May I touch your chest?
[ALBEDO]
Eh?
[MOMONGA] Uh! This is
necessary! Play it cool!
Act natural, like
it's no big deal.
Uh, you don't mind that, right?
[MOMONGA]
You blew it, n00b!
Of course not! Touch me
as much as you wish!
[MOMONGA]
Uh...
[moans]
[MOMONGA]
Let's think this through.
The fact I can do something
reserved for a hentai game
means this isn't a new
version of Yggdrasil,
and chances are slim that
this is some new DMMO-RPG.
Is it possible that this
virtual world somehow
became real all of a sudden?
No way. That's nuts.
But, really, talking
to the NPCS,
smelling their scent,
touching them...
All of these things
have been impossible
to program into games.
[MOMONGA]
Hey!
How long did I plan
on fondling her?
[AINS] A-Albedo. I'm sorry,
I didn't mean to--
This is it, isn't it?
You're going to
take me right here?
[AINS]
Uh--
[ALBEDO] Oh! What shall
I do about my clothes?
Should I remove them on my own?
Or would you prefer to
get rid of them yourself?
[AINS]
Whoa! Hold on a moment, Albedo!
This isn't right!
[AINS clears throat]
[AINS] Now is not the time
to be doing such things.
[ALBEDO gasps]
I'm so sorry, Lord Momonga!
[AINS] It's fine, Albedo.
I forgive you completely.
More importantly, I have
an order for you.
It would be my
pleasure to serve you.
[AINS] Except for the
Guardians of the fourth
and eighth floors,
I want everyone to meet
at the sixth floor's
fighting arena.
Have them gather
there in one hour.
As you wish, my lord.
[MOMONGA]
This is terrible.
Tabula...
I can't believe I
took the NPC you made
and tainted it like that.
[MOMONGA] Dammit. I'll
worry about that later.
I have plenty of other problems
to take care of first.
[MOMONGA]
It worked!
The ring's teleportation ability
has no issues.
I can still use items.
[MOMONGA] It looks like Albedo
and the others are still loyal,
just like they were
programmed to be.
[MOMONGA] So then, what about
the other characters?
[MOMONGA]
The twin dark elves that Chagama
created should be the
Guardians of this floor.
Where are they?
[AURA yells]
[laughs]
Crushed it!
[AINS]
Aura.
We're honored to have
you, Lord Momonga!
Welcome to the sixth
floor amphitheater.
[AINS] I will only intrude
for a little while.
You must be joking, right?
You are the ruler of the
Great Tomb of Nazarick.
Your power here is absolute.
There isn't a
guardian that would
ever consider you an intruder,
least of all my brother and I.
[AINS]
Speaking of...
Mare! You're being rude
to Lord Momonga!
Stop cowering and get
down here already!
[MARE]
But, Sis, I'm scared! Come on.
Mare!
[MARE]
Okay, okay, fine! I'm coming!
[MARE grunts]
[MARE yelps]
[AURA]
Good grief.
[MARE pants]
We're gettin' old, here.
[MARE]
I'm hurrying!
Ah!
[MARE] I apologize for making
you wait, Lord Momonga.
[AINS]
It's fine.
Now, I'd like for the two of
you to help me with something.
[BOTH gasp]
Amazing!
Is that the legendary
item that will only bend
to your whim, Lord Momonga?
The fabled weapon of the Tomb?
[AINS]
Indeed.
It was created through
the combined efforts
of the guild's past members.
A testament of our dedication.
The Staff of Ains Ooal Gown.
Each stone in the
mouths of the seven
crowning snakes is
a god level artifact.
On top of that, the power
in the staff itself
transcends god level.
It is truly legendary.
Its base stats are on par
with any world level item.
In fact, the DPS of
its auto-attack alone
could one-shot--
[clears throat]
[AINS]
Well, anyways. That's how it is.
Incredible!
Awesome! It's so cool!
[AINS] I would like the
two of you to help me
run some tests with it.
Right! We won't
let you down, lord.
[AINS]
Also, Aura.
I've called for the other
Guardians to meet here.
They should arrive
within the hour.
Huh? Does that mean
Shalltear's coming?
[AINS]
Yes.
[MOMONGA] In Yggdrasil, if
you wanted to conjure magic
you just had to click
the appropriate icon
on your console.
But now, that icon
doesn't exist.
However, if I focus hard
enough, I don't need it.
I feel the attack
range of my spells,
their individual cooldown rates.
Even how much MP I have!
I can do this.
[AINS]
Summon! Primal Fire Elemental!
Oh, wow!
[PRIMAL FIRE ELEMENTAL roars]
[AINS]
The Primal Fire Elemental.
Its level is in the upper 80s.
[BOTH gasping, giggling]
[AINS]
So, would you like to fight it?
Yeah! I'd love to!
I just remembered,
I have a few errands
I still need to tend to. Bye!
--[AURA] C'mon!
--[MARE whimpers]
[AINS] Primal Fire Elemental.
Attack the dark elf twins!
[AURA yells]
[gasps]
[whimpers]
Magic Shield!
[AURA yells]
[MOMONGA] I had a feeling
this would be easy for them.
Now I know my other magic
skills work, as well. But...
[AINS]
"Message."
[beeping]
[MOMONGA]
No go.
I can't connect to a GM
or my guild members.
[SEBAS]
I'm here.
Is there something
you need, Lord Momonga?
[MOMONGA] Wha--? My
"Message" spell connected?
[AINS] Sebas? How do things
look on the outside?
[SEBAS] Well, lord,
there is a slight problem.
[AINS] Hm. I have called all
the Guardians to gather.
Come to the amphitheater on
the sixth floor immediately.
You can report what you
saw once you're here.
[SEBAS]
Understood.
[AINS]
Well done. That was impressive.
That was fun!
I haven't exercised
that much in a while!
[AINS]
You two must be thirsty.
[AURA]
I have to admit, Lord Momonga,
I thought you'd be scarier.
[AINS]
Oh, is that so?
I can do that if
you'd like me to.
I like you this way.
It's the best!
[AINS]
Hmph.
[SHALLTEAR] My, my. It appears
I'm the first to arrive.
[MOMONGA]
Well.
I don't have the foggiest
idea what's going on.
But it seems as if the
NPCs are all loyal to me.
Hm. In that case,
I should probably
keep playing my role and
act like a proper superior
in front of them.
While I'm at it, I'll
learn everything I can
about this world. I was
max level in Yggdrasil.
I wonder how strong
I'll be here?
And, if this is another world,
should I even try to
return to my old one?
It's not like I had anything
special back there.
I had no friends or family.
All I ever did was
work, eat, and sleep.
In all honesty, my life
wasn't worth much.
My lord. We, the Guardians,
pledge our fidelity.
I am the guardian
of the first, second,
and third floors, Shalltear
Bloodfallen. I serve and obey.
[COCYTUS]
The guardian of the fifth floor.
Cocytus. I serve and obey.
I am the guardian
of the sixth floor,
Aura Bella Fiora.
I am her brother,
and also the guardian
of the sixth floor,
Mare Bello Fiore.
[BOTH]
We serve and obey.
The guardian of
the seventh floor.
Demiurge. I serve and obey.
The leader of the Guardians.
Albedo. I serve and obey.
Other than Victim,
guardian of the eighth floor,
and Gargantua, who faithfully
guards the fourth,
all of the Guardians have
gathered as requested,
and pledged their
undying loyalty.
Supreme One, we
await your orders.
You need but to ask it
of us, and it shall be done.
[AINS]
Magic... NPCs... Items...
Now that the system of
the DMMO-RPG, Yggdrasil,
has completely changed, I must
blindly nagvigate my way
through this new world
and put on a brave front
for my Guardians.
They have pledged their
loyalty to an absolute
and Supreme Overlord.
If I don't meet
their expectations,
it could be disastrous.
I'll have to keep my composure
and move without error.
Chapter two: "Floor Guardians."