The village is burning.
[growls]
[VILLAGER 3A groaning]
Vice Chief. These
people need help.
Make sure they get back
to E-Rantel safely.
General?
What is it?
Something's wrong here.
The king ordered us to track
down and terminate the bandits
that have been attacking
villages, right?
That's correct.
Okay.
Then, why did they send us out
here with only 50 soldiers?
Especially when Baharuth
might be responsible?
[GAZEF]
It's a top-secret operation.
You know who's behind this.
The noblemen want you to fail.
If they can remove the
King's most trusted general,
then they would have a
clear path to the throne.
It's so transparent!
That's enough, Vice Chief.
But, sir, you know
I'm telling the truth.
We're walking straight
into a trap.
Our forces should head back
to E-Rantel as fast as possible.
If we split up now,
it will only weaken us.
A few villages may be lost.
That is a small price
to pay in order to keep
the most powerful swordsman
in the country alive.
[gasps]
[GAZEF]
I was born a commoner.
[VICE CHIEF]
So was I.
I know what it's like to
live in these villages.
To fear monsters at every turn,
always waiting for death.
Same here.
Then you know what
it's like to have hope,
praying that someone
out there would actually
show up to protect you.
Of course, I wished
every single day
that a hero would arrive.
But, in the end, not
one person ever came.
Then let us be the
ones who do show up.
We'll let these people know
that it's okay to have hope.
That prayers are answered.
That heroes exist.
[AINS]
Hm...
[MOMONGA] I just need
to figure out how to work
this Mirror of Remote Viewing.
Then we can really secure the
surrounding area of Nazarick.
[clapping]
Congratulations, my lord.
I knew you'd do it.
[AINS] Thanks, Sebas.
I appreciate your support.
Of course. That is my duty
as your personal butler.
The sole reason I was
created by Lord Touch Me
was to carry out your orders.
No matter how tedious
they might seem.
[AINS]
Very well.
Let's see what's happening
in this new world of ours.
[AINS]
Hm. A town festival?
No. Definitely not.
[AINS] Hm. Those men don't
appear to be bandits.
[AINS grunts]
[MOMONGA]
What's up with me?
How can I watch this
violence so calmly?
I would have passed out
at the mere sight of it
in the real world.
[AINS gasps]
[SEBAS]
What are your orders?
[AINS]
Leave them be.
I see no good reason to
interfere in their affairs.
As you wish, my lord.
[MOMONGA]
Touch Me?
[PLAYER 1B]
What an easy encounter.
[PLAYER 1D] Just two more
XP and I get to level up.
[PLAYER 1E] Then stop goofing
around and kill him already.
[MOMONGA grunts]
[PLAYER 1E]
Damn inhuman.
[PLAYER 1D]
I'll fix his mug.
[MOMONGA gasps]
[MOMONGA]
Why did you save me?
[TOUCH ME] Because saving
a person who's in trouble
is always the right thing to do!
[AINS chuckles]
[MOMONGA] I guess that now
is as good a time as any
to test my strength
in this new world.
I'd have to do it
eventually anyway.
[AINS]
Sebas. I'm paying them a visit.
Raise the security level
of Nazarick to maximum
while I'm away.
[AINS]
Tell Albedo to meet me there,
armed and ready for battle.
Then prepare the reserves.
I want soldiers who are skilled
at stealth, or can use
the "Invisibility" spell, ready
to move in at a moment's notice.
[SEBAS]
Consider it done.
[MOMONGA] I will strive to live
by your example, Touch Me.
[AINS]
Gate.
Enri!
[KNIGHT 3A laughs]
Don't look!
[ENRI'S FATHER grunts]
Run, Enri! Quickly! Take Nemu!
Now! Get away from here!
[panting]
[ENRI] I have to find a way
to save my little sister.
[KNIGHT 3A gasps]
[ENRI]
Huh?
[KNIGHT 3B]
What is that?
[BOTH whimper]
[AINS]
"Grasp Heart."
[KNIGHT 3B groans]
[MOMONGA]
Well, that's a relief.
I was afraid that ninth
tier undead spell wasn't
going to work on these humans
and I'd have to retreat.
I could always use
my melee armor,
but I'd like to save
it for another day.
[KNIGHT 3A]
It's a monster!
[MOMONGA] Hm. I felt nothing
after killing that soldier.
Interesting.
It seems as if I've
stopped being human
in both a physical
and a mental capacity.
[KNIGHT 3A whiimpers]
[AINS] What kind of man can
murder women and children
but doesn't have
the nerve to face me?
Well, I'm here now.
You'll help me test my power
whether you want to or not.
Dragon Lightning!
[KNIGHT 3A yelps]
[KNIGHT 3A screams]
[AINS] Pathetic. And that was
only a weak fifth tier spell.
[AINS] Let's try making
an undead. Death Knight!
[MOMONGA] Whoa! It's
taking over a dead body?
It didn't work like
that in Yggdrasil.
[DEATH KNIGHT groans]
[gasps]
[AINS]
Death Knight.
Kill anyone in the village
who looks like this.
[roars]
[AINS]
U-Uh...
[MOMONGA] I need to think my
orders through from now on.
What's the point of summoning
a defensive monster
if I'm just gonna send him away?
[ALBEDO] It took longer
than expected to get here.
I'm sorry you had to wait.
[AINS]
Don't apologize.
You arrived right
on time, Albedo.
[ALBEDO] Thank you for
saying so. Now then.
How would you like me to
deal with these pathetic
lower life forms?
[AINS]
These two are no threat.
The humans wearing the armor
are the enemies we are after.
[ALBEDO]
I understand.
[AINS]
It looks like you're bleeding.
Drink this.
[ENRI]
Blood?
If you insist.
I'll drink it. But my--
No, don't do it, Enri!
[MOMONGA]
What the hell is going on?
Did they forget I just
saved their lives?
Why don't they trust me?
[ALBEDO]
How dare you insult your savior!
[ENRI, NEMU gasp]
[AINS] Albedo, don't!
Lower your weapon at once.
[ALBEDO]
As you wish, my lord.
[AINS] This is not blood.
It's a healing potion.
Wow.
[AINS]
I assume the pain is gone now?
[ENRI]
Yes, it is.
[AINS] Hm. Tell me, have you
ever heard of magic before?
Uh, yes.
I have a friend who
frequents our village.
He's a pharmacist
who practices magic.
[AINS] Perfect. Then it's
not hard to understand.
I am a magical caster as well.
"Anti-Life Cocoon."
"Protection from Arrows Wall."
[AINS] I just cast two
protection spells around you.
You'll both be safe
as long as you stay put.
But, just in case,
take these, as well.
If you blow the horns, an
army of goblins will appear
to do your bidding.
Do not hesitate to
use them if needed.
[ENRI]
Excuse me!
Thank you so much for saving us.
We are forever grateful.
Thank you very much, Mister!
[AINS]
It was no problem.
Uh, wait!
May I please have the name
of the man who saved me?
[AINS]
My name?
[MOMONGA]
Yes. They should all know.
[AINS]
You shall remember it well.
And tell everyone of my powers.
I am Ains Ooal Gown!
[gasps]
[KNIGHT 3C yells]
[KNIGHTS, VILLAGERS murmuring]
[CHILDREN whimpering]
[pants]
[gasps]
[roars]
[KNIGHT 3E gasps]
[KNIGHT 3E yells]
[KNIGHT 3E groans]
[DEATH KNIGHT growls]
[whimpers]
[KNIGHT 3F]
Die!
What?
[KNIGHT 3F screams]
[KNIGHT 3G gasps, yelps]
[LONDES] It's only
killing the men in armor
and it's enjoying it!
[KNIGHT 3H]
Gods, help us all!
[KNIGHT 3I]
We're doomed!
[BELIUS]
You idiots!
Hurry up and take
down that monster!
[KNIGHTS gasp]
This can't be happening.
I'm too rich to die
in a hellhole like this.
You men! Get over here, now!
Be my shield so I can escape!
Stand your ground, Belius!
[BELIUS whimpers]
[whimpers] Protect me!
I have money.
I'll give you 200 gold pieces!
No, make that 500 gold!
[screams] Screw it!
I'll pay 1,000!
[LIVING CORPSE 3A groans]
[screams]
[BELIUS groans]
Don't just stand there.
Help me! Please!
[BELIUS screaming]
Money. Take it all. Save me!
[KNIGHT 3I]
No! No way! I can't do it.
[KNIGHT 3H]
Screw this!
Hold steady!
[KNIGHTS gasp]
Stay strong!
We will stand our ground
and defend our brothers.
Let's give the archers
time to retreat.
Prepare for battle!
[KNIGHTS grunt]
[KNIGHT 3I screams]
[KNIGHT 3J groans]
[KNIGHT 3H groans]
[yells]
[LONDES groans]
[AINS] Stop, Death Knight!
You've served me well.
[KNIGHTS gasping]
[VILLAGERS gasp]
[AINS]
My name is Ains Ooal Gown.
It is a pleasure
to meet all of you.
Don't worry about
my Death Knight.
No harm will come to you now.
Tell your supervi--
I mean, owner of my kindness.
However, next time you commit
such heinous acts in this area,
I will bring death
to your entire kingdom.
Leave. Make sure you speak
my name to everyone.
[KNIGHTS scream]
[MOMONGA sighs]
Acting is a tough gig.
[VILLAGE CHIEF]
Uh, pardon me, sir.
[AINS]
Hm?
Why did you come here?
[AINS] I could not stand by
and watch innocent people
be murdered. Call it
a "moral obligation."
[VILLAGERS gasp]
[AINS] Be at ease. This village
is under my protection.
You no longer need to be scared.
[VILLAGERS gasp]
[AINS sighs]
[AINS] I don't do this kind
of work for free though.
I expect to be compensated
for my efforts.
[VILLAGERS murmur, laugh]
[MOMONGA] As I thought,
the villagers don't question
my intentions as long as
they think I'm doing this
for financial gain.
They would react
negatively if they saw
my real face, even though
it was common in Yggdrassil.
It's too bad I didn't
think of concealing it
before stepping in
to this situation.
It's a pain, but I'll
have to use a spell
to keep those girls quiet.
Here's hoping
memory-wiping magic
works in this place.
[AINS] I requested money
from the village so as
not to arouse any suspicions.
But information was
what I was truly after.
I am unfamiliar
with this new world
and need to learn all
I can about the area.
Failing to educate myself
will only make me weak
to any enemies.
The village chief and his
wife believed my story
about being a hermit who
was quite knowledgeable
about magic, but
who knew nothing
of the world around him.
They were eager to educate
me about this village
and the surrounding areas.
I wonder though.
[MOMONGA] What kind of people
use magic in this world
that these peasants would
so easily trust me?
Even though my face is concealed
by this cursed mask, they
dropped their guard just because
I claimed to be a magic caster.
In Yggdrasil, even n00bs
could get this mask
by staying logged in
over Christmas Eve.
Sadly, I quickly learned
that all of my Yggdrasil
currency was useless here.
Of course, the gold
itself has some value,
but it could be dangerous
to flash the coins around.
After that, I asked about
the surrounding territories.
There are three realms.
Nazarick, and this village,
known as Carne,
are part of the
Re-Estize Kingdom border.
On the other side of
said border is the domain
adjacent to the
great mountain range
that runs north and south.
The Baharuth Empire.
The two countries are on
bad terms to say the least.
They've hated each other for
years and they often battle
on the open plains
between them near
the capital city of E-Rantel.
There is one final country.
The Slane Theocracy, which
is located to the south
of both provinces.
The village chief assumed
the Baharuth Empire
was responsible for
the attack based on
the crests of the
Knight's shields.
However, there's
a possibility that
the Slane Theocracy staged this
event to maintain hostilities
between Re-Estize and Baharuth.
If I had thought to
take a knight hostage
for questioning, we
would have found out
for sure who was responsible.
Is there something
bothering you?
[AINS]
No. Everything is fine.
Is there anything
else of importance
that I should know
about this region?
[VILLAGE CHIEF]
Let's see.
The closest city to our village
is the capital, E-Rantel.
Goblins, orcs and ogres
inhabit the area.
But you should be safe
if you stay on the road.
The adventurers
hunt on that land
and do a good job of
keeping those bastards'
populations in check.
[AINS]
Adventurers?
They're mercenaries
who deal with
monsters in exchange
for payment.
If you're interested in
hiring some of them,
there's a guild in
E-Rantel where you can
request their services.
[AINS]
An Adventurer's Guild?
And just how big of
a city is E-Rantel?
I'm not sure.
Definitely larger
than our village.
[AINS]
I suspected that.
[MOMONGA]
If I want to find out more,
I'll have to make a home
for myself in the capital.
[AINS] I could use my
Wand of Resurrection.
It would breathe life back
into the dead villagers.
However, these people
may not be as trusting
of a magic user who's
as good at reversing death
as he is at bringing it.
I can only imagine
how much trouble
I'd get myself into
if I cast it.
[ENRI, NEMU sobbing]
[AINS]
For now, I'll restrain myself.
They should all be
content with the fact
that I saved their village.
[MOMONGA] Thanks to my good
deed, the story of how
Ains Ooal Gown saved
Carne Village will spread
across the countryside.
My reputation
should grow quickly.
And if there are other
players from Yggdrasil
stuck in this world,
they will hopefully hear
of me and seek me out.
I shouldn't kill any more
humans unless necessary.
I wouldn't wanna
antagonize any players.
Also. A man with a
reputation needs a cause.
One that would allow
me to win the support
of one of the countries.
[MOMONGA sighs]
I'm exhausted.
[AINS] Today's mission
was a great success.
Let's head back home, Albedo.
[ALBEDO]
Right away, my lord.
[VILLAGER 3D panting]
Hey there.
[AINS]
You seem to dislike humans.
[ALBEDO]
What's to like about them?
They are weak and pathetic.
Just tiny insects that exist
to be crushed under foot.
[AINS]
Listen to me.
I want you to show them
respect. Act if you need to.
But I demand that you treat
the humans with kindness.
[ALBEDO grunts]
[MOMONGA] It feels hypocritical
to ask that of her
when I don't have
feelings for them either.
Must be a side effect
from being an undead.
What are we going to do, Chief?
I'm afraid I don't have a plan.
[AINS]
The problems keep stacking up.
Village Chief. Is there
something wrong here?
Lord Ains! Thank goodness!
I was just told
there are more soldiers
heading toward the village
at breakneck speed.
[AINS]
Is that so?
[AINS] Don't worry, I can
handle this situation.
Please gather the surviving
villagers around your house.
When you're done, come
meet me at the town square.
Yes, of course.
[gasps]
I am the Chief
Royal Warrior from
the Re-Estize Kingdom.
Gazef Stronoff.
The King has ordered me
to hunt down the knights
that have been attacking
surrounding villages.
Your people are safe now.
We will do all we
can to protect you.
Thank you, General Gazef.
[AINS grunts]
Are you the chief
of this village?
Who is this man
standing beside you?
He looks peculiar.
This gentleman saved--
[AINS]
No need to worry about that now.
It is a pleasure to make
your acquaintance, General.
My name is Ains Ooal Gown.
I'm a simple magic user
who stumbled upon this town
while it was being
ransacked by those knights.
What?
These people would have
been lost without you.
Thank you, Sir Ains.
[GAZEF'S SUBORDINATE]
General!
Huh?
We've spotted a large army
of unknown origin,
and they're surrounding
the village even as we speak!
[MOMONGA gasps]
[AINS] The Slane Theocracy's
special ops unit
carried out the attack
on Carne Village
in order to draw out Gazef,
the cheif warrior of
the Re-Estize Kingdom.
Though he's aware of the trap,
Gazef bravely attacks the enemy
in order to protect
the villagers.
But I care little for the
humans and their squables.
This is an opportunity for me
to test the powers
of Ains Ooal Gown!
I shall not waste it.
Chapter four: "Ruler of Death."