CHIYU, LOOK...
I’M NOT TALKING
TO YOU, HARU.
OH!
HMM? SO THAT’S WHAT YOU
THINK OF ME?
THAT I’M TOYING
WITH ARITA TO AMUSE MYSELF?
IF I’M WRONG, TELL ME.
I KNOW HARU,
AND THERE’S NOTHING
HE HATES MORE
THAN BEING THE CENTER
OF ATTENTION.
I SEE.
WELL, EVEN IF YOU’RE
RIGHT ABOUT ME,
I FAIL TO SEE
HOW THIS CONCERNS YOU.
OF COURSE IT DOES.
I’VE KNOWN HARU LONGER
THAN ANYONE ELSE
IN THIS ENTIRE SCHOOL.
HE’S MY FRIEND.
OH...YOU’RE HIS FRIEND.
WELL I’M SORRY, BUT I’M
MORE THAN JUST HIS FRIEND.
THE TRUTH IS I’VE
ASKED ARITA, HERE,
TO BE MY BOYFRIEND.
AND WE’RE ABOUT TO HAVE
OUR FIRST DATE.
( gasps )
( gasping )
( whimpers )
( thinking )
OH GOD, OH GOD,
I DON’T BELIEVE IT.
NOW I’M GONNA
HAVE TO CHANGE SCHOOLS!
YOU HAVE A NICE DAY...
( whimpering )
FRIEND.
HMM.
Haru: WHAT WERE YOU
THINKING BACK THERE?
YOU DO REALIZE YOU CAN’T
SOLVE EVERY PROBLEM YOU HAVE
BY ACCELERATING YOUR WAY
OUT OF IT, RIGHT?
YES, THAT’S A CRITICAL LESSON
THAT ALL BURST LINKERS
MUST LEARN.
IT’S GOOD YOU
UNDERSTAND THAT.
UH, NO.
THERE’S NOTHING
GOOD ABOUT THIS.
LOOK, I PROVOKED KURASHIMA
FOR A REASON.
THERE’S SOMETHING ABOUT HER,
SO I EGGED HER ON,
AND NOW I’VE CONFIRMED
MY SUSPICIONS.
HUH? WHY WOULD YOU
BE SUSPICIOUS OF CHIYU?
SHE WOULDN’T
DO ANYTHING WRONG.
OH? ARE YOU TWO
MORE THAN JUST FRIENDS?
NO, NO, NO!
IT’S NOTHING LIKE THAT!
I’VE JUST KNOWN HER
FOR AGES!
A-AND BESIDES, SHE’S
ALREADY GOT A BOYFRIEND!
WELL THAT’S GOOD TO KNOW,
BUT EACH OF YOU HAVE CAUGHT
MY ATTENTION FOR COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT REASONS.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
IT’S A LITTLE
DIFFICULT TO EXPLAIN,
BUT JUST KNOW
THAT IT HAS TO DO
WITH ONE OF THE REASONS
I’VE SOUGHT YOU OUT.
OH...
♪
( singing in Japanese )
Kuroyukihime:
HERE’S TO YOUR
FIRST VICTORY.
AT THIS RATE, YOU’LL
REACH LEVEL TWO IN NO TIME.
UH, YEAH, THANK YOU.
BUT I STILL HAVE A LOT
TO LEARN BEFORE GETTING
THAT FAR.
YOU DO HAVE A HARD
JOURNEY AHEAD OF YOU.
OF THE ESTIMATED
1,000 BURST LINKERS
THAT ARE OUT THERE,
ONLY A SELECT FEW HAVE EVER
MADE IT TO LEVEL FOUR.
AND IF YOU RUN INTO A PLAYER
FROM LEVEL SEVEN OR EIGHT,
IT’S SAFE TO ASSUME
THEY’RE A LEGION LEADER.
W-WHAT’S A LEGION?
IT’S SORT OF LIKE A TEAM
THAT YOU WOULD FIND
IN OTHER ONLINE GAMES.
IT’S JUST THAT HERE
WE CALL THEM "LEGIONS."
CURRENTLY, THE ACCELERATED
WORLD HAS SIX MAJOR LEGIONS
RULING OVER A NUMBER
OF DIFFERENT ZONES.
ALL THESE LEGIONS
ARE LED BY BURST LINKERS
WHO HAVE REACHED LEVEL NINE.
EACH HAS THEIR OWN COLOR:
BLUE, RED, YELLOW, GREEN,
PURPLE, AND WHITE.
THEY’RE KNOWN
AS THE "SIX KINGS
OF PURE COLOR."
I’VE NEVER HEARD
OF A GAME LIKE THIS,
WHERE ONLY SIX PEOPLE
HAVE EVER REACHED
THE HIGHEST LEVEL.
NOT SO FAST.
I NEVER SAID LEVEL NINE
WAS THE HIGHEST LEVEL.
WELL, HOW MANY PEOPLE
ARE AT LEVEL TEN, THEN?
BRAIN BURST 2039
IS SOMETHING PEOPLE
HAVE BEEN PLAYING
FOR SEVEN YEARS NOW,
EVER SINCE THE PROGRAM
WAS ANONYMOUSLY RELEASED.
BUT DUE TO THE SEVERE RULES
THAT COME WITH THE GAME,
NO ONE HAS EVER
REACHED LEVEL TEN.
IS THAT BECAUSE YOU
HAVE TO FIGHT ALL THE TIME?
HAVE, LIKE, 10,000 WINS
OR SOMETHING?
YOU ONLY NEED FIVE WINS,
BUT THOSE WINS HAVE TO BE
AGAINST LEVEL NINE OPPONENTS.
AND IF YOU LOSE JUST
ONE OF THOSE FIGHTS,
YOU LOSE ALL YOUR POINTS.
AND THEN THE PROGRAM
AUTOMATICALLY UNINSTALLS.
( gasps softly )
Kuroyukihime:
THIS PROGRAM HAS REMAINED
A SECRET FOR SEVEN YEARS.
IT’S QUITE A FEAT.
ANY IDEA HOW THEY’VE DONE IT?
NO.
BECAUSE IT HAS SOME
VERY DEMANDING REQUIREMENTS.
LIKE WHAT?
I’D SAY ONE OF THE MOST
SIGNIFICANT REQUIREMENTS
IS THAT EVERY BURST LINK PLAYER
HAS TO HAVE WORN A NEURO-LINKER
FROM THE DAY THEY WERE BORN.
THE NEURO-LINKER IS STILL
A FAIRLY NEW TECHNOLOGY.
EVEN THE FIRST-GENERATION
DEVICE ONLY CAME OUT
15 YEARS AGO.
THAT MEANS NO ADULT
HAS EVERY PLAYED BRAIN BURST.
ALL OF US WHO PLAY THE GAME
ARE KIDS.
AND BECAUSE OF THIS,
WE TRY TO KEEP THAT PRIVILEGE
TO OURSELVES.
AND ONCE THE PROGRAM
UNINSTALLS, IT LEAVES
ABSOLUTELY NO TRACE.
WHATEVER YOU SAY ABOUT IT
WILL BE DISMISSED AS NONSENSE.
TWO YEARS AGO,
ALL THE YOUNG KINGS
REACHED LEVEL NINE
AT APPROXIMATELY
THE SAME TIME.
THEY SOON RECEIVED A SYSTEM
MESSAGE TELLING THEM
THE HORRIBLE RULES IN PLACE
FOR REACHING LEVEL TEN.
YOU WOULD’VE EXPECTED SOME
SORT OF BLOODY POWER STRUGGLE
TO BREAK OUT,
BUT INSTEAD THE KINGS
CHOSE TO REMAIN
AT LEVEL NINE INDEFINITELY.
THEY CALLED A TRUCE AND DIVIDED
THE ACCELERATED WORLD
INTO REALMS EACH OF THEM
WOULD RULE.
THE WHOLE THING’S A FARCE.
FIRST THEY DESTROY
COUNTLESS BURST LINKERS
TO REACH LEVEL NINE,
AND THEN THEY CREATE A TRUCE?
WHY?
( gulps )
SO IS THAT IT?
IS THAT WHAT YOU’RE PLANNING?
TO CHALLENGE THE SIX
KINGS OF PURE COLOR?
NO. I’VE ALREADY DONE THAT.
WHAT?
THERE HAVEN’T ALWAYS
BEEN SIX.
THERE USED TO BE SEVEN KINGS,
AND DESPITE THE FACT THAT THEY
WERE EACH ESSENTIALLY RIVALS,
THERE WAS ALSO A STRONG BOND
BETWEEN THEM.
BUT THAT CHANGED
TWO YEARS AGO.
ONE NIGHT, THE BLACK KING
BETRAYED THE OTHERS AND TRIED
TO HUNT THEM ALL DOWN.
WHO IS THIS BLACK KING?
I’M THE BLACK KING,
OTHERWISE KNOWN
AS "BLACK LOTUS."
I WAS THE ONLY ONE
WHO REJECTED THE TRUCE,
AND INSTEAD ARGUED THAT
WE SHOULD RISK IT ALL
AND FIGHT TO THE END.
BUT THEY OVERRULED MY IDEA,
AND WHEN THEY DID,
I BEHEADED THE RED KING,
THE PERSON CLOSEST TO ME
CALLING FOR PEACE.
( breathing heavily )
HIS BRAIN BURST PROGRAM
WAS INSTANTLY UNINSTALLED,
WHICH CAUSE HIS GIRLFRIEND,
THE PURPLE KING,
TO SCREAM IN ANGUISH.
THE BLUE KING BECAME ENRAGED.
I FOUGHT IN A FURIOUS FRENZY,
BUT IN THE END, I WAS UNABLE
TO DEFEAT ANYONE ELSE.
AFTER 30 MINUTES HAD PASSED,
I LINKED OUT.
AND EVER SINCE THAT DAY,
I’VE BEEN ON THE RUN, HIDING.
I’VE BEEN BRANDED
THE GREATEST TRAITOR
IN THE ACCELERATED WORLD.
AS A RESULT,
THERE IS AN ENORMOUS
BOUNTY ON MY HEAD.
A FITTING END
FOR A COWARD LIKE ME.
WHY DID YOU DO THAT?
BECAUSE THE ONLY
THING I CARED ABOUT
WAS REACHING LEVEL TEN.
ACCORDING TO THE SYSTEM MESSAGE
WE RECEIVED WHEN WE MADE LEVEL
NINE,
ANY PLAYER WHO MANAGED
TO REACH LEVEL TEN
WOULD HAVE THE CHANCE TO MEET
THE CREATOR OF BRAIN BURST.
AND IN THAT MEETING,
YOU WOULD FIND OUT
THE TRUE MEANING OF THE GAME,
AS WELL AS ITS ULTIMATE
GOAL AND PURPOSE.
I’M STILL DESPERATE
TO FIND THE ANSWER.
WE EACH ACCELERATE AND FIGHT
FOR VARIOUS REASONS.
SOMETIMES IT’S FOR MONEY.
SOMETIMES IT’S FOR SUCCESS.
SOMETIMES FOR FAME.
BUT IS THAT ALL THERE IS?
IT CAN’T BE!
THERE HAS TO BE MORE.
SOMETHING GREATER THAN WHAT
OUR MERE MORTAL COILS
COULD HAVE EVER HOPED FOR.
( gasps softly )
( thinking )
YOU KNOW, I GET IT.
MAYBE NOT ALL OF IT,
BUT I GET WHERE SHE’S
COMING FROM.
I KNOW WHAT SHE MEANS.
WELL, HAVE I THOROUGHLY
DISGUSTED YOU?
DO YOU DESPISE ME NOW?
NO. IT DOESN’T MATTER
WHAT THE GAME IS.
IT’S STUPID TO GIVE UP
AND WANDER AROUND AIMLESSLY
WITHOUT TRYING
TO FINISH THE GAME.
REACHING THE HIGHEST LEVEL
HAS TO BE WHAT BRAIN BURST
IS ALL ABOUT.
WHY ELSE WOULD IT EXIST?
OH.
( chuckles )
I DON’T BELIEVE IT.
YOU’RE ALREADY MORE
OF A BURST LINKER THAN I AM.
HEY, I’M TRYING
TO BE SERIOUS, HERE.
LOOK, I THINK I SEE
WHERE YOU’RE COMING FROM,
AND I’LL CONTINUE
TO HELP YOU OUT.
IF I CAN, I’D LIKE
TO REACH LEVEL TEN
MYSELF SOME DAY.
THANK YOU.
( gasps softly)
I TRULY APPRECIATE THIS,
HARUYUKI.
I TRUSTED MY INSTINCTS,
AND THEY WERE RIGHT.
I’M QUITE PLEASED
THAT OF ALL THE PEOPLE,
I CHOSE YOU.
( stammering )
YEAH, OKAY, THAT’S GREAT.
A-ANYWAY, LET’S GET BACK
TO THE TOPIC AT HAND.
( sighs )
AS I WAS SAYING,
I’VE MANAGED TO SURVIVE
THESE PAST TWO YEARS,
BUT IT HASN’T BEEN
BY ACCEPTING CHALLENGERS
AND WINNING FIGHTS.
I’M ONLY AROUND
BECAUSE FOR TWO YEARS,
I HAVEN’T MADE A SINGLE
CONNECTION TO THE GLOBAL NET.
REALLY?! NOT EVEN ONCE?
NO, BUT DUE
TO MY SOCIAL STATUS,
I CAN’T STAY
COMPLETELY OFFLINE.
THERE IS ONE NETWORK
I MUST CONNECT TO
ON A DAILY BASIS.
YOUR SOCIAL STATUS?
WHAT, ARE YOU SECRETLY
ROYALTY OR SOMETHING?
DON’T BE SILLY.
OH, RIGHT,
YOU’RE TALKING
ABOUT SCHOOL STUFF.
THEIR LOCAL NET.
WAIT--YOU MEAN
THAT’S NOT SAFE?
IT WOULD SEEM IT ISN’T.
TWO MONTHS AGO,
SOMEONE USED THE SCHOOL’S
LOCAL NET TO CHALLENGE ME
TO A DUEL.
THAT MEANS WHOEVER IT WAS
ATTENDS OUR SCHOOL.
Haru: NO WAY!
( gasps )
ACCELERATION!
AT SCHOOL?
WHY CHALLENGE ME HERE?
( grunts )
OH, NO!
Kuroyukihime:
ONE OF THE FUNCTIONS
WITHIN BRAIN BURST
IS THE ABILITY TO SWITCH
TO A DUMMY AVATAR
FOR SPECTATING
AND WATCHING FIGHTS.
THIS ALLOWS YOU
TO WATCH A FIGHT WHILE
HIDING YOUR REAL IDENTITY.
HOWEVER, WHEN I WAS ATTACKED,
( grunts )
I HAD MY DUMMY AVATAR
SET TO THE EXACT SAME ONE
I USE ON THE LOCAL SCHOOL NET.
SO THEN...
THAT MEANS--
EXACTLY.
WHOEVER IT WAS
KNOWS MY TRUE IDENTITY.
THEY KNOW
I AM REALLY BLACK LOTUS.
TO REVEAL YOUR TRUE IDENTITY
IS THE ULTIMATE TABOO
FOR A BURST LINKER.
( grunts )
I WAS CARELESS TO THINK
THAT I WOULD NOT BE CHALLENGED
INSIDE THE LOCAL SCHOOL NET.
I’M NOW CONSTANTLY
ON GUARD FOR AN ATTACK
IN THE REAL WORLD.
THAT CAN HAPPEN?
YOU CAN GET ATTACKED
IN THE REAL WORLD?
IT CAN, BUT NO ONE
HAS TRIED TO ATTACK
ME THERE, YET.
THAT ISN’T THE CASE
FOR THE SCHOOL NET.
IN THE PAST TWO MONTHS,
THIS PERSON HAS CHALLENGED
ME MORE THAN TEN TIMES.
NOW THAT THEY KNOW
MY REAL IDENTITY,
THEY ARE PROBABLY
AFTER MY BURST POINTS.
WELL WHY DON’T YOU
JUST DEFEAT THEM
USING YOUR DUEL AVATAR?
THEN THEY WOULD GO AWAY.
IF I DO THAT, THEY
WILL MOST LIKELY GIVE UP
ON TRYING TO CHALLENGE ME
AND INSTEAD SELL MY REAL
IDENTITY TO ONE OF THE KINGS.
SO, WHAT’S YOUR PLAN, THEN?
IF YOU’VE BEEN EXPOSED,
YOU HAVE ONLY ONE OPTION:
TO FIND OUT YOUR ENEMY’S
REAL IDENTITY AS WELL.
OF COURSE!
THEN THEY’D HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO LEAVE YOU ALONE.
SO, THAT SHOULD BE
PRETTY EASY TO DO, RIGHT?
IS IT?
YEAH. YOU JUST NEED EVERYONE
IN THE SAME PLACE.
SO DURING A SCHOOL ASSEMBLY,
USE THE SCHOOL’S NETWORK
TO CHALLENGE THEM.
IT SHOULD WORK SINCE ALL
STUDENTS ARE REQUIRED TO STAY
LOGGED IN DURING SCHOOL HOURS.
AND ONCE A PLAYER
RECEIVES A CHALLENGE,
THEY CAN’T TURN IT DOWN.
THE GAME WILL SHOW YOU
WHERE THEIR AVATAR IS SITTING,
AND YOU CAN USE THAT
TO FIND OUT WHO THE STUDENT IS.
HMM. VERY IMPRESSIVE.
I THOUGHT THE SAME THING,
BUT IT TOOK ME AN ENTIRE DAY
TO COME UP WITH THAT PLAN.
SO THEN YOU TRIED IT?
I DID, AND WHAT I FOUND
WAS ASTONISHING.
TELL ME.
WHO WAS IT?
NO ONE.
HUH?
THERE WAS ONLY ONE PLAYER
ON THE MATCHING LIST,
AND THAT WAS ME.
BUT THERE’S MORE:
I COULDN’T FIND
THIS PERSON’S NAME
ON THE LIST,
EVEN AFTER GETTING
OUT OF THERE WITH A DRAW.
IT SEEMS WHOEVER THIS IS,
THEY’RE CLEVER.
THEY FIGURED OUT
HOW TO BLOCK A CHALLENGE.
( sighs )
IS THAT EVEN POSSIBLE?
IF IT IS, IT MEANS
THEY’RE AN INCREDIBLY
TALENTED HACKER,
GOOD ENOUGH TO CRACK
A REPORTEDLY IMPENETRABLE
PROGRAM.
OR THEY SOMEHOW
KNOW THE GAME’S CREATOR.
SO I’M GUESSING THIS IS HOW
I FIT IN TO ALL THIS.
YOU WANT ME TO HELP YOU
FIND OUT WHO THIS ENEMY IS,
RIGHT?
YES, VERY GOOD.
THE NAME OF THIS AVATAR
IS CYAN PILE,
A LEVEL FOUR BURST LINKER
WHO, GOING OFF THEIR COLOR,
IS BEST
AT CLOSE-RANGE COMBAT.
LEVEL FOUR, HUH?
AND FROM WHAT I’VE GATHERED,
THIS PERSON IS A LITTLE
DESPERATE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
THEY’RE AFRAID THEY’RE
GOING TO LOSE THE POWER
TO ACCELERATE.
I CAN TELL BY THEIR MANIC
FIGHTING STYLE.
IT’S VERY TYPICAL OF A PLAYER
WHO IS LOW ON POINTS.
OKAY, GOT IT.
IS THERE ANYTHING ELSE
I NEED TO KNOW?
YES...DON’T FORGET
ABOUT THE GUIDE CURSOR.
IT’S AN EXCELLENT
SOURCE OF INFORMATION.
IT’LL POINT TO YOUR ENEMY’S
LOCATION IMMEDIATELY
AFTER A FIGHT STARTS.
USE IT.
OH, I GET IT.
SINCE ALL THESE STAGES
ARE BASED OFF REALITY--
EXACTLY. BY REMEMBERING
WHERE THE CURSOR WAS POINTING,
YOU CAN TRACK DOWN
YOUR OPPONENT
IN THE REAL WORLD, AS WELL.
AFTER I WAS ATTACKED,
I MADE A LIST
OF ALL THE STUDENTS THAT
WERE IN THE SAME VICINITY
AS ME AT THE TIME,
THEN I USED THAT LIST
TO COME UP WITH THE MOST
LIKELY SUSPECT.
THE NEXT TIME I’M ATTACKED,
HARUYUKI,
YOU NEED TO BE THERE,
AND I WANT YOU TO USE
THE AUTO-VIEW
TO OBSERVE THE FIGHT.
THAT WAY, YOU CAN
RECORD THE DIRECTION
OF CYAN PILE’S CURSOR.
YEAH, IF WE HAVE TWO
POINTS OF REFERENCE...
THEN WE CAN PINPOINT
THE LOCATION,
AND IN RETURN, FIND OUT
WHICH STUDENT WAS THERE
AT THE TIME...
AND WE CAN CONFIRM
CYAN PILE’S IDENTITY.
( grunts softly )
LAST WEEK,
BEFORE I APPROACHED YOU,
I CREATED A FILE
ON WHOM I THOUGHT
WAS THE MOST LIKELY SUSPECT.
( grunts softly )
( beeping )
( gasps )
CHIYU, A BURST LINKER?
NO WAY!
THERE’S BEEN A MISTAKE!
THAT’S IMPOSSIBLE!
SHE’S, LIKE, TERRIBLE AT GAMES.
A-AND SHE’S NOT A STALKER,
EITHER!
SHE JUST ISN’T
THAT KIND OF PERSON.
I SWEAR IT!
REALLY?
YOU SAW IT FOR YOURSELF--
HOW HOSTILE
SHE WAS TOWARD ME.
YEAH, BUT THAT’S
NOT WHY SHE WAS UPSET!
IT’S BECAUSE YOU AND I
HAD CABLE LINKED TOGETHER.
WHY WOULD THAT BOTHER HER?
YOU SAID YOURSELF THAT
SHE HAS HER OWN BOYFRIEND.
WELL...THAT’S TRUE.
BUT, STILL...
ALL RIGHT, STEP BACK
AND LOOK AT THIS
FROM ANOTHER ANGLE.
MAYBE SHE GOT UPSET
BECAUSE SHE WAS PLANNING
TO RECRUIT YOU FOR HERSELF,
BUT THEN I CAME IN AND RUINED
EVERYTHING BY SNATCHING YOU UP
FOR MY PURPOSES,
WHICH COMPELLED HER
TO GET MAD AND CONFRONT ME.
IT’S PLAUSIBLE, ISN’T IT?
YEAH, I GUESS.
I NEED TO FIND THIS OUT
ON MY OWN, THOUGH.
REALLY? YOU KNOW
YOU CAN’T JUST GO
AND ASK HER DIRECTLY, RIGHT?
YEAH, OF COURSE
I KNOW THAT.
BUT IF THE TWO OF US
CABLE LINK,
THEN I CAN CHECK HER MEMORY
FOR THE PROGRAM.
THAT’S TRUE.
SO...I’LL GO
AND CABLE LINK WITH HER.
( whimpers )
OH, MAN... WHY DID
I SAY I WOULD DO THIS?
A CABLE LINK?!
( moans )
Taku: HARU?
HUH?
HEY, TAKU!
THE NEXT KENDO TOURNAMENT
YOU HAVE IS GONNA
BE THE NATIONALS, RIGHT?
YEAH, BUT I DON’T KNOW
HOW WELL I’LL DO IN THAT ONE,
THOUGH.
OH, COME ON.
I’M SURE YOU’RE
GONNA BE FINE.
KNOWING YOU,
YOU’LL PROBABLY END UP
WINNING THE NATIONAL TITLE.
DON’T MAKE IT SOUND EASY,
’CAUSE IT WON’T BE.
( grunting softly )
( sighs, gulping )
AHH, THAT HIT THE SPOT.
TASTES EVEN BETTER
SINCE YOU’RE THE ONE
WHO PAID FOR IT.
HUH?
( whimpers )
OH, WHAT DO I DO?
I’M SO NERVOUS.
I’M REALLY WORRIED.
WILL I WIN OR LOSE?
( grunts )
( stammers )
( sighs, laughs )
OH, COME ON.
STOP MESSING WITH ME.
( laughs )
THANKS FOR THE DRINK.
( children laughing,
chattering )
Girl: ...KEEP UP!
I’M TRYING.
Haru: TAKU?
YEAH?
LOOK...
DO YOU THINK THAT CHIYU...
WELL, DO YOU THINK SHE WOULD
EVER WANT SOMETHING BAD ENOUGH
SHE WOULD LIE, OR DECEIVE
A PERSON TO GET IT?
( sighs )
I DON’T KNOW.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
OF COURSE SHE WOULDN’T!
THEN I GUESS YOU
HAVE YOUR ANSWER, DON’T YOU?
UH--
OH YEAH. YOU’RE RIGHT.
HUH. SORRY I EVEN ASKED.
( chuckles )
FORGET I BROUGHT IT UP.
IT’S FINE.
THAT’S WHAT FRIENDS ARE FOR.
ISN’T THAT RIGHT?
UH--
HMM. RIGHT.
NOW, THEN...AHH...
I THINK I’LL TAKE OFF
AND RUN ANOTHER LAP OR TWO.
OKAY.
GOOD LUCK AT THE TOURNAMENT.
I’M SURE YOU’LL BE GREAT!
THANKS, TAKU.
OF COURSE IT’S NOT HER.
THERE’S NO WAY.
Chiyuri: WHY DIDN’T YOU
GET BACK TO ME LAST NIGHT?!
I TRIED TEXT, CALLING--
EVERYTHING!
REALLY?
I SENT YOU AN EMAIL, TOO.
( sighs )
SORRY.
WELL, SPIT IT OUT.
WHY’D YOU COME HERE?
WELL, I WAS WONDERING
IF YOU WOULD...
CABLE LINK WITH ME!
( gasps, stammers )
I CAN’T BELIEVE THE ONLY WAY
YOU CAN APOLOGIZE
IS BY CABLE LINK.
YOU SHOULD HAVE AT LEAST
BROUGHT A CABLE WITH YOU,
THEN.
AAH!
( whimpers )
I HAVE TO WARN YOU--
THE ONLY CABLE I HAVE
IS THIS ONE.
B-BUT THAT’S SO SHORT!
IS THAT THE ONE
YOU USE WITH TAKU?
NO, OF COURSE NOT,
YOU IDIOT!
TAKU BRINGS HIS OWN CABLE,
AND IT’S LIKE A METER LONG!
( yelling, whimpering )
( grunts )
LET’S GO!
GET ON WITH IT.
( grunts )
OKAY...
YOU DON’T WANNA DO THIS
SITTING IN A CHAIR OR SOMETHING?
HMM?
WELL, HERE GOES.
UM...
( grunts softly )
( grunting, whimpering )
SORRY...ALMOST GOT IT.
( clicks )
( gasps )
♪
LISTEN, I’M REALLY SORRY
ABOUT THE OTHER DAY...
RUINING THAT LUNCH
YOU MADE FOR ME.
( Haru thinking )
IS THERE A BRAIN BURST
FOLDER ANYWHERE IN HERE?
I WAS UPSET...
I REALIZED YOU HAD
TOLD TAKU ABOUT ARAYA.
THEN I IMAGINED THE TWO
OF YOU TALKING ABOUT ME.
THE LAST THING I WANT
IS TO FEEL
LIKE I’M PITIED.
I WANT THE THREE OF US
TO BE EQUALS.
I DON’T WANNA FEEL LIKE
I’M DIFFERENT.
HARU,
YOU HAVE IT ALL WRONG...
I DIDN’T TELL TAKKUN
ABOUT YOU BEING
BULLIED AT SCHOOL.
HE ONLY KNEW ABOUT THE LUNCH
BECAUSE WHEN I WAS AT HIS
TOURNAMENT,
I TOLD HIM I WAS GONNA
MAKE ONE FOR YOU, TOO.
WHAT?
DO YOU KNOW HOW LONG IT’S BEEN
SINCE YOU’VE TALKED WITH ME
LIKE THIS?
SINCE YOU’VE SHARED
ANYTHING ABOUT YOURSELF?
YEAH, I KNOW YOU’RE
HAVING A TOUGH TIME AT SCHOOL.
BUT STILL, I’D NEVER
TALK TO ANYONE ELSE ABOUT IT.
BESIDES, I KNOW IF I DID
YOU WOULD JUST HATE ME
FOR INTERFERING.
( whimpering )
BUT, HARU, YOU’RE
NOT BEING FAIR TO ME!
YOU SAID THINGS WOULD
NEVER CHANGE BETWEEN US--
THAT WE WOULD
ALWAYS BE FRIENDS.
( whimpers )
I JUST DIDN’T WANT
THINGS TO BE DIFFERENT.
I WANTED EVERYTHING
TO STAY THE SAME.
( sighs )
THE THREE OF US...
TOGETHER FOREVER.
BUT NOW YOU’RE WITH THAT GIRL
ALL THE TIME.
HERE I’VE BEEN WORRIED
ABOUT YOU FOR YEARS,
AND SHE SOLVES
ALL YOUR PROBLEMS
IN ONE DAY!
IT’S NOT LIKE THAT!
IT’S JUST THAT SHE’S
THE STUDENT VICE PRESIDENT.
THEN WHY ARE YOU
LETTING HER DO THIS?!
SHE DRAGS YOU AROUND
LIKE YOU’RE HER PET,
AND ALL SHE EVER DOES
IS TELL YOU WHAT TO DO!
NO, YOU DON’T UNDERSTAND!
IT...REALLY
DOESN’T BOTHER ME.
BUT IT BOTHERS ME!
( gasps )
YOU STARTED AVOIDING ME
EVER SINCE WE GOT
INTO JUNIOR HIGH!
( crying )
AND YOU STOPPED
COMING BY MY HOUSE.
WHAT WAS I SUPPOSED TO DO?
UH--YOU’VE GOT A BOYFRIEND NOW.
BUT YOU WERE THE ONE WHO SAID
THAT NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENED
BETWEEN THE THREE OF US,
WE WOULD ALWAYS BE FRIENDS!
WERE YOU LYING?!
NO! OF COURSE NOT!
BUT COME ON!
WE’RE NOT LITTLE KIDS ANYMORE!
IT DIDN’T USED TO BOTHER ME
AT ALL, BUT NOW...
I CAN’T STAND IT.
TAKU JUST KEEPS
GETTING COOLER AND COOLER,
AND YOU’RE
BECOMING SUPER CUTE.
AND WHENEVER
I’M WITH YOU GUYS NOW,
I JUST FEEL LIKE
THE BIGGEST LOSER.
WHY DO YOU SAY THAT?
WHY DO YOU HATE YOURSELF
SO MUCH?
COME ON.
JUST LOOK AT ME.
BUT THAT’S NOT TRUE, HARU.
THERE’S SO MANY
AWESOME THINGS ABOUT YOU.
TWO YEARS AGO,
IF YOU WOULD’VE JUST...
I’M SORRY.
I WASN’T SUPPOSED
TO SAY THAT.
I WANTED YOU TO KNOW
THAT NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS,
YOU’LL ALWAYS HAVE
TWO FRIENDS HERE FOR YOU.
HOLD ON. DON’T TELL ME
YOU DID ALL THIS SO TAKU
AND I COULD STILL BE FRIENDS.
I DID, BUT I WAS WRONG.
NOTHING STAYS THE SAME,
AND YOU CAN’T STOP PEOPLE
FROM CHANGING.
( gasps )
THE TRUTH IS, WHEN I SAW YOU
AND KUROYUKIHIME TOGETHER,
I REALIZED YOU
DIDN’T NEED ME ANYMORE...
AND I DIDN’T LIKE
HOW THAT FELT.
( breathing heavily )
I’M SO SORRY.
I WAS ONLY THINKING
ABOUT MYSELF,
AND I NEVER STOPPED
TO THINK ABOUT YOU.
THAT’S RIGHT, HARU.
WE’RE ALL GOING
THROUGH OUR OWN STUFF.
SAME WITH TAKKUN.
I’M SURE KUROYUKIHIME
HAS HER STUFF, TOO.
( Haru thinking )
THERE’S NOTHING
UNUSUAL HERE.
I KNEW IT
COULDN’T BE TRUE.
THERE’S NO WAY
SHE COULD BE CYAN PILE.
( gasps )
WHAT WAS THAT LAG ABOUT?
( beeping )
HOLD ON!
THIS IS A BACKDOOR PROGRAM!
♪
( indistinct singing )
♪ IT’S A BURST OF SENSATION ♪
( singing in Japanese )
Kuroyukihime:
NEXT STAGE: DECLARATION.
A MOMENT OF ETERNITY
CAPTURED IN ACCELERATING TIME,
WHERE A GIRL RISKS HER LIFE
TO DECLARE HER LOVE.