OKAY, THEN.
WELL, I’VE GOTTA GO NOW.
WE’LL END IT HERE.
SEE YA LATER.
( grunts softly )
♪
( thinking )
FIVE MORE DAYS TO GO.
Megumi: HIME!
STOP.
I CAN’T THINK LIKE THAT.
THE LAST THING
HARUYUKI WANTS
IS FOR ME TO BE MOPING AROUND
WHILE I’M AWAY ON A TRIP.
HIME.
I’LL GIVE MYSELF
TO THE COUNT OF THREE
TO SNAP OUT OF IT.
HEY...
ONE.
DON’T MAKE ME DO THIS...
TWO.
THREE.
( Megumi laughing )
( yells )
MEGUMI!
WHY DID YOU DO THAT?
( laughing )
WELL, I KEPT CALLING OUT
YOUR NAME,
BUT YOU WOULDN’T ANSWER ME,
SO...
WE GOTTA GO.
THE SEE KAYAK TOUR
THAT WE SIGNED UP FOR
WILL BE LEAVING SOON.
OH, THAT’S RIGHT.
I FORGOT.
SORRY.
I’M GONNA PASS ON THAT.
I’D GO, BUT...
I’M NOT REALLY FEELING WELL.
( sighs )
MMM.
( giggles )
WELL, THEN I’LL PASS, TOO.
HMM?
ARE YOU SURE?
HOW’S IT GO?
OH, YEAH!
"IF IT FLOATS
"BUT DOESN’T COME
WITH A LIFEBOAT,
THEN WALK AWAY."
THAT’S OUR OLD FAMILY MOTTO.
( grunts softly )
Kuroyukihime: SO WAS THERE
SOMEONE IN YOUR FAMILY
WHO WAS ON A SHIPWRECKED
CRUISE LINER OR SOMETHING?
( grunts )
Both: AHH...
Haru: EVERYONE IS THE HERO
OF THEIR OWN LIFE’S STORY.
THIS IS TRUE FOR ME,
TAKU,
AND CHIYU.
THE SAME CAN EVEN
BE SAID FOR MY MOM.
WHEN IT COMES TO HER
OWN LIFE’S STORY,
SHE’S THE STAR OF IT.
AND IT GOES WITHOUT SAYING
THAT THE SAME IS ALSO TRUE
FOR KUROYUKIHIME SENPAI.
IN FACT,
I’M SURE HER LIFE’S STORY
IS MUCH MORE DRAMATIC
AND SERIOUS THAN MINE
WILL EVER BE.
THE STORY YOU’RE
ABOUT TO SEE
TOOK PLACE IN APRIL 2047.
WHILE ME, TAKU, AND CHIYU
WERE BUSY DEALING
WITH DUST TAKER,
OR SEIJI NOMI, IN TOKYO,
KUROYUKIHIME SENPAI
WAS OFF ON A SCHOOL TRIP
IN OKINAWA,
HAVING AN ADVENTURE
OF HER OWN.
THIS IS HER OWN STORY...
THAT I WILL
NEVER KNOW ABOUT.
I HAVEN’T SEEN
YOU LOOK LIKE THAT
FOR AGES NOW.
WHAT TO YOU MEAN?
WELL, EVEN WHEN YOU AND I
FIRST MET,
YOU ALWAYS LOOKED LIKE
YOU WERE SORT OF LOST
OR SOMETHING.
AT LEAST UNTIL LAST FALL
WHEN YOU MET THAT BOY!
( grunts softly )
BUT NOW, YOU HAVE THAT
LOOK AGAIN
LIKE YOU WANT TO GO BACK...
NOT TO TOKYO,
BUT TO SOME OTHER WORLD
BESIDES THIS ONE!
MEGUMI.
YOU HAVE SOME OTHER WORLD
THAT I DON’T EVEN KNOW ABOUT
THAT YOU LIKE TO RETREAT TO,
DON’T YOU?
AND MAYBE IN THAT WORLD,
WELL...
THAT’S WHERE THE REAL
HIME CAN BE FOUND.
OR MAYBE NOT.
THE REAL ME?
COME ON.
HERE. I’LL SHOW YOU.
UH?
( grunts, yelps )
( yells )
( giggles )
( yelps )
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?!
STOP!
NOW, NOW, NOW,
DON’T FIGHT IT, HIME.
MEGUMI, I’M SERIOUS!
COME ON!
KNOCK IT OFF!
( squeals )
( giggles )
I’M GONNA SHOW YOU
SOMETHING NEW--
A WHOLE DIFFERENT WORLD
YOU KNOW NOTHING ABOUT.
( giggles )
( Kuroyukihime screaming )
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( indistinct singing )
♪ AND WATCH IT GO SLOW ♪
♪ SLOWLY OPEN UP MY EYES ♪
( indistinct singing )
( singing in Japanese )
♪ NEVER LET IT GO,
NEVER LOSE MY WAY ♪
( singing in Japanese )
Megumi: AW...
I SAID I’M SORRY, HIME.
I WAS JUST
TRYING TO HAVE FUN.
PRETTY PLEASE?
Kuroyukihime: I KNOW WE’RE
ON A SCHOOL TRIP, MEGUMI.
BUT THAT WAS TAKING THINGS
WAY TOO FAR.
BUT IT’S JUST THAT LATELY,
YOU ALWAYS SEEM SO BUSY.
I THOUGHT THAT AT LEAST
ON THIS TRIP...
I’D GET A CHANCE TO HAVE YOU
ALL TO MYSELF,
IF EVEN FOR A LITTLE BIT.
( sighs )
YOU’RE FORGIVEN.
JUST DON’T DO IT AGAIN.
THANKS!
I’LL BE MORE CAREFUL!
ALL THAT BABBLE
ABOUT DIFFERENT WORLDS
AND THE REAL ME--
IT’S LIKE YOU WERE
HINTING AT SOMETHING.
( grunting )
WELL, THAT STUFF
ABOUT ANOTHER WORLD IS TRUE.
BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
I KNOW A THING OR TWO
ABOUT THAT, AS WELL.
YOU WHAT?
Megumi: BACK WHEN I
WAS A LITTLE KID,
THERE WAS A BOOK
I WAS TOTALLY IN LOVE WITH.
IN THE WORLD
THAT BOOK CREATED,
THERE WERE ALWAYS
NEW PEOPLE TO MEET,
AND ADVENTURE TO BE HAD.
I READ THAT BOOK
EVERY DAY,
OVER AND OVER AGAIN.
I NEVER GOT TIRED OF IT.
BUT THEN ONE DAY,
THE BOOK DISAPPEARED.
AND NOW I CAN’T REMEMBER
WHAT THE BOOK WAS CALLED
OR WHAT IT WAS EVEN ABOUT.
I JUST REMEMBER
THERE WAS A SPELL
AT THE BEGINNING
OF THE BOOK
THAT YOU HAD TO SAY OUT LOUD
IN ORDER TO START READING IT.
AND I KNOW THAT...
UNLESS I’M ABLE
TO REMEMBER THAT SPELL,
I’LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO ENTER THAT WORLD AGAIN.
SO, THESE WERE FAIRY TALES
FROM YOUR CHILDHOOD?
THAT’S THE OTHER WORLD
THAT YOU WOULD SLIP AWAY TO?
THAT’S RIGHT.
MAYBE THAT’S WHY...
I JOINED THE LITERARY CLUB
AT SCHOOL.
I WAS THINKING IT
WOULD BE A WAY FOR ME
TO RECREATE THAT STORY
ALL ON MY OWN.
AND HOW’S THAT GOING?
NOT WELL AT ALL.
( grunts softly )
Megumi:
WHAT’S THE MATTER, HIME?
SOMETHING WRONG?
( grunts )
NO, IT’S JUST,
YOU KNOW...
WELL...
ARE YOU SURE YOU DON’T
NEED TO BUY ANYONE A SOUVENIR?
YEAH, I’M SURE.
I DON’T HAVE
A SPECIAL SOMEONE
WAITING FOR ME
BACK IN TOKYO,
UNLIKE YOU DO.
I SEE.
WELL, THEN...
I KNOW.
LET’S DO THIS:
YOU AND ME,
WE’LL BUY A LITTLE SOUVENIR
FOR EACH OTHER
DURING THIS TRIP.
AND THEN ONCE WE’RE
BACK AT SCHOOL,
WE CAN EXCHANGE OUR GIFTS.
YOU MEAN LIKE
A SURPRISE PRESENT?
I WASN’T EXPECTING YOU
TO COME UP
WITH SUCH A GREAT IDEA.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
NOTHING.
LISTEN,
THIS MEANS WE’VE
GOTTA SPLIT UP.
THERE’S NO WAY WE CAN DO THIS
IF WE SHOP TOGETHER.
OKAY, THEN.
LET’S DO OUR OWN THING
FOR, LIKE, 30 MINUTES.
THEN, WE CAN MEET UP AGAIN
AT THE HOTEL ENTRANCE
AT 4:00.
SURE. THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
I’LL SEE YOU THEN.
I’M GONNA FIND SOMETHING
THAT’LL BE THE BIGGEST SURPRISE
YOU’RE GONNA GET THIS YEAR!
( thinking )
A SURPRISE, HUH?
( chuckles )
THIS’LL BE FUN.
A DUEL?!
HERE IN OKINAWA?!
IS THIS THE OLD
CASTLE STAGE?
IT LOOKS A LITTLE DIFFERENT.
MAYBE THIS IS HOW
IT LOOKS IN OKINAWA.
Ruka:
IT’S NOT THE OLD CASTLE!
( grunts )
THIS IS THE GUSUKU STAGE!
( whimpers )
RUKA...
W-WAIT FOR ME!
( yelps )
Kuroyukihime: HMM.
YOU MUST BE ONE
OF THOSE SCHOOL TRIP KIDS
STAYING AT THE HOTEL.
AND YOU TWO ARE BURST LINKERS
WHO HAPPEN TO BE LOCALS
FROM THIS AREA?
ATTEEMEE--I MEAN,
OBVIOUSLY.
MY FAMILY’S BEEN IN UCHINANCHU
FOR GENERATIONS.
YEP, MINE, TOO.
WELL, PRETTY MUCH.
I’VE GOTTA SAY,
I’M SURPRISED.
A LOCAL BURST LINKER.
AND NOT JUST ONE.
VERY INTERESTING.
AH, YOU’RE UP FOR IT.
OKAY, ME AND YOU.
LET’S DO IT!
( whimpers )
ALL RIGHT, RUKA.
BE CAREFUL.
SHE’S LEVEL NINE.
( chuckles )
THAT MEANS NOTHIN’.
SHE’S ONLY TWO LEVELS HIGHER
THAN OUR MASTER.
( yelling )
( grunting )
( grunts, groans )
( gasps )
( grunts )
( yelling )
Ruka:
YUKUSHIASSA!
SHE CREATED A HUGE HOLE
IN THE CENTER
OF THE BATTLEFIELD.
THAT’S ENOUGH, RUKA.
LET’S JUST ASK HER ALREADY.
NOT YET!
AN UCHINAA WARRIOR
CAN’T LOSE TO SOME SAMURAI
FROM YAMATO!
TIDAL WAVE!
DEATH BY...
( yelling )
BARRAGING!
( grunts, yells )
( Kuroyukihime grunts )
( grunts )
( panting )
YOU WIN.
MMM. YOU FOUGHT QUITE WELL.
YOUR FEINT AND KICK
WERE ESPECIALLY GOOD.
IT’LL BE EVEN BETTER IF YOU
CAN MAKE THE TRANSITION
MORE SEAMLESS.
GOT IT, NEE-NEE.
I’LL WORK ON THAT.
( whimpers )
W-WAIT, RUKA.
WE HAVEN’T TALKED ABOUT
WHAT WE CAME FOR.
I...I FORGOT
ALL ABOUT THAT.
NEE-NEE, WE NEED SOMEONE
AS GOOD AS YOU
TO DO US A FAVOR.
WOULD YOU AT LEAST
HEAR US OUT?
WELL, I SUPPOSE
I CAN CERTAINLY LISTEN
TO WHAT THAT MAY BE.
Both: NIFEE DEEBIRU!
ALL RIGHT, UM,
LET’S SEE...
THERE’S A COFFEE SHOP
CLOSE BY CALLED SABANI.
IT’S AT THE END
OF THIS MAIN STREET.
SO WHY DON’T WE
LOG OUT AND MEET UP
AT ONE OF THOSE TABLES THERE
IN A FEW MINUTES?
HUH? W-WAIT A SECOND.
( grunts )
( whimpers )
WANNA MEET?
IN THE REAL WORLD?
Both: WHOA.
( grunts )
I BELIEVE IT WAS YOU TWO
WHO INVITED ME HERE,
SO LET’S HEAR IT.
( both gasp )
WASSAIBIIN.
IT’S JUST--I DIDN’T KNOW
YOU’D BE A MAJOR CHURAKAGI
( giggles )
Mana:
"CHURAKAGI" MEANS BEAUTY.
SHE THINKS YOU’RE
REALLY PRETTY.
OKAY, MY NAME IS...
RUKA ASATO FROM CLASS 2-2
AT KUBE JUNIOR HIGH.
( gasps )
AND I’M MANA ITOSU
FROM CLASS 1-3.
I ALSO GO TO THAT
SAME SCHOOL.
Both: IT’S NICE
TO MEET YOU.
( coughs )
I DON’T BELIEVE IT.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
THOSE NAMES YOU TWO
JUST GAVE ME,
ARE THEY YOUR REAL NAMES?
WELL YEAH,
OF COURSE THEY ARE.
( sighs )
AMAZING.
WHEN YOU SAID
TO MEET YOU GUYS
IN THE REAL WORLD,
I WAS AFRAID I’D
BE WALKING INTO SOME SORT
OF TRAP.
I DON’T GET IT.
WHAT’S THE MATTER?
IT’S JUST...
LOOK, THIS MASTER OF YOURS,
WHEN THEY GAVE YOU
BRAIN BURST,
DIDN’T THEY TEACH YOU
ANY SPECIFIC RULES
THAT COME ALONG WITH IT?
( both gasp )
Both: AND...GO!
Both: RULE ONE--
DON’T USE ACCELERATION
FOR ANYTHING BAD.
AND RULE TWO--
DON’T TALK ABOUT ACCELERATING
TO JUST ANYONE.
END OF RULES.
AND THAT WAS ALL?
Both:
YEP. THAT WAS IT.
UNBELIEVABLE.
THIS SO-CALLED
MASTER OF YOURS--
I THINK I MIGHT NEED
TO HAVE A WORD WITH THEM.
Both: REALLY?
NEE-NEE, THAT’D BE SO GREAT!
URISSAN!
WE’VE BEEN RACKING
OUR BRAINS
TO COME UP WITH A WAY
TO GET YOU TO DO THAT.
HUH? DO WHAT?
THE WHOLE REASON
WE ASKED YOU HERE IN PERSON
IS ’CAUSE WE WANTED TO SEE
IF YOU’D BE WILLING
TO MEET OUR MASTER.
( sighs )
( indistinct chattering )
( grunts softly )
( chuckles )
Kuroyukihime:
SO LET ME GET THIS STRAIGHT...
RUKAT’S THE PROTEGE
OF A BURST LINKER
WHO MOVED HERE FROM TOKYO,
AND MANA IS RUKA’S PROTEGE?
RIGHT. SEE, THERE’S
ONLY THREE OF US RIGHT NOW.
BUT WE WANNA
EXPAND OUR CIRCLE
SO THAT ONE DAY,
OUR ACCELERATED COMMUNITY
IS BIGGER THAN TOKYO’S.
AIAIBIIN.
BUT YOU SEE,
SOMETHING HAPPENED RECENTLY
THAT JUST MIGHT
RUIN ALL THAT.
FIRST OUR MASTER
TRIED TO FIGURE OUT A WAY
TO FACE THE PROBLEM,
BUT NOW IT SEEMS
HE’S COMPLETELY GIVEN UP.
WELL WHAT HAPPENED?
TO BE HONEST,
I DON’T KNOW.
I WISH WE DID,
BUT WE DON’T REALLY
UNDERSTAND IT OURSELVES.
ALL OUR MASTER TOLD US
WAS THAT SOME SORT
OF MAJIMUN APPEARED.
THAT’S WHY WE’RE HERE.
WE NEED SOMEONE
AS STRONG AS YOU
TO HELP OUT OUR MASTER.
Both: PLEASE.
WE’RE BEGGING!
YOU CAN BEG ME TO HELP YOU
ALL YOU WANT,
BUT I CAN’T COMMIT TO ANYTHING
UNTIL I KNOW A BIT MORE
ABOUT THIS MAJIMUN,
OKAY?
( chuckles )
( both gasp )
SO I GUESS IF WE
WANT TO FIND OUT MORE,
THEN THE NEXT STEP
IS FAIRLY OBVIOUS:
LET’S GO MEET YOUR MASTER!
( squeals )
YOU REALLY MEAN IT?
IT’S HAPPENING WHEN YOU
SAID IT WOULD, MANA.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
COME ON!
LET’S GO TO MY HOUSE!
WAIT. NOT SO FAST.
( both grunt )
I THINK IT’S BEST IF WE
DON’T DO THIS IN THE REAL WORLD.
IF HE’S FROM TOKYO,
THERE’S A CHANCE
WE MAY HAVE CROSSED PATHS
IN THE ACCELERATED
WORLD BEFORE.
OH, SO THAT’S WHAT
YOU’RE WORRIED ABOUT.
GOOD POINT.
IF OUR MASTER WERE TO SEE
WHAT A CHURAKAGI SHE IS,
THERE’S JUST NOT TELLING
WHAT HE MIGHT DO!
( sighs )
( grunts )
( gasps )
OH, NO!
( both gasp )
( chuckles )
OH, THERE YOU ARE.
( panting )
SORRY I’M LATE.
DON’T WORRY ABOUT IT.
I JUST MADE IT
BACK HERE MYSELF.
I HAD A HARD TIME DECIDING,
AND KNOWING YOU...
WERE HAVING JUST AS HARD
OF A TIME
FINDING THE PERFECT
THING FOR ME.
WELL, THAT MADE ME HAPPY.
TIME FLEW BY.
( grunts softly )
I’M SORRY, MEGUMI,
BUT I...
FORGOT ALL ABOUT
YOUR PRESENT.
( sighs )
NO, THAT’S FINE.
THE TRIP’S NOT OVER YET.
YOU STILL HAVE PLENTY
OF TIME LEFT
TO FIND ME SOMETHING
IF YOU WANT TO.
I KNOW, BUT I PROMISED YOU.
( voice breaking )
REALLY, IT’S FINE.
I MEAN IT.
( grunts softly )
OH, NO. I-I REALLY
DIDN’T MEAN TO.
IT’S ODD--I DON’T KNOW
WHY I’M CRYING.
MEGUMI.
I’M SORRY, BUT CAN YOU
JUST GO ON AHEAD WITHOUT ME?
I’M GOING BACK TO THE ROOM
TO LIE DOWN FOR A BIT.
MEGUMI, WAIT!
♪
I’M SORRY, MEGUMI.
THERE’S NO EXCUSE
FOR WHAT I DID.
IT’S NOT YOUR FAULT.
I JUST GOT WAY TOO EXCITED
AND THEN MADE A FOOL
OF MYSELF.
AND NOW I FEEL LIKE AN IDIOT.
YOU KNOW WHAT, HIME?
JUST LEAVE ME ALONE
FOR A HALF AN HOUR OR SO,
AND I’LL BE BACK TO MY
OLD SELF AGAIN.
I PROMISE.
MEGUMI, I’LL CONFESS.
WHAT YOU SAID EARLIER TODAY
ON THE BEACH IS TRUE.
THAT OTHER WORLD--
IT IS A PLACE I ESCAPE TO.
AND THE WAY
THAT TIME WORKS THERE--
WELL, IT’S DIFFERENT.
MY VERY FIRST FORAY
INTO THAT WORLD
WAS SEVEN YEARS AGO.
AND SINCE THEN,
I’VE SPENT A GREAT DEAL
OF TIME THERE.
TRUTH IS, I’VE SPENT SO MUCH
TIME IN THAT WORLD
THAT NOW I’M NO LONGER SURE
WHICH WORLD IS THE REAL ONE.
AND BECAUSE OF THAT,
I’M NOT EVEN SURE WHICH WORLD
I REALLY BELONG IN ANYMORE.
IT’S MADE ME START ASKING
QUESTIONS ABOUT MY LIFE--
LIKE, "WHAT PURPOSE IS THERE
FOR ME TO EVEN EXIST?"
BUT WHENEVER I’VE COME CLOSE
TO LOSING MYSELF,
YOU’VE ALWAYS
BEEN THE ONE TO SAVE ME.
EVER SINCE OUR FIRST
DAY AT SCHOOL,
WHEN YOU CAME OVER
AND INVITED ME
TO HAVE LUNCH WITH YOU,
YOU HAVE BEEN THE ONLY PERSON
WHO HAS BEEN ABLE TO KEEP ME
GROUNDED IN THE REAL WORLD,
ESPECIALLY
WHEN I NEED IT MOST.
I’VE LET MYSELF
LOSE SEVERAL CLOSE TIES
IN THAT OTHER WORLD.
BUT NOW I’M STARTING
TO GRADUALLY REBUILD THEM.
HOWEVER, IN THIS WORLD,
MEGUMI,
THE ONLY FRIEND I HAVE
IS YOU.
THAT’S IT.
( crying )
HIME.
MEGUMI.
THANK YOU.
WHAT YOU JUST SAID
MAKES ME SO HAPPY.
BUT STILL,
I’M REALLY SORRY.
YOU HAVE NOTHING
TO APOLOGIZE FOR.
I WAS THE ONE WHO
FORGOT ABOUT BUYING A GIFT.
NO, I-IT’S NOT THAT.
YOU SEE, THERE’S SOMETHING
YOU DON’T KNOW,
SOMETHING I SHOULD’VE
APOLOGIZED FOR A LONG TIME AGO.
HIME, BACK THEN, I...
( electronic beeping )
( gasps )
Female Computerized Voice:
SCHOOL TRIP COMMITTEE MEETING
STARTING.
WAIT. THAT’S MY ALARM.
( gasping )
HIME, I’M SO SORRY!
I CAN’T BELIEVE I FORGOT
ABOUT THE COMMITTEE MEETING!
I’LL GET READY SUPER-FAST.
JUST WAIT FOR ME, OKAY?
( sighs )
( crickets chirping )
( low rumbling )
( roaring )
( sighs )
Woman 1: MENSOOREE!
Woman 2: NIFEE DEEBIRU!
Woman 3: BEST PRICES
IN OKINAWA!
HERE I WAS,
WARNING YOU ON THE DANGERS
THAT COME WHEN YOU
FORGET ABOUT THE REAL WORLD
AND LOSE YOURSELF
IN THE ACCELERATED WORLD,
ACTING LIKE I KNEW IT ALL,
WHEN I WAS DOING THE SAME THING
TO POOR MEGUMI.
I REALIZE, HARUYUKI,
I HAVE A LONG WAYS
TO GO MYSELF.
I HAVE A FEELING YOU’RE
INVOLVED IN A TERRIBLE
PREDICAMENT RIGHT NOW,
BUT UNLESS YOU
ASK ME TO HELP,
I’LL LET YOU HANDLE IT ALONE.
DO YOUR BEST, HARUYUKI,
AND I’LL DO WHAT A BURST
LINKER IS SUPPOSED TO DO
WHILE I’M OVER HERE.
Ruka: NEE-NEE!
UH?
THERE YOU ARE!
( Ruka gasps )
Mana: THIS PLACE
LOOKS REALLY EXPENSIVE.
THE SABANI
WOULD’VE BEEN FINE.
Kuroyukihime:
DON’T BE STUPID.
IF YOU WERE TO DIVE THERE
WITHOUT SOME SORT OF
DISCONNECTION FAILSAFE,
WHOA.
WHAT WOULD YOU
DO IF YOU COULDN’T
MAKE IT BACK TO A PORTAL?
( whimpers )
THERE’S NO NEED
TO STRESS ABOUT THAT.
YEAH. NANKURUNAISA.
IF SOMETHING GOES WRONG,
THEN THE WAITRESS
WOULD JUST EVENTUALLY COME BY
AND UNPLUG OUR NEURO-LINKERS.
YOU WILL DO AS I TELL YOU TO!
UNDERSTOOD?
( both grunt )
( gasps )
( whimpers )
LOOK, I MADE A PROMISE
TO MEET YOUR MASTER,
AND THAT’S PRECISELY
WHAT I’LL DO.
BUT I CAN MAKE NO GUARANTEES
AFTER THAT.
IT’S EVEN POSSIBLE THIS
WILL ALL JUST END IN A FIGHT.
Ruka and Mana: OKAY.
ALL RIGHT, WE’LL COUNT DOWN
FROM FIVE AND DIVE.
FIVE, AND FOUR,
THREE--
HOLD ON.
WAIT A SEC.
WAIT FOR WHAT?
KANDARI.
HER YUTA BLOOD AWAKENED.
YUTA?
SHE’S AN OKINAWA SHAMAN?
YEP, SHE’S A SAADAKAUMARI.
SORRY,
BUT I NEED ANOTHER ONE.
ANOTHER WHAT?
THIS. ANOTHER CABLE.
UH, SURE.
BUT WHERE DO YOU WANT ME
TO PLUG IT IN?
JUST LEAVE IT
RIGHT THERE, PLEASE.
( grunts )
IT’S OKAY.
JUST DO WHAT SHE SAYS.
( sighs )
ALL RIGHT.
THIS TIME, FOR REAL.
All: UNLIMITED BURST!
THE WEATHERED STAGE.
SO, WHERE’S YOUR MASTER?
THIS WAY.
( both panting )
Kuroyukihime:
YOUR MASTER IS IN HERE?
HAITAI, MASTER.
HUH? OH.
( slowly )
HAISAI.
Mana: AW, COME ON.
ARE YOU REALLY DRUNK
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE DAY?
YOU’RE STARTING TO ACT
LIKE EVERY OTHER UCHINAA-OJII.
( slurring )
I’M NOT AN OJII.
I’M STILL ONLY 16,
YOU KNOW?
BARKEEP,
KEEP THAT 300-YEAR-OLD
KUSU LIQUOR COMING.
( grunts )
( electronic beeping )
ALL RIGHT. ENOUGH!
THIS ISN’T THE TIME FOR YOU
TO SIT AROUND DRINKING!
LOOK, MASTER,
WE’VE BROUGHT SOMEONE,
SOMEONE WHO CAN REALLY
HELP US.
WHAT? YOU WERE SERIOUS ABOUT
GETTING AN OUTSIDER TO HELP US?
WHAT’S THE POINT?
IT’S USELESS.
WE’RE SCREWED.
WE’RE SCREWED!
( gulping )
( groans )
I MEAN ONE OR TWO PEOPLE
HELPING OUT
AGAINST A GIANT MONSTER ISN’T
GONNA MAKE A LICK OF DIFFERENCE.
Kuroyukihime:
HEY, YOU.
I’M A LEVEL SEVEN,
AND I COULDN’T COME CLOSE
TO STOPPING THAT THING.
EVEN A LEVEL EIGHT WOULDN’T
BE ABLE TO PUT HIM AWAY.
THERE’S JUST NO WAY.
UNLESS YOU BRING ME
A LEVEL NINE KING,
IT’S A WASTE OF TIME.
Kuroyukihime:
HEY, LET ME SEE YOUR FACE.
NAH. I BET EVEN A KING
WOULD HAVE TROUBLE
GOING UP AGAINST THAT THING.
YOU’D HAVE TO FIND SOMEONE
WHO SPECIALIZES
IN PHYSICAL ATTACKS
LIKE VANQUISH, OR BETTER YET,
WORLD END, HERSELF.
I SAID, "HEY"!
STOP BARKIN’ AT ME!
I TOLD YOU, UNLESS YOU
COULD PULL OFF A MIRACLE
AND BRING ME THE BLACK KING,
THEN I’M NOT
GONNA BUDGE FROM...
THE BARSTOOL.
I THOUGHT THAT WAS YOU.
IT’S BEEN A LONG TIME,
C.K.
OH--
UH, W-WAIT, WAIT,
NO, I-I NEED A TIME OUT.
I-I--THOSE LEGS,
THAT LOOK,
AND THE FACT THAT YOU’RE
CALLING ME C.K.
NO WAY.
THE REAL THING?
IN THE FLESH?
THE BLACK KING?!
BLACK LOTUS?!
SERIOUSLY?!
( whimpers )
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( song ends )
Kuroyukihime:
NEXT STAGE: REVOLUTION.
THE LONG-LOST STORY
RESURRECTS
WHEN AN INNOCENT PRAYER
BRINGS FORTH THE TRANSITION.