( whistle blows )
( scattered chatter )
( panting )
( thundering )
YOU WANT ME TO
TAKE ON BOTH OF YOU?
THAT’S
RIGHT.
DEFEAT US,
AND YOU’RE
OFF THE HOOK.
AFTER THAT, YOU’RE FREE TO GO
JOIN THE BLACK KING OR ANY
OTHER LEGION, FOR THAT MATTER.
IS THAT WHAT...
VANQUISH HAS TOLD YOU?
( thundering )
( yells )
( grunts )
COME ON.
IS THAT ALL YOU’VE GOT?
IT’S STILL NOT TOO LATE
TO CHANGE YOUR MIND.
AS LONG AS YOU PROMISE
TO AMEND YOUR WAYS,
WE’LL FORGIVE YOU.
NO WAY!
HE SHOULDN’T BE ABLE
TO MOVE RIGHT NOW.
WHAT KIND OF PAIN
THRESHOLD
DOES HE HAVE?
BLUE KNIGHT.
PLEASE HEAR ME OUT.
I DON’T EXPECT YOU TO
FORGIVE ME FOR WHAT I’VE DONE.
BUT ALL I ASK IS FOR YOU
TO GIVE ME A LITTLE TIME.
JUST TO TRAIN HIM!
Blue Knight:
COBAL, MARGA.
Both: SIR!
THROW HIM
INTO THE PORTAL.
I WILL LET HIM GO
JUST THIS ONCE.
Both:
YES, SIR!
THANK YOU...
( panting )
Chiyuri:
13.66 SECONDS...
HARU...
HMM!
OH...
♪
Megumi: ARE YOU SURE
YOU WANT YOUR HAIR
UP LIKE THIS?
I STILL THINK BRAIDS
WOULD SUIT YOU BETTER.
JUST DO IT.
I FEEL LIKE SOMETHING
DIFFERENT TODAY.
YEAH BUT, I JUST THINK
A PONYTAIL WILL GET
IN THE WAY A LOT.
LIKE WHEN YOU
LIE DOWN AND STUFF.
Kuroyukihime:
I’M SENDING
YOU A TO-DO LIST.
Computer voice:
SENDING FILE.
PLEASE RELAY MY WISHES
TO THE STUDENT COUNCIL.
UH...HEY.
WHAT’S UP?
Megumi:
UH...
SO. YOU WERE JUST
SAYING THAT YOU
NEEDED TO GET GOING?
UH, YEP,
THAT’S RIGHT!
SEE YOU LATER,
HIME.
HAVE FUN.
BUT DON’T STAY TOO LONG!
DID I...
INTERRUPT SOMETHING?
NO. DON’T WORRY
ABOUT IT.
( gasps )
( sighs )
S-SO. YOU FEELING
ANY BETTER?
YES, MUCH BETTER,
THANK YOU.
BUT HAVING ANY FUN
IN A HOSPITAL IS
RATHER CHALLENGING.
NOT TO MENTION THE
DIFFICULTIES THAT COME WITH
TRYING TO FIND A DECENT MEAL.
WELL, THAT’S
THE WAY
IT IS.
BUT YOU’VE GOTTA TAKE IT EASY
AND DO WHAT THEY SAY SO YOU
CAN FULLY RECOVER.
YES. THAT’S TRUE...
SO...IT’S ALMOST EVENING.
YEAH!
IT LOOKS
THAT WAY.
IT SURE IS
A BEAUTIFUL SUNSET.
SO, WHAT DO YOU
THINK OF MY HAIR?
THIS IS HOW YOU SAID
YOU LIKED IT YESTERDAY.
DID I MISUNDERSTAND?
AAH...NO, NO!
I DO LIKE IT,
AND I DID NOTICE
IT FIRST THING.
I JUST...WASN’T SURE
HOW TO TELL YOU THAT.
SEE, IF I SAID IT LOOKED
NICE, YOU MIGHT’VE THOUGHT
I WAS JUST SAYING IT TO SAY IT.
AND I DIDN’T
WANT THAT.
SO, DOES IT
SUIT ME OR NOT?!
YES, OF COURSE!
YOUR HAIR LOOKS
REALLY GOOD LIKE THAT!
YOU DON’T MEAN IT.
YOU’RE JUST BEING NICE.
NO, I’M BEING HONEST!
I SWEAR IT!
IT LOOKS...
REALLY GOOD.
I LIKE IT.
I’M SORRY
I SUCK AT THIS.
OH, SAVE IT!
SO. DID YOU GO
AND SEE
KURASHIMA?
YES, TAKU AND I
BOTH WENT.
WE TOLD HER
EVERYTHING.
WE TOLD HER ABOUT
ACCELERATED WORLD.
AND THE BACKDOOR
PROGRAM TAKU INSTALLED.
AND ABOUT LYING TO HER.
I SEE. SO, HOW DID
SHE TAKE ALL THAT?
SHE WAS REALLY,
REALLY MAD.
SHE STARTED GRABBING BOOKS
AND HURLING THEM AT US.
THEN SHE GOT MORE UPSET AND
STARTED CRYING, WHICH PROGRESSED
INTO HER SLAPPING US BOTH.
OH, I SEE.
AND NOW, SHE WON’T
EVEN TALK TO US.
NOT A WORD.
I CERTAINLY CAN’T
BLAME HER FOR
BEING ANGRY.
BUT I HAVE TO ADMIT,
PART OF THE FAULT HERE
LIES ENTIRELY WITH ME.
I REALLY SHOULD
APOLOGIZE TO HER.
NO. THAT’S OKAY.
TAKU AND I ARE THE ONES
WHO SCREWED THIS ALL UP,
AND WE NEED TO MAKE IT RIGHT.
TAKU FEELS
THE SAME WAY.
HE SAID HE PLANS
TO ATONE FOR ALL
OF HIS MISTAKES.
HE SAID THAT?
HE DID.
I KNOW YOU’VE
SAID HE GOES TO
A DIFFERENT SCHOOL.
IT’S SOMEWHERE
IN SHINJUKU,
RIGHT?
YEAH. TAKU’S A SUPER
SMART GUY, SO HIS PARENTS
MADE HIM GO TO A SCHOOL
WHERE HE’D GET
A BETTER EDUCATION.
AND HE’S REALLY GOOD
AT SPORTS TOO.
INTERESTING.
THAT’S WHY I THINK
HE’LL BE A GOOD
ADDITION TO NEGA NEBULOUS.
HE’LL BE A GREAT FIGHTER.
HE AND I HAVE PLANS
TOMORROW TO GET TOGETHER
FOR A TAG-TEAM FIGHT.
HE SAID BY THE TIME YOU’RE
READY TO LEAVE THE HOSPITAL,
HE’LL HELP ME GET TO LEVEL TWO.
HE MEANS A LOT
TO YOU.
I CAN SEE THAT.
HMM?
I’M KIND OF JEALOUS.
YOU’RE LUCKY.
AFTER ALL THAT’S
HAPPENED, YOU STILL
FORGIVE EACH OTHER.
YOU’VE MOVED ON
FROM THE BETRAYAL
AND THE HATE.
TAKU’S MY
BEST FRIEND.
THAT’S WHY.
ARE YOU SURE YOU
REALLY WANT TO DO THIS?
YES.
( girls chatting )
I CAN’T BELIEVE THOSE TWO.
IF HARU AND TAKU HAVE ANYTHING
ELSE THEY WANT TO TELL ME,
I WISH THEY’D JUST
SPIT IT OUT ALREADY.
( groans )
THEY MAKE ME MAD!
Taku: HARU,
TO YOUR RIGHT!
YEAH,
I SEE HIM!
( grunts )
WHOA! THAT’S
THE AVATAR
WHO CAN FLY!
THIS ISN’T THE TIME
TO BE STAR STRUCK!
( grunts )
Haru:
5 SECONDS LEFT!
Taku: FOUR.
THREE.
TWO...
AND ONE!
Haru: YES!
THREE WINS IN A ROW!
( gasps )
OH, COOL!
Announcer:
CONGRATS!
GOOD GAME, MAN!
CAN’T WAIT TO TELL
EVERYONE I FOUGHT WITH
THE FLYING AVATAR. THANKS!
BE SMART ABOUT
WHAT LEVEL-UP
BONUS YOU PICK.
SEE YA!
THANKS FOR
A GOOD FIGHT.
WAY TO GO.
THANKS, TAKU.
I CAN’T WAIT TO TELL SENPAI
ABOUT THE GOOD NEWS.
OR MAYBE LEVEL 2 IS
STILL NOT ENOUGH TO
REALLY IMPRESS HER.
DON’T WORRY,
YOU’RE DOING FINE.
I’LL BE HERE WATCHING
YOUR BACK, AT LEAST
UNTIL YOU REACH LEVEL 4.
I OWE YOU THAT MUCH.
WHAT?
LOOK. I WANT TO
HELP YOU BECOME A
FIRST RATE BURST-LINKER.
I HOPE THAT’S COOL.
I KNOW THAT WON’T MAKE UP
FOR EVERYTHING,
BUT IT’S
THE LEAST I CAN DO.
LISTEN, TAKU. I CAN’T STOP YOU
FROM FEELING RESPONSIBLE
FOR WHAT HAPPENED.
BUT...I’M THE REASON
WHY SENPAI GOT HURT
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
IT WAS MY OWN
STUPID FAULT.
NO. WHAT I DID
WAS UNFORGIVABLE.
I KNOW THAT NOW.
YOU SAW IT YOURSELF,
HOW UPSET CHI WAS.
MY CRIME IS WORSE.
WAY WORSE.
I DON’T KNOW.
HEY. I THINK
THAT’S ENOUGH
FOR TODAY.
LET’S GO HOME.
OKAY. GIMME A SEC.
LET ME FINISH THIS FIRST.
FINISH WHAT?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
DON’T LEVEL UP YET.
( gasps )
NO, HARU!
STOP!
HUH?
THE BURST POINTS
I HAVE LEFT...
ARE EIGHT?
HARU!
BURST OUT NOW!
( panting )
( gasping )
Taku: IT’S MY FAULT.
I’M SO SORRY.
I SHOULD’VE TOLD YOU.
EVEN IF YOU HAVE
ENOUGH POINTS TO GO
AND LEVEL UP YOUR AVATAR,
YOU SHOULD WAIT
AND HOLD OFF A BIT.
I’M A TERRIBLE TEACHER.
I’VE TOTALLY FAILED YOU.
I’M SORRY, HARU.
NO, I’M
THE IDIOT HERE.
THERE WAS A WARNING THAT
POPPED UP ON THE SCREEN
TELLING ME IT WOULD COST ME
300 POINTS TO LEVEL UP.
I SHOULD HAVE STOPPED
AND DONE THE MATH,
BUT I DIDN’T.
I WAS WAY TOO EXCITED.
ALL RIGHT, FIRST.
LET’S LOOK AT
WHERE WE STAND.
ARE YOU SURE YOU’RE RIGHT
ABOUT THAT? YOU ONLY HAVE
EIGHT POINTS LEFT?
YEAH. IF I LOST A DUEL NOW TO
AN OPPONENT OF THE SAME LEVEL,
THEN I’D BE OUT FOR GOOD.
ALL MY BURST POINTS
WOULD BE GONE FOREVER.
YOU’RE RIGHT. IN WHICH
CASE, THAT ONLY LEAVES
US WITH ONE OPTION:
CHALLENGE ME TO A DUEL
SO I CAN GIVE YOU
HALF MY POINTS.
AFTER THAT, WE’LL STICK WITH
PLAYING TAG-TEAM MATCHES AGAINST
THOSE WE KNOW WE CAN BEAT,
AT LEAST UNTIL
YOU REGAIN
YOUR POINTS.
WAIT!
HOLD ON A SEC!
WHAT’S THIS ABOUT
"GIVING" ME
YOUR BURST POINTS?
ARE YOU REALLY JUST GONNA
LET ME KEEP BEATING YOU
AND BEATING YOU,
AND YOU’RE NOT EVER
GONNA FIGHT BACK?
IT’S OUR ONLY CHOICE,
HARU.
LOOK, I’VE GOT
A TON OF POINTS
TO SPARE RIGHT NOW.
BELIEVE ME, THIS
IS REALLY OUR
BEST OPTION. OKAY?
NO WAY,
I WON’T DO THIS!
I HATE THE IDEA OF
BEATING ON YOU AND
YOU NOT FIGHTING BACK.
THAT’S JUST...
NOT RIGHT.
YEAH, BUT WHAT OTHER CHOICE
DO WE HAVE RIGHT NOW?
IF YOU END UP LOSING
ALL YOUR POINTS,
THEN THAT MEANS YOU’LL END UP
LOSING BRAIN BURST FOREVER TOO.
AND THE SAME GOES FOR THIS
POWER THAT COMES ALONG WITH IT.
YEAH, I KNOW, BUT...
I JUST...
ARE YOU TRYING TO SAY...
THAT YOU DON’T YOU TRUST ME?
HUH?
IT’S TRUE.
WITH YOUR POINTS SO LOW, IT’D BE
EASY FOR ME TO TAKE ADVANTAGE
OF THIS AND ATTACK YOU.
I COULD PROBABLY TAKE YOUR
BURST POINTS DOWN TO ZERO
IN A MATTER OF SECONDS.
NO, IT’S NOT
THAT. THAT’S NOT
WHAT I’M SAYING!
IT JUST SEEMS WRONG.
THE IDEA OF YOU AND ME
FIGHTING LIKE THIS. IT TAKES
THE HONOR AND FUN OUT OF IT.
HARU...?
SENPAI USED PHYSICAL FULL
BURST TO PROTECT ME, AND
SHE’S IN THE HOSPITAL NOW.
HER POINTS MUST BE
REALLY LOW.
BUT THROUGH ALL OF THIS,
SHE HAS NEVER ASKED
ME FOR POINTS.
AND IF I WERE TO OFFER
THEM TO HER, I’M SURE SHE’D
BE COMPLETELY OFFENDED.
SHE’S WAY BEYOND ME
ON EVERYTHING.
HER LEVEL, STRENGTH,
EXPERIENCE.
YOU SEE, SHE’S THE KIND
OF BURST-LINKER I WANT TO BE.
SHE SET AN EXAMPLE,
AND I WANT TO FOLLOW IT.
( chuckles )
I KNOW ONCE YOU’VE DECIDED
SOMETHING, THERE’S NO
CHANGING YOUR MIND.
I GIVE UP.
OKAY. I’LL TRY AND SEE
IF WE CAN COME UP
WITH ANY OTHER WAYS
TO REGAIN YOUR POINTS.
BUT UNTIL WE’VE DONE THAT, YOU
CANNOT LOG ONTO THE GLOBAL NET.
LOOK, TAKU. I’M SORRY.
I KNOW I’M BEING
KINDA SELFISH.
( gasps )
THOSE SLIPPERS. YOU
STILL KEPT THEM AROUND
AFTER ALL THESE YEARS?
DIDN’T YOU?
NO. AFTER I LEFT
GRADE SCHOOL, MY
PARENTS TOSSED THEM.
OH...
( neuro-linker beeps )
HUH?
OH, IT’S CHI.
SO, DID YOU
GET THEM?
YEAH.
THESE ARE IT,
RIGHT?
( gasps )
Taku: ARE YOU REALLY
GONNA EAT ALL THESE?
HMM...
YOU DON’T HAVE
TO FINISH
EVERY SINGLE ONE
OF THEM RIGHT NOW.
IT’S BEEN MY DREAM TO EAT
EVERY FLAVOR OF ENJIYA
ICE CREAM IN ONE GO.
I SAID BUYING THESE
FOR ME IS THE ONLY WAY
I WOULD FORGIVE YOU.
AND THAT WON’T
HAPPEN TILL EVERY
LAST ONE IS GONE.
YEAH, BUT...
I JUST WANT THIS
TO BE OVER ALREADY.
EVERY TIME I SEE YOU GUYS,
HARU’S GOT THIS HORRIBLY SAD,
PITIFUL LOOK IN HIS EYES.
AND TAKU, ALL YOU DO
IS APOLOGIZE.
WELL, THAT’S ’CAUSE...
YOU ALWAYS LOOK LIKE
YOU WANNA YELL AT US.
YOU THINK
I LIKE THIS?
I DON’T WANNA BE
ANGRY ALL THE TIME.
BUT IF I SAID:
"IT’S ALL GOOD, GUYS.
DON’T WORRY ABOUT IT.
I’M NOT BOTHERED
BY THIS AT ALL."
DON’T YOU THINK THAT
WOULD BE A LITTLE BIT STRANGE?
YEAH, OKAY.
YOU’RE RIGHT.
YOU HAVE A POINT.
MMM...
SO ANYWAY,
WHAT’S YOUR PLAN NOW?
ARE YOU STILL GONNA KEEP PLAYING
THIS BRAIN BURSTING THINGY?
UH...
WELL, YEAH.
AT LEAST,
THAT’S WHAT
I WAS HOPING.
( sighs ) BECAUSE
KUROYUKIHIME’S
PLAYING IT TOO.
IS THAT WHY YOU GUYS
ARE SO INTO THIS?
LOOK, SHE MAY HAVE BEEN
THE ONE WHO INTRODUCED
ME TO IT,
BUT THAT’S NOT THE
REASON WHY I WANNA
KEEP PLAYING IT.
THE BRAIN BURST
PROGRAM IN
ITSELF ISN’T BAD.
I JUST GOT
CARRIED AWAY AND
ABUSED ITS POWER.
HARU’S GOT THIS
SUPER COOL AVATAR,
IT CAN EVEN FLY.
SO?
I STILL DON’T GET IT.
I MEAN, IT’S JUST ANOTHER
FIGHTING GAME. WHO CARES?
YEAH, BUT IT ISN’T
JUST A FIGHTING GAME.
INSTEAD OF US
SITTING HERE TRYING
TO EXPLAIN IT TO YOU,
I THINK IT MIGHT
BE EASIER IF WE
JUST SHOWED YOU.
Taku: CHI, GRAB ONE OF
THOSE BOOKS ON YOUR DESK.
AND THEN THROW IT AT ME.
WHAT?
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
THIS SHOULD SHOW
YOU WHAT BRAIN BURST
CAN DO. RIGHT?
HUH? OH, I SEE
WHAT YOU’RE DOING.
I CAN’T
BELIEVE
YOU GUYS.
YOU THINK
YOU’RE SO CLEVER
RIGHT NOW.
( sighs )
YOU ASKED FOR IT!
I’M THROWING THIS
AS HARD AS I CAN!
BURST LINK!
( gasping )
Taku: IF YOU THINK
THAT WAS JUST
LUCK, TRY AGAIN.
( growls )
BURST LINK. BURST LINK.
BURST LINK.
( panting )
DO YOU SEE?
EVEN SOMEONE LIKE
YOU CAN’T DENY
HOW COOL THAT WAS.
NOW YOU KNOW HOW
POWERFUL BRAIN BURST
REALLY IS--
( Chiyuri grunts )
Haru: AAH!
THAT WAS
HARSH.
AH, SHUT UP,
HE ASKED
FOR IT!
GREAT, NOW MY TUMMY’S
STARTING TO HURT.
Taku: BUT YOU STILL
HAVE A LOT LEFT.
THEN HELP ME
FINISH.
( giggles ) WE’RE ALL
GONNA EAT ’EM TOGETHER.
IT’S YOUR PUNISHMENT!
YOU SERIOUS?
OW...
COME ON.
LET’S DIG IN.
YOU SURE?
NOW HURRY UP,
BEFORE THEY ALL MELT.
OKAY, I THINK THAT
I’M GONNA GO FOR THE
SPECIAL PUDDING FLAVOR.
AND YOU, TAKU?
LET’S SEE...
PINE BOMBER.
VERY BERRY CHERRY.
DANGEROUS BANANA.
CHOCO BOUNCER.
( gasps )
BOUNCER.
HMM?
HEY, WHAT’S WRONG?
HARU’S STILL
AT LEVEL 2.
HUH?
A BOUNCER,
OF COURSE!
HEY! WE COULD GET
OURSELVES A BOUNCER.
A WHAT?
Haru: Y-YOUR HAIR
LOOKS NICE TODAY.
HUH?
OH. I JUST HAVE IT
LIKE THIS WHILE I’M EATING.
IT WAS GETTING
IN THE WAY OTHERWISE.
UH...OH...
BY THE WAY. GOOD NEWS.
I GOT A CLEAN
BILL OF HEALTH.
THEY SAID
I COULD GO HOME
ON WEDNESDAY.
REALLY?
THAT’S GREAT!
YES, NO MORE
PRISON FOOD FOR ME.
( laughs )
SO THEN, HOW ARE YOUR
TAG-TEAM MATCHES PROGRESSING?
DO YOU THINK YOU’LL BE ABLE
TO REACH LEVEL 2 BY WEDNESDAY?
YEAH. UM, I’M STILL
WORKING ON IT.
ACTUALLY, I’M
ALREADY AT THAT LEVEL.
BUT THE LAST THING I WANT IS
HER TO FIND OUT I SCREWED UP.
WELL, JUST SO YOU KNOW,
HARUYUKI...I’D LIKE FOR US
TO HAVE OUR OWN TERRITORY.
I’M THINKING THAT NEGA NEBULOUS
COULD CLAIM THE UNOCCUPIED
SUGINAMI DISTRICT.
BUT WE REALLY SHOULDN’T
MAKE THAT CLAIM UNTIL
YOU REACH LEVEL 2.
WELL, IT COULD
STILL HAPPEN.
I’M SUPPOSED TO
HAVE ANOTHER DUEL
LATER TODAY.
OH, REALLY?
A TAG-TEAM MATCH
WITH TAKUMU?
UM, YEAH...
WITH HIM.
I SEE...
WAIT, IS SOMETHING WRONG?
NOT AT ALL, GOOD LUCK.
JUST...DON’T BE IN
TOO BIG OF A RUSH, OKAY?
THE PROBLEM WITH LEVELING UP TOO
QUICKLY IS THAT IT PUTS YOU IN A
BAD POSITION WITH YOUR POINTS.
( screams )
BUT YOU WOULDN’T MAKE
SUCH A MISTAKE, I’M SURE.
YEAH, BUT...
I’LL BE CAREFUL.
PLEASE FORGIVE ME FOR
BEING SUCH AN IDIOT.
I CAN’T BELIEVE
HOW STUPID I AM.
Haru:
I CAN TAKE
IT FROM HERE.
WHOEVER THIS IS
MIGHT BE WATCHING
US ALREADY.
YEAH, OKAY. IF
ANYTHING HAPPENS THOUGH,
CONTACT ME RIGHT AWAY.
( grunts )
Taku: THIS GUY IS THE ONLY
PLAYER IN BRAIN BURST WHO
DOES THIS BOUNCER THING.
HE’S SORT OF
LIKE A BODYGUARD.
Haru:
A BODYGUARD?
YEAH. I’VE NEVER
REALLY MET HIM
IN PERSON.
BUT I’VE WATCHED HIM
FIGHT SEVERAL TIMES.
THE NAME
OF HIS AVATAR
IS AQUA CURRENT.
THE BURST LINKERS HE HELPS
ARE THE ONES WHOSE POINTS
ARE DANGEROUSLY LOW.
HE PARTNERS UP
WITH THEM
IN TAG MATCHES
UNTIL THEIR POINTS
ARE BACK TO
A SAFE NUMBER.
HE CAN DO SOMETHING
LIKE THAT?
SO HE MUST BE A REALLY
HIGH-LEVEL PLAYER.
NOT REALLY. HE’S KNOWN
AS "THE ONE," ’CAUSE
HE’S STILL AT LEVEL 1.
A BODYGUARD
WHO’S STILL
AT LEVEL 1?
YEAH, I KNOW.
BIZARRE, RIGHT?
I’M NOT REALLY SURE
HOW HE DOES IT.
HE HAS RULES AND
CONDITIONS YOU MUST MEET
TOO IF YOU WANT TO HIRE HIM.
THE FIRST RULE IS THAT
YOU HAVE TO BE
LEVEL 2 OR LOWER.
OTHERWISE, HE WON’T
EVEN BOTHER WITH YOU.
THE NEXT IS THAT YOU
MUST REVEAL YOUR TRUE
IDENTITY TO HIM.
THAT’S BASICALLY YOUR
PAYMENT. LEVERAGE HE
CAN KEEP ON YOU.
Haru:
GOT IT.
Computer voice:
MESSAGE FROM KUROYUKIHIME.
Taku: I TRIED TO GIVE
HIM MY IDENTITY, BUT HE
INSISTED ON HAVING YOURS.
DON’T WORRY ABOUT IT.
SO HOW AM I SUPPOSED
TO FIND THIS GUY?
Taku: YOU WON’T KNOW
UNTIL YOU GET TO
THE MEETING PLACE.
APPARENTLY, IT’LL ALL BE
REVEALED THERE.
Haru:
AND I HAVE
TO BE ALONE?
I MEAN, WE DON’T
EVEN KNOW FOR SURE
IF THIS IS SAFE.
OR IF HE’S
EVEN LEGIT.
DO YOU WANT ME TO
WATCH OUT FOR YOU?
NO, DON’T
DO THAT.
IF HE SPOTS YOU,
HE MAY DISAPPEAR
FOR GOOD.
AND I DON’T WANT
HIM TO THINK I’M
HIDING SOMETHING.
( gasps )
( beeping )
Waitress:
HERE’S YOUR
ORDER, SIR.
UM, WHOSE BAG
IS THIS?
I DON’T KNOW. I ASSUMED
IT BELONGED TO WHOEVER
YOU’RE WAITING FOR.
Male computer voice:
ENTER YOUR NAME.
Haru: NO, WAIT...
( camera clicks )
AAH!
UH...UH...
SO THAT’S HOW
HE DOES IT.
Male computer voice: PAYMENT
RECEIVED. THE MISSION WILL
COMMENCE AT 13:40.
STAY IN POSITION.
Haru: 13:40...?
SO, WHAT’S THIS MEAN?
I’M SUPPOSED TO WAIT
10 MINUTES TO BURST LINK?
JUST WHERE EXACTLY
IS HE WATCHING FROM?
OH, WELL. NO POINT IN
WORRYING ABOUT THAT NOW.
GUESS I HAVE TIME TO TAKE
A QUICK BATHROOM BREAK.
I DON’T KNOW WHY PLACES
LIKE THIS MAKE WANT TO
GO PEE, BUT THEY DO.
( grunting, screaming )
( loud thud )
( straining, gasping )
HUH?
( screaming )
I’M SORRY!
I’M SO SORRY!
I-I’M FINE.
I JUST...
( gasps )
YOU LOOKING
FOR THIS?
SORRY,
I JUST--
AAH!
HUH?
UM...
Y-YEAH?
PLEASE GIVE THAT
BACK TO ME.
SO, UM...
YES?
DOES THIS MEAN
THAT YOU’RE
AQUA CURRENT?
( grunts )
( sighs )
I DON’T KNOW
WHAT YOU MEAN.
THAT BAG DOESN’T
BELONG TO ME.
SORRY, I LIED.
( groaning )
SO TIRED.
Student 1: WHAT?!
YOU MEAN THE SAME MAYUZUMI
WHO WON THE LAST TOURNAMENT?
HMM?
Student 2: YEAH.
NOW THAT HE’S NOT
COMPETING, THE GUYS
ON OUR TEAM
THINK THEY HAVE A CHANCE
AT WINNING THIS
YEAR’S TOURNAMENT.
Student 1:
AWESOME!
MAYUZUMI?
DO THEY MEAN TAKU?
MAYBE I SHOULDN’T HAVE
PRETENDED LIKE I DIDN’T PUT IT
TOGETHER AND KNOW WHO SHE IS.
BUT I HAVE TO ADMIT,
I’M KINDA SHOCKED IT’S A GIRL.
I GUESS I SHOULDN’T
HAVE ASSUMED THE
BODYGUARD WOULD BE A GUY.
SOMETHING WRONG?
NO!
NOT AT ALL!
OH, NO, I THINK
I MADE HER MAD.
I HOPE THIS DOESN’T
SCREW THINGS UP.
I STILL NEED HER
TO ACCEPT MY REQUEST.
HUH...
AAH!
UH...SORRY, I DIDN’T
MEAN TO DO THAT.
WAIT!
HOLD ON A SEC!
STOP STALLING.
WE’RE...
GONNA DO THIS HERE?
BUT, UH....
Woman 1: ARE THEY
REALLY GOING TO
CABLE-LINK IN PUBLIC?
Woman 2: THAT GIRL
HAS NO SHAME.
LOOK, CABLE-LINKING
IS PRETTY MUCH JUST
A COUPLES’ THING.
AND YOU AND ME,
WE JUST MET.
WE DON’T KNOW
EACH OTHER.
I’M JUST AFRAID IF WE
DO THIS HERE,
PEOPLE ARE GONNA
GET THE WRONG IDEA.
I CAN’T HAVE SOMEONE
OVERHEAR THIS CONVERSATION.
SHE KINDA REMINDS
ME OF SENPAI.
ALWAYS TELLING PEOPLE
WHAT TO DO AND
BOSSING THEM AROUND.
OKAY, FINE.
Kuroyukihime:
TAKUMU FORFEITED.
I KNEW IT.
( knock on door )
YOU’RE HERE.
SO, UM...
BURST LINK!
♪
Kuroyukihime:
NEXT STAGE: "RESTORATION."
A TORTURED SOUL MUST LEARN
TO RAISE HIS FIST
IN ORDER TO RESTORE
SEVERED BONDS.