Haru:
WHAT DO YOU
EXPECT ME TO DO?
JUST GIVE YOU MY POINTS?
STAND HERE, LET YOU BEAT THE
CRAP OUT OF ME, THEN HAND
OVER TODAY’S PAYMENT TO YOU?
Seiji: I GOTTA SAY, YOU’RE
ACTING A LOT TOUGHER NOW THAT
YOU’RE INSIDE THAT DUEL AVATAR.
SHOULD I REMIND YOU
THAT IN THE REAL WORLD,
YOU’RE STILL SQUIRMING
UNDER MY FOOT LIKE A BUG?
DUSK TAKER.
I’VE NEVER HEARD
OF HIM BEFORE.
BUT HE IS AT
A PRETTY HIGH LEVEL.
WAIT A SEC...
YOU’VE BEEN GOING AROUND AND
THREATENING OTHER BURST LINKERS
AS WELL, SETTING TRAPS FOR THEM!
AND THEN YOU MAKE THEM PAY YOU
WITH THEIR BURST POINTS.
THAT’S HOW YOU KEEP LEVELING
UP WITHOUT EVER FIGHTING
ANYONE, ISN’T IT?!
VERY GOOD.
YOU’RE EXACTLY RIGHT.
BUT BEFORE I TAKE YOUR POINTS
AWAY FROM YOU TODAY,
THERE’S SOMETHING ELSE
I’M GONNA TAKE FROM YOU FIRST.
WHAT’S THAT?
LET’S JUST SAY...IT’S SOMETHING
VERY IMPORTANT TO YOU.
LOOK...A STAGE HAS
ALREADY BEEN SET FOR US.
LET’S GET THIS FIGHT
GOING NOW, SHALL WE?
( grunts )
DON’T GET COCKY.
I’M NOT SO EASY
TO BEAT IN THIS WORLD.
SO...IF YOU WANNA FIGHT...
THEN BRING IT ON!!!
( chuckles )
♪
( Seiji yells )
HOW’RE YOU FEELING NOW?!
YOU’RE NOTHING BUT A COWARD.
YOU DON’T HAVE THE NERVE TO
ACTUALLY FIGHT SOMEBODY.
THE ONLY WAY YOU’RE EVER GONNA
REACH THE TOP OF BRAIN BURST
IS BY PULLING SLIMY TRICKS ON
PEOPLE IN THE REAL WORLD.
YOU DON’T DESERVE
TO BE A BURST LINKER!
ONE MORE HIT
AND YOU’RE FINISHED.
( gasps )
SORRY...I’VE FOUGHT ENEMIES
LIKE YOU BEFORE.
BUT NONE OF THEM HAVE EVER
BEEN ABLE TO STOP ME.
ALL I’VE GOTTA DO IS KEEP
DRAGGING YOU AROUND,
CHIPPING AWAY AT YOUR HP,
AND YOU’LL BE DONE.
( gasps )
Haru: AAH!
OOH! UGH!
DAMN IT!
WHY NOW?!
( laughs ) YOU’RE BETTER
THAN I THOUGHT YOU’D BE, SENPAI.
BUT THEN AGAIN, THERE’D BE
NO POINT IN MAKING YOU MY DOG
IF YOU WEREN’T.
YOU CAN REGENERATE?
JUST LIKE...
A LIZARD’S TAIL...
I WOULD GO WITH OCTOPUS
OR SEA ANEMONE.
ALTHOUGH THE PREVIOUS OWNER
PREFERRED TO COMPARE IT TO
A STARFISH.
WHAT?
PREVIOUS OWNER?
AAH!
REMEMBER WHAT I SAID EARLIER?
THAT I’M GOING TO TAKE SOMETHING
IMPORTANT FROM YOU?
WELL, NOW YOU’LL SEE...
EXACTLY WHAT I MEANT.
DEMONIC COMMANDEER.
( gasps )
WHAT HAPPENED?
MY HP GAUGE HASN’T
GONE DOWN...
IS THERE, LIKE, SOME KIND
OF LAG TIME BEFORE HIS
SPECIAL MOVE KICKS IN?
WELL THEN...
ALL I’VE GOTTA DO IS FLY UP,
GET SOME SPEED, AND THEN
PUMMEL YOU INTO THE GROUND!
( gasping, grunting )
( laughs )
WHAT’S THE PROBLEM, SENPAI?
WHAT? MY WINGS...!
WHAT HAPPENED TO MY WINGS?!
OH, YEAH...
THAT!
AAH...
UGH...
THIS IS WHAT HAPPENED TO THEM.
( gasping )
( laughing )
YOUR AVIATION ABILITY?
WELL, THAT’S MY ABILITY NOW.
NO...THIS CAN’T BE HAPPENING.
IT CAN’T! NO WAY!
I HATE TO BREAK IT TO YOU...
BUT IT’S TRUE, ALL RIGHT.
( gasping )
Kuroyukihime: IN THE HISTORY
OF ACCELERATED WORLD,
THERE HAS NEVER BEEN
AN AVATAR WHO CAN FLY.
HARUYUKI, YOU’RE THE ONE WHO’S
GOING TO CHANGE THIS WORLD.
NO! SHE TOLD ME HERSELF.
SHE SAID I’M THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN FLY IN THIS WORLD.
THOSE WINGS BELONG TO ME.
THEY’RE MINE!
NO...THEY’RE ALL THAT I HAVE.
THEY’RE...THEY’RE MINE.
OH, PLEASE, STOP
WHINING ABOUT IT.
IT’S PATHETIC.
DEMONIC COMMANDEER IS
THE ONLY SPECIAL MOVE I HAVE.
BUT IT’S QUITE HANDY.
WITH IT, I CAN STEAL ONE OF
MY OPPONENT’S SPECIAL MOVES,
ENHANCED ARMAMENTS,
OR EVEN THEIR ABILITIES.
AND THE BEST PART ABOUT
MY SPECIAL MOVE IS THAT
IT HAS NO TIME LIMIT.
IT LASTS FOREVER.
THE ONLY LIMIT IS THE NUMBER
OF THINGS I CAN STOCKPILE
AT ONE TIME.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN IT LASTS
FOREVER? YOU CAN’T BE SERIOUS!
BUT THEN...THAT MEANS
I’LL NEVER GET MY WINGS BACK.
NO...NO!
THOSE WINGS ARE MINE.
GIVE THEM BACK!
( grunts )
OH, YOU’LL GET THEM
BACK EVENTUALLY.
I’LL GIVE ’EM BACK THE DAY
YOU GRADUATE FROM THIS SCHOOL.
PROVIDING, OF COURSE,
YOU KEEP GIVING ME
YOUR POINTS ON A DAILY BASIS.
I DON’T BELIEVE IT.
THIS CAN’T BE HAPPENING...
( grunts )
WELL...PLAYTIME’S OVER.
OF COURSE, THIS IS JUST A DREAM!
ALL I HAVE TO DO IS WAKE UP!
AAH!
I’LL BE TAKING THIS
WEEK’S CONTRIBUTION.
( disconnecting noise )
( gasps )
THANKS FOR THE POINTS, SENPAI.
YOU ARE WAY TOO GENEROUS.
I THINK WE NOW KNOW WHICH
ONE OF US IS THE MOST SUPERIOR.
IN BOTH THE ACCELERATED WORLD
AND IN THIS ONE.
I DO HOPE
YOU’LL FALL IN LINE.
WITH YOU AT THE BOTTOM OF THE
LADDER AND ME AT THE TOP...
IT’S ONLY NATURAL
FOR YOU TO DO MY BIDDING.
THAT’S THE WAY THIS WORLD WORKS.
( whimpering )
SAME GOES FOR YOU.
DON’T FORGET WHAT I SAID.
YOU BELONG TO ME NOW.
ONE LAST THING...
IT SHOULD GO WITHOUT SAYING...
BUT IF YOU TELL
EITHER MAYUZUMI SENPAI
OR YOUR MASTER ABOUT THIS,
YOU WILL NEVER SEE
YOUR WINGS AGAIN.
I STILL NEED TO PREPARE
A LITTLE MORE BEFORE I
CAN TAKE THOSE TWO ON.
SEE YA.
HARU, WHAT’LL WE DO?
I’M SCARED.
EVERYTHING HE SAID
REALLY FRIGHTENS ME.
WHY DID HE HAVE TO TALK TO US
LIKE THAT?! IT WAS SO AWFUL!
( gasps )
I’M SORRY, CHIYU.
I NEVER MEANT FOR YOU
TO GET SCARED LIKE THIS.
I THOUGHT I COULD
BEAT HIM ON MY OWN...BUT...
IT’S ALL OVER. ( sobbing )
I CAN’T DO ANYTHING
ABOUT IT NOW.
HE’S GONE AND TAKEN
MY WINGS AWAY FROM ME.
I CAN’T FIGHT ANYMORE.
WITHOUT THEM, I’M NOTHING!
( gasps )
NO...THIS ISN’T WHAT
I WANTED AT ALL! HE’S
RUINING EVERYTHING!
AND IT’S JUST...WHEN THE THREE
OF US WERE FINALLY GETTING BACK
TO THE WAY IT USED TO BE.
AFTER ALL THE TROUBLE
I WENT THROUGH...
( both sobbing )
♪
( doorbell chimes )
TAKU...
WHY WON’T YOU
TELL ME ANYTHING?
I SPOKE WITH CHI, BUT ALL
SHE SAID WAS TO TALK TO YOU.
BUT YOU’RE NOT EVEN
SAYING A SINGLE WORD!
WHAT’S GOING ON?
IS IT SOMETHING THAT
YOU CAN’T TELL ME?
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
IF YOU REALLY CAN’T TELL ME,
THEN I WON’T KEEP ASKING YOU.
BUT...AT LEAST
ANSWER ME THIS...
WHAT DOES CHI
MEAN TO YOU?
THE POOR GIRL IS CRYING
IN PAIN, AND YOU’VE
JUST IGNORED HER.
I CAN’T STAND IT ANYMORE.
CHI IS OUR FRIEND,
SO HOW CAN YOU DO THAT TO HER?!
DON’T YOU THINK I KNOW THAT?!
AND BESIDES...YOU STARTED THIS.
YOU’RE THE ONE WHO SENT ME THAT
PHOTO WITH THE VISUAL MASKING
PROGRAM IN IT!
IF YOU HAD JUST REALIZED
THAT FILE WAS WAY TOO BIG
TO BE A NORMAL PICTURE,
NONE OF THIS WOULD
HAVE HAPPENED!
( shuddering breath )
YEAH? WHAT ABOUT YOU?
JUST WHAT EXACTLY DOES
CHIYU MEAN TO YOU, TAKU?
IF YOU CARE SO MUCH ABOUT
HER, THEN GO BE WITH HER
INSTEAD OF COMING TO HARASS ME!
I WANTED TO...
BUT I COULDN’T...
ADMIT IT! YOU’RE STILL IN LOVE
WITH CHIYU, AREN’T YOU?!
YOU WISH THE TWO OF YOU
WERE STILL GOING OUT!
YES! I STILL LOVE HER!
I THINK ABOUT HER MORE THAN
I THINK ABOUT ANYBODY ELSE!
AND IT’S BECAUSE I LOVE HER
THAT I’VE STEPPED BACK TO LET
HER FIGURE OUT WHAT SHE WANTS.
EVEN IF IT TAKES HER FOREVER
TO MAKE THAT DECISION,
I’LL STILL BE THERE, WAITING.
REALLY?
JUST LIKE THAT?
YES.
AND WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO IF SHE
DECIDES THAT, IN THE END, THE
PERSON SHE WANTS ISN’T YOU?
HOW ARE YOU GONNA FEEL IF CHIYU
SAYS SHE WANTS TO BE WITH
SOMEONE ELSE INSTEAD?
IF THAT’S
HER CHOICE, FINE.
EVEN IF THE GUY SHE PICKS
HAPPENS TO BE YOU...
IF SHE THINKS YOU’LL MAKE
HER HAPPY...THEN FINE.
’CAUSE ALL I WANT IS
FOR HER TO BE HAPPY!
IS THAT HOW
YOU REALLY FEEL?
YEAH...
SO, WHAT YOU’RE SAYING IS THAT
YOU’LL BE WILLING TO JUST LET ME
HAVE CHIYU, IS THAT RIGHT?
HUH?
OH, I SEE...
I GET IT NOW, TAKU.
YOU’RE NOW IN LOVE WITH
KUROYUKIHIME SENPAI NOW,
AREN’T YOU?
THAT’S WHAT THIS IS ABOUT.
WAIT. WHY AM I
SAYING THESE THINGS?
THAT’S WHY YOU REALLY WANT ME
AND CHIYU TO GET TOGETHER.
NO!
I DON’T MEAN THAT!
IT’S SO OBVIOUS NOW.
YOU WANT SENPAI FOR YOURSELF!
HARU...I THOUGHT YOU AND I MADE
A PROMISE NOT TO KEEP SECRETS
FROM EACH OTHER ANYMORE.
OR MAYBE...YOU THINK THAT YOU
CAN NEVER TRUST ME AGAIN!
NO...THAT’S NOT IT...
( gasping ) TA...KU...
GOODBYE.
LOOK, I’M SORRY I HIT YOU.
OH, YEAH. I TOTALLY FORGOT THAT
THIS GAME HAD ALREADY COME OUT.
I THINK I’LL BUY IT.
LOAD IT ONTO MY NEURO-LINKER
AND JUST GET LOST PLAYING.
IF IT’S A HUGE PROGRAM
AND NEEDS TONS OF SPACE...
I’LL ERASE SOMETHING ELSE.
BRAIN BURST TAKES UP
A RIDICULOUS AMOUNT OF SPACE...
THAT’S IT, I SHOULD
JUST ERASE IT!
THEN NOMI’S PLAN WOULD FALL
APART...AND HE WOULDN’T BE
ABLE TO KEEP THREATENING CHIYU.
I CAN DO IT, IT’S NO BIG DEAL.
THINGS WOULD JUST BE
LIKE THEY WERE BEFORE.
BACK TO WHEN I WAS AT MY
LOWEST POINT, CONSTANTLY
BULLIED BY ARAYA AND HIS GANG.
BUT SO WHAT?
THAT’S LIFE.
THINGS COME AND GO.
I’LL JUST TRY AND PRETEND
LIKE I NEVER HAD IT
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
Seiji: OH, YOU’LL GET
THEM BACK EVENTUALLY.
I’LL GIVE ’EM BACK THE DAY
YOU GRADUATE FROM THIS SCHOOL.
PROVIDING, OF COURSE,
YOU KEEP GIVING ME YOUR
POINTS ON A DAILY BASIS.
( whimpering, sniffling )
DAMN IT! ALL RIGHT. I ADMIT IT!
YOU WIN, NOMI. YOU GOT ME!
Female announcer:
THE NEXT STOP: SASAZUKA
NICHOME, SASAZUKA NICHOME.
I’VE STILL GOTTA
GO WIN FIGHTS.
OR ELSE I’LL NEVER
EARN MORE POINTS.
I’M PRETTY CLOSE TO
THE GREEN LEGION’S TERRITORY.
I NEED AN OPPONENT.
ANYONE WILL DO!
IT’S THE WORLD’S END STAGE.
( motorcycle approaching )
( Haru gasps )
Ash Roller: LET’S YOU AND ME
GET BUSY, BABY!
MEGA LONG TIME, NO SEE, CROW!
UH, HI...
WASSUP?!
MISS ME SO MUCH THAT YOU CAME
ALL THE WAY TO BITTER VALLEY
JUST TO SEE ME?
BITTER VALLEY?
COME ON,
GET WITH IT.
FEEL MY VIBE, BRO.
I’M OBVIOUSLY
TALKIN’ ABOUT SHIBUYA!
OH...
WHAT’S THE DEALIO?
YOU SEEM DOWN.
I DON’T THINK "BITTER" IS
THE RIGHT TRANSLATION OF SHIBU.
HUH? ARE YOU FUCKIN’ SERIOUS?!
YEAH. FOR BITTER VALLEY
TO MAKE SENSE, THE PLACE
SHOULD BE CALLED "NIGAYA."
WELL, THEN WHAT’S A BETTER
TRANSLATION OF SHIBU?
I DON’T KNOW.
"ROUGH," MAYBE?
HUH?
ROUGH VALLEY...
HMM...
AH, FUCK IT.
NO ONE GIVES A SHIT!
WELL, YOU DID ASK ME...
SHUT YOUR CUM GUZZLER!
DON’T BE THINKIN’ YOU’RE SOME
KINDA BAD ASS JUST ’CAUSE
YOU GOT MORE POINTS THAN ME.
THIS IS GONNA MAKE YOU
SHIT YOUR PANTS!
HUH--? WHA--?
MISSILES?!
THAT’S RIGHT, BABY!
MISSILES WITH HOMING DEVICES,
YA BIG FLYING TURD.
NOW, GO ON.
TAKE TO THE SKY SO
I CAN MAKE YOU CRY!
WAIT...WHY AREN’T
YOUR WINGS OUT ALREADY?
WE’RE DOIN’ THIS
FOR REAL NOW.
SOMETHING’S HAPPENED...
SO I’M JUST GONNA BE FIGHTING
YOU ON THE GROUND TODAY.
HMM, ALL RIGHT.
FINE.
BUT THIS AIN’T GONNA
BE EASY, BITCH!
NOW, LET’S BOOGIE,
BITCH TITS!
( cackling )
I’VE FOUGHT MISTER ASH
MANY TIMES BEFORE.
I KNOW HOW TO BEAT HIM...
NOW!
UGH!
HEY, HEY, HEY!
DID YOU SEE THAT, BRO?!
IT’S MY NEW TRICK.
V-TWIN FISTS, BABY!
YEAH...HUH?
I THOUGHT I COULD WIN...
BUT OF COURSE I CAN’T.
I’M USELESS WITHOUT MY WINGS.
WHAT THE FUCK, CROW?
YOU DIDN’T TAKE
THAT MUCH DAMAGE.
WHY THE HELL
AREN’T YOU FLYIN’?
BECAUSE I CAN’T.
HUH?
LOOK, I GIVE UP.
JUST FINISH ME OFF.
THE ONLY REASON
I STARTED THIS DUEL...
WAS TO SEE IF I COULD STILL
HOLD MY OWN IN A FIGHT
WITHOUT MY WINGS.
BUT NOW I’VE REALIZED
THAT I CAN’T.
SO PLEASE, JUST END IT.
I’M NOT REALLY SURE WHAT THE
HELL IS GOIN’ ON,
BUT ARE YOU TELLIN’ ME
YOU CAN’T GET YOUR WINGS OUT?
AND BECAUSE YOU CAN’T FLY,
YOU’RE JUST GONNA LAY THERE
AND SAY YOU CAN’T WIN?
THERE’S JUST NO POINT
IN ME GETTING UP, OKAY?
LET ME ASK YOU SOMETHING...
DO YOU REMEMBER THE SECOND TIME
WE FOUGHT, WHEN YOU LIFTED UP
MY BIKE’S REAR TIRE?
YEAH...
YOU HAD ME, BRO.
WITH THAT ONE MOVE, YOU
PRETTY MUCH DISABLED THE
BIGGEST WEAPON I HAVE...MY BIKE.
BUT WHAT DID I DO?
DID I QUIT? DID I JUST SAY:
"FUCK IT. I GIVE UP"?
NO, BUT...
MY WINGS ARE PRETTY MUCH
GONE FOR GOOD.
THEY’RE NOT COMING BACK.
IT’S NOT THE SAME.
YOU STILL HAVE YOUR BIKE.
YOU WON’T UNDERSTAND.
SUCK IT!
OH!
GIGA SUCK IT!
NO, TERA SUCK IT, YA DUMBASS!
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA HOW
I FELT WHEN I SAW YOU FLY
FOR THE FIRST TIME?
AND LOOK, IT’S NOT JUST ME,
ALL THE OTHER BURST LINKERS TOO!
WHERE ARE YOU RIGHT NOW?
HUH?
I’M ASKING WHERE YOU
JUMPED IN FROM.
KOSHU HIGHWAY.
I’M TAKING A BUS.
OKAY, WE’LL FINISH THIS FIGHT
AND LET IT END IN A DRAW.
THEN GO STRAIGHT HOME
AND COME UP AT 9!
UH, UP WHERE?
I’M TALKIN’ ABOUT THE UNLIMITED
NEUTRAL FIELD, YA FART SUCKER.
AAH!
UH, EXCUSE ME!
WHERE THE HELL
ARE YOU TAKING ME?!
RIGHT THERE, DUDE.
CHECK IT.
YOU MEAN, THE OLD
TOKYO TOWER?
HELLS YEAH!
OKAY, WELL...YOU
WANNA TELL ME WHY
WE’RE GOING THERE?
YEAH, ABOUT THAT.
THERE’S THIS PERSON
I THINK YOU SHOULD MEET.
UH, WHO?
I’LL CUT TO THE CHASE:
SHE’S MY GUARDIAN.
REALLY?
WHO IS SHE?
SHE STEPPED AWAY FROM DUELING
A LONG TIME AGO, SO CHANCES ARE
YOU’VE NEVER HEARD OF HER.
SHE SCARED SO MANY PLAYERS,
THEY GAVE HER TITLES LIKE
STRONG ARM AND ICBM,
JUST TO NAME A FEW OF ’EM.
UH, ICBM?
SHE HAD ANOTHER NICKNAME TOO.
I THINK IT WAS "ICARUS."
YEAH, THAT ONE’S
NOT SO SCARY.
BEFORE YOU CAME ALONG...
SHE WAS THE ONLY BURST LINKER
IN THE ENTIRE ACCELERATED WORLD
WHO WAS CLOSE TO
BEING ABLE TO FLY.
MISTER ASH...UM...
SO, WHAT NOW?
DON’T INTERRUPT ME,
MICRO WANG!
I’M WAITING FOR
THE WIND TO STOP.
UH...OKAY...
( wind blowing )
HELLS YEAH, BITCHES!
HERE’S OUR CHANCE!
HANG ON TIGHT!
HUH?
( yells )
VERTICAL CLIMB SET-UP!
HOLY COW!
WHAT?
DID YOU FORGET ABOUT MY
WALL-CLIMBING ABILITY?
OH, YEAH, THAT’S RIGHT.
YOU USED THAT IN
OUR SECOND FIGHT.
SHIT!
THIS WIND IS SHIT!
HUH?
AAH!
BETTER HOLD ON
MEGA TIGHT!
I REALLY DON’T
UNDERSTAND A WORD
YOU’RE SAYING!
( growls )
FLY HIGH!
YES!
A NICE, SAFE LANDING!
THAT’S IT! I’M NEVER GONNA
RIDE IN ANYTHING WITH LESS
THAN FOUR WHEELS EVER AGAIN!
YOU’RE MISSIN’
THE POINT, BRO.
BIKES ARE FUN TO RIDE
’CAUSE THEY CAN TIP OVER.
YEAH, BUT WE NEARLY DID
A WHOLE LOT MORE THAN
JUST TIP OVER BACK THERE.
( gasps )
YO...GET OFF
THE BIKE.
YEAH, OKAY...
SO, THIS IS
MISTER ASH’S GUARDIAN?
IT’S BEEN A LONG TIME, ASH.
IT’S GOOD TO SEE YOU.
I’M GLAD TO KNOW THAT YOU
HAVEN’T FORGOTTEN ABOUT ME.
UH, I-I-IT’S GOOD
TO SEE YOU TOO, MASTER.
AND THERE’S, LIKE,
NO WAY I COULD EVER
FORGET ABOUT YOU.
WOW, I’VE NEVER SEEN HIM
SOUND SO NERVOUS.
AND YOU MUST BE
SILVER CROW.
UH, YES, MA’AM!
IT’S-IT’S NICE
TO MEET YOU.
I’M SKY RAKER.
AND THE PLEASURE IS ALL MINE.
IT’S AN HONOR TO MAKE
YOUR ACQUAINTANCE, MR. CROW.
♪
Kuroyukihime:
NEXT STAGE: "IMAGINATION."
DRIVEN BY HIS STRONG
DESIRE, HARUYUKI AIMS
FOR THE SKIES ONCE AGAIN.