Teacher: LASTLY,
THE PRINTING PRESS... ALL RIGHT.
SO WHEN YOU ADD THAT
TO THE LIST ALONG WITH--
Computer:
YOU’VE GOT MAIL.
Teacher: ALONG WITH
THE COMPASS AND GUNPOWDER
YOU HAVE WHAT IS
MORE COMMONLY KNOWN AS
THE THREE GREAT INVENTIONS
OF THE RENAISSANCE AGE.
NOW...
HOW HISTORICALLY SIGNIFICANT
WERE EACH OF THESE INVENTIONS?
WELL, IF YOU WERE TO COMPARE
THESE TO AN INVENTION FROM
THE 21st CENTURY IT WOULD BE
EQUIVALENT TO THE INVENTION
OF THE QUANTUM MOBILE
COMPUTER TERMINAL,
WHAT WE CALL THE NEURO-LINKER.
THIS HAS BEEN, BY FAR,
ONE OF THE GREATEST INVENTIONS--
( loud electronic sounds,
Haru gasping )
THE NEURO-LINKER CREATED
AN IT REVOLUTION THAT AFFECTED
THE DAILY LIVES
OF EVERY MEMBER OF SOCIETY.
( Araya laughing)
BRING ME TWO YAKISOBA BUNS,
ONE MELON CREAM BUN,
AND A STRAWBERRY YOGURT
TO THE ROOF AT LUNCHTIME TODAY.
AND DON’T BE LATE, OR ELSE.
Teacher: ALL RIGHT. I THINK
I’VE MADE THIS PRETTY CLEAR
HOWEVER, IF THERE ARE
ANY QUESTIONS, CLASS,
NOW WOULD BE
THE TIME TO ASK THEM.
( grunts )
AW, STOP BEING
SO SCARED,
PUDGE BOY.
AS LONG AS WE STAY
OUT OF SIGHT FROM
THE SECURITY CAMERAS,
NO ONE CAN SEE A THING.
( chuckles )
YO, WHAT’S THIS CRAP?
WHY AM I HOLDING
ONLY ONE YAKISOBA BUN?
Haru: IT WAS ALL
THAT WAS LEFT.
COME ON!
YOU CAN’T EVEN
HANDLE A SIMPLE ERRAND?
LISTEN HERE, PIGGY.
TOMORROW I WANT
TWO MELON CREAM BUNS
AND FIVE STRAWBERRY YOGURTS.
AND YOU BETTER HOPE TO GOD
YOU DON’T SCREW IT UP.
THIS IS YOUR FINAL LAST CHANCE,
YOU GOT THAT?
WHY WOULD YOU CALL SOMETHING
YOUR “FINAL LAST CHANCE”?
THAT’S COMPLETELY REDUNDANT.
BONEHEAD.
BONEHEAD!
( sighs )
IF I COULD JUST
SAY THAT TO HIS FACE.
( stomach rumbles )
( sighs )
( beeps )
OPEN DIRECT LINK.
( beeping )
SORRY I’M LATE.
LET’S GO.
( grunting )
Girl: LOOK! IT’S
THE STUDENT VICE PRESIDENT!
Girl Two:
WOW, SHE’S PRETTY.
( indistinct chatter )
THAT’D BE SO AWESOME.
( giggling )
SO, KUROYUKIHIME...
HOW DO YOU CREATE
SUCH AWESOME AVATARS?
MINE DON’T COME OUT
LOOKING NEARLY AS COOL.
IT’S NOT EASY
TO TRY AND DESIGN
YOUR TRUE NATURE.
HOW’D YOU GET
THAT GLOSSY TEXTURE?
Whoop.
( groaning )
( indistinct chatter )
Girl: WOW!
KUROYUKIHIME LOOKED AT ME!
( chatter continues )
( panting )
Haru: WHAT AM I GETTING
SO WORKED UP ABOUT?
GIRLS LIKE THAT
ARE NEVER GONNA BE
INTERESTED IN SOMEONE LIKE ME.
THIS IS IT.
THIS IS THE ONLY PLACE I HAVE.
( grunts )
HERE, I’M AN AMAZING ATHLETE.
WHO NEEDS THAT
CRAPPY REALITY ANYWAY?
( grunting )
REAL CLASSROOMS ARE LAME.
WHY DO WE STILL EVEN HAVE THEM?
WHY CAN’T EVERYTHING BE
IN THE VIRTUAL WORLD?
DAMN IT!
FASTER.
I WANNA GO FASTER.
IN THIS THIS WORLD...
AND THE REAL ONE.
FAST ENOUGH TO LEAVE EVERYONE
BEHIND AND GO SOMEWHERE...
NO ONE ELSE CAN!
( bells, cheering )
Girl: AHA!
Haru: AHH!
SO, THIS IS WHERE
YOU’RE HIDING!
I’VE SPENT MY ENTIRE
LUNCH BREAK TRYING TO
FIGURE OUT WHERE YOU ARE.
HUH! WHAT IS ALL THIS?
YOU’RE ON LEVEL 152,
WITH 2,630,000 POINTS?!
YOU’RE...
A COMPLETE IDIOT!
AHH!
THIS IS INSANE.
COME ON, LINK OUT NOW!
IT’S MY LIFE,
I’LL DO WHAT I WANT.
LEAVE ME ALONE.
OH, OKAY.
SO THAT’S HOW YOU’RE
GOING TO BE, HUH?
FINE, LINK OUT!
HMPF.
( grunts )
AH!
CHIYU?! WHAT’RE
YOU DOING HERE?
HMM. ( giggles )
I HIT YOU WITH
A FORCED LINK OUT!
THAT MEANS I WIN!
YOU DO REALIZE THIS
IS THE BOY’S RESTROOM
YOU’RE IN!
HAVE YOU GONE CRAZY?
YOU’RE THE ONE
WHO’S CRAZY.
SO HOW DID YOU
EVEN FIND ME ANYWAY?
( sighs )
WELL, I SAW
WHAT HAPPENED TO YOU.
( gasps )
HARU, WHY DON’T YOU
SHOW THOSE EMAILS
THEY SEND YOU TO A
TEACHER OR SOMETHING?
MAYBE IF I’M LUCKY
THEY’LL GET SUSPENDED.
BUT THEN THEY’LL
JUST COME BACK.
THEN, WHY DON’T YOU
TELL TAKU ABOUT IT?
I’M SURE
HE WOULD BE HAP--
DON’T TELL TAKU
ABOUT THIS!
I’M FINE, OKAY.
I’VE ACCEPTED THAT THIS
IS WHAT SCHOOL IS FOR ME.
I’M A LOSER.
I KNOW THAT.
SO DON’T WASTE YOUR TIME.
H-HOLD ON A SEC.
AT LEAST TAKE THIS.
IT’S LUNCHTIME.
YOU NEED TO EAT.
HERE. I MADE
ALL YOUR FAVORITES.
GO AWAY!
( gasps )
I DON’T WANT IT!
( whimpers )
Haru: I KNOW I SHOULD
APOLOGIZE TO HER,
SO WHY CAN’T
I MAKE MYSELF DO IT?
I’M SUCH A COWARD!
CHIYURI... SHE WAS CRYING.
DIRECT LINK.
( gasps )
LEVEL... 166?
THERE’S SOMEONE WHO’S
BETTER AT THIS THAN ME?
THIS WAS IT.
THIS WAS MY ONE THING!
I DON’T BELIEVE IT!
VIRTUAL GAMES WERE ALL I HAD.
NOBODY COULD EVER BEAT ME HERE.
( crying )
AT LEAST THAT’S WHAT I THOUGHT.
Girl: WERE YOU THE ONE
WHO WAS ABLE
TO GET THAT
RIDICULOUSLY HIGH SCORE?
WANT TO ACCELERATE?
WANT TO TAKE THIS EVEN FURTHER,
YOUNG MAN?
IF SO, SCHOOL LOUNGE,
LUNCH TOMORROW.
( gasps )
COULD THAT REALLY HAVE BEEN HER?
( indistinct chatter )
HEY THERE!
HUH?
WHAT’S WRONG?
DO YOU NEED
SOMETHING?
WELL, I...
I JUST... UM...
Girl: WHO’S THE FAT KID?
Boy: DOESN’T HE KNOW THAT
FIRST YEAR STUDENTS AREN’T
WELCOME IN THIS LOUNGE?
WELL, YOU SEE I...
Kuroyukihime:
AH, YOU’RE HERE.
HUH?
IT’S ALL RIGHT EVERYBODY.
HE’S WITH ME.
WOULD YOU BE SO KIND AS
TO LET HIM COME THROUGH.
HUH...
MMM...
WAIT A SEC...
BUT HIME...
SORRY, UM,
WHAT’S THIS FOR?
NOTHING TO BE
ALARMED ABOUT,
JUST PLUG IT INTO
YOUR DEVICE.
WHAT?!
BUT PEOPLE ONLY DO
THIS WHEN THEY’RE,
LIKE, DATING EACH OTHER.
AHH!
SORRY FOR DRAGGING YOU ALL
THE WAY HERE, HARUYUKI ARITA.
CAN YOU USE NEURO SPEAK?
YES, BUT...
WOULD YOU MIND TELLING ME
WHAT THIS IS ALL ABOUT?
IS THIS SOME SORT OF
ELABORATE PRANK OR SOMETHING?
WELL, I GUESS
IN SOME WAYS, IT IS.
YOU SEE...
WHAT I’M ABOUT TO DO IS
SEND YOU AN APPLICATION.
I’M SENDING IT DIRECTLY
TO YOUR NEURO-LINKER.
Computer voice:
LOAD APPLICATION?
IF YOU ACCEPT IT,
YOUR CURRENT REALITY
WILL BE DESTROYED.
REBUILT IN ITS PLACE
WILL BE A WORLD
LIKE YOU HAVE
NEVER DREAMED OF.
Haru:
SHE WANTS TO DESTROY...
MY REALITY?
THAT’S PERFECT.
IF IT CAN DESTROY MY REALITY,
LET’S DO IT.
WHAT EXACTLY IS IT...
THIS BRAIN BURST PROGRAM?
I’LL EXPLAIN ONCE
IT’S SAFELY INSTALLED.
UM..."SAFELY"?
INSTALLATION FAILURES
ARE NOT INCREDIBLY UNCOMMON.
HUH?!
"WELCOME TO..."
"THE ACCELERATED WORLD"?
I HAD A FEELING YOU’D
BE OKAY WITH THIS PROGRAM.
GLAD TO SEE I WASN’T WRONG.
YOU KNOW, IT TOOK A GOOD
TWO MINUTES FOR ME TO DECIDE
WHETHER OR NOT I WANTED
TO ACCEPT THIS PROGRAM.
I PREPARED A LITTLE SPEECH,
BUT I CAN SEE NO PERSUASION
WAS NEEDED ON YOU.
UH...
Boy: HEY!
FAT ASS!
THINK YOU WERE GONNA GET
AWAY WITH THIS, DID ’YA?
YOU WERE SUPPOSED TO BRING
ME MY MELON BUNS AND YOGURT.
NOW YOU GOTTA PAY.
Hime: WELL,
HELLO THERE.
HUH?
YOU’RE ARAYA,
CORRECT?
( chuckling )
YOUR FRIEND HERE HAS
TOLD ME ALL ABOUT YOU.
HUH?
ABOUT THE MIX UP.
HOW YOU WERE SUPPOSED
TO BE SENT TO A ZOO,
BUT SOMEHOW ENDED UP
AT OUR SCHOOL INSTEAD.
WAIT!
I DIDN’T SAY THAT!
Haru:
WHAT’S SHE DOING?
WHY’D SHE SAY THAT?
( clears throat )
( yells )
SO...THAT’S
WHAT YOU TOLD HER?!
THAT DOES IT!
YOU ARE DEAD,
PIGGY!
NOW!
SHOUT IT.
BURST LINK!
B-B-BURST LINK!
( grunts )
HUH?
WHAT... IS THIS?
I’D PREFER IT IF YOU
DIDN’T STARE AT MY LEGS.
I HAD HOPED THEY WERE
OUTSIDE OF THE VIEW
OF THE SECURITY CAMERAS,
BUT THIS IS FINE.
UM, WHAT JUST HAPPENED?
WHAT WE’VE DONE IS UTILIZE
ONE OF THE FUNCTIONS
OF THE BRAIN BURST PROGRAM.
WE’VE SIMPLY...
ACCELERATED.
ACCELERATED?
EXACTLY.
THE ACCELERATED WORLD.
WE’RE NOW BOTH STANDING IN
THE REALM OF THE BURST LINKER.
BURST LINKER?
ACCELERATED WORLD?
WHAT?
HMM.
( groans )
IT WOULD APPEAR THAT
EVERYTHING AROUND US
HAS FROZEN IN TIME,
BUT THAT IS NOT THE CASE.
( grunting )
THIS BLUE WORLD
IS SIMPLY A 3-D
RECONSTRUCTION OF IMAGES.
THESE IMAGES ARE
ALL PULLED FROM
THE MULTIPLE SECURITY CAMERAS
HERE WITHIN THE LOUNGE.
BY UTILIZING
ACCELERATED BRAINWAVES,
WE ARE ABLE TO SEE
THIS WORLD THROUGH
OUR NEURO-LINKER.
WE’VE ACCELERATED
OUR BRAINWAVES?
YES, BY ABOUT ONE THOUSAND
TIMES THEIR NORMAL RATE.
HUH?
SO ONE SECOND IN REALITY
FEELS LIKE
ONE THOUSAND SECONDS.
IN THIS DIMENSION THAT’S
16 MINUTES AND 40 SECONDS.
SO, THEN...
BY USING THIS POWER...
WHEN SOMEBODY SUCH AS YOURSELF
IS ABOUT TO GET PUNCHED,
THEY CAN ACCELERATE
AT A CRITICAL MOMENT.
NOW YOU HAVE TIME TO ASSESS
THE BEST COURSE OF ACTION...
AND THEN PROCEED.
I SEE.
I NEVER DREAMED THERE’D
BE A WAY TO AVOID GETTING HIT.
BUT DON’T AVOID IT!
WHAT?
YOU SHOULD MAKE SURE HE LANDS
THAT HIT GOOD AND HARD.
HUH?
JUST TRUST ME.
NO WAY!
ARE YOU CRAZY?!
THAT PUNCH IS GONNA
HURT LIKE HELL!
BUT THIS IS YOUR CHANCE.
HUH?
LOOK, HE KNOWS
WHAT HE’S DOING.
HE AVOIDS
GETTING IN TROUBLE
BY ALWAYS OPERATING OUTSIDE
THE VIEW OF THE CAMERAS.
BUT I’VE PROVOKED HIM
AND HE REACTED.
HE’S GONE AND LOST IT IN
FRONT OF SEVERAL CAMERAS
AND MULTIPLE WITNESSES.
YOU NOW HAVE A PERFECT
OPPORTUNITY FOR REVENGE.
YEAH BUT...
COULDN’T I USE BRAIN BURST TO...
BEAT HIM IN A FIGHT INSTEAD?
YES, YOU COULD DO THAT.
AFTER ALL, YOU ARE
NOW A BURST LINKER
WITH POWERS THAT NORMAL
PEOPLE CAN’T COMPETE WITH.
( breathing heavily,
sighs )
NO. OKAY,
YOU’RE RIGHT.
I’LL JUST STAND THERE
AND TAKE THE PUNCH.
IT’S A PRETTY PERFECT CHANCE.
HUH!
YOU HAVE MADE
A VERY WISE CHOICE.
LET’S MAKE THE MOST OF IT,
SHALL WE?
HOW?
WHEN WE STOP ACCELERATION,
THROW YOURSELF BACKWARDS
AS HARD AS YOU CAN.
BUT, IF I DO THAT
I’LL CRASH INTO YOU.
YES. LIKE I SAID,
WE’RE MAKING THE MOST OF IT.
DON’T WORRY ABOUT ME.
I’VE THOUGHT THIS THROUGH.
ALL RIGHT.
PUT ON YOUR BEST SHOW.
I’LL TRY.
BURST OUT!
B-BURST OUT!
( both gasp )
( grunting )
Haru:
SENPAI?
( everyone screaming )
Man: TEACHER!
GET A TEACHER!
ARE YOU OKAY?
Hime:
LOOK HURT!
BUT--BUT
YOU’RE BLEEDING!
DON’T WORRY.
IT’S JUST A SMALL CUT.
LIKE I SAID,
WE’RE MAXIMIZING
THE DAMAGE HERE.
THIS WAY, ARAYA WILL
NEVER BOTHER YOU AGAIN.
EVER.
( gasps )
THAT WAS VERY WELL DONE.
HERE’S TO THE FUTURE
OF OUR FRIENDSHIP,
HARUYUKI...
( stammering )
Hime: I FORGOT TO TELL YOU,
DON’T REMOVE THE NEURO-LINKER
UNTIL YOU’RE BACK
AT SCHOOL TOMORROW.
AND MOST IMPORTANTLY,
WHATEVER YOU DO,
DO NOT CONNECT
TO THE GLOBAL NET.
NOT EVEN FOR A SECOND!
GOT IT?
( sighs )
Computer: DISCONNECT
FROM THE GLOBAL NET?
CHIYU.
Chiyu:
I HEARD ABOUT WHAT
HAPPENED AT LUNCH.
Haru:
HUH, AT LUNCH?
OH...
THAT CREEP HITTING YOU
AND SENDING YOU FLYING.
UH... YEAH.
IS THAT FROM
THE INCIDENT?
HUH?
THAT BANDAGE
ON YOUR FACE.
ARE YOU OK?
YEAH, I’M FINE.
IT’S JUST A SCRATCH.
WELL, THAT’S GOOD.
HEY HARU, IS IS IT TRUE YOU
CABLE LINKED WITH KUROYUKIHIME?
HUH?
WELL, UH... YEAH.
HMM...
HMM.
HEY, BY THE WAY...
ABOUT YESTERDAY...
Boy:
HEY! HARU! CHI!
( sighs )
Haru: TAKU!
GREAT.
PERFECT TIMING.
YOU HEADED HOME?
I SAW THE FOOTAGE OF YOU
AT THE KENDO TOURNAMENT
THE OTHER DAY.
IT WAS YOUR
FIRST YEAR COMPETING,
AND YOU WON.
THAT’S AMAZING!
NAH.
I JUST GOT LUCKY.
I OWE IT ALL
TO CHI FOR COMING
TO SUPPORT ME
AND BRINGING ME
THAT AWESOME LUNCH.
SO A LUNCH FROM CHIYU
GIVES YOU SPECIAL POWERS,
DOES IT?
YEAH. I GUESS.
BUT YOU SHOULD KNOW
THIS FOR YOURSELF, HARU.
DIDN’T YOU ALSO GET
ONE OF HER LUNCHES YESTERDAY?
( chuckles )
HM?
HOW DID YOU KNOW ABOUT THAT?
HUH?
Haru: DID TAKU TELL HER
TO MAKE ME THAT LUNCH?
BUT WHY WOULD HE DO THAT?
WAIT!
SHE DIDN’T TELL HIM
ABOUT ARAYA, DID SHE?
OF COURSE.
THAT’S WHY SHE MADE IT.
( gasps )
( grunts )
HEY, HARU!
GOTTA GO.
I JUST REMEMBERED THERE’S
A SHOW I WANNA WATCH.
SEE YOU LATER, GUYS.
( both sigh )
IT’S ALL OVER.
TAKU KNOWS!
( panting )
JUST WHEN I FINALLY
GET GOT RID OF ARAYA.
WHO AM I KIDDING?
IT’LL ALWAYS BE THIS WAY.
THIS IS MY CRAPPY REALITY.
( laughing )
STOP LOOKING AT ME LIKE THAT.
I CAN’T STAND IT ANYMORE!
TAKE ME WITH YOU.
THAT’S WHERE I WANT TO BE.
UP THERE!
I WANT TO FLY
SOMEWHERE FAR AWAY!
( echoing voices )
SO, IS THAT YOUR WISH?
Haru: I FEEL LIKE
I HAD A REALLY WEIRD DREAM.
BUT WHAT WAS IT ABOUT?
MOM, I NEED
LUNCH MONEY.
( sighs )
HARUYUKI,
YOU’RE NOT ON THE NET.
OH, RIGHT.
Computer:
CONNECTING TO THE GLOBAL NET.
SEE YA LATER.
DID I JUST...
ACCELERATE?
AM I IN A VIRTUAL WORLD?
BUT WHY?
IS THAT...
UH...
IS THIS... THING ME?
( gasps,
motorcycle revving )
I HAVEN’T FOUGHT IN THE WORLD’S
END STAGE IN A WHILE.
LUCKY ME!
AND EVEN BETTER,
MY OPPONENT IS A NEWBIE.
NOW I’M MEGA LUCKY!
YOU ON THE OTHER HAND...
ARE GIGA UNLUCKY!
( laughing )
( gasps )
♪
Hime:
NEXT STAGE, TRANSFORMATION.
WHEN HARUYUKI
GETS A NEW AVATAR
AND IS CHALLENGED TO A FIGHT,
HIS WORLD BECOMES
CHANGED FOREVER.