(YELLING)
NO!
I’M NOT DONE YET!
(GRUNTING)
(VIBRATING
NOISE)
(GASPING)
CITRON...
CALL!
(CHUCKLES)
I DON’T GET IT.
WHY, CHIYU?!
THAT REALLY IS
QUITE AMAZING.
I THINK I LIKE THIS
HEALING ABILITY.
(LAUGHS)
IT TRULY IS
A MIRACULOUS POWER.
(LAUGHS)
NOMI!
WHAT DID YOU
DO TO CHIYU?
(LAUGHING)
ANSWER ME, NOMI!
♪
THE AVIATION
AND HEALING ABILITIES.
BOTH OF THESE
INCREDIBLY RARE
POWERS ARE NOW MINE.
THE RUSH I GET FROM
PLUNDERING IS TRULY AWESOME.
THIS FEELING OF ABSOLUTE POWER.
TAKING AWAY A PERSON’S HOPES
AND DREAMS, THEN JUST
TRAMPLING ALL OVER THEM!
OH, I LOVE IT SO MUCH,
I CAN’T GET ENOUGH OF IT!
YOU BASTARD.
GIVE IT UP, SENPAI.
THIS FIGHT’S BEEN DECIDED.
ONLY THING YOU CAN DO NOW
IS GET BACK DOWN ON YOUR
KNEES AND BEG ME FOR MERCY.
WHAT ARE YOU
WAITING FOR? DO IT.
I LOVE TO WATCH YOU BEG.
AND I’M SURE MY NEW PARTNER
IS LOOKING FORWARD TO
SEEING IT TOO.
NOMI!
(TAKU YELLING)
TAKU!
NO ONE GETS AWAY WITH
MAKING CHI CRY!
OH, PLEASE.
YOU’RE JUST
EMBARRASSING YOURSELF,
MAYUZUMI SENPAI.
TAKU!
NO!
AAH!
SEIJI: BE GONE ALREADY!
(GASPS)
NO...
NO!!
TAKU!
SEIJI: (LAUGHS) YOU LOSERS
NEVER CEASE TO AMAZE ME
WITH YOUR STUPIDITY.
YOU STRUGGLE SO HARD,
THROWING AWAY YOUR
LAST SHRED OF DIGNITY.
(SHUDDERING BREATHS)
I MUST SAY, MAYAZUMI SENPAI,
I THOUGHT YOU WERE
MORE CLEVER THAN THAT.
SO DISAPPOINTING.
IN THE END, YOU’RE JUST
ANOTHER BUG TO BE SQUASHED.
NOMI...
I HATE YOU...
I HATE YOU!!
ARMOR OF CATASTROPHE:
THEN DESTROY HIM.
(GASPS)
DESTROY AND DEVOUR.
FEAST ON HIS FLESH,
DRINK HIS BLOOD DRY,
AND SWALLOW HIM WHOLE.
DESTROY...
DEVOUR...
NO...MI...
WHAT? YOU STILL HAVEN’T
GIVEN UP YET, ARITA SENPAI?
DO YOU REALLY WANT TO SUFFER
THE HUMILIATION OF UTTER
DEFEAT LIKE YOUR FRIEND HERE?
ARE YOU THAT DESPERATE
TO PROVE YOUR SO-CALLED
"FRIENDSHIP"?
UGH, HOW NAUSEATING.
NO...MI...
ARMOR OF CATASTROPHE:
YES, DEVOUR HIM.
RIP HIM APART.
DEVOUR!
(HARU SCREAMING)
YOUR ATTACKS ARE STEMMING
FROM HATRED NOW.
SHUT UP, NOMI!
I’M SICK OF YOU!
GET THE FUCK
OUT OF MY LIFE!
GET OUT, GET OUT,
GET OUT, GET OUT!
WHY YOU SNEAKY
LITTLE PIECE OF...
(HARU YELLING)
STOP. PLEASE STOP.
GET OUT!
(YELLING)
STOP IT!
(GRUNTS)
TEACHER:
COME ON, ARITA.
GET UP.
HARU: OH, I GUESS...
TIME RAN OUT.
(ANGRY BREATH)
ARITA!
HEY, WHAT’S WRONG?
YOU GOTTA PEE?
(LAUGHING)
HARU!
STOP, WHAT ARE YOU
PLANNING TO DO?
COME ON,
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
IT’S CLEAR.
NOMI DID SOMETHING
TO CHIYU.
AND WHAT’S YOUR PLAN, HUH?
FIND HIM AND GO
PUNCH HIM IN THE FACE?
AND THEN YOU’LL GET
BUSTED FOR BEATING UP
A FIRST YEAR STUDENT?
(ANGRY GRUNT)
SO WHAT?
YOU THINK WE SHOULD
JUST DO NOTHING?
HE’S THREATENING CHIYU
SOMEHOW AND IS FORCING
HER TO DO WHAT HE SAYS!
I KNOW!
BUT IF WE LOSE OUR HEADS
AND DO SOMETHING STUPID,
WE’LL PLAY RIGHT INTO HIS HANDS!
LOOK, I’M ANGRY
ABOUT THIS TOO.
MAYBE EVEN MORE THAN YOU.
MAYBE. YOU DID LUNGE
AT HIM AND ATTACK
HIM EVEN BEFORE I DID.
YEAH, I KNOW.
I CAN’T REMEMBER THE LAST
TIME I SNAPPED LIKE THAT.
HARU...
THE TWO OF US WILL
DO THIS TOGETHER.
YOU AND ME,
WE’RE GOING TO
PROTECT CHI.
TAKU: THIS AREA IS A BLIND
SPOT FOR THE SECURITY CAMERAS.
IN CASE NOMI HAS TAPPED INTO
THEM AND IS USING THEM FOR
SURVEILLANCE, IN THIS SPOT...
HE CAN NEITHER
SEE NOR HEAR US.
SO, WHAT IS IT?
WHAT’S HE
BLACKMAILING YOU WITH?
COME ON, CHI, PLEASE.
TELL US.
LISTEN, THERE’S NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT, I PROMISE.
WITH YOUR POWER,
WE CAN BEAT HIM.
SO WHATEVER HE
THREATENED YOU WITH...
HE DIDN’T.
HUH?
HE DIDN’T COME TO ME
AND THREATEN ME.
I WAS THE ONE
WHO WENT TO NOMI.
I ASKED HIM
TO BE MY PARTNER.
I SAID IF HE SHARED
HIS POINTS WITH ME,
I’D BE HIS HEALER.
NO WAY...
COME ON, DON’T BE STUPID.
WHY WOULD YOU DO
SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
HOLD ON A SECOND.
DID HE PLANT A BUG ON YOU?
NO. LISTEN.
IT’S TRUE.
I’VE JOINED UP WITH
NOMI, SO JUST ACCEPT IT.
YOU CAN’T BE SERIOUS.
I’LL SAY IT AGAIN:
THIS IS ALL ENTIRELY
MY CHOICE.
THE IDEA WAS MINE
AND MINE ALONE.
THIS CAN’T BE TRUE...
I THINK IT’S BEST GOING FORWARD
THAT WE AND NEGA NEBULOUS
STAY OUT OF EACH OTHER’S WAY.
I MEAN, WE ALL KNOW
EACH OTHER’S REAL IDENTITIES.
BYE.
CHIYU.
( SHUDDERING BREATHS)
I THOUGHT YOU BECAME A
BURST LINKER SO THE THREE
OF US COULD BE TOGETHER AGAIN!
PLEASE, YOU CAN’T GO!
(QUIET SOBBING)
WANNA...STOP BY?
SURE...
YOU WANNA
EAT SOMETHING?
I’VE GOT FROZEN PIZZA,
BUT THAT’S ABOUT IT.
THAT’S FINE.
THANKS.
IF IT’S TRUE THAT SHE
JUST WANTED TO GET
MORE POINTS...
THEN TEAMING UP WITH
NOMI INSTEAD OF US
WOULD BE THE BETTER MOVE.
BUT THIS IS CHIYU. SHE’S NOT
SMART LIKE THAT WITH GAMES.
COMPUTER: HEATING STARTED.
I MEAN, SHE’S THE KIND OF
PLAYER THAT COULD EVEN LOSE
DURING A SCRIPTED
RPG BATTLE, YA KNOW?
DO YOU ACTUALLY BELIEVE
SHE WOULD BE THAT
INTERESTED IN POINTS?
NO.
YOU’RE RIGHT,
SHE WOULDN’T BE.
THOUGHT SO.
THANKS.
AND BECAUSE OF THAT...
I’M SURE THAT IT HAS
TO BE SOMETHING ELSE.
LIKE MAYBE SHE DECIDED
ON SOME KIND OF WHIM.
OR SHE’S BEING TRICKED.
YEAH, BUT...
THAT LOOK IN HER
EYES WAS SO SERIOUS.
ESPECIALLY ABOUT
BEING WITH NOMI...
HEY. LET’S EAT.
ONCE THESE THINGS GET COLD,
THEY TASTE PRETTY NASTY.
(GASPS)
NOT FAIR, HARU!
YOUR SLICE IS WAY
BIGGER THAN MINE!
(TAKU SNIFFLING)
TAKU...
(TAKU CRYING)
TAKU.
LISTEN, I BELIEVE
IN CHIYU.
BUT I DO NOT BELIEVE
WHAT SHE TOLD US TODAY.
HARU...
YOU KNOW I’M RIGHT.
SHE WOULD NEVER TEAM UP
WITH NOMI JUST BECAUSE
SHE WANTS POINTS.
THERE HAS TO BE ANOTHER
REASON, SOMETHING SHE
CAN’T TELL US.
YEAH, I AGREE,
BUT...
AND PLUS, EVEN IF SHE
DID VOLUNTARILY TEAM UP
WITH THAT CREEP...
NOTHING GOOD IS
GONNA COME FROM IT.
HE’LL JUST USE HER UP,
AND WHEN HE’S DONE,
THROW HER AWAY.
IS THAT OKAY WITH YOU?!
’COURSE NOT!
BUT COME ON, WHAT
CAN WE DO ABOUT IT?
ISN’T IT OBVIOUS?
WE HAVE TO STOP NOMI BY
DESTROYING DUSK TAKER.
THEN WE CAN GET OUR
ANSWERS AND KNOW
WHAT’S REALLY GOING ON.
AND CHIYU CAN
TALK TO US AGAIN.
AM I WRONG?
NO, BUT THAT’S NOT GOING
TO BE AS EASY AS IT SOUNDS.
I KNOW THAT THIS MIGHT COME
ACROSS AS WEAK, BUT WE SHOULD
THINK ABOUT THIS CAREFULLY.
FIRST OFF, HIS NAME
DOESN’T EVEN SHOW UP
ON THE MATCHING LIST.
SO EVEN JUST SIMPLY
CHALLENGING NOMI TO A
FIGHT IS GONNA BE IMPOSSIBLE.
BUT YOU MANAGED TO CATCH
HIM DURING HIS EXAM. SO
OUR CHANCES AREN’T ZERO.
AND ON TOP OF THAT, YOU
AND I HAVE ONE MAJOR
ADVANTAGE OVER HIM.
WE DO?
AND WHAT’S THAT?
JUST THINK ABOUT IT.
IN ORDER FOR NOMI TO
KEEP DOING SO WELL ON HIS
TESTS AND KENDO MATCHES...
HE’S GOTTA BE BURNING
THROUGH POINTS AT A
PRETTY FAST RATE.
HE’S ONLY AT LEVEL 5,
AND HE’S CONSTANTLY USING
THE PHYSICAL COMMANDS.
AND EACH TIME HE
DOES THAT, IT ALWAYS
COSTS HIM 5 POINTS.
HE CAN’T HAVE A WHOLE LOT
OF POINTS LEFT IN RESERVE.
THAT’S TRUE.
AND HE DOESN’T TAKE PART
IN TYPICAL DUELS, EITHER.
HE PROBABLY HAS HARDLY
ANY POINTS TO SPARE.
RIGHT.
SO IF WE BEAT HIM A FEW TIMES,
WE SHOULD BE ABLE TO STRIP HIM
OF HIS POINTS ENTIRELY.
YEAH, BUT...THE QUESTION
IS, CAN WE BEAT HIM IN A FIGHT?
HE NOT ONLY HAS AVIATION
ABILITY, BUT HE PRETTY MUCH HAS
THE HEALING ABILITY NOW TOO.
YEAH, IT WON’T BE EASY.
BUT THERE IS STILL ONE
WAY THAT WE CAN BEAT HIM.
TAKU. HAVE YOU EVER HEARD
OF SOMETHING CALLED THE
"INCARNATE SYSTEM"?
THE WHAT?
TAKU: THE POWER
OF ONE’S WILL?
HARU: YEAH. SEE, DUSK
TAKER’S SLICING TECHNIQUE
AND MY SWORD OF LIGHT,
BOTH OF THOSE ARE SUPER SPECIAL
MOVES THAT TAP INTO A BURST
LINKER’S VISUALIZATION POWER,
AND USE IT AS
AN ENERGY SOURCE.
THAT’S AWESOME.
I CAN’T BELIEVE SKY RAKER
TAUGHT YOU SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
YOU KNOW...
I GOTTA SAY, HARU,
YOU REALLY HAVE A
WAY OF GETTING OLDER
WOMEN TO LIKE YOU.
THAT’S REALLY THE FIRST
THING YOU WANNA COMMENT ON?
JOKING ASIDE...
IF I DON’T HAVE THAT
SAME KIND OF POWER,
THEN I WON’T BE THAT
MUCH HELP TO YOU IN BATTLE.
BUT STILL, HOW DO I GO
ABOUT GETTING IT?
MM...
WE GO BACK TO MISS RAKER,
AND ASK FOR HELP?
BUT ASH ROLLER
WILL BE LIKE:
(ASH ROLLER VOICE) "HEY, HEY!
THIS ISN’T A FREAKIN’
CHARITY! BEAT IT CANDY-ASS!"
OR IF NOT THAT,
THEN SOMETHING CLOSE.
I NEVER KNEW YOU WERE
SO GOOD AT MIMICKING.
I THINK THERE HAS
TO BE ANOTHER WAY.
LET’S JUST GIVE IT A
LITTLE MORE THOUGHT.
ALL RIGHT. IF I COME
UP WITH SOMETHING,
I’LL LET YOU KNOW.
AND HEY, SORRY ABOUT
MAKING YOU MISS
KENDO PRACTICE.
IT’S ALL GOOD.
BYE.
(QUIET BREATH)
WHAT CAME OVER
ME BACK THERE?
AND THAT VOICE...
WHATEVER IT WAS...
IT CAME FROM MY HEART.
SENPAI!
PLEASE!
WAIT FOR ME!
UGH!
IS IT BECAUSE I’VE
LOST MY WINGS?
IS THAT WHY
YOU’RE LEAVING ME?
YOU’RE SAYING
THAT YOU DON’T
NEED ME ANY MORE?
BECAUSE YOU HAVE
YOUR OWN WINGS?
SO. JUST ’CAUSE YOU HAVE
THOSE WINGS...YOU’RE GONNA
FLY OFF AND LEAVE ME?!
WELL. NOW YOU
CAN’T GO ANYWHERE.
YOU’LL BE LOCKED AWAY
FOREVER. DEEP IN THE
DEPTHS OF DARKNESS.
HERE...
WITH ME...
THAT’S RIGHT.
YOU’RE JUST LIKE ME NOW!
(SCREAMING, PANTING)
IN THAT DREAM, I WAS...
THAT’S WRONG!
THAT’S NOT WHAT I REALLY WANT!
THE ONLY THING I WANT
IS TO BE WITH HER...
(QUIET GASP)
OPEN DIRECT LINK.
COMMAND DIVE CALL.
NUMBER ZERO 1.
COMPUTER: MAKE A DIVE CALL
TO SAVED CONTACT ZERO ONE?
YES.
NOW CALLING.
(DIALING)
KUROYUKIHIME:
GOOD MORNING,
HARUYUKI.
(GASPS)
SENPAI!
YOU’RE THE ONE
WHO CALLED ME.
SO, WHY ARE YOU
ACTING SO SURPRISED?
OH, UH, HI.
GOOD MORNING,
SENPAI. I’M SORRY.
I GUESS I JUST DIDN’T
THINK THAT YOU
WOULD ANSWER.
ACTUALLY, I JUST
WOKE UP AND WAS THINKING
ABOUT GOING BACK TO SLEEP.
BUT REGARDLESS,
THIS PLACE, IT’S A
LITTLE ON THE DREARY SIDE.
MAY I CHANGE IT?
Y-YEAH, SURE.
(GASPS)
I BOUGHT THIS
YESTERDAY.
THE COLOR SEEMS
A LITTLE BIT OFF
FROM THE DEMO, THOUGH.
IT’S FINE.
LET’S SIT DOWN
AND CHAT.
LISTEN. I HAVE NOTHING AGAINST
JUST SITTING HERE AND WATCHING
THE SCENERY WITH YOU, BUT...
IS THAT REALLY WHY
YOU CALLED ME?
NO, YOU’RE RIGHT.
I’M SORRY.
IT’S FINE.
THERE’S NO NEED
TO APOLOGIZE.
I JUST SIMPLY ASSUMED
THAT IT WAS SOMETHING URGENT.
ACTUALLY, I WAS
JUST...LONELY.
NOT BEING ABLE TO SEE
YOU...BEING SO FAR APART
FOR ALL THIS TIME.
IT’S REALLY BEEN
SUPER HARD FOR ME.
FOR ME TOO.
I MISS YOU SO
MUCH, HARUYUKI.
IT’S ODD...IN THE PAST,
I’VE SPENT DAYS, EVEN WEEKS
INSIDE THE ACCELERATED WORLD.
AND NONE OF THEM FELT AS LONG AS
THE ONE SHORT WEEK I WAS APART
FROM YOU IN THE REAL WORLD.
ME TOO, SENPAI.
SENPAI...
WE’RE...GONNA BE ABLE
TO SEE EACH OTHER
AGAIN SOON, RIGHT?
YES. IN THREE MORE DAYS.
TAKU: HARU, I DID
SOME RESEARCH.
BUT IT SEEMS THE INCARNATE
SYSTEM IS PRETTY MUCH
A TOP-SECRET TECHNIQUE.
HARU: WELL, YEAH,
OF COURSE.
THAT REALLY DOESN’T SURPRISE ME.
YOU WOULDN’T SHARE SOMETHING
THAT AMAZING WITH JUST ANYBODY.
TAKU: YEAH.
AND I DON’T
THINK MISS RAKER
IS THE ONLY ONE
WHO KNOWS ABOUT IT.
HARU: NO, PROBABLY NOT.
I MEAN, EVEN ASH ROLLER
KNOWS IT EXISTS.
TAKU: SO THERE’S A PRETTY
GOOD CHANCE THEN THAT A KING
WOULD KNOW ALL ABOUT IT.
THAT GOES FOR
OUR MASTER, TOO.
HARU: WELL, SHE’S
NEVER MENTIONED IT.
AND WE CAN’T
ASK HER NOW.
IF WE DID, SHE’D
KNOW SOMETHING
WAS UP FOR SURE.
TAKU: I DON’T
KNOW, IN THIS CASE,
TELLING HER MIGHT BE--
HARU: NO. IF
SHE KNEW, SHE’D
DEFINITELY COME BACK.
AND SHE’D DESTROY
NOMI AND CHIYU.
TAKU: (SIGHS)
YOU’RE RIGHT.
SO MAYBE ANOTHER
KING, THEN.
HARU:
YEAH, MAYBE.
WE JUST GOTTA ASK
ONE OF THE SEVEN.
WAIT, I KNOW WHO
WE SHOULD ASK.
THE ONE IN
NORTH SUGINAMI!
TAKU: YOU’RE NOT
TALKING ABOUT
SCARLET RAIN?
HARU: YEAH. WHY NOT?
I’M SURE NIKO WOULD
KNOW ABOUT IT.
OH!
(GASPS)
THANK YOU.
TAKU: HARU,
WHAT IS IT?
HARU:
IT’S CHIYU.
HEY.
MORNING.
CHIYU...
TAKU: I SEE.
SO OUR GUESS YESTERDAY
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED
WAS PROBABLY RIGHT.
HARU: YEAH, BUT WE CAN’T
KEEP GOING AROUND
MOPING ABOUT IT.
I’M THINKING IT’S BEST
IF WE GO TO NERIMA
AFTER SCHOOL TODAY.
DO YOU THINK YOU CAN
YOU SKIP PRACTICE?
TAKU: YEAH,
NO PROBLEM.
COMPUTER: HARUYUKI ARITA,
PLEASE COME TO THE SCHOOL
COUNSELING OFFICE AT ONCE.
ARITA. LISTEN...
I KNOW IT’S HARD
TO IMAGINE,
BUT I WASN’T POPULAR
IN SCHOOL EITHER.
HARU: HUH?
AND BELIEVE ME, I GET THAT
A KID YOUR AGE HAS A TON OF
THINGS THEY’RE DEALING WITH.
I DO. I MEAN,
I REALLY GET IT.
ARITA!
UH, YES?
IF YOU HAVE SOMETHING
YOU NEED TO TELL ME, SON.
WELL, NOW’S YOUR CHANCE.
FOR EXAMPLE: ON SUNDAY
THE 14TH, WHERE WERE YOU,
AND WHAT WERE YOU DOING?
I, UH...
YEAH?
GO ON.
YOU CAN TELL ME.
ON SUNDAY THE 14TH, I CAME TO
SCHOOL TO MEET UP WITH A FRIEND
OF MINE WHO’S IN THE KENDO CLUB.
AND IS THAT ALL?
YES, THAT’S IT.
AND I THINK I’M GOING
TO RECORD THE REST
OF THIS CONVERSATION.
TAKU: HARU.
SOMETHING BAD
HAS HAPPENED.
HARU: YEAH. I KNOW.
I JUST FINISHED GETTING
INTERROGATED BY SUGENO.
TAKU: WHAT THE HECK
IS GOING ON?
WHAT HAPPENED?
HARU: ALL I KNOW IS I
HAVEN’T DONE ANYTHING
TO BE ASHAMED OF.
(STUDENTS WHISPERING)
ARITA, COME
WITH ME FOR
A MINUTE.
I’D LIKE TO
HAVE A WORD
WITH YOU.
ON THE ROOF.
BECAUSE I’M SURE
YOU DON’T WANNA
TALK ABOUT THIS HERE.
HOLD ON.
WAIT A--
IT’S FINE!
COME ON.
HARU...
(GRUNTS)
(ISHIO GRUNTS)
(PUNCHING NOISE)
MY GIRLFRIEND WAS IN THE
SHOWER ROOM WHEN THEY FOUND
THAT CAMERA, YOU DAMN CREEP!
AND YOU KNOW WHAT ELSE?
SHE’S BEEN SO FREAKED
THAT SHE HASN’T BEEN ABLE
TO COME TO SCHOOL FOR
THE LAST TWO DAYS!
(SHUDDERING BREATH)
IF YOU THINK I’M JUST GONNA
FORGET ABOUT THIS LITTLE
STUNT OF YOURS, YOU’RE WRONG!
(PANTING)
YOU CAN KEEP HITTING ME
AS MUCH AS YOU WANT.
BUT ALL YOU’LL GET FROM ME IS
THIS: I DIDN’T DO IT.
WHAT WAS THAT?
I DIDN’T DO IT!
AND IF THAT ENDS UP
BEING THE TRUTH,
THEN YOU HAVE MY PERMISSION
TO GO AND HIT ME
AS MUCH AS YOU WANT.
BUT LISTEN: IF IT TURNS OUT
THAT YOU ARE THE ONE WHO DID IT,
THEN I’M GONNA SMASH
YOUR NEURO-LINKER TO BITS!
I CAN HANDLE THIS.
I FACED THIS KINDA
STUFF BEFORE.
I’VE EXPERIENCED WAY
WORSE ON MANY OCCASIONS.
( SCATTERED CHATTER )
MALE STUDENT:
UGH...
DON’T CRY.
AND DON’T SMILE.
GIVE THEM EITHER,
AND YOU LOSE.
I NO LONGER WALK AROUND
WITH MY HEAD DOWN.
I’LL CLAW MY
WAY UP FROM HERE.
KNOCK ME DOWN,
AND I’LL GET BACK UP!
I’M NOT THAT KID EVERYONE
BULLIED LAST YEAR...
NOT ANYMORE.
SKY RAKER: REALIZE
WHAT’S TRULY IMPORTANT
TO YOU AND FIGHT FOR IT.
THAT’S RIGHT.
BECAUSE THIS TIME, I’VE GOT
SOMETHING WORTH PROTECTING.
(MUNCHES)
(LAUGHS)
(GASPING)
♪
KUROYUKIHIME:
NEXT STAGE,
"INSURRECTION."
THE TIME FOR
REBELLION
GROWS NEAR.
GUIDED BY THE RED
KING, HARUYUKI HEADS
TO AKIHABARA FOR ANSWERS.