SO THIS BURST LINKER
WHO DOESN'T APPEAR
ON THE MATCHING LIST--
DO YOU KNOW HIS NAME?
IT'S RUST JIGSAW.
(gasps)
DIFFERENT GUY.
HUH! LOOKS LIKE
THE LITTLE ONE HERE
KNOWS A THING OR TWO
ABOUT ALL THIS.
WELL, YEAH.
YOU SEE...
ANOTHER BURST LINKER
WITH THE EXACT
SAME ABILITY
HAS STARTED SHOWING UP
ON THE LOCAL NETWORK
THAT I NORMALLY
CONNECT TO.
HE WHAT?! WE CAN'T
JUST IGNORE THIS.
MAKER, WHAT IS
JIGSAW'S LEVEL,
AND WHAT'S HIS COLOR?
WELL, HE'S JUST LIKE YOU.
HE'S A LEVEL 6.
AND AS FOR HIS COLOR,
IT'S LIKE HIS NAME IMPLIES--
RUST.
HIS SPECIALTY IS HUNTING
CLOSE-RANGE AVATARS
WHILE MAINTAINING A MIDDLE-
TO LONG-RANGE DISTANCE.
IN OTHER WORDS,
YOU'RE THE EXACT TYPE
HE LIKES TO FIGHT.
OKAY. THAT MIGHT WORK
BETTER FOR US.
THANKS FOR THE INFO.
I'LL TAG-TEAM WITH
THE KID HERE
AND BE THE BAIT.
YOU'LL WHAT?!
HUH?!
LISTEN, YOUR NAME
WILL CERTAINLY HELP
WHEN IT COMES
TO LURING THIS GUY IN.
BUT I DON'T THINK
THE SAME CAN BE SAID
FOR THE NEW KID.
WHO IS HE,
AND WHERE'S HE FROM?
ACTUALLY, HE MAY BE
MORE FAMOUS THAN ME.
HE'S WITH THAT REVIVED LEGION--
NEGA NEBULOUS.
HE'S SILVER CROW.
WHOA!
UH...
(singing in Japanese )
HEY!LEOPARD FROM PROMINENCE
IS GONNA FIGHT!
WHY'S SHE TEAMING UP
WITH SILVER CROW
FROM NEGA NEBULOUS?
RUST JIGSAW
ONLY FIGHTS SOLO.
YOU REALLY THINK
HE'S GONNA SHOW
WHEN HE SEES HE'S
FIGHTING A TEAM?
WORD YOU CAN
NO LONGER FLY
HAS SPREAD PRETTY FAR,
SO IF HE'S CAUGHT
WIND OF IT, TOO,
HE'LL TAKE THIS AS
A GOOD OPPORTUNITY
TO ATTACK.
I SEE. SO IF HE THINKS HE
CAN KILL ME STRAIGHT AWAY,
THEN IT'LL QUICKLY BECOME
A NORMAL ONE-ON-ONE FIGHT
WITH YOU.
I JUST REALIZED
SOMETHING.
IF JIGSAW IS GONNA BE
CONNECTING TO THIS
LOCAL NET,
THAT MEANS HE HAS TO
PHYSICALLY BE SOMEWHERE
INSIDE THIS BUILDING.
I MEAN, LIKE,
IN THE REAL WORLD!
TRUE.
SO WHAT DO YOU THINK?
IS THERE SOME WAY
WE MIGHT BE ABLE
TO FIND HIM HERE?
IT'S A LONG SHOT,
BUT THERE'S A WAY.
WELL, WHAT IS IT?
I'LL EXPLAIN IT LATER.
BUT FIRST...
YOU SHOULD ONLY USE
THE INCARNATE SYSTEM
IF HE USES IT ON US.
THE RED KING
SAID THE SAME THING.
BUT HOW COME?
IT'S FOR YOUR OWN
WELL BEING.
HUH?
INCARNATION IS A POWER
BORN FROM THE CRACKS
IN YOUR SOUL.
EACH TIME YOU USE IT,
YOU'RE DRAW A LITTLE CLOSER
TO THE DARKNESS
WITHIN THOSE VOIDS.
THE...DARKNESS?
THE ARMOR
OF CATASTROPHE--
THE ONE YOU DEFEATED.
THAT CURSE
IS A DIRECT RESULT
OF THE FIRST
DISASTER'S WILL
GOING OUT OF CONTROL.
THIS IS THE REASON
WHY THE KINGS
TRY TO HIDE
THE EXISTENCE OF
THE INCARNATE SYSTEM.
INCARNATION IS JUST
LIKE BRAIN BURST
ITSELF.
THERE ARE
TWO SIDES TO IT,
AND THEY'RE THE
OPPOSITE OF EACH OTHER.
JUST LIKE WITH HOPE...
COMES AN ELEMENT
OF DESPAIR.
THAT MAY BE TRUE,
BUT I STILL WANT TO BELIEVE
THAT INCARNATION
IS A POWER FOR GOOD.
AND PLUS, I ALSO BELIEVE
IN BRAIN BURST.
THIS GAME SAVED ME.
VERY WELL.
YOU'RE JUST LIKE
RAIN SAID YOU WERE.
THANKS TO YOU,
THE ACCELERATED WORLD
MAY FINALLY BECOME...
HE'S HERE!
OKAY, HE'S TAKEN
THE BAIT.
FIRST THING
JIGSAW WILL DO
IS LAUNCH
A LONG-RANGE ATTACK
TO BREAK US UP,
AND THEN HE'LL TRY
TO TAKE YOU OUT,
SO DON'T FALL FOR IT.
STAY CLOSE TO ME.
OKAY, GOT IT!
THAT MUST'VE BEEN
HIS LONG-RANGE
SPECIAL MOVE--
THE WHEEL SAW.
THE BLADE'S SO THIN,
IT'S HARD TO SEE.
YOU HAVE TO GAUGE IT
BY THE SOUND.
AFTER WE DODGE
THE NEXT ONE,
ZERO IN ON HIM.
DON'T HESITATE! JUMP!
(grunting)
Haru:IT'S HIM--
RUST JIGSAW!
THINK YOU'RE
GETTING AWAY?
STOP.
WHAT IS THAT?
GOOD THING YOU'RE
A METAL COLOR.
YEAH, BUT...
WHAT WAS IT?
ANOTHER ONE OF
HIS MOVES?
STEEL SAW.
IT'S A MOVE
THAT PUTS JIGSAW BLADES
IN THE AIR.
IT KEEPS US AT BAY
WHILE HE ATTACKS
WITH LONG-DISTANCE
CIRCULAR SAW BLADES.
THIS GUY'S TRULY
A CLOSE-RANGE FIGHTER'S
WORST ENEMY.
SO WHAT'S
OUR PLAN, THEN?
TRANSFER YOUR
SPECIAL MOVE GAUGE TO ME.
HUH? UH...
(grunting)
(electric whirring )
SHAPE CHANGE.
GET ON. HURRY.
WHOA!
WHEEL SAW!
HANDLE IT.
OKAY!
IT'S FAST,
BUT NOT AS FAST
AS A BULLET.
G.J.
(grunting)
LET GO!
( screaming)
AAAH!
GOOD GAME.
(gasps)
OKAY, GET UP.
WE'RE LEAVING NOW.
WE MIGHT BE ABLE TO
SPOT HIM IF WE HURRY.
WHO?
THE REAL RUST JIGSAW.
I INTENTIONALLY INFLICTED
A GREAT DEAL OF DAMAGE
TO THE RIGHT SIDE
OF HIS SHOULDER.
WHENEVER YOU'RE HIT
WITH THAT MUCH PAIN,
YOU'LL STILL FEEL IT
FOR A LITTLE BIT
IN THE REAL WORLD.
WHEN WE LEAVE
THE BUILDING,
LOOK FOR PEOPLE FAVORING
THEIR RIGHT SHOULDER.
YEAH, GOT IT.
THAT'S HIM!
PLEASE! COME TO OUR CAFE!
(grunts)
HEY, CROW.
I JUST LOST HIM.
Taku:HMM. SO WHILE
I WAS WORKING HARD,
TRAINING BY MYSELF,
YOU WERE OFF ON ANOTHER DATE
WITH AN OLDER WOMAN.
Haru:LIKE I SAID,
IT WASN'T LIKE THAT.
AND IT WAS, LIKE,
THE SACRED LAND FOR DUELS.
I'VE ALWAYS
WANTED TO GO THERE.
THIS IS SO NOT FAIR.
WELL, WHAT ABOUT YOU?
HOW'D ALL THAT TIME
YOU SPENT TRAINING
WITH NIKO WORK OUT?
UNFORTUNATELY,
SHE ONLY STUCK AROUND
DURING THE BEGINNING
AND END OF MY TRAINING.
THE REST OF THE TIME,
SHE WAS GONE,
HUNTING DOWN ENEMIES.
OH, I SEE.
SO WERE YOU ABLE TO
MASTER INCARNATION?
HMM. WELL, TO QUOTE
THE RED KING,
"IF YOU TRY TO USE
THAT WEAK-ASS ATTEMPT
IN A REAL BATTLE, TEACH,
YOU'LL BE DEAD."
BUT I THINK I GOT THE IDEA.
REALLY?
THAT'S GREAT, TAKU.
THANKS.
AND, REGARDLESS OF HOW
IT TURNS OUT IN THE END,
YOU DID WELL, TOO, HARU.
NOW WE JUST NEED TO
WAIT ON THE MATCHMAKER
AT THE AKIHABARA B.G.
LET'S HOPE THE DESCRIPTION
YOU GAVE HIM
OF JIGSAW'S REAL IDENTITY
IS ENOUGH
TO TRACK HIM DOWN.
YEAH. THANKS.
LET'S HOPE.
ALL RIGHT. SEE YOU
TOMORROW AT SCHOOL.
(sighs)
MAN, THIS SO
ISN'T GONNA BE EASY.
JUST HANG IN THERE,
CHIYU.
I'LL FIGURE OUT A WAY
TO RELEASE HIS GRIP
ON YOU.
I PROMISE.
ALL RIGHT, LIME BELL,
IT'S TIME FOR OUR DEBUT FIGHT.
ARE YOU READY?
HARU!
HUH?
WORD IS...
CHI TEAMED UP WITH NOMI
AND FOUGHT IN SHINJUKU
LAST NIGHT.
(gasps)
A 100% WIN RECORD?!
YEAH. THAT'S WHAT
MY FRIEND IN SHINJIKU
TOLD ME.
DUSK TAKER GOT HIS GAUGE
CHARGED IMMEDIATELY.
AND THEN,
ONCE HE STARTED FLYING,
THERE WASN'T A SINGLE
DUEL AVATAR IN SIGHT
WHO COULD EVEN COME CLOSE
TO DEFEATING HIM.
WOW. IT WAS THAT BAD.
A LONG-RANGE FIGHTER
WITH AVIATION ABILITY.
AND WITH A HEALER IN TOW?
HE'S IN HIS OWN CLASS.
ANY PLAYER,
AT HIS SAME LEVEL,
WITH NORMAL CAPABILITIES,
IS BENEATH HIM.
NOMI. THAT BASTARD!
LISTEN, I HATE
TO SAY THIS, BUT...
I'M AFRAID THE SITUATION
MIGHT BE EVEN WORSE
THAN WE IMAGINED.
HUH?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
HARU, THROUGH
THIS WHOLE ORDEAL,
WE'VE ALWAYS HELD ON
TO ONE BIT OF HOPE.
NO MATTER
HOW STRONG NOMI GETS,
THERE'S OUR MASTER.
AND AS SOON
AS BLACK LOTUS RETURNS,
SHE'D BE ABLE TO SOLVE
ALL OUR PROBLEMS
IN ONE BLOW.
BUT NOW...
HOLD ON! TAKU,
ARE YOU TRYING TO SAY
THAT SENPAI
WOULD LOSE TO NOMI?
TRUST ME, HARU,
I DON'T WANT THAT
TO BE TRUE.
BUT WE HAVE TO IMAGINE
A WORST-CASE SCENARIO
AND DO WHATEVER WE CAN
TO PREVENT THAT FROM
HAPPENING BY SATURDAY.
DON'T YOU AGREE?
YEAH. YOU'RE RIGHT.
WHATEVER WE CAN, HUH?
BUT UNTIL WE CAN FIGURE OUT
HOW HE'S ABLE
TO KEEP HIS NAME
OFF THE MATCHING LIST,
WE CAN'T DO ANYTHING.
THIS IS SO FRUSTRATING.
YOU HAVE
NO NEW MAIL.
I GUESS THAT MEANS
MISS PARD'S GROUP
AND THE MATCHMAKER
HAVEN'T COME UP
WITH ANYTHING, EITHER.
WE'RE ALL STRIKING OUT.
(gasps)
(rings )
(panting)
WHAT?
I JUST...WANT TO TALK.
FINE.
IF YOU WANT TO TALK,
THEN TALK.
HAVE YOU...BEEN
SKIPPING YOUR CLUB?
YEAH.
DID NOMI TELL YOU TO?
MAYBE.
DON'T DO THAT!
YOU SHOULD NEVER
PUT BRAIN BURST
AHEAD OF
YOUR OBLIGATIONS
IN THE REAL WORLD!
OH, YEAH?
LOOK WHO'S TALKING.
FIRST OFF, I'M NOT
IN A SCHOOL CLUB.
AND SECONDLY, I'VE NEVER
SKIPPED MY HOMEWORK
BECAUSE OF A GAME.
YEAH, BUT EVERY
FREE SECOND YOU HAVE,
GUESS WHERE YOU ARE.
LET'S NOT DO THIS.
WE'RE TAKING IT
WAY TOO SERIOUSLY.
IT'S STILL JUST A GAME.
IT'S AMAZING, THOUGH.
LISTEN TO THIS.
YESTERDAY,
I WENT UP TWO LEVELS
IN JUST ONE DAY.
THE SPECTATORS--
THE ONES IN THE GALLERY--
THEY SAID IT MIGHT BE
THE FASTEST IN THE HISTORY
OF BRAIN BURST.
CHIYU...
I'VE LOST TRACK
OF ALL THE OFFERS
I'VE GOTTEN FROM
THE OTHER LEGIONS.
IT SEEMS I'M QUITE
THE POPULAR ONE
ALL OF A SUDDEN.
COME ON, CHIYU!
STOP IT!
THIS ISN'T
LIKE YOU AT ALL!
I GET WHY YOU'RE
GOING ALONG
WITH NOMI, OKAY?
IT'S BECAUSE
OF THAT VIDEO!
BUT I'M THE ONE
WHO GOT YOU INTO
THIS WHOLE MESS!
I SCREWED UP!
I LET NOMI PLAY ME!
I LET HIM FIND
MY WEAK POINT.
(sobbing)
LISTEN...
IF I LET HIM
TAKE YOU AWAY, TOO,
THAT'S--THAT'S MORE
THAN I CAN BEAR!
YOU'RE MISSING
THE POINT, HARU.
YOU DON'T GET IT.
YOU DON'T
UNDERSTAND ME AT ALL.
MY AVATAR MAY BE OBEYING NOMI
IN THE ACCELERATED WORLD,
BUT WHILE WE'RE IN
THE REAL WORLD, I'M HERE.
UH...
RIGHT IN FRONT OF YOU,
WHERE IF YOU WANTED
TO TOUCH ME, YOU COULD.
AND YET EVEN NOW,
YOU STILL DON'T GET IT.
NOBODY'S TAKEN ME AWAY
FROM YOU.
I'M DOING THIS
BECAUSE I WANT TO BE
DOING IT, OKAY?
I ALWAYS HAVE.
AND I ALWAYS WILL!
YOU'RE...WHAT?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND,
CHIYU.
WHAT ARE YOU
TRYING TO SAY?
BUT--
SORRY, BUT...PLEASE
BUTTON YOUR SHIRT.
LISTEN,
I BELIEVE IN YOU.
SO PLEASE...
DO YOUR BEST TO
BELIEVE IN ME, TOO.
I WON'T LOSE TO
SOMEONE LIKE NOMI.
EVERYTHING HE'S
STOLEN FROM ME--
I'M GONNA GET IT BACK.
I PROMISE.
OKAY, THERE'S GOTTA BE
SOMETHING I CAN DO.
THINK! COME ON,
HARUYUKI ARITA! THINK!
THINK ABOUT ALL THE INFO
YOU'VE GLEANED
SINCE NOMI FIRST APPEARED--
EVERY SINGLE WORD,
EVERY SLIGHT DETAIL.
STUDY THEM AND COME UP
WITH SOME KIND OF THEORY.
THIS IS THE LAST MOVE
YOU HAVE, YOUR FINAL WEAPON.
THIS IS ONE THING
NOMI CAN'T TAKE FROM YOU.
THERE HAS TO BE
SOME CLUE SOMEWHERE--
SOMETHING THAT'LL REVEAL
HIS SECRET,
HIS WEAK POINT.
(laughing)
NOMI'S SECRET.
OH, YEAH,
THERE'S RUST JIGSAW.
IF ONLY WE HAD CAUGHT HIM
BACK THERE.
WAIT, WHAT WAS
THAT GESTURE?
I THOUGHT HE WAS PUSHING
SOMEONE OUT OF THE WAY.
BUT...I KNOW THAT MOVEMENT.
IT'S FAMILIAR.
WAIT A SEC.
( gasps )
HE WAS CLOSING
A VIRTUAL WINDOW.
BUT HOW? HE WASN'T WEARING
A NEURO-LINKER.
SO THEN...WAS IT
ANOTHER DEVICE?
SOMETHING OTHER THAN
A NEURO-LINKER?
SEE?I WENT
ALL OLD-SCHOOL.
WHAT DEVICES PRECEDED
THE NEURO-LINKER?
NERVE GEAR--
THE FIRST V.R. MACHINE
IN THE 2020s.
BUT THAT WAS ONLY
FOR FULL DIVES.
THE NEURO-LINKER
WAS THE FIRST DEVICE
TO TRULY INTEGRATE
WITH AUGMENTED REALITY.
ACTUALLY, NO. I THINK
THERE WAS ANOTHER DEVICE
IN BETWEEN THE TWO.
IT WAS THE ONE THAT MADE
AUGMENTED REALITY POSSIBLE.
"THE BRAIN IMPLANT CHIP."
(gasps)
SO THAT'S
YOUR SECRET.
THIS TIME, NOMI,
I'M PUTTING AN END
TO THIS FOR GOOD.
ALL RIGHT, SEIJI NOMI--
GAME OVER.
THE SAME THING GOES
FOR DUSK TAKER.
OH, WHAT'S THAT?
ARE YOU SAYING
THAT YOU'RE FINALLY
WILLING TO ADMIT
YOUR COMPLETE
AND UTTER DEFEAT?
"PLEASE, STOP WITH
THE BULLYING, NOMI.
I GIVE UP ALREADY."
YOU WISH!ACTUALLY,
WHAT I'M TRYING
TO TELL YOU
IS THAT YOUR GAME
IS OVER!
SENPAI...
YOU REALLY ARE SLOW
ON THE UPTAKE,
AREN'T YOU?
THERE'S
ABSOLUTELY NOTHING
THAT YOU OR MAYUZUMI
CAN DO.
I'M GONNA DESTROY
THE BLACK KING
AND RULE THIS SCHOOL.
LOOK, TRUTH IS,
I'M NOT GONNA STOP
UNTIL THE ENTIRE
SUGINAMI AREA IS
UNDER MY CONTROL.
I WON'T ALLOW YOU
TO DO THAT!
I'VE FIGURED IT OUT!
I KNOW WHY YOUR NAME'S
NOT ON THE MATCHING LIST!
IT'S 'CAUSE YOU HAVE
A SECOND V.R. DEVICE
NO ONE CAN SEE
HIDDEN IN YOUR HEAD!
AN ILLEGAL BRAIN
IMPLANT CHIP.
THAT'S RIGHT.
I KNOW WHAT IT IS--
A SMALL BIOCHIP INSERTED
DIRECTLY INTO THE CEREBRUM.
A BRAIN IMPLANT CHIP.
AFTER ONLY THREE YEARS
IN PRODUCTION,
IT WAS DISCONTINUED
AND BANNED--
PARTLY BECAUSE OF
THE DANGERS
THAT CAME WITH
BRAIN HACKING,
BUT ALSO BECAUSE
GUYS LIKE YOU USED IT
TO CHEAT ON THE SCHOOL
ENTRANCE EXAMS.
WHENEVER YOU LOG ONTO
THE SCHOOL'S NETWORK
FOR LESSONS OR TESTS,
YOU DON'T USE
YOUR NEURO-LINKER.
YOUR USE THE CHIP.
THE ONLY TIME
YOU'RE ONLINE WITH
YOUR NEURO-LINKER
IS RIGHT BEFORE
YOU BEGIN A DUEL.
AND THAT'S HOW
YOU'RE ABLE TO DO IT,
HOW YOU AVOID BEING
ON THE MATCHING LIST.
A SINGLE SCAN WILL BE ENOUGH
TO REVEAL THAT CHIP.
ONCE THEY FIND OUT,
YOU'LL BE EXPELLED,
AND THE CHIP WILL BE
DEACTIVATED AND DESTROYED.
THAT'S IT.
IT'S ALL OVER, NOMI.
I USED TO THINK
YOU WERE A GRUBBY
LITTLE PIG,
BUT NOW I SEE
YOU'RE A DIRTY RAT.
ALWAYS SCAMPERING
AROUND HERE
AND SNIFFING AROUND
OVER THERE!
THEN YOU SHOULD HAVE
CRUSHED ME WHEN YOU
STILL HAD THE CHANCE.
NOT DOING THAT
WAS A HUGE MISTAKE.
YES, I'M BEGINNING
TO SEE THAT'S TRUE.
SO WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
I HAVE YOUR VIDEO,
AND YOU HAVE MY CHIP.
ARE WE EACH GOING
TO EXPOSE EACH OTHER?
THAT'LL JUST
RUIN OUR LIVES
IN THE REAL WORLD.
I THINK YOU'RE FORGETTING
SOMETHING, NOMI.
YOU AND I ARE BOTH
BURST LINKERS.
THERE'S A FITTING WAY
FOR US TO DECIDE THIS.
I SEE. YOU WANT US
TO BATTLE, DON'T YOU?
(sighs)
I REALLY HATE THAT.
SAME GOES FOR THE NAME
"BURST LINKER", TOO.
I FIND THAT
WHOLE MENTALITY
TO BE TOTALLY LAME.
HEH.
BUT IF THAT'S WHAT
YOU SAY YOU WANT,
I GUESS YOU LEAVE ME
WITH NO OTHER CHOICE.
HOWEVER, I WOULD
LIKE TO MAKE JUST ONE
LITTLE SUGGESTION.
WHAT'S THAT?
I'M SURE WHAT
YOU'RE PICTURING
IS SOME LONG
SERIES OF BATTLES
THAT DON'T END
UNTIL ONE OF US
FINALLY LOSES
ALL THEIR POINTS.
BUT INSTEAD, WHY
DON'T WE SETTLE IT
IN ONE GO?
ONE LAST DUEL--
JUST THE WAY
YOU LIKE IT.
IN THE UNLIMITED
NEUTRAL FIELD,
THERE'S AN ITEM THAT
PLAYERS CAN CHARGE
WITH ALL THEIR POINTS.
AND THEN IT'S
WINNER TAKES ALL.
YOU GET THE PICTURE,
RIGHT...
ARITA SENPAI?
(gasps)
I SEE. SO THAT'S HOW
THINGS PLAYED OUT.
YEAH. AND I'VE JUST
SENT YOU A LIST
OF THE CONDITIONS
NOMI NEGOTIATED
AFTERWARDS.
TAKE A LOOK
AND LET ME KNOW
WHAT YOU THINK.
I FEEL LIKE ACCEPTING
HIS PROPOSAL IS DANGEROUS.
THERE'S ALWAYS THE RISK
OF BEING AMBUSHED
IN THE NEUTRAL FIELD.
PLUS, KNOWING NOMI,
AND THE FACT
HE'S ALLOWED ME
TO COME, TOO,
MEANS HE'LL HAVE SOMETHING
UP HIS SLEEVE FOR SURE.
YEAH, BUT HE SAID WE
CAN CHANGE THE VENUE
AND START TIME
AS OFTEN AS WE WANT.
THAT'LL MAKE AN
AMBUSH PRETTY MUCH
IMPOSSIBLE.
THAT'S TRUE.
HE'D EITHER NEED
TONS OF BURST POINTS
OR HAVE AN AMBUSH CREW
WILLING TO STAY OUT THERE
FOR DAYS AND DAYS ON END--
POSSIBLY EVEN MONTHS.
WELL, DO YOU THINK
HE HAS ANY FRIENDS
WHO'D BE WILLING
TO DO THAT FOR HIM?
I MEAN, IF HE DID,
CHANCES ARE...
NOMI WOULD BE A HECK OF
A LOT MORE RESPECTABLE
AS A BURST LINKER
THAN HE IS RIGHT NOW.
GOOD POINT.
THIS IS A FIGHT BETWEEN
BURST LINKERS LIKE US
AND THOSE WHO
USE ACCELERATION FOR
THEIR OWN GAIN, LIKE NOMI.
THIS DUEL WILL BE
ABOUT SELF-RESPECT
AND WHAT WE BELIEVE IN.
AM I RIGHT?
COMPLETELY!
SO LET'S WIN THIS!
(panting)
Haru:TAKU, LET'S GET THIS
ALL OVER WITH
BEFORE KUROYUKIHIME SENPAI
GETS BACK IN TOWN.
THIS IS THE MOMENT
OF TRUTH.
♪
(singing in Japanese )
NEXT STAGE--
CONSOLIDATION.
A BLACK FLASH CUTS
THROUGH THE DESPAIR--
A SIGN OF THE STRONG BOND
THAT TIES THEM ALL TOGETHER.