I’M GOING TO GIVE YOU
SOME WINGS:
MY ENHANCED ARMAMENT,
GALE THRUSTER.
I’M SURE YOU’LL BE ABLE
TO USE THOSE WINGS
TO REACH HEIGHTS THAT
I COULD HAVE NEVER IMAGINED.
( gasps )
AS YOU KNOW NOW,
I DID SOMETHING REALLY FOOLISH,
AND AS A RESULT,
I LOST A FRIEND.
THAT’S WHY I DON’T EVER
WANT YOU TO MAKE THAT SAME
KIND OF MISTAKE.
REALIZE WHAT’S TRULY IMPORTANT
TO YOU AND FIGHT FOR IT.
FIGHT...FOR WHAT’S
TRULY IMPORTANT TO ME.
I WILL!
AND THANKS AGAIN
FOR EVERYTHING.
OKAY, MISS RAKER, I WON’T
FORGET WHAT YOU TAUGHT ME.
AND SOON I’M GONNA FLY AGAIN
WITH MY OWN POWER.
WHEN THAT HAPPENS,
I’LL COME BACK
AND RETURN YOUR WINGS TO YOU.
I PROMISE!
OKAY.
WELL BEST OF LUCK,
MR. CROW.
( panting )
( gasps )
UH...
( grunts softly )
( no audible dialogue )
Haru: ( thinking )
CHIYU, TAKU, I’M SO SORRY.
BUT I PROMISE THAT I WILL
FIND A WAY TO STOP DUSK TAKER,
EVEN IF THAT MEANS
LOSING MY WINGS FOREVER.
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( indistinct singing )
♪ AND WATCH IT GO SLOW ♪
♪ SLOWLY OPEN UP MY EYES ♪
( indistinct singing )
( singing in Japanese )
♪ NEVER LET IT GO,
NEVER LOSE MY WAY ♪
( singing in Japanese )
COME ON, CHI.
LET’S GO!
( laughing )
BUT HOW THE HECK
AM I SUPPOSED TO DO THAT?
I MEAN...
I STILL HAVEN’T FIGURED OUT
WHY HIS NAME’S NOT
ON THE MATCHING LIST.
( electronic ringing )
IT’S A DIVE CALL.
BUT FROM WHO?
( gasps )
O-OPEN DIRECT LINK!
A BEACH?
WAIT, IS THIS
A VIDEO STREAM?
Kuroyukihime:
LONG TIME, NO SEE.
IT’S BEEN THREE DAYS NOW.
HOW HAVE YOU BEEN DOING,
HARUYUKI?
S-SENPAI!
( chuckles )
OH, THIS IS HENOKO BEACH.
I JUST SAW SOMETHING
YOU WOULD’VE LIKED--
A FIGHTER PLANE
FLYING OVERHEAD.
Megumi: AW, COME ON!
( grunts )
STOP TAKING YOUR TIME
AND JUST SHOW IT TO HIM.
( grunts )
HEY, MEGUMI,
WHY’D YOU DO THAT?
LOOK, YOU MADE ME
SPEND ALL MORNING WITH YOU
LOOKING FOR THAT SWIMSUIT.
SO YOU MIGHT AS WELL
SHOW IT OFF!
( whimpers )
SEE YA, ARITA.
HAVE FUN.
WELL, IT’S JUST THAT--
I MEAN...
( sighs )
I AM IN OKINAWA,
AFTER ALL.
YEAH! RIGHT!
I AGREE.
YOU SHOULD MAKE THE BEST
OUT OF YOUR TRIP.
I-IT LOOKS GREAT ON YOU.
( gasps )
( sighs )
WELL THANK YOU.
( whimpering )
♪
OH, THIS THING?
IT’S NORMALLY IMPOSSIBLE
TO SEE, BUT...
WHEN I’M IN THE SUNSHINE,
IT TENDS TO SHOW UP A BIT MORE.
( sighs )
PLEASE DON’T FEEL BADLY
ABOUT IT.
IN MY OPINION, IT’S THE ONLY
BADGE OF HONOR THAT I OWN.
IT’S THE FIRST WOUND
AND SCAR I’VE RECEIVED
THAT ISN’T
FROM FIGHTING SOMEONE,
BUT RATHER
FROM PROTECTING THEM.
IT’S ACTUALLY A LITTLE REMINDER
THAT HELPS KEEP ME GOING.
( thinking )
IF I TOLD HER ABOUT NOMI,
SHE’D PROBABLY
YELL AT ME FIRST.
BUT THEN SHE WOULD
LEAVE OKINAWA TO COME BACK
AND HELP ME.
AND THAT’S THE REASON...
I SHOULDN’T TELL HER.
I CAN’T.
S-SENPAI, LOOK--
OH?
I’M GOING TO GET STRONGER!
I PROMISE!
I REALIZE THAT YOU’RE THE ONE
WHO IS PROTECTING ME NOW,
BUT...I’LL GET THERE
ONE DAY!
AND WHEN I DO, I’LL BE
STRONG ENOUGH TO PROTECT YOU!
( giggles )
I TOLD YOU BEFORE,
THERE’S NO NEED TO HURRY.
IF I DON’T HAVE THE FUN
OF BEING ABLE
TO LOOK AFTER YOU,
WELL...I’LL GET BORED.
OH, BY THE WAY,
I GOT A RATHER ODD EMAIL
FROM TAKUMU.
( grunts softly )
IT WAS ABOUT NOMI,
THAT FIRST-YEAR STUDENT
WHO WE ALL BELIEVE
MIGHT BE A BURST LINKER.
HE WANTED ME TO LOOK
INTO THE SCORES HE GOT
ON HIS ENTRANCE EXAMS,
SEE WHERE HE SCORED BEST.
HUH?! WELL,
SO WHAT DID YOU DO?
I LOOKED IT UP ON THE STUDENT
COUNCIL’S DATABASE
AND SENT HIM THE INFO.
SO DID SOMETHING HAPPEN?
N-NO! NOTHING SPECIAL!
OKAY, THEN.
WELL, I’VE GOT TO GO NOW.
WE’LL END IT HERE.
SEE YA LATER!
( sighs )
( footsteps )
( panting )
( boys laughing )
Boy 1: CHUBBERS THERE
IS LAST LIKE ALWAYS!
Boy 2: IT’S BE FASTER
IF YOU ROLLED AROUND THE TRACK
INSTEAD OF RAN, PIGGY!
( boys laughing )
( gasps )
TAKU.
( no audible dialogue )
( heart beating quickly )
DID HE JUST SAY,
"BURST LINK"?!
WHY NOW?!
( yells, grunts )
TAKU!
WHY THE HECK DO YOU
WANT TO FIGHT ME NOW?
( gasps )
WAIT...I’M HERE
TO WATCH A REGISTERED DUEL?
Nomi: WELL, WELL, WELL.
I EXPECTED YOU TO BE MORE
OF THE CAUTIOUS TYPE,
MAYUZUMI SENPAI.
YOU SURPRISED ME.
Taku: I FIGURED YOU WOULD BE
ACCELERATING RIGHT ABOUT NOW...
NOMI.
OH, REALLY?
ALL THE FIRST-YEAR STUDENTS
ARE IN THE MIDDLE OF TAKING
THEIR PLACEMENT EXAM.
AND FIFTH PERIOD FOR YOU
IS SOCIAL STUDIES,
WHICH YOU ACED ON YOUR
ENTRANCE TESTS.
IF YOU WERE
GOING TO ACCELERATE,
IT’D BE JUST BEFORE
THE EXAM ENDED.
SO I KEPT ACCELERATING
UNTIL WE FINALLY MET UP.
AND HERE WE ARE.
Nomi: AND NOW THAT YOU’VE
DONE THAT, WHAT?
HAVE YOU COME TO GIVE ME
A LECTURE?
NO. I’VE USED
ACCELERATING POWERS
TO CHEAT IN MANY WAYS, MYSELF.
ALTHOUGH ACING THE TEST
COMPLETELY IS GOING TOO FAR.
IT ONLY DRAWS ATTENTION
TO YOU.
AND THAT’S WHERE THE TWO
OF US DIFFER.
I TAKE AS MUCH AS I CAN GET
WHEREVER I CAN GET IT.
FIGHTING TO ACQUIRE MORE
IS WHAT THIS WORLD
IS ALL ABOUT.
THAT’S WHY I TRULY LOVE
TAKING THINGS FROM PEOPLE.
BUT WHEN SOMEONE
TAKES SOMETHING FROM ME,
WELL, THAT REALLY
MAKES ME MAD.
AND YOU ARE TRYING TO TAKE
1.8 SECONDS AWAY FROM ME.
SO TO MAKE SURE THAT YOU
NEVER TRY AND DO THIS AGAIN,
I’M GOING TO FORCE YOU
TO PAY ME BACK...
WITH YOUR BURST POINTS.
ACTUALLY, I’LL BE THE ONE
WHO’S DOING THE TAKING.
Taku: I’M TAKING BACK
THE AVIATION ABILITY
YOU STOLE FROM MY BEST FRIEND,
ALONG WITH HIS WINGS!
( whimpers )
TAKU...YOU KNEW?
I HEARD ABOUT THE DUEL YOU HAD
WITH ASH ROLLER LAST NIGHT.
I’M SORRY, HARU.
I SHOULD HAVE
FIGURED IT OUT SOONER.
BUT NOW,
IT’S MY TURN TO FIGHT
FOR YOU!
( gasping )
( sighs )
Haru: TAKU...
DO IT, TAKU!
TAKE HIM DOWN!
SO HIM HOW STRONG YOU ARE!
I WILL.
AND I’LL GET YOUR WINGS
BACK FOR YOU, HARU.
I PROMISE!
( Nomi making
retching noises )
PLEASE STOP.
ALL THIS POSTURING,
AND FRIENDSHIP,
AND SANCTIMONY
MAKES ME WANNA HURL.
I’M DONE WITH YOU PEOPLE.
I’LL JUST TAKE MY POINTS
AND BE ON MY WAY.
I’VE STILL GOT FIVE MORE
QUESTIONS LEFT ON MY TEST.
BE CAREFUL, TAKU!
IF YOU CUT OFF HIS TENTACLES,
THEY’LL JUST GROW BACK!
AND THAT BLADE ON HIS
RIGHT ARM IS SUPER SHARP!
( scoffs )
( grunts )
( yelling )
TAKU!
GAME OVER, NOMI.
YOU’VE JUST LOST.
REALLY?
AND JUST HOW DO YOU
FIGURE THAT?
YOU’RE BUILT FOR SPEED,
NOT STRENGTH.
YOU CAN’T BREAK THE WALLS
HERE IN THE PURGATORY STAGE.
AND WITH THE ONLY EXIT
BEING BEHIND ME,
YOU HAVE NO CHANCE OF WINNING.
SO, UNLESS YOU WANT ME
POPPING UP LIKE THIS
EVERY TIME YOU HAVE A TEST,
YOU’LL RETURN THE WINGS
THAT YOU STOLE
FROM SILVER CROW.
DO THAT, AND I’LL
LEAVE YOU ALONE FOR GOOD.
YOU’RE RIGHT.
GETTING PAST YOU
WILL BE KIND OF TRICKY.
RETRACT ALL WEAPONS.
( Haru gasps )
NO, I’M NOT SURRENDERING,
YOU IDIOT.
I JUST NEED BOTH HANDS
TO BE FREE
IN ORDER TO USE
MY SECRET MOVE.
YOUR WHAT?!
ALTHOUGH...
I WAS HOPING I DIDN’T
HAVE TO RESORT TO THIS.
YOU SEE, I’M NOT A FAN
OF HAVING TO CALL OUT
THE NAME OF MY MOVES.
BUT, OH WELL.
I GUESS I HAVE NO CHOICE.
TAKE, GET, GRAB, ERASE.
TAKE, TAKE, TAKE.
( gasps )
WHAT IS THAT?!
A SPECIAL MOVE?
NO--WAIT.
IT CAN’T BE.
HIS SPECIAL MOVE GAUGE
ISN’T GOING DOWN.
SO THEN, WHAT IS IT?
( gasps )
OVERRIDING THE WORLD.
IN OTHER WORDS,
YOUR WILL RESHAPES REALITY.
TAKE, TAKE, TAKE, TAKE...
Haru: OH, NO!
TAKU!
FORGET ABOUT MY WINGS!
FINISH HIM NOW!
LIGHTNING CYAN SPIKE!
WHAT?!
( gasps )
( grunting )
( Taku groans )
( groans, gasps )
( yells )
( grunting )
WHAT WAS THAT
YOU WERE SAYING EARLIER,
MAYUZUMI SENPAI?
SOMETHING ABOUT ME
NOT HAVING THE STRENGTH
TO BREAK THE WALLS
IN THIS STAGE?
TO BE HONEST, I WAS HOPING
TO AVOID SHOWING YOU THIS.
Nomi: BUT IT DOESN’T MATTER.
YOU WON’T UNDERSTAND IT,
ANYWAY.
( gasps )
THE LOGIC BEHIND THIS TECHNIQUE
IS KNOWN BY THE SIX--
OR RATHER, THE SEVEN KINGS
AND THEIR CLOSES AIDES.
AND BY US.
IT’S THE INCARNATE SYSTEM!
BUT HEY, YOU’RE A BRIGHT GUY.
NOW THAT YOU’VE EXPERIENCED
THE HUGE DIFFERENCE
IN OUR SKILL LEVEL FIRSTHAND,
( grunts softly )
I’M SURE YOU’LL
HAVE NO PROBLEM
UNDERSTANDING THAT FOR THE REST
OF YOUR TIME AT THIS SCHOOL,
YOU’RE GONNA SERVE ME
LIKE A DOG.
THE FACT IS...
THE TWO OF YOU
HAVE NO OTHER CHOICE!
( Taku screaming )
( grunts )
I DON’T GET IT.
HOW DID NOMI FIND OUT
ABOUT THE INCARNATE SYSTEM?
I MEAN, IT’S NOT SOMETHING
YOU CAN JUST FIGURE OUT
ON YOUR OWN.
( Taku groaning loudly )
( gasps )
( groaning )
Nomi:
WE’VE GOT 500 SECONDS LEFT.
HMM. YOU HELD OUT LONGER
THAN I EXPECTED,
MAYUZUMI SENPAI.
GUESS YOU’RE BETTER AT THIS
THAN YOU ARE AT KENDO.
BUT TAKING THOSE
1.3 SECONDS FROM ME
IN REAL LIFE IS STILL
GONNA COST YA.
SO IT’S TIME TO PAY UP
( groaning )
WITH A LITTLE
PAIN AND SHAME,
AND OF COURSE,
YOUR BURST POINTS.
NOMI, WAIT!
HUH?
JUST HEAR ME OUT!
TAKU USED UP A TON
OF HIS POINTS
SO HE COULD CHALLENGE YOU
TO THIS DUEL.
SO PLEASE, TAKE THEM
FROM ME INSTEAD!
( grunts )
( groans )
( sighs )
COME ON, NOMI.
I’M BEGGING YOU.
( whimpering)
OH, MY GOD!
YOU’RE PATHETIC!
IN, LIKE, EVERY MEANING
OF THE WORD,
YOU’RE PATHETIC.
EVEN A GUY LIKE ME
THINKS THIS IS SOMETHING
YOU SHOULD NEVER DO
ON A BATTLEFIELD.
I DON’T CARE
WHAT PEOPLE THINK!
I’LL GIVE YOU NEXT WEEK’S
POINTS AS WELL!
SO PLEASE!
OKAY, FINE.
I’LL DO IT.
YOU KNOW, YOU REMIND ME
OF THE ROLLIE POLLIES
I USED TO LOVE TORTURING
IN THE GARDEN
AS A LITTLE KID.
BUT I GUESS IT’S
ACTIONS LIKE THIS
THAT ALLOWED YOU
TO GET THAT FLYING ABILITY
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
( grunting softly )
( grunts )
WILL YOU HURRY UP,
MAYUZUMI SENPAI?
OH, DON’T TELL ME THAT YOU’RE
TOO WEAK TO EVEN MOVE A FINGER.
( grunts softly )
HIT YES, TAKU.
COME ON.
I HAVEN’T GIVEN UP YET.
Haru: IF YOU SWITCH
TO BATTLE ROYALE MODE,
I CAN FIGHT HIM!
THIS IS SOMETHING I WANT!
SO PLEASE, TAKU!
HIT "YES"!
THANK YOU, TAKU.
ALL RIGHT, NOMI,
LET’S DO THIS!
( grunts )
( grunts loudly )
( yelling )
IMPOSSIBLE.
DAMN DOG!
SO WHEN DID YOU FIGURE OUT
HOW TO USE THIS TRICK?
COME ON,
VISUALIZE IT.
FASTER...
THAN THE SPEED OF LIGHT!
Kuroyukihime: THAT’S RIGHT...
YOU ARE FAST.
THE FASTEST.
( yelling )
WELL, WELL, WELL.
AN INCARNATION ATTACK.
LET ME GUESS--
YOU WERE UP ALL NIGHT
WORKING ON THAT FANCY MOVE,
WEREN’T YA?
I DON’T KNOW. MAYBE.
READY TO GIVE UP?
YEAH, RIGHT.
YOU’RE NOT THE ONLY ONE
WHO SPENT LAST NIGHT
LEARNING SOME NEW TRICKS.
I HAVE TO ADMIT,
THESE WINGS
REALLY ARE AMAZING.
THE ADVANTAGE IT GIVES YOU
IS SO INCREDIBLE,
BUT I’M ACTUALLY KINDA STUNNED
AS TO WHY YOU’RE
STILL AT LEVEL FOUR.
BUT YOU CAN REST ASSURED,
I WILL MASTER THEIR POWER
AND PUT THEM
TO MUCH BETTER USE
THAN YOU EVER DID.
SORT OF LIKE THIS.
EQUIP PYRO-DEALER.
( gasps )
( grunts )
( laughs )
AVIATION ABILITY
AND LONG-RANGE FIREPOWER
IS AN EXCELLENT COMBINATION.
AND WITH THE FIELD-DESTRUCTION
BONUS I JUST GOT,
I CAN RECHARGE MY
SPECIAL MOVE GAUGE.
NOW I CAN GO ONE FOREVER.
LET’S JUST BE HONEST.
I’M UNSTOPPABLE.
Haru:
I WOULDN’T BE SO SURE!
HUH?
IN ORDER FOR YOU
TO BE TRULY UNSTOPPABLE,
THERE’S ONE CONDITION
THAT YOU’RE FORGETTING ABOUT!
UH?
AND THAT’S THAT?
WELL...
YOU’D HAVE TO BE THE ONLY ONE
HERE WHO COULD FLY!
MMM?
THIS IS IT.
I’M GOING TO BORROW
YOUR WINGS.
MISS SKY RAKER!
ARMOR UP!
GALE THRUSTER!
♪
Sky Raker:
A HEART THAT YEARNS
FOR THE SKY...
THAT IS THE TRUE SOURCE
OF POWER FOR GALE THRUSTER.
BELIEVE IN YOURSELF.
YOU SHOULD BE ABLE
TO FLY AGAIN, MR. CROW.
NOW GO.
( yelling )
( gasps )
( beeping )
( whimpering )
SO THEN...
YOU WERE HIDING THAT CARD
UP YOUR SLEEVE THE WHOLE TIME.
OKAY, YOU’VE GOTTA TELL ME...
HOW DID YOU
GET A HOLD OF THAT TOY?
DID YOU BUY IT WITH POINTS
OR DID YOU STEAL IT
FROM SOMEONE LIKE--
YOU WOULDN’T UNDERSTAND
IF I TOLD YOU.
OH, AND WHY’S THAT?
THE PERSON WHO CREATED
THESE SKY-BLUE WINGS
ENTRUSTED THEM TO ME!
ALONG WITH HER
HOPES AND DREAMS!
IT’S SOMETHING YOU
WOULD NEVER UNDERSTAND.
SOMEONE LIKE YOU ONLY
SEES THE ACCELERATED WORLD
AS A MEANS TO AN END!
YOU SHOULDN’T EVEN
CALL YOURSELF A BURST LINKER!
( scoffs )
A BURST LINKER?
AND SINCE WHEN DID I
EVER CALL MYSELF THAT?
WHAT?
THAT’S WHAT THE FIRST
GENERATION OF PLAYERS
CALLED THEMSELVES.
WE WOULD NEVER USE THAT TERM.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN, "WE"?
COME ON, LET’S FINISH THIS.
YOU READY?
LET’S MATCH OUR INCARNATION
AGAINST ONE ANOTHER
AND SEE WHOSE DESIRE
IS THE STRONGEST.
INCARNATION
ISN’T ABOUT DESIRE!
IT’S ABOUT HOPE!
( yelling )
( grunting )
( grunts )
( yelps )
NO! I’M NOT DONE YET!!!
( grunts )
( yells )
AAH!
( groaning )
WHAT? ARE YOU PLANNING
ON DRIVING BOTH OF US
INTO THE GROUND?
I’LL ACTIVATE MY DEFENSES,
AND YOU’LL JUST END UP
DESTROYING YOURSELF.
YEAH?! WELL GUESS AGAIN!
( gasps )
TAKU!
DO IT!
LIGHTNING CYAN SPIKE!
( grunts )
( screaming )
HARU.
THANKS, TAKU.
I KEPT MY FAITH IN YOU.
I KNEW YOU WERE
TAKING DAMAGE ON PURPOSE
SO THAT YOU COULD CHARGE UP
YOUR SPECIAL MOVE GAUGE.
EXACTLY.
AND I HAD FAITH YOU
BELIEVED IN ME, TOO.
Haru:
SEE THAT, NOMI?
YOU DIDN’T LOSE THIS FIGHT
BECAUSE OF GALE THRUSTER
OR EVEN AN INCARNATION ATTACK.
YOU LOST BECAUSE WE
WEREN’T ALONE!
AND IT’S FOR THIS SAME REASON
THAT YOU’LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO BEAT US IN THE FUTURE.
( bell ringing )
UH!
WHAT WAS THAT?
AND WHERE’S IT COMING FROM?
( ringing continues )
( gasps )
( both gasp )
CITRON...
( bell ringing )
CALL!!!
( gasps )
( chuckles )
( both gasp )
( gasps )
I DON’T GET IT.
Haru: WHY?
WHY, CHIYU?!
♪
( singing in Japanese )
( song ends )
Kuroyukihime:
NEXT STAGE: INVITATION.
NEW CHALLENGERS COME FORWARD.
AND A BATTLE BEGINS
IN A TROPICAL PARADISE.