Niko: IT’S THE ARMOR
OF CATASTROPHE.
CHROME DISASTER.
BUT HOW?
WE SHOULD’VE STILL HAD
PLENTY OF TIME IN THIS
WORLD BEFORE HE GOT HERE.
Haru: WAIT A SEC.
HE MUST HAVE ACCELERATED
WHILE HE WAS ON THE TRAIN!
( grunting )
DECEIT FIRE CRACKER!
I’LL EAT YOU ALIVE.
ALL OF YOU!
( yelling )
( roars )
( gasps )
THIS ISN’T A FIGHT.
IT’S A MASSACRE!
♪
YOU BLOOD-THIRSTY BEAST.
EVERYONE RETREAT!
( clamoring )
Haru: I’M SUPPOSED TO HELP
DELIVER THE FINAL JUDGMENT BLOW
BY RENDERING THAT THING
POWERLESS?
THERE’S NO WAY!
( gasps )
Kuroyukihime:
YOU’LL GO NO FURTHER.
S-SENPAI...
( growls )
( gasps )
( weak gasping )
WHAT’S GOING ON?
WHAT’S WRONG WITH ME?!
AFTER EVERYTHING I SAID TO
SENPAI FOR JUST SITTING THERE.
AND NOW LOOK...
I’M DOING THE EXACT
SAME THING!
Kuroyukihime:
"WHEN A BURST LINKER
LOSES THEIR WILL TO FIGHT,
THEY CAN’T CONTROL
THEIR DUEL AVATAR."
WHEN THE LITTLE
BRAT SAID THAT,
SHE WAS RIGHT.
IT’S HARD FOR ME TO ADMIT THIS,
BUT I STILL REGRET
WHAT I DID TWO YEARS AGO.
DEEP DOWN, MY INSATIABLE
APPETITE FOR VIOLENCE
AND VICTORY...
FRIGHTENS ME A GREAT DEAL.
BUT YOU, HARUYUKI...
ARE THE OPPOSITE OF THAT.
( gasps )
YOUR ISSUE IS THAT
YOU MISTAKENLY BELIEVE
BEING DEFEATED
WILL SOMEHOW MAKE YOU
LESS WORTHY TO THE TEAM.
THAT’S WHY IN OUR RECENT
TERRITORY BATTLES,
YOU HAVEN’T PERFORMED
NEARLY AS WELL AS YOU ONCE DID.
IT’S THE TRUTH,
AND YOU KNOW IT!
I’M NOT THAT GOOD!
DON’T BE AN IDIOT!
( gasps )
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS,
I WILL NEVER ABANDON YOU.
THE BOND THAT EXISTS
BETWEEN US IS STRONGER
THAN YOU THINK.
YOU MUST HAVE
MORE FAITH IN IT!
( gasps )
HOW CAN SHE
FIGHT LIKE THAT?
IT’S LIKE SHE’S
TRULY ENJOYING IT!
( grunting )
( roars )
RUN, SENPAI!
GET OUT OF THERE!
RUNNING IS NOT
AN OPTION FOR ME,
HARUYUKI.
I’VE ALLOWED THE YELLOW KING
TO EXPOSE MY UGLY SIDE
IN FRONT OF YOU.
AS YOUR MENTOR AND GUARDIAN,
I HAVE TO TAKE ON THIS FIGHT.
OTHERWISE, I COULD NEVER FACE
YOU IN THE REAL WORLD.
BUT WHAT’S THE POINT IF
YOU KNOW YOU’LL LOSE?!
THIS IS NOT ABOUT
WINNING OR LOSING.
THERE IS NO
HONOR IN RETREAT.
IT DOESN’T MATTER
WHO YOUR OPPONENT IS...
ONCE YOU ENTER THE BATTLEFIELD,
ALL THAT COUNTS
IS THAT YOU FIGHT
TO THE END!
SHE’S RIGHT.
I USED TO BE SO FOCUSED
WHEN I FOUGHT THAT I
NEVER EVEN THOUGHT ABOUT
WHAT OTHER PEOPLE
MIGHT SAY.
BUT NOW I’M SCARED
THAT IF I LOSE, THAT
THEY’RE JUST GONNA LAUGH AT ME.
EVEN HERE IN THE
ACCELERATED WORLD,
I WAS WORRYING ABOUT
WHAT OTHER PEOPLE THINK OF ME.
COME ON...
I CAN DO BETTER,
I KNOW IT!
SO THEN,
HARUYUKI.
READY TO GO DOWN
WITH STYLE?
YES!
( gasping )
( grunting )
( Kuroyukihime
screaming )
SENPAI!
SAY SOMETHING!
WHY? WHY DID YOU DO THIS?
DAMN IT, SCARLET RAIN.
ANSWER ME!
WHY DID YOU
FIRE AT US?!
YOU KNOW THAT IF YOU
DEFEAT HER, BLACK LOTUS
WILL LOSE ALL HER POINTS!
SHE’LL BE OUT OF
THIS WORLD FOR GOOD!
SO WHAT?
( gasps )
TO A BURST LINKER,
ALL OTHER LINKERS
ARE ENEMIES.
AND WHEN YOU LOSE
TO AN ENEMY,
YOU LOSE POINTS.
LET YOUR POINTS RUN
DOWN TO ZERO AND
YOU’RE BANISHED FOREVER.
THAT’S JUST
HOW IT GOES.
YEAH, BUT COME ON.
WE’RE NOT ENEMIES,
WE’RE---
WE’RE WHAT?
"FRIENDS"?
YOU’RE SO FUCKIN’ NAIVE
IT MAKES MY STOMACH TURN.
( gasps )
HERE, LET ME
GIVE YOU ONE LAST
BIT OF ADVICE.
IN THE ACCELERATED WORLD,
THERE ISN’T A SINGLE
PERSON YOU CAN TRUST.
ALLIES.
LEGION MEMBERS.
FRIENDS.
EVEN THE WHOLE
GUARDIAN-PROTEGE BOND
IS A TOTAL SHAM!
ONCE I’VE TAKEN HIM OUT,
I’M COMIN’ AFTER YOU ALL.
IF YOU WANT TO AVOID
THAT FATE, I SUGGEST
YOU START RUNNING.
BECAUSE THE NEXT
TIME WE MEET...
IT’LL BE AS ENEMIES.
WHY DOES IT HAVE TO
COME DOWN TO THIS?
IS THERE REALLY
NO OTHER WAY?
Kuroyukihime:
SUCH A BABY.
THIS IS WHY
I HATE CHILDREN.
SENPAI...
( gasps )
( grunting )
Haru:
SHE DIDN’T SHOOT!
Kuroyukihime: NO.
SHE’S TOO BUSY BROODING.
MORE THAN ANYONE ELSE HERE,
THAT GIRL WANTS TO BE ABLE
TO TRUST SOMEONE.
SHE’S UNABLE TO LET GO
OF A BURST LINKER’S
LAST BOND.
( surprised gasp )
IT’S CLEAR
TO ME NOW.
THOSE TWO WERE
GUARDIAN AND PROTEGE.
CHROME DISASTER,
OR RATHER CHERRY ROOK,
WAS THE RED KING’S GUARDIAN.
( gasping )
( metal clangs )
WELL, DON’T JUST
STAND THERE.
I’LL BE FINE.
GO ON.
GO HELP NIKO.
SHE IS OUR FRIEND.
( gasps )
OKAY!
( shouting )
Y-YOU DUMBASS.
WHY’D YOU SAVE ME?
WE’RE FRIENDS,
AREN’T WE?
( surprised grunt )
I TOLD YOU NOT TO BE
SO FUCKING NAIVE!
YOU’RE THE ONE
BEING NAIVE.
YOU’RE A KING!
STOP TRYING TO AVOID
WHAT HAS TO BE DONE.
AT THIS POINT, BRAIN BURST
IS NOTHING MORE THAN A
CURSE TO YOUR FRIEND.
YOU HAVE TO
DO THIS, NIKO.
YOU’RE THE ONLY ONE
WHO CAN SET HIM FREE.
YEAH...
I KNOW.
YOU’RE RIGHT.
LET’S END THIS, CHERRY.
( roaring )
( gasps )
Haru: HE CAN FLY, TOO?
NO. IT’S JUST
A MASSIVE JUMP.
HE’S TRYING TO GET TO
THE NEAREST LEAVE POINT
SO HE CAN LOG OUT.
NIKO.
THIS TIME YOU’LL
FIRE, RIGHT?
THE JUDGMENT BLOW?
YEAH. I’LL DO IT.
FOR HIS SAKE.
GOOD. THEN I’LL KEEP HIM
BUSY UNTIL YOU GET THERE.
YOU CAN’T DO
IT ALONE.
LOOK, HE MAY BE HURT, BUT
HE’S STILL REALLY FAST.
IF HE CATCHES YOU,
THAT’S IT.
YOU’RE DONE.
YEAH? WELL, AT LEAST
I’LL GO DOWN FIGHTING!
( gasps )
THE LEAVE POINT MUST BE
AT THE FOOT OF SUNSHINE CITY.
IF HE’S IN THE MIDDLE
OF A LEAP...
THEN HE WON’T BE
ABLE TO DODGE ME!
I’VE GOTTA AIM FOR
THE MOMENT HE LANDS.
WHAT?!
IT’S A WIRE!
SO THAT’S HOW
HE WAS ABLE
TO DO THAT.
ALL RIGHT.
HOW CAN I STOP HIM?
I GOT IT!
FASTER!
I’VE GOTTA GO EVEN FASTER!
ALL RIGHT!
( shuddering breath )
( sighs )
( grunting )
( grunting, yelling )
( screaming )
( gasps )
( straining )
( grunting )
HIYA!
( yelling )
Cherry Rook:
ALL I WANT...
IS TO BECOME
STRONGER.
THAT’S ALL.
I CAN TELL THAT
YOU FEEL THE SAME WAY.
YOU ALSO WANT
THE POWER, DON’T YOU?
YOU THINK ’CAUSE YOU
WANT TO BE STRONGER
YOU’RE FORGIVEN?
YOU CHOSE TO WEAR
THAT ARMOR, YOU ATTACKED
COUNTLESS AVATARS.
YOU EVEN TRIED
TO DEVOUR NIKO,
YOUR OWN PROTEGE!
THERE IS NO
EXCUSE FOR THAT!
WE ALL WANNA BE STRONGER!
WE ALL WANT THE STRENGTH AND
COURAGE WE NEED TO FACE ALL THE
HARDSHIPS WE HAVE TO GO THROUGH!
IT’S NOT JUST YOU!
( groaning )
( gasps )
Niko: YOU DID IT,
SILVER CROW.
NOW...
LEAVE THE
REST TO ME.
( gunshot )
Niko: IN THE REAL WORLD,
CHERRY AND I DON’T KNOW
WHO OUR PARENTS ARE.
WE WERE BOTH ABANDONED
WHEN WE WERE LITTLE.
THE BOARDING SCHOOL WE
GO TO IS A SCHOOL FOR
ORPHANED KIDS JUST LIKE US.
( gasps )
BECAUSE MY
PERSONALITY IS
WHAT IT IS,
I HAD A HARD TIME
FITTING IN AT SCHOOL.
I WAS ALWAYS OFF
IN THE CORNER,
PLAYING VR GAMES ALONE.
BUT 3 YEARS AGO, A BOY
WHO WAS A COUPLE YEARS OLDER
CAME UP AND TALKED TO ME.
HE WAS TRYING SO HARD TO
TELL ME SOMETHING, HIS FACE
HAD TURNED BRIGHT RED.
IT WAS PRETTY FUNNY.
THEN HE ASKED IF I WANTED
TO PLAY A GAME HE THOUGHT I’D
LIKE A WHOLE LOT MORE.
WHEN I BECAME A BURST LINKER,
HE TAUGHT ME EVERYTHING
HE KNEW SO I COULD FIT IN.
HE EVEN RISKED HIS LIFE TO
PROTECT ME FROM HARM.
BUT IT WASN’T LONG BEFORE
I CAUGHT UP TO HIM. AND
THEN PASSED HIS LEVEL.
BEFORE I KNEW IT,
I WAS LEVEL 9.
AND AFTER THAT, I WAS
MADE LEGION MASTER.
I BECAME OBSESSED.
I NEVER ONCE STOPPED
TO THINK ABOUT WHAT
HE MAY BE GOING THROUGH,
OR IF SOMETHING
WAS BOTHERING HIM.
WE MET IN THE REAL
WORLD EVERY DAY AT SCHOOL.
BUT I DIDN’T EVEN NOTICE
THAT HE WAS ACTING STRANGE.
ALL HE WANTED...WAS
TO BE MY GUARDIAN FOREVER.
THAT’S WHY HE SOUGHT MORE
POWER AND WAS TEMPTED BY
THE ARMOR OF CATASTROPHE.
IF ONLY I HAD SAID
SOMETHING TO HIM...
BUT I DIDN’T!
I DID NOTHING!
( crying )
NIKO, IT’S TRUE.
BRAIN BURST IS WAY
MORE THAN JUST A GAME.
I’M SCARED ALL THE
TIME THAT I’M NOT
STRONG ENOUGH...
THAT MY MASTER WILL
JUST ABANDON ME SOMEDAY.
BUT THEN I REMEMBER.
I KNOW HER
BEYOND THIS GAME.
I KNOW HER REAL FACE,
HER NAME, HER VOICE.
WHATEVER HAPPENS, THAT
BOND WE HAVE FROM THE REAL
WORLD...WILL NEVER DISAPPEAR.
START OVER WITH HIM
IN THE REAL WORLD AND
BECOME FRIENDS AGAIN.
( gasps )
HERE IN THE
ACCELERATED WORLD,
WE’RE BOTH IN
DIFFERENT LEGIONS...
BUT IN THE REAL
WORLD, YOU AND I
BECAME FRIENDS.
WHAT?!
FRIENDS?!
YEAH, RIGHT.
IN YOUR DREAMS!
YOU MIGHT MAKE A GOOD
UNDERLING, BUT THAT’S
ABOUT AS FAR AS YOU’D GET.
( moans )
Kuroyukihime:
AN UNDERLING
TO WHOM, I MIGHT ASK?
( gasps )
SENPAI!
TAKU!
OF COURSE.
THE ONE-HOUR DEATH
PENALTY IS OVER.
SO NOW
YOU’RE RECOVERED!
MAN, YOU WERE PULLING
SOME CRAZY MOVES
BACK THERE.
Taku:
LOOK WHO’S TALKING.
Kuroyukihime:
WELL NOW,
SCARLET RAIN.
I BELIEVE YOU HAVE
SOMETHING YOU WOULD
LIKE TO SAY TO ME?
MY BAD.
THAT’S ALL?!
WELL, WHAT DO
YOU EXPECT?!
AT LEAST I FOUGHT
THROUGH THE
WHOLE THING.
YOU WERE THE ONE
LYING THERE SLEEPING
DURING MOST IF IT!
Kuroyukihime:
AND JUST WHO’S
FAULT WAS THAT?!
Both: HUH?
WHAT’S GOING ON?
( whooshing noise )
Kuroyukihime:
TRANSITION TIME.
THE ELEMENTS THAT
MAKE UP THE UNLIMITED
NEUTRAL FIELD ARE CHAOTIC.
THEY CHANGE AT
FIXED INTERVALS.
I KNOW IT’S QUITE
A SIGHT TO BEHOLD.
BUT ENOUGH STANDING AROUND.
THERE ARE THINGS
WE HAVE TO DO.
Niko:
SHE’S RIGHT.
Kuroyukihime:
LISTEN UP, EVERYONE.
YOU NEED TO OPEN YOUR
STATUS SCREENS AND CHECK
THE ITEM STORAGE.
IF THE ARMOR OF
CATASTROPHE IS IN THERE,
MAKE SURE YOU DELETE IT.
Haru:
IT’S NOT THERE.
IT’S GONE...
FOR GOOD!
YEAH...
SAME HERE.
Kuroyukihime:
EXCELLENT.
THEN THAT
COMPLETES
OUR MISSION.
I THINK IT’S
TIME WE ALL GO
AND CELEBRATE.
Niko: YEAH, LET’S
GO CRACK OPEN A
BOTTLE OF CHAMPAGNE!
Kuroyukihime:
YOU IDIOT. WE’RE
MINORS, REMEMBER?
( laughing )
Voice: I’M HUNGRY!
( gasps )
Taku:
IS SOMETHING
WRONG, HARU?
NO, IT’S ALL GOOD.
I’M FINE.
HARU: I GUESS...
I JUST IMAGINED THAT.
Voice:
I’M HUNGRY!
EVERYONE’S WATCHING.
I BET SENPAI IS TOO.
WHEN’S HE GONNA
FIRE THAT THING?
IF I GET SHOT DOWN
AGAIN, I’LL LOOK LIKE
A COMPLETE IDIOT.
NO WAY! THIS ISN’T GOING
TO BE LIKE LAST TIME.
DON’T RUN!
MY ENEMY ISN’T
THAT RIFLE.
IT’S THE AVATAR
CROUCHING BEHIND IT,
CONTROLLED BY A BURST LINKER.
WHAT I HAVE TO DO IS
SENSE THE SECOND HIS BRAIN
SENDS THE SIGNAL TO ATTACK!
AAH!
Kuroyukihime:
WELL DONE. YOU
DODGED THAT BRILLIANTLY.
YEAH...WELL...
YA SEE, I...
I JUST WATCHED THE
GUY THIS TIME AND NOT
THE BARREL OF THE GUN.
AND I SAW A SLIGHT
MOVEMENT RIGHT
BEFORE HE FIRED
OH? REALLY?
INTERESTING...
THAT SNIPER MIGHT
HAVE HAD A
SENSORY POWER.
MEANING HE COULD
SENSE WHEN AN ENEMY
IS FOCUSING ON HIS GUN.
AND ONCE HE REALIZES
THAT’S HAPPENING, HE
LOCKS ONTO THEM.
WAIT. SO YOU’RE TELLING ME
THE REASON I KEPT GETTING
SHOT DOWN BEFORE WAS...
BECAUSE YOU WERE
FOCUSING ON THE GUN
MORE THAN THE SHOOTER.
( moaning )
DON’T WORRY
ABOUT IT.
Haru: I’M HOME.
Haru’s Mother on machine:
HARUYUKI...
I’M GONNA HAVE TO SPEND
THE NIGHT AT THE OFFICE AGAIN.
( Niko laughing )
( grunts )
Haru’s mother: AND I’M SORRY,
BUT ONE OF MY CO-WORKER’S KIDS
IS COMING OVER TO STAY
AT OUR PLACE.
( laughing )
BE NICE TO HER, OKAY?
BYE.
YOU BROKE INTO
MY PRIZED
COLLECTION AGAIN!
( grunts )
HEY, BIG BROTHER.
WELCOME HOME!
I’VE NOTIFIED
THE OTHER FIVE KINGS,
INCLUDING RADIO,
AND TOLD THEM
THAT DISASTER
HAS BEEN DEALT WITH.
THAT SHOULD BE
THE END OF IT.
I WANTED TO RAISE THE
POINT ABOUT THE YELLOWS TAKING
THE ARMOR IN THE FIRST PLACE.
BUT I HAVE NO
PROOF OF IT.
YEAH, OKAY.
WHAT ABOUT...
CHERRY ROOK?
( surprised grunt )
WELL...IT LOOKS
LIKE HE’LL BE
MOVING NEXT MONTH.
IT SEEMS THAT SOMEWHERE OUT
OF THE BLUE, SOME DISTANT
RELATIVES CAME FORWARD.
THEY LIVE IN...
FUKUOKA.
THAT’S FAR...
THAT’S WHY HE
SAID HE WAS IN
SUCH A HURRY.
HIS BIGGEST FEAR
WAS, IF HE MOVED,
THEN THE ONLY WAY FOR
US TO CONNECT WOULD BE
THROUGH BRAIN BURST.
BUT THERE AREN’T A WHOLE
LOT OF OTHER BURST LINKERS
OUTSIDE OF TOKYO.
SO HE WANTED TO FIGHT
AND RAISE HIS LEVEL
WHILE HE WAS HERE.
IT WAS THAT HURRY
THAT LED HIM
TO THE ARMOR.
BUT IN SPITE...
OR MAYBE EVEN THANKS
TO HIM LOSING
BRAIN BURST...
HE’S BACK TO HIS
OLD SELF AGAIN.
HE’S JUST LIKE HE WAS WHEN
HE FIRST APPROACHED ME.
WHICH MADE
ME REALIZE...
EVEN IF HE’S NOT A BURST
LINKER NOW, AND HE STILL
GOES AND MOVES TO FUKUOKA,
OUR FRIENDSHIP
IS NOT OVER.
THERE’S A LOT OF OTHER
VR GAMES WE COULD PLAY.
UH, YEAH. THERE’S
A WHOLE TON OF ’EM.
THAT’S WHAT
I THOUGHT.
SO...IF YOU KNOW OF ANY
VR GAMES OUT THERE THAT’RE
GOOD, JUST LET ME KNOW.
I WANT A GAME...
HE AND I CAN PLAY
FOR A REALLY LONG TIME.
( chuckling )
YEAH, OKAY.
YOU’RE WELCOME
TO ANY OF THESE.
JUST GO AHEAD
AND HELP
YOURSELF.
OF COURSE,
THEY ALL TEND
TO BE THE SAME.
( laughing )
OH!
UH, WHAT’S THIS?
W-WELL...IT’S
JUST A LITTLE
"THANK YOU."
WOW. NIKO. DID
YOU REALLY MAKE
THESE FOR ME?
HEY, LOOK, IF YOU
DON’T WANT ’EM,
THEN GIVE THEM BACK!
MM-MM, NO.
LOOK!
I WANT ’EM!
THANKS! I WAS
JUST SURPRISED,
THAT’S ALL.
( munching )
MMM!
NIKO, THEY’RE
REALLY GOOD!
( gasps )
REALLY GOOD.
( whimpering )
WHY THE HELL
ARE YOU CRYING?!
UGH!
YOU BIG BABY!
THEY’RE JUST
COOKIES!
STOP IT,
YOU STUPID IDIOT!
EITHER EAT OR CRY,
BUT DON’T STAND
THERE AND DO BOTH!
( chewing,
whimpering )
♪
Kuroyukihime:
AN INTRUDER
VIOLATES THE PEACE.
AS A NEW SEASON
ARRIVES, A NEW
BATTLE BEGINS.