YOU'VE GOT MAIL.
A VOTE?
CHOOSE A NICKNAME
FOR THAT CREEP ARITA?
(telephone rings )
UH, HEY.
IT'S ME--HARUYUKI.
HEY! HOW HAVE YOU BEEN?
WHAT'S UP?
WELL, TO BE
PERFECTLY HONEST,
I HAVE SOMETHING
I WANT TO ASK YOU.
DO YOU THINK YOU HAVE
SOME TIME LATER TODAY
TO MEET UP WITH ME
AND TAKU IN PERSON?
IT'S KIND OF IMPORTANT.
YOU KNOW IT'S
RAINING OUT, RIGHT?
BUT I DO HAVE
A HUGE CRAVING
FOR A BIG PIECE
OF CAKE...
WITH LOTS OF
STRAWBERRIES ON IT!
YEAH, SURE! I'LL BUY YOU
WHATEVER YOU WANT, YUNIKO!
JUST CALL ME NIKO,
SILLY!
I KNOW A SUPER-YUMMY
CAKE SHOP,
SO WHY DON'T
THE THREE OF US
MEET THERE?
SEE YA SOON,
BIG BROTHER!
(singing in Japanese )
SO HOW'D IT ALL GO?
DID YOU GET THE RED KING
TO AGREE TO MEET US?
YEAH. I DON'T KNOW
HOW, BUT I DID.
JEEZ, LOOKS LIKE
THAT RUMOR IS SPREADING
LIKE WILDFIRE.
WELL, I HAVEN'T
DONE ANYTHING WRONG.
I KNOW THAT.
I STILL CAN'T BELIEVE
THAT SUGENO CALLED YOU IN
WITHOUT A SHRED
OF EVIDENCE.
NOMI PROBABLY
GAVE HIM MY NAME.
WHAT?NOMI?
I SHOULD TELL YOU
THE WHOLE STORY.
HUH?
FROM THE START...
THIS WHOLE THING
HAS BEEN ONE
GIANT TRAP
SET UP BY NOMI.
AND I WALKED
RIGHT INTO IT.
I SEE. SO THAT PHOTO
I SENT YOU
HAD A VIRUS IN IT.
I'M SORRY, HARU.
I SHOULD'VE TOTALLY
CHECKED FOR THAT.
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
NO...
I SHOULD'VE NOTICED
SOMETHING WAS STRANGE
AS SOON AS I SAW
HOW BIG THAT FILE WAS.
BUT I DIDN'T.
INSTEAD, I BARGE
INTO YOUR HOUSE
WHEN YOU WERE GOING
THROUGH A REALLY HARD TIME
AND STARTED
MOUTHING OFF TO YOU.
AND TO MAKE THINGS
EVEN WORSE,
I PUNCHED YOU.
HARU...
UH...YEAH?
PLEASE, I WANT YOU
TO HIT ME.
THERE'S REALLY
NO NEED FOR THAT.
IF YOU DON'T,
I'LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO FORGIVE MYSELF.
TAKU, WAIT!
LOOK, THE TRUTH IS,
YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO SHOULD BE
HITTING ME AGAIN.
HUH?
CHIYU, I'M SORRY.
WHEN I FELL FOR THAT
VISUAL MASKING TRAP
OF HIS,
I RAN INTO
THE GIRLS' SHOWER
THINKING IT WAS
THE GUYS'.
AND WHEN I DID,
I SAW CHIYU IN
THE SHOWER.
I'M SORRY.
I SEE.
SO THAT EXPLAINS
HOW SHE GOT INVOLVED
IN ALL THIS.
I'M REALLY SORRY.
I KNOW I SHOULD'VE
TOLD YOU SOONER.
LOOK, THAT'S ENOUGH.
WHATEVER YOU
HAPPENED TO SEE,
I REALLY DON'T WANT
TO KNOW ABOUT IT.
OUT OF RESPECT FOR CHI.
YOU'RE A TRUE
GENTLEMAN, TAKU.
LONG TIME NO SEE,
BIG BROTHER.
YOU'RE STILL
AS ROUND AS EVER.
SAME FOR YOU, TEACH.
YOU'RE STILL AS GLOOMY AS EVER.
YAY! MY STRAWBERRY
LABYRINTH!
I GOT HERE EARLY
SO I WENT AHEAD AND ORDERED IT.
OH, YOU'LL BE FINE WITH
A COUPLE OF COFFEES, RIGHT?
UH...YEAH, SURE.
AND TWO COFFEES
FOR THESE GUYS, PLEASE.
HA HA!
AHH! MMM!
HUH?
YOU CAN'T HAVE ANY!
I KNOW THAT.
JEEZ, JUST KIDDING.
HERE YOU GO. AHH...
AHH...
HA HA! I LIED.
AHEM.
RIGHT. ANYWAY,
NIKO, LISTEN--
LET'S TALK ABOUT
WHY WE CAME HERE.
(mumbling)
SURE. I'LL LISTEN FOR
TEN MORE STRAWBERRIES.
I'M NOT ENTIRELY SURE
THAT'S A FAIR TRADE,
BUT...
WELL, TEACH HERE--
I MEAN TAKUMU--
THERE'S A TECHNIQUE
WE'D LIKE YOU TO
TRY AND TEACH HIM.
CAN YOU SHOW HIM
HOW TO USE THE
INCARNATE SYSTEM?
UH...
WHAT'D YOU SAY?
( gasps)
WE'RE GONNA BORROW
THE BACK ROOM FOR A BIT.
MM.
Haru:UH, NIKO?
HEY, WAIT UP!
LISTEN, TURD-BRAIN!
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU THINKING?
BLABBING ABOUT INCARNATION
IN FUCKIN' PUBLIC?!
(gasps)
I'M SO SORRY!
OKAY, BEFORE WE GO ANY FURTHER,
YOU LOSERS ARE GONNA TELL ME
WHO TOLD YOU ABOUT
THE INCARNATE SYSTEM
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
NOW, STOP STANDING THERE
AND START TALKING!
I SEE--DUSK TAKER.
SO IT'S A DUEL AVATAR
WITH ROBBING ABILITIES.
TOSS IN THE FACT THAT
HE CAN USE INCARNATION,
AND I CAN SEE
WHY HE'D BE TOO MUCH
FOR THE TWO OF YOU
TO HANDLE BY YOURSELVES.
YES, THAT IS
UNFORTUNATELY
THE CASE.
WELL, I FEEL YOUR PAIN,
I REALLY DO.
BUT, TO BE BLUNT,
THIS IS ANOTHER
LEGION'S PROBLEM.
IN FACT, IF I WERE
TO JUST IGNORE IT
AND LET THIS BE
THE DOWNFALL OF
NEGA NEBULOUS,
THAT WORKS OUT
EVEN BETTER FOR ME.
UH...
BUT IF I DID THAT...
YOU'D GET ALL SAD-FACED
AND SAY,
"WHAT?! OH, COME ON!
"YOU CAME TO US WHEN
YOU HAD TROUBLE WITH
YOUR LEGION
AND WE HELPED YOU OUT!
YOU OWE US NOW!"
OR SOME SHIT LIKE THAT!
LOOK...
(sighs)
I KNEW ASKING FOR HELP
FROM YOU GUYS
WAS GONNA COME BACK
AND BITE ME ON THE ASS.
BUT EVEN STILL,
ASKING ME TO TEACH YOU
THE INCARNATE SYSTEM--
THAT'S SURE ONE HELL OF
A PRICEY PAYBACK
YOU'RE WANTING.
SO ARE YOU SAYING
YOU'RE WILLING TO
HELP US?!
DAMN IT.
IF I'D KNOWN
THIS WAS WHAT YOU GUYS
WERE GONNA ASK FOR,
I WOULD'VE GOTTEN
THE ROYAL PALACE,
NOT THE STRAWBERRY
LABYRINTH.
THANK YOU SO MUCH!
UHH!AAH! WHAT THE HELL
IS WITH YOU AND MY FEET?!
YOU'RE SUCH
A FUCKING PERVERT!
ALL RIGHT,
PLUG THIS IN.
WELL, WHAT IS IT?
RELAX.
IT'S NOT SOME KIND OF TRAP.
JUST TRUST ME.
THIS ROOM BLOCKS OUT
ALL RADIO WAVES,
SO IF WE WANT TO CONNECT
TO THE GLOBAL NET,
WE HAVE TO USE
A CABLE.
I'VE GOT TO GET BACK
TO MY DORM ROOM BY 6:00,
SO THAT MEANS I'VE ONLY
GOT ABOUT 30 MINUTES
THAT I CAN SPEND
WITH YOU GUYS.
THAT'LL GIVE US 500 HOURS
IN THE ACCELERATED WORLD--
ABOUT 20 DAYS.
IN THAT TIME, YOU'LL LEARN
SOME INCARNATE SKILLS
YOU CAN USE
IN ACTUAL BATTLES.
THANKS,
BUT I'M ONLY GOING
TO NEED A WEEK.
THAT SHOULD BE
ENOUGH.
WELL, GET A LOAD OF YOU
THERE, TEACH.
I THINK IT'S TIME WE TEST
JUST HOW STRONG THAT RESOLVE
OF YOURS ACTUALLY IS.
YOU GUYS READY?
MM-HMM.
All:UNLIMITED BURST!
(gasps)
CRAP, IT'S THE
ICE AND SNOW STAGE.
I HATE THIS ONE.
HEY, CROW, DOES THAT
METAL ARMOR OF YOURS
HAVE ANY RESISTANCE
TO THE COLD?
UH...YEAH, SORT OF.
NOT FAIR!
(grunts)
YAAAH!
(screaming)
I MEANT IT ONLY
HAS RESISTANCE TO
THE COLD DAMAGES!
BUT I STILL FEEL THE COLD!
YIKES, I'M FREEZING!
AHEM!
OKAY, I'LL START
BY GIVING YOU THE BASIC GIST
OF THE INCARNATE SKILLS.
YES, PLEASE!
FIRST OFF,
EVEN IF YOU USE IT,
YOUR SPECIAL MOVE GAUGE
WON'T GO DOWN.
SECONDLY, AN ATTACK
USING INCARNATION
CAN ONLY BE DEFENDED
BY INCARNATION--
NO EXCEPTIONS.
AND LASTLY...
THEY SHINE.
THEY SHINE?
CROW, SHOW US
A LITTLE SOMETHING.
LET ME SEE THE POWER
YOU'VE MANAGED TO
PUT TOGETHER SO FAR.
UH...OKAY.
MY HAND IS A SWORD...
A SWORD THAT'S AS FAST
AS THE SPEED OF LIGHT
AND CAN CUT
THROUGH ANYTHING!
WELL, THAT'S BETTER
THAN I EXPECTED.
PRETTY IMPRESSIVE...
FOR A FRIGGIN' NOOB.
NOOB?!
(gasps)
FOR AN INCARNATION
THAT'S STRONG ENOUGH
TO USE IN BATTLE,
IT SHOULD SHINE
LIKE THIS.
WE CALL THIS
THE OVER RAY.
THERE ARE FOUR BASIC
INCARNATE SKILLS,
AND THAT WAS
THE FIRST OF THEM--
RANGE ENHANCEMENT.
WOW!
AND THIS IS
THE SECOND ONE--
SPEED ENHANCEMENT.
GOT IT?
WHAT ABOUT THE THIRD
AND FOURTH ONE?
ATTACK ENHANCEMENT
AND ARMOR ENHANCEMENT--
THAT'S THE OTHER TWO.
BUT...I'M NOT ABLE TO USE
EITHER OF THOSE ABILITIES.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
YOU CAN'T USE THEM?
YOU'RE A KING.
YOU SEE,
I CAN'T USE THOSE MOVES
BECAUSE I KNOW
I'M NOT STRONG ENOUGH.
THE REAL WORLD SCARES ME.
THE CLOSER I GET TO IT,
THE MORE CHANCES I GIVE IT
TO FIND WAYS TO HURT ME.
SO I KEEP MY DISTANCE.
IT WAS THAT FEAR
AND THOSE PSYCHOLOGICAL SCARS
THAT CREATED SCARLET RAIN.
NIKO...
SO THERE YOU GO.
THAT'S WHY I CAN'T USE
THE OTHER TWO ASPECTS
OF INCARNATION
TO STRENGTHEN MY AVATAR'S
OFFENSIVE AND DEFENSIVE POWERS.
IN OTHER WORDS,
YOU'RE SAYING
THE TYPE OF INCARNATE
SKILLS YOU CAN ACQUIRE
AREN'T TOTALLY
DEPENDENT ON THE NATURE
OF YOUR OWN INDIVIDUAL
DUAL AVATAR.
EXACTLY. INCARNATION
IS MEANT TO BE USED
FOR CONFRONTING
YOUR OWN WEAKNESSES,
NOT FOR DEFEATING ENEMIES.
THAT'S WHY
YOU SHOULD NEVER USE
AN INCARNATE SKILL
AGAINST AN ENEMY
UNLESS THEY USE IT
ON YOU FIRST. GOT THAT?
GOT IT.
GOOD. ALL RIGHT,
LET'S BEGIN YOUR TRAINING.
PILE, WHAT TYPE
OF AVATAR ARE YOU--
CLOSE-RANGE OR LONG-RANGE?
WELL, IT'S OBVIOUSLY
CLOSE-RANGE.
ALL BLUE-COLOR
TYPES ARE.
AND HIS IS EVEN
SUPER-VIVID.
YEAH, THAT'S WHAT
I THOUGHT AT FIRST, TOO.
BUT LOOK AT HIS
ENHANCED ARMAMENT.
OH. YOU'RE RIGHT.
I HAD A FEELING
IT MIGHT COME TO THIS.
IN ORDER FOR ME
TO LEARN INCARNATION,
I'LL TO FACE MY
PSYCHOLOGICAL SCARS HEAD-ON.
ALL RIGHT,
I'LL STEP OUT, THEN.
NO, DON'T.
THIS IS SOMETHING
I WANT YOU TO HEAR.
I SHOULD'VE TOLD YOU
A LONG TIME AGO.
CYAN PILE IS FUNDAMENTALLY
A CLOSE-RANGE FIGHTER.
AND YET IT CAME EQUIPPED
WITH THIS LONG-RANGE
TYPE WEAPON.
AND THE REASON FOR THAT IS
BECAUSE IT'S MOST LIKELY
AN EXPRESSION OF MY FEAR.
WHAT FEAR?
IN ELEMENTARY SCHOOL,
FROM THE THIRD GRADE
TO THE FIFTH GRADE,
I WAS BULLIED
ON A DAILY BASIS.
(gasps)
FOR WHATEVER REASON,
THE OLDER STUDENTS
IN MY KENDO CLASS
SINGLED ME OUT
AND DECIDED TO PICK ON ME.
THEY USED ME
AS THEIR PRACTICE DUMMY,
STRIKING AT MY THROAT
OVER AND OVER AGAIN.
I'VE STILL GOT
A SCAR FORM IT.
TAKU, I HAD NO IDEA.
THIS PILE DRIVER
IS PROBABLY THE RESULT
OF BEING JABBED SO MUCH--
A MANIFESTATION
OF MY FEAR AND ANGER.
ALL I WANTED TO DO
BACK THEN
WAS TO TAKE AN IRON SPIKE
AND SKEWER EACH AND EVERY ONE
OF THOSE BULLIES.
SO, RED KING,
EVEN THOUGH MY AVATAR
IS A CLOSE-RANGE FIGHTER,
IT WAS CREATED
WITH A PIERCING WEAPON
INSTEAD OF A BLADE.
AND THAT'S YOUR ANSWER.
WELL, NOW I UNDERSTAND
YOUR SCARS.
IF YOU CAN
OVERCOME THAT FEAR,
THEN YOU SHOULD
BE ABLE TO MASTER
THE ATTACK ENHANCEMENT
ABILITY...
BECOMING A TRUE
CLOSE-RANGE FIGHTER.
GOT IT.
ALL RIGHT,
THE TEACH AND ME
ARE GONNA START THE
ACTUAL TRAINING NOW.
UH, OKAY. I GUESS
I'LL DIVE OUT, THEN.
I'LL START DOING
A LITTLE INVESTIGATING
TO SEE IF I CAN FIND OUT
HOW DUSK TAKER
KEEPS HIS NAME
OFF THE MATCHING LIST.
HEY, THANK YOU, HARU.
WAIT, I'M GONNA
TEACH YOU
ONE MORE KEY
TO USING
INCARNATION.
THAT RANGE
ENHANCEMENT ABILITY
YOU USED EARLIER--
DID YOU GIVE
A NAME TO IT?
UH, A NAME?
ONE OF THE MOST
IMPORTANT ASPECTS
TO USING
INCARNATE SKILLS
IS HOW SOLIDLY
AND QUICKLY YOU CAN
VISUALIZE IT.
GIVE IT
A NAME FIRST.
THEN USE THAT NAME
AS A TRIGGER.
WELL, DON'T JUST
STAND THERE--THINK!
UM...OKAY.
WELL, HOW ABOUT...
LASER SWORD?
UGH!THAT'S
SO FUCKING LAME!
ALL RIGHT, THEN WHY
DON'T YOU TELL ME WHAT
YOU NAMED YOUR MOVE?
RIGHT. LIKE I'D
DO THAT, DUMBASS.
HUH?
GOOD LUCK, TAKU.
THIS WAY. NOW.
UH...OH, SORRY.
I WAS JUST ABOUT
TO LEAVE ANYWAY.
WE'LL GO OUT THE BACK.
JUST FOLLOW ME...
SILVER CROW.
WHAT?!
YOU KNOW MY NAME?!
THERE'S NO USE
IN RUNNING.
IT'S TOO LATE ANYWAY.
SCARLET RAIN TOLD ME
TO HELP YOU WITH
YOUR INVESTIGATION.
MY NAME
IS BLOOD LEOPARD.
BUT IF YOU WANT,
JUST CALL ME LEOPARD,
NOT BLOOD.
AND IF YOU MUST
SHORTEN THAT,
"PARD", NOT "LEOPA".
WAIT! HOLD ON!
GIVE ME A SEC!
SO THIS ISN'T JUST
SOME ORDINARY CAKE SHOP.
IT'S RED LEGION'S
PROMINENCE, THEIR BASE.
AND THIS WAITRESS...
IS A BURST LINKER?
I GUESS THAT
MAKES SENSE NOW.
SHE DID SEEM KIND OF RUDE
FOR A WAITRESS.
IT'S BEEN TEN SECONDS.
YOU CAN CONTINUE THINKING
WHILE WE'RE MOVING.
(grunting)
JUST SO WE'RE
ON THE SAME PAGE,
I'LL LET YOU KNOW
WHAT MY MASTER
HAS TOLD ME.
THERE'S
A BURST LINKER
WHO DOESN'T APPEAR
ON THE MATCHING LIST,
EVEN WHEN
HE'S CONNECTED TO
THE LOCAL NETWORK.
AND WHAT YOU WOULD
LIKE TO DO
IS FIND OUT HOW HE
DOES IT, CORRECT?
YEAH, THAT'S
PRETTY MUCH IT.
I'VE HEARD A FEW
RUMORS RECENTLY
OF INTRUDER BARGING IN
ON LOCAL NETWORKS.
ANY IDEA WHO'S
BEHIND IT?
THOSE DETAILS
ARE UNCLEAR,
BUT THEY'VE BEEN
BREAKING INTO
THIS ONE NETWORK.
WHICH NETWORK
WOULD THAT BE?
AKIHABARA.
AKIHABARA?
THAT'S THE YELLOW
LEGION'S TERRITORY.
YES, WE'LL
GO THERE NOW.
WHOA!
UHH!HUH?
HURRY UP AND GET ON.
NO WAY. I MEAN,
IT'S JUST THAT I--
START.
(engine starts )
(grunting)
ARE YOU
REALLY GONNA GO
DRESSED LIKE THAT?
CHANGING WOULD BE
A WASTE OF TIME.
WELL, WHAT ABOUT
THE SHOP?
MY SHIFT ENDED AT 5:00.
ARE WE DONE WITH
THE QUESTIONS?
UH, YEAH.
OKAY.
YOU SHOULD HOLD ON.
AAH!AAAAAAH!
AAAAAAH!
DON'T RUN AWAY!
I'VE DEFUSED THEM!
SO JUST FACE THEM HEAD-ON!
THIS WON'T GO ANYWHERE
UNTIL YOU'VE LEARNED
TO CONQUER YOUR FEARS!
OKAY!
AAAAH!
YOU WANT TO JUST
GIVE UP HERE?
NO. ONE MORE TIME...
PLEASE.
THAT'S THE SPIRIT.
HERE IT COMES!
I CAN'T RUN AWAY.
HARU MANAGED
TO DO IT BY HIMSELF.
HE GOT STRONGER.
AND SO CAN I!
UM, WE REALLY KIND OF
STAND OUT RIGHT NOW.
SO?
SO IF WE CHARGE INTO
THE YELLOW LEGION'S
STRONGHOLD LIKE THIS,
WE RISK DRAWING
LOTS OF ATTENTION.
N.P. WE'LL BLEND IN
JUST FINE.
HUH?
OH, I GET IT.
THIS WAY.
UHH!
( video game sound effects )
IS THIS FOR REAL?!
YOU WIN!
OH, YEAH!
WHATEVER.
WOW! I DON'T BELIEVE IT!
THIS IS AN ACTUAL ARCADE!
WITH ALL THE OLD-SCHOOL
ARCADE GAMES AND EVERYTHING!
THIS IS AMAZING!
AWW. I DON'T HAVE
MUCH REAL MONEY--
NOT EVEN 100 YEN.
NOT IMPORTANT.
BUT WAIT--
(grunting)
SO, UM, WHERE
ARE WE GOING?
A DIVE CAFE.
(ding)
THERE'S ONLY ONE CHAIR.
THEY DIDN'T HAVE
A TWO-SEATER BOOTH
AVAILABLE.
WE CAN BOTH
SQUEEZE IN.
YEAH, BUT,
WON'T THAT BE KINDA--
N.P. NESTLING UP
WITH A CHILD
IS NO BIG DEAL
FOR ME.
UHH!
WELL, IT IS
A BIG DEAL FOR ME!
AND CONSIDERING
THE FIRST CONDITION
EVERY BURST LINKER
HAS TO MEET,
SHE AND I
CAN'T BE MORE THAN
THREE YEARS APART!
NOW, ONCE WE DIVE,
LOOK FOR THE GATE
MARKED "AKIHABARA B.G."
AND GO THROUGH
THAT ACCESS POINT.
DO WHAT?
COUNTING DOWN...
FROM ONE...ZERO.
BUT WAIT!
OPEN DIRECT LINK!
HUH? AAH!
I PREPARED THAT
TO HELP YOU BLEND IN.
GOOD FIT.
AAH! AAH!
♪
WHERE ARE WE?
THE AKIHABARA
BATTLE GROUND--
A SACRED PLACE
FOR BURST LINKERS.
WHOA. REALLY?
IS THIS, LIKE,
THE YELLOW LEGION'S
HEADQUARTERS
OR SOMETHING?
NOT AT ALL.
THIS IS THE ONLY
AREA IN AKIHABARA
THAT IS
DEFINITELY NEUTRAL.
FOLLOW ME.
EVENING, MATCHMAKER.
WELL, WELL, WELL.
LOOK WHO'S HERE.
SO HOW LONG
HAS IT BEEN?
JUST ABOUT
EIGHT MONTHS.
DID YOU COME BACK HERE
BECAUSE YOU MISSED
HAVING A SERIOUS FIGHT?
OR HAVE YOU COME TO EARN
A LITTLE POCKET MONEY?
SORRY, BUT I'M AFRAID
WE DIDN'T COME HERE
TONIGHT TO FIGHT...
OR, FOR THAT MATTER,
GAMBLE.
WAIT!YOU CAN
GAMBLE HERE--LIKE
WITH REAL MONEY?!
IT'S NOT MORE THAN
A STUDENT'S LUNCH MONEY.
EVEN IF YOU WIN,
IT'S NOT MUCH.
TRUE! HA HA HA!
LISTEN, I'D LIKE
SOME INFO
ABOUT THE LOCAL
NETWORK INTRUDERS.
YOU KNOW
THE BURST LINKERS
I'M TALKING ABOUT--
THE ONES
WHO DON'T SHOW ON
THE MATCHING LIST.
WHERE'D YOU HEAR
ABOUT THAT?
I'LL BE ASKING
THE QUESTIONS HERE.
YOU DON'T NEED TO PAY ME.
ALL I'M ASKING YOU TO DO
IS TELL ME WHAT YOU KNOW.
IT'S BECOMING A MAJOR PROBLEM
FOR US AS WELL.
REALLY?HOW?
LISTEN UP, KIDDO.
THIS IS SACRED GROUND
FOR FIGHTERS THAT NO ONE--
NOT EVEN THE YELLOW KING
WHO RULES AKIHABARA--CAN TOUCH.
BUT THAT SAID,
ABOUT A WEEK AGO,
SOME RUDE LITTLE TWERP
TURNED UP.
AND WITHOUT EVEN
REGISTERING TO FIGHT,
HE STARTED CHALLENGING
OPPONENTS
THAT WERE OBVIOUS
EASY WINS FOR HIM.
AND ALTHOUGH IT SAID
HE WAS CONNECTED
TO THE LOCAL NETWORK,
HIS NAME DIDN'T SHOW UP
ANYWHERE ON THE MATCHING LIST.
IF WE DON'T FIGURE OUT
A WAY TO STOP THIS GUY,
HE COULD THREATEN
THE WHOLE EXISTENCE
OF AKIHABARA B.G.
SO THEN...
THIS BURST LINKER
WHO DOESN'T APPEAR
ON THE MATCHING LIST--
DO YOU KNOW HIS NAME?
IT'S RUST JIGSAW.
♪
(singing in Japanese )
NEXT STAGE--
DETERMINATION.
HARUYUKI FINALLY
UNCOVERS THE TRUTH.
EVERYTHING IS SET IN PLACE
IN PREPARATION
FOR THE FINAL STAGE.