(doorbell rings )
TAKU! UH--
CHI-CHIYU.
(singing in Japanese )
NOMI TOLD ME
TO COME HERE.
HE SAID I SHOULD
MEET YOU GUYS
AND TELL YOU I PLAN
ON BETRAYING HIM
AS A WAY TO REGAIN
YOUR TRUST.
AND THEN I WAS TO ASK
IF I COULD COME TO
THE UNLIMITED FIELD
WITH YOU,
WHERE I COULD HEAL HIM
OVER AND OVER AGAIN.
BUT THEN I FIGURED,
NO MATTER WHAT I SAID
TO YOU TWO,
YOU WOULDN'T
BELIEVE ME.
SO I DECIDED
THE BEST THING
FOR ME TO DO
WAS JUST
TELL THE TRUTH
AND BEG YOU GUYS.
HUH?BEG FOR WHAT?
BEG YOU GUYS...
TO TAKE ME WITH YOU!
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND,
BUT I HAVE TO
BE THERE!
IF YOU SAY NO,
I WON'T BLAME YOU.
BUT THAT STILL
WON'T STOP ME.
I'LL JUST GO TO
THE OTHER SIDE
AND WAIT FOR YOU...
NO MATTER
HOW LONG IT TAKES--
MONTHS, YEARS!
YOU CAN'T...BE SERIOUS.
WHAT'S GOTTEN INTO YOU?
YOU'RE THE ONE
WHO USED TO SAY THAT
BRAIN BURST WAS JUST A GAME.
SO WHY GO
TO SUCH EXTREMES NOW?
OKAY, THEN.
WE'LL GO TOGETHER.
TAKU?
LISTEN,
REMEMBER WHAT I DID
SIX MONTHS AGO?
I ATTACKED OUR MASTER.
BUT THEN YOU FORGAVE ME.
YOU BELIEVED IN ME,
AND I WILL NEVER
FORGET THAT MOMENT.
SO I'M CHOOSING
TO BELIEVE IN CHI, TOO.
THANK YOU, TAKKUN.
OKAY, WE'LL GO--
ALL THREE OF US.
Computerizedvoice:
MEET AT KOENJI STATION.
TIME--20:05.
SENDING MAIL.
CHANGED TO ITSUKAICHI STREET.
TIME--20:07:30.
SENDING MAIL.
CHANGED TO KOENJI OVERPASS.
TIME--20:10.
SENDING MAIL.
CHANGED TO
HIGASHI KOENJI--
CHANGED--JYUNJYOU DISTRICT.
CHANGED TO STATION
TRAFFIC CIRCLE.
MEET AT UMESATO
JUNIOR HIGH SCHOOL.
TIME--NOW.
ALL RIGHT, WE'LL DIVE
IN ONE MINUTE.
LET'S DO IT.
SEND MAIL?
SENPAI...I KNOW
THAT IF I LOSE,
YOU'RE GONNA BE
REALLY ANGRY AT FIRST,
AND THEN BE REALLY SAD.
BUT PLEASE, YOU HAVE
TO UNDERSTAND--
I MUST DO THIS...
SO THAT I CAN SOMEDAY
BECOME YOUR KNIGHT!
SENDING MAIL.
HERE GOES!
All: UNLIMITED BURST!
IT DOESN'T LOOK
LIKE ANYONE'S HERE.
NOMI'S NOT HERE YET,
EITHER.
MAYBE HE DOVE JUST
A SPLIT-SECOND LATER.
OKAY, IF HE DOESN'T
TURN UP IN THE NEXT
FIVE MINUTES,
WE'LL LEAVE FROM
THE NEAREST PORTAL.
WAIT A SEC!
NOMI!
READY?
♪
I KNOW I SAID YOU COULD
CHANGE THE START TIME
AND VENUE
AS MUCH AS YOU WANTED,
BUT YOU REALLY WENT
A BIT OVERBOARD,
DON'T YOU THINK?
I'VE LEARNED THAT
WHEN IT COMES TO
DEALING WITH YOU,
THERE'S NO SUCH THING
AS BEING TOO CAREFUL.
RIGHT, WHATEVER.
THIS HERE IS
THE SUDDEN-DEATH DUEL CARD.
THIS IS THE ITEM
THAT WILL TRANSFER
ALL OUR POINTS ONTO...
I LOOKED UP THE RULES
FOR THAT CARD,
ONCE YOU ACTUALLY
GO AND ACTIVATE IT.
EXACTLY.
THE DUEL DOESN'T END
UNTIL SOMEONE
FINALLY DIES.
ANY OF US WHO MEET THAT FATE
WILL LOSE ALL THEIR POINTS
AND THEIR APPLICATION
OF BRAIN BURST WILL
AUTOMATICALLY UNINSTALL.
FINE! BRING IT!
(bleeps)
(bleeping )
THIS IS JUST LIKE
A DUEL BETWEEN
LEVEL-9 KINGS.
A SUDDEN-DEATH MATCH
WITH ALL YOUR POINTS
AT RISK.
SENPAI...EVERY DAY,
THIS IS THE SORT OF
PRESSURE YOU HAVE TO
LIVE WITH, ISN'T IT?
YOU'RE NOT GONNA USE
YOUR WINGS STRAIGHT AWAY?
FINE!
(grunting)
A STAGE TRAP?
BUT THIS IS
THE MOONLIGHT STAGE!
THERE AREN'T TRAPS HERE!
THEN IT IS AN AMBUSH?
NO WAY.
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
STATIC PRESSURE.
(grunting)
AAH!
HOW DID YOU PULL OFF
AN AMBUSH?
WITH ALL THE CHANGES
WE MADE TO THE
STARTING VENUE,
IT SHOULD'VE BEEN
IMPOSSIBLE FOR YOU
TO NAIL
A SPECIFIC TIME.
I HAVE TO ADMIT--
YOU GUYS--
YOU SIMPLY NEVER FAIL
TO AMUSE ME.
I'VE LEARNED THERE'S
NO SUCH THING AS
BEING TOO CAREFUL
WHEN IT COMES
TO DEALING WITH YOU.
WELL, APPARENTLY,
YOU DIDN'T LEARN THAT
WELL ENOUGH, DID YOU?
YEAH, BUT THERE'S NO WAY
YOU COULD'VE BEEN HERE
THIS WHOLE TIME.
THAT WOULD'VE BEEN,
LIKE, MONTHS ON END.
NO, OF COURSE HE WASN'T.
YOU KNOW, MAYUZUMI SENPAI,
SOMETIMES YOU'RE HILARIOUS.
I ASSUME YOUR LITTLE FRIEND
HAS TOLD YOU ABOUT
THE CHIP I HAVE?
THEY CALL IT THE B.I.C.--
THE BRAIN IMPLANT CHIP.
THERE'S A WAY
TO PROGRAM THE CHIP
SO THAT ITS TERMINAL REACHES
DEEP INTO THE RECESSES
OF YOUR BRAIN.
OF COURSE, THIS IS
VERY DANGEROUS,
AND A NORMAL PERSON
WOULD NEVER DO IT.
BUT THAT GUY UP THERE
LIKES TO LIVE ON THE EDGE.
HIS TERMINAL REACHES INTO
THE REGION OF HIS BRAIN
THAT CONTROLS
HIS INTERNAL CLOCK.
IN REAL-WORLD TIME,
HE DOVE INTO THIS FIELD
AT 8:00 THIS EVENING.
BUT DON'T BE FOOLED.
THAT DOESN'T MEAN
HE'S BEEN WAITING HERE
FOR MONTHS ON END.
WITH THE USE
OF HIS B.I.C.,
HE HAS COMPLETE CONTROL
OVER HIS ACCELERATION.
HE'S THE ONLY ONE
IN THE ACCELERATED WORLD
WHO CAN DECELERATE.
WHAT? HE CAN--
DECELERATE?
(sighs)
YOU KNOW, MR. TAKER,
IS IT POSSIBLE THAT
YOUR GENERAL CHATTINESS
IS WHAT ALLOWED
THIS SITUATION TO ARISE?
IN MY OPINION, NO.
DID YOU SEE THE LOOK OF
SURPRISE ON THEIR FACES?
PRETTY GREAT, RIGHT?
I BET THEY'VE EVEN LOST
THEIR WILL TO FIGHT.
I WOULDN'T BE SO SURE.
THE THIN ONE THERE
IS PUTTING UP QUITE A FIGHT.
THAT'S JUST BECAUSE
HE'S A METAL COLOR.
GIVE ME THREE MINUTES,
AND I'LL TAKE CARE
OF THE BLUE ONE.
ACTUALLY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
30 SECONDS SHOULD DO IT.
DON'T WORRY.
I HAVE EVERY INTENTION
OF EARNING MY REWARD.
30 SECONDS?
YOU THINK IT'S
GONNA BE THAT EASY?
(gasps)
WHERE'S MY VOICE?!
I FORGOT TO TELL YOU--
MY MOVE LOCKS DOWN
YOUR VOICE
AS WELL AS YOUR MOVEMENT.
THAT MEANS YOUR VOICE COMMAND
ISN'T GONNA WORK.
SO BE A GOOD BOY
AND JUST WATCH.
(laughs)
WELL, NOW...
I SEE THAT YOU'VE
COME PREPARED.
THIS SHOULD AT LEAST
MAKE THINGS A LITTLE
MORE INTERESTING.
TELL ME--DO YOU HAVE
A NAME FOR THAT MOVE?
UGH. DO I LOOK
LIKE THE TYPE
WHO NAMES STUFF
LIKE SOME STUPID GAMER?
DIDN'T THINK SO.
I JUST LIKE TO FIND OUT
AS MUCH AS I CAN
ABOUT MY OPPONENT
BEFORE I TEACH THEM
A LESSON THEY'LL
NEVER FORGET.
HEH.
AAAAH!
CYAN...
BLADE!
WELL, LOOK AT YOU.
HEH!I GET IT NOW.
YOUR LOSS TO ME MUST'VE
REALLY STUNK BADLY...
IF IT MOTIVATED YOU
TO INCARNATE
A RIDICULOUS SWORD
LIKE THAT.
BUT FINE.
IF IT'S A SWORDFIGHT
YOU WANT,
THEN IT'S A SWORDFIGHT
YOU'LL GET.
TAKU, STAY STRONG!
YOU'VE GOTTA BELIEVE
IN YOURSELF!
(screaming)
WELL, NOW,
I'M MILDLY IMPRESSED.
YOU SHOULDN'T BE.
AS LONG AS WE'RE
FIGHTING FAIRLY,
I'LL ALWAYS BE
STRONGER THAN YOU!
HA HA HA!
YOU CAN ACT TOUGH,
BUT IT'S CLEARLY
JUST A FRONT.
I CAN SEE YOU HAVE
ONE FATAL FLAW!
(grunting)
AAH!
HA HA!
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
AREN'T YOU GONNA
AT LEAST TRY
AND PROTECT YOUR NECK,
SENPAI?
DAMN IT.
I CAN'T LOST TO HIM.
DESPITE EVERYTHING
THAT HAPPENED, I NEVER QUIT.
I NEVER GAVE UP
MY SHINAI SWORD.
ALL RIGHT, YOUR CHOICE.
IF YOU REALLY WANT ME
TO SLASH A GAPING HOLE
IN YOUR WINDPIPE SO BADLY,
THEN I GUESS
THE ONLY CHOICE I HAVE
IS TO FINISH YOU!
(grunting)
YOU'RE DONE NOW.
DEMONIC COMMANDEER!
AAAH!
UHH!
YOU KNOW WHAT
YOUR PROBLEM IS?
YOU'RE TOO GREEDY.
SOMETHING ALWAYS
STRUCK ME AS ODD--
THE FACT THAT YOU
DIDN'T JUST STEAL
LIME BELL'S
HEALING ABILITY.
BUT THE REASON
FOR THAT...
IS BECAUSE
YOU'RE MAXED OUT.
THERE'S A LIMIT
TO THE NUMBER OF
ABILITIES
YOUR DEMONIC
COMMANDEER CAN STEAL.
AREN'T THERE?
THE PERSON WHO
TAUGHT ME INCARNATION
TAUGHT ME
SOMETHING ELSE.
CYAN PILE'S
TRUE CAPABILITIES
LIE ENTIRELY WITHIN
ITS PILE DRIVER.
YOU PROBABLY THOUGHT
IT WAS SOMETHING
YOU COULD EASILY
TAKE OUT,
BUT YOU WERE
SADLY MISTAKEN.
I SEE. SO THEN,
THAT LITTLE STICK OF YOURS
MUST'VE BEEN MADE FROM
SOME PARTICULARLY PAINFUL
AND PATHETIC MEMORIES.
MY MEMORIES REALLY
AREN'T ALL THAT BAD,
NOT WHEN YOU COMPARE IT
TO THE SCARS
THAT PRODUCE AN AVATAR
LIKE YOURS, DUSK TAKER.
YOU STEAL THINGS
BECAUSE INSIDE YOU,
THERE'S NOTHING LEFT.
BUT I THINK THAT NOW
YOU MAY HAVE FINALLY
REALIZED
NO MATTER
WHAT YOU TAKE--
POWERS, FRIENDSHIP,
LOVE, EVEN HOPE--
IT'S ALL POINTLESS...
BECAUSE NOT ONE
OF THOSE THINGS
WILL EVER TRULY
BELONG TO YOU!
(laughing)
NOTHING LEFT INSIDE?
THAT ISN'T ME.
THAT'S HIM.
HE WAS TWICE MY SIZE,
WITH A MATCHING TEMPER,
AND EVERY DAY, HE TOOK
MY TOYS AND MY MONEY.
HE EVEN MANAGED
TO TAKE AWAY
THE ONLY GIRL
I EVER MADE FRIENDS WITH!
AND THAT BASTARD
WAS MY OLDER BROTHER!
YOU LOOKED HIM UP,
DIDN'T YOU?
WELL, NOW YOU KNOW.
MY GUARDIAN WAS MY BROTHER.
HE INSTALLED BRAIN BURST
IN MY NEURO-LINKER
AND THEN FORCED ME
TO EARN POINTS FOR HIM.
AND I DID. I WORKED
LIKE A SLAVE FOR HIM.
IF I DIDN'T DO IT,
HE'D BEAT ME TO A PULP
IN THE REAL WORLD.
HE TOOK EVERYTHING
FROM ME.
NO MATTER WHAT I DID,
IT WAS NEVER ENOUGH!
HE EVEN TOOK AWAY
MY SELF-RESPECT.
BUT IT MADE REVENGE
EVEN SWEETER.
LITTLE BY LITTLE,
I BUILT UP MY POINTS.
IT TOOK FOREVER,
BUT EVENTUALLY MY AVATAR
GOT ITS FIRST
SPECIAL MOVE.
I GOT MY HANDS
ON A B.I.C.,
FIGURED OUT
THE INCARNATE SYSTEM
AND THEN TOOK BACK
EVERYTHING MY BROTHER
HAD STOLEN FROM ME.
I AMBUSHED HIM
IN THE UNLIMITED FIELD,
TOOK HIS ABILITIES,
AND THEN USED INCARNATION
TO ANNIHILATE HIM.
EACH TIME HE REVIVED,
I KILLED HIM AGAIN.
I KEPT ON GOING!
I KILLED HIM OVER
AND OVER AGAIN!
RIGHT BEFORE I WAS
GONNA FINISH HIM FOR GOOD
AND TAKE HIS
BRAIN BURST FOREVER,
I HEARD HIM BAWL
LIKE A BABY.
IT WAS HYSTERICAL.
YOU KNOW, JUST THINKING
ABOUT THAT MOMENT NOW
STILL MAKES ME LAUGH.
(laughing)
HE'S THE ONE WHO TRULY
HAS NOTHING LEFT!
HE LOST BRAIN BURST
AND THE ABILITY
TO ACCELERATE.
I CAN'T THINK OF A MORE
MISERABLE LIFE THAN HIS.
I'M DIFFERENT.
I'M GONNA TAKE EVERYTHING,
EVEN THESE DELUSIONS
OF FRIENDSHIP
AND UNBREAKABLE BONDS
YOU ALL BELIEVE IN.
I'M TAKING
EVERY LAST BIT OF IT!
AAAAH!
CHI!
NOMI! LIME BELL
ISN'T PART OF THIS
SUDDEN-DEATH MATCH.
YOU CAN'T TAKE HER
AS A HOSTAGE!
OH, BUT I BEG
TO DIFFER.
AAAAH!
YOU BASTARD!
CAREFUL THERE.
I REALLY WOULDN'T
TALK TO ME LIKE THAT
IF I WERE YOU.
AW, POOR GIRL.
SHE DIVES INTO
THE UNLIMITED FIELD
FOR THE FIRST TIME,
WHERE THE PAIN
IS DOUBLED,
AND LOOK WHAT SHE
HAS TO ENDURE.
AAAAH!
STOP IT!
UNLESS YOU HAVE
A LITTLE ATTITUDE ADJUSTMENT,
THIS IS GONNA KEEP ON GOING.
STOP IT!
PLEASE!
LET HER GO.
JUST QUIT HURTING CHI.
AAAH!
THIS IS WHAT YOU GET
FOR BELIEVING
IN YOUR FRIENDS.
ACTUALLY, IT'S BECAUSE
YOU PRETEND
TO BELIEVE
IN YOUR FRIENDS
THAT YOU WILL NOW
LOSE EVERYTHING!
TAKU!
ADMIT IT--IF YOU REALLY
TRUSTED EACH OTHER,
YOU COULD'VE
FINISHED ME OFF
ALONG WITH HER!
YOU'RE WRONG.
YOU'RE WRONG!
YOU DON'T KNOW ANYTHING!
YOU HAVE NO IDEA HOW MUCH
TAKU CARES ABOUT CHIYU.
THERE'S NO WAY YOU COULD!
DAMN IT,
WHY CAN'T I MOVE? WHY?!
I HAVE TO GO HELP THEM!
(screaming)
IS THIS WHERE
IT'S ALL GONNA END?
MINE AND TAKU'S TIME
AS A BURST LINKER--
IS IT REALLY OVER NOW?
IS THIS ZERO FILL?
IT HAS TO BE.
WHEN YOU LOSE
ALL SENSE OF WILL,
WHEN THE FLAME IN YOUR HEART
GOES DARK,
YOUR AVATAR
BECAUSE NOTHING MORE
THAN A COLD LUMP.
THIS IS IT.
THIS IS THE END.
Silver Crow:
ARE YOU POSITIVE?
I CAN'T DO THIS.
IS THAT YOUR ANSWER,
HARUYUKI ARITA?
BUT...I CAN'T EVEN
MOVE A FINGER.
SO YOU'RE GOING
TO QUIT?
JUST LIKE THAT? AFTER
ALL YOU'VE ACCOMPLISHED
THROUGH BRAIN BURST?
WHAT?
YOU'RE JUST
GOING TO GIVE UP?
SENPAI?
HOW WOULD YOU LIKE TO
ACCELERATE EVEN FURTHER...
YOUNG MAN?
(grunting)
(screaming)
HUH?
(screamingcontinues)
(gasps)
YOU SERIOUSLY SHOULDN'T
SURPRISE ME LIKE THAT.
LETTING YOUR PREY ESCAPE--
YOU'RE STARTING
TO SLACK OFF.
THAT'S UNCALLED FOR.
I WAS GIVING IT MY ALL.
YOU SHOULD BE COMMENDING
THAT BOY INSTEAD.
IT LOOKS LIKE,
IN THE END,
THIS FAITH YOU HAVE
IN FRIENDSHIP WAS
NEVER OF ANY USE.
AND NOW IT'S TIME TO
SAY GOOD-BYE, CYAN PILE!
TAKU!
WHAT?NO!
(allgasping)
WHAT?NO WAY.
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
THIS CAN'T BE HAPPENING!
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
IT'S THE BLACK KING--
BLACK LOTUS.
HOW THE HELL WERE YOU
EVEN ABLE TO GET HERE?
SO YOU'RE DUSK TAKER?
CLEARLY YOU'VE STILL
GOT A LOT TO LEARN.
THERE ARE WAYS TO FIGHT
IN THE ACCELERATED WORLD
THAT YOU HAVEN'T
EVEN DREAMT OF.
SENPAI.
(neighs)
LET ME REMIND YOU
OF SOMETHING, DUSK TAKER.
UNLIKE NORMAL BATTLEFIELDS
YOU'RE FAMILIAR WITH,
THE UNLIMITED NEUTRAL FIELD
LITERALLY HAS NO LIMITS.
THEREFORE, IN THIS WORLD,
BOTH TOKYO AND OKINAWA
ARE LINKED...
WHICH MEANS I COULD SIMPLY
DIVE INTO THIS FIELD
FROM OKINAWA
AND FLY HERE TO TOKYO.
FIRST, I TAMED THAT
LEGEND-CLASS ENEMY,
AND THEN I SPENT 15 HOURS
GETTING ALL THE WAY HERE.
BUT IN THE REAL WORLD,
THAT ALL TRANSPIRED
IN LESS THAN ONE MINUTE.
YOU WHAT?
THAT IS INSANE!
WHAT KIND OF PERSON
WOULD EVEN THINK OF DOING
SUCH A BIZARRE THING?
WHY WOULD YOU
EVEN BOTHER?!
YOU THERE--
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
HMM?
I AM BLACK VICE,
VICE PRESIDENT
OF THE ACCELERATION
RESEARCH SOCIETY.
IT'S NICE TO FINALLY
MEET YOU, BLACK KING.
SO THIS IS A SOCIETY,
NOT A LEGION?
HAVE YOU EVER HEARD
OF A BURST LINKER
CALLED SULFUR POT?
UH, I THINK THOSE
MIGHT'VE BEEN HIS REINS.
HEH. NOW I HAVE
ANOTHER REASON TO
DESTROY YOU TWO.
FOR EVERY BIT OF PAIN
YOU'VE CAUSED MY
LEGION MEMBERS,
I'M GOING TO RETURN
YOU THE SAME AMOUNT
AND DOUBLE IT.
ACTUALLY,
MAKE THAT TRIPLE!
OH. THAT SOUND SCARY.
LOOK OUT!
HMM?
UNFORTUNATELY FOR YOU,
PHYSICAL RESTRAINTS
DON'T WORK ON ME.
HMM.
VORPAL STRIKE!
LAYERED ARMOR.
GET UP, SILVER CROW!
I'LL DEAL WITH THIS ONE.
YOU DEAL WITH YOUR ENEMY.
DEFEAT DUSK TAKER!
♪
(singing in Japanese )
NEXT STAGE--
REINCARNATION.
BELIEVE IN YOUR FRIENDS,
BELIEVE IN YOURSELF.
THE TIME FOR
YOUR REINCARNATION IS NOW.