( panting )
( gun cocks )
( gun fires )
( screams )
( grunting )
( wailing )
NOT DONE YET.
START!
I HAVE TO GET BETTER.
I HAVE TO BE STRONGER
AND FASTER.
I HAVE TO DO IT FOR HER.
SO THAT I CAN KEEP UP
AS HER PARTNER.
Senpai:
LISTEN CAREFULLY, HARUYUKI.
THE RIGHT TO CONTROL
A TERRITORY IS DECIDED
EVERY SATURDAY NIGHT WITH
A TURF WAR BETWEEN THE LEGIONS.
THE LEGIONS GO AGAINST EACH
OTHER WITH THE SAME NUMBER
OF FIGHTERS,
REGARDLESS OF THEIR LEVEL.
TO WIN, THEY MUST MAINTAIN
A WINNING PERCENTAGE
OF 50% OR HIGHER.
GO ON,
WE CAN TAKE CARE OF THIS.
WE’RE COUNTING ON YOU, HARU.
TAKE ’EM OUT WITH
YOUR USUAL ATTACK!
YOU GOT IT!
FIRST THING I’LL DO
IS TAKE OUT
THE ENEMIES FOOTHOLD.
THEN I’LL SWOOP DOWN FROM
THE SKY AND FINISH ’EM OFF!
( gasps )
AHH!
( chuckles )
DAMN IT!
THAT MOVES GETTIN’ A LITTLE OLD,
DON’T YA THINK?
ONCE PEOPLE HAVE SEEN IT
A FEW TIMES AND FIGURE OUT
WHAT IT IS,
IT MAKES YOU AN EASY TARGET.
( gasps )
( screams )
Girl: WHAT WAS THAT SCREAM
ALL ABOUT?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
♪
( bells chiming )
SO, THAT’S WHY YOU
BUILT THIS APP?
TO DO THIS
EXTREME TRAINING?
LOOK, WHEN I FIRST
STARTED FLYING
I WAS TOTALLY UNBEATABLE.
BUT EVER SINCE
I’VE MOVED UP
TO LEVEL 4
I’VE BEEN
STUCK IN A RUT.
WE HAVEN’T BEEN ABLE
TO EXPAND THE TERRITORY
FOR NEGA NEBULOUS
ONE SINGLE BIT.
YEAH, BUT USING
AN ILLEGAL PATCH LIKE THAT
AND PUSHING YOUR PAIN TOLERANCE
WAY BEYOND ITS NORMAL LIMITS,
IT’S KINDA CRAZY.
YEAH, BUT IF YOU TAKE
AWAY MY FLYING ABILITY,
THEN ALL YOU’RE LEFT WITH
IS A FRAGILE AVATAR
WHO’S ONLY GOOD
AT CLOSE-RANGE COMBAT!
SO I HAVE TO DO THIS.
I HAVE TO FIND A WAY
TO DODGE
ANTI-AIRCRAFT FIRE!
LOOK, I KNOW YOU’LL GET THERE,
JUST DON’T RUSH IT.
I’M SURE OUR MASTER SAID
THE SAME THING TOO, RIGHT?
THIS IS SO BORING!
AFTER ALL THAT’S HAPPENED,
WE CAN FINALLY WALK
HOME TOGETHER LIKE WE USED TO,
AND ALL YOU GUYS TALK
ABOUT’S THAT STUPID GAME.
I’M SORRY, CHI.
BUY ME SOME ENJIYA ICE CREAM
AND PROVE IT.
I WANT EVERY JUMBO
PARFAIT ON THEIR MENU!
MMM...ICE CREAM? AGAIN?
Chiyuri: PLUS A TIRAMISU
DORAYAKI.
Taku:
OKAY.
Haru:
HE’S RIGHT.
EVEN SO...
I HAVE TO TRY.
I WANT TO GET STRONGER.
Girl:
WELCOME HOME, BROTHER.
YEAH, THANKS.
WAIT, WHAT?
( giggles )
SHE AN ANGEL?
IS THIS SOME KIND
OF HEAVENLY VISION?
SORRY, I GOTTA GET
BACK IN THE KITCHEN.
I’M BAKING SOME
COOKIES RIGHT NOW.
( humming )
SHE LOOKS WAY TOO REAL.
THIS CAN’T BE SOME
KIND OF FANTASY
OR DELUSION.
WHICH CAN ONLY MEAN...
THAT SOMEONE’S GONE AND TAMPERED
WITH MY NEURO-LINKER.
AND THEY BUILT SOME SORT
OF VISUAL ILLUSION TRAP.
WHO ARE YOU?
BECAUSE THERE’S NO WAY
MY LITTLE SISTER
WOULD EVER BE THIS CUTE!
OW! WHY ARE YOU
DOING THIS TO ME?
( screams )
NO WAY! SHE EVEN FEELS
LIKE SHE’S A REAL PERSON!
( grunts )
YOU’RE STILL HERE.
OF COURSE
I’M STILL HERE, SILLY.
DON’T YOU REMEMBER ME?
I’M TOMOKO SAITO
FROM NAKANO.
SAITO FROM NAKANO?
YEP THAT’S ME,
I’M NOW IN THE 5TH GRADE.
FROM WHAT I WAS TOLD
YOU AND ME ARE
LIKE SECOND COUSINS
OR SOMETHING.
SORRY I KINDA BARGED IN,
BUT IT’S REALLY
NICE TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
Woman: ONE OF OUR RELATIVES
WILL BE STAYING WITH US
FOR TWO OR THREE DAYS.
SOMETHING TO DO WITH
A SUDDEN BUSINESS TRIP.
AND I’M OFF TO SHANGHAI TODAY.
SO, PLEASE TAKE CARE
OF HER FOR ME, OKAY?
( sighs )
I HOPE YOU DON’T MIND
THAT I USED YOUR KITCHEN
WITHOUT ASKING,
BUT I THOUGHT YOU
MIGHT BE HUNGRY,
SO, I WENT AND
WHIPPED UP A BATCH
OF THESE FOR YOU.
THANKS.
THAT WAS NICE.
GUESS I’LL TRY ONE.
HEY, HOW DID YOU MANAGE
TO GET A KEY?
WHEN I ASKED YOUR MOM
IF I COULD STAY,
SHE ISSUED ME
AN INSTANCE KEY.
HMMM...
THESE ARE GREAT!
WOW! ARE THEY REALLY?
I’M SO GLAD.
HOLD ON, JUST DON’T MOVE.
( giggles )
ALL RIGHT. SO, UM...
W-WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
PLAY SOME KIND
OF GAME MAYBE?
TO BE HONEST, I REALLY DON’T
PLAY A WHOLE LOT OF GAMES.
I ACTUALLY DON’T LIKE
THE NEURO-LINKER ALL THAT MUCH.
THEN HOW ABOUT AN
OLD-FASHIONED 2-D MOVIE?
NO THANKS. I’D RATHER
THE TWO OF JUST
TALKED INSTEAD.
SO, WHAT’S IT LIKE BEING
IN JUNIOR HIGH SCHOOL?
I WANNA HEAR
ALL ABOUT IT!
YA’ KNOW, I GOTTA SAY,
YOU’RE A REALLY FUNNY PERSON!
IF I HAD A KID SISTER,
I WONDER IF THIS
IS WHAT IT
WOULD BE LIKE.
SO WAIT, THAT MEANS WE’LL
BE LIVING UNDER THE SAME ROOF
FOR THREE DAYS UNTIL MOM
COMES BACK FROM HER TRIP.
NO WAY, GET REAL!
THIS JUST SEEMS WAY TOO PERFECT.
IS THIS GIRL ACTUALLY
MY SECOND COUSIN?
THE SAITOS FROM NAKANO.
NOTHIN’.
NOT A SINGLE PHOTO
OF HER ANYWHERE.
LET ME CHECK THIS OUT.
Tomoko:
UM, ’SCUSE ME.
HUH?
AH, CRAP!
WOULD YOU MIND IF I CAME
IN THERE AND JOINED YOU?
AH, NO WAY!
COME ON. YOU’VE BEEN
IN THERE FOR LIKE EVER NOW.
I’M TIRED OF HAVING
TO WAIT SO LONG.
OKAY. I’LL GET OUT NOW.
I’M SORRY THAT YOU HAD TO WAIT.
BUT JUST GIVE ME A MINUTE!
LOOK, WE’RE COUSINS.
IT’S REALLY NOT A BIG DEAL.
I DON’T KNOW.
I KINDA THINK THAT IT IS
A BIG DEAL.
HUH?
BUT PLEASE DON’T STARE
AT ME LIKE THAT
IT MAKES ME UNCOMFORTABLE.
TOMOKO?
YEP, THAT’S ME.
WHAT IS IT?
OKAY, DROP THE ACT.
YOU’RE A NEW BURST
LINKER, AREN’T YOU?
HUH?
LOOK, YOU’VE GOT
TAN MARKS ON YOUR NECK.
AND PLUS I JUST CAME
ACROSS A FEW OF
THE PHOTOS MY GRANDPA
HAD POSTED ON
HIS HOME SERVER.
I’VE GOTTA ADMIT THOUGH...
YOU’RE LIKE, TEN TIMES
CUTER THAN THE REAL ONE.
( sighs )
I CAN’T BELIEVE YOU DID
ALL THAT DIGGING AROUND.
YOU’RE WAY TOO SUSPICIOUS,
YA KNOW THAT?
SO I GUESS YOU FORGED
THAT MAIL TO MY MOM,
ASKING TO STAY HERE
WHILE YOU’RE PARENTS
ARE OUT OF TOWN.
SO WHAT’S UP?
WHAT ARE YOU PLANNING?
ARE YOU THINKING
YOU’D TRY AND USE ME
TO HACK MY LEGION MASTER?
DO WHAT?
WHAT’RE YOU BABBLING ABOUT?
HEY, I DON’T BLAME YOU,
OKAY?
I CAN UNDERSTAND WHY YOU
WOULDN’T WANT TO TAKE ON
THE BLACK KING DIRECTLY.
IT WOULD BE PRETTY HARD
TO TAKE OUT BLACK LOTUS
IN A FAIR FIGHT.
BUT SNEAKING
AROUND LIKE THIS?
GO ON.
WHAT WERE YOU SAYIN’?
JUST WHO DO YOU THINK
I CAN’T TAKE OUT
IN A FAIR FIGHT?
WELL, I MEANT, IT’S JUST...
AFTER ALL YOU’RE--
ENOUGH OF THIS CRAP.
YOU LISTEN TO WHAT I HAVE
TO SAY AND YOU LISTEN GOOD.
YOU’VE JUST INSULTED ME,
SCARLET RAIN,
AND BECAUSE OF THAT
I’M GONNA MAKE YOU PAY!
( screaming )
WATCH OUT!
( grunting )
( screaming )
YOU’RE SO DEAD.
SCARLET, HUH?
SO THAT MUST MEAN
SHE’S A BURST LINKER
FROM THE RED LEGION.
HARUYUKI?
TO WHAT DO I OWE THE PLEASURE
OF RECEIVING THIS CALL?
SORRY, I KNOW IT’S LATE.
BUT I’VE GOT A QUESTION
I REALLY NEED TO ASK YOU.
WELL, THEN, WHAT IS IT?
HAVE YOU HEARD OF
A BURST LINKER THAT
GOES BY THE NAME
SCARLET RAIN?
DID I SAY
SOMETHING WRONG?
OH, RIGHT. I’VE ONLY MENTIONED
THEIR NICKNAMES TO YOU
IN THE PAST,
NOT THEIR ACTUAL NAMES.
BUT YOU KNOW, YOU SHOULD
REALLY DO YOUR HOMEWORK.
YES, I KNOW
WHO SCARLET RAIN IS.
IT’S THE NAME OF
THE SECOND RED KING.
WHAT?
( panting )
HOLD ON. SO YOU’RE
THE RED KING?
BURST LINK!
UM, ARE YOU SERIOUSLY
THE RED KING?
AH, CRAP.
NO, I SHOULDN’T
RUN FROM THIS.
RED SPECIALIZES
IN LONG-RANGE COMBAT.
IF I WERE TO RUN AWAY RIGHT NOW
IT WOULD BE COMPLETE SUICIDE!
SO, NOT GONNA RUN ARE YA?
HOW VERY BRAVE!
BUT HAVE YOU FORGOTTEN
WHAT I SAID?
ABOUT WHAT?
ABOUT THE FACT THAT I AM SO
GONNA KILL YOU RIGHT NOW,
YA FUCKIN’ PERVERT!
THAT WAS REALLY JUST
AN UNAVOIDABLE ACCIDENT!
AND DON’T FORGET,
YOU’RE THE ONE WHO TRIED
TO GET INTO MY BATH!
NOT THE OTHER WAY AROUND!
FROM MY EXPERIENCE,
HEAVILY-ARMED OPPONENTS
LIKE HER ALWAYS HAVE
A VULNERABLE SPOT.
AND THAT’S THEIR BACK!
I’LL AIM FOR THE JOINTS
WHERE THE ARMOR IS THINNEST!
AH, THAT’S HOT!
YEAH, I FORGOT.
I’M SILVER CROW!
A METAL COLOR!
FLAMES DON’T AFFECT ME!
HA! YOU ARE SO GOIN’ DOWN!
IN YOUR DREAMS, ROOKIE!
( laughs )
AH!
W-WAIT! H-HOLD ON!
YOU’RE SHOOTING AT ME INSIDE
MY OWN APARTMENT BUILDING!
ARE YOU CRAZY!
( screaming )
WHOA, SHE’S DESTROYED HERSELF
ALONG WITH THE BUILDING.
NO MATTER HOW TANK-LIKE
HER AVATAR IS,
THERE’S NO WAY IT
COULD SURVIVE THAT--
Scarlet Rain:
HEAT BLAST SATURATION!
Haru:
HOLY CRAP!
OH, HE’S FLYING, PERFECT.
I’VE BEEN WAITING FOR A CHANCE
TO TRY OUT
MY ANTI-AIRCRAFT FIRE.
YEAH WELL, IF I WERE YOU,
I’D KEEP IN MIND THAT IT’S
ALWAYS A SINGLE ROBOT WHO TAKES
DOWN THE GIANT BATTLESHIP!
EXCEPT FOR WHEN THE PERSON
PILOTING THAT ROBOT
IS SOME PATHETIC PERVERT.
YA DUMBASS!
HAILSTORM DOMINATION!
HERE GOES NOTHING!
I THINK I CAN SEE ’EM!
SILVER CROW’S
ALL OR NOTHING KICK!
( screaming )
LOOKS LIKE I WIN.
GIVE UP?
YEAH, I SURRENDER.
SO, WILL YOU LISTEN
TO MY REQUEST NOW?
WHAT REQUEST?
I WANT TO MEET YOUR LEGION
MASTER IN REAL LIFE.
THE TWO OF US,
IN THE FLESH.
WELL, HARUYUKI.
GOOD MORNING.
YEAH, AND GOOD MORNING
TO YOU TOO.
UM, YOU LOOK VERY...
I MEAN,
YOU’RE SURE HERE EARLY.
OF COURSE I AM.
IT’S EASIER
TO GET TO
THE SECOND-YEAR
CLASSROOMS FROM HERE.
UM, YEAH, THAT’S TRUE.
AND I PREFER WAITING
FOR YOU RATHER THAN HAVING
TO MAKE YOU WAIT FOR ME.
AND WHEN YOU WALK THROUGH
THE ENTRANCE
I GET TO LOOK UP
AND SEE YOU.
AND FOR THE REST OF THE DAY
I CHERISH THAT MOMENT
AT EVERY TURN.
BY THE WAY,
THAT CALL LAST NIGHT?
WHAT WAS THAT
ALL ABOUT ANYWAY?
HUH?
WELL, AT FIRST YOU HAD
MENTIONED SOMETHING
ABOUT THE RED KING.
OH, YEAH.
UM...
WELL, ABOUT THAT...
Haru: AND THAT’S
WHAT HAPPENED.
Senpai:
WHAT CAN I SAY?
I’M DOING MY BEST
NOT TO GIVE
YOU A LECTURE.
YOU REALLY SHOULD HAVE FIGURED
OUT IT WAS HER MUCH SOONER.
BUT I CAN SEE HOW SHE MAY
HAVE CAUGHT YOU OFF GUARD.
I CAN’T BELIEVE SHE WOULD
DO SOMETHING SO FOOLISH.
A REAL LIFE HACK
IS VERY RECKLESS.
YEAH, I THOUGHT
THE SAME THING.
SO, WHY DOES SHE
WANT TO MEET WITH ME?
DID SHE TELL YOU?
WHAT’S HER END GAME?
SHE SAID SHE’D TELL
YOU ALL THAT WHEN YOU MEET.
WELL...
HE’S MOVING.
LOOK, YOU SHOULD
CONSIDER THIS A VALUABLE
LEARNING EXPERIENCE.
YEAH. I THINK I’VE LEARNED
ALL KINDS OF THINGS
FROM THIS ENCOUNTER.
YOU HAD A ONE-ON-ONE
BATTLE WITH A KING.
AND NO MATTER HOW MANY
BURST POINTS YOU HAVE,
THAT’S A FIGHT
YOU CAN’T BUY.
SO TELL ME, WHAT WAS
THE SECOND RED KING LIKE?
SHE’S INSANE!
YOU SHOULD HAVE SEEN
WHAT SHE
DID TO CITY HALL!
SHE TOOK NEARLY HALF OF IT
OUT IN A SINGLE BLAST!
AND SHE REDUCED MY WHOLE
APARTMENT BUILDING TO RUBBLE.
FROM WHAT I’VE
HEARD ABOUT HER,
SHE TOOK ALL
HER LEVEL-UP BONUSES
AND DIRECTED THEM EACH
TOWARD ONE THING,
HER LONG-RANGE FIRE POWER.
WHAT ABOUT THE RED KING?
DID SHE MOVE AT ALL
DURING YOUR BATTLE?
MM-HMM, BUT ONLY ABOUT,
50 CENTIMETERS.
REALLY?
THAT’S VERY IMPRESSIVE.
THE STRONGHOLD.
THE IMMOBILE FORTRESS.
THAT’S ANOTHER NAME FOR HER.
NOT ’CAUSE SHE DOESN’T MOVE,
’CAUSE SHE DOESN’T HAVE TO.
IF I’D KNOWN ALL THAT
ABOUT HER I PROBABLY WOULD
JUST HAVE GIVEN UP
STRAIGHT FROM THE START.
I THOUGHT THE NAME
FOR THE RED KING
WOULD BE STARTING
WITH THE WORD "RED,"
NOT "SCARLET."
AS I SAID ON THE PHONE,
YOU NEED TO STUDY MORE.
IN THE HISTORY OF
ACCELERATED WORLD,
JUST ONE PERSON
HAS EVER USED RED
IN THEIR TITLE,
AND THAT WAS RED RIDER.
ARE YOU OKAY?
Senpai:
I BEHEADED THE RED KING.
THE PERSON CLOSEST TO ME
CALLING FOR PEACE.
LOOK, SENPAI, I’M SORRY,
BUT WAS THE FIRST RED KING
SOMEONE SPECIAL TO YOU?
NEVER MIND. I’M SORRY.
IT’S REALLY NONE
OF MY BUSINESS.
BOTH THAT CALL FROM ME
LAST NIGHT
AND THAT QUESTION
I JUST ASKED.
I REALLY WASN’T THINKING.
I’M SO SORRY.
NO IT’S ALL RIGHT.
DON’T WORRY ABOUT IT.
I HAD THOUGHT THAT I’D FIGURED
THIS WHOLE THING OUT
AND GOTTEN OVER IT
A LONG TIME AGO.
I HAD COME TO A CONCLUSION
ON THIS SUBJECT.
THAT ALL OTHER BURST LINKERS
WERE MY ENEMIES.
SO TO SUDDENLY
FEEL THIS WAY.
WELL, IT’S COMPLETELY
RIDICULOUS.
LOOK, YOU HAVE MY WORD.
I WILL NEVER DO ANYTHING THAT
MAKES ME FIGHT AGAINST YOU.
I PROMISE. I’LL NEVER
EVER BE YOUR ENEMY.
YOU ARE MY GUARDIAN
AND I AM YOUR PROTEGE.
THAT’S WHAT MATTERS
THE MOST BETWEEN
THE TWO OF US.
IT HAS TO!
SENPAI?
Haru: MAYBE SHE KNOWS
SOMETHING I DON’T.
A SITUATION WHERE A GUARDIAN
AND PROTEGE HAVE TO FIGHT.
BUT EVEN STILL,
IF THAT DOES HAPPEN.
I WILL NEVER FIGHT HER.
EVER!
♪
Announcer:
NEXT STAGE, "ESCALATION."
THE ARMOR’S HISTORY
IS REVEALED.
HARUYUKI AND HIS FRIENDS
ARE CAUGHT IN A SITUATION
THAT BEGINS TO SPIRAL
OUT OF CONTROL.