XeXeeD: THESE PLAYERS WHO THINK
IT'S ALL ABOUT THEIR AGILITY‐‐
(LAUGHS)
MAN, THEY'RE LIVIN' IN A DREAM.
I MEAN, SURE, FIRING SPEED
AND EVASION ARE IMPORTANT,
AND TIME WAS, IF YOU
ROCKED THOSE TWO THINGS,
IT'S ALL YOU NEEDED
TO BE THE BEST.
'TIL NOW, THAT IS.
YEAH, HATE TO SAY IT,
BUT IT DON'T WORK
LIKE THAT ANYMORE.
IN FACT, I GOT A MESSAGE
FOR THE FOLKS
WHO SPENT
THE LAST EIGHT MONTHS INDOORS
BOOSTING THEIR AGI.
SUCKS TO BE YOU RIGHT NOW,
DON'T IT?
‐ Crowd: (ANGRY SHOUTS, BOOING)
‐ Player: YOU SUCK!
Moderator: NOW THAT'S THE KIND
OF COMMENT WE'D EXPECT
FROM THE TOP PLAYER
OF "GUN GALE ONLINE,"
ONE OF THE MOST
CHALLENGING VRMMOs!
TALK ABOUT CONTROVERSIAL!
XeXeeD: I GUESS,
BUT WHO KNOWS
IF I'LL BE
ON "MMO STREAM" AGAIN,
SO MIGHT AS WELL STIR THINGS UP!
Moderator: OH, PLEASE!
SO, DO YOU THINK YOU HAVE A SHOT
IN THE UPCOMING
BULLET OF BULLETS?
XeXeeD: DAMN RIGHT, HONEY.
I WOULDN'T BE IN IT
IF I DIDN'T THINK
I COULD WIN IT!
Crowd: (BOOING)
Yamikaze: IT WON'T BE
THAT EASY, XEXEED.
THE B. o. B.'S A SOLO TOURNEY,
SO IT'S WAY DIFFERENT.
WHAT WORKED FOR YOU UP TO NOW,
DOESN'T MEAN IT'LL WORK AGAIN.
IF I WERE YOU, I WOULDN'T CHALK
MY WINS UP TO MY STATUS TYPE.
XeXeeD: YEAH, WELL,
IF ANYTHING, MY RESULTS
POINT TO SOME BIG CHANGES
HAPPENIN' IN "GGO."
YOU'RE ALL ABOUT AGI, YAMIKAZE.
GO FIGURE YOU'D BE IN DENIAL.
Yamikaze: (GROANS)
XeXeeD: WAKE UP, PEOPLE!
'TIL NOW, THE BEST STRATEGY
WAS BOOSTING YOUR AGI
AND SHOOTING A POWERFUL GUN
AS FAST AS YOU COULD,
BUT THE REALITY IS,
THE BALANCE OF GAME PLAY
IN AN MMO IS ALWAYS CHANGING,
ESPECIALLY IN GAMES
LIKE THIS ONE,
WITH LEVELS THAT DON'T LET YOU
RE‐SPEC YOUR STATS.
YOU HAVE TO THINK AHEAD AND BE
SMART WHEN USING YOUR POINTS,
'CAUSE THE BEST WEAPON
IN ONE LEVEL ZONE,
MIGHT NOT WORK FOR YOU
IN THE NEXT.
BESIDES, THE NEW GUNS COMIN' OUT
ARE GONNA HAVE
HIGHER STRENGTH REQUIREMENTS
AND ACCURACY BONUSES.
(CHUCKLES)
Player #2: (SCOFFS)
YOU REMEMBER WHEN HE WAS TALKING
'BOUT HOW GREAT
BEIN' AN AGI‐TYPE WAS?
THAT DICK TOTALLY SCAMMED US.
Players: (MURMURING)
Player #3: YOU'RE NOTHING
BUT A FAKE, XEXEED,
AND NOW YOU'LL FACE JUDGMENT
FROM SOMEONE WITH REAL POWER.
Players: (LAUGHING)
XeXeeD: ALL I'M SAYIN' IS
WHAT'S REALLY IMPORTANT
IN THE END
IS THE PLAYER'S ABILITY TO‐‐
(GASPING)
Moderator: UH‐OH.
I GUESS WE HAVE
A BAD CONNECTION HERE.
DON'T WORRY, FOLKS.
I'M SURE HE'LL BE BACK SHORTLY.
STAY TUNED
FOR MORE "MMO STREAM."
Players: (GASPING)
Player #3: THIS IS REAL POWER,
REAL STRENGTH!
LET YOUR FEAR CARVE
ONE NAME INTO YOUR BRAINS...
THE NAME I SHARE
WITH THIS WEAPON...
DEATH GUN!
Asuna: DECEMBER SEVENTH, 2025.
HAS IT ALREADY BEEN A YEAR?
(GASPS)
I WONDER WHAT THE DIFFERENCE
IS BETWEEN THE REAL WORLD...
AND THE VIRTUAL.
Kirito: THE AMOUNT OF DATA.
THAT'S ALL.
Asuna: (GASPS)
YOU SCARED ME.
Kirito: SORRY 'BOUT THAT.
I'M ON TIME, THOUGH.
(GIGGLES) WHAT?
Asuna: (GIGGLES)
NO, I'M SORRY.
I WAS SPACING OUT.
ANYWAY...
HELLO, KIRITO.
HOW ARE YOU DOING TODAY?!
Kirito: IT'S BEEN GOOD SO FAR,
BUT IT'S EVEN BETTER NOW.
Asuna: WHAT ARE YOU STARING AT?
Kirito: NOTHING! JUST...
THAT OUTFIT LOOKS GOOD ON YOU.
IT BRINGS BACK
A LOT OF MEMORIES.
Asuna: I GUESS IT DOES.
NO RAPIER, THOUGH.
LOOKS LIKE YOU WENT OVERBOARD
ON THE BLACK TODAY.
Kirito: YEAH!
SUGU THREW EVERYTHING
IN THE WASH THIS MORNING,
AND THIS IS ALL I HAD LEFT.
Asuna: THEN STOP
PUTTING YOUR LAUNDRY OFF.
‐ Kirito: (SIGHS)
‐ Asuna: (LAUGHS)
I CAN'T BELIEVE WE BOTH
DRESSED IN OUR OLD COLORS TODAY.
‐ WHAT ARE THE ODDS OF THAT?
‐ Kirito: WELL...
IF WE SEE EACH OTHER
EVERY DAY FOR A YEAR, IT'S‐‐
Asuna: STOP. THAT WAS
A RHETORICAL QUESTION,
SMARTY‐PANTS. COME ON.
Kirito: OKAY, OKAY.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT YOU,
BUT I THINK THE IMPERIAL PALACE
IS INTERESTING.
Asuna: INTERESTING?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
Kirito: IT'S TWO KILOMETERS
NORTH TO SOUTH,
1.5 EAST TO WEST,
AND IT TAKES UP
20% OF CHIYODA WARD.
THERE AREN'T ANY SUBWAYS
OR TUNNELS UNDER IT,
AND IT'S A NO‐FLY ZONE.
IT'S KINDA COOL,
DON'T YOU THINK?
I MEAN, IT'S THIS
BIG RESTRICTED AREA
RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE OF TOKYO.
NOT ONLY IS IT CUT OFF
FROM EVERYTHING PHYSICALLY,
BUT INFORMATION‐WISE AS WELL.
SEE THAT?
IT'S A SURVEILLANCE CAMERA.
THIS PLACE WAS SET UP WITH
ITS VERY OWN CLOSED NETWORK.
YOU CAN'T EVEN ACCESS IT
FROM THE OUTSIDE.
Asuna: WOW.
THAT'S A WEIRD‐LOOKING CAMERA.
Kirito: YEAH.
NOT ONLY IS THIS PLACE
THE HEART OF TOKYO,
BUT IT'S ALSO
AN ISOLATED WORLD OF ITS OWN.
MAYBE I'M EXAGGERATING
ITS COOL FACTOR.
‐ I GET LIKE THAT.
‐ Asuna: (GIGGLES) YOU THINK?
WOW!
Kirito: THIS USED TO BE
THE INNER CITADEL.
Asuna: COME ON! LET'S GO!
(NO AUDIBLE DIALOGUE)
Asuna: HEY, YOU KNOW
THAT QUESTIONNAIRE
THEY GAVE US TO FILL OUT,
THE ONE ABOUT OUR FUTURE PLANS?
DO YOU KNOW WHAT YOU
WANT TO DO YET?
Kirito: HMM.
I GUESS, IF ANYTHING,
I WANNA GO FROM PLAYING GAMES
TO BEING A CREATOR.
Asuna: A CREATOR?
WHAT, FOR GAMES?
Kirito: NO, NOT FOR GAMES.
I WANNA MAKE
A HUMAN‐MACHINE INTERFACE
TO REPLACE THE FULL‐DIVE TECH
WE USE NOW.
I'VE BEEN GOIN'
TO ALL THESE TECH FORUMS
TO LEARN MORE ABOUT IT,
BUT IT'S A HECK OF A LOT
OF INFORMATION TO ABSORB.
Asuna: AFTER I GRADUATE,
ALL I WANT IS TO BE WITH YOU.
‐ Kirito: HUH?
‐ Asuna: I‐I MEAN...
I‐I WISH WE COULD
FIGURE OUT A WAY
TO LIVE WITH YUI
IN THIS WORLD, TOO!
Kirito: WE'LL BE ABLE
TO LIVE WITH HER SOMEDAY,
AS SOON AS WE FIGURE OUT
HOW TO ACCESS AUGMENTED REALITY
AT WILL.
THE ONLY THING
STANDING IN THE WAY
IS THE DIFFERENCE
IN THE AMOUNT OF DATA.
Asuna: DIDN'T YOU SAY SOMETHING
LIKE THAT A LITTLE WHILE AGO,
THAT THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN OUR WORLD
AND THE VIRTUAL
WAS THE AMOUNT OF DATA?
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN, ANYWAY?
Kirito: LET'S SEE.
IT'S LIKE THIS.
IF WE WERE HOLDING HANDS
IN "A. L. O.,"
IT WOULDN'T BE THE SAME
AS IN THE REAL WORLD, WOULD IT?
Asuna: NO, IT WOULDN'T.
YOU CAN FEEL A LOT MORE
TOUCHING A REAL HAND.
HEY, IS THAT WHAT YOU MEAN
BY THE DIFFERENCE
IN THE AMOUNT OF DATA?
Kirito: YUP. AND CAN YOU IMAGINE
WHAT IT WOULD BE LIKE
IF WE COULD REPRODUCE
THE FEEL OF SKIN AND A PULSE?
WOULD WE BE ABLE
TO TELL THE DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN A REAL HAND
AND AN AVATAR'S HAND?
Asuna: I KNOW I COULD
IF I WAS TOUCHING YOUR HAND.
BUT IT'S NOT JUST TOUCH, IS IT?
I MEAN, IN THE REAL WORLD,
WE GET A LOT OF INFORMATION
FROM HOW SOMETHING SOUNDS
OR TASTES.
EVEN IF OUR AMUSPHERE RIGS
COULD ACCESS AUGMENTED REALITY,
WE'D STILL KNOW THE DIFFERENCE.
Kirito: YEAH. THE SECOND
YOU SAW OR TOUCHED SOMETHING,
YOU'D KNOW
IF IT WAS REAL OR NOT.
BUT HOPEFULLY
SOMEONE'LL COME ALONG
AND MAKE
A TECHNOLOGICAL BREAKTHROUGH,
AND WHATEVER THAT IS,
IT'LL HAVE TO OUTPUT
A TON OF SENSORY DATA
ALL THE TIME.
Asuna: THEN WE COULD
BREAK DOWN THE WALL
BETWEEN BOTH WORLDS
AND BE WITH YUI FOREVER.
DO YOU THINK THAT DAY
WILL EVER COME FOR US?
Kirito: YEAH.
Asuna: THEN GET TO WORK
AND MAKE IT HAPPEN, 'KAY?
Kirito: OKAY.
Waiter: WELCOME, SIR.
Kikuoka: HEY, KIRITO!
OVER HERE! (CHUCKLING)
Kikuoka: GO AHEAD.
ORDER WHATEVER YOU WANT.
IT'S ON ME.
Kirito: THANK YOU, SIR.
THAT'S VERY KIND OF YOU.
Kikuoka: COME ON. YOU DON'T
HAVE TO BE SO FORMAL WITH ME.
RELAX, AND TALK TO ME
LIKE YOU WOULD IN "A. L. O."
Kirito: OKAY. IF YOU SAY SO.
THEN I GUESS I'LL...
(GASPS)
(GROANS)
I'D LIKE
THE PARFAIT AU CHOCOLAT,
THE FRAMBOISE MILLE‐FEUILLE,
AND A HAZELNUT LATTE.
‐ (SIGHS)
‐ Kikuoka: SORRY TO MAKE YOU
COME ALL THE WAY OUT HERE,
KIRITO.
Kirito: IF YOU'RE
THAT SORRY ABOUT IT,
WHY'D YOU ASK ME
TO COME TO GINZA?
OH, AND DO YOU THINK
YOU CAN NOT CALL ME
BY THAT NAME IN PUBLIC?
Kikuoka: WHAT'S WITH
ALL THE ATTITUDE?
I THOUGHT WE WERE BUDS.
I WAS THE FIRST TO VISIT YOU
IN THE HOSPITAL, REMEMBER?
Kirito: (SIGHS)
Kirito: HE'S RIGHT.
WHEN I CAME TO,
THE FIRST ONE THERE
WASN'T MY FAMILY.
IT WAS THE LEADER
OF THE TASK FORCE,
SEIJIROU KIKUOKA
FROM THE TECH BUREAU
AT THE MINISTRY OF INTERNAL
AFFAIRS AND COMMUNICATIONS,
A.K.A. THE VIRTUAL REALITY
SECTION.
Kikuoka: (HUMMING)
Kirito: SO WHAT'D YOU
WANNA SEE ME ABOUT?
IF IT'S ANYTHING
"S. A. O." RELATED,
I TOLD YOU EVERYTHING I KNOW.
Kikuoka: ACTUALLY,
I WANNA TALK TO YOU
ABOUT SOMETHING ELSE.
HAVE A LOOK AT THAT.
Kirito: WHO'S HE?
Kikuoka: THIS WON'T BE PLEASANT.
SO LAST MONTH,
ON NOVEMBER THE 14TH...
THE LANDLORD OF AN APARTMENT
COMPLEX IN NAKANO, TOKYO,
NOTICED A FOUL ODOR
WHILE CLEANING.
IT WAS COMING
FROM ONE OF THE UNITS,
SO HE DISABLED THE LOCK
AND DISCOVERED THIS MAN DEAD.
HIS NAME WAS TAMOTSU SHIGEMURA,
AND HE WAS 26.
HE'D BEEN DEAD FOR FIVE DAYS.
THEY FOUND HIM IN BED.
HIS PLACE WAS A MESS,
BUT NO SIGNS OF BURGLARY.
HE HAD SOMETHING INTERESTING
ON HIS HEAD, THOUGH.
Kirito: AN AMUSPHERE?
Kikuoka: YEAH. IT WAS RULED
AN UNNATURAL DEATH,
SO THEY DID AN AUTOPSY.
THE CAUSE OF DEATH WAS FOUND
TO BE ACUTE HEART FAILURE.
Kirito: WAIT. HEART FAILURE?
YOU MEAN HIS HEART STOPPED?
THEY FIND OUT WHY?
Kikuoka: NO, THEY DIDN'T.
Waiter: HERE YOU ARE, SIR.
Kikuoka: UNFORTUNATELY,
SINCE SO MUCH TIME HAD PASSED
SINCE HIS DEATH AND FOUL PLAY
WAS RULED OUT AS THE CAUSE,
THE AUTOPSY
WASN'T VERY THOROUGH.
WE DO KNOW HE'D BEEN LOGGED IN
FOR TWO DAYS STRAIGHT
AND HADN'T EATEN ANYTHING
THE WHOLE TIME.
Kirito: WELL,
THAT'S NOT THAT UNUSUAL.
PLAYERS DO IT ALL THE TIME.
WAIT. WHY ARE YOU TELLIN' ME
ABOUT THIS?
Kikuoka: HE HAD A GAME
INSTALLED ON HIS SYSTEM
CALLED "GUN GALE ONLINE."
YOU KNOW THAT ONE?
Kirito: YEAH. "GGO."
IT'S THE ONLY MMO IN JAPAN
WITH PROFESSIONAL PLAYERS.
Kikuoka: THIS PAST OCTOBER,
THERE WAS A TOURNAMENT
TO DECIDE THE MOST POWERFUL
PLAYER IN "GGO."
THE DECEASED
WAS THE GUY WHO WON IT.
HIS CHARACTER'S NAME WAS XEXEED.
Kirito: WAS HE PLAYING "GGO"
WHEN HE DIED?
Kikuoka: NO. WHEN IT HAPPENED,
HE WAS APPEARING
ON A SHOW CALLED "MMO STREAM"
AS XEXEED'S AVATAR.
WE KNOW THE TIME FROM THE LOGS.
THIS NEXT BIT OF INFO
STILL NEEDS TO BE CONFIRMED.
ACCORDING TO
ANOTHER PLAYER'S BLOG,
AT THE SAME TIME SHIGEMURA
HAD THE HEART ATTACK,
SOMETHING STRANGE
HAPPENED IN "GGO."
Kirito: WHAT?
Kikuoka: SOME PLAYERS
WERE AT A BAR IN‐GAME
WATCHING THE SHOW, WHEN ONE
OF THE PLAYERS STOOD UP
AND STARTED ACTING ERRATICALLY.
THE BLOG STATES
THE PLAYER WAS SHOUTING STUFF
ABOUT "JUDGMENT" AND "POWER"
AT XEXEED'S IMAGE ON THE TV
AND THEN FIRED HIS GUN AT IT.
AT THE TIME,
ANOTHER PLAYER IN THE BAR
HAPPENED TO BE RECORDING AUDIO.
HE UPLOADED IT TO A VIDEO SITE.
SINCE THE FILE HAD A JAPAN
STANDARD TIME COUNTER EMBEDDED,
WE KNOW THAT THE SHOT FIRED
AT THE TV AND SHIGEMURA'S AVATAR
DISAPPEARING FROM THE SHOW
HAPPENED AT ABOUT THE SAME TIME.
Kirito: PROBABLY
JUST COINCIDENCE.
Kikuoka: THERE WAS
ANOTHER DEATH, THOUGH.
Kirito: WHAT?
THIS ONE HAPPENED
ON NOVEMBER THE 28TH
SOMEWHERE IN SAITAMA PREFECTURE,
SAME SETUP AS BEFORE.
THE DECEASED WAS FOUND
IN THEIR APARTMENT.
A GUY DELIVERING THE NEWSPAPER
HAPPENED TO LOOK IN THE WINDOW.
HE SAW THE VICTIM LYING IN BED
WEARING AN AMUSPHERE RIG,
SAID THE SMELL WAS...
‐ Woman: (COUGHING)
‐ Woman #2: AHEM!
Kikuoka: LET'S SKIP THE DETAILS
OF THE CORPSE'S CONDITION.
ANYWAY, HEART FAILURE
WAS THE CAUSE OF DEATH.
THE VICTIM WAS ALSO
A TOP‐RANKING "GGO" PLAYER.
HIS CHARACTER'S NAME WAS...
USUSHIO TARAKO? WELL,
HE WAS PLAYING WHEN HE DIED.
IT HAPPENED IN THE CENTRAL PLAZA
IN GLOCKEN.
HE WAS IN THE MIDDLE
OF A MEETING WITH HIS "SQUAD."
I GUESS THAT'S
THE SAME AS A GUILD.
A STRANGE PLAYER WENT UP TO HIM
AND SHOT HIM, POINT‐BLANK.
Kirito: DO YOU KNOW
IF IT WAS THE SAME GUY
WHO SHOT XEXEED?
Kikuoka: MOST LIKELY.
HE SAID STUFF
ABOUT JUDGMENT AND POWER
AND THEN IDENTIFIED HIMSELF
WITH THE SAME CHARACTER NAME.
Kirito: WHAT NAME?
Kikuoka: DEATH GUN.
Kirito: DEATH...GUN?
ARE YOU ABSOLUTELY SURE BOTH
VICTIMS DIED FROM HEART FAILURE?
Kikuoka: WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
Kirito: WAS THERE ANY DAMAGE
TO THEIR BRAINS?
Kikuoka: I WAS WONDERING
ABOUT THAT, TOO,
SO I ASKED THE CORONER
IF HE FOUND ANY TRACE OF DAMAGE
TO EITHER OF THEIR BRAINS,
AND HE SAID THEY WERE BOTH FINE.
BESIDES, THE NERVEGEAR RIG
USED HIGH‐OUTPUT MICROWAVES
POWERFUL ENOUGH
TO FRY THE SIGNAL ELEMENTS
AND DESTROY THE BRAIN.
ON THE OTHER HAND,
THE AMUSPHERE RIG WAS DESIGNED
SO THAT IT COULDN'T EMIT
ELECTROMAGNETIC WAVES
THAT POWERFUL.
AT LEAST, THAT'S WHAT
THE DEVELOPERS CLAIM.
Kirito: IT SOUNDS LIKE YOU GUYS
HAVE DONE YOUR HOMEWORK,
BUT EVEN SO, YOUR STORY'S
BUILT AROUND COINCIDENCE
AND RUMORS.
Kikuoka: TRUE. IT COULD BE
A COINCIDENCE OR EVEN A HOAX.
I'M NOT SOLD EITHER WAY.
FOR NOW‐‐AND THIS IS
HYPOTHETICAL, MIND YOU‐‐
DO YOU THINK IT'S EVEN
REMOTELY POSSIBLE
TO STOP A PLAYER'S HEART
IN THE REAL WORLD
WITH VIRTUAL BULLETS
FROM A VIRTUAL GUN?
Kirito: (GASPS)
NO. I DON'T THINK SO.
BUT HYPOTHETICALLY
LET'S SAY THIS DEATH GUN
DID SEND SOME KIND
OF KILLER SIGNAL TO XEXEED
AND THAT TARAKO GUY'S
AMUSPHERES.
WHAT WOULD IT BE?
COULD THE SENSATION OF A TOUCH
STOP A HEART?
MAYBE A TASTE OR SMELL,
A SIGHT, A SOUND,
OR SOME OTHER SENSATION.
‐ Kikuoka: (CHUCKLES)
‐ Kirito: HUH?
OKAY, WHOA. YOU ALREADY THOUGHT
OF THIS, HAVEN'T YOU?
OH, I GET IT, YOU AND YOUR TEAM
CAN'T FIGURE IT OUT,
SO YOU INVITE ME FOR COFFEE
TO PICK MY BRAIN?
Kikuoka: NO!
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I‐I'D NEVER DO SOMETHING
LIKE THAT TO YOU, HONEST.
I LIKE TALKING TO YOU
AND JUST WANTED YOUR OPINION.
Kirito: WE'RE DONE.
YOU WANT MY OPINION, HERE IT IS.
YOU CAN'T STOP A PLAYER'S HEART
IN THE REAL WORLD
BY ACTIONS IN‐GAME.
SHOTS FIRED AND THE HEART
ATTACKS ARE COINCIDENCES.
Kikuoka: WAIT! HOLD ON!
LISTEN, YOU CAN ORDER
SOMETHING ELSE!
JUST SIT DOWN,
AND HANG OUT FOR A BIT.
PLEASE.
I CAN'T TELL YOU
HOW RELIEVED I AM
TO HEAR YOU PUT IT INTO WORDS.
FACT IS,
I'M OF THE SAME OPINION AS YOU.
I DON'T BELIEVE THESE TWO DEATHS
WERE CAUSED
BY IN‐GAME GUNSHOTS EITHER.
AND NOW THAT WE'VE TALKED,
I WANT TO ASK YOU OFFICIALLY.
WOULD YOU LOG IN TO "GUN GALE
ONLINE" AND MAKE CONTACT
WITH THE PLAYER
CALLING HIMSELF DEATH GUN?
Kirito: AND ONCE I DO
FIND THE GUY, THEN WHAT?
YOU WANT ME TO GET SHOT?
IS THAT IT?
‐ Kikuoka: WHOA, NOW. COME ON.
‐ Kirito: WELL, SCREW THAT!
‐ I DON'T WANNA GET KILLED!
‐ (CUPS RATTLE)
Kikuoka: THAT'S NOT POSSIBLE!
WE JUST AGREED IT WASN'T,
DIDN'T WE?!
BESIDES, THIS DEATH GUN GUY
IS ONLY GOING
AFTER SPECIFIC TARGETS!
THEY HAVE TO MEET HIS CRITERIA!
‐ Kirito: CRITERIA?
‐ Kikuoka: UH‐HUH!
HERE'S THE DEAL.
XEXEED AND USUSHIO TARAKO
WEREN'T JUST ANY OLD PLAYERS.
THEY WERE TOP RANKED,
SO IT'S SAFE TO ASSUME
HE'S NOT INTERESTED IN NEWBIES.
BUT IF YOU WERE STRONG ENOUGH
TO BEAT KAYABA
AT HIS OWN GAME, THEN‐‐
Kirito: THAT'S DIFFERENT!
LOOK, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'VE HEARD,
BUT "GGO"
IS NO WALK IN THE PARK!
IT'S FILLED WITH PRO GAMERS!
Kikuoka: HOLD THE PHONE!
YOU SAID, "PRO GAMER."
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN, "PRO"?
Kirito: IT MEANS PROFESSIONAL,
LITERALLY.
"GUN GALE ONLINE"
IS THE ONLY VIRTUAL MMO
WITH A GAME‐COIN
TO REAL‐CURRENCY
‐ CONVERSION SYSTEM IN PLACE.
‐ Kikuoka: WHAT?
Kirito: IT MEANS WHATEVER MONEY
YOU EARN IN THE GAME
GETS PAID BACK TO YOU IN COLD,
HARD CASH IN THE REAL WORLD.
BEIN' A PRO MEANS YOU HAVE
A CONSTANT STREAM OF INCOME
FROM THE GAME
COMIN' IN EVERY MONTH,
AND IF YOU'RE A TOP PLAYER,
THAT MEANS MONTHLY
YOU'RE MAKING
TWO TO THREE HUNDRED THOU.
IT'S AN AWESOME GIG.
THAT'S WHY THE HIGH‐LEVEL GUYS
IN "GGO" ARE SO HARDCORE.
THEY POUR MORE TIME
AND PASSION INTO IT
THAN PLAYERS FROM OTHER MMOS.
SOMEONE LIKE ME
CAN'T JUST LOG IN
AND MATCH PLAYERS LIKE THAT.
YOU SHOULD FIND SOMEONE ELSE‐‐
Kikuoka: WHOA,
HOLD IT! HOLD IT!
WHO ELSE AM I GONNA FIND?
YOU'RE IT!
I NEED YOUR HELP
IN THIS INVESTIGATION,
AND IF TAKING THESE PROS ON
IS GOING TO BE THAT BIG A DEAL,
I CAN PAY YOU THIS MUCH.
Kirito: (GULPS)
I DON'T GET WHY
YOU'RE SO HUNG UP ON THIS.
YOU FIND HORROR STORIES
LIKE THESE ALL THE TIME ONLINE.
Kikuoka: YEAH, I KNOW.
BUT STILL, IT'S GOT
MY BOSSES WORRIED.
THE EFFECT OF FULL‐DIVE
TECHNOLOGY ON THE REAL WORLD
IS THE HOTTEST TOPIC TODAY.
LITERALLY EVERYONE'S
RESEARCHING IT.
Kikuoka: PEOPLE ARE GOING
TO TRY TO USE THESE DEATHS
TO REGULATE THE TECHNOLOGY.
WE WANT TO KNOW THE FACTS
BEFORE THAT HAPPENS.
WE WANT TO BE SURE.
THAT'S WHY WE'RE INTERESTED.
Kirito: YOU GUYS COULD JUST GO
DIRECTLY TO THE ADMINS ABOUT IT.
Kikuoka: RIGHT, BUT ZASKAR,
THE COMPANY THAT DEVELOPED
AND HOSTS "GGO," IS IN THE U. S.
THEIR ADDRESS,
PHONE NUMBER, AND EMAIL,
NONE OF IT'S BEEN MADE PUBLIC,
SO WE CAN'T CONTACT THEM.
EVER SINCE THE SEED
WAS RELEASED,
ALL KINDS OF SHADY VR WORLDS
HAVE POPPED UP.
Kirito: YEAH.
Kikuoka: MAYBE THEY'RE LEGIT,
MAYBE THEY'RE NOT, BUT IF WE
WANT TO FIND ANYTHING OUT,
THE ONLY WAY TO DO IT IS TO TRY
CONTACTING THEM IN THE GAME.
I'M NOT ASKING YOU TO GET SHOT.
WE'LL TAKE WHATEVER
SAFETY PRECAUTIONS WE HAVE TO.
JUST EVALUATE THE SITUATION,
AND REPORT BACK.
SO WILL YOU HELP US, OR WHAT?
Kirito: FOUR THOUSAND PEOPLE...
DIED IN AINCRAD.
IT'S BEEN A YEAR,
AND FINALLY THOSE MEMORIES
ARE STARTING TO FADE.
BUT NOW MORE PEOPLE ARE DYING
IN ANOTHER VIRTUAL WORLD,
AND I'M GETTING PULLED BACK IN.
IT'S LIKE SOMEONE
DOESN'T WANT ME TO EVER FORGET.
Asuna: OHH. NOW I GET IT.
I THINK I FIGURED OUT
WHY YOU BROUGHT ME HERE TODAY.
Kirito: OH. YOU DID, HUH?
Asuna: MM‐HMM.
IF OUR WORLD IS MADE UP
OF AN AXIS CALLED TIME
AND A PLANE CALLED SPACE,
THEN THE CENTER OF OUR REALITY
IS THIS PLACE
IN THE HEART OF TOKYO
WHERE A CASTLE USED TO STAND.
AND THE AXIS OF ALL THE VIRTUAL
WORLDS POPPING UP NOW,
THANKS TO THE SEED, IS A PLACE
THAT ALSO HAD A CASTLE ONCE,
AINCRAD.
THAT'S WHY THIS SUNSET
FEELS SO NOSTALGIC NOW.
Kirito: YOU'RE RIGHT. IT DOES.
YOU KNOW, WHAT YOU JUST SAID
HELPED ME FIGURE
SOMETHING OUT, TOO.
Asuna: HUH? REALLY?
Kirito: YOU REMEMBER
WHAT AINCRAD LOOKED LIKE?
WELL, MAYBE ITS SHAPE
WAS SUPPOSED TO REPRESENT
THE AXIS OF TIME
AND THE PLANE OF SPACE.
Asuna: MAYBE, BUT IF ITS
VERTICAL AXIS REPRESENTED TIME
AND ITS FLOORS SPACE,
THEN THE COMMANDER MADE A WORLD
THAT TAPERED TO NOTHING.
EVERYTHING ENDED
ONCE YOU REACHED THE TOP.
UNFORTUNATELY, A CERTAIN SOMEONE
DESTROYED IT HALFWAY UP.
NOW WE'LL NEVER KNOW
HOW IT ENDED.
Kirito: YES, MA'AM!
SORRY ABOUT THAT, MA'AM!
Both: (LAUGHING)
Kirito: ASUNA, LISTEN. I‐‐
Asuna: WHAT?
Kirito: NAH.
HEY, IT'S GETTIN' COLD.
YOU WANNA
START HEADIN' BACK NOW?
Asuna: MM‐HMM.
OH, AND NEXT TIME WE COME,
LET'S BRING LIZ AND LEAFA
AND THE OTHERS.
WOULDN'T IT BE FUN
TO GET EVERYONE TOGETHER
FOR A PICNIC HERE?
Kirito: YEAH, IT WOULD,
ESPECIALLY IN SPRINGTIME.
Man: I'M IN POSITION.
Woman: ROGER.
TARGETS HAVEN'T CHANGED
THEIR COURSE OR THEIR SPEED.
THEY'RE FOUR HUNDRED METERS
FROM YOU,
FIFTEEN HUNDRED FROM ME.
Man: PRETTY FAR.
CAN YOU MAKE THE SHOT?
Woman: NO SWEAT.
Man: OKAY, THEN.
FIRE WHEN READY.
‐ I'M COUNTING ON YOU, SINON.
‐ Sinon: ROGER.
THIS PRESSURE...
THIS ANXIETY...
THIS FEAR.
FIFTEEN HUNDRED METERS?
THAT'S NOTHING,
LIKE TOSSING A WAD OF PAPER
INTO A TRASH CAN.
NO WAY.
THIS IS NOTHING
LIKE HOW IT FELT THAT DAY.
NEXT.