Death Gun: WITH THAT NAME
AND YOUR SWORD SKILLS,
ARE YOU THE REAL DEAL OR WHAT?
(NO AUDIBLE DIALOGUE)
Kirito: IF HE KNOWS ME,
I SHOULD KNOW HIM.
THAT'S IT.
HE'S AN "S. A. O." SURVIVOR.
WHO IS HE,
AND WHERE DID WE MEET
IN "S. A. O."?
(NO AUDIBLE DIALOGUE)
Death Gun: ANSWER THE QUESTION.
OR DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND?
Kirito: NO, I DON'T.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
BY "REAL DEAL"?
Death Gun: NEVER MIND.
WHETHER YOU'RE
A FAKE USING HIS NAME
OR THE REAL GUY,
SOMEDAY I'LL KILL YOU.
Kirito: (PANTING)
LAUGHING COFFIN.
THE EMBLEM ON HIS WRIST
BELONGED TO THE MURDER GUILD
FROM "S. A. O."
LAUGHING COFFIN.
GOD KNOWS HOW MANY PLAYERS
THEY KILLED IN THEIR TIME.
BUT THEY'RE NOT THE ONLY ONES
GUILTY OF MURDER.
(GASPS)
Schmidt:
IF THE TIP WE GOT'S GOOD,
WE SHOULD BE NEAR
LAUGHING COFFIN'S BASE,
BUT BEFORE WE CHARGE IN,
LET'S KEEP ONE THING IN MIND.
THOSE GUYS ARE RED PLAYERS.
ONCE THE BATTLE STARTS,
THEY'RE NOT GONNA THINK TWICE
ABOUT KILLING ANY ONE OF US,
SO DON'T YOU HESITATE.
YOU DO, AND YOU'RE DEAD.
Player: (GASPS)
Schmidt: WE'VE GOT TWO THINGS
GOING FOR US, THOUGH.
WE OUTNUMBER THEM, AND WE'VE
GOT HIGHER SKILL LEVELS.
SO WHO KNOWS? MAYBE THEY'LL
SURRENDER PEACEFULLY.
HELL, A GUY CAN DREAM, CAN'T HE?
Players: (LAUGH)
Players: (GRUNTING, YELLING)
Schmidt: DAMN IT.
SOMEONE MUST HAVE LEAKED
OUR PLANS TO THESE BASTARDS!
Player 2: (CHUCKLES)
Kirito:
THEY CAUGHT US OFF GUARD,
BUT WE REGROUPED IN TIME.
WE CAN DO THIS.
Player 3: YOU'RE OUTNUMBERED.
SURRENDER NOW, OR ELSE.
Player 4: COME ON.
DROP YOUR SWORD.
Player 3: DO IT!
YOU CAN'T TAKE ANOTHER HIT!
Player 4: DROP THE SWORD NOW!
Player 5: (LAUGHING)
Player 4: (SCREAMS)
(SWORD SLASHES)
Player 5: (CHUCKLING)
Player 6: (GROANS, GURGLES)
Kirito: IT TURNED INTO
A BLOOD‐SOAKED NIGHTMARE
AFTER THAT.
WE WON THE BATTLE,
BUT BY THE TIME IT WAS OVER,
WE'D LOST TEN OF OURS.
AS FOR LAUGHING COFFIN,
TWENTY OF THEM REFUSED
TO SURRENDER AND WERE KILLED.
OUT OF THAT TWENTY,
TWO LIVES WERE CLAIMED
BY MY SWORD.
THAT GUY...
IF HE'S ONE OF THE SURVIVORS
FROM LAUGHING COFFIN,
THEN HE MUST HAVE TALKED TO ME
AT SOME POINT AFTER THAT BATTLE,
OR MAYBE HE'S ONE
OF THE TWO PEOPLE I KILLED.
NO, THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
THAT'S CRAZY.
Death Gun: ...THE NAME I SHARE
WITH THIS WEAPON, DEATH GUN.
Kirito: OH, MY GOD.
HIS VOICE WAS
THE SAME AS DEATH GUN'S.
WAS THAT HIM?
COULD HE BE DEATH GUN?
Sinon: YOU LOOK LIKE
YOU'RE ABOUT TO LOSE IT.
Kirito: NO, I'M OKAY.
Sinon: GUESS YOUR FIRST MATCH
WAS TOUGHER THAN YOU THOUGHT.
YOU GOT BACK
PRETTY EARLY, THOUGH.
NOT TOO SHABBY FOR A NOOB.
GOD, IF YOU'RE LIKE THIS
AFTER ONE MATCH,
YOU'LL NEVER MAKE IT
TO THE FINALS.
YOU BETTER MAN UP, GUY.
REMEMBER, WE GOT
THINGS TO SETTLE.
HEY, LET GO!
WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
ARE YOU OKA‐‐
(GUN CLINKS)
Kirito: (SCREAMS)
Player 7: THAT PLAYER
GOT A DEATH WISH OR WHAT?
Spiegel: HMM.
Player 8: WHA?
Players: (GASPING)
Spiegel: HUH. I CAN'T BELIEVE
HE KEEPS WINNING
FIGHTING LIKE THAT.
HIS NEXT MATCH
IS IN THE SEMIFINALS.
YOURS IS, TOO,
SO GET OUT THERE AND ROCK.
GOOD LUCK.
Sinon: STINGER IS MY TARGET.
HIS MAIN WEAPON IS
AN FN‐SCAR CARBINE RIFLE.
AS A SNIPER,
IF I LET HIM GET TOO CLOSE,
I'M DONE FOR.
BUT ON THIS MAP,
IF HE WANTS TO CLOSE IN ON ME,
HE'S GONNA HAVE TO GO
THROUGH THERE,
AND THAT'S
WHERE I'LL TAKE HIM OUT.
(SIGHS) DAMN HIM.
HE WANTED ME TO WASTE
MY FIRST SHOT
TO BUY HIM TIME
SO HE COULD ADVANCE.
TOO BAD FOR HIM,
'CAUSE I KNOW THE PATH
MY FIRST BULLET TOOK.
MY SECOND ONE'LL BE
RIGHT ON TARGET.
YOU SHOULD HAVE GOT
OUT OF THE CAR, BUDDY.
IF YOU DID, YOU MIGHT HAVE
SEEN THE BULLET LINE
IN TIME TO DODGE IT.
(FANFARE PLAYING)
Sinon: HE'S GONNA TRY
AND CLOSE IN ON ME
USING THE SHADOWS FOR COVER.
MY ONLY CHANCE IS NAILING HIM
WITH THE FIRST SHOT,
BEFORE HE FIGURES OUT
MY LOCATION.
HE WON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT HIT HIM.
WHAT'S MY PROBLEM?
WHY DO I WANT
TO BEAT HIM SO BAD?
IS IT 'CAUSE HE
REMINDS ME OF ME?
DOES HE THINK HE CAN DODGE
MY BULLET AT THIS RANGE?
DOES HE EVEN WANT TO?
(HEART BEATING)
DON'T...
DON'T‐‐
DON'T SCREW WITH ME!
(SHELL CLATTERS)
FIGHT ME.
COME ON, FIGHT!
OR MAYBE YOU THINK
I'M NOT WORTH THE EFFORT.
Kirito: YOU GOT IT ALL WRONG.
ALL I WANT
IS TO COMPETE IN THE FINAL.
THERE'S NO REASON
TO FIGHT ANYMORE.
Sinon: THEN GO ON
AND SHOOT YOURSELF,
AND GET IT OVER WITH!
OR WOULD THAT BE
A WASTE OF AMMO?
OR MAYBE YOU WANTED ME
TO SHOOT YOU
'CAUSE YOU THOUGHT IT WOULD
EVEN THE SCORE BETWEEN US.
TO YOU, IT'S JUST A GAME,
JUST ONE STUPID MATCH.
THAT'S ALL IT IS TO YOU,
IS THAT IT, A GAME?
WELL, JUST 'CAUSE YOU FEEL
THAT WAY DOESN'T MEAN I DO!
BUT IF WE DO MEET IN THE FINAL
BRACKET OF THE PRELIMS,
I'LL BE PLAYING TO WIN.
Kirito: OH. I GET IT.
ALL RIGHT, IF WE BOTH MAKE IT,
NO HOLDING BACK.
I'M SORRY.
WHAT I DID WAS WRONG.
SURE, IT'S A GAME.
IT'S ONLY ONE MATCH.
BUT STILL, THAT'S WHY
WE HAVE TO GIVE IT ALL WE GOT.
IT'S WHY WE'RE HERE.
IT'S HOW WE LIVE,
HOW WE KEEP SURVIVING.
IF ANYONE SHOULD HAVE
KNOWN THAT, IT'S ME.
SINON, GIVE ME A CHANCE
TO MAKE IT RIGHT WITH YOU.
LET ME GIVE YOU
THE FIGHT I PROMISED.
Sinon: I SWEAR,
IF YOU'RE MESSING WITH ME...
Kirito: YOU GOT ANY BULLETS
LEFT ON YOU, OR ARE YOU OUT?
Sinon: YEAH, I GOT ONE.
Kirito: OKAY,
THEN LET'S HAVE A DUEL.
HERE'S THE RULES.
WE'LL STAND TEN METERS APART,
YOU WITH YOUR RIFLE,
AND ME WITH MY SWORD.
I'LL TOSS THIS BULLET UP,
AND WHEN IT HITS THE GROUND,
WE START.
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
Sinon: HANG ON.
IF WE'RE TEN METERS
AWAY FROM EACH OTHER,
IT WON'T GIVE YOU ENOUGH TIME TO
SEE THE BULLET LINE AND REACT,
AND WITH MY HECATE,
I'LL DEFINITELY HIT YOU.
AT THAT RANGE, I CAN'T MISS.
Kirito: YOU WON'T KNOW FOR SURE
TILL YOU TRY.
Sinon: WHY'S HE ACTING
SO CONFIDENT?
DOES HE HAVE A PLAN
OR SOMETHING?
WHATEVER IT IS,
I'M READY FOR IT.
OKAY.
IF THAT'S HOW YOU WANT IT,
LET'S GO.
I KNEW IT.
HE DOES HAVE A PLAN.
Kirito: 'KAY. GET SET.
Sinon: NO WAY.
THAT'S IMPOSSIBLE!
YOU KNEW WHERE I WAS AIMING.
BUT HOW? HOW'D YOU KNOW
I WAS GOING FOR YOUR LEG?
Kirito: I KNEW,
'CAUSE I COULD SEE YOUR EYE
THROUGH THE LENS OF YOUR SCOPE.
Sinon: THAT'S HOW HE
PREDICTED MY BULLET'S PATH?
THAT'S AMAZING.
THAT KIND OF POWER'S
WAY BEYOND ANY V. R. GAME.
IF YOU'RE SO STRONG
YOU CAN DO THAT,
WHY'D YOU LOOK SO AFRAID BEFORE?
Kirito: YOU'RE WRONG.
IT'S NOT STRENGTH.
ALL IT IS IS A SKILL.
Sinon: NO, IT'S NOT.
TECHNIQUE ISN'T ENOUGH TO CUT
A BULLET FROM MY HECATE IN HALF.
YOU AND I BOTH KNOW THAT.
IT TAKES STRENGTH,
AND ALL I WANT TO KNOW
IS HOW TO GET IT.
IT'S WHAT I‐‐IT'S WHAT
I'M HERE TO FIGURE OUT.
Kirito: LISTEN, COULD YOU
SHOOT A PLAYER IN HERE
IF YOU KNEW, IN THE REAL WORLD,
THAT PLAYER WOULD DIE FROM IT?
AND WHAT IF YOU
HAD TO KILL THAT PLAYER,
'CAUSE IF YOU DIDN'T,
YOU OR SOMEONE YOU LOVE
WOULD DIE INSTEAD?
IF YOU HAD THAT POWER,
COULD YOU STILL PULL
THAT TRIGGER?
Sinon: DOES HE KNOW
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED
TO ME THAT DAY?
MAYBE SOMETHING LIKE THAT
HAPPENED TO HIM, TOO.
Kirito: I CAN'T
GO THROUGH THAT AGAIN.
SO I'M NOT AS STRONG
AS YOU THINK I AM.
I DON'T KNOW
THE NAMES OF THE TWO‐‐
NO, THREE PEOPLE I KILLED
IN THAT OTHER GAME.
I HAVE TO LIVE WITH IT
EVERY SINGLE DAY.
AND EVERY DAY,
I KEEP HOPING I'LL FORGET.
I'M FINE.
ANYWAY, I GUESS THIS MEANS
I WON THE DUEL, DOESN'T IT?
Sinon: HUH? OH.
YEAH, I GUESS.
Kirito: WELL, WOULD YOU MIND
SURRENDERING THEN?
I'M NOT A BIG FAN
OF SLASHING AT GIRLS.
Sinon: HUH?
NEXT TIME, I'M NOT GONNA LOSE.
SEE YOU IN THE FINALS.
AND MAKE SURE YOU SURVIVE
UNTIL YOU SEE ME AGAIN.
RESIGN.
Players: (GASPING)
Spiegel: HUH?