♫
bang: What is it now?
- ( Man moaning )
- Bang: Come on! Get up!
Tell me, charanko,
have you learned nothing
in the past six months?
When first
I made you my disciple,
I said to train
like your life depended on it.
I don't think your skills
will ever improve.
You've no talent
for the martial arts!
You are hereby
expelled from the dojo.
Never return!
♫
♫ hero
( singing in japanese )
♫ go, go
♫ hero
( singing in japanese )
♫ go, go
♫ hero
( singing in japanese )
♫ one punch
genos: Bang is acting strangely?
Charanko: That's right.
He changed my training
to full-contact, and he--
he beat me mercilessly.
He'd been so kindhearted before.
There's something going on.
And I was hoping
you guys would know
what that something might be.
Genos: I do not know.
Blizzard: Bang, like
the class-s hero, silverfang?
King: Don't know if you saw,
but we're kinda trying
to play games here.
Charanko:
I guess the group has grown.
Genos: However,
I can make an educated guess.
It probably
has to do with garou.
Charanko: Garou?!
The guy who was
kicked out of our dojo?
What'd he do?
Genos: I see.
So you have not heard,
I take it?
Garou is now known
as a criminal.
He has been added
to the association's wanted list
as a violent monster.
Bang himself has volunteered
to take him down.
Charanko: A monster?! Garou?!
Genos: Apparently
there was an incident at hq.
The association has been
keeping it under wraps,
but, should
a violent battle ensue,
it could quickly
spin out of control.
Perhaps that is the reason
why bang pushed you away.
Charanko: I had no idea.
So master bang...
Considers me a burden?
Genos: But that is
simply my hypothesis.
Your thoughts, master?
Saitama: I don't know, man.
I mean, it's not like
I know the old dude
all that well or anything.
"Silverfang"...
Now, that's a cool hero name.
How'd I get stuck
with caped baldy?
There's still one thing
bothering me, though.
( Charanko gasps )
Saitama: Who are you?
Genos: Charanko, a pissant
who is bang's
current top disciple, master.
You two have met.
Saitama: Huh? For real?
Charanko: I just can't
allow myself to be a burden.
For the sake of my master,
I need to stop garou.
But it's not like he's
gonna pop up right next to me.
( Groans )
And even if I did manage
to find him, I'd only--
- ( bicycle brakes squeal )
- Garou: Hey, numb-nuts.
You're a hero, right?
Mumen rider: Yes, indeed.
I'm called mumen rider.
- Garou: Time to hunt.
- Mumen rider: Hunt?
What on earth
are you talking about?
This entire discussion
is a bit odd.
Garou: To complete my evolution
into a monster,
I need prey like you.
( Tank top vegetarian growls )
There you are.
Garou: Huh?
Hero: You sure this is the guy?
Vegetarian: Oh, I'm sure.
Now time for a little payb--
garou: Are you here
seeking vengeance,
tank top vegetarian?
I left you
within an inch of your life,
and now you
throw that life away?
That's some next-level stupid.
Your musclehead friends
won't be leaving alive, either.
Now die! ( Grunts )
♫
what?
Tank top master: I hear
you roughed up my friend here.
Garou: A class s?! ( Cackles )
Looks like I hooked a big one!
This is perfect!
I'm friggin' stoked!
Tank top master:
Tank top tackle!
Hero: There it is! Master's
kick-ass signature move!
Hero #2: The tank top tackle
has taken out tons of monsters!
Tank top tiger: Get him, master!
That bastard has no chance
against the likes of...
( Heroes gasping )
Tank top tiger: No way!
How is he still standing?!
Tank top blackhole:
Hey! Listen up!
You got lucky, freak!
Tank top master:
Who in the hell is this guy?
( Garou chuckles )
Tank top master:
Is he even human?
( Door slides open )
Man: Have you put
all your affairs in order?
Bang: I'm an old man,
alone in the world,
the same as you.
Bomb: Don't be ridiculous.
I'll have you know
I bid farewell
to several hundred disciples.
Bang: You cut ties
with everything you had
to come
to your younger brother's aid,
and, for that,
you have my thanks.
Bomb: Well, if we don't stop
that garou fellow,
he'll come after my dojo
soon enough.
Of course I came!
Bang: We must be careful
with this one, brother.
You cannot imagine
how fierce and powerful
that wretch
may have become by now.
Bomb: Certainly fierce enough
to call for my assistance.
Tank top tiger: Yeah!
Another tank top punch!
- How'd you like that?!
- Tank top blackhole: Whew!
When he survived
master's tackle,
I was scared for a second!
Hero #1: This won't
take long at all! Get him!
Tank top master:
One thing's for certain.
He is human.
But then, why?
Why are my senses telling me
to kill him here and now?
( Garou gags )
Tank top master: Enough.
- Garou: Huh?
- Tank top master: Time to die!
Mumen rider: No! Stop!
( Gags )
Tank top master:
Why'd you stop me?
( Mumen rider gasps )
Have you forgotten who you are?
A class-s hero on the verge
of killing a human?
You already won the fight!
We're supposed
to protect people!
Tank top tiger:
This bastard attacked a hero!
- It's his own damn fault!
- Blackhole: Stay out of it!
We'll teach him
not to mess with the tank tops.
Tank top master:
Pipe down. That's enough.
What he says is true.
I didn't earn the right
to wear the tank top of a hero
so I could do harm to humans.
Listen up.
Let this be a lesson
to never harm others again.
Garou: Yeah, all right.
I'm leaving.
Sorry for the trouble.
Like hell!
I'm gonna slaughter
every last one of you bitches!
Tank top master:
That's too bad, but expected.
You die right here, right now!
- ( Gags )
- Garou: Damn.
Looks like it slipped out.
I try to avoid using
the old geezer's style.
Eh, whatevs.
Tank top master: No way.
He was hiding his true strength?
Garou: Imagine that.
A class-s hero
down on his knees.
Tank top master:
Don't think you've won.
You caught me off guard is all.
- ( Groans )
- ( Garou laughs )
Shut up,
and stay right where you are.
You got a front-row seat
to see garou the monster
murder all your bros.
Tank top master: Garou? Oh, no!
He's that human
who calls himself a monster!
No, please! Don't do it!
Leave them alone!
Mumen rider: Justice crash!
♫
( gagging )
Garou: Now...
Which one of you is next?
( Heroes gasping )
( Tank top master roars )
Garou: That fighting style
of yours is pretty predictable.
( Tank top master gasps )
Garou: You're all done,
tank top master.
Right. All that's left
is a little cleanup.
Hero #1: You cocky scumbag!
Let's see how you do against
a whole legion of tank tops!
Hero #3: Damn you!
- ( Heroes gasp )
- ( Garou chuckles )
- ( Heroes gagging )
- ( Blows striking )
( Hero shrieks )
Charanko: That's enough, garou!
You're a disgrace to the dojo!
Take this!
Fist of flowing water crush...
Bang: It seems
we have arrived too late.
Bomb: Truly a horrible sight
to behold.
So tell me,
do you have any idea
what garou's next move might be?
What's wrong?
Bang: Charanko.
Hero: I heard a rumor
that the hero hunter
took down tank top master.
Hero #2: No way.
He defeated a class-s hero?
Hero #1: I heard
tank top's disciples
and mumen rider
were all beat to hell, too.
Hero #2: So he's hunting heroes
from class s and class c?
What are we supposed to do?
Hero #3: Come on. Show
a little backbone, will you?
How about the three of us
capture this "hero hunter"
ourselves?
Hero #2: Yeah, right.
Hero #1: He beat
a class-s, remember?
Hero #3: Yeah,
but think about it.
This dude
isn't some scary monster.
He's just a tough human being.
Hero #2: Yeah, but he learned
how to fight from silverfang.
Hero #3: Well, I happen to know
a little martial arts myself.
If an opponent comes at you
like this, deflect!
Attack from the front?
First you dodge, then punch!
And if he managed
to drop in on you from above,
- kapo--
- ( Hero #2 whimpers )
Hero #1: Hi, sir!
Mumen rider: I can't believe
you came all this way
to see me.
Thanks, man. I appreciate it.
Saitama: Sure. Picked up
some bananas on the way.
Mumen rider:
Ah, that sounds great.
Oh, they're for you, then.
Saitama: I read about
everything that happened
in the hero association
newsletter.
Mmm.
It said that dozens of heroes
were beaten by a single
butt-kicking monster.
Lucky you survived, huh?
Here. Have a banana.
Mumen rider:
It was a human that did it.
Saitama: What?
Mumen rider:
But he called himself a monster,
and he was tough as hell,
scary strong for a human being.
Saitama: Was he stronger
than that fish-monster thing
- we faced before?
- Mumen rider: Huh.
While deep sea king
was insanely tough,
this guy was different somehow.
Saitama: Oh?
Tank top master: His moves,
they're sophisticated
martial arts techniques.
It seems silverfang
raised a true monster
when he trained
that freakin' guy.
Saitama: Uh, who's this guy
that butted in
to our conversation?
Mumen rider: What?
That's tank top master,
- the class-s hero.
- Saitama: Oh, right!
He was in the newspaper.
It said he took
the worst beating of all.
( Tank top master scoffs )
At least say
that I put up
the best fight! Damn.
I never imagined
I'd lose to a punk like him.
Those martial arts he used
were brutal as hell.
Saitama: Martial arts?
- How 'bout a banana?
- Tank top master: Huh?
Uh, okay.
Saitama: So, this monster guy,
think maybe
you could give me the deets?
( Wind blows )
- Garou: Hey there, kid.
- Boy: Huh?
Garou: That's
an interesting-looking book
you got there.
( Heroes groaning )
Boy: This blonde guy is king.
He's a class-s hero.
He's the strongest ever.
And this is lightning genji,
a class-a hero.
I see him patrolling around
my neighborhood all the time.
I got his autograph. See?
( Garou laughs )
Yeah, so you did.
I want his autograph, too.
You think maybe
you could help me find him?
Boy: For sure.
So you're into heroes,
too, mister?
Garou: That hero almanac
is pretty cool.
Say, you think I could
borrow it for a week or so?
Boy: No way!
Get your own if you want one.
Garou: Don't be all stingy!
What's with these kids?
Whoa! Look at that!
It lists all the monsters, too.
Now, that's exciting.
Boy: What?
You like the monster pages?
But they're so scary. Uh...
Garou: The scarier, the better.
These guys are way cooler.
Boy: You're kidding.
That's some weird taste, mister.
Garou: Aw, man.
I wish I were listed
in this book.
Boy: You wanna be a hero?
Me, too. Same here,
but I suck at sports and stuff.
Garou: That's probably
for the best.
Boy: That really
wasn't very nice.
Garou: Well, it's patrol time.
I better get going.
According to that almanac,
golden ball from class a
shows up at his usual pub
around this time.
Catch you later, turd.
Boy: Be careful on patrol,
mister. See you.
Garou: I will. By the way,
don't call me "mister." Got it?
I'm not some old grandpa.
Boy: Huh? Sorry.
You say something, mister?
Garou: It's like that, huh?
Go home, runt.
Tank top master: He was fast.
He parried, sidestepped,
or slipped through
every attack I threw at him,
and he was able to read
any attempt I made
at throws and counters.
His moves reflect his opponent's
power back at double strength.
They target pressure points
and joints, any weaknesses.
Where he strikes, you suffer
a loss of physical function.
Most monsters rely on
their immense strength and size,
which they unleash
with extreme violence,
but garou is different.
His techniques are devised
for breaking humans.
In other words,
he's built for the sole purpose
of defeating heroes.
Saitama: Huh.
?
Saitama: Yeah.
Just feeling curious.
Thought I'd give it a shot.
Know anybody good? Uh, was it...
Chumpo?
Charanko:
It's charanko, damn it!
Saitama: Have a banana.
No hard feelings, okay?
Charanko: That's
a terrible place to put it!
( Sighs ) If you want help
learning martial arts,
you should ask master bang.
He seems to have
taken a liking to you, so--
saitama: Nah. I mean,
the old dude
might strain himself.
Charanko:
That's ageist and rude!
You can't just waltz
into a tournament
and challenge professionals.
First, you master
the basic forms.
No, may be best
to build stamina.
Running up and down a couple
hundred stairs would help.
Actually the dojo
could use a good cleaning.
Saitama: Look, if you don't
know anyone, just forget it.
Charanko: No! Wait a second!
- Saitama: Huh?
- Charanko: Just wait, okay?
There's a mixed-martial-arts
tournament I signed up for.
I'm pretty sure I still
have the admission ticket.
Here.
Saitama: It's all crumpled up.
Charanko: I registered to fight,
but I'm gonna have
to forfeit my spot.
This'll get you inside, though,
so take it,
and go watch the matches.
You'll get to observe
lots of fighting styles.
Saitama: Cool, man. Thanks.
( Echoing ) Staring.
You said you're
gonna forfeit, right?
Charanko: Well, yeah.
I'm injured.
Saitama: It says
the top prize is three million.
Charanko: Yeah.
I mean, it's a big tournament.
Saitama: Three million
is a nice chunk o' change.
Charanko: Just to be clear,
you can't enter
in someone else's place.
Hey. Are you listening?
Garou: You're the class-a hero,
golden ball, right?
Golden ball: Huh?
Garou: I'd like a word
with you, outside.
Golden ball:
I'm kinda drinking here.
Kick rocks.
What in the hell?!
Aw, man, you wasted it.
( Garou chuckles )
( Golden ball chuckles )
All right, then, tough guy.
There's a parking lot nearby.
We'll do it there.
- ( Footsteps shuffling )
- I've seen your kind before,
dweebs looking to take on
a professional hero.
( Groans )
If it's liquid courage
giving you brass balls,
better step off now.
While you can still walk,
that is.
Garou: Quiet down.
I'm not drunk.
But you're--
( gasps )
Bastard.
Golden ball:
Not too sharp, are you?
Some hero hunter.
How did tank top master lose
to a jerk-off like you?
See, I ain't too bad
at hunting, myself,
so I'll lay you out quick
and get me another beer!
Huh? ( Scoffs )
He read the trajectory
from my hand movement.
In that case,
try this on for size!
Rebound shot!
- ( Garou groans )
- Golden ball: Whoopsie.
You're lucky
nothing vital got hit.
So what do you think?
Ain't heroes incredible?
Garou: You think
that was just luck?
I'd say it's about
your coordination
being off
'cause you're hammered.
You're gonna wish you'd
finished me with that shot,
- 'cause now you're a dead man.
- Golden ball: Don't worry.
I got plenty of balls
left for you,
shape memory golden bullets!
Mode, multishot!
Killer move...
Golden breakout!
He's dodging all that
with minimal movement.
This guy's on another level.
Still, I got one last shot.
Better make it count!
( Gasps )
Garou: So what do you think?
Ain't monsters incredible?
It's over now.
Die.
Golden ball: Huh?
♫
Spring mustachio:
I didn't see you
in the pub for our rendezvous,
so I thought perhaps
you'd forgotten about our drink.
Garou: Class-a hero
spring mustachio. ( Scoffs )
Spring mustachio:
How kind of you to know.
And I presume you are
the much-rumored hero hunter.
Garou: We have a winner!
And your prize is that
you're gonna get crushed, too.
Golden ball: I managed
to injure his right leg,
so he'll be a little slow
on his footwork.
Spring mustachio: I see it.
Thank you
for the helpful information.
( Garou scoffs )
These are pretty tight quarters
for that pointy stick
you're waving around.
Spring mustachio:
Let's find out, shall we?
( Yelling )
Checkmate, old sport.
Hyah!
Tomboy!
Garou: Oh, yeah?
I think not!
( Spring mustachio groans )
- ( Gasping )
- Garou: Didn't you know?
Your fancy moves
are listed in the hero almanac.
Once I've got that info,
it's over.
Golden ball:
Listen up, you cocky dirtbag.
You've got the upper hand,
but even we managed to hurt you.
( Garou scoffs )
Oh, I'll be getting
much stronger.
If you think
you can take me down, go for it.
Until then,
I'll be as cocky as I want.
Woman: So the hero association
- makes lots of money, right?
- Man: Not true.
Don't talk nonsense, my dear.
It takes a lot of capital
to maintain peace around here.
We're not a for-profit company.
Woman: Then how were you able
- to buy me this?
- Man: Huh?
Woman #2: And you always
spend so much on us.
Man: Those are
just gestures for peace.
As a director
of the hero association,
having fun with you
is a necessary expenditure.
People like me who fight evil
on the front lines
must take every chance we get
to relax
if we're going to do our best.
Woman #1: "Relax," huh?
Do you need to "relax"
every day?
Man: Yes, I do.
Maybe next time,
I'll bring amai mask along.
- Woman #2: What?
- Woman #1: Are you serious?!
Woman #2: I'm, like,
his biggest fan!
Man: I'll introduce you
for a kiss on the cheek.
Woman #1: I don't know.
That seems kind of fishy.
Woman #2:
You really, really mean it?
Garou: Introduce him to me, too.
I'd be happy
to put a kiss on your cheek.
- ( Punch thumps )
- Woman #1: Come on. Just relax.
- ( Garou scoffs )
- Woman #2: It's for peace.
Garou: I was pumped after
hunting down those class as.
Now I feel
like I stepped in shit.
"Fighting evil
on the front line"?
What a load of crap.
Saitama: Oh, good. Finally.
- Garou: Hmm?
- Saitama: I've looked all day.
Garou: Was he tailing me?
Is he a hero, too?
Never seen that face before.
Probably some nobody
trying to climb the ranks
by catching a big fish like me.
But tables turn!
Saitama: Huh?
( Rumbling )
What's the big idea?
Tryin' to rob me?
Who do you think you are?
Don't bother me
when I'm shopping.
( Garou groans )
Saitama: Excuse me.
I'd like this one.
Clerk: 3,000 yen, please.
Saitama: Kinda steep,
don't you think?
( Singing in japanese )
♫
( wig rustles )
- Saitama: Not too shabby.
- Genos: Master...
- ( Saitama gasps )
- Genos: Has it come to that?
Saitama: Hey,
it's not like that!
I'm not planning to wear a wig
the rest of my life
or anything!
Genos: Hello, doctor?
Genos here.
There is an emergency.
No. It has to do with
master saitama's condition.
Those reinforced
artificial hair fibers,
is it possible for them
to be grafted into living skin?
Yes. It appears
necessary after all.
Black hair-fibers
are available, correct?
How soon would you be able
to perform
the implant procedure?
I see. Wednesday next week?
All right, then.
Yes, I, too, will be there.
Understood. Begin preparations.
Thank you, doctor.
Master saitama!
Are you available
anytime next wednesday?
Saitama: Look, you can't
transplant hair fibers
into someone's head
without asking.
I'm using this to enter
a fighting tournament...
As charanko.
( Genos gasps ) This is today.
Saitama: Yep!
Just kinda curious.
Gonna see what's up with all
this martial-arts stuff.