Gyoro-gyoro:
The hero association
has been greatly weakened
by our onslaught,
yet our greatest weapons
still await
their turn to participate.
The monster association's
overwhelming victory
is imminent,
o monster king orochi!
The question is,
now that they are off-balance,
how will
the hero association respond?
¶
¶ hero
( singing in Japanese )
¶ go, go
¶ hero
( singing in Japanese )
¶ go, go
¶ hero
( singing in Japanese )
¶ one punch
sourface: All right, charanko,
I'm gonna pound the true spirit
of martial arts into you.
Come at me!
Announcer: Oww! What can I say?!
Single-blow charanko!
Our four semifinalists
are now set!
Which one will take home
the championship?
- ( Wig rustles )
- ( Saitama sighs )
Wearing this thing
makes my head all itchy.
Sourface: What are you doing?!
You're up!
Huh?
Why are you holding
your head like that?
- You nervous or something?
- Saitama: Oh. Mm-hmm.
Sourface: Well,
if I hadn't dropped my guard
during our bout,
then I'd be the one
trying to keep from trembling
before the finals.
The semifinal you just missed
was incredible.
Suiryu won again,
and with a single kick!
And now you have
another dangerous guy to face.
He's the dark horse
of this whole tournament,
if you ask me.
Watch yourself
out there, charanko.
Saitama: He's acting
like a good mentor to me now,
but I'm not who he thinks I am.
¶
garou: Watchdog man.
It's time.
Just you and me.
- ( Crowd screaming )
- Man: Emergency!
A group of monsters
is attacking watchdog plaza!
Man 2: They're what?!
Man 3: Other cities
are reporting in
with monster attacks
as well, sir!
Monsters: 'Sup, bitches!
It's party time!
Amai mask: Hmm.
Hero: Stop!
Release those heroes!
Now you will face dogman!
¶
is that all your poison can do?
Monster: Oh. So you're
not a living creature.
Dogman: Well, now that
you've figured that out...
- Monster: Huh?
- Dogman: Self-destruct!
( Monster laughs )
The pup's pilot must be nearby.
Man 2: Where's
the antivenom serum for city y?
Man 1: There's still
no word on it yet, sir.
Man 2: Damn it.
Man 4: It'll be okay.
Class s is on the move.
( Weapon fires )
( Monster winces )
Drive knight: Monsters are
appearing simultaneously
in cities across the country.
The hero association
lacks intel.
- Choose.
- ( Monster whimpers )
Drive knight: My tactical
transformations cause your death
by maximum excruciation,
or you die quickly and easily
by revealing all you know.
Amai mask: You had the gall
to interrupt my concert.
Now you die.
- Monster: I found you.
- ( Child emperor gasps )
Monster: Sssso you're the one
controlling the robots.
Child emperor:
The toxin analysis is complete,
but my backpack's
all the way over there.
( Both gasp )
( Pig god chuckles )
Child emperor: Pig god!
Pig god: I heard explosions
and figured
I'd see if I could help.
Monster: Who interferes dies!
( Snakes hiss )
Child emperor: No!
She's poisonous!
I can cure it!
Huh?
( Pig god gobbling )
Child emperor: Eh?
Eh...
Wait! The venom could still--
( pig god slurps ) Huh?
No problem. Tasty.
- ( Belches )
- Child emperor: Uh...
Man 1: Child emperor has sent
the antivenom formula!
Man 4: Good. Now we can help
those who need it most.
Man 2: Those class-s heroes
are truly miracle workers.
Announcer: It's now time
for the second round
of our semi-finals!
This is a must-see matchup--
choze, whose relentless attacks
have demolished
every opponent he's faced,
versus charanko, who has won
every match with a single blow!
Choze: Who cares?
Anyone can finish an opponent
with one hit.
I execute my opponents
at a leisurely pace
to showcase
my infinite superiority.
My infallible genes
have been passed down to me
by the countless
generations of my bloodline.
I am their culmination,
a genetic masterpiece!
I exist as a superior breed
beyond mere homo sapiens.
Here, I declare my dominance
for all to see,
but ultimately
this world is mine to rule!
Saitama: You sure
are a chatterbox.
So you're kinda like
g.M.O. Corn or something?
Choze: I will murder you.
Your pain will be exquisite,
your eyes filled with tears,
your mouth contorted in pain!
Referee: Begin!
- ( Saitama yawns )
- Announcer: Unbelievable!
Another single-hit knockout!
With that, charanko advances
unscathed to the finals!
Saitama: The tournament's
already over?
Announcer: His power
seems to know no bounds!
( Jet engine roaring )
Man 1: We've lost contact with
the class-a heroes in city I!
Man 2: Get them backup!
Summon a class-s hero to--
- hero: Hold it!
- Man 2: Hmm?
Hero: I've been hiding
under the rubble...
Waiting for some reinforcements
to arrive.
Some class-a heroes
are now on the scene.
With these numbers,
we can handle this.
- Flashy flash: No. You'll fail.
- ( Heroes gasp )
Flashy flash: To fight a foe
with inadequate force
only heightens the damage
done to one's self.
Hero: Are you saying
we're inadequate?
Flashy flash:
Just shut up, and watch.
( Heroes gasp )
¶
Hero: So that's class-s power.
Heroes: Whoa!
Smile man: Don't you think
this is causing
even greater damage?!
Huh?! Whoa!
( Hero 1 grunts )
Smile man: You stop it?
Hero 1: All I did
was piss it off.
( Groans )
¶
flashy flash:
I'll have to go all out.
( Gasps )
- Hmm?
- ( Heroes gasp )
Smile man: Over there!
Hero 1: That's terrible tornado!
( Woman vocalizing )
( Tornado chuckles )
( Heroes scream )
¶
tornado: Hey! You there!
Why are you all standing around
like a bunch of idiots
when we're
so obviously shorthanded?!
Smile man: We were fighting
the octopus when--
tornado: I don't wanna hear it!
You especially, flashy flash.
I thought you were
supposed to be class s,
but now I'm not so sure!
Flashy flash: Hmm.
Tornado: Useless morons.
Flashy flash: Tough talk
from the airheaded woman
who dropped in
to steal my kill!
- Yeah, that's right.
- ( Smile man wailing )
- Flashy flash: You better run.
- Hero 3: What if she hears you?
You're gonna get
all of us in trouble!
( Flashy flash scoffs )
You forget yourself.
Hero 1: We couldn't
do a damn thing.
Gyoro-gyoro: As I predicted,
these class-s heroes
are most troublesome.
Orochi: It matters not.
We can make
any number of monsters.
Atomic samurai:
I'm sure you're all aware
of why I asked you to come.
It involves garou,
the hero hunter.
A search is under way.
Silverfang is
pursuing him, but...
It's possible garou
might defeat the old man.
Granted, silverfang
is highly skilled,
but he's facing
a former student.
He might go easy on the boy.
Therefore, we of
the holy order of the sword
will find garou first
and kill him.
We need numbers
to make that happen.
I am asking for your help.
You four are among the strongest
swordsmen in the order.
Swordsman: He must
be quite a threat
for you to ask such a thing
very well.
I'll send out my disciples.
Atomic samurai: Amahare.
Swordsman:
You were right to come to us.
- I will lend my blade.
- Atomic samurai: Zanbai.
Swordsman: You can consider it
as good as done.
Atomic samurai: Nichirin.
Thank you all.
I appreciate everyone's--hmm?
( Swordsman laughs )
You want the holy order
of the sword on crime watch?
Atomic samurai: Haragiri.
Haragiri: Our aim
is to achieve true skill.
Improving our art
is the only thing
that concerns the holy order.
Nichirin: I think you've had
quite too much to drink.
- Let's--
- haragiri: Silence.
I wasn't done
speaking my mind yet.
I've brought something special
( all gasp )
Haragiri: Monster cells.
By incorporating them
into your body,
you obtain power
beyond human limitations!
( All gasp )
Haragiri: Now we can
be monsters ourselves.
Zanbai: He's gone insane.
Amahare: Where'd you get these?
Haragiri: The monsters
have joined together
and formed
their very own association,
and they approached me
with an offer.
By surrendering my humanity,
I was allowed to join them
and was given strength
beyond the limits of this flesh.
Atomic samurai:
Oh, tell me you didn't.
Haragiri: I did!
I am no longer a mere human.
The power flowing through me
is incredible!
Now you all
must become monsters as well!
( Swordsmen gasp )
Atomic samurai:
You've lost your way, haragiri.
( Haragiri laughs )
With my quick draw talent,
you know I could behead
all four of you at once!
Anyone who refuses will die.
Atomic samurai: Unfortunate.
Haragiri: It is unfortunate,
atomic samurai,
for I was instructed
to kill you, regardless.
You have three seconds. Join me!
Devour the monster cells!
3, 2, 1...
Atomic samurai: Think not.
The rest of us
aren't fools like you.
( Birds chirping )
We're going.
But we have a new target,
the monster association.
Announcer: It's time!
Welcome to the super fight
final match!
The seedings had charanko
as an overwhelming underdog,
but from what we've seen,
we might have an incredible
upset on our hands!
( Crowd cheering )
Announcer: By the sound of it,
the fans in the stadium
know they're in
for something special here,
but this man's determination
remains unfazed!
It seems unthinkable that he'd
struggle against anyone!
Suiryu
of the dark corporeal fist
versus the underdog charanko!
Saitama: Why's he staring?
Does he know this is a rug?
Announcer: Who will
emerge victorious?
Ooh! Look at suiryu's smirk!
Has he sensed his opponent
is outclassed?
Charanko seems to be trying
to hide his nervousness
by looking like
a complete doofus!
Saitama: This is
how I always look.
Referee: Get ready!
Suiryu: Charanko,
let's have fun.
- Saitama: Huh?
- Referee: Begin!
Announcer: Here we go,
fight fans!
Saitama: Hey!
Announcer: Suiryu takes
an early offensive,
but, for some reason,
he stops just short of contact!
Announcer: He's attacking
with incredible speed!
Saitama: Since it's the finals,
I wanted to see his moves,
but that wind is a pain.
Is he doing that on purpose?
Suiryu: What's the matter?
I know you can see it coming.
Announcer: A flurry of kicks,
but he's stopping just short
every time!
All charanko can seem to do
is guard his head.
Has he already lost
the will to fight?
Suiryu: The ring announcer
is clueless.
I was just getting warmed up.
Hey, you're strong.
I can tell.
We're cut from the same cloth.
Saitama: Hmm?
So he's not just trying
to blow the wig off?
Suiryu: It's your eyes.
They don't seek rank or glory.
Your eyes are looking
for something fun.
Saitama: Well...
You might be right.
Suiryu: So, what was it
that brought you
to enter this tournament?
I'm in it to bag
that prize money.
Saitama:
That's what I want, too.
Suiryu: And one more reason.
I'm always on the lookout
for challenging opponents
to go up against.
Of course, in the end,
I am gonna win,
but the process
is still fun, you know?
Saitama: Fun, you say? Huh.
Suiryu: Yeah.
It's fun being strong.
Saitama: I see.
Suiryu: Hmm?
Saitama: I came here,
because I wanted
to experience martial arts.
I heard the fighters here
were strong,
but if I fought back,
even a little,
the match was over.
Zakkos: They've been
chitchatting for a while.
Sourface: They're probably
talking about the long hard road
they each took to get here.
Saitama: I was starting to think
coming here was a waste of time,
but thankfully
you seem different.
( Suiryu chuckles )
I see.
Then, how about
we do it this way?
I will provide
your martial arts experience,
and you simply do your best
to make our match fun for me.
Saitama: Oh! Now we're talking.
Suiryu: Okay, then.
Shall we begin?
Here goes!
¶
announcer: That was
even faster than before!
Suiryu is getting serious
about this match!
Suiryu: I won't let up!
Announcer:
Charanko's been launched!
Saitama: Still on.
Announcer: Ouch! Down he goes!
What an incredibly
brutal attack!
Will charanko be able
to stand up after that?
Sourface: Charanko, no!
Zakkos: Too late.
He never stood a chance.
Suiryu: Did I go
too hard on you?
Saitama: I'll admit
that last one had me scared.
Suiryu: Eh?
Saitama: I thought for sure
my wig was coming off.
( Suiryu chuckles ) All right.
This is the fight
I've been waiting for!
Sourface: Man,
he's really hanging in there!
If he keeps this up,
he might have a chance.
- Lightning Max: No.
- Sourface: Hmm?
Lightning Max:
Take a closer look at suiryu.
He's only been using
leg techniques.
Snek: He's holding back
and just toying with his prey.
Sourface: Are you saying...
Lightning Max: This match
is about to get real ugly.
Suiryu: Your weapon
is that punch of yours, right?
Let me have it!
You said you'd
make it fun for me.
( Saitama gasps )
Suiryu: He read that I was
going for a countermove.
He may be a white belt, but he
has real fight experience.
Protecting his head like that
shows sharp instincts.
Tell me, what do you do
for your day job?
Saitama: My job?
Uh, I go for walks,
defeat monsters,
stuff like that.
Suiryu: What?
You're out fighting monsters?
That sounds a lot like
the kind of thing heroes do.
Saitama: Well, I figured
I might be a hero someday,
so it's kind of like research.
( Suiryu sighs ) Another one
aiming to become a hero.
Doesn't seem like a job
for a quality fighter.
I fought
a few class-a heroes earlier,
but it was underwhelming.
They were so weak.
They're heroes in name only.
They just flaunt
virtue and justice
to make people feel
protected and grateful.
At their level,
no matter how hard they try,
they're not
gonna save the world.
These fine intentions,
noble thoughts, lofty morals,
and heroic justice
only serve
as a layer of impurities,
creating boredom
in the life of fun that I seek.
You're obviously strong like me,
so why not live
the free and easy life
and not worry about that crap?
Huh? What'd I say?
I offer advice because I see
you're one of the strong,
but--( Grunts )
Announcer: A clean hit!
Uh, what?
Saitama: Impurities?
What's that got to do with it?
You're not the only one
doing what he wants to do.
Suiryu, was it?
Here's a little advice from me.
If you just wanna have fun,
I suggest you don't get
any stronger.
( Crowd gasps )
Saitama: Aww, man,
why do I keep doing that?
I almost ended it
too quick again.
( Suiryu gasps )
Man: Did you see that?!
Announcer:
Wh-what the heck happened?!
I-I can't believe this!
Charanko is at the center
of a shocking development!
In the middle of the match,
he was outed as wearing a wig!
The referee is conferring
with the judges.
What could this mean?
Referee: Uh, we have a ruling.
After the wolfman incident
that occurred
in the last tournament,
a new mandate was written
that went into effect
at the start
of this competition.
Masks and other head coverings
are strictly prohibited.
His wig has been ruled
a head covering.
Therefore,
charanko is disqualified!
Announcer: Whoa!
And, just like that,
the match has been decided!
Suiryu is our champion!
- ( Crowd murmuring )
- Man 2: What a joke!
Man 3: Let 'em fight!
Sourface: Charanko.
All this time,
you've been hiding away
your shameful condition.
Zakkos: Actually,
he's an imposter.
Snek: Saitama? Why is he here?
Lightning Max: Wait.
Do you know this guy?
Referee: We'll confirm later
that you're who you claim to be.
Saitama: Time to go.
- Suiryu: Playtime's over.
- Saitama: Eh?
Suiryu: Now it's time
to fight for real.
( Joints crack )
Referee: Huh?!
¶
suiryu: I'm not stopping!
I haven't shown you
what I can really do!
Announcer:
The ring split in two!
Suiryu: You're not
going anywhere!
Announcer: Wh-wh-what?!
The two of them
are still fighting!
Saitama: Weren't we
having fun, though?
Suiryu: There's nothing fun
about losing!
Man 4: Whoo! Hell, yeah!
That's right! Keep going!
Announcer: And the crowd
just cannot get enough of this!
Suiryu is attacking
like a man possessed!
I've never seen him
like this before!
Suiryu: Now you will understand.
This is martial arts!
Dark body flying dragon fist!
Announcer: He's kicking!
He's punching,
unleashing pure fury!
There's no stopping him!
Suiryu: What the hell?
I'm not getting to him.
Announcer: The ring cracked!
Lightning Max:
That power stance.
He's gonna kill him.
Sourface: Get away!
( Suiryu yells )
What? No way!
Saitama: I think
I'm finally beginning to get it.
Suiryu: How was that?
Understand what martial arts
are all about now?
Saitama: Yes, I believe I do.
They're fighting moves
that make you look awesome.
Suiryu: How...
Shallow!
After everything I threw at you,
that's your conclusion?!
Saitama: I might just try
that spinny thing.
Defeating a monster like that
would be totally sweet.
Thanks, dude.
( Suiryu growls )
Don't mock me!
Saitama: Oh.
Announcer: And suiryu
gets booted with a hip attack!
- Saitama: Oops.
- ( Crowd laughing )
Saitama: Come on.
That was so not cool-looking.
Referee 2: All right, guys!
Let's grab him!
Saitama: Uh-oh.
Security: He's making
a run for it! Stop him!
Security 2:
Block the back exit!
Security 3: Catch him!
Suiryu: For the first time
in my life...
I lost.
¶
( singing in Japanese )
genos: I was defeated.
I stood no chance.
Among the enemy are monsters
beyond anything seen before
( footsteps rumbling )
¶