( Suiryu groans )
Saitama: I heard
your call for help.
I'm here to answer it.
( Suiryu gasping )
Saitama:
You fought hard on your own.
Let me take care of the rest.
¶
Suiryu: I know that head.
¶ hero
( singing in Japanese )
¶ go, go
¶ hero
( singing in Japanese )
¶ go, go
¶ hero
( singing in Japanese )
¶ one punch
¶
bakuzan: A hero?
You, little man?! ( Laughs )
You've gotta be shitting me!
( Laughs ) More like a puny runt
out to make a name for himself.
Pathetic! You have no idea
how outclassed you are,
chrome-dome!
You're nothing but a--
wait. ( Gasps )
( Wails )
Saitama: Hey, hold up.
Do I know you, or--
bakuzan: Shut your face!
This time around,
bakuzan the monster
will be the victor!
My deathblows are
about to rain down upon you!
Art of darkness hell killer!
Demon sweeper low kick!
¶
saitama: You guys, too, huh?
Bakuzan: I can't believe
you're still standing.
Impressive,
but, after that blow,
you've seen the unimaginable
difference in our strength.
Bear killer mid-kick!
Suiryu: Is he
protecting the injured?
He'll be slaughtered.
Hey! You gotta
protect yourself!
Bakuzan: Carnage punch!
( Laughs )
I'll give you one last chance
to apologize for our match.
( Laughs )
( Sighs ) Party pooper.
Must have gone into shock
or something.
Time to end this.
I'll get rid of all of you
in one fell swoop!
Hell-bringin' hand chop!
Saitama: Nope,
I just don't remember him.
( Suiryu gasps )
Saitama: No idea who that was.
Meh.
¶
- ( suiryu gasps )
- Saitama: Man, that must have
really sucked for you
after winning the tournament.
Well, maybe, next time,
there'll be
less monsters around.
Suiryu: Uh, yeah,
and thanks for saving me
and everything.
Tell me, who are you,
I mean, really?
Saitama: I'm saitama.
I'm a hero.
Suiryu: Saitama? So...
That means charanko
was just an alias, wasn't it?
Saitama: Uh, crap.
Suiryu: I don't get it.
What were you doing here?
Some undercover mission
for the hero association?
Saitama: No. I wanted
to experience martial arts
and bag that prize money.
There's this guy
calling himself a hero hunter.
They say
he's a martial arts master,
so it kinda piqued my interest,
you know?
Suiryu: I see. You were looking
for ways to counter him.
Saitama: Well, I wouldn't
exactly say that was the reason.
I just happened upon
an entry ticket.
And, to be completely honest...
- ( Music stops )
- I was bored.
Suiryu:
You've gotta be kidding me.
Still,
it's thanks to you I'm alive.
Saitama: Sorry I
didn't get here sooner.
- Suiryu: Wait! Saitama...
- Saitama: Huh?
Suiryu: Please,
you shouldn't go out there.
There's this group raising hell.
They call themselves
the monster association,
and they're bad news.
- Saitama: For real?
- Suiryu: Yeah.
And what's worse
is that they have the ability
to transform humans
into monsters, too.
That guy you just beat
was one of them.
Remember bakuzan,
your second match?
Saitama: Oh,
so that's who he was.
I mean, it's hard for me
to remember
every opponent I punch.
Suiryu: The point is, it's
dangerous out there right now.
I think it's best if we lay low.
Goketsu's out there.
We should avoid him.
Saitama: Goketsu?
Suiryu: Another monster
that used to be human.
I threw everything I had at him,
but it didn't do a damn thing.
That strength, it was horrific.
( Rotors whirring )
Genos: When my repairs are done,
I must return at once.
Even if he caught me off-guard,
a monster that can beat me
with one punch
must not be allowed to survive.
I need to assemble
the class-s heroes
with master saitama,
then strike together.
Saitama: So this guy's
pretty strong, huh?
Suiryu: Even with
the most meticulous preparation,
I'm not sure
if anyone can beat him.
Saitama: I see.
So where did this monster go?
Suiryu: Um, through that wall.
Saitama: Ah.
So all that noise earlier
was him, huh?
I'll check it out.
Suiryu: No!
Weren't you listening to me?
I told you! He's unstoppable!
Saitama: I heard you. No prob.
Suiryu: You still
don't get it, do you?!
Goketsu was once a famous
and exceptional martial artist.
He's dangerous.
You'll be killed for sure!
Saitama: Whoa.
A martial arts master, huh?
Perfect. It might help
my indigestion.
- ( Suiryu groans )
- Saitama: Uh...
Hey, you're injured.
Take it easy.
Suiryu: I'm not letting go.
I won't let you throw away
your life when I owe you mine!
( Groaning )
¶
( crying )
( Grunts )
I just couldn't stop him.
( Sighs )
( Boom )
- I think I get it now.
- ( Booming continues )
I finally understand
what it means to be a true hero!
And now he's going
to throw his life away.
What a waste.
Saitama was destined
to save so many more people.
( Crying )
( Gasps )
Saitama: Oh, by the way,
there's something
I forgot to mention earlier.
That thing about me lying
to get into the tournament,
( whispering )
Could we keep it a secret?
Suiryu: Uh...
So was goketsu
tough to take down?
Saitama: Well, when they
only take one punch,
it's kinda hard to compare.
Suiryu: There's something else
I want to ask you.
Saitama: What's up?
Suiryu: I don't know
if I could overcome my fear,
but I'd like to try,
and, if I did,
do you think
I can become a hero?
- Saitama: I don't know.
- Suiryu: Huh?
Saitama: But, you know,
if I became one,
then I think maybe anybody can.
It's natural
to be afraid at the start.
I mean, before I got too strong,
I was scared, too.
Suiryu: A hero who's too strong?
Not bad. Not bad.
Oh! Can I ask you
another question, saitama?
- Saitama: Sure.
- ( Suiryu chuckles )
Could I be your disciple?
( Saitama chuckles )
Absolutely not.
¶
puri-puri prisoner: Damn it.
His whole body's
covered in spikes.
How do I fight him?
Man: Prisoner!
Don't use your hands on him!
Man 2: Use your ball and chain
to pound him senseless!
Man 1: Yeah!
Make him hug your ball!
Puri-puri prisoner:
Hmm? I thank you
for your words
of encouragement, gentlemen.
You'll get kisses
of gratitude later,
but, for now,
I must insist that you flee!
Man 3: No use.
He can't hear a word.
Man 1: So, does he have
to fight completely naked, or...
Puri-puri prisoner:
You fresh-faced boys so bravely
cheering me on like this,
your love will not be forgotten!
Love! ( Gasps )
That's it. That's the answer.
I can accept the pain
with love so deep
there will be
nothing left to fear!
( Monster groans )
Puri-puri prisoner: Angel hug!
- ( Cracking )
- ( Monster screaming )
Puri-puri prisoner: Love!
Man 4: He keeps staring at us...
Bloody and naked.
( Cell phone buzzing )
Puri-puri prisoner: Yes, hello.
You've got puri-puri.
What?
It broke into my comfy,
cozy home and stole my honeys?
- ( Crack )
- And where is this monster now?
- Saitama: They're gone?
- Hero: Yeah.
They all left together
about 30 minutes ago.
Saitama: So they
arrived as a group,
went crazy,
and then left all at once?
What were they up to?
Damn it. How did I miss
such a huge disaster?
The other heroes
were out here fighting.
Man, what was I thinking?
Crushing monsters
is my job, right?
( Grunts ) Wait a second.
I don't fight monsters
just because I wanted a job.
That's not it at all.
I might have forgotten
something important,
like the reason I became a hero
in the first place
I mean, I started out
just having fun,
but, since joining
the hero association,
I've been bored out of my mind.
That hero-hunter guy
got me curious again.
That's the reason I entered
the martial arts tournament.
But, against suiryu
and the others,
even against a monster
who was a master martial artist,
I didn't really feel anything.
I didn't get
anything out of it.
- ( Brakes squeal )
- King: Saitama. Hey.
Saitama: Hmm?
Hey, king.
( Wind blowing )
Are you sure
it's safe to be out here?
King: Well, I heard
all those alarms going off,
but it seems to be
pretty quiet now.
What's wrong?
You look kinda bummed.
Saitama: I, uh--
I got a lot on my mind.
King: I get it,
but, hey, you're still young.
- Don't go giving up yet.
- Saitama: Thanks, man.
King: I mean,
there's still a decent chance
it might grow back. Plus, uh,
there are treatments--
saitama: Whoa, whoa! Wait a sec!
That's not
what I'm talking about!
It's more
of a big-picture thing.
King: Ah, gotcha.
But being down isn't like you.
You're always so strong.
Saitama: Well, I'm not
gonna be getting any stronger.
- I know that much.
- King: What?
Saitama: I'm saying
I've become too strong.
No matter who I fight,
I don't feel anything.
I gain nothing from it.
There's nothing
I can learn from anyone,
- so what's the point?
- King: I don't know, man.
This is just me talking,
but isn't having
that much strength
kind of awesome?
Saitama: Maybe, but...
Not having any room
to learn and grow
means there's no way for me
to enjoy the process
of learning and growing.
No matter
how many enemies I face
or monsters I defeat,
I'm just bored out of my mind.
I never thought being a hero
could be so lonesome.
King: So you feel lonely,
saitama?
Saitama: Guess I do.
King: There's a ballroom
dance school near the station
you could check out,
if you want.
Saitama: Why would I do that?
King: If you're lonely,
you could make some new friends.
Saitama: No, that's not
exactly what I'm talking about.
King: What, then?
Saitama: It's kinda
hard to explain.
I'm not interested,
and I don't have
much time these days.
King: Well,
once things settle down,
how about taking a trip
for a change of pace?
Saitama: A trip? Hmm.
There's not really
anywhere I wanna go.
( King sighs )
Good grief, dude.
You say you're bored and you're
looking for some excitement,
but then you won't take on
any new challenges or anything.
There was a time
I felt that way, too.
- ( Saitama gasps )
- King: Listen to me.
Life is simply
a journey to nowhere.
If you want a change of scenery,
you need to get there
your own way.
Saitama: This is
starting to sound hokey.
King: It seems to me
you've got this all wrong.
You think being strong means
you've reached your destination.
I doubt the path
to becoming a hero
comes to an end with such
a cut-and-dried finish line.
( Saitama groans )
Are you trying to lecture me?
It's not like
you're some veteran hero.
King: It's inherently wrong
to go into a fight
seeking satisfaction
from the fight itself.
Battling with great courage,
working to benefit society,
isn't that what it means
to be a hero?
Saitama:
What's with the philosophy?
King: If that ideal
is your goal, you've just begun.
There's a long road to walk
before you become
the strongest hero.
( Saitama gasps ) That's true.
King: Which means
that the pursuit
of that ideal still remains.
Within you, saitama,
there is a great deal
of unrealized potential.
If that's true, to say
that you've already reached
the limit of your growth,
well, that starts to sound
shallow and arrogant,
now, doesn't it?
Saitama: That's deep.
( King clears throat )
What does it actually take
to be the ultimate hero?
Is it an unwavering
sense of justice?
The courage
to face any hardship?
Until you've found the answer
to that question,
how can you say you feel bored?
Those are
my thoughts on it, anyway.
Plus I read it in a manga.
Saitama: Wow.
You just blew my mind
the "ultimate hero."
Maybe I should be thinking
about what that truly means.
Honestly, that might
make me even more bored.
King: If you're
really that bored,
then wanna come over
and play some games?
Saitama: Nah, that's totally
not what I'm feeling right now.
I'm numb, and nothing's
gonna change that.
King: Come on. It'll take
your mind off things, dude.
Sometimes you wanna lose, right?
So I'll let you lose.
Saitama: Ha ha!
You can't trick me.
Besides, it's not
like I'd get upset
just because I lost some game.
Yep, I feel totally
emptied out right now.
King: Yeah? Tell you what.
Just to keep things fair,
how 'bout I play
with one finger from each hand?
Saitama: That's it, jerk-off!
I'm gonna crush your ass
this time!
¶
garou: I never thought
he'd be the one to beat me.
His speed and power
were exceptional.
It was far more
than I'd bargained for.
I was lucky just to get away.
Martial arts
designed for human opponents
were a poor match against
his four-legged fighting style.
That was a good lesson.
( Chuckles )
This is the freaking best.
I know I can become
so much stronger.
¶
huh? Is that...
Yeah, it's him.
I won't get a second chance.
My body can handle it.
The pain is gone.
In fact, I'm so stoked,
I'm drowning in power.
King, prepare to be hunted!
What will his first move be?
I can't wait to find out!
Here goes! Get ready to die!
King: Huh?
( Rubble falling )
Saitama: That dude was trying
to attack you. You know him?
King: Nope.
Never seen that guy before.
Saitama: Fighting monsters
is bad enough.
Now we gotta fight hoodlums,
too? Give me a break.
That reminds me, have you
heard about everything going on?
King: What are
you talking about?
Saitama: I don't know
all the details,
but monsters
are rampaging like crazy,
and there's some guy out there
calling himself a hero hunter?
It's been pretty busy lately.
King: Sounds like it.
Saitama: That hero-hunter dude
- does have me kinda curious
- king: Yeah?
Saitama: As far as I know,
there's never been a human
who calls himself
a monster before.
Reminds me of my early days,
when I was calling myself a hero
and doing my own thing.
So I'm hoping
he lives up to his claim.
He might even
be stronger than me, you know?
King: Might be.
Hope you run into him soon.
¶
Sonic: Show yourself.
Who are y--
two of them.
You fools came and attacked me,
so I assume you're ready to die!
Man: "Attacked"?
That sounds so unfriendly.
Man 2: Wouldn't you agree,
speed-o'-sound Sonic,
last surviving member
of the final 44?
( Sonic gasps )
Wait. You're from the village?
Man 2: We're of the golden 37.
I am tempest wind.
Man 1: I am hellfire flame.
Sonic:
What's your business with me?
Tempest wind: To recruit you.
Interested in doing
something big?
Sonic: How big are you talking?
Tempest wind: Listen.
We're planning on taking over
this little planet.
We'll conquer it as monsters
who transcend mankind.
Hellfire flame: There's
a new group for monsters only.
It's called
the monster association.
Tempest wind and I are members.
We plan on flipping
this entire world on its head.
Sonic: Sounds like
a bunch of horseshit to me.
Where would I fit in
to all this?
Tempest wind:
We want to be certain
that we can take down
flashy flash. You could help.
Sonic: Sure I could,
but I'm not interested
in helping or your stupid games.
Get lost,
unless you prefer to die.
Tempest wind: Let's give him
a taste of what we can do.
Hellfire flame: We said,
"monster association," remember?
That's because...
Tempest wind: We are monsters!
You can be a monster, too.
Hellfire flame: It is better
than any enhancement drug
or mere implant.
( Sonic shuddering )
Tempest wind: The thought
of getting stronger
tempts you, doesn't it?
This is a monster cell.
All you have to do to transform
is ingest it.
Here. You can have this one.
The monster association awaits.
Sonic: No matter
how hard I train,
I see no path
that ends in me beating him.
I'd pay any price
to defeat saitama,
but now that price
is giving up my humanity.
When I lost to him,
I felt as if
there were no difference
between life and death,
and I have no attachments
to my human self.
Saitama, I've decided
to be a monster.
Woman: A few monsters
remain in some areas,
so we can't lift
the evacuation order just yet.
Man: It has been
one hell of a day.
Woman: The toughest of those
remaining is martial gorilla.
He seems obsessed
with his own threat level
and declares he'll keep fighting
until he's raised to demon.
Man: City w, huh?
Have the heroes nearby
surround the city.
- Zombieman: No need.
- Man: Huh?
Zombieman:
Don't bother sending in
a bunch of fresh meat.
It's a waste of resources.
Man: Zombieman?!
Zombieman: Just leave
everything to me.
Man: R-Roger!
Zombieman: Time to get to work.
Martial gorilla: Hey!
Now where the hell did all...
Zombieman: If I'm reading
this situation right
these attacks were masterminded
by something organized.
He's not paying attention.
Perhaps I could track him
back to his lair
martial gorilla: Hmm?
Well, there's
a sturdy-looking fellow.
Zombieman: Drat.
He's going after a citizen.
Martial gorilla:
Are you a pro hero, big guy?
Armored gorilla: Sorry?
Martial gorilla:
Holy crap! A gorilla!
Armored gorilla: Yeah,
and you're a gorilla, too.
Martial gorilla:
What are you, anyway,
some freelance monster?
Armored gorilla: What the hell
are you talking about?
I'm just out running errands
and buying groceries.
Martial gorilla:
You're out shopping?
What kind of monster
pretends to live like a human?
You're a disgrace
to gorilla monsters.
Armored gorilla: Uh, I'm not
sure what I should say here.
Martial gorilla:
I see you as a potential enemy,
so you have to die! ( Gasps )
( Groans )
Armored gorilla: Take
your weird issues elsewhere.
Zombieman: Changing target.
I'm following him instead
bomb: We've been
searching all day,
but, in the end,
all we accomplished
was disposing of some monsters,
though I do understand
that's your day job, of course.
A question for you--
in the midst of all
this panic and chaos,
is it possible some hero
or monster got to garou?
Bang: No, that's not
what happened, brother.
Garou is many things,
but weak is not one of them.
- ( Bomb sighs )
- Bang: I trained him.
That's why it's
my responsibility to defeat him.
Garou...
Do you know what it means
to become a monster?
If you're going down
into darkness,
at least let it be at my hands.
Bomb: It seems
the sun will be setting soon.
Man: We've received a vital
report from drive knight.
It concerns
this monster association.
They are our new enemy.
While their objectives
are uncertain,
they're clearly positioning
themselves as our rivals,
implementing a method for
turning humans into monsters.
Their leader is known
as the "monster king," orochi.
We've also received
the approximate location
of their lair. It's city z's
abandoned ghost town.
Man 2: The area
that was taken by the monsters.
Man 3: This monster association
went through a lot of trouble
to kidnap an executive's son.
Perhaps it means
they want to negotiate.
Man 4: Yes.
It's their way of saying,
"don't try anything stupid."
Perhaps they're hoping
they can talk their way
out of extermination.
Anything's possible.
Man 3: There's a thought.
If the ghost town monsters
formed some sort of coalition,
that would add up.
Sitch: The kidnapping,
the riots, the chaos,
everything that happened
could have been
their way of staging a protest.
These aren't random acts.
These monsters possess
the intellect and will
to act as a group.
I feel the likelihood
that they will reach out to us
is extremely high.
Man 2: That's not
a bad strategy.
We could end this,
approach them as a ruse,
then wipe them out.
Woman: Let's hear
what they have to say first.
Our primary objective remains
the safe return of the hostage.
Man 5: Correct.
Esteemed advisor narinki
is by far one of our top donors.
If anything happened to his son,
he would surely cut us off.
The boy must be rescued. Hmm?
Man 6: We've received a message
from the monster association!
We've received a message
Sitch: What is it?
Man 6: We've received
a message...
Man 4: Tell us!
Man 5: I think
something's wrong with him.
Man 6: We've received a message
from the monster association.
We've received a message--
( Screams )
Monster: I said
we've received a message
from the monster association.
( Sizzling )
¶
Sonic: I'm sure it was the right
call to cook this thing.
Common sense says it's not safe
to eat meat like this
while it's still raw.
I'll try not to think about it.
( Laughs )
I'm coming for you, saitama.
Watch your back.
¶