Man: You've lost contact
with metal bat?
Man 2: Yes.
I've already put out a call
for backup,
all class-a heroes and above.
Man 3: Centichoro,
the gigantic bug monster,
threat level dragon. Thoughts?
Woman: It's like
a force of nature.
Man 3: This far exceeds
what happened two years ago.
We may not have the numbers
to defeat a monster like this.
Woman: King is engaged
in another battle somewhere,
but what of
the other class-s heroes?
- ( Alarms blaring )
- ( Telephones ringing )
Man 1: Multiple
emergency calls coming in.
( Gasps )
What's happening?
( Rumbling )
Mohican: Damn it.
It's got us cornered!
Pineapple:
If we don't do something quick,
we're dead!
Mohican: Aw, crap!
Pineapple: Look!
It's metal knight!
Mohican: There's our backup!
( Laughs )
Metal Knight: You're in the way.
A weapons test is not
some spectacle. Clear the area!
Heroes: Oh! Sorry, sir!
Metal Knight: Not a scratch.
For a biologic, its armor
is remarkably resistant.
( Centichoro growls )
Pineapple: Is that giant bug
still after us?
Mohican: I think metal knight is
trying to keep it off our backs.
Pineapple: That's good for us,
but what about metal bat?
( Both gasp )
( Monster laughs )
You in a hurry, heroes?
You can't escape!
Monster 2:
Hand those two over now!
Heroes: Monsters?!
( Monsters laugh )
Monster 3: Let's see.
The report said that metal bat
was going head-to-head
with centichoro.
Where is he? What is he doing?
Man 1: This is unprecedented.
Monsters of threat level demon
and above
are appearing simultaneously
in every city!
Our response teams
are being overwhelmed!
It's too much.
We can't keep up!
¶
¶ hero
( singing in Japanese )
¶ go, go
¶ hero
( singing in Japanese )
¶ go, go
¶ hero
( singing in Japanese )
¶ one punch
¶
( metal bat groans )
Garou: Guess you
were worn down already.
I wanted to see
how tough you were,
but I won't get a true taste,
since you're running on fumes.
Metal bat: Shut your mouth!
¶
Garou: All that blood loss.
I don't even know how
you're able to stay conscious.
On top of that, a bunch
of your bones are broken.
Is it hero pride
that keeps you standing?
( Gasps )
( Metal bat roars )
Garou: His swings
are coming faster?
( Metal bat yells )
Garou: More powerful, too.
That shouldn't be possible.
But that's
exactly what's happening.
( Metal bat yells )
Garou: With every hit he takes,
every time he gets hurt,
he becomes physically stronger.
How do you even make sense?
Metal bat: Screw makin' sense.
It's about fighting spirit.
Garou: Is he for real?
Metal bat: Let's get this show
on the road, "hero hunter."
I still got a giant centipede
to beat the crap out of.
Garou: This guy's a nut-bag.
Just how long's
that fighting spirit gonna last?
Either way, I'm game.
¶
- ( yells )
- Metal bat: Hmm?
- Huh?
- Garou: Over here!
You jackass!
Metal bat: I got a personal rule
to never let muggers
or hero hunters off the hook.
I'm gonna take
that rotten spirit of yours
and pound it into shape!
Garou: Swing and a miss, moron!
- ( Metal bat growls )
- ( Garou laughs )
Is this your entire strategy?
Just gonna keep swinging that
thing around 'til you're dead?
Metal bat: 'Til I'm dead?
Ain't nobody got time for that.
'Til I win!
Killer move!
Fighting spirit brutal tornado!
- ( Roars )
- Garou: Hah!
'Cause i'm
so scared of spinning!
( Chuckles )
¶
hate to break it to you.
Parrying an amateur attack
like this one is kid stuff.
( Metal bat groans )
Garou: Finally.
And stay down this time.
Tank top master and metal bat
were both nothing
but muscleheads.
Against a human martial artist,
they have no way to compete.
Huh. Taking down
the hero association
might be easier than I thought.
Whoa. What's this?
Could that goon
really have so much power?
( Chuckles ) If you'd
have caught me square on,
I'd have been in trouble.
Girl: Big brother!
( Garou gasps )
Girl: Big brother bat.
( Metal bat scoffs )
Girl: What's going on here?
Who is that weird man?
Garou: Your sister?
Metal bat: Zenko! Stay ba--
zenko: Big bro!
Garou: You had
your best chance there,
but you blew it.
You won't get another one.
Now to put you down for good.
Zenko: Stop right there!
My brother promised me
there'd be no violence
when I'm around,
so you can back off!
No more fighting allowed!
- Garou: Huh?
- Zenko: This fight is done!
Garou: You wanna tell me
exactly why I have to follow
your family's ridiculous rules?
( Zenko growls )
It's over!
Garou: Oh, right. Guess I did
have something else to do.
No time to waste on a jackass.
Until next time.
Metal bat:
You started this fight,
you arrogant bastard.
Garou: You get to live
for now, metal bat.
- Enjoy.
- Metal bat: I'll enjoy--
zenko: Forget him!
We need to get home now!
There's a monster!
( Metal bat gasps ) Oh, crap!
The executive and his kid
are in danger.
I gotta get to 'em!
Zenko: What?!
You're kidding, right?!
Hold it! I won't let you!
You're gonna get killed!
Metal bat: Zenko,
just go on home, all right?
Zenko: Hi-yah!
Stubborn blockhead!
- ( Thud )
- Uh...
Big bro?
¶
monster 3: Hmm.
So that's the hero hunter
everyone's been talking about.
He's pretty good for a human.
Monster 2: He didn't
even finish off the hero
when he had the chance.
Monster 3:
You judge far too quickly.
That man could be put
to good use, hedro-jellyfish.
Hmm?
( Hedro-jellyfish cackles )
Metal bat's younger sister.
Never can have enough hostages!
- Garou: Hey.
- Hedro-jellyfish: What?
( Gurgles )
Garou: So the eyes that have
been watching me all day
were yours, huh?
( Hedro-jellyfish gurgles )
Garou: What? You survived that?
Monster 3: Hold, hero hunter.
Garou: Two against one, huh?
Monster 3:
We are not your enemies.
Take a look at this.
I'm sure
it will pique your interest.
- Garou: "Monster association"?
- Monster 3: I knew he'd bite.
Why not come with us?
We can escort you
to our hideout.
- ( Paper rips )
- Eh?
Garou: Not interested. Piss off.
( Monster 3 laughs )
I'll just pretend
I didn't see that.
One day soon,
we will meet again.
As long as you
continue hunting heroes,
it is simply inevitable.
Hedro-jellyfish:
We'll be watching you.
¶
garou: Whatever, creeps.
Monster:
Talk about disappointment.
Mohican: No way!
My mohi-punch did nothing!
Pineapple:
Same with my pine cannon.
Monster: Pineapple gets
5 points. Mohican get 2.
That's on a 100-point scale,
by the way.
You're so weak,
I can't even think of a joke!
Do you know how hard
I've trained for this,
how much I've pushed
my horn and body
for the day
of the final battle?!
Any idea at all?!
- Monster 3: Rhino wrestler!
- Rhino Wrestler: Hmm?
Monster 3: Bring the hostages!
We're pulling out!
Rhino Wrestler:
Aww, come on, now!
I thought we were gonna
take down metal knight!
Monster 3: No!
That thing you see
is nothing
but a remote-controlled drone.
Today is not the final battle.
You're not to go off
on your own.
Rhino Wrestler: All right, then!
So do I take
both of these creatures or what?
Monster 3: No.
Just the child will do.
Pineapple: Please! You can't!
Mohican: Damn it! We're not
gonna let metal bat down.
You can take the kid
over our dead bodies!
Rhino Wrestler: That's the plan!
Did you see that, Phoenix Man?
What threat level do you think
they're gonna give me?
Phoenix Man: Who knows?
Centichoro,
mission accomplished!
It is time to withdraw!
( Centichoro grumbles )
Metal Knight:
Escaping underground?
Not so fast!
I won't let go!
Phoenix Man:
That's good for now.
The final battle is yet to come.
Man: Kill it!
Man 2: Keep it up, heavy Kong!
Heavy Kong: Damn.
Still no backup.
Where the hell are they?
Monster:
You're a class-a hero, right?
Just how many
class-a scalps will it take
for me to raise my threat level?
( Blow lands )
Lightning Genji:
It's immune to my stun rods.
Bad luck getting matched up
with this monster.
Monster 2: Actually,
lightning genji of class a,
I'd say you're having
rather good luck,
for other cities are facing
far more violent monsters
than me.
- ( Rumbling )
- ( Lightning genji panting )
Good god. What in heaven's name
is happening?
( Pounding on door )
Sourface: Hey!
Stop sitting on your ass,
and come out of there!
It's go-time, charanko!
Hurry it up, you doofus!
Saitama: All right.
Guess I'll go.
Announcer: Ladies and gentlemen,
we've kept you in suspense
long enough!
Competitors for super fight 22,
it is time to enter the arena!
( Crowd cheering )
First up, a newcomer,
the class-a, rank-19 hero
of the fighting style
hyper karate max,
welcome lightning Max!
Lightning Max:
Got my eyes on the prize.
Announcer:
Our sole female fighter,
with blazing fast attacks,
including her palm bells fist,
ring-ring!
Ring-ring: Can we
just start already?
Announcer: From "the way
of the cruel" school, benpats!
The perennial
top-four competitor,
whose slithery arms
can strike opponents anywhere,
class a's lowest-ranked hero,
snakebite snek!
Snek: Why did he
have to say, "lowest-ranked"?
Announcer:
And that's not all, folks!
From the fist of thunder,
with his super-conductor body,
boltane!
Bazuzu, master of
the nuclear fist!
From the many fists, gatling!
With his gentle self defense,
hamukichi!
With his giant smothering
killing technique, Dave!
Master of psycho-analytic
martial arts, logy!
Mentai, the spice fist fighter!
Giga-pro wrestler, jakumen!
From the way of the chosen one,
choze!
Formerly of the fist
of flowing water crushing rock,
master of sourfacekempo,
sourface!
Sourface: I think
I'm gonna hurl.
Returning for
his seventh straight appearance,
will the man who won't quit
finally win his first fight?
From the take-the-plunge
true fist, zakkos!
Zakkos: I'll get my first win
and propose to my lady.
Announcer: All right, moving on.
The man who wrote
"please don't aim for my head"
on his registration form?
Is he really here to fight?
From the fist of seltzer water
on the rocks, charanko!
( Crowd booing )
Saitama: Why are they
already booing me?
Man: Hey, isn't that
genos from class s?
Man 2: I guess he's a fight fan.
Announcer: A great contender,
some say the greatest,
he's already
won two championships.
He's conquered
every opponent come his way!
But the man himself
says he's never gone all out!
Master of the dark hell
killing jutsu, bakuzan!
Bakuzan: Winning
the championship today,
that will have true meaning.
Announcer:
Another face from the past,
he boasts
of unparalleled strength.
It's the first time we've
seen him in seven tournaments!
A four-time past champion,
the man himself,
dark corporeal fist, suiryu!
Suiryu: All right!
( Crowd cheering )
Announcer: He's spent
the past three years
travelling and enjoying life
and says he's only here
for the prize money.
Could his carefree attitude
be the secret to his power?
This time, he'll have
to contend with bakuzan.
Bakuzan: So that's suiryu.
If I kill him,
that would make me
the strongest active fighter.
Suiryu: I sense
his piercing aura,
but the one I was hoping to face
would be
the last tournament's champion.
As long as I'm here,
I'd at least
like to challenge myself.
Announcer: This is
your super fight 22!
And now that the introductions
are over, let the match begin!
( Sourface exhales )
Deep breaths. Stay calm.
You're okay.
It's all gonna be okay.
Saitama: Hey, gramps,
nervous about something?
Sourface:
Don't call me "gramps"!
I may outrank you,
but I'm 20, same as you!
Saitama: Wait.
He's younger than me?
Zakkos: Hey, you!
You claim a martial arts style
no one's heard of.
I smell an amateur.
Martial arts aren't a joke.
Withdraw now,
or else I'll have to crush you
without mercy.
Saitama: Not gonna respond?
Sourface: You're the one
he's talking to!
Zakkos: You can't even
tie your belt right.
Nice bow.
Sourface: Haven't you
learned anything?
You're hopeless.
Zakkos: Super fight
is the pinnacle
of mixed martial arts.
It's not some playground
for ignorant newcomers.
Sourface: He's not an amateur.
We were both in bang's dojo.
Zakkos: Seriously?
That's tragic.
How the standards have fallen.
Sourface: What'd you say?!
Zakkos: Bang was slated
to be chief judge today,
but he cancelled last minute,
and that little stunt
is causing all kinds of trouble.
Sourface: Master bang did what?
Zakkos: The "treasure
of the martial arts world"
decided to ditch
his dojo and disciples,
all so he could run off
and play hero.
Sourface: I won't stand
for this insolence!
And you,
why aren't you getting angry?
- Saitama: Uh...
- Sourface: I quit
and walked away, but you
stayed on as his last disciple!
Saitama: Oh, gotcha.
Ah, it's all right.
Let him have his say.
Sourface: What's that?!
Saitama: I didn't
come here to argue.
He says he's gonna
crush me in the ring.
Now, that's more my speed.
He doesn't seem
all that strong, though.
Sourface: Heh.
That's telling him, charanko.
( Zakkos scoffs )
I'm gonna butcher you
like a butcher butches!
Bomb: I don't mind
being on garou's trail,
but you're sure
he'll simply show up?
( Thinking ) Hmm.
He's certainly in a mood,
isn't he?
Huh?
I think something's
taking the bait.
It's after the class-a
we've been shadowing.
Bang: What? Let's move.
( Crowd murmuring )
( Monster laughs )
The demonic pugilist
is here to level this city
to the ground!
Bang: Well, it isn't garou.
You can sit this one out, bomb.
( Hero gasps ) Huh?
Silverfang? Great timing.
We can--uh...
Huh?
Demonic pugilist:
You're a class-s hero, right?
I know you. You're
that famous martial artist.
When I was human,
I was a fighter, too,
but sanctioned bouts
weren't nearly enough for me.
Eventually, my lust
for violence changed me.
See? Now I'm a monster!
( Screams )
Hero: That's, uh...
( Squelch )
Bang: We must find him
before he ends up
like this sad creature.
Announcer: All right!
It's time for our first match,
Max versus ring-ring!
- Referee: Begin!
- ( Lightning Max gasps )
Announcer: Ring-ring leaps in!
Ring-ring: Heart hard hit!
( Heroes yell )
( Hero gasps ) A whip
can generate that much power?
( Monster laughs )
You're about 100 years too young
to approach super s head-on!
You pathetic bunch
of worthless hero pigs!
( Monster chomps )
Man: Heavy Kong, no.
Monster: This is the best
class a can offer?
They sure don't have
much fight in 'em.
So, anyway, be sure to spread
the word for me, all right?
The one who took heavy Kong
down for the count
was the great martial gorilla.
( Chuckles )
( Monster roars )
( Lightning genji sighs )
This is going nowhere.
Monster: You won't escape.
( Pounds drum )
( Lightning genji groaning )
I-I just couldn't win.
( Groans )
Monster 2: Interesting
with the right matchup,
even threat-level tigers like us
are able to defeat
class-a heroes.
( Monster 1 giggles )
Perhaps there was no need
for us to hide away after all.
Man: We have word heavy Kong
was defeated in city w.
Man 2: The bad news
keeps coming.
We can't reach metal bat
or metal knight on comms.
Man 3: The mammoth creature
in city I
is devouring buildings
and seems to be growing!
It's also ossifying.
We cannot let it continue!
Man 4: Toxins!
The monster in city y
is using a neurotoxin
to paralyze the heroes
that try to stop it!
Man 1: It's no use.
There's just too many of them.
Man 2: If this continues,
we'll be wiped out.
Monster: Both the monsters
and the humans
appear to have misjudged
our relative abilities.
We were far stronger
than we initially thought,
while the humans were weaker.
Even their best heroes
hardly pose a threat.
Hero: Hey! Snap out of it!
- What's wrong with you?!
- ( Hero 2 growling )
Hero 2: Darkness blade,
pull it together!
Super s: When I punish someone
with my whip,
it imparts a special stimulus
that turns them
into love slaves.
Hero 1: No! Please! Stop this!
Super s: If you desire
a taste of my love,
you will fight to your deaths!
( All yell )
( Hero 1 gasps )
Are you guys...
Super s: My, my.
More suitors have come
to vie for my affection.
Oh, how titillating!
- ( Gasps )
- Blizzard: Really?
That's all it takes
to be threat level demon?
Not a bad wager.
If I defeat you,
their minds will be freed, yes?
Then they'll be in my debt,
like killing two birds
with one stone.
Hero 1: I knew it!
The blizzard bunch!
Blizzard: Soon, you'll be
bound and behind bars.
Super s: Oh, I wish you wouldn't
toy with my sadistic instincts.
I don't want kill you
too quickly.
Announcer: Well, that was quick!
An easy knockout
for Max against ring-ring!
( Crowd cheering, booing )
Rumor had it
that his fighting skills
were not yet
up to a competitive level.
Still, despite his low seed
in this event,
he advances uninjured
and seemingly with ease
past his first opponent!
Lightning Max: I wouldn't
exactly say I was uninjured.
Zakkos: He managed to win
without using
the gunpowder in his shoes.
Saitama: Hey, what's this
"low seed" stuff mean?
Sourface:
It's a preliminary ranking
for those considered
less capable.
They're strategically
placed in a position
where it's more difficult
to win at all.
Saitama: I see.
So the people running this thing
consider him to be weaker
than the others.
Sourface: Those who leave
the martial arts
to become heroes are looked at
as having taken
the easy way out.
It's a matter of discipline.
Saitama: What about bang?
Sourface: Master bang is unique.
And, unless you've forgotten,
you're a low seed
yourself, charanko.
Saitama: What?
Oh. You're right.
So the two in the corners
aren't necessarily
the strongest.
It's just
that they think I'm weak.
Zakkos: No, I assure you
those two are quite fierce,
but, once I beat you,
I'll face bakuzan,
a true contender.
Saitama: Uh,
according to these brackets--
oh! You're weak sauce, too.
Announcer: Our second bout,
zakkos versus charanko,
is about to begin!
Zakkos: I'm so gonna murder you.
¶
( singing in Japanese )
( Zakkos gags )
Announcer: Holy crap!
Charanko can hit!
He's off his feet!
Could zakkos be knocked out
by a single slap?
Hold up.
This isn't about charanko
being strong at all, is it?!
It's about zakkos
being just so weak!
He even invited
his girlfriend here today,
intending to propose to her,
but I'd say that now
all his life plans
have gone
completely off the rails!
- ( Crowd laughing )
- Saitama: Ooh.
I may have done a bad thing.
Announcer: Wait a minute.
I've just been given
some new information.
It seems his girlfriend
didn't show up
in the first place!
- Safe! He's safe!
- ( Laughter continues )
Saitama: Whew. I was worried.
Zakkos: This sucks so much.
Genos: The outcome
I was expecting.
At this rate, the tournament
will end before master
ever has the chance
to taste true martial arts.
Suiryu: Zakkos's moves
weren't all that bad.
Nicely done. See you
at the finals, Mr. New guy.
¶